Hi everybody, and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm your host, Digibro, for the evening.
I've got my usual suspects, Nate the best guy ever, Omedetou, Okaasama, uh, what, congratulations mother, is that what you said?
Yeah, that's what I said, I'm a Jess.
I've got, I've got, Endless Jess with me, yeah, yeah, yeah. Patreon.com slash Ben Saint.
Hmm, hello.
And we have a very special guest today, a fellow YouTuber whom all of us sort of became acquainted with and fans of at the same time in the last couple of months.
Mr. Mumkey Jones.
Oh, konnichiwa, I can speak Japanese too.
That sounded like a Spanish accent to me.
Well, that was a great, that was a great snob impression.
Whoa.
We've invited Mumkey aboard, Mumkey said that he, he told me I'd be most interested in talking about politics or Elliot Roger, and I thought, let's talk, let's talk about empathy and how so much of the problems in our society are a result of people not understanding one another and, and just sort of, I guess that's really it.
Mumkey, I want you to introduce us to this concept sort of as you did in your Elliot Roger video.
You have this 30 minute analysis of why Elliot Roger did what he did.
For those who don't know, Elliot Roger is the guy who, I don't know.
Elliot Roger is the supreme gentleman.
Yeah, that's right.
Elliot Roger is the boy who dared to do what the rest of us were too cowardly to do.
You know, you laugh, you laugh guy, but, but, but, but he's a beautiful boy.
With a tortured soul.
I, I agree, I agree.
All right, let's move on.
Yeah, Mumkey, explain to us what's the deal with Elliot Roger.
Okay, so to start off, I think it's important to distinguish the difference between sympathy and empathy because I think why people are scared to empathize is that they're confusing it with the definition of sympathy.
To empathize with somebody is just to be able to put yourself into their position mentally.
You're not making a judgment call saying what they did was right or wrong.
You're just saying, I can see their point of view and that's completely different from sympathy, which is where you're putting a judgment call on it.
So in the case, go ahead.
Oh, I was just going to say, I'm reminded of what Aristotle said that the mark of an educated mind is the ability to understand another's perspective without having it yourself.
And that's actually one of the biggest problems we have politically is that people just want to put out their talking points and not try to understand other people's agendas and all that.
But we're not going to get political, I think.
So the story with Elliot Roger.
Feel free. We don't give a fuck on this show.
Bernie, I still love you. I'll never forget.
We've got about 10 minutes before this podcast degenerates like all of them, the complete frothing madness.
So you can say whatever you want. It doesn't matter.
Okay.
So the story of Elliot Roger. I did an audiobook reading on my channel, Mumki Jones.
And there was a lot of discussion in the comments of people relating to Elliot because he was a very lonely boy growing up.
He had trouble making friends. He couldn't interact with the opposite sex at all.
He was addicted to World of Warcraft and it impacted him very much on a social level.
So there are people who were expressing in the comments of those videos that they could relate to him on those levels.
But the problem is that a lot of them also expressed fear for relating to Elliot Roger in a public sphere because of the potential judgments that would be cast upon them
for even talking about themselves and a murderer in the same sentence.
So it's like this fear of empathizing with somebody who did something bad, which that shouldn't be a fear at all because
Elliot Roger is an example of a person that we should be able to learn from.
And when we halt the conversation with this fear, we're not doing anything to prevent the next Elliot Roger from happening.
I had seen Elliot's videos before I listened to the audiobook.
That considers them a personal education tool.
They're obviously very hard to watch, not even just in the context of what they are, but just because you can tell that the guy in them is putting up this front and he's trying to act cool.
It's sort of embarrassing.
It's cringey in a conventional sense of the word.
It makes me really cringe.
But the reason it makes me cringe is because I can see him being like, hmm, I, the supreme gentleman, you know, I am a powerful God-like man.
I forget what he said.
But hearing him say those things, you know, those are thoughts that I've had and those are, I used to feel like that.
You know, like there's been times in my life when I might have said things very similar to that.
I definitely said things.
Not so much about the supreme gentleman, but I legitimately thought I was a God when I was like 17.
It's like when I first learned, when I first learned about like spirituality and stuff and like the idea that like you get from the universe, whatever you put into it, I was like, I can control everything.
My fate is in my command, you know.
Did you, have you listened to the audiobook?
No, I have not.
Did you know that Elliot became obsessed with that idea and tried to will himself to win the lottery and spend thousands and thousands of dollars?
Did he like, did he read the secret or something?
He did read the secret.
That's the one book he specifically talks about is the secret.
Oh God.
Ben, remember when Grace came up to us and was like, guys, you have to read the secret?
Well, now I'm glad I didn't because I would have been a fucking murderer.
Thank you, Grace.
You need to ban the secret.
The secret is causing all these mass shootings.
You need the secret control.
Well, the thing is my, like, the reason I know that book-
Every page is blank except for it says the secret is kill everybody.
The reason I know that book specifically is that my dad is actually a huge fan of that book.
Like, he totally believes in like that, you know, whatever, like if you put good energy into the universe and good energy will come back to you.
And like, to me, I think really the secret, it's just the exact same thing as religion, which is just-
Right, right.
You can't have confidence in yourself, so you have confidence in something higher than you.
Even though really all you're doing is just being confident and that makes things happen for you.
Like, that's all you need.
Right, that's exactly what it is.
All you need to do is, like, believe that you can get things and then that will trick you into being able to get things.
It has nothing to do with the universe at large.
It's just, just be confident.
Well, it's like, it's like, if you're thinking about something, that you say something that you want, you know, if it's on your mind all the time,
the inevitable consequence of that is going to be you taking, like, taking action, you know, relating to it.
Right, so in that way, your thoughts do, you know, bring things into existence, but it, you know, through your action.
It's not magical.
Or like, some weird spiritual fucking string theory particle effect.
Yeah.
You know, not-
Quantum collapse.
Not to cast shade on my dad and his beliefs or anything.
I just think it's all really goofy to me.
Like, I'm just like, you're just, I mean, you're just a hard worker.
That's why you get everything you want, you know?
Yeah, yeah.
But, but anyways, yeah, with Elliot Roger, like, because I think what made his case so famous was that he was literally a 4chaner, right?
Like, uh, Bumky, am I correct on that?
He was definitely on BB.com, the bodybuilding website, and then some other website.
Oh my god.
We don't know for sure that he ever posted to 4chan, but there are a lot of speculation about it.
Oh, okay.
Right, because I remember when, when the event happened, like, when he shot all those people, I remember 4chan, like, not shutting up about how he
was one of us, you know?
That's just because he's so one of us.
He clearly, he clearly is.
He talks about how he loved, he loved Pokemon as a kid.
He talks about playing World of Warcraft.
He is totally one of us.
Well, and also just his beliefs are, like, varied slash pole, right?
Like, he's sort of anti-women.
Well, specifically for women, yeah, I mean, that's kind of his...
So, like, you know, when it happened, everyone was kind of like, he's one of us.
And to me, it was like, you know, I've got experience watching shows like Welcome to the NHK or, like, you know, different stories that make people feel that way,
where they're like, this, this reminds, or even Evangelion, you know, where it's like, when you look at Shinji Ikari and he kind of reminds you of all the
fucked up times of your teenage life, you know, like, I think that's what Elliot Roger makes people think about, because it is real.
It's, you know, it's, it's not like...
How do I put it?
It's not a real pain, you know?
He was in serious agony every part of his day, and it doesn't matter that, like, he was fed well, he had a house, he had money.
None of that touched the higher level of the Maslow's hierarchy that he was completely unable to get anything he needed from, you know?
Isn't that like a verbatim quote from Monkey's review?
Yes, it is.
Look, just because I mentioned Maslow's hierarchy doesn't mean I'm fucking...
It was, it was a well put, it was a well put, alright?
Just because I mentioned the same thing in the same exact context.
That's, that's, that's stupid.
You know, I think it is important to try and have empathy for people like Elliot Roger, but no matter how much I try, I don't think I can.
Oh, fuck off, dude.
The more that I learned about it, no, because I watch his dumb little videos, and I just can't help but think that he's another bitter, pathetic, little sociopathic, four-channer piece of shit loser...
Yeah, just like me, dude, just like me.
And who I really have empathy for is all the people in his life who had to deal with him for 22 years before he finally went off the deep end.
He should have killed, he should have killed people and killed himself.
It would have been worth the sacrifice to get him off the face of the planet. Please do.
That kind of relates to what I said at the very beginning, the difference between empathy and sympathy.
Empathy is a skill where you are able to mentally put yourself into his position.
Sympathy, I think, is what you're talking about, where you feel sorry for...
Oh, no, I'm the best at empathy. Don't get me wrong. I can empathize with anyone in the world.
You know, I do empathize with him in one way, and that is the desire to commit violence and kill a lot of people.
That's one thing that I can deeply empathize with, and I think about every single day of my life.
In that aspect, that's a way in which he is a perfect human being who was right.
You know, I feel very much like one of the people commenting on Mumki's videos, and just the people who are...
I'm a big four-channer myself. When I watch Mumki's video and just hear all the things read through Elliot's book,
I feel a massive correlation with my life and the experiences I've had.
Not being able to get the things I want, the frustration, the way...
You know, just the way that things feel like they've tilted, like, it used to be able...
You could just grab a bitch, drag her back to your cave, rape her. That was the best.
You know, we need to go back to those days.
But, you know, I wish Elliot had lived to see the last episode of Steven Universe,
because he really just needs to take a moment.
You know, I'm serious, because the problem was...
Oh, you mean the most recent episode.
Yeah, the problem with Elliot was that a lot of us do this, too.
Mindful education.
That's right. Mindful education. We focus too much.
We obsess over the things that have gone wrong in our lives that, you know, aren't going the way we want them.
And we can get... And I'm not really saying that just trying to think differently would immediately correct the problem,
but it's a matter of perspective.
And if you can, you know, change your attitude about...
Just like, if Elliot had focused on being proactive about doing stuff,
and of course, like, yes, that's his whole problem, he couldn't be.
He was kind of, you know, damaged in however way to be like this.
If he had had just a slightly different perspective, he could have done things differently.
I feel so bad, because he didn't deserve what happened.
Elliot's observations about men and women are not necessarily wrong all the time.
It's just that he lacked perspective on them.
That reminds me of the time that I solved the gun control debate
and didn't tell anybody, because I figured out the answer
and I realized the world was too stupid to hear it and no one would listen.
Are you going to tell it to us, or are you going to keep it?
Yeah, sure, I'll tell you.
No, keep it. Keep the secret. I don't want gun control solved.
This is the secret volume, too, right now.
Okay, let's see it. What's the secret?
Well, so it's like, the way to prevent, like, another Elliot Roger type of mass shooting
is two steps.
Step one is sex education, and step two is autism genocide.
Wait, can I touch it?
We don't be dead!
Yeah, we're all on the spectrum!
We're all on the fucking spectrum!
I really don't believe that.
I believe that. I completely believe that.
I think that's complete bullshit.
That's like saying we're all on the broken leg spectrum.
Well, what if I don't have it?
Wait, what are you saying?
You think the autistic spectrum is bullshit?
No.
I think that the idea that everyone is on it is bullshit.
For the record, Jesse, we're all on the spectrum is literally a joke catchphrase I made up.
That's...
No, it's not a joke, it's true.
I've heard people say that.
Everybody displays behaviors that categorize autism.
Everybody does it.
Yeah, that's the thing.
It's... I mean, everyone displays...
It's kind of like saying we're all on the death spectrum.
Yes, it's true, but unless you're like...
Boy, are we.
But you don't describe someone as like...
You know that cheeky joke people say when someone's like,
I'm dying, and someone's like,
well, you're always dying.
It's like, yeah, but fuck off, that guy's dying.
Okay, okay, but seriously, remember that.
Yeah, we're all on the spectrum, but some people are autistic.
Here's a thing...
There's like a difference.
Here's a thing I did years ago.
Look, I just...
Lines on the sand, it's all just lines on the sand.
Hang on, okay.
Because remember, Jesse, years ago when you made your ModPie video,
and I did all this massive amount of research just desperately trying to debunk the fact
that ModPie from My Little Pony was in fact autistic.
And you couldn't because I was right.
The point is, I did the actual research involved.
I read the actual American Standard Psychology, whatever it is, DSL3 or whatever,
to look at the traits, and all it is is a list of exemplified traits
or exerted traits of the individual.
So like if you have trouble talking to people...
It's a list of traits of an annoying asshole.
And when someone has a lot of those traits, we used to call them an annoying asshole.
But the thing is, everyone in the psychological community has decided to call it autistic
and treat it like an illness when really it's just being an annoying asshole.
I agree. I agree.
And we should put them in jail. We should put them in some kind of concentration camp somewhere.
I agree that the term is basically useless, and I don't like it,
but I'm just saying that the problem is the words that we're using to describe it.
I mean, I don't even know why we're talking about this right now.
We're just having a fucking word debate.
I want to go out on about it.
We're trying to add a price with autism.
But it got derailed.
Wait, wait, let me touch on the first thing you said on how to prevent these kinds of things.
Jesse, sex education. You're close there.
You're close there.
But what we actually need instead of sex education, we have sex education.
What we need is dating education.
That's what I was going to say.
Let me finish. As laid out in fucking...
Let me finish!
You can't interrupt me before I get a chance to elaborate.
As laid out by Christian Weston Chandler in the pages of Sonichu,
where he details a specific...
It's so badly that you have to make Jesse fucking lose his shit.
He details the plan for how we need to give Sonichu's a dating education
so they can learn to fucking flirt with each other and have sex by the third date.
Okay, I'm sorry, Jesse. I sincerely apologize.
God damn it.
And if we took people like Christian and put them in a special place
with Lego blocks and fucking where they could be amongst themselves
and learn to socialize with people of their own kind,
then we could maybe reintroduce them to society one day.
I agree with that.
I agree with that because one of the biggest problems with Chris
is that he was never institutionalized or given special education.
Right.
But if the problem you're trying to solve is gun control,
so your solution to gun control is sex education and autism destruction.
Well, no, it's because it's going back to what you said in your video,
where like the debate is always between ban guns or get more mental health treatment
and the true answer is that none of those are really going to be effective
because you just can't, you're always going to have people like Elliot.
Which is kind of monkey's point, you can't do much about it.
Yeah.
But what I'm saying is like look at the specific case of Elliot or people like Elliot.
Elliot hated women because he didn't understand women
and he didn't know how to get laid.
And because sex education is such a fucking joke,
no one teaches us those things.
If you go to like the red pill subreddit and see like how bitter
most people on there are.
Yeah.
Everybody on the red pill.
Like I used to go there a long time ago,
but eventually I...
But eventually, you know, you go there, everyone's mad there
because everyone on there is a beginner.
They're all angry young men who don't understand this yet.
And when they finally figure it out, they stop going on there.
That's why it seems like everyone on there who has a crazy misogynist.
Would be going on a forum for beginning on how to get women.
Yeah, if you're there it means you have a problem.
Right.
Yeah, so what we just got to do is, you know,
when we see a fucking kid who is a retarded weirdo
who can't get with women,
we got to fucking slap him around a bit and say,
this is how you fucking talk to women.
This is how you be a functioning person.
Stop being an autist and then he won't end up killing you.
I'm a big believer in corporal punishment.
I think it needs to have a strong place in society.
There needs to be physical ramifications for being annoying,
being dumb and wasting my time.
I want to get into all this because I, you know,
by virtue of my career, I've met a lot of autistic people,
especially Chris, especially Matt.
He's excluded, of course.
Well, very especially because aside from monkey,
the rest of us come from the My Little Pony community.
Oh, no!
You unzip me, Digi! You unzip me!
Which is overrun with autism.
The world was so close to forgetting that.
You had to bring it all back.
Bring it back flashbacks.
Well, that's the thing, right?
When you hear that, it seems obvious, right?
People would joke about that, like,
hey, MLP fans are probably a bunch of autists.
But for those of us who just really...
They think it's a joke, but they don't really understand.
It's actually true because the kind of show that it is
attracts that kind of crowd
because it's something that's childish and easy to understand,
easy to empathize with, the characters have big expressive faces.
This is also why there's so many autistic anime fans.
And there's been studies done about this,
like real professional studies about the correlation
between autism and, like, cartoons and anime.
Yeah, specifically.
I did my master's thesis on the correlation
between autism and anime.
Having known Cider for three years,
that is not even slightly surprising.
Weren't you like a math major?
No, I was just kidding. I was just wishful thinking.
Anyway, the studies that have been done on it
are that basically because anime characters,
their faces are extremely expressive.
You can instantly get what they're thinking
in a way that you can't with real people.
So it makes it a lot easier for, like,
autistic people to connect with those characters
because they can kind of get what they're thinking more easily.
And anime characters are usually pretty straightforward
and, you know, and they spell out
sort of their personalities.
And MLP was like that, too.
But as a result of spending so much time
with autistic people, I've come to realize
that just like everyone else,
autism has nothing to do with whether
they're a good or bad person.
Because I've met, there's plenty of people
with Asperger's and autism who I've met
who are really cool.
They're not as easy to communicate with
in terms of, like, you know, understanding
some jokes or something like that
or just being able to socialize.
But some of the autistic people I know
are amazingly creative, like, make awesome stuff,
are cool people.
You know, I've posited that I think Hideo Kiano,
who made Eva, is definitely some...
somewhat spurgy, you know?
But he clearly knows how to channel that
into something great and make art.
And then I've also known a lot of autistic people
who are fucking intolerable.
And invariably, what I've come to realize
is that it's because of how they were raised,
just like everyone else.
My cousin Evan, who is extremely autistic,
he's like, you know, to the extent that
he doesn't even remotely understand
how to be not a rude piece of shit all the time.
Like, he's mostly raised by his mom,
like, by herself.
And his mom's a fucking crazy person.
She's like, she's a total bitch,
and she's high like 24-7.
And like, she always...
she has like a victim complex about the fact
that he's autistic.
Like, she thinks it's because of vaccines,
and so she's just like, always woe is me.
My son was poisoned by the government,
and that's why I've been saddled with this
autistic son, you know?
And like, as I...
As I watch them live together,
you know, because they've lived with...
Both my families lived with them,
and they've lived with us,
because they're fucking dirt poor,
because she can't fucking hold a job,
because she's crazy, you know?
And like, I'm not surprised
that Evan came out the way he is
when that's who raised him,
because she taught him to see himself as a victim.
She taught him to see himself as an autistic kid
who's not normal, who no one can relate to.
And so, he doesn't even understand
the idea of like, communicating with people,
whereas I've known other autistic people
who are extremely self-aware
about their autism,
and like, trying to control it,
and trying to understand people,
and they're great.
That is why...
Okay, that is why it frustrates me.
You know, okay, the whole...
the over-diagnosis problem we got going on,
where more and more people are autistic,
but the question is,
is there actually more autism,
or is autism just more diagnosed?
Or is it even a problem, you know?
Yes, and it frustrates me,
because in past eras,
or maybe in other cultures,
people would maybe see someone
who we in America,
or in the psychological community,
would label as autistic,
and consider, oh, they have a mental disability,
whereas in other societies,
they might say, oh, well,
it's just a quirk,
so they just behave in this unusual way.
Yeah, you're exactly right.
That goes back to what Jess is saying.
Back in the day,
they would just call that person a stupid asshole,
but now we understand the advanced science
of, no, it's actually a mental disorder.
But isn't it healthier
to call that person a stupid asshole?
I mean, yeah, I mean...
It would be better for them in the lab run.
Absolutely, I agree.
It's like tomato-tomato, right?
Like, is it a mental disorder,
or is it just a quirk?
I mean, does it really make a difference
when we call it?
Well, I think it matters,
because it's about how you treat that person,
when they're integrated into society, you know?
I do think that they're,
like Jesse said,
there's some healthy angle
in being like, hey,
because I think when we tell people,
when we diagnose people,
and we give them that sort of easy answer,
it doesn't teach them that
what they're doing is wrong.
It teaches them that they're a victim.
It teaches them that...
Yeah, I don't like it.
Oh, you've got autism,
therefore you're...
It's kind of like an excuse
that people can use,
and it's no excuse.
You still should be constantly trying
to better yourself,
just like everyone else.
You might have more of a lower ceiling
for what you're capable of, like mentally,
but that doesn't mean
that you shouldn't be trying to reach that ceiling,
and if there are autistic people
who can do good things,
then that means we should be trying to get
every autistic person to a point
where they can do good things.
Not saying you're autistic,
so fuck you, you know?
You're just...
You know what?
You have no opportunities,
so just try to live.
Try your best.
It's kind of a silly example,
but just to illustrate the point,
like, Forrest Gump, you know, was a retard,
but, you know, he did a lot of cool stuff,
and that's just to say that, like,
your life doesn't have to be defined
by your limitations.
You know, you can do all kinds of crazy shit.
You know, it's a good...
I mean, it's amazing to me
how often I will see
or hear, like, old people,
like, you know, people in their...
either from their 40s
up to their 70s and stuff,
and I'll hear them say things
or act in ways that I'm like,
this person is clearly autistic,
but is of an era where that wasn't a thing,
where, like, people didn't call him that,
and they've somehow lived this long.
Like, you know, because, like Jesse said,
it used to be you were just considered
a stupid asshole,
but stupid assholes were still expected
to get jobs.
Stupid assholes were still expected to,
like, you know, to find a way
to survive in society.
So, like, clearly,
in historically,
autistic people were able
to function well enough to live.
You know, like, whereas...
So you think the problem is now that we're aware
of autism as a disorder,
now we're coddling these people
and we're making a whole new generation of victims?
Is that the problem?
And perhaps, to compound that,
perhaps there's an additional problem
of the fact that we've gotten so comfortable
with sort of the marketing machine
of, like, showing us perfect people all the time
so we're less used to these people with,
you know, weird quirks
or we don't really meet them as much, you know?
And that's why it all comes back
to my autism holocaust idea,
because once word gets around
that autists are getting sent off to camps,
then autistic people will try their damnedest
to not see autism,
and the problem will be solved forever.
My God.
I'm just afraid, Jesse,
I'm just afraid that I'll be caught up in that first wave.
I've known Ben a long time,
and I'm worried about him.
I'm worried about this plan.
He knows what he's talking about.
That's always been...
That's why I have...
I've described my political views
as the Aberdorf-Linkler policy,
where, like, on the one hand,
I really think in, like, this authoritative way
that, like, hey, if we just, like, controlled everyone,
we could make a perfect society.
However, I would not fit into that perfect society at all,
so I'd be fucking myself,
so we have to be free and liberal
and, like, go against that.
Um...
I do want to play off of a...
I'll go ahead.
No, you go.
I want to play off of Jesse's idea
of the concentration camp thing,
because Elliot Rodger,
that was actually his solution for women
in the final seven pages of the book.
Oh, really?
There would be a society where it's only men.
Men don't even know that women exist.
All the women are in camps,
and the attractive ones are artificially inseminated
so that we can create new men.
And that was Elliot's idea of a perfect society.
So his solution wasn't to give men women.
It was just to remove them entirely.
Exactly.
There was no...
Oh, okay.
You know, that's really...
That's a really weird idea for someone who's like...
No, it makes perfect sense.
It makes perfect sense,
because the competition for women
is what brings out the bestial side of men.
And for him, without that temptation,
they have nothing to hurt each other
and treat each other unfairly over.
I mean, every comedian makes the joke
that men wouldn't do anything
if we weren't trying to impress women.
I don't agree with that.
But also, if you remove the competition for women,
that was the competition Elliot was losing his whole life.
If you just remove that, then his standing...
I'm just fascinated that that's like...
What he got out of it was not...
I need to...
It was less important to him that he could actually hook up with a woman
than that he could prove that he could or something.
It was all about his self-worth, you know?
That's really what it came down to.
In his mind, women and sex were...
Any guy could just jack off, you know?
We can do it, but...
Sorry, go on.
What was it?
You cut out.
In Elliot's mind, women and sex were evil
and needed to be exterminated from society.
Right, but I think that clearly comes from a place of...
I mean, I don't want to say sour grapes,
but if he had easy access to it and was a confident guy,
I suspect his attitude would have been different.
Obviously.
I think that's a safe assumption.
I mean, to him, it was like women...
Okay, because women have the power to choose which men to sleep with,
and to him, they always chose wrong,
because they weren't choosing him.
All evil, because they chose the most brutal of men, he would say.
Yeah.
You know, so to expand this beyond just autism and stuff,
and just into greater empathy,
like the way I sort of see society,
I find everybody very easy to empathize with,
not usually easy to sympathize with at all,
but very easy to empathize with.
And the reason is that I have a sort of...
And Nate, I know you agree with me on this,
a very deterministic viewpoint when it comes to the world,
that the reason people are...
I'm looking for a reason to not believe this deterministic,
but I've yet to find one, so...
Right.
Well, the way that people are is pretty much always a result of
what they have been, right?
Like what they've gone through.
You're born with a certain kind of temperament,
certain genes, you know, like you have a certain nature,
but then you are also nurtured into...
Like a Pokemon.
Exactly.
You might be born with a...
Oh, now I get it.
Now I understand.
Oh, you know, you're born...
You come into this world...
If only Elliot had known about the hidden staff.
Yeah, if only he'd known!
If only he'd known!
Yeah, Elliot was thinking of everything in terms of the IVs,
but he forgot all about the EVs,
because that's what it's...
Yeah, you know, you come into this world
as a little fucking... as a little goddamn...
Chimchar.
Chimchar, and you might use sassy,
but you know, even a sassy chimchar
can still learn flamethrower, you know?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Sassy chimchar, that's a stereotype.
So anyways, yeah, we all are kind of the result
of our upbringing,
and I think the biggest problem that I see
our autism upbringing...
The biggest problem I see in society
is no one...
No one seems to...
God, fucking damn!
Society of our kids.
Not the people.
I feel like you're an animal right now.
I know it's a very tall order
to stop thinking about autism,
but let me...
So, you know...
What if Jesse had found the death note?
Oh, wow!
The world would be gone.
There'd be no one left.
This world is too autistic.
Jesse would have used it immediately, too.
As soon as he found out what it could do,
I have no doubt that Jesse would have killed
like everybody would have done.
I never would have done a face reveal video.
Yeah, good plan.
Anyways...
God, you guys fucking distract me so hard.
I would kill everyone but monkey.
Oh, that's nice.
That's nice.
So, the only person worth living with.
So one of the things that bothers me the most
in the world is when I'm in a room
full of people who aren't me
and we're watching a television
on the news,
and invariably, if something bad happens,
then people will always be like,
that person's a monster.
Or like, wow, what a fucking...
What a piece of shit.
I don't know where people like that come from.
How could you do something like that?
And I'm like, it's not that hard
to understand these people.
It's not hard.
Like an ISIS killer or something.
All you gotta do is put yourself in their shoes
and you can immediately get why they would do the thing
that they did, right?
They're an uneducated,
probably young person
who comes from a shit-hole country
and who's been taught their whole life
in this other country are the cause of their problems.
ISIS is fairly educated.
I mean, depending on who's in...
What?
No, like the people who leave from the west
and go join, they're usually pretty...
Well, okay, yeah, but those are not the majority
of ISIS members.
I don't mean to say...
The majority of ISIS members are bumpkins
from around, you know,
those countries that get picked up locally.
Like just most terrorists
are people who have been taught
that the problems in their lives
and their society come from this other society
and if they can destroy it,
then they'll be rewarded for it, right?
That's pretty easy to understand and empathize with.
Like, I totally get why if you were in that situation,
you would do that.
Wow, Digi, you're making this whole ISIS thing
sound pretty good, honestly.
I've even heard from people
who don't even really understand psychology that much.
Like, if you actually watch ISIS recruitment videos,
it's really easy to understand
why this works on people.
Because the ISIS recruitment videos
make America look like fucking monsters.
And I mean, they deserve it so a lot of the time.
It's like, they killed our families
and they fly drones around and they kill our young
and if you destroy them,
then you'll make the world better.
And it's like, that's hard to argue with.
And you know what else is interesting?
I've been watching a podcast by this guy, Sam Harris,
who's a philosopher and writes a lot of books about stuff.
He's one of the four horsemen of atheism,
but that doesn't matter.
He just, like, he talks a lot about how people...
It sounds like someone, Elliot Rogers,
would have been a fan of.
Well, hence my interest as well.
Well, you know, it's just...
He talks a lot about how people,
specifically about ISIS,
how people do not get
why ISIS would do what they do.
Or rather, they always rationalize it one way,
as like, oh, they're doing it for, you know,
socioeconomic issues, like America bombed,
you know, Syria or whatever,
and so the guy joined ISIS or whatever.
Despite the fact that, like,
ISIS consistently all the time puts out propaganda
saying, join us, like,
we are going to give you,
you know, like, we're returning to this form of life
where, like, you know, men are exalted
or whatever, women are, like, subservient.
And, like, if you die, you go to, you know,
wherever and you get virgins or whatever it is.
It's like, people don't understand
that the propaganda is true
and they're really quick to try to
make things conform to, like,
how they would react in a situation like,
oh, this must be a socioeconomic thing.
Exactly, it's a lack of empathy.
We're trying to look at everything from
what would inspire us from a Western perspective.
Like, well, all I care about is money,
so obviously it must be a money issue.
And I hear that a lot too, like, you know,
because average people, because they don't understand psychology,
which if you asked me, like, how would I fix society,
everyone has to be educated in psychology.
Because as soon as you understand psychology,
everything else, everything bullshit in society
totally breaks down because it all just makes so much sense.
Like, religion, when you understand, psychologically,
why people go to religion, then it...
I don't know if I buy this, did you?
I think psychology is just...
That's because your name's fucking Saint!
You have a bias in this one.
Ben was a psychology major, you know, right, Ben?
What? You're a psychologist?
Oh, it was philosophy, it was philosophy.
You fucking idiot, you fucking idiot, Nate.
How dare you? How dare you suggest that I would study psychology?
It's the same thing.
Yes, yes, our dad is a psychologist, and that's fine.
But psychology is reactive to, you know, people, right?
Psychology is just categorizing behaviors, right?
Psychology does not explain behavior.
Psychology is like a catalog of behaviors,
and like theorizing about behavior.
Just because you study psychology
does not give you, like, great insight into people, right?
Like, psychology is the acumen...
The knowledge we have of psychology
was gained through an understanding of people.
You know, the understanding goes the other way.
I think when you look at someone...
Does that make any fucking sense? Am I talking crazy here?
You're talking crazy, I don't get it.
But I think the way...
If you look at someone and you can understand where they're coming from,
is that not psychology? Is that not what profiling is?
Like, looking at someone and figuring out why they're acting the way that they are,
that's what psychology is, right?
And like...
Yeah, yeah, I guess by comparing them to similar cases,
you can come to some kind of...
Right, well, I'm saying that if you understand, like,
okay, people who are religious,
they don't know why they are religious.
The way they understand it is like,
oh, if I believe in God, I'll be rewarded in this and this way.
And from a psychological standpoint,
the reason people gravitate towards something like that
is that it sort of gives them an easy thing to cling to.
They don't have to rely on themselves,
they can rely on this higher power that's communicating with them.
But once you understand that as like a psychological principle,
then it's like, oh, okay, religion's obviously bullshit
because the only reason it exists is so that we can trick ourselves
into feeling happy about something.
That's the only reason it's there.
I don't know.
I mean, you say that,
but then there are plenty of religious psychologists out there.
Digi's only point is that we can gauge insight is smart.
Oh, come on, that's so dismissive.
I don't like that whole...
I think it's very possible to...
It's kind of like there's a lot of scientists who are also religious.
It's because they're just not making like that mental leap kind of.
Why don't you have some empathy, okay?
Why do you be like, oh, well, anyone who's religious...
Look, I'm not religious, but I think it's unfair to be like,
oh, anyone who is religious just has failed to connect the dots
in the way that I have.
Oh, God, whatever.
Monkey was saying something.
Monkey.
Digi, I agree with what you're saying,
but I think one stipulation I'd put on your argument
is that the way you're talking about it,
it's like people choose to go to religion because of these rewards,
but that's not true.
90% or 5% of people are born into religion,
and then it's taught to them from the very youngest ages.
I don't want to use the word brainwash because that is dismissive,
but that's pretty much what it is.
You're taught this and you're told this is the truth, no matter what.
Very few people choose to go to religion.
But that's why I think...
That's the thing.
What I'm sort of getting at here is that I don't think anybody really chooses who they become.
I don't really believe that we have a lot of choice in our lives.
I agree with you on that.
You gain more choices the more self-aware you become,
and the more you understand the world around you,
it opens up more opportunities.
But to get to that point, you have to be lucky.
My dad, I don't want to slam him too much
because he's a very good person, I think.
He's a busy dad.
My dad is very sympathetic towards people who are...
Mr. Bro.
My dad is very sympathetic to weaker people
and good people, but he doesn't have a lot of sympathy
for people who he sees as could have made different decisions.
And I don't really believe in that.
I don't believe that everyone can make a different decision.
And one of the things my dad often says is like,
libraries are free, everyone should be able to go...
If you want to better your life, just go read
and go read about how to better your life.
And I'm like, yeah, but see, you know that,
but a lot of people just don't know that.
If you never are told, hey, if you read books,
it will make you successful,
then you will never think to go do that.
They never let you use the computer,
they make you sign up for shit,
they make you give them a bunch of information
that a poor person can't possibly have.
Even if you're told that you can better yourself
through education, you don't really get it
until you actually go and do it.
Exactly.
When you see it, it's all luck.
The guy who, like some teenage gangbanger
who joins a gang and fucking ends up killing
a bunch of people and then getting shot,
that guy probably never understood the value of education
because no one taught it to him
because he just didn't grow up in that environment.
You have to already have an in
if you want to get to even where any of us is.
I was raised in a family
where graduating high school and going to college
were just expected.
There was no even consideration
that I would do anything else.
I guess that worked out pretty well.
I know we don't really want to get into this,
but I just find it interesting that you're looking at it
from this perspective because we definitely have
a different viewing on this topic
because I think that you have exactly zero choices
in your life because the only thing that determines
what you're going to do is the physical forces
of the universe on the cells of your body
and that consciousness is an illusion
I'm more or less with you.
I don't think, when people talk about choice
in the way of like, I could have done this
instead of doing that, I don't really believe in that
because I think that...
But what is the scale of choice we're talking about
because you make choices every day?
Do you though?
I had the choice to come on this podcast
that could have said, did you bro?
He's not my bro and I could have left.
Let me do this. Let me go through an exercise real quick.
Because what was your life?
This is something I learned from Sam Harris.
So today, as you were getting ready to do this,
what were the choices going through your mind
as you decided whether or not to do this podcast?
In your brain, for the things that you were planning to do...
So I can either do the podcast,
I can jerk off, or I can take a nap.
Those are my three choices.
What are the odds you would have done the other two things?
Do you really think you made a meaningful choice?
Or you could have applied yourself
and killed five people.
Six people and injured 14.
Seven if you count himself.
What kind of weaponry did he use, anyway?
He had two handguns.
Is that two handguns?
Pretty good for handguns.
He was going around like a John Woo movie.
Two handguns and slow motion.
Now he's sounding even cooler.
He was in his BMW or the car the whole time.
He was just driving around.
Oh, really?
I relate to him.
Every day you're more like him.
You know what's worse?
You shave Digi, now you look just like him, too.
Did you look in the mirror
and slowly comes into focus and his face is alien?
Not only do I drive him...
That's the problem, success.
The richer Digi gets, the closer he gets.
Can we go back to what Nate was saying?
I think they threw off his thing.
I was just saying that if you really examine
the mental pathways that you're following,
you'll find that it's not like you really
made a mental list for yourself
of like, okay, I could do A, B, or C choices.
It's really more like your brain is populated
by your memories or your understanding
of what's going on, which is kind of like your RAM.
And then the first one that hits,
that's the one you end up doing.
Can you connect this to Pokemon in any way?
Yes.
Which stat does this tie into?
It's like which... fuck.
I don't want to say which starter.
Let's say you choose...
Let's say you were going to make the choice
between Pokemon Red or Pokemon Blue, right?
Yeah, okay.
The kind of person you are
is going to determine which game you buy.
Is your favorite color red or blue?
You'll probably pick that one.
Or is one of them more popular than the other?
You might pick the one that's less popular
because that's the kind of thing I would do.
And the forces that you feel in your brain that you...
I mean, this is my perspective.
The forces that you feel that are a choice
are actually just kind of the...
You're CPU processing the information
and then it spits out an answer.
That's my opinion.
It's really just that you don't have control
over your own thinking
or your own mental workings, right?
You don't control your brain.
You just are your brain and whatever it does is what you do.
And by the way, Monkey, how old are you again?
Are you 21?
21.
Alright, that's cool. Just wondering.
I don't know why you had to ask that in such a weird way.
I was curious because I'm 26.
He wants to know if I'm legal because we're meeting up after the show.
That's right, that's right.
But yeah, because of the way...
To get way the fuck back to a point I was making earlier.
Like, when I see people saying stuff like that
about ISIS or killers and stuff like that,
whenever someone's like, wow, what a monster,
I'm like, but you get it, right?
Surely you can understand where that person's coming from
and if we could do that, then we'd have such an easier time
of fixing those things.
And I think the real reason that we can't
is that you'd have to create an objective standard
and you can't do that
because everyone sees the world differently
and I think...
Maybe this is true of every culture,
but certainly here in America we are very self-righteous
and self-important about our view of the world.
We see it as everyone who doesn't feel exactly how we feel
is wrong, but we're outnumbered.
There's way more people in China who believe
that what they're doing is right
and we're not going to convince them to join our side.
So trying to set up that kind of objective standard
is virtually impossible
and even within one society,
what I want the world to become doesn't match
what my next door neighbor wants the world to become.
And that's sort of the problem,
but I think that if everyone understood psychology
and we were all able to figure out
why we're thinking the things we're thinking,
then it would help us to break down
all the differences between us
because we could say,
well, the reason those people believe that
is that it fulfills them in these psychological ways.
And if they understand that,
then maybe they can figure out
what would be the most beneficial way of thinking for them.
And then the result of all this
is that we end up with the Sybil system from PsychoPass
and it turns out to be evil and...
Yeah, it's tough to say what really the best solution is.
And in the far future, right,
when we're living in the dystopian,
I don't know if it's dystopian,
we're living in the far future
and the Sybil system has taken over
and all documents from the modern day have been destroyed
and someone finds Digi's review
or Digi's analysis of PsychoPass
and it becomes like a blueprint
to how to take down their corrupt society.
Well, my analysis of PsychoPass
was that I thought the system was great
and that's why my original review
was super controversial.
So it becomes like their holy texts.
It becomes like the pillar of their society.
I think one of the most controversial things
I've ever said was that
I think the Sybil system is a good idea
because it's a completely authoritative system
and it goes against everything our society believes in.
People actually stop and thought about what that meant
for you to say that.
I think they'd be pretty, you know,
they would raise a few eyebrows.
Well, it's pretty funny.
Yeah, he casually uses the N-word.
That's the most controversial thing he said.
Yeah.
Well, I think that...
Okay, let's not start pretending that the N-word
isn't anywhere wrong.
Just for the record, the N-word is nigger.
Yeah, that's right.
If anyone was confused about what the N-word is,
it's nigger, okay?
Just so we're all on the same page.
Nigger, see?
Digi, Digi, I'm calling.
I'm calling the fucking police.
Well, no, that actually goes right into the topic
of this whole thing.
That's the problem with the world.
Nobody has empathy.
Everyone's a nigger.
Everyone in the whole world is a fucking sociopathic nigger,
and they all need to go to nigger jail,
which is just regular jail.
Well, you know, I have a couple of songs
on my upcoming album about this.
About nigger jail?
No, about, like, why I say the word...
Society is the true nigger jail.
About why I say the words nigger and nigger so much,
which I think it's a fundamental lack of understanding
to think that, okay, God, this drives me insane.
There's this rapper called Milo, who I'm a fan of,
but he seems to have a sort of disdain
for white people listening to his music,
and he's often mentioned how it's not okay
that his white fans will say nigger at him and stuff,
and I'm like, but dude, you say the word in your music,
and your music is free, it's freely out there.
Anyone can listen to it.
And the people who are listening to your music,
those words are now in their head.
You know, like, if you grow up listening to rap music,
it doesn't matter what race you are.
You have grown up hearing the word nigger fucking constantly,
and it means something to you.
It doesn't mean, like, a black guy.
It just, like, it means the unbelievable number
of things nigger can mean.
It can mean, you know, like, as YG's saying,
my nigger, my nigger, which is obviously a positive context
for the word, or, like, you know, fake niggas.
Like, it's not saying, like, fake black people.
It's fake niggas, you know?
Like, these all mean something to me just as much as they mean
something to whoever wrote those songs,
and, like, I was raised on that.
You can't erase that from my mind through fucking white guilt,
you know, which I think is bullshit.
Just to play devil's advocate.
So are you saying that there's no situation
where there could be a certain, you know, racial
or cultural context in which he would like, you know,
in which anything, not even that word,
but something could be intended specifically
for a certain group, or, you know, it shouldn't be...
I mean, certainly, but if you're...
Okay, here's the thing, when you're releasing...
If you're not a racist, then saying nigger cannot be wrong.
End of story.
Yeah, I would agree with that.
Yeah, I agree, I agree.
Like, there's definitely people who say...
And I hear, because I live in Virginia,
we're, like, right at the cross-section
of the South and North, right?
There's, like, incredibly racist people here.
You know, like, super-racist, hillbilly fucks live in Virginia,
even though right a neighborhood over is all black people.
You know, there's no real racial tension here
because it's such a, like, liberal-leaning city,
but there's people who, like, really grew up
with ingrained racism, and they still talk about it that way.
And so I will hear sometimes, like, white ladies in their 40s
being, like, oh, those niggers over there.
You know, like...
Dang.
And I'm, like...
It's not racist because they said nigger.
It's racist because they're racist,
because they obviously think of black people as lesser.
It has nothing to do with what language...
If they said those blacks over there,
or even just those African-Americans,
like, it's still racist because the context is that they're...
they're just insulting black people for being black, you know?
Okay, just to play Devil's Gap one more time,
I know what people would say to this,
is that, did you're not understanding,
there's a cultural heritage to that word.
It's been used to insult for generations.
But the thing is...
Oh, fuck you.
I'm just saying.
Cultural heritage.
Nate, I just want to warn you, you're at two now,
and if you play Devil's Advocate three times in a row,
you actually become the devil.
So just...
So just please, please, you're on thin ice, okay?
I think that...
I think that language is always evolving.
If you ask...
And this is...
Every time someone gets into an argument about, like,
a prescriptive versus descriptive linguists,
do you know those terms?
Like, a prescriptive linguist is something...
I don't know shit.
Alright, someone who is a prescriptive linguist
is someone who says that a word is like this,
and everyone should use the word the same way.
A descriptive linguist says,
this is how people are actually using the word,
this is what it actually means,
so that's what it means.
So, in other words, prescriptive, wrong, descriptive, right?
Exactly.
And if you read the dictionary...
I really thought that this podcast would be us,
you know, outlying our plans for mass murder.
I didn't think that this would be what I signed up for,
this linguistic debate.
Well, to get through it real quick.
So, the actual, like, Oxford dictionary is descriptive.
Like, whatever language means at the time,
that's what it says in the dictionary.
They update it constantly
to reflect the current definitions of words.
They add in, like, lots of meme words have been added in.
Like, all those are real words because they're out there.
They mean something, and therefore they are words.
And I think that to try and drag a word,
kicking and screaming back to its origin point,
is totally missing the point.
The word nigga does not mean that anymore.
It has proliferated culture to such an extent
that there's no getting rid of it.
And there's words that have, like, I think faggot
has waned in popularity lately.
And I think the reason for that is that
I think most people kind of see it
as an insult towards gay people, right?
Like, when you say faggot, it feels like it means
you're gay and that's bad.
And that's why not as many people are using it.
And we have a great replacement word.
I don't see it that way.
I mean, I don't think it's...
I think faggot's fine.
I don't have a huge problem with it.
But I do think that because it feels more like that,
it's waning away.
But see, that totally depends on the person saying it.
Now it's all this, like, nuanced stuff about
whose fucking feelings are, like, the authority on the matter.
Right.
Like a chime in on the nigger discussion,
that you might have an anecdote that you might find amusing.
I do agree with everything DigiBro is saying, actually.
And I regret that earlier I said the n-word
and started all this.
I should have just said nigger because in my view,
it is completely about the context.
Calling somebody a nigger to their face
in an inflammatory way is, of course, wrong.
But if we're having a discussion about nigger,
why would you say the n-word?
But back when I was in high school,
we were reading...
It was like to kill a mockingbird, you know, one of those books.
And it was when you go in a circle
and each person reads, like, a paragraph and it goes on.
And there's this...
Oh boy.
There it comes.
There's this little super religious uptight bitch
named Mikayla in my class.
Oh, everybody knows I'm a fucking Mikayla, man.
I hate Mikayla.
We've all got our own bitch.
And you know what, Mikayla is, like, the perfect name
for that kind of person.
That's like the nigger for that kind of person.
From now on, when I say Mikayla, that's...
So here's my story about Mikayla.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is where I discovered that she is a hideous human being.
Because she refused to say any cuss words, right?
She would skip over it.
The word bitch was in it, so she skipped over the word bitch.
Next sentence, she said the word nigger.
And I couldn't fucking believe it.
Are you fucking kidding me, Mikayla?
Okay, was she guilty or was she just like,
yeah, that's what I do.
She thought nigger was okay to say, but not bitch.
Oh, my God.
That tells me something about her home life, you know.
Is it possible that she actually didn't know the word?
No, this was 11th grade.
Well, maybe because Mikayla's are such niggers,
she thought it was okay.
Oh, my God, that is priceless.
Yeah, no, but I...
Anyway, just to finish off what I was saying before that,
I just think because Faggot has...
Not to say that I think it has negative implication,
but I think enough people feel kind of wrong about saying it,
that it's faded in popularity as a word.
You don't hear it nearly as much.
Everyone clearly thinks it's a problem.
But the word nigger is not a bad word
in like 99% of the context it's used in.
Like, if you listen to, again, if you listen to any rap music,
you've heard the word a thousand million times,
usually in a positive context.
And like, so when people think that word,
it's not usually to mean like, you know, fucking black people.
It's usually to just...
I mean, the people who use the word by far the most are black people, you know.
Just to chime in with my perspective,
I did not grow up saying or hearing the word.
I didn't know the word until like a black friend of mine
in like 5th or 6th grade told it to me and explained it to me.
Yeah, and, you know, I never listened to rap.
I never listened to rap growing up.
So I don't make a habit of saying the word
because it's not part of the way that I grew up speaking.
But I totally agree with you guys in that it has plenty of...
Yeah, there's plenty of use.
And you know what?
Alright, I'm doing it.
I'm playing devil's advocate one more time.
I'm going to lose the devil!
I have no sympathy for the devil!
But we can definitely have empathy.
That's right.
So, okay, just about the usage of the word.
I'm just noticing that there's something going on here
where like it's about like the feelings of the people using it.
And I just want to raise the issue of
what if like there's a small group of people
who views a word a certain way
and they're kind of contained in their own community.
And then let's just say everybody else uses it a different way.
Are those people wrong to be, let's say, offended by the word?
That's a great question.
And I don't think anyone's wrong to be offended.
But I think that on some level we have to draw a line, right?
I agree.
It's a practical issue.
I would just say that those people should understand
and take into consideration that different people
use words differently.
I mean, here's the thing.
I say nigger all the time because of the fact
that it's not that I don't expect people to be offended.
It's that those kind of people I'm okay with losing.
Like every time I make a video,
I make a decision between like...
Because, you know, if you're not saying certain words
in your videos, there's only one reason.
It's that you don't want to offend other people.
And the only reason in the world not to try to offend people
is that you think it will affect you somehow.
That it will either make you feel bad
or it'll make so fewer people watch your videos, right?
And so...
Did you, that sounds like you're a sociopath.
That just sounds like being practical, dude.
The only reason to not hurt people's feelings
is so it doesn't hurt me somehow.
I think that's what...
I think, like, I mean, people will say, like,
you know, oh, I'm concerned about others,
but I think being concerned about others
is a result of being concerned about yourself.
Yeah, like, why do people start neighborhood watches?
It's because they don't want to get their shit jacked.
You guys are all evil.
No, I totally am with Ditchy on this one.
Yeah, you're totally right.
It's all...
I've never read a book by Ann Rand,
but I'm all about that Randian objectivity,
objectivist's rational self-interest mindset.
That's what it's all about and everything else.
Everything else is just a fucking lie and vanity.
I think that everything makes...
I'm not shit.
I just think everything makes the most sense
if you look at it, like, logically, right?
Like, okay, why do we have emotions?
Because in our best self-interest,
like, if we want to survive better,
then it's in our best interest to connect with other people.
Because as a community, we have better chances of survival.
We can watch each other's backs.
We can, you know, do all that.
So how do we make ourselves care about other people?
Well, that's where, like, emotions would come in, right?
You get sad when someone dies,
because ultimately it affects the community,
which means it affects you.
And, like, you don't necessarily understand it that way.
You don't perceive it that way.
But all the emotions you feel, they make sense
if you look at it from the perspective of, like,
how does this affect me, you know?
So I do think...
And that's the reason why we have such a hard time
empathizing with people who we don't think affect us.
Like, if we're at war with another culture,
then those people dying, we're like,
well, that benefits us.
So fuck them, you know?
Whereas if it was our teammates dying,
then it's like, we've lost something.
So, you know...
So I do think that all of it comes down to self-interest.
This reminds me of this guy I used to work with
who confessed to me that he would be upset
if his parents died only because of the financial burden
it would cause him.
Well, he says that.
Well, that is one legitimate reason that I would be upset
for that reason as well as other reasons.
I mean, I am very emotionally attached to my parents.
And it's not like if they died, it'd be like,
oh, it's all me.
I'd be sad about their death.
I'd be sad because it's them.
But the reason I have those emotions in the first place
is that they make sense.
Your parents are the ones who are protecting you.
They're a huge part of your life.
They brought you here.
They're a huge part of what you associate
with sustainability.
It's like having these figures who, for most of your life,
were your sustainability.
So, of course, you're going to feel tragically hurt if they die.
So I feel like that guy is not wrong.
He's just looking at it from an extremely cynical perspective.
I mean, that guy must have a rocky relationship.
If, in fact, he was telling the truth
and not just having a goof, which I suspect personally.
Not just being edgy.
I would never associate with edgy people.
Get the fuck out of here.
I listened to an interview with Anne Rand.
It really bothered me because the guy...
No, it was an old interview.
It was black and white. It was real old.
But the guy interviewing her was like,
he was being such a dick.
I saw other interviews where he was totally civil.
But with Anne Rand, he clearly had an animosity towards her ideals
and was trying to catch her out and kind of point...
He was really trying to come at it from, like,
you're wrong and let me prove it.
He was like, oh, you say that it's all about mankind's rational self-interest,
but you're married, aren't you?
You financially support your husband, don't you?
What the fuck's up with that? How does that jive with your gay ass philosophy?
It's basically what he was to say.
He does you piece of shit.
I watched those interviews after I read all the books.
And holy shit, that fucking guy just did...
Forget the mouth.
You know the same one. You're talking about the same one.
Glasses, piece of shit, asshole, I remember him.
No, no, he wasn't right here.
I don't necessarily agree with, like, Anne Rand's stance that, like...
Alright, but this guy's the problem. This fucking idiot.
It's like, wait a minute.
It's so easy. That guy just needed some fucking empathy
because if he had even an ounce of it,
it would have been so easy for him to square the idea
of financially supporting someone else with one's rational self-interest.
It is not complicated.
There's a world where, like, maybe have a greater understanding
of the fucking way that life works.
It is not difficult to understand how those two things can jive with each other.
I've always said that, like, the reason I have sort of a...
Not necessarily, like, socialist,
I would say I'm probably somewhere between that and, like, a libertarian.
Again, I'm, like, an Aberdorf linkler. I believe in every fucking thing.
But, like, I think, like, the socialist ideas make sense
because, ultimately, having more people who are better off
will benefit us because we make progress faster.
Like, if more of the, like, uneducated and badly off people
were doing better and they had better odds of, like, becoming scientists or whatever,
and then we got more scientists and we're chugging along better.
You know, like, it makes sense to lift people up from the bottom.
And for what it's worth, Ayn Rand...
Like, I mean, anyone can, like, espouse beliefs
and not necessarily uphold themselves to them.
Ayn Rand herself did live on welfare for the last part of her life.
So, totally against everything she stood for.
But, uh...
Look, I can't even find that hilarious.
Consider yourself a book writer, storyman,
as opposed to a philosopher.
Nobody's perfect.
Yeah.
Is it Ayn Rand or Ayn Rand?
Nobody cares.
Ayn Rand sounds like it's short for Anus Rand.
Yeah.
And I can't take someone seriously who's named Anus.
She looked a bit like an Anus in her later years.
She is an ugly woman, that is for sure.
Yeah, she was no Dagny Tiger.
Yeah, but she had a beautiful heart, though.
A lot of Natalie Shrugged character, yeah.
Why are you laughing?
Because women are shit.
Lol, okay.
Um...
You know...
If Elliot...
If Elliot Rodgers were in charge,
she would have been in a fucking cage
being artificially inseminated.
And that would have just been wrong.
In that interview that you saw,
did, like, was that glasses guy,
like, trying to prod her about her philosophy?
And she said,
well, at least I'm beautiful on the outside.
And then he looks at the camera like,
I don't know.
That was probably cut for time.
You know, I'm sure it was good.
He, like, he adjusts his tie,
and makes an audible goal.
She's like a borderline Skeletor.
Oh, whatever, man.
She's an old-ass bitch.
Cut her some slack, for fuck's sake.
Even when she was young,
she was fucking weird with you.
She's an old-ass dead bitch.
Come on.
I've never seen...
I've never seen young men.
I'm Googling her.
You're fucking lying to me.
I don't think Ayn Rand ever was young.
I think she was born a crotchety old-ass.
She looks fucking fine, dude.
She looks perfectly fucking fine.
Whatever.
Oh, I looked at...
She was born from a haggle on the fourth.
She looks like Franz Kafka,
but a woman.
Yeah, I guess she does.
It's the photography of the time.
Okay, well...
Hey, let's bring this conversation
back to empathy,
and let's talk about...
Do you guys have any thoughts on
who in our society, or who in the world,
needs or deserves more empathy than they get?
Me.
Hmm.
I agree.
I agree with that.
I have a very controversial answer
that I'll probably regret saying.
Uh-oh.
Go ahead and go for it.
That's what I was hoping for.
That is exactly what I wanted.
So, all jokes and memes aside,
I do think society is too hard on pedophiles,
and that's because they assume
all pedophiles want to...
I agree with that wholeheartedly.
Oh, I'm so glad you brought that up.
I really wanted to talk about your thoughts on that.
What a surprise.
We all agree with that.
All right, first of all, first of all,
this is the only neighborhood you could have
walked into, and everyone's like,
oh, yeah, pedophiles, of course.
No, no, it makes perfect sense, though,
because I think a lot of people would agree
that if you take a step back and look at it,
they didn't ask to be that way.
Exactly.
That's the biggest thing.
First of all, if we can have this whole cultural revolution
about the gays and say the gays...
I don't know why I'm emphasizing the gays.
The gays.
But if we can say that gay people are born that way,
and we're all confident in that now,
why are we not extending the same thing to pedophiles?
Because they're associated with hurting children,
just like the gays used to be back in the day.
Right.
And it's extended to things that are absolutely ludicrous,
like in most places in the world.
Ludicrous?
Whatever, ludicrous.
My favorite rapper.
My favorite rapper, ludicrous.
Yeah, I enjoyed his rap folding paper.
I was...
What was I fucking saying?
Oh, I've completely lost.
They extend things to things that are ludicrous.
They extend the idea of gays being...
I've lost it. It's gone.
His great pedophile anthem pimping all over the world.
I don't want to fuck anything except the loli.
Except the loli.
Oh, yeah, you should listen to my loli rap.
Oh, you know, okay, whatever.
It's not a rap.
Whatever.
My fucking song.
I'm all mixed up now.
Think about ludicrous.
You know what?
If Corey in the house is an anime,
then the loli song is a rap.
So there you go.
I was going to say that things have extended to a ludicrous degree
by banning even...
I'm talking about anime of loli porn.
That's what I'm trying to say.
Absolutely ridiculous.
Didn't Australia ban Hentai that had flat-chested girls in it?
No, no.
Australia did one better.
Australia banned all pornography with A-cup breasts,
including live-action pornography with women over the age of 18.
Things have gone so far over the fucking deep end.
It's ridiculous.
That makes me so angry.
You know what?
Okay, whatever you might have to say about pornography.
I think that doing that, banning that specific pornography,
is fucking dehumanizing to people with small boobs.
Of course.
Even way more so than porn itself could ever be.
Yeah.
And you know, just the opposite end of that spectrum
is how people get into tizzy when...
Like, there's a little bit of a tizzy about
if Tifa's gonna have big tits,
even though the character has big tits.
And I talked to plenty of girls in the real world
who have big tits that are like...
Are you a liar?
No, it's true.
I swear to God.
And they tell me that the fact that Tifa would be reduced
in chest size is dehumanizing to actual real-life big-titted women.
You have to fit within this fucking narrow limit
of what's socially and morally acceptable.
If you just physically don't fit that standard,
there is something wrong with you, and it's so fucked up.
Makes me so mad.
Yeah, let me...
Okay, I was on Twitter the other day as I often am,
and I saw one of my followers, an artist,
and she posted a thing that was like, you know,
my art then and my art now,
and it was like a drawing of like an idle girl
with a microphone doing a song and dance, whatever.
And the new one was better,
but I couldn't help but notice that the old one was skinny,
and the new one had like a noticeable potbelly.
And I was like, is that...
I wonder, is that part of the improvement
that I'm meant to be seeing here?
Is the implication here that that is necessarily better?
She's become enlightened about body positivity, dude.
Can we all agree that fat people
deserve to be ashamed of themselves?
They deserve to be thrown to concentration camps
and burned a lot.
I'm speaking as someone...
I'm not grotesquely fat,
but I feel ashamed of how fat I am right now,
and I find that to be healthy.
I think I should be ashamed because I should be healthier.
I should be working out.
It's a motivating fucking factor.
Because you feel exponentially better
when you're not fat.
I've been there, and it's a much better...
Not only do you feel better, you function better.
I think that shame is a healthy component of a good society.
I agree.
Shame is important.
How else do you get people to desert you?
Shame, shame, and go vote it up.
We can't force people to do things.
You can't force people to eat healthy.
So instead, we've got this shaming mechanic.
You have to do something if you want people to...
We're not going to say...
I don't think it's right to have us pretend
that we find something attractive that we don't.
How unfair is it?
If you're super fat,
and you're like,
oh, body positivity, I deserve to look the way I want,
people should respect that,
do you extend that same thing to just horribly ugly people?
Would you pretend you found them attractive?
Because you'll notice that in all of this art
that's coming out of Tumblr,
no matter how fat the characters are,
they're still drawn with normal proportioned faces.
Oh my god.
Oh my fucking god.
This is such a pet peeve of mine.
When people draw May from fucking Overwatch,
they'll draw her with huge tits,
and a huge ass and giant thighs,
and a tiny waist.
They draw her looking fucking sexy as hell,
like hyper-sexualized, hyper-idealized body image,
and then they'll do that and say,
yes, so progressive, an overweight character,
a fat character, someone that I can relate to,
no, no, you fucking hypocrites,
you fucking bastards, you should all die,
you should all die for failing to understand this,
that it's not the fucking same,
that what you're doing is exactly the same
as the thing that you claim to be against.
Oh my fucking god, when people don't get that.
I see these trifling ass hoes
that are just big fat women who say like,
I, you know, people should love me for who I am,
but of course I'm not gonna date a fat guy, obviously not,
why would I do that?
That'd be fucking retarded, no way.
I see it, it's real, it's real.
When people draw, yeah, like I would respect someone
who drew like a comic or something
with a character who is legitimately fucking ugly.
By the way, it's bad if men do that too.
But when someone draws someone who is obviously hot,
just they have really big thighs
and pretend that that is somehow pushing an envelope,
fuck them, fuck them.
Oh, there's a lot of passion on this subject, I like it.
Yeah, this is a great show.
Yeah, just, that drives me crazy.
Like the idea, look, we're on the...
My audio is clipping like crazy, so sorry for that.
We are a YouTube...
This is a YouTube internet podcast,
inevitably, there's no way that a significant portion
of our audience is not fat.
Right, right.
And that's fine.
That's fine.
You're not a worse person, necessarily, for being fat.
Well, I mean, you are, but like, you know...
But it sure isn't making you a better person.
But here's the thing, I think most fat people
appreciate that they're not attractive.
Like, okay, one of my best friends,
my friend Dansan, I don't know if you guys have seen him,
he's like 300 fucking pounds.
He makes no excuses for that.
He thinks of himself as like,
I am not attractive, I'm not trying to go out
and like fucking pick up chicks.
I don't expect anyone to think I'm good looking.
You know, like, he's...
Yeah, he kind of...
I mean, he's not ugly.
Like, that's the thing, he's really fat.
He's chiefly, dude, he's chiefly.
I would say you can be ugly, right?
And you can recognize that you are traditionally ugly.
And you can still, like, you know, be positive
about yourself and be proactive.
And you can still go out and be social
and meet people and fucking fuck people if you want.
There are people that will fuck you no matter how ugly you are.
And that goes for men and women.
If you want to be...
If you want to be the place where the ugly people live.
If you want to be happy with yourself,
the key to that is not to, like, try to convince you
that you're something you're not.
It's to be happy with what you are.
If you're fucking fat, don't be like,
everyone should say that I'm beautiful.
No, you're ugly, deal with that,
and be happy anyways.
Just be happy for other reasons.
Let me put a caveat on this.
A lot of people will...
To an extent, I agree that, like,
there is a reason for fat stigma.
And that's because being fat is not necessarily healthy
and a person can improve themselves
potentially, you know, get thinner.
Yes, that can be done.
But I feel like a lot of people when they do that,
they sort of make this sort of insinuation
that anyone can look...
Anyone can be as thin as they want to be.
Anyone can have the body that they want.
And there are things about people's bodies
and there are ways that people look.
Including, to a certain extent, weight.
Not entirely, that are out of people's control.
And I think it's unfair to act as though
every aspect of a person's appearance
is under their control.
Yeah, I completely agree.
I just think, like, I think that...
How do I put it?
You can't make yourself a 10.
But you can at least make yourself healthy.
And it'll give you more confidence.
It'll probably make you just like a better person all around.
Like, you know, that same friend, Don Son,
he was 350 pounds at a time.
He got onto a diet
and he lost...
He did the keto diet.
He lost 100 pounds in a year.
He burned off 100 fucking pounds.
And, like, it didn't make him attractive.
Like, first of all, he never got...
He still just looks like himself.
Just a slightly skinnier version.
He got, you know, muscular
and he was still fat, but you could tell
he was like, you know, a beast.
But he wasn't doing it because he thought it would make him hot.
He was doing it because he was fucking out of shape.
And he had difficulty...
You know, we would go on, like, these hikes and stuff,
like, every year. Like, the first time,
it was almost impossible for him.
He would have a hard time going to fucking Otacon
and walking around. And so he got fucking fit.
And ever since then, he's been a way more confident person.
And here's the funny thing.
He regained that 100 pounds.
Like, as soon as he got a job,
he completely stopped working out,
fell off his diet, regained 100 pounds.
But he's still, like, you know, all the...
But he kept the confidence?
Yeah, he kept the confidence. Like, everything he learned
from gaining. That's a good deal.
Because he knows he could do it if he wanted to.
Like, if he wanted to lose 100 pounds,
he knows how it works now, and he could do that.
And it's like, well, you know,
he's comfortable with himself as a...
Like, he never really had a huge problem with the fact
that he was fat as, like, a personal thing.
Like, he always just saw it as, like, yeah, whatever.
I just like to eat a lot, you know, like, fuck it.
And by the way, let me just touch for a second
on what I believe is the origin of all of this
and is the biggest problem with this
and probably the biggest problem in the universe.
And it's... Yeah, that's right, that's right.
It's bigger than asteroids?
Is that what it was?
Well, it depends.
Maybe, maybe. I mean, they're kind of interlinked.
But it really is
an entitlement to
happiness and a cultural
desire to remove all
unhappy things from your life.
Because there's this perception, and it's getting
bigger and bigger, that
you should not have to experience bad things
in your life. And that
the more happiness you have
just all the time, your life is
objectively better. That is, in fact, not true.
Happiness is way overrated
because it doesn't get jacked shit
done. The only things that are
worth doing in life are things that are in
the pursuit of happiness and that
achieve a larger goal that makes humanity
better.
I don't know how much I agree. I believe it.
I think it's fine to cut, like,
I mean, that's like saying that you
have to have negative things
in your life. I don't think that's true at all.
They build character, dude. You do. You absolutely do.
Even having to get up in the morning
is a negative thing you have to do.
Do you think I'd be better off if I
subjected myself to every retarded comment
I get, as opposed to banning
those people? Okay, there are practical
limits to what I'm talking about here.
I'm saying that, like, I think there's a huge difference
between saying, I'm going
to avoid things that make me upset
and everyone else has to
make it so I don't see
something that makes me upset.
Hey, you know, that brings me to a great
and indefinitely, definitely
controversial monkey. You know, you're cool
and all, but your topic was not controversial enough.
This is going to blow your controversy
of your pedophile thing out of the water.
I have lots of empathy
for shitty commenters.
Yeah, that's weird. Get the fuck out of here.
I don't understand that.
I think that we need
when you read a shitty comment, you really
have to take a step back.
And that this person just does not have
the context that he needs
to be not a shitty commenter.
I have plenty of empathy for them, but
it's like, okay, understand
okay, if someone, like,
stabbed me in the leg
and I completely understood
all of the reasons that they stabbed me in the leg
I would still stab them back.
Like, it doesn't...
Even if it was a mistake,
I mean, okay,
let's say it was a total...
stab you, you would stab them back.
No, let's say it was a total
let's say it was a total accident.
I wouldn't stab them back,
but I would expect reparation.
Right? Like, let's say I'm standing...
Are you fucking Indian?
Like, if someone, like,
throws a spear for some reason,
like, there, let's... That's racist!
I was thinking
before he said anything about the word Indians.
Oh, Lord, reparation, spear-throwing, this is off the rail.
Well, I literally take sure
you see Ace Ventura, too, the part where
the African guy throws the spears into his legs
because he's trying to give him a spear. Like that, right?
So let's say, let's say someone's like
trying, like, someone's trying to throw
a spear at a target and they violently
miss. In that incredibly specific scenario,
if you're Ace Ventura
and your friend is trying to give you a spear,
and the spear hits me in the leg,
then I'm not just gonna be like,
oh, you know what, you missed, it's all good.
I'm gonna be like, pay for my fucking surgery,
because I can't walk anymore,
you know? So that's the way
I see it with comments, is like, no matter how
stupid the person is, no matter how much I
understand that they don't get what they've done,
the fact is that they've made me mad
and now I need to get something
in return, you know?
But did you have to be mad?
Yeah.
Did it need to make you mad?
Aren't you choosing to be mad?
For deliberately fucking with another person.
That's my philosophy on the whole world.
Are they deliberately fucking with you,
or they just not have the fucking
context that they need?
Are you such a Ben Saint that you completely
control what makes you mad
at all times?
No, no, listen, I don't control it,
but it's my responsibility
what I get mad. Listen, this is what we need to do.
What we need to do, each one of us, all five of us.
Wait a minute, no, it's not your responsibility
what makes you mad, that's what you're saying.
Yes it is, it is my responsibility
what makes me mad.
It's your responsibility to not fuck with people
I don't leave shitty comments on other people's videos
they leave it because they're bad people.
I don't know, maybe someone thinks your comments are shitty
maybe somebody out there thinks your comments are shitty
and gets mad about them, you know what?
Hang on, Moki, what were you saying?
I think what we need to do is each one of us
go down the line and name
all the types of comments that piss us off
so that people know to never post those again.
Go ahead Ben.
Oh well, lucky for you, we've addressed this a little bit.
I assume you know about comment or rules, our podcast.
Yes.
I don't think I was there, but there was a whole thing about it.
Oh, I just wanted to trick you guys
but it didn't work.
I got to fucking let this cat out of my room
she's driving me insane.
God damn it, no, I'm not letting this happen.
Anyway, how is it my fault
if someone else decides to fuck with me?
What's about a mentality, so after what you approach
you know, what do you experience?
I mean, but it's a fucking comment on the internet
how does that actually affect you, why do you care?
Because they're stupid, it's not okay
for people to be stupid, they should be rounded up
and sent to concentration camps.
They're people,
it's not their fault they're stupid,
it's not their fault they're stupid, they're the product of their upbringing
and their environment and their...
But how do we know Ben?
Ignorance of the law is not an excuse Ben.
They could be malicious...
What is that from?
An excuse, yeah, what is an excuse from?
Ignorance of the law is not, is that from a...
That's just a fucking line for real life, that's just like a thing that happens.
It sounds like something the Brisco brothers would say or something.
I want to tell you but I also don't want to tell you
because you don't...
It's from Cool Cat, it's from fucking YMS's...
No, it's from the Daddy Derek guy.
Oh yeah!
His fucking anti-copyright thing.
Ignorance of the law is...
God, I can't do his voice at all.
It's not an excuse.
What world are you living in
where you have complete control over who and what makes you mad?
I'm not, I don't have complete control of it
but it's my problem.
Well that's the thing Ben, what...
Okay, I agree with the idea,
my whole problem with social justice warriors and all that shit
is that I see it as
if you're the one who has a problem
you have to go about solving it.
Ben, you get mad at me 10 times a day!
Are you admitting that it's all your fault and never mine?
Um...
Oh shit.
I guess to a certain extent I would agree with that.
I win! I win forever!
You get in here folks!
Ben fell into my fucking trap!
That is a pretty good one.
I think getting angry about internet comments at all
is kind of on you because it's the internet.
You have to expect that shit
and to get upset about it is pretty hard.
You're absolutely 100% wrong.
I think the internet is meant for bad comments.
No, I have such a problem with that mindset
because that's like saying
like, okay, if you...
It sounds like you want to save space.
What I want is reality.
I want the world,
I want the internet to become what it is
which is reality.
In reality, if you walk up to someone...
You have the right mind of evil and hatred.
But that's the thing, it's not.
There was a time, I think, if you were talking about...
That is reality though.
If you were talking about the early 2000s
or something like back when it was all just
like a boys club of a bunch of 4chaners,
then sure, but that's not what the internet is anymore.
Everyone's on it.
A second ago you were giving a prescriptive, descriptive
argument about linguistics
and now you can't accept that the internet has changed.
It's not the definition you're used to.
No, I'm saying that the internet has changed.
There was a time back in the 2000s
when it was just
a wretched hive of scum and villainy.
When if you went online,
you should expect that it was going to be shit.
But I don't think it's like that anymore
and I think that us saying,
oh, you should expect that on the internet.
That's like saying, don't try to change anything.
Just accept things as they are.
Well, you know what, Digi?
That is exactly what I would say.
You should not try to change anything because the way
the comments are on the internet is just how people are.
Those are real people.
That is how things are.
I agree with you that that's how things are.
We should be changing how things are.
Yes, but any of you
are on the internet and they can let their true flags fly.
They can show their true colors.
And guess what?
A lot of people are stupid.
A lot of people don't take the time to fully understand something
before commenting on it and forming an opinion.
Would you not rather that it wasn't like that?
I would rather that it was possible.
It is like that.
It's not about expectation.
It's about hopes.
I have very low expectations for everything.
All of humanity, I think they're all worthless.
I have no expectations for anybody,
but I hope they can be better.
I hope that Harambe gets resurrected,
but it's not going to happen.
You have to be realistic.
If you're being realistic, it's being weak.
If you don't think you can make the world better,
then you've given up.
You're being a pussy.
Make the world better.
That's why I bleached the best series I've ever made.
I really want to shit on you
for that safe space comment.
And I'll tell you why, because you fucking stupid memers.
You whiny little petulant 4chan
fucked.
As soon as someone tells you
that maybe you should be responsible for your own actions
and not be a fucking cunt, what do you fall back at?
Oh, you just want a safe space.
What the fuck is the comment section then?
If not your fucking safe space,
where you think you can say whatever the fuck you want
and fuck with people and piss people off.
If you go on 4chan and everyone's complaining about
oh, these college kids, they want safe spaces.
Oh yeah, those stupid diluted college kids.
They want a place where no one fucks with them.
Well, what the fuck is 4chan?
If not a safe space
for bitter sociopathic little edulord fucks
to wallow in their own misery
and bring everyone down to their level.
What is it if not a safe space? You fucking fuck!
Yeah, it's an echo chamber.
I completely agree.
There's lots of them. They're all over the place.
I love being there and saying shit.
The reason why I use the term safe space
is because it sounds like you guys
are advocating for censorship in your comment sections.
And I hate censors.
No, I'm advocating for death and murder
and censorship in a comment section.
That is not a thing.
Comment section is a platform I give the audience.
I don't have to give it to them.
They don't deserve it. I shouldn't give it to them.
But I do because I have some benefit from it
which is that I like reading comments sometimes.
But there is no such thing
as censoring a comment section
because it's entirely mine.
It's like if you said
someone came onto my front lawn
and screamed,
and I kicked them out.
If you would call that censorship,
that's no different from saying
that kicking someone out of your comments is censorship.
It's not censorship. If they want a platform,
they have the entire world.
They can go make their own.
You want to go talk shit about me?
Go somewhere else on the internet.
I can't ban you from our anime.
They do.
If you bring that to my comment section,
that's my house.
I give you the platform.
It's all me.
You don't deserve it and it's not yours.
I agree with you.
I just think we need to respect
what we were saying before
is that everyone is the product of their environment
and everyone is the product of circumstance.
A shitty comment is the product of the circumstances
in which it was written.
What you were saying about taking responsibility
for the fact that you're mad,
what I think the social justice warriors aren't doing
is that.
Everyone has to change to meet my needs.
They're like, I'm offended.
When people say that, they're wrong.
I'm offended because you said this word.
Therefore, everyone has to stop saying the word.
No. What you should be saying is
I'm offended so I'm going to take measures
so that I will not encounter this word.
If you come to my comment section,
I have a very easy means
of taking measures
so that you can't bother me anymore,
which is that I ban you.
It's my comment section
where I have the control.
What would be an SJW thing to do?
What would be asking for a safe space?
Would be if I went on to the internet
and said, guys, everyone's leaving shitty comments
about me. Everyone has to stop.
Block all these websites. Block
our anime. Block this place.
Let me call the government
and file a petition to get our anime taken down
for talking shit about me.
That would be the SJW mindset.
Yeah.
I think that the appropriate response
to a shitty comment than a shitty commenter
is a shadow ban.
I think that engaging them
is a...
I have had...
You have no idea.
This is not the same...
I don't know how it's been for Jesse,
but for me, I have had
an unbelievable number of people
say this to me for their shitty comments.
I've had so many times
where someone writes something that's kind of
snide and shitty, and I come back at them
and I'm like, I correct them,
and then they'll say, oh, sorry,
I was just kind of mad in the moment
and I didn't think you would actually read this.
Well, that kind of
highlights my point.
It's the product of the circumstance.
I'm saying...
I am extremely empathetic
towards commenters, but there's
the only reason for me to do that,
the only benefit for that
is that I like
that more people have been educated.
If those people apologize and all that,
that's cool and it makes me feel all warm and fuzzy
that someone maybe is smarter now
and they'll think more about their comments,
but that doesn't mean that I'm going to do that for everybody,
because sometimes I'm just in a bad mood
and fuck out all of them.
Let me kill yourself.
It doesn't bother me.
Twist your balls up and advise.
I know you don't subscribe to it.
These people should not get away with it.
It's not okay to be stupid.
It's not okay to fuck with people.
They deserve wrath.
But there is no wrath.
Responding to them is what they want.
It is not a punishment.
It is not a punishment for you
to call them out publicly.
It is a reward.
It makes other people want to do it more.
I don't think it does, Ben,
but it does.
I think most of the people who leave shitty comments
think it's funny.
They think everybody wants that.
These are not like these mythical trolls
that people think exist who just want a response.
These are legitimate retards
legitimately saying retarded shit.
They deserve to be called out for.
If I could provide another anecdote, I do have a good one.
Verbally beaten up, just like they would be
physically beaten up if they said it in real life.
Yeah, I agree.
The feeling of being verbally beaten up
I know, and that's a big problem,
and I wish I could somehow change it.
I wish that I could invent an app
that let me punch through my computer screen
and knock someone's teeth out, but until that day comes
Alright, monkey, monkey, what's your anecdote?
So this isn't specifically about shitty commenters.
It's more about trolls on the internet,
but back in the day there was this YouTube channel
that's still up, but it's not active called Reactor.
And he was just a huge troll
and he would fuck with people, and specifically
he made a video pretending that
Grade A Under A had endorsed him
and then he made it an advertisement
on Grade's videos.
How this is relevant is that
Grade went to his video, Reactor's video
and left just a...
He left a huge
fucking paragraph
complaining and crying like a little man baby
that Reactor had done this.
And in that instance, Reactor won
because Grade responded to the troll
and complained about it.
That story makes me so happy.
Fuck Grade A Under A.
So if you blow up on a shitty commenter
then they win.
You look like a fucking idiot.
That's not a shitty commenter.
That's a genius doing some like video.
I think it's the same.
Agreed, agreed. That guy's a whole new level.
I'm gonna cut it and plant my flag here for a second
because I've told you guys many times
that I don't like the idea
of shutting down my comments.
I know did you views it as like
this is something that I control
and I'm giving you the platform
because it's all in me.
Why shut them down when you can just shadowban into the ocean?
That's a lot of work and I don't have fucking time for that.
When you get to my level of fame
you will quickly realize why
you want to close the comments.
I totally agree that I am an idealist.
Closing down my comments is like a utopia
that I have to earn first.
I have to get to a certain level before I can...
There's this one time
there was this one time on my girl
I don't know which one but like these two guys
were just arguing back and forth forever.
I wasn't even involved. One guy said
Gerlangen was the shittiest anime ever
and this other guy was defending it and this went on
for a literal year.
I'm sure that you've had this before, did you?
But a fucking year! They were still arguing
and then I eventually came in and it was...
I just came in and I said guys
this is absolutely fucking
ridiculous you need to stop
just please let's all agree
we are not going to agree on this
and that's the end of it and they actually listened
they both responded and were like
like I said I love it
when people make up for it
and I've done it countless times
the funny thing is other people responded
to this first post and started
another argument after, totally unrelated
you've told the story before on this show
but probably in commentary
probably
like what Mumki is saying about letting the trolls
win, I think the moment
you've won is when you're not bothered anymore
and the moment you're not bothered anymore
is when they're gone
and it's so easy to do, you banned them
you never have to deal with it again
or when you fucking beat them
into submission, I fucking
the same thing Nate that happened to you
happened to me the other day, only instead of arguing
for one year, two people were arguing like one day
and that got me to that level
that you were at within one day
I think it was like
two responses of people talking amongst themselves
about Metro and I said enough of this
I have to come in, I told these people
shut the fuck up you annoying idiot
this shit will not stay out
I agree with everything you said 100%
and this guy got so
Mumki shut up I'm telling a story
sorry I thought he stopped
go on Jesse, alright finish your point
but I
told these guys to shut up and this guy got so
butthurt that it turned into like a long thing
of me just verbally jack hammering
him in the face pussy until
he cried like a little bitch and eventually
after like 17 responses
of me shitting on him
he just goes okay god
so he's acknowledging that I am a god
he's acknowledging that he has
nothing left to say
and he's running home and crying like a little bitch
I won and I felt good about it so that's how you beat them
you beat them at your own game
if they want to be shitty to you, you be 10 times
as shitty to them until they cry like little
bitches and go home and die
that's how you win I think kind of proves Ben's point
because I saw one comment he said was like
dude I'm sorry I didn't expect you to read this
like I had no idea that like you
and like I'm just saying that's the perspective
he had no idea
I had a similar
I had a somewhat similar interaction
I had a somewhat similar
comment thread in the comments
of that video that we
posted in the chat a while back that was about
the guy arguing for objectivity
and art you know the really fucking stupid guy
who said that it was all a scam by
fucking land developers because
he's clearly an insane madman
I'm glad that I
don't remember the name of the channel because I don't want
to give him exposure because he's retarded
anyway someone made
a shitty comment that was like
oh so
if someone thinks that a pile of shit is
more beautiful than a work of art
are they right and I was like obviously
yes it's obviously their opinion
and then in response he just
kept calling me stupid and deluded
stupid and deluded
oh yeah I'm like
you're demonstrably wrong you don't
understand what an opinion is and he's like
well you're stupid and deluded
I just leave it at that
how do I
stupid and deluded
how do I argue with that
he's not looking at ideas
the same way you are he's got his own little
world he's living in
he's just like
here's an opinion I have really strongly
and I'm like yeah but it's just your opinion
and he's like no but I have this opinion
really strongly
first I want to let monkey talk before I go on another
huge rant what were you going to say
I was just saying I
I empathize with what you're saying
100% I see your perspective
it's just that from my personal philosophy
I view it as censorship
but I understand your point of view and I agree to disagree
right
I want to talk about
the comments section is mega city one
and I am judge dread
the price of justice is freedom
I want to bring this back out
it's like another big
like social
overlooking point because like
the way I see it like you know I empathize
I said this earlier I empathize with everybody pretty easily
right
but functionally
we have to draw lines about people's behaviors
right like if someone goes around killing people
then like
in an ideal society
where everyone understands each other
and we are all empathizing perfectly
then like we understand that that person
we know that we have to correct them somehow
right I love the idea
of the correctional facility
a place you send someone and it actually
of course this is not what we have in America
in an ideal world
where they actually work
where there's actually correctional facilities that would be great
right but functionally
right now we don't have that
and when someone commits a crime
we have to do something about it and like so
unfortunately
you just got to kill people sometimes
some people just have to die
and like that's kind of
my perspective on comments
the reason that I'm so comfortable with banning them
is that like
back when I was a smaller YouTuber
and I could actually respond to everybody
and I could make everybody understand where I was coming from
then that was
it was a beautiful time but it's long past
if I put out a video now that gets 400,000 views
and it gets
10,000 comments
then it's like if someone's really shitting up my comment section
like in a way that it's
that I find it to be detrimental to my video
that person has to die
like they have to get banned
because they are just harming
they're doing more harm than good
I thought we were talking about capital punishment
how did this get back to comments
I'm saying there's no difference, I view it all the same way
if someone goes around
on a killing spree
if someone's before that point
let's say like Elliot Roger
ideally we could have saved him before he got there
if we understood
we just need to follow the prostitute
and he would have been fine
I think I have something
that might be controversial
since we're all sharing our
unpopular opinions
although we all seem to agree
on half of them
I believe that mass murder
is not inherently wrong
well it depends on
I mean those Jews
weren't really going to much good over there
Nate?
I'm saying
in theory
if you could mass murder the right
targets
if you could find people who were just bad
because they do exist, there are people who are just bad
and need to die
I was so right, if Jesse found the death
it would have gone down exactly that way
I mean I would do the same
like I just said
okay there's this great line
from a Jane's Addiction song where he says
some people should die
that's just unconscious knowledge
and I love it
some people should die
because it'll help the world
the problem with all these mass shooters
is that they don't have their priorities straight
when it comes to targeting these people
they always make mistakes
they all get wrapped up in generalizations
it's all women or it's all Jews
it's not a group, it's all bad people
just kill the bad people
I've solved another social ailment
thank, you're welcome world
the only reason
then this comes back to the Aberdorf Linkler thing
the only reason I can't completely
subscribe to that is that I'm almost sure
that if all of society decided
we were gonna do that, I'd get killed
so that's the only reason I can't totally back it
if we were all like
let's just kill all the bad people
this is just an ideological cowardice
well that's true Digi, but to that I say
society is welcome to try
that's a good point
I'm just saying to one of my major issues
with Elliot Rogers that
he didn't target the specific people
who caused him this pain
he just went for any random people on the street
right, but there was no
specific person
it wasn't rejection specifically
but there were specific people
like James who fucked with him
like Sumai
listen to your sister
on the subject of James
I was really moved
listening to the Elliot Rogers audiobook
where you get to the part where James finally breaks
off the friendship
I want to know if your tears were genuine
I get that question all the time
I was just into the part
okay okay
he actually went out and killed a bunch of people
to get into the mindset
that's some true method acting
right there
oh shit, you made me lose track
of my point with all this fucking Elliot Rogers talk
damn it
I'm not only wrong to kill random people
but if you can really study
people and figure out which ones
are just shitty, probably shitty commenters
at home
what your fucking viewers, you don't know when you're next
oh yeah, I remember
who gets to decide who is next
well that's a thing
I think there was
back in the day, in the ancient times
everything was determined by
literal physical strength
the people who were the strongest
it makes sense, if you're in a survivalist
environment where it's like
you have to be literally strong to survive
because you have to fight tigers
and beat people up
who are fucking with your women
the physically strong
are the ones who get to have rights
that's my ideal word
I think the main reason
we got away from that
is that weak people figured out
how they can keep themselves alive
we figured out that if we can manipulate
the physically strong people
I say we because I am physically weak
us weak people figured out
that if we can manipulate the physically strong
then we can figure out
if we can convince them that we are valuable
then we can make
are you just talking about women right now?
no, women don't factor in
this is ancient society
women don't exist
they're just baby factories
in ancient times
I'm talking about weak people
if you're not the guy who's out there
beating up boars and stuff
then how do you prove to those guys
that you shouldn't be left on the hills of Thermopylae
like the Spartans
if you were fucking a defective birth
they literally left you
on the hills of Thermopylae
as I always say that we should be doing to old people
that's what they did to their old as well
because to them
all that mattered was being physically strong
and able to fight, that's all their society was based around
but meanwhile in Athens
there were all these boy fuckers
who were
beating around and like navel gazing about philosophy
and they were like how do we convince
the strong people that we are necessary
well if we figure out
how to make new weapons for them
to use and shit
and then convince them that they couldn't figure this out themselves
it's totally us, we're the smart y'all
you guys go out there and fucking bench more iron
we're gonna make these
we'll give you new tools
we convinced them
one hand
well arguably
that's how we got to this point
specialization is how society progresses
right well but here's the question
does society's
progress matter
because if it was still
just a society of the physically strong
then it would just be like a small group
of wandering nomads
and they're still living
just like every other animal in the world
who is just the same thing
they've been for fucking millions of years
they're just around
humans would be that if not for the fact that
a bunch of weak humans went like
okay well shit like if we want to survive
in this dog eat dog world
we gotta like build a robot that can
eat dogs
I'll tell you why it's important that society progresses
because there's going in this dog eat dog world
you gotta build a robot that eats dog
there's people like
I mean this is an extreme example
people like Stephen Hawking
we need those kinds of people
and we need them to survive despite
society will just take a lot longer
to get good if only the swolest
people are also our scientists
we need people that we keep alive despite
their physical limitations
we need those guys because some of them
they've got some good ideas and we want to use those
it's a question like do we
need them
in terms of like us as a species
well let me tell you my perspective is
I want humanity to proceed
as fast as possible to founding
Starfleet, colonizing the universe
meet aliens through all that fun shit
even in a recent episode of his let's play
literally said the faster we get to Star Trek
the better and I was like oh my god he's one of us
me and Nate say that exact phrase
all the time
the faster we get to Starfleet the better
but like
that's how we want it to go
and like sure
I guess you could say
that if we look at it as the earth is going to die
one day and humans are going to get off
this planet then maybe we really did
need that as a survival instinct for our species
to get like to get good at
smarts and get the fuck out of here like maybe
that was actually necessary
and we're going to do better than every other species
on this godforsaken rock you know
but like not withstanding the sun
exploding the ice skips melting
comets becoming come blown into us
we're definitely going to blow ourselves up
definitely going to blow ourselves up
not withstanding all that
if we were just a bunch of nomadic tribes
wouldn't we still be well off
no we would not
and the answer is because if the strong
were the ones in charge we never would have had
anime
oh my god you're right
anime is entirely a culture of the week
it's all about how you do it
I agree with everyone we need the strong
we need the smart people like Stephen Hawking
who are not strong but are smart enough to help us advance
we need all those people but my point is
none of those people are commenters
well alright
well we do need the idiot
comments on my japanese anime
drones to fucking turn the wheels on all these
fucking machines
who's going to make the sandwiches you know
like they said in growing pains or whatever
the dog killing robots will make the show
so basically what we have to do is get to a
society where our robots are good enough
that we can kill all the stupid people
oh my god this makes perfect sense
this is no it works right
if we get our technology good enough
that we only need the smart people
and we don't need anyone to pull the levers
then we can annihilate all those people
and then all the dumb shit will disappear
like all the religions and stuff like that all will just be gone
because we don't have dumb people anymore
this is beautiful
one thing I can say for sure is that this podcast
has definitely convinced me to have less empathy
going forward
you know what I think now is as good a time
as any to talk about how
yesterday
all my empathy died all at once
and
it has everything to do
with our good friend
monkey here oh no
yeah that's right okay so
I'll be happy to tell you so
yesterday I was
it was after work and I had gone to the gym at work
which is this empty
I've never seen another person there it's just this empty shitty place
with a couple of workout equipment things
and I like to listen to shit while I work out
and I saw that there was a live stream that monkey was doing
so
I started on and I'm listening to it
and Ben was like
in the chat
in the chat all the
a bunch of PCP guys were there did you had been there
monkey said hey to him Ben was there
you know we were talking for a little bit
and I was there
I was posting I was ready to
experience the warm embrace of a friend
of a new friendship
and in fact
there was frequent mention of like
oh look at all these PCP guys
oh it's so cool they're all here
oh Ben's here did you sir
everyone important is here
wow what a great time we're having here
meanwhile I'm getting the fucking shaft
and by the way I'm gonna put up on
go on Ben what
the literal founder
of the PCP
best guy ever
just shafted unceremoniously
I captured screenshots of my vain attempts
of my vain attempts to reach out
to form some kind of human connection
but nothing I got fucking shaft
and people were in the chat saying like
dude you should say hi to best guy ever
you should say hello and I've got pictures
so I don't know what kind of conspiracy this was
to just ruin my self image
of my self worth but it succeeded
monkey you succeeded
I was just distracted by the wonders of your yellow
episode I wanted to know what that was
oh don't it no
no you got too far
delete it and just fuck yourself
for the record
monkey only looked at like one in every
hundred messages of that chat
and I posted a billion messages
you'll see they're on screen
they're gonna be on screen you're gonna see them right now
I've got them
you keep saying that but I'm the one who has to edit this
I probably won't do that
we'll work something out
maybe we'll put a folder with them
and there's I don't know
anyway that's why I hate you monkey and
you're not cool
well anyways does anybody have parting
thoughts on this monkey do you have any parting
thoughts on this empathy topic and
oh come back to me
I gotta think about it
Ben do you have any parting thoughts
oh fuck on the
topic of empathy
um
I've just been playing devil's advocate this whole time
don't have any empathy for anyone it's stupid
watch out Ben that's a dangerous road
I was the devil
I played devil's advocate three times in rapid succession
right before the show so I've actually been the devil
all along
like bloody Mary like you looked in the mirror
yeah
devil's advocate
slowly Elliot Rogers face comes into
focus in the mirror
I went to the bathroom and I looked in the
mirror and I was like
mind comp had some good points to make
maybe we should look into
the relative IQ's of the different races
and also shitty commenters
are real cool and we should all make them and bam
I just transformed
yeah
I can easily
see you doing that just playing devil's advocate
Ben looking intensely into the mirror
like wow you know commenters aren't so bad
they're actually kind of okay
you're a monster Ben
I'm literally a monster right now
Jesse do you have any parting thoughts on this empathy
for you Ben
yeah kill them all
I agree I don't know I think I had
something intelligent to say like way back at the beginning
but I blew it
mate you have any
you have any parting thoughts
on empathy
I think our philosophies align
fairly well on this you and me didgy
I think empathy
I wish there was more I think that
we'd all do a lot better
you know I meme a lot but really I'm all about
I'm all about
like a politician coming on
like one of those commercials the ass
like you know guys
America
I meme a lot
but the true meme
is Pokemon go to the post
Pokemon go to the post folks
I want humanity to do well
I want as many people to be as happy as possible
because that's my standard for the success
of the human race
and I'm committed to it
that's my team I've chosen so
I think we would be good for that
and I think we'd all be a little better and
all that shit
I'm actually glad Ben brought up the idea
of playing devil's advocates
that's something I was thinking of
before the show even started
was how empathy is an important tool
for any
argumentative approach
much like Ben and I think Nate and a lot of you guys
I like to play the devil's advocate
most of the time when I'm arguing
it's not even for something I personally believe
and it's just for fun
and I would like to think that I can argue
in favor of any stance and that's all
oh my god it's Maddox you're Maddox
it's the biggest debate in the universe
but it's because of empathy
the ability to put yourself into the shoes
of somebody else's position is what allows you
to play devil's advocate
so for you guys Ben to say
I'm devil's advocate but I hate empathy
that doesn't make any fucking sense
because you need it in order to play devil's advocate
so I think empathy
in terms of politics it's very important
and there's not enough of it
and I think we could solve a lot of problems
if we just thought about what the opponent
was saying rather than just trying to
put out our own position
but if you even
acknowledge that your opponent
that there's any rationalization
or any idea at all
behind your opponent's position
it weakens yours
stupid audience who doesn't understand that
you guys are fucking morons
if you have a strongly held position
it's not in your interest
to play devil's advocate
or acknowledge another point of view
who would have thought that the secret to empathy
was to be the devil
actually it kind of makes sense because
who was the first one
Jesse has been saying that all along
who was the first one to hold a
contrary position to God
who but Lucifer
his first of the angels
the first to play devil's advocate
is the problem with Maddox's show
the biggest debate in the universe
which is that he's trying to play devil's advocate
against himself and play both sides of a conversation
but he lacks the empathy
to do that
is that autism man is that demon autism
yeah he's just he
that old dragon odd
that dragon odd
oh god yeah
you know my parting thoughts
to go back to what monkey said at the very beginning
that I think that
the first reason that we're lacking empathy
is that people confuse it for sympathy
and so many people think that by understanding
someone you have to agree with them
and you don't you can completely be like
you know I feel like
like I said earlier you have to kill some people
you gotta you gotta break a few eggs
to make an omelet
but at least you can feel like
you know understand
that that's not a good thing
in an ideal society we wouldn't have to do that
like you know if you empathize with everyone
you just went like look I understand
why Elliot Roger did the things he did
doesn't mean I have to excuse him
you know even if I say you know he couldn't help it
it wasn't his choice even if I say that
that doesn't mean that he's absolved
and that we have to let him go
because that's what people seem to think
every time you say every time you're like oh he couldn't
you know he was put in that position
what was he supposed to do it's like
oh are you saying we shouldn't punish him
no I'm not saying that kill the guy
he's clearly a problem for our society
people aren't able to have nuance
nigger jail is just jail by the way
there's no difference
that's right
if you ask me
we literally made that exact joke
twice
yeah he did
I can attest to this
if you ask me
the real monsters are the people
that can't empathize with someone like Elliot Roger
I think that if you can't
read his autobiography and at least empathize
with some of his feelings about feeling rejected
you know feeling like you've been dealt
an unfair hand and feeling like there's
no hope for you and how you wish things were different
but they can't be
I think it's fucked up if you can't empathize
I can tie this into my girl and log in part 2
where I talked about how the real villain
is only people like a dine
who despite reasonable arguments
being presented have a dogmatic view
of things and are unwilling to change their stance
because of it that's the real evil folks
you ruined it you made it anime
I'm sorry
but yeah that is one of the main points
I was trying to make with my Elliot Roger
video and you did it dude
the news correspondence they didn't even read the
autobiography they just had their
set in stone beliefs and they were
going to use this tragedy take advantage
of it to express their
previously held opinions
the news is fucking disgusting and even worse
even worse than their own opinions
it's the opinions that they expect
to jive with their viewers that they don't even hold
necessarily themselves
that's my devil's advocate
and in an actually devilish
evil context
they're playing devil's autism
and that's the dangerous game
that Elliot was playing
and he lost me
oh no
alright that's it for this show everybody say goodbye
wait wait wait I want to just
I haven't been on a
podcast in a while and I just want to let everyone know
that I'm posting on my fucking personal
YouTube channel and taking a page out of
monkey hears book
and I'm doing a Nuzlocke series
and if you'd like to see that click on
please click on my little icony there and go check that out
and check out all of the monkey's channels
he's not only was a great guest on here
but he makes great videos
you surpassed me and subscribers
you son of a bitch
cold corona
I've been at work
and I've heard it through for months
crafting the ultimate masterpiece
crafting videos
and I'm going to take over YouTube
and the PCP with that
what a star studded cast this is
cold corona show it up
sorry cold corona
I just you know when you mess with the bull
you get
you get surpassed
when you mess with the mammoth swine
you get the tusks
guys I just want to say thank you all
for having me on here and you're all super cool
and I hope I can come back someday
yeah I hope so monkey
I hope you come back too it was a great having you
alright everybody say goodbye
bye
yeah
I'm
supposed to be working
working
right now
I'm supposed to be working
working
right now
I'm supposed to be working
I am an asshole
I am a stupid
I've got a
deadline
don't want to do it