Okay, I'm doing me record.
Boom!
Done.
Did I record?
I can't believe it's not recording.
I want a cereal box of Ben that's, oops, all capitalism.
Oops.
That's pretty good.
You should have saved that for the episode.
Damn it.
You're right.
You know what?
I'm recording.
Yeah, fuck it.
It's all in there.
Put it in.
Put it in there.
Don't miss a second of this gold.
Just get a cereal box, you know, with the Kickstarter and whatnot, getting these donations, getting
the DCC places.
Right.
We should sync quick and then begin.
On the count of three, say sync.
One, two, three.
Sync.
All right.
That's good enough.
Welcome, everybody, to the Pro Crastinators Podcast.
The Pro Capitalism Podcast, rather, and we're here to just have a great time with
everyone.
I'm waiting.
I couldn't beat other decisions for the name change.
That is too bad.
These things happen.
I'm the best guy ever.
We got Ben Saints.
We got Munchy.
We got Tom.
You know them.
There they are.
No, we don't.
We don't have Munchy at all, actually.
Well, luckily, they have glowing icons down below.
I am signed in on Munchy's account because I am here at Slime, wait, RFCKcon, RFCKcon
6, aka Bronycon 2.
But we've been to many Bronycons.
That's not Bronycon 2.
Yeah.
Even Munchy had been to many Bronycons.
For who is it Bronycon 2?
Is it just the RFCK?
Well, for all the RFCK boys, that Bronycon was the last Bronycon was the only Bronycon.
They've all been calling this Bronycon 2, which I just...
They're not even...
Me too, I guess.
Yeah.
Well, yeah.
It's a meme, as the kids say.
But they'll give.
Maybe you've heard of it.
I mean, most of these guys were the guys who were at Bronycon, and they met each other
for the first time there.
So to them, this is basically the second big slime meetup.
You know, speaking of like this conversation...
And by the way, we have slime.
We literally have...
You have incredible.
There's like lots of slime around.
It's so fucking great.
We're sloshing.
This particular point about being...
We're the old fucks doing...
We've been to Bronycon many times, done lots of meetups, radcons, et cetera, et cetera.
It reminds me that in Yes, in the thing I did with Digi and the other anime guys, Jack
is Boy in Core, as well as Man Mode, our seasonal wrap-up, it's at the point now where Jack
is Boy is 18.
The other guys were 20, 25, something like that.
I am 29.
I am the oldest person in the group talking about children's cartoons.
It's like shit, doesn't it?
It's beginning to be deeply unsettling.
There's no way around it.
At this age, you should be creating children's cartoons.
Unironically true.
If I don't own the means of production by now, I'm beginning to doubt I ever will.
And that's the most concerning thought.
Hell yeah.
You gotta find some up-and-coming mangaka and be their producer and take all their cash.
That's the way.
Street smarts and my moral ambiguity to do what's necessary.
Finance my anime, Nate, please.
Together we'll take over the world.
That makes sense.
Well, let's talk quickly about a little thing that I'm sure we're all excited about.
Radcon 4 Kickstarter, as of the time of you hearing this, right now launched it.
It wasn't done.
Let me look at that.
It wasn't done before.
Yeah, it's doing real well.
Have you not seen the recent event?
I have.
Take a little look.
I have seen it.
Oh!
Take a look.
Okay, well, listen, here's what I already knew.
Like, you know, I kind of feel like I should tell the entire story of my weekend, like,
sort of in relation to it, but like, I don't want to drag the conversation to the side.
Okay, well, tell you what, let's just get the important detail is guys, Radcon 4 Paradise
Kickstarter is launched.
There are incredible goodies you can get by signing up for it.
And the project, look, I'm not going to pretend that we're in dire straits right now.
We are currently almost just 24 hours, like 28 hours after launching, we're at over $7,000
and that's 87% funded with over 100, 101 backers, and we've got like 30 days to go.
So I'm feeling pretty good.
Yeah.
We have two $1,000 pledgers who decided who who decided that the campaign should end
on a fucking Tuesday.
I just gave it 31 days, dog.
It's a month.
I don't know.
Doopsy, doopsy, I guess.
Listen, now the Kickstarter is going to fail and it's all your fault, so.
Listen, guys, I just want to remind everybody, look, we, by the time you hear this, I would
love it if we hit our stretch goals, keep going.
There are so many rewards and we have stretch goals waiting if we reach the ones we've already
got.
So I have no fear.
So go give money now at Radcon 4 Paradise.
Click the top link in the description.
No doubt.
Support the thing.
It's going to be on happening in like a month and a half.
Here you go.
Pretty incredible.
I was pretty confident it was going to hit its goals.
I didn't think it was going to hit them in like three days.
That looks good.
It's looking good.
It was very nice to see.
I was a little worried before we launched it.
We were all worried.
This is all going to go to shit.
Oh no.
What if it makes more money than Vapors 2?
God, I hope it does.
God, terrible.
And I'll just say that I was worried for...
The situation really has changed.
I get all nervous.
I'm like, oh God, I know now that we need to make more money than we asked for last
time in order to actually break even.
I hope we get there.
It's looking good right now.
But the situation really, people are thirsty.
It's been two years since Radcon 3.
Like Radcon 3 we went into with kind of a cloud of like, ooh, should we even be doing
a Kickstarter?
Like did you hadn't finished this thing?
Sure, this is our first one.
All that's gone.
Radcon 3 was such a success.
There was nothing bad about it.
It just took a little while to get done.
But we delivered on every fucking thing.
So as far as I can tell, people are pretty, people are rewarding us so far for our good
behavior.
Oh, the good boy points.
I'm finally catching man.
You're catching.
You got to feel this man.
So I didn't know that this RFC KCON was happening.
Well I knew it was happening this weekend.
I thought it was starting Friday.
But on Thursday I get people like, wait no.
I have to like, I have to back up because I went on a date on Thursday, on Wednesday
and I got super hammered and I was completely hungover and obliterated and I lost my phone
and I lost my wallet.
I lost everything.
My life is in shambles, right?
So everything.
Did you find them again by chance?
No.
No, it's all gone.
Oh, Jesus.
It's all gone.
Did you take them, do you think?
I don't think so.
But I mean.
That would be really funny.
But okay.
I guess you never know.
All right.
So yeah, that happened on Wednesday and I go out on this date and I lose everything
and my life is ruined.
And then.
It's too bad.
I go.
So then Thursday I'm obliterated and people are banging on my door and I'm like, what
the fuck?
Leave me alone.
I don't ever want to wake up again.
And it's fucking munchy and caszy at my house.
Like Ben, we got to go slime house right now.
Like people are getting here.
Like they're already here.
We got to go meet them.
Oh.
Oh, please.
No.
Typical Ben.
And then like only like, and then I completely forget that Radcon 4 is the thing that's happening.
And then the next.
Jesus Christ.
We do all this.
We do slime.
You know, you do slime things.
You know, you do all the obvious stuff that you do with slime, right?
Of course.
Like I don't even need to like insult you by insinuating that you wouldn't know what to
do with slime if you had some.
I appreciate that.
But you do that.
And then the next day munch is like, oh, hey, Ben, remember the Radcon 4 Kickstarter?
And I'm like, oh, God, that launched.
Oh, fuck.
He's like, oh, yeah.
It's like $4,000 and like six hours.
I'm like, okay.
Good.
Nice.
True.
And then yeah.
And then this morning I asked him like what it was at and he said like 5,000 and I was
like, oh, okay.
Pretty good.
Slowing down.
But that's fine.
And then like I checked now and it's like 7, 7, 200.
Lamal.
Yep.
I'm, I'm depressed because I mean, I'm sad that I lost my wallet and my, and my phone.
Like that, like imagine, imagine you, imagine if that happened to you, dear viewer.
Would you be this common collected about it?
Absolutely not.
You would be, you would be ravaged.
You would be, you would be in, in disarray, um, devastated.
But like I'm almost as sad because the bartender hates me and I feel bad.
Oh no.
I went back to the, I went back to the bar that I was at where I know for a fact I must
have lost it because I had it when I walked in and I didn't have it when I walked out.
So it disappeared there 100%.
And I go inside and I'm like, hey, hey, um, did you guys find like a wallet or a phone
around here?
And the bartender like glares at me.
He like sets his jaw and he glares at me and he's like, no, no, we didn't.
And I'm like, oh, okay, hey, do you, do you recognize me?
He's like, yeah, you were asking about it all last night.
We don't have it.
We still don't have it.
And I'm like, oh God, like I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
You hate me so much.
Like what did I do?
I mean, I didn't say this.
But like, I walk out.
It must have been very obnoxious.
I guess.
I guess I must have been obnoxious.
But like I walk out and I'm like, oh God, I must, for someone to hate me that much,
I must be the worst.
No doubt.
So wait, you don't remember it?
You came, like were you drunk when you came there and asked over and over again?
Well, I was, it was the second bar I'd been to.
I was a little drunk when I went in.
I was pretty fucking obliterated when I left.
You're really creating a rogues gallery of people you've had negative experiences with
while drunk.
There's them.
There's your neighbors.
They're all going to form up.
The neighbors are fine.
We patch things up with the neighbors.
Those guys are cool.
Okay.
Or so it would appear.
So it would seem.
So wait, sorry, what was the question?
No question.
Please move on.
Fine.
Anyway, but I'm saying like this interaction with this one bartender, like seemingly like
being like peeved at me, like like set the entire tone from a lesser man would have let
it ruin their weekend, but not me.
I've sold it on fortitude, the game, moral fiber.
So did that have a negative impact on RFC K stuff?
I mean, you weren't able to play, I guess fucking slime tag or whatever, you know, your
phone and shit.
Well, I mean, I was a kingpin anyway, so I wasn't like competing, but yeah, we did.
Okay.
Let me, let me give you some highlights of RFC Kcon.
We did the IRL gang violence, a game which I invented, by the way.
It's the one, basically you use your phone as a gun and the goal is that rowdies and
killers like spread out over an area and you have to shoot each other by taking a picture
of each other.
Did people correctly wear colors and posting it in the proper discord channel?
Were they pink and purple decked out?
Yes, you have to wear, you have to wear your team color.
You know, during that game, a frame sent me a picture of Kazian said, I got her for
Yenet and I appreciate that.
There was one of her in mid, she looks like really weird and off balance and tilted because
she's like in the minute of turning around to run away.
It's kind of like that one of you in mid run.
The one of me.
The legendary.
Yeah, bolting.
Yeah.
In fact, I think I have it right here as a matter of fact, here, take a look.
Is this the one?
I had a leaning, oh wait, the wrong, wrong chat here.
There we go.
Oh, that's dynamic.
I mean, this is the killing shot.
This was the killing shot.
Yeah, they both have their fucking guns out.
Wait, post the one of you, post the one of you sprinting.
Okay, we'll have to find that one.
I don't have it on hand, but we can take, we'll put it both for consideration.
It must be in the meetup server.
No doubt.
All right.
So we did that and then yesterday we went out to the Boston Common.
We made signs, we made protest signs.
We went out and we marched around the Boston Common and we raised slime awareness.
Right.
We all went out in like a big group with like signs and we just said like, slime war now.
Slime war now.
GMO.
Get GMO.
So we can link that.
Wait, how did you know about GMOs?
Cause there's a live stream of it.
I think Kof was holding the camera or something.
Look right here, somebody was holding the camera, this slime awareness protest.
Fuck, I didn't know anyone streamed it, lol.
Okay.
It was really funny.
It was really, it was really cold out, but it was actually pretty fun and like it didn't
even get boring because we just kept, we just like kept walking the whole time.
We walked by like the skating rink and like every, like people on this, like, like there
were tons of people on the skating rink and like a whole bunch of them like turned to
like look and be like, what the fuck are these guys doing?
Nice.
There was, okay, we like stopped on sort of like a footpath that's sort of like a fork
in the footpath and we just stand there and we all start singing the new Los Angeles city
and like we're chanting and we start singing the anthem and literally like the fucking
cops like roll up like and they just like stop in front of us and are just like looking
at us for a while.
And we just keep chanting and like they just wait there for a minute and then they just
like keep going.
It's just waiting to see if you're saying the end word.
We stared him down.
So that urge to kill was rising, but well done fighting it down.
It was pretty cool.
Like nobody, like nobody like gave us any trouble about it.
Like people just like seemed either like confused or like curious or amused.
It was really fun.
Appropriate.
And then last night we did the, I feel like, I feel like Radcon 4 has already started for
me because me and Munchy we did the long awaited RFCKCon lecture.
So we basically have another, what I guess you could broadly categorize as a PCP lecture
coming out, probably before Radcon even happens, Ethan's going to edit it.
So I don't know exactly how long it will be, but it's Ethan's track record for speed
of editing is a bit dubious.
I would say.
That's true.
Where's stealing your dad's?
Well, actually he finished a few of them.
Wasn't what you're saying that like they're done?
He just hasn't.
Not all of them.
Why would you ever not release a video that's done?
I don't understand them.
I don't know.
If frame, if frame was asking Munchy where's stealing your dad's and Munchy said like,
no, it's not my fault.
It's Ethan's fault.
And Ethan dodged and weaved and dove out of the line of sight of the question so he couldn't
be asked it.
Dove like he tried to dodge from my killing blow at last slide fast, where I fucking
executed him.
It was glorious.
Yeah.
Feel the shame.
The killers obliterated in real life gang violence.
Yes.
Finally.
They won something.
They started, the Rowdies had like 11 people to the killers six and like in the end, like
four of the killers were still alive.
Yeah.
Like the killers just, the killers like routed them.
It was pretty incredible.
Incredible.
Way to go guys.
And last, there's some victory.
RCKCon's been wicked fun.
It's sad that like people, oh, it's sad people are trickling out.
A weird thing happened.
And this is interesting just as a thing I did not know could happen with an Airbnb.
But like, okay, so we get to the house and it's this like quaint little like grandma
house, right?
Like this, this older woman, this older woman like owns it and we get here and she's like,
I think she's like a little confused like why like 10 guys are just like gonna be just
like partying here.
But like, she doesn't, she's not gonna, she doesn't care.
Like she's, she's, she's cool with it.
She seems, she's pretty nice.
She's a total juvie core though, but, but she, so she seems nice enough.
And then she calls us, we have the house rented for two days and she calls Monday and she's
like, Hey guys, um, I'll just let you stay another day if you just like shovel the driveway
for me.
Dang.
And we're like, yeah, like, I mean, most people already had their flights booked so they couldn't
stay.
Right, right.
But a few of us were like, yeah, why not?
I'll stay another day.
Yeah.
Cause like, cause it snowed.
Sure.
Cause it snowed and you are like, you are legally obligated to keep your sidewalks clean.
So she would have had to like come up herself and clear the driveway or something.
So she was just like, I don't want to do that.
I'll just let them do it and they can stay another day.
And she's like, yeah.
And like, don't worry about being out by noon.
You can just be out anytime.
I don't care.
Damn, that's great.
Yeah.
It was like, she's just like, just like stay in my house.
I don't give a shit.
I mean, if it's there and she like doesn't have another Airbnb lined up, it's no skin
up her back.
No, like, yeah, it costs her nothing.
She's like, I might as well let them stay.
Why not?
So is today the extra day?
Now we don't have tomorrow.
The extra day.
Today, today, we were supposed to be leaving noon today.
Now we're leaving noon tomorrow now.
That's cool.
Nice.
So that's great.
So we are now into the extra day.
See, what are you going to do?
Do you have any plans?
No, I have no idea what the plans were.
I had every intention of showing up and then I didn't know.
I didn't know.
Oh yeah, you could still come.
I know.
I could, I could like head in after this, I guess, question mark.
Wait, yes.
Do it.
Tom, you absolutely should.
Wait, didn't, didn't people message you?
Cassie messaged me.
I found out that it was going on when I saw the first live stream upload on YouTube like
halfway through yesterday.
I'm like, oh, I guess I missed that.
Wait, what?
I told, okay, I told like Cassie and Munchie like, hey, message, message crack, message
Tom.
We, like we literally talked about like, hey, is Tom going to show up?
Everyone dropped the ball because no one messaged me at all.
This is what happens when you don't have a Nate in your organization.
All these things fall through the cracks.
You got to hire someone to be your Nate guy.
That's so fucking stupid.
Yeah, it is.
I was doing nothing for the last two days, I could have been there.
That's so...
Ugh.
I mean, you know what?
To be fair, Tom, why didn't you message, you know, anybody who could maybe give you
answers here?
Well, I mean, if you didn't know, it was already happening.
I didn't know it was happening.
Okay.
I guess that's true.
Why would I message Ben and be like, hey, Ben, this thing that I don't know is going
on?
Is it going on?
Okay, fair point.
To be fair though, we couldn't let you like stay over anything because like we are, we
are like overbooked on like beds, like people like, like every, like every bed is like taken
and like, and people that don't even like, didn't even pay to stay here, keep like, like
getting wasted and like passing out on our beds and it's not cool, damn it.
Yeah.
But I guess, I guess that's my fucking RFCK story so far.
Really excited for them.
The journey continues.
The madness ensues.
Yeah.
Continuously.
Who was, I know Johnny Miller Chip was like you to, to go in over there and then everyone.
Johnny Miller Chip, he was cool.
Johnny Miller Chip.
Oh God, I'm going to feel bad.
I'm going to forget people.
Johnny Miller Chip, Ephraim, Koff, Ethan, Connor, Levy Jevy, Bevan, Nobby, Spidey Juice,
Pizza Chan.
Yeah.
I know.
The whole cat.
What about Paradox Crotch?
Oh, Chad was here.
Chad from BronyCon.
Oh, yes.
Oh, Chad.
Oh, fantastic.
Yeah.
Fantastic.
He didn't have the hair though.
That's okay.
I forgive him.
Uh, Azcan, who is like only like, not, not, he's like a pseudo slime.
GCF.
He's more of a GCF.
Slime adjacent.
Yeah.
God, I, I know I'm forgetting a couple and I'm going to feel so bad.
I, I didn't mean for you to like list everyone.
I was just wondering.
Yeah.
I'm really bored right now actually.
It sucks.
Sorry.
Let's move on.
Excuse me.
You know, Dive.
Let's throw out of the reward.
Hey, how come Crocs never comes to these things?
Is he like far away or something?
I mean, everybody comes from far away, but like, yeah.
I guess you're right.
Well, if Crocs did come to, um, number two, I think Crocs came to RFCKcon two.
Okay, fair enough.
Fair enough.
Yeah.
Um, well, there you go, everybody.
Keep your eyes peeled for RFCKcon seven and maybe you too can join these boys.
We got, we wanted, we wanted, we wanted to do the next one in like the summer or the
spring because like it's really fucking cold out these last couple days.
It sucks.
All right, let's move on with our lives.
Yeah.
So, so I will a little bit, uh, like Radcon for the, I was, it sort of fucked up my, my
weekend, um, just because of the, the stress and the fact that, um, at like the 11th, the
11th hour, it was like, we wanted to get this thing done as soon as possible because there
was a possibility that, um, the Kickstarter could take days to get approved before we
could launch it.
So we wanted to get like the, the, the trailer done and the art done and everything and the,
you know, all the texts correct.
But it was basically just me and Nate because RFCKcon had started and, uh, Tom wasn't around
for some of it.
And it was like, uh, I was trying to also get time for doing the Lord of Ghosts comic.
And I think all of that sort of like, like, uh, bubbled over into like, uh, I'm, I quote,
unquote, burnt out lol stupid and, um, I, I prioritize Radcon for, and that's all good.
And that's the Kickstarter, the Kickstarter going well really quickly was very relieving
for me, but I sort of fallen off, off the wagon a little on drawing, uh, which, you
know, I'll get back to it on Monday, but I've, I've, I've seen a new anime guys.
It's, it's, it's, it's that one that, the one with the glasses.
Favorite or whatever.
Yeah.
I watched a couple episodes back in the day, didn't get it, but that was like five years
ago and I just haven't bothered to check.
Well, um, is it that old?
I have, you know, it probably more like three years, maybe three or four.
I have never seen this before.
Maybe two.
I have not either.
San, San Getsuno Lion.
Um, it's Digi's number one of the last decade.
So yeah.
That's bullshit.
So it's kind of a recent discovery for him.
This art, this art style looks familiar though.
I feel like I've seen other things by the same artist.
Yes.
I forget who did it, but yeah.
The funny like lips are funny, but the, um, the thing I really like in episode seven
is, well, it's, it's an anime about a sort of depressed learner, loser, boy, uh, Shogi
professional guy.
Um, he's good at Shogi and he does that and he doesn't know how to talk to people or make
friends and because of tragic things and just general social awkwardness and it's kind
of sad, but then, you know, he has all these wiki friends and sort of cheer him up and
it's cool and cute and nice, uh, very emotional, very well, uh, very artistic and all that.
But in episode seven, there's this conversation he has with this, um, this, uh, sports boy,
this, uh, baseball man.
Um, and, uh, you know, he's really nervous because this guy's younger than him and much
taller and stronger and, uh, he's like, you know, being a socially awkward Nimwit, Nimrod.
Um, and he doesn't know what to say and this guy's asking him a question about, you know,
you know, being professional because this guy is a pro, pro, uh, Shogi player despite
being still in school and it's like he, this baseball boy looks up to him in that way and
he's like, he sees the determination in this baseball guy's eyes and he's like, I can't
lie to this guy.
I can't do what I do in every other conversation and just give him some flip and answer that
wouldn't be right.
So he opens up, he does, he does, he bears his soul.
He says something that's really true to himself and kind of embarrassing to admit.
And in this conversation, the guy resonates with it and he understands and he gets it.
And then Shogi boy is like, what is this feeling?
I feel happy.
I've connected with a human being and there's less, like, this is almost romantic, sort
of like, I can't believe you can talk to people and have them understand you.
And that's like so fucking valuable and I love it.
And it's like, that was the coolest moment.
It was a really cool moment because that's like, ah, I know that feel.
Sometimes that happens to me.
Sometimes I'm, I can't resonate or talk to anyone and like have them understand what
I'm feeling.
But when it works, it's so fucking real.
Well, you know what that reminds me of a little bit?
It's that like, even us in our group here, when we like talk about stuff and like meetings
or just whatever online, it's like generally via text, you know, sometimes we're on calls.
Mostly it's like through text and like, that's fine and all, but just like when we're actually
in person at something like, oh, I don't know, a rad con, it like, you know, cause like,
what do they say, like 90% of communication is nonverbal.
It's like, it's like, oh, this is kind of like how humans are like supposed to interact
and like, ah, it's just like way better and doesn't suck in every way.
We were talking about that and like people, there are people that like use, they used
to have like beef and stuff.
There's people who like use like not like each other, but then like as soon as they met
each other in person, like that all like didn't matter.
You forget what it is.
Wow.
That's like who gives a shit about that.
It always happens pretty much always.
Yep.
It's, it's, I'm so, I'm so excited for rad con for, I'm so excited to be there and just
to hang out and play video games and be silly and watch lectures and just have fun moments.
I can't wait to like go and get breakfast or whatever we do, like we eat food or whatever
we do.
Yeah.
I just think about that all the time of how like, oh, people like have friends and like
hang out on the regular and it's not something that happens like once every year, how strange.
What a concept.
I mean, that's the right way to live, but it totally is.
It's the, that's the sort of thing of those like it's so, that scene in that, in the enemy,
in the enemy was so powerful because this guy doesn't really connect with people generally.
Like it need to be a very specific kind of brain person to, you know, to click with him.
I mean, he can, he can socially under, you know, he's fine in social situations.
But like this was such a big moment for him because it's like a person that he's talking
to who really gets him on one strange little way that like he's never really admitted before.
And it's, it's one of those like, you don't want to admit that like, you don't click with
everyone you meet, even if you like them.
Like there's some, there's a certain like some, like with my brothers, like I know them
so well, we're so like close that it feels so different from meeting like a very close
acquaintance.
I mean, you guys are like high up there in terms of like people who I resonate with much
more than people I've met through school because you only see them, you know, you, you are
in proximity to them, but that doesn't necessarily mean that you, you know, feel the same way.
Like, I don't know.
Michelle tells me just for example, because I work at home, I don't, I honestly don't
interact with a lot of people day to day, except through internet, but like she'll have
like coworkers at various places and like it's just, they just, they don't connect,
you know, like they're, what are they going to talk about?
Like you can be nice, you can say things, how relatable, you talk about the movies,
you can talk about this or that and it's like, all right, did you hear about new product?
Fantastic.
One of these days, one of these days, it's going to be like, you know how like people
watch, I think you've said this, Nate, like, like people watch sports, like not because
they really care about sports, which is because it's like something to talk about.
So you like have like, you have context into no doubt, like what people are saying.
Well, eventually you get to the point that you just got to have kids, not because you
actually want to, just because otherwise what the fuck else are you going to talk about?
You have to relate about something.
That's why the internet is too powerful.
It's making people like find people that they actually connect with, like just, they're
just really far away from each other and then they don't, they don't need to watch sports
or have kids.
They don't need to do these things.
As a result, they don't invest in their local environment, perhaps they're not like focused
on, they don't develop the skills that people used to have to of like, oh, I should be able
when I'm out just to be able to like make friends and talk to people in a casual way.
You got to have a some balance of both.
I would think that.
Yeah, you definitely do.
But it's, it's, it's so much more like succulent and delicious to have a really cool internet
friend and then meet them in real life, then to practice talking to people you don't really
care about sometime that are nearby.
It's difficult.
Yep.
It's true.
I also sometimes think about how like those same people, like for example, like those
moms at work or whatever, who you can't really relate to, like if you, if you were to sit
down, like let's say you were just locked in a cave with them for no reason, like it's
one of those wacky situations where people get trapped in like a box together and you
learn like their whole backstory.
Everybody generally has some pretty interesting shit to say about their life, but like, will
you get that while stalking Kmart shelves next to them, you know, for several days?
Yeah.
That is the question.
Maybe not.
I've always had like dreams and thoughts like that, like, ah, if only, if only me and my
class were locked on a desert island, I would be able to make a friend or two.
Yeah.
But it's impossible.
You just, you can't do it in real life because life isn't structured for that sort of thing.
Everyone's moving too fast and there's always things to do.
You just got to get drunk and hang around people and maybe they'll open up and then you'll find
out that they're interesting.
That's true.
But putting yourself in as many of those situations or you lose your wallet and you're fucking
out.
Oh God, I lost everything.
Oh God, Nate, you have to call our parents and tell them that they need to get up the
device manager app and find out where my phone was last time.
Okay.
This is the first time hearing of that.
I can do that.
Well, I've been meaning to call you, but I can't because I don't have a phone.
Every time I think about it, I tap my pocket and I'm like, oh no.
That is a truly nightmarish.
Okay, remind me after and I will do that.
The one saving grace was that I, the one thing I didn't lose was my debit card because apparently
I had already given the bartender my card to open a tab with.
So when I lost my wallet, the card was not in it.
So that's something I used.
Thank God.
At least you can still spend capital.
If you can't do that, what good even are you?
You're not barely doing that.
I had like 30 bucks in cash in my wallet.
No.
I'd be more annoyed by just the sheer loss of like a license.
I have to get that.
Yeah.
I have to read.
That is worse.
I have to reapply for, I have to get another driver's license and shit.
Yeah.
You better hurry, Ben.
If you don't have an ID for Radcon, you're fucked.
You're not going to be able to get on the flight.
I mean, that is true.
That is true.
Oh, fuck.
That's true.
Better.
Yeah.
Get on that.
Do you keep your passport in your wallet?
No.
We don't do that.
No, not a passport, but my driver's license, my ID.
You will need an ID.
Yeah.
I have a totally different topic, but I did want to discuss because I am passionate about
it.
All right.
Preface, I'm going to say the word.
I'm going to say the R word, everybody.
Are you ready?
Here it is.
Right.
Deliratory.
Responsibility.
Roster fag.
Roster fag is the word.
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
Smash bros, everybody.
Smash bros.
Oh, we were talking about this.
I hate.
Yeah.
Okay.
Be me, little old bestie boy, watching the stream for the new exciting reveal of the
new, the final fifth climactic crowning jewel, no doubt, on the DLC pack.
And it's the new fucking fire emblem guy.
I mean, Jesus Christ, just kill me right now.
Like, okay.
Like people want to defend like, like fire emblem people want to defend it.
They're like, no, they're not really all the same guys.
Like if you've played the game, you know that they're all different.
They're the same.
These people, these people must understand that they are the freaks, right?
They're like, they know, you know, delusion is a powerful drug.
As a fire emblem husk, I can't really think.
I can't call myself a fan because I've been, I've been destroyed by the series so many
times.
But like, you know, games are all right.
It's just sort of like completely divorced from what it used to be, what it used to appeal
to me as, but you know, regardless, the most annoying thing about fire emblem in smash,
especially the fact that like they, like they know and they drew attention to the fact that
it's another sort of person with blue hair and they think that like what they did was
a good enough way to differentiate it and it fucking isn't.
It just isn't.
It's a blue haired lord.
It's exactly the same person.
But like the worst thing about it is not like super smash brother.
I don't even have a switch.
I don't care about the game.
It is how fire emblem in the, in the culture, you know, the pop culture of smash huge game.
So many people know smash and the overexposure of fire emblem over the years has made people
think fire emblem is fucking stupid.
Statistically speaking, let me just, just to render, there are games as well, like being
more of like anime waifu bullshit.
No doubt.
It's like some of my favorite games of all time are being buried under two different
layers of like, like dismissal.
Obfuscation.
Yeah.
Look at these stats.
The most, uh, uh, representatives from anything.
There's like, there's like 11 Mario characters.
I think I'm not counting Yoshi.
I think there's like nine Pokemon.
But then there's, there are now eight fire emblem characters.
And I was looking over statistics just for the record.
People are like fire emblems doing better.
Okay.
True.
I got none of this is my real case, but it's just funny to look at like individual games
from like Final Fantasy and, uh, and Pokemon and like even like Call of Duty, like individual
games and Mario, of course, have sold more than the totality of the fire emblem series.
So to pretend that like in terms of like popularity, that these are like, it deserves eight slots.
There's no case to be made.
Yeah.
It is a fact now.
I really likes fire emblem.
Look, he really likes it.
He, uh, apparently he didn't get to decide who was going to be in, which just even more
makes this feel like a cynical corporate decision.
Like there's, this is the fourth, the fucking fourth fire emblem character that is put in
specifically to shill a new fire emblem game.
But wouldn't this, wouldn't the cynical corporate decision be to put in something from a more
popular franchise?
Well, if there's a new game, there's a new DLC that's coming out like directly after
this is announced.
It's a cynical corporate decision in order to make products be sold of certain things.
Yeah.
They're trying to boost the fire.
The fire emblem game.
The smash bump is insane.
I mean, so many people learn about fire emblem.
I mean, most people learn about fire emblem probably through smash.
Like back in the day.
No doubt.
Back in the day, there were no fire emblem.
There was like fire emblem for GBA.
That was rare.
Like I don't think I, I literally don't think I knew what fire emblem was before they started
showing up in smash.
I am so fucking angry.
I have seen so many comments of people like, you know, like on YouTube things, like the
the only reason people know what fire emblem is is because of smash and everyone was like
thumbs up is like, yeah, this smash does everything and I'm the only one I think the only one
I know who got into fire emblem first, yeah, yeah, because it was good because it was a
I saw it in a magazine and it's like, oh, this looks cool and it was.
I was so smart back then.
You were smart.
You were a smart boy.
No doubt about it.
See, my, my thing is like, particularly people were pissed about not Dante not being in smash
with this reveal because like some hints that looked like on the same day there was a Devil
May Cry announcement from the Devil May, they were like, oh, keep this date in mind.
Why would you do that?
For Devil May Cry and everyone was just like, oh, it's happening.
It's gonna be and instead they're just like, oh, Devil May Cry 3 on switch will have real
time style switching like the new games and it's like, oh, we can do that on PC for the
last like four years.
Like, I don't care.
So it's like you made a mod paid on switch.
Good job.
And it's just like, well, the uber boner killer, just like the one two punch of just, everything's
bad.
We've talked about this a little bit before, but like, so we said that like, they were,
they do do the thing where they're like, oh, just another enemy swordsman.
We're sick of that.
What we'll do for you is do the thing that I assume the character can do in game, which
is like, this is one of the things like every five of them character is kind of like dedicated
to one set of weapons or maybe two or something.
I'm assuming that like what makes this main character different is that they can use a
variety of all like the both the axes or hammer or whatever and spear and sword.
Okay.
But, but Nate, Nate, yeah.
Think about this.
If only there was another, uh, relevant character that like switched weapons and wasn't primarily
a sword guy, maybe a real war red trench coat, you know, I'm just saying, do you think maybe
it started as Dante and they're like, wait, we need to push fire emblem.
There's a costume.
There's a costume for the female one that has a white hair, a red trench coat, like
black pants.
Oh, get fucked, Nintendo.
It's like my car.
It's an eldegard thing.
Like there's a character in fire.
But it doesn't look just like Dante.
I don't, I don't even care.
I just hate you.
All right.
I was so close to actually giving a single solitary shit about smash and you took it
away from me.
It was almost that.
Do you think, do you think, uh, a preferable one would have been like a goomba?
Dude, it could have been anybody.
The fire emblem meme is so tired out.
Like it could have been, you know, goomba, goomba for me.
Let's just take the, the example case of goomba.
I would like goomba more because this, this choice of fire emblem feels so cynical to me.
It feels so like corporatized, uh, like, we know Sakurai likes fire emblem, but like
he said himself, he was not the one who decided who was going to be in the game.
It was decided that it would be by Nintendo.
They're the ones who chose and they chose like the per, there is no personality.
Like okay, they're a teacher.
That's like one plot element or something.
It doesn't matter to anything.
Are they just silent protag or something?
Yes.
They are a silent protagonist.
That's correct.
And it's just another.
It's not like this is the first fire emblem character, right?
This is the millionth, I mean, I wouldn't even go into how annoyed I was by like the
direct itself where he was describing like the gameplay of fire emblem through the ages.
Like there aren't seven other characters in the game already.
We don't need that.
Okay.
But that, that aside.
But I started this point with the roster fag, the word roster fag.
And one of the important, the, the main thing I wanted to say on this point was that I've
been being called a roster fag a lot.
And it's true by the description of the term roster fag as in people who primarily care
about like who gets in and like representation as opposed to like gameplay.
I mean, that's absolutely me.
Okay.
But, but the thing is, like if you're just accusing people like me who primarily care
about inclusion and stuff because I view smash as a greatest hits, even Sakurai himself
said in the stream, smash has become something more.
Celebration of gaming.
Exactly.
And it, it so is.
So Digi, you're wrong about this whole animation.
Keep them out of my fucking games.
I don't want Goku.
I don't want Naruto.
No, I agree.
Fuck that.
Nah.
Goku was cool.
I think Goku could.
I like Goku.
But in terms of, in terms of like all anime, in terms of all anime, I think Goku is the
only one who, who could fit.
But anyway, um, fucking wait, what were you saying?
I was going to.
Well, I mean here, I'll just keep it.
You can feel free to interrupt anytime.
But like I was, I was saying that those people who are just calling me a roster fag, one
person said I was like, like a child on my thing.
Okay.
I think so.
Um, but their point, rather my point is that like if, if you primarily care about who gets
in, like the, the gameplay is totally secondary and can be customized in any way you want
to be.
People are like, oh my God, like a bileth or whatever has like so many amazing moves.
Like that's what I care about.
And I'm over here like, look, Sakurai tailors the moveset to be whatever he, it could be
anything for almost any character.
That is no diff, at the very least that does not exclude if Goomba got in, Goomba could
have the exact same moveset as Violet.
Like it's unthinkable that like some other character could have like a, you know, like
forward moving.
A long side B.
Like like attack canceling.
Exactly.
Stun or something.
It's, um, intellectually dishonest to assume that somebody is mad about a character, um,
like doesn't have the capacity to understand that the game could be the same, whether
or not that character is in.
It's not about the game.
It's about, you know, the celebrate like everyone loves the reactions to smash, even if they
don't play it.
For me, that's the most important thing, but that's just like, I went nuts when I saw
King K.
Rule because I like him.
He's a cool character and he hasn't been in the games and it's like, you know, he got
Ganon.
You got Bowser.
Why not?
And then there he is.
And it's like, yeah, cool.
So everyone thought King K. Rule is dead.
He'll never return to gaming like he's a deceased character.
And then in like the most important game of our generation, he just bursts forward in
beautiful HD rendering.
I would never have expected them.
Like nobody knows a shit about King K. Rule and why would they do it, but it's kind of
cool though.
It's such a different like question.
Like smash character based on like gameplay and like tournament and like viability and
where are they going to sit on like the meta and just like, it's not even, it's kind of
like, here's an announcement, we're going to talk about this video game and everyone
who likes that video game is like YouTube reviews.
It's like nobody goes to a review to learn about a thing.
They just go to see that the thing they like is being called cool and they're like, yeah,
I feel cool now.
They just want to say, yeah, my favorite thing.
That's why everyone has like ridiculous unrealistic expectations and they hold onto them because
it's fun.
It's fun to like imagine like, wouldn't it be so fucking cool if Swans was getting into
Smash?
That'd be so fucking funny.
And you know, he got in kind of, it's like, it's a community experience, more so than
a video game thing.
Nobody cares about the balance.
I mean, people who play it professionally obviously do and you know, casually a little
bit.
I mean, it's exactly like Endless War.
Nobody gives a shit about the video game.
It's all about the community.
It's all about that community engagement.
It's, you know, because I know that like a lot of people, because I've done Smash streams,
like obviously I've made it kind of a part of my thing and like I've done tournaments
and stuff.
So like I know there's people even in that little community who like way, way more care
just about gameplay.
And that's fine.
I just don't think that that in any way does anything to exclude like my additional and
kind of totally separate concern about like how I want Smash to be a celebration of like
classic games.
That's why like for me, like I understand if everybody else disagrees.
But for me, the number one character as like it would be such a magical like re-experiencing
of my childhood considering how dead he's been would be Gino, because Gino just represents
so much about like my childhood and the games I grew up playing, it would mean so much to
me.
Dude, I was thinking about Gino the other day.
Yeah.
I started crying.
It was amazing.
It is amazing.
It is amazing to think about.
I was just thinking about Gino sometimes I'm like, wow, I can't fucking believe it.
It's Gino.
That game is so good and I don't know.
I want to play it again.
Gino is so fucking cool.
He is a...
He is.
Like, do you get...
Hey, viewers, you fucking Zoomers who don't even know what the fucking like Gamecube was
your first like games station like fuck off.
At this point, it would be the Wii at the very...
Yeah.
Yeah, it would.
It would.
That's right.
Insane.
Gino is literally like a fucking like angel from like beyond space for who is like here
on earth on like a holy quest to like retrieve the seven stars and like repair the fucking
rainbow road or whatever.
And he inhabits this body of like a wooden puppet superhero and uses his fucking like
cool superhero guns and shit.
So like...
Dude.
To like assist Mario fucking Mario and Gino and Malo the cloud prince on their fucking
quest.
Blast the fuck out of other goombas.
Shoot laser beams and shit and like bullets and so fucking cool.
The Zoomers play Mario and Luigi and like Paper Mario and actually those are probably
too old for them.
But like those games, the Mario RPG since the OG Mario RPG Legend of the Seven Stars,
there's always been like star characters or like there's like a little like starly
glittering thing.
Like that character is...
But all of that...
Dude, yeah.
Like owes its existence to Gino.
Like that's okay.
Because he was so hype and so based.
Okay.
Like the stars, like the star spirits are cool.
Like they're in other Mario games.
Like I'm kind of glad that...
They're nothing compared to Gino.
I'm kind of glad that they stuck around.
I've seen them.
I've played them all.
But never have they ever been a tenth as cool as fucking Gino.
No.
Just that's why he should be in.
Just like the raw concept of what he is is like so awesome.
Indeed.
Indeed he is.
So that's our pitch for Gino getting in.
And so we Sakurai wants it.
I know Sakurai hasn't mentioned him in many years.
I believe Brawl.
He said like he wanted Gino in for various reasons they couldn't do it.
But I mean Cloud's in, a million third parties are in, they're six, six.
More character slots are open.
Come on.
One of them's got to be Gino.
One of them.
When are they going to put in Seda from Dark Cloud?
When are they going to put in Madotsky from Yume Nikki?
When are they going to put that Altillir Alchemist with the thick thighs?
That's the one that all the kids are screaming about.
When are they going to put in Altillir Heidi?
Dude, when are they going to put in O'Cami?
When are they going to put in O'Cami?
Yeah, Fortnite.
Can we get the, you know, some of those Fortnighters, just get them in.
Can we get Ninja's new skin in Smash and Fortnite?
That sounds good.
Can we get Ninja's skin in like the physical release?
Like his actual skin?
Can we get Ninja's skin like in my closet, like as a skin suit?
That would be, that's you know, that's what I'm looking forward to.
This is a threat made against his person.
Take that to the police.
Let me tell you a thing that I learned about Endless War that I didn't even know.
You can kill people and you can scalp them.
I knew this much, but you can take people's scalps and you can make leather out them and
you can craft leather into couches to decorate your house.
Oh yeah.
So you can like make entire couches out of like people's skin if you really want to.
If you want to kill like the same person over and over again.
A celebration of video games?
Can we get an Endless War assist trophy in Smash boys?
Can we make it happen?
Imagine the Endless War like stage with him in the background and like occasionally just
shoot him with his bone ready beam.
Take any map and make it green.
Just you know.
Green filter over the whole thing.
I think you should be able to play as Endless War and you're literally just completely immobile.
It's like a pillar.
Yeah, you're just an obelisk.
You cannot move.
You just have various ways to shoot your bone herding beam.
Yeah, that sounds good.
Although it's not going to work against guys like Kirby.
No bones.
No bones to be.
Oh God, what if Kirby eats Endless War?
Oh no.
No.
His bones don't stand a chance at that point.
Dude, then he gets slim.
All right, enough of this circle jerk.
The point is made.
Yeah.
One thing.
One more circle jerk.
I have never about Fire Emblem.
I have ever since Brawl, no Wii U, Smash, I've always resented the fact that they started
doing the new Fire Emblem games.
And they started that after, well, they started with GameCube and they skipped over the two
best Fire Emblem games in the franchise who have no representation whatsoever.
What about Lin?
Seven and eight.
Lin is like an assist trophy thing.
It's not enough.
Okay.
I would be even happier with a Wii fighter.
But like, you know, her or Hector, Lin or Hector from Fire Emblem 7 and Ephraim or
Joshua from Fire Emblem 8 would be like, maybe not Joshua because he's a sword boy,
but he's a very cool sword boy.
He's a red and black sword boy.
That sounds really cool.
But Ephraim is like a turquoise lance boy and it's like...
Wait, did you say Ephraim?
Yeah, Ephraim.
It's the same name.
Is Ephraim named after Ephraim from Fire Emblem?
You know, the...
Yes.
His parents played the game.
They loved it so much.
Ephraim is just a real name that exists in the real world.
The guy in Lighthouse is named Ephraim.
I guess so.
Ephraim.
Yeah.
Okay.
Fair enough.
Is that Ephraim's Christian name that God gave him when he was born or is that...
No.
No?
Okay.
All right.
Just checking.
Never mind.
But yeah, like I've always thought like...
Yeah.
Like Hector, big ax man, like Berlin band, like different sort of build, Ephraim.
It'd be a heavy.
Turquoise hair, most important, different color hair, like either of those would be great
and it's just always been said to know that those games, because of how much Fire Emblem
characters there are, I can't in good conscience hope for Hector to get in because at this
point any Fire Emblem character will be laughed out of the theater.
I will be beaten to a pulp if I say I want Hector in Smash because there are too many
and now like they're not...
Unless like Fire Emblem 7 has like a remake and they do it again, it's not going to be
a new game.
There's no reason for them to put Hector in.
So it's doubly disappointing.
I hate everything.
I have low hopes for the future of Smash games beyond this because we know things are going
to be cut back so much.
This game is like an anomaly.
But like if they cut like everyone except like, like Marth, and I'll give them one other,
take your pick, any of the others, if they do that, then I can be like, okay, you can
put in a new Fire Emblem, no problem, put in like Hector, that sounds sick.
I think Marth, Ike and Roy was a good trio of Fire Emblem because they were all different
play styles, different things about them.
That's true.
But now we got so many fucking duplicates.
It's insanity.
Do you know even...
How many of these guys could just be Echo Fighters?
I mean, well, one of them is an Echo Fighter, Lucina is a clone, right, as opposed to an
Echo Fighter?
Or is she an Echo Fighter?
I don't fucking know.
I forget.
It's a nightmare.
I don't know.
I remembered something that I think people will be hyped to know.
It's about the RFCK Lecture, but in the proud tradition of me injuring myself at these
things, I injure myself in the middle of it, in the RFCK Lecture, I suffer a physical
injury to my body, which I continue to have to this very moment.
Wow.
Ben is just such a killer, he has to try and kill himself constantly.
I like that hook.
I want to know and find out what body part is injured.
I won't say what happened, but I get injured.
Remember when I broke my fucking foot at Red Con 2?
It's kind of like that, but like, funnier, but like sadder.
And the show goes on, I assume, beyond this.
Oh yeah, no, I don't fucking, I don't, I never give up.
Excellent, excellent.
And by the way, I was going to say one last thing about Byleth, which was just, I always
say I'll be happy with any character, so like, I'm always happy to have a new character,
but given the limited slots is why I have some reservations here.
Well, I mean, now we know that the slots are not limited.
They could just keep doing this forever.
But there could have been seven good characters, instead of six, that would have been better,
you know?
Yeah, I mean, there's already characters that I've never played ever in Smash, and I don't
You know the truly sad thing, though?
I mean, that's true.
The truly sad thing, actually, I've gone, like, as a result of, like, Smash and everything,
I've played Fire Emblem, I've played Earthbound, I've played Mother 3, I've tried to find most
of the obscure ones.
I like to do that stuff.
Like, after playing, or after listening to, or reading the JoJo manga, I like went and
listened to like all those albums that things are named after just for fun.
But anyway, I was just going to say that, like, I was thinking a little bit about getting
this new Fire Emblem, and tragically, based on, unfortunately, considering everything
I've said, I kind of want even more to get the new Fire Emblem now, just so I know what
the fuck's up with it.
No, they got you.
I know, see, it's working.
They got the fucking hooks in you.
All right, here's the explanation.
It sounds like a comfy game to play, and because this isn't like, this is Baby Mode
Fire Emblem, it's not like I have to worry about, like, actually playing a hard game.
This game, you can grind infinitely, you can train up, oh, it sounds relaxing, so.
I just seen, I saw a lemon tart player when he was in London, and he explained that, you
know, you can put, you can change, you know, back in the day, it was like a narrative story
where, you know, each level is a map, and you have to use strategy to get your way to
the end with losing zero people, hopefully.
Fire Emblem is now morphed into a game that is less about, you know, serious strategy.
I mean, there's lots of options, but you can easily make a character OP, or like min
max to heck, and you can also marry them, and I don't know.
I mean, he likes it, I could see it, the appeal.
But he likes-
All the girls are terrible.
There's no good ones.
Convince me otherwise.
You can't.
I'm just saying compared to other girls, this series, they're just, they're so normal.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
The whole series, you got Lynn, you got Florina.
Okay, Lynn is great, but-
Florina is very good.
There's definitely a few others I can't think of the moment.
I mean, I like Eldegard, sure she's cute, whatever.
Okay, never mind.
Like, the one with the pink hair in the new game, she's pretty cute, I guess.
No, no, no, new game bad, I hate new-
Oh yeah, right, sorry, my bad.
But yeah, the new game is fine.
I think I might go get it to play in my bed.
There's certain things about the graphics that repulse me, just the fact that-
The loss of sprites has been such a blow.
I mean, that's one thing, but I saw in battle, you have a bunch of faceless, nameless subordinates surrounding your party, your character, and they look so cocky-pasted.
Is the implication that you control-
Does that imply that all along in Fire Emblem, it's actually been not a one-on-one fight with literally 10 troops on the board?
It's actually that each person controls a squad and then they-
I can imagine that was more of the point, because graphical and technological abilities were not capable of showing that many things on screen earlier on.
Well, I mean Fire Emblem started a lot earlier and there was kind of a political legacy to-
Okay, that's true, that's true.
Once they were focusing on individual animations for the characters, adding a bunch of extra people on is sort of like, you have to animate them and make them do things, but now they have the resources to do that, but it still kind of looks cheap and lame and I don't like them being there.
But that's just a mean thing.
Just stop putting them in Smash, just cut it out guys. Please say Psych. Please say Psych, Sakurai.
I'm waiting for it.
We were saying during the stream like, alright, this is a misdirect. Goku is gonna spirit bomb them to death and Goku's gonna be confirmed. I cannot wait, but it did not happen. I'm still waiting.
But from what I've heard, Byleth as the main character is like you and therefore is no personality at all.
Just like Robin, just like Robin in the other one. It was just like a tactician with no personality.
That's the thing, I played Fire Emblem Awakening.
I think they did have lines. They have lines. They do say things. They have their own character. You are not literally them. You've changed what they look like, but they have a story and an arc and a character and a personality.
Whereas this one is literally you. It's just a blank.
Yeah, as far as I understand. I mean, I may be wrong on that as well.
But anyway, fuck it. Who cares? Fire Emblem sucks.
Yeah, you're right.
Can you believe we got, okay, I know it was like a meme. Honestly, this is the most angry that I get. Not Byleth. Byleth I kind of understand.
The fact that it became a meme that Robin got in and not Crom and then they put Crom. Just no. Who cares about Crom? I fucking hate Crom.
He's the worst inclusion in Smash of all time as far as I'm concerned.
Crom.
The meme that he deserved to get in was never true. Ever. I hate Crom.
Crom is definitely the golden of Fire Emblem Smash.
He's like the fat Pikachu. No, not the, he's the new Pikachu. He's the Pikachu with the heart on its tail.
The female Pikachu.
A damn diversity inclusion and it's bullshit.
Yeah, all right, there's my case.
Moving on. I mean, I'm tapped. That's what I wanted to mostly talk about.
You didn't even mention starting to go donate to Radcon for?
What else is going on?
We can go to voicemails anytime if you want.
I played Terraria on RFCK stream.
Oh, I'm a big fan.
And that was real fun. And I've been playing it since.
Yeah.
I've been on my own just getting a whole lot of cool stuff.
I got so many sick dies.
My character wearing a white wedding dress.
I gave her like a shimmering gold die for the wedding dress.
So now she's like super incredible.
And I got like a cool cape with like a shimmery purple obsidian die for that.
And like a red acid die for her goggles.
And it's like, I'm the coolest guy of all time.
Get a screen cap when you get it.
Multiplayer Terraria on Roddy Fricker's cop killers has been really fun.
And like, I'm glad we're doing it and I want to do it forever.
Building slime base.
Maybe I'll get into it too.
Yeah, you should. You should join a game.
I do love Terraria. I just haven't played in a long time.
We're building slime base and it looks really cool.
I've got so much slime.
When I come back, you'll have so much slime, including pink slime,
because I killed a few pinkies.
Nice.
Oh, gross.
Man.
Disgusting, Roddy.
Shit.
Okay, understand.
It's bouncy, bro.
Yeah, I mean, it's cool.
It's cool for what it is, I guess.
Yeah, dude, slime base.
I also got some like, this purple obsidian shimmery purple die is so killer.
I have some spare so I can give you some.
Did you give me the shimmering gold die for my slime mount?
And like, it looks really cool.
It looks like it's like gold embossed.
I think Munchie gave you that.
Okay, but it looks really cool.
It looks like foil.
This is very nice.
A lot has changed since I last played slime mounts and all these dies and shit.
Dude, writing your slime mount around is like a game changer.
Jumping on things heads with your slime mount is like the best attack you have.
Sick.
They've got this thing now where in your world, they either have corruption
or they have the crimson area, which is the equivalent,
but it's slightly different and it's got like a Cthulhuid brain boss
if you smash the things at the bottom.
And I'd never seen it before and it was like really cool.
Wait, is that in...
Oh, it sounds like it's really...
Is that in the RFCK game?
No, no, it's in my world.
I was expecting the corruption as usual with the flying guys,
but instead it was like this red tunnel of blood down into the depths
and all of these weird like gross brain spiders and it was...
Remember your first time creating your...
What do they call them?
They call it a stage, your boss stage, like down to fighting your first wall of flesh
and you make a super long one.
I've never done one.
I've never gotten that far.
No?
Because I used to play by myself.
Oh, it's good.
Oh, it's good stuff.
I always play alone because I'm a lone wolf.
But I kill them all with my guns and shit.
We kept trying to summon that like corruption worm
and he just kept despawning for now.
He would just come and we'd fight him and he would just...
We were too high up.
Yeah, he would just go away.
And we'd be like, no, come back.
Yeah, that's some bullshit.
Why?
That's some bullshit.
Mm-hmm, lame.
You gotta plan for these things.
Anyway, Tora is a great game.
Even if it's not 100% flawless with all its bugs and stuff.
I'm getting the shakes.
It's pretty cool.
I forgot it was good, but it is.
Hey, what about the Minecraft server?
It's fixed, right?
Oh, good news, everybody.
Minecraft server is back up.
We fixed the issue.
Thank God.
All is well.
I was afraid you were gonna be like,
actually, it's never coming back.
Oh, okay.
You know what?
I'm glad you mentioned that.
It took some doing.
We had to actually get in contact with the server host.
With Minecraft itself.
With Mr. Minecraft.
He called us on the phone.
He said, boys, this PCP server's been raking it in for me.
I can't leave you boys hanging.
We're gonna be kind of at juicy pay.
Anyway, they basically told us what was wrong.
It was like a setting thing that was causing the problem.
He fixed it for us.
We know now what it is.
It should never happen again.
We have, in fact, upgraded Pixelmon.
All the Pixelmon stuff is what we want to do from the beginning.
All is well.
Minecraft is up and running.
I was doing my Nuzlocke stream yesterday.
At the beginning, I'm like, okay, let's go play Nuzlocke.
I load into LOL Minecraft, the server, as I go run over to Lumia's graveyard that she's
built outside Cool Guy Village, AKA Gay Guy Village for all the deceased pokes.
Oh, it's beautiful.
Oh, and down in the basement, there's a little fire pit for the voicemail god.
Future home of the voicemail god in this tomb.
It's glorious.
I can't wait to lock him in there forever.
Now I can continue my quest for a giant Volcarona with a modest nature.
The Holy Rail.
One day.
Maybe would breeding them be a fast way to get them or something?
Probably yes.
There's probably ways to...
I wonder if I could get an Everstone.
That's how you control free nature.
You get one with the nature that you want, and then the offspring keeps the nature.
Something like that, yeah.
There's ways to do it.
I've never really fucked with it before, but I guess I could.
Excellent.
I was talking to Gib about this on Twitter.
We went back and forth a little bit.
I started playing Okami HD a few days ago.
Holy fuck.
Alright, that game is incredible.
What are you playing it on, by the way?
What system?
PS4.
I found it on eBay for $5.
I thought that was a worthwhile use of money.
The last game I just played through was God of War.
The PS4, God of War.
It blows my mind that this old PS2 game, just scaled up to 1080p,
just looks so much better than God of War.
That's fucking artistry over realism, guys.
I've been banging on this drum for years,
and they didn't have to do anything to make Okami look better
than every game that's ever come out in the history of the world.
I hadn't thought about how much that game would definitely appeal to you
of all people.
Dude, it's like perfect.
I remember Okami.
Okami was fucking awesome.
I'm playing through it.
I'm trying to reverse engineer and figure out how they did all the fucking cool shit.
When I realized all the trees are sprites, they're not models,
but then when you do the fucking Zendatsu basically thing
and cut them, they turn into polygon models to fall over.
This game must have been so resource intensive for a PS2
because the way they do the outline thing is that they duplicate all the meshes
and make them transparent so you can just see the outlines around them.
Everything has double the polygon count it needs to in order to make that outline work.
They use sprites all over the place to cut down on the polygon headroom.
Oh, it's fucking gorgeous.
It's amazing.
I love it so much.
Just thinking about seeing a black tree with the little white ribbon around it
and being like, oh, it's another one.
I haven't done that one yet.
Get the brush out and turn it into Sakurai.
The first time I did the bloom power on the big Sakiya sapling thing
and it does the whole cutscene where all these flowers just come out,
I literally came.
I was like, this is the best.
Why did we...
I just stared at Kratos' volcano pores that they had to have on all of his body
for 15 hours and it was the worst.
This is just five polygons and it's pure artistry.
I've had it in games so much.
Fuck this bullshit.
Oh, it's the worst.
I know that was a clover production.
Was that Kamiya?
It was. Kamiya was the guy.
Kamiya.
Kamiya is the build of the boy himself.
Why is Matthew Matosis going to make a Kamiya review?
That's a good idea.
After watching his beautiful Joe, because it seemed like beautiful Joe...
I think Game Grumps played it for five minutes and I was like,
this sucks. This doesn't look good.
But after watching Matthew Matosis' video, I suddenly understand and appreciate it a lot.
Dude, I loved beautiful Joe back in the day.
I watched that video recently too. It was fucking sick.
Huh.
Yeah.
And so knowing that that is the same people who would go on to do clover and be Okami...
Didn't the studio immediately die after Okami?
Capcom killed them pretty quick, which sucks.
Yeah, it sucks.
Awesome.
They made a sequel, Okami Dan, which is not as good, but it's still kind of cute.
Did you see the tweet from Kamiya posted a couple months ago saying that he wants to do a sequel to Okami
and they're pushing to try and get platinum to be able to make it?
And I'm just like, if they do that, I will come in Ocean.
It'll be the best fucking day of my life.
Watch as they make it like super HD realism.
That was originally what the game was going to look like, apparently.
Holy shit, thank god they came to their senses.
It was originally going to be a realistic game and they changed the aesthetic.
The original announcement trailer, I guess, has realistic graphics.
Ew.
Yeah.
They fucking saved themselves.
That was the thing at the time.
Look at what we can render with today's technology.
That's like an equivalent of how Star Wars was fixed in editing.
Talk about like a saving grace, like later in production or something.
But like, the game's just so fucking good.
I can't believe, like aesthetically it's just so on point and the mechanics are great.
It basically has Zendatsu from Metal Gear Rising before Zendatsu with the brush.
And you can like slice things in half and it's fucking sick.
And I'm just going around just like, what can I cut in half?
Like cutting rocks in half, cutting trees in half.
Where are you in the game right now?
I just got to the second big area, the forest area.
And I got to go into the dungeon and save the kid's dog.
Oh, you will love the boss there.
I'm ready.
I'm ready for that.
I just fought Wakka.
Okay.
I love how Kamiya like has nods to Devil May Cry and like every game he does.
Cause like in Bayonetta, she says some of the cheesy one-liners that Dante said, like
flock off Featherface and you're fighting Griffin.
And then in Beautiful Joe, Alistair is like Dante's sword from the original Devil May Cry.
And that's a boss in the game.
And in this one, you know, Wakka's just like, let's rock baby, which is Dante's fucking catchphrase.
I'm just like, Dante is everywhere.
Everybody's Dante.
It's great.
I love it.
Give me more references to the best game ever made.
Maybe I should play fucking Devil May Cry because I love Wakka so much.
Dude, Devil May Cry 1 is so good.
I can highly recommend it.
Absolutely.
I should get it.
Is that like a HD like collection of them?
Yeah.
It's on PS3.
It's on PS4.
It's on Switch.
You got, you got options.
You can go anywhere.
It's like a dollar.
It's fucking sick.
Real good.
DMC1.
Classic.
The definitive.
Holds up.
It holds up.
Yeah.
But like after, after Beautiful Joe, I'm, I'm, I'm hoping and praying that Mathematosis
does a big analysis of Okami because it would be the biggest, like, um, like I haven't,
I haven't seen a review of Okami that was good enough to be like, you don't really get
it.
You don't, you don't really smart enough to, to explain the feels on display here.
Yeah.
I like Okami way more than I like Devil May Cry and I never played Beautiful Joe.
And I don't think I'd like it that much.
I feel a little bit the same about Beautiful.
I watched much of his video and I was like, yeah, this seems nice.
It doesn't seem like the game because I'm not really, I'm not, I'm not that into brawlers
and stuff.
I mean, that's my job.
Yeah.
The reason, I took me forever to play Okami because like the way people would pitch it
to me, they were like, it's like Zelda, but you're a wolf.
And I'm like, well, Zelda's gay, so I'm not playing that shit.
There was, there was literally already a Zelda where I was a wolf.
Right.
Oh yeah.
It kind of is like the whole like ranking system in fights as well.
Have you tried doing the thing to get the blue fangs?
Yeah, I figured that out.
It was fucking sick.
You just got to like slice the body while they're dying and you get the fucking demon fangs.
I'm like, yeah.
So like, like style points for, for doing things like each, there's a bunch of different enemies
and they all have specific brush techniques that cause them to be getting the blue fangs
from them.
Yeah.
And I was just like, I was like, I was thinking like playing it in the beginning.
I'm like, this is pretty good.
I'm like, it's definitely the combat is meatier than Zelda.
And when I saw Hideki Kamiya's, like, oh, maybe this won't, this will be like fun.
And then I go to the dojo and like the guys, this old man's like, I'll teach you new techniques.
I'm like, they're, they're combat upgrades in this.
And then the dude's head like flips around and it goes from an old man to like a fucking
badass old man.
And he like teaches you the moves.
I'm like, oh, this is the best game ever made.
10 out of 10.
Hey, wasn't, isn't there a thing in that game?
I think this haunted my nightmares for a long time.
It's like during loading screens, you can like mash buttons to like get items that like,
I mean, they keep every moment is technically gameplay, including loading screens with that.
But then I remember haunted me and I like, I fucked up trying to get all those very
difficult.
I don't know.
I think who was it?
Like copyrighted that.
And then they, they had to take it out of the HD version.
What?
Yeah.
It's in the PS2 and we, I think, but like, you can mash the button to get the, to get
the blue fang if you like tap the button enough times to get the pause to appear.
But in the HD version, which I also have, they got rid of that because of like somebody
copyrighted that as a game mechanic because they wanted to keep it.
That sounds like EA.
It sounds like an EA move to me or an animation move.
But yeah.
Okay.
That makes sense.
Cause like my friend Ashley, who's super fucking into Okami, she was telling me about the
minigame and I couldn't get it to work because I'm playing on the HD.
I was like, what am I doing wrong?
Now I know it's just been taken out.
Like if I was playing that game, I would be mashing too.
And I would be like, what the fuck?
I, there's no like, what do you, should they put like a disclaimer at the beginning of
the game so that people who have played previously know?
I think it just doesn't, like you press the button, in the minigame you press the button
the dog port appears and you have to make like 20 of them appear before it loads.
And I think now you press the thing and it doesn't appear.
There's nothing that happens.
That would make sense, man.
Okay.
Well, fair enough, fair enough.
That's too bad though.
That's too bad.
That's just like, if I want to play that version of Okami again, what are my options?
Emulate the PS2 game.
Emulate or just have the PS2 version.
Or just own it, yeah.
Which I'm sure I do somewhere.
I will say I have the PS2 version as well because I accidentally bought the PS2 version
at the same time because I ordered a fuck ton of PS2 games last week on eBay.
I just was like bye, bye, bye, bye.
Like I'm just in a bad mood.
I guess I'm doing shopping therapy right now.
And I played the, I started up the PS2 one just to see the difference.
It's so much better to play it in HD just because like, I'm not a huge advocate of HD remakes
because I think it's just like milking it.
But like this aesthetic benefits so much from additional pixel counts.
Like it's not like, it's not like something like, you know, like another PlayStation 2 game
like Shadow of the Colossus where like it's cleaner.
But it's, you know.
I remember it on a CRT and it looking good, but yeah, it definitely looks better in HD.
Right, playing these, playing these on like a CRT would probably still be good.
But like when you, because I have like PS2 component cables and everything to try and make them look
as good as possible on an HDTV, it's still not even close to running a native 1080.
Here at Slime, here at RFCKCon, Spidey's got like a switch, I think, or a Wii or something with like games.
And there's like, she's got like N64 games that are like hacked for widescreen.
And it's really funny that you like, they look like total shit because they're not designed to be viewed in widescreen.
Like they're playing like war, like some like Wario game, like a 3D Wario.
And like on the edges of the screen, like polygons and objects, you will just be blatantly like
popping in and popping out, even though they're not like, even though they're not that far off the screen,
just because like they're past, yeah, they're past the borders of what would have been displayed at the original resolution.
Dude, if you can get a picture of that or like some footage, I would love to see that.
That sounds fascinating.
That would be really interesting.
I wish I had a phone, lol.
Oh yeah, maybe a bar or something.
Oh, how unfortunate.
And then, okay, it was even funnier.
A Paper Mario, a thousand year door.
Like, you know how a lot of that game is like letterbox, like there's black bar at the top and the bottom?
Sure, yeah, yeah.
Well, like, that's only as wide as the original screen.
So like, it's just, the black bar just stops and like,
It's just a black rectangle.
Then there's just a full screen after that.
Yeah, yeah, the outer, like the edges of the screen are full, are full-sized.
They're not letterboxed.
That sounds like the worst way to play any video game ever.
And when there's like a screen transition, that like the screen is supposed to flash white,
only like the center, like 4x6 rectangle flashes white and like the edges just don't do it.
It's very funny.
I would just rather play it in the original version.
Yeah, no, no, obvious.
Like, this is not meant to be released.
This is like a hacked version.
This is a naughty commercially released product.
Well, right, right.
I wouldn't do that hack if someone gave me the option.
Well, I mean, if that's how you're gonna play it on the Switch, it might be the only way.
Oh yeah, I guess so.
Or maybe not, I'm not sure.
Oh, disgusting.
Just fucking hack my Switch.
I've heard people doing it.
I haven't hacked a system in quite a while.
Surely there's got to be like an option.
It would be easy to include an option to just like put black bars on the side so it's not an HD.
I mean, like at this point, I don't even know if I'd even bother hacking my Switch,
just because like technology has gotten to the point where you can go on like AliExpress
and get like a $100 handheld that'll play everything up to like N64 for like under a hundred bucks.
And it's just like, I'll just get that.
I don't have to worry about firmware updates.
It's like undoing the hack.
It's just like, it's just designed to do that.
Yeah, yeah.
Makes sense.
Good old AliExpress.
Thanks, Chinese.
Copyright don't mean nothing.
I agree.
Like half of them just ship with like all the Super Nintendo games on there already.
And it's just like, hilarious.
Fascinating.
All right.
Well, what do you say we go on to voicemails?
Let's do it.
I'm going to do a quick demonstration about all kinds of stuff.
And let me just remind everybody one more time, hit on over to that Kickstarter.
Oh, before we go, I will say that the next thing on my list of play after O'Connor is
I bought literally every Disgaea game except for the newest one because it was really expensive
still.
And I have no idea about the series at all.
I just thought the art looked cool.
And they were really cheap.
Just go by the first one, Tom, and see how you like it.
And then, you know, if you're into it.
Here's, I played the first Disgaea in high school and I loved it.
Like a lot of it was the aesthetic.
It has a really cool aesthetic, but I was really into like the tactical grid based RPGs.
I do like those kind of games.
Yeah, I don't, I don't think I would like them anymore.
I think I don't, I would not be as patient as I used to be.
It sounds very dense, which kind of scares me, but at the same time, maybe I'll enjoy
it.
I don't know.
But like, I played them.
So I really like the first one, but I didn't do any of like the randomized dungeons.
So I actually just kind of played like just the baby mode game.
And then like, I got the, I got the next game.
They made La Pucelle tactics and I thought it was so fucking lame and boring and I hated
it.
It was way worse.
And I never played another, another, it's Nipponichi, right?
Is this the studio?
Yeah, that's them.
And like, I never played, it was same with Dark Souls.
Like, like the first one only played at once, played the second one, got bored was like,
fuck it, never played another game in the series.
Dark Souls 3 is so much better.
Also Bloodborne and etc.
Bloodborne is peak.
And of course Sekiro.
The best of the bunch.
Well, the thing, Ben, interesting, I found out, because there was a game I almost bought,
almost did buy.
Why don't these companies, why don't these companies just stop making shitty second
entries?
They really should.
They just skipped that one.
There's another Disgaea called Disgaea D2, which is a direct sequel to Disgaea 1, has
all the same main characters.
It's like a continuation of their story.
Yeah, I know they did, they did make direct sequels later, which I would have been slightly
more interesting because they did not care about the world of La Pucelle.
Like, all the actual characters, none of them have much of an arc.
They all kind of just are their personality.
It's like a comedy story, right?
It's kind of just the time to take the piss.
Yeah.
Well, it's just like, when I devote like, okay, maybe 60s a bit much for a Disgaea game,
but like 40 hours to a game, I'm just saying, I prefer when there's kind of like a story
that compels me as opposed to like, basically the facsimile of a story with just like funny
characters, because I'm telling you right now, the comedy is terrible.
I did not think any of the writing was very good in like any of those games in Disgaea.
Damn.
The first one was the best.
I remember liking it as a kid.
It's downhill from there.
I remember liking it as a kid, but yeah, it would probably come off.
How many jokes do we need about Etna being insecure about being flat?
Like how fucking many do I need?
At least 50.
At least.
That was their answer.
One for every hour of game play.
Kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill.
Kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill.
Oh, they're killing everyone.
Everyone's dying.
Thank you for the slime.
I appreciate it.
Slime.
I think it's purple.
It's good.
Everybody get the fuck out of here.
Get out of there.
Sorry about the slime noise.
This is why I don't play Endless War.
Everyone's obnoxious as fuck.
Every time you try the exclamation point podcast, it gets interrupted and you die.
That was the sound of opening up Discord and seeing you have 40,000 notifications from
people saying yo, SlimerNalia.
You know what?
That reminds me.
All right.
Let's go to the voicemail.
Because the first thing we've got to stop by is we have some updates from our men on
the street of SlimeCon 6, wherever the fuck it's called.
So let's check in with them real quick.
Of course, the speak pipe link is down below if you want to leave your voicemails as well.
All right.
Our first one here of two is from Iframe at RFCKCon.
Let's hear what he has to say for us.
Take it away.
Hey, guys.
It's me, Iframe, at RFCKCon 6.
Hello.
Hey, Iframe.
And we're just out here talking about how Ben is the best PCP member on the face of the
earth.
Isn't that right, Ben?
That's a first.
I have beliefs.
I believe in justice.
Yeah.
Who are you talking to right now?
Hey, Coss.
Coss.
What is this?
Ben St.
Is this a PCP voicemail?
This is a PCP voicemail.
Hey, Nate.
You better fucking play this.
You coward.
They're all fucking angry.
Stop it.
Hey, Nate.
All right.
Well.
I was tempted to not play for that long.
You should have just immediately turned it off as soon as I said that and be like, I'm
the power play here.
Sorry about that.
Sorry about the loud noise.
Peace out, bitches.
I think that was Chad.
Good old Chad.
There you go.
That's nice.
Yeah.
That's what it's like.
Maybe I won't go after all.
That sounds like you're not going to say anything.
Dude, Tom.
You should get the fuck over here.
Immediately.
You better fucking get here right now or we will come and fucking hunt you down with
slime weaponry, the likes of which you've never seen.
That sounds kind of fun too, though.
Now I'm going to win my options.
We love slime.
We have another voicemail.
Our second and final voicemail for Morse.
Slime war.
This one is simply called slime.
Let's see what the people have to say.
Here we go.
Slime.
I think this is from the protest.
I think that's it.
Wow.
That's incredible.
He's pushing like a rusty wheelbarrow while he's saying slime.
He's coming back from the mines and he's singing his slime mining song.
Slime.
It's a great song.
You just say slime really loudly.
Slime.
That feel when you got slime.
Yeah.
I've got slime.
Let's get to the real voicemails here.
Hell yeah.
Links down below.
Speak pipe.
Okay.
So first up, we've got a voicemail here of interest and this is reporting to you from
YouTube claim hell.
All right.
Let's see what we have to say.
Go.
Hey, PCP.
I have a question for y'all.
It's a voicemail god.
So I'm wondering for anyone who's uploaded to YouTube, which I think that applies to
most of you. What's been like your worst story or your just horror copyright story, videos
getting claimed, that kind of thing? I just uploaded one of my first videos in a long
time and it was getting claimed every time. It took 8 re-edits of the same video, putting
on different effects and transitions and shit just to get it through. So I'm wondering
if you guys have a similar horror story, you know, maybe worse, maybe not as bad. Fuck
YouTube, am I right?
The worst time I ever had fucking with copyright was, it was actually via the me and digi debate
on like Bernie vs Yang.
Yeah, why's that?
Well, just because I wanted to monetize it and I put it up and it would say it was fine
but then I released it and it immediately went to not suitable for monetization. I ended
up uploading like 5 different versions of it and just fucking around with each one and
trying to be like, okay well I'll change the title in this one, I won't say the word
versus because if I change that, and I would just try to change little inconsequential things
and sometimes it would change whether or not it was monetizable but I think it was on a
delay, like I think I would change something and then wait and nothing happened and then
change something else and then it would go to be monetized but actually it was like the
previous change that had done it and it just hadn't, so it took me, I spent like an entire
day just like fucking with the title and the tags and re-uploading and re-uploading that
video just to get it to be monetized. It did ultimately work but it wasn't fucking worth
it because it got like 5,000 views so it didn't matter.
Fair, yeah, that happens. I know that our boy, voicemail god Sean here is asking because
he made a video like for the Nuzlocke where he won the rival battle thing but here was
the problem. This is an interesting case study for a guy who's like new to making videos.
He was like, it was like a seven minute long video and he put a lot of work into it but
the problem was that the base footage was like audio of like what do they call it, don't
say run from My Hero Academia and it was like a seven minute clip from My Hero Academia
of the anime and anime people are ruthless with this shit and the audio so like the final
version. You're totally fucked.
You're totally fucked. So like the way, here's the big brain strats. Basically, first of all
you can't use like big songs. You can only use like background songs none of like the
big momentous which means you're fucked if you want to use it basically. You will get
claimed most of the time. You got to use like no more than like 10 second clips at a time
at most and you got to break them up and you got to maybe insert your own audio recreated
or whatever. Maybe he's like an 8-bit remix of the song, whatever you got to do and you
will just get fucking claimed over and over and over again but like his final version
is hilarious. It's got like, it's got an overlay of like me holding my hand, my head in my
hands over like the entire video. It's like tinted pink. The audio is like tweak to fuck.
It's like painful to listen to moment to moment. It was just such an abortion was made of like
the original quality of this thing to get it past the filters and you know what, in the
end it did work. No one would ever claim this is a replacement for that original footage
of My Hero Academia. This is definitely an original production. There's no doubt in
So he did it. Good job on that for sure. Unfortunately, it was painful to experience for all human
listeners, but YouTube had no problem with it. So there's a little advice there. I've
had, I mean, fuck man, my old videos like the best anime ever, I've used tons of like
copyrighted music and clips and stuff. They get claimed to shit. I don't even expect to
make any money off of them, but keep your clip short. Don't use copyrighted music.
I mean, I've got a lot of...
Use covers of songs. That's a big stretch.
I've got a really annoying one. I've got two, but the first one was, I think my mini
clip video on Hippocrates, where for a short period there's like, there's a glitch where
a guy won't die and I wanted to put like, who wants to live forever? This Queen song.
But I was thinking, well, that's going to get claimed. I can't put Queen. So I found
an eight bit version of it and I put that in. And the eight bit version got claimed
instead as its own thing. So I'm like, oh, but I, you know, it came, that came up after
I released it and I was like, well, I don't want to take it down, re-edit it with the
real Queen. But now that I go back and watch it, it sucks because you, without Queen vocals
there, it doesn't really work.
Yeah. Yeah, it's so true. It's just like, we just have to deal with this reality. If
we want to use copyrighted clips like that, like you can get maybe like five seconds of
like, I don't know, a Justin Bieber song and get away with it, but not too much more than
that. Yeah, that was the break.
My second one was like, the fucking Kingdom Hearts one GRPJ, where like I had the music
from, you know, the beginning, the pop song, I got claimed for that. Oh, the pop song.
That'll do it.
And it was incredibly long render time. And I was like, oh, oh no, because my computer
back then was as good as I have now. So look, it took like another six hours to redo it.
And I was like, that's a whole day that it's not out. And I hate it. I hate it. Rerendering
is the worst part.
It really is.
You know, you know what's my, I think my number one worst story is probably the worst case
scenario for me is when I have a video, it like appears to be fine because this can happen
to you, especially if you work with anime a lot. You release the video thinking that
there's no claims and then later it gets claimed for something that was in it. And like my
biggest nightmare is the Chris Chan lecture will just like be claimed in the future for
like no reason.
Yeah. And I'll have to like re upload it.
You see that that's what I'm getting at. It's that my my the original Gernlogin part two
was not claimed. Like it was demonetized. It got claimed to that extent. I didn't give
a shit. At least I'm pretty sure. Maybe I had monetized on it originally. But like something
like a week or two afterward, it had accrued like 20,000 views. And for me, this is the
very beginning of my channel. I was like, I was like, fuck, yes, I'm finally making a
video that people like or that care about whatever. And then it was, I used like the
ending song from kill me baby. Maybe people know that. I don't know. And that got claimed
and it devastated me. And so what I had to do, I had no choice. I could eat, I tried
to remove the audio, but it was totally fucked. I needed the audio there. I had to re render
the video with a different song I got from somewhere else was like another anime song.
And I uploaded just a new version of the video. And like I still feel bad about like all the
comments and like stuff that was that's locked away in that old, by the way, you can find
that old version if you go to like, I've got like a playlist on best care that's like,
like the bad shit or like the old destroyed files or something like that. So that's the
the one that everybody knows actually the second version. I was uploaded after this,
which I still feel bad about. But hey, whatever. So when I have to like fix a project and re
upload, that's the worst case scenario for me. So fix everything you can before you release
it. I mean, if you can get away with using covers or eight bit remixes or just using
video game music for the most part, that usually works. Those are much safer because
audio is way easier to get tripped up on, especially after the fact that video. Yeah.
Yeah. But then I mean, man, there's some instances, I don't know how long is clips
or but like, remember when Digi just made that he made that video about girlish number
as like his favorite video or like his favorite anime that he's and then it gets like, like
months later, it gets copyright claimed and like gets a strike by the company, even though
he's just like praising and he's not using like more than a few second long clips. They
just don't. I think it's because they're Japanese and they just don't know what he's
doing. They don't know how good this is for them. I don't know what it sounds like. It
sounds like a lot of these these companies just hire someone else. Yeah. And they don't
give a shit. They're just like, they're paying us to track all this. They probably get more
money. The more claims they do, their paid per claim or something, you know, yeah, I wouldn't
be surprised. I wouldn't be surprised. Okay. All right. Let's go on to our next voicemail.
This is from frog drive. Let's see what frog drive has to say. Go. I'm at the gym being
the most absolute Chad that I am. I'm taking a shower, hard workout. Then I suddenly can't
resist it any longer. I reach down to my erect cock. My entire mind is overrun by the complete
sexual excitement for the pace you pay dating sim. The thought of Nate's masculine body
overwhelms me. I would always be safe in those big arms. Then the thought of the softness
of munchies paints a onesie rouses me even more or give and take. I know it'd be very
sensual with me down there based on his performance from his hit TV show, the last straw. And you
know, Tom Oliver would be just as good. So good. He would only need one arm. And Ben, Ben
would be the most slimy and dirtiest of them all. Bast. I open my eyes. An old man is
watching me. I aim the head of my penis towards his face. He covers away. I continue thinking
about the ravenous experiences I have with all the PCP members. Once the game is released,
I'm getting near my climax in fantasy. I'm on the floor surrounded by the PCP performing
a book hockey. They come on my face. I'm climaxing. But right as it happens, I visualize Vizipop
performing nefarious acts on her dog. Oh boy. I'm disgusted with myself for coming from
beastiality. This is the 15th time it's happened. I return home in a disheveled forlorn. Maybe
once the PCP dating sim is out, I can finally come from a human experience again. Damn. Let's
hope so. God. What a tale. What a tale of pathos. Well, best of luck. What can I say,
but fuck yeah, bro. Hey man, February 14th. The dating sim is out. I think I think that's
the right date. It's less than one month away. Goodness gracious. Shit. We should definitely
play that. Next up. At Radcon 4. Yeah, I think we should. Oh, you're so right. You're so
right. No doubt. At least for like one live stream or something, we should like live stream.
It's mandatory. It's a great idea. Like we'll us chat or the PTA to tell us who to fuck.
Great idea. Great. Oh yeah. That's the perfect thing for the PTA to win. Our decisions. Yes.
Yes. You know, just to encourage everybody out there, hey, you can always up your pledge
if you want to go into the PTA to be part of these things that we're talking about. Do
not be afraid. There's probably maybe like 10 people at like PTA or above right now,
but we want to thrive in community. I think there's like maybe more than that. Yeah, there's
in the teens, I think. Yeah. Okay. Okay. Hey, by the way, hey, by the way, last, I
was just looking at, I was looking at some stats. Radcon 3. First day, it raised about
2,000 in some. And on the second day, it was up to like 2,500. Yeah. We are in the middle
of our second day. First day, we raised almost 6,000. Today, we've raised like, we're up
to 7,500. And it's only like 5pm. Can I just point out, we started this at 87%. We are
now at 90%. We've gained like 150 or 200 bucks just like during this hour. We need 800 more
dollars to reach our goal. 800 dollars. Is this what it feels like to be Jeff Bezos?
Just making money, just like sitting around doing nothing. Like without even noticing.
Yeah. It feels good. We'd better start thinking of some pretty good stretch goals. Oh, indeed.
We've got a few good ones. Calendar at 111111. I mean, the people as suspected are going
gangbusters for both the OVA. And I've seen quite a bit of buzz about the calendar as
well. Yeah. We can make some. I think the people want the calendar. I agree. God, I'm
going to have to pick out like what anime character I am. Yeah, I know, right? The guy who just
left the last voicemail, he's going to be stoked for the calendar. You better be pledging,
dude. Oh, I've got some great ideas. Oh, I've got some great ideas. Oh, is this how it
feels? The joy of being an ethot? Like, oh, I get to be this sexy anime. I think it is.
I think it is. We're tapping into a new market here. It's sound, it's perfect. It's perfect
for us. Okay, next one up. This voicemail is from, okay, this is Alternative. Alternative
as a Nate, BGE, breadest guy ever. Let's, let's hear what he has to say. Take it away.
Go. Capitalism. When I step back and think about it, it is, it is concerning to me. Some
of the things I'm noticing. We're commodifying things like handshakes. This is going to hurt
people who buy into this shit even a little bit. How do you not realize you're being fucking
played by the system? You are nothing. You will never be anything. It's about the destruction
of innocent people who are in a society that takes advantage of them and commodifies human
interaction. God, I think you want to fucking kill myself.
All true. All true. Nate, when did you become cool?
I did that rant on a canton about an anime and it was, it was really cool.
I released a highlight video of, of basically of this like 20 minute long discussion about
this anime with a little addendum at the end, but we'll, we'll link in the description.
So it's, it's just like this part. It's the first couple of minutes are, are this main
discussion here about this new anime that Ben, I mean, you should check out at least
the first couple minutes of, of our discussion. It is.
What is the, what's the anime? So it's, it's called, the English name is like, if my favorite
pop idol made it to the Budokan, I would die. But it's like, oh, she got Budokan.
It sounds like a fucking nightmare, but go on.
It is. It's about an idol. It's about the main character is a super fan of an idol group.
And the thing is, she's like obsessively into it and she's making many, many life mistakes
in like, she's throwing so much money away. She's got like no other friends. I mean, to
me, her life appears to be spiraling downward fast and it's deeply concerning. But like
the anime presents it in like, she, she's a really pretty girl like the main, as opposed
to all the other super fans are gross guys, but it's okay. Our main character is a pretty
girl. So it's actually really nice guys.
I see.
And, oh my God, what made me want to fucking pull the trigger.
This does look fucking horrifying.
It is horrifying. The last thing that, I'll just spoil this for everybody. The last thing
that happens in the episode one is that it's heavily hinted that while it looked like the
idol that our main girl is so obsessed with actually is like creeped out by her, fittingly
so. She is absolutely a creeper and it's unhealthy. Ben, secretly, capitalism works because actually
the idol is in love with her biggest fan all along.
Oh my God, I knew it. I knew it could happen. And I knew it could be me.
Just like it could happen with me and my favorite Twitch ethot. If I keep pouring the money
on them, she will love me.
Just keep patroning.
That's right.
The PCP, they will love me back.
It's basically just the worst case scenario. And like it's played off. I think it's supposed
to be a comedy, but it's too real. It's too fucking real and it's uncomfortable to watch.
Yeah.
Sounds nasty.
It is very nasty. But you know what was interesting? I was thinking about this, Ben. It was that
a lot of people heard my rant and were like, yeah, Nate's a commie like me now. I like
him now. He's good.
Sad.
But the main thing was I approached this. I think we arrived. Me and the bread boys
arrive at a similar position of this situation is extremely fucked up. But I'm thinking
about like all the guys. And like there's one girl, but let's be real. It's mostly
guys, like almost entirely. And this pretty girl is a fantasy. I feel so sad at seeing
these guys make such horrible mistakes. Like all the people calling the PCP asking for
romantic advice or whatever, at least those guys are like trying. These guys have given
up and are just like, I'm just going to throw money away on idols. And it's so sad. And
I want these people, I want these kings to lift their head so that their crown does not
fall anymore.
You don't understand.
So whereas I think a lot of other people approach it or you know, this crowd is like, you know,
the abuse of the idols and like the frankly, the idols are complicit in this fucking system.
And I have very little sympathy for them.
Well, well, I mean, I mean, I'm sure it's I'm sure it's not like the best for anyone.
Indeed. That's the real thing. That's the real thing. And it's so weird. Like the idols
in the show are like way into this like obviously parasitic social dynamic.
Because they're making fucking bank.
I mean, they are making bank, no doubt. But they let the fans so close to them. Someone's
going to do something one day. Oh God, it's a powder keg about to explode.
No, dude, they're making bank though.
Well, keep it up, girls. Keep it up. It's working well so far.
All right. Anyway, so go check that out, everybody. Great anime, Oshiga Budokan. The most
intellectual anime of the season. No doubt about it. Sounds Kino.
All right. One more voice. Oh, thank God. We've heard enough from these. We've heard
enough from these freaks. We actually have three. Okay, my mistake.
It's all right. We'll go faster here. Keep it together, lads. We're almost there. Okay,
this one is from Don't Let The Masks Live.
This is from Pancakes Stuck Between Ben St. and A Hard Place.
All right. Let's go. Take it away.
Hey, PCP. I just pulled a big Ben St. Yikes yesterday.
Oh, no. And I was hoping you'd give me some Sage advice.
Deep cringe posts?
So I was out and about shopping when I saw this nice girl and I wound up turns it, hey,
you look nice. Big mistake.
I could tell that she was very flustered about it, so I was just going to leave and take
a big rip on my bait. But then she stopped and said, hey, you know, like, vaping's bad
for you, right? So I pulled out my gun and slid into her fat, gaping yapper and said,
you know, bullets are bad for you, right? Long story short, she's in a trunk, so I
was wondering what my options were. I don't think I'm disclaims or anything, but I also
can't let her get to the police.
Finish the job, dude. Put the bullet in you.
Are you me? That is literally me.
If that were a scenario in the TPC procrastinator's dating sim, which I'm sure it is, or if it's
not already, it now must be. I would have made all the exact same choices you did, so
I'm proud of you.
Dude, before you dump the body, check and see if she has Ben's wallet and phone. We
still haven't had one.
That's a great idea, great idea. Key items obtained, Ben's Saint's wallet and phone.
No.
Yeah.
I miss them.
Your wallet's going on a homestuck-esque adventure.
Guys, my phone, my phone was the phone from BronyCon that got the I Love Poenut sticker
on the back.
Oh, right.
And it's gone.
The world's better off, frankly.
Are you sure you can't, I mean, if you can use the thing to find a device, you could
get it back, right?
Maybe.
Contact mom and dad. This can be done. I mean, I'll tell.
They can use an app that will tell them when the phone was last sensed by the network.
Right.
Usually, a thief will power down the phone so it can't be tracked anymore, and then they
hard reset it, which will wipe everything, and then they can just do whatever they want.
Sure, but it might not have been stolen. You never know.
It's worth trying.
You know what?
That sticker on the back, who'd want to touch it, really?
It's worth trying, man. Come on.
It's worth it.
Yes, I said I was going to do it already.
Okay, okay.
Yes, yeah, I will.
Why do you think he wants to wrap this up? He's got to find his phone every minute.
The clock ticks.
I've got to go back to that bartender and be like, I'm sorry, sir, please forgive me.
Forgive me for imbibing alcohol at your establishment, sir.
What if the bartender stole it, and he's just mad because he's covering up his crime?
Real situation that you fall like the tracking device. Oh, it says it. What? It's in the
bar. It points directly to him. Oh, God, he had it all along. What do you do, Ben?
He just smirks at me.
Try and take it, kid.
Maybe I forgot to tip. Maybe I forgot to tip, and that's why he hates me. And he stole
my phone for revenge.
Can't blame him. Can't blame him.
All right.
He's been next voicemail.
Cringe-posting on Twitter this whole time.
I was going to say, the way I should play this is pretend someone actually stole my
phone like a year ago, and I've just been cringed. It's just been someone else cringed
and posting in my name this whole time.
Oh, that would explain everything.
Guys, I love Joe Biden.
So I'm in punishment. You didn't do any of it.
Klobuchar 2020.
All right. Next voicemail from our old friend Sheepolution. All right. Take it away. Go.
Hello.
I am excited about Redcon 4.
Same.
I would like to donate to Redcon 4.
I don't have a credit card.
Kickstarter only accepts credit cards.
How do I donate?
Yeah.
Redcon 4.
This is a horrible problem.
This is a horrible problem that plagues every Kickstarter that has ever existed, and I do
not know why they haven't fixed it.
There is no solution.
I mean, somebody came to me and said, Nate, I want to do it via PayPal.
Is there anything to do?
Yeah.
I don't know why.
I don't fucking know why Kickstarter doesn't accept PayPal donations.
Even if, like, technically it is possible for us to get your money, but we need Kickstarter
to get to the goal for things to come.
Like, here's the solution.
I mean, if it gets over the goal, it's possible, but then if there's like so many people, we'd
have to do all the management for that.
I mean, I'm not saying we're going to use-
That's not even that hard.
We can do it.
I did have, like, a window after the Vapors 2 Kickstarter was done where I let people,
you know, like, send me PayPal things, and I would base, and I would, like, I wrote them
down and like, okay, this person-
We can't be fucking with all that shit for Redcon 4.
You know, it honestly wasn't worth it.
Like, I'm glad that, like, those people that wanted to buy the books got to, but, like,
in terms of, like, how much did I actually make?
Like, I mean, I only sold, like, maybe, like, ten more, and, like, it's like, you know,
it was sort of, like, not worth the effort on my end.
Like-
I mean, you know, there's a couple factors here, but I think one of them is, Redcon is
supposed to be kind of an exclusive thing.
I don't even think it's necessarily a- like, let's just say if we kept giving out things
a little beyond, that a little bit waters down, I think, other people's, like, it's
a locked-in, you got this time to donate, you get the t-shirt, the pen, these are one-time
things.
Yeah.
That's just one of the many factors, but, you know.
Here's what I would say, I would say probably your best bit is either try and get a credit
card if you can.
It's not that hard.
Or-
I mean, it's not.
Or if you're not willing to do that, just, like, get someone you know who does have a
credit card to do it for you.
I mean, I have a bank card that is, like, a credit card to use for most of my early life,
but, you know, just like, it's a debit card for my bank.
That works.
I mean, can you get prepaid debit cards from, like, the grocery store and just load money
on it?
Yes.
The answer is yes.
And you can do that sort of thing, too.
Look, there's a will, there's a way, people.
Like, if you think, if you sit down and think critically, look, I understand, you're not
looking to do that much work to get this done, but I will tell you the solutions.
These prepaid debit card things, like, those work.
That would solve the answer, so you just go buy, I don't know, however much, if you want
to get a $150 tier one, make sure you leave a little bit for shipping, get like, get like
a $200 one, and then whatever's left on, you just use on your groceries like normal, like,
you can certainly do that.
Buy coffee, buy gas, whatever it is.
Yeah, whatever you would normally buy, so no money will be wasted that way.
That's a great idea.
I forgot those were a thing.
But there's, I think there's an even better solution, and it's simple, this requires
almost no work.
Becoming adult.
And this is what I would do.
I mean, I have credit cards, but like, you know, it's fairly simple, not impressive,
like, if you don't, if you're like too young or whatever, just like, ask like your mom
or dad, say like, look, mom, dad, here is the money in my bank account.
I have the money right here.
If you please donate to this, I will give you the money right now, and then you have
lost nothing and are just helping me.
And then you just put in your information for like the shipping and the names and all
that stuff.
But like, how, easy.
But like, how embarrassing though, like, I'll bet a bunch of these kids, like, they
probably like, they're sitting in the room, they're like staring at the Radcon for kicks,
they're thinking about donating, their parents walk in like, oh shit, flip over to porn,
like, sorry, mom.
I was actually just jacking on.
Mom, can I use your credit card?
I need to buy a bunch of strangers posing in scantily clad outfits in a calendar.
It's really important to me.
They walk in, you know, you quickly close your incognito browser to the Radcon for kickstarter.
They say, what were you looking at, son?
You're like, nothing, can I borrow your credit card?
They're like, what for son?
I need to buy porn, I need to buy tons of porn, please.
No, you were looking.
As long as it's nothing degenerate or weird.
You were listening to the PCP again, weren't you?
They say they're kicking you down off the chair, they start kicking you in.
And then out comes the belt.
Not on my watch.
Not that commie alt-right shit.
No, no, Sarah, it's too much of that.
Oh, you mean that infamous NazBull podcast?
PCP.
But listen, OK, I think we've provided two very workable solutions, either work with
somebody who has a credit card, if you know, if you have a friend or somebody, like, that's
easy, just pay them back.
I'm sure they'd be willing to.
It's very simple.
Or go buy one of these prepaid credit cards at like any grocery store and just put however
much you need and a little extra, you know.
Don't forget the shipping cost.
It can be pricey if you're international and shit.
So make sure you leave Runway.
There you go.
All right.
We've given you the solution.
Next one.
Next one is our last one.
OK, here we go.
And oh, I'm very excited for this.
This is every voicemail response ever.
That's what it says.
Let's give it a listen.
Go.
Hey, guys.
Mass Effect, Malfil here.
I just can't believe I got placed in the voice jail.
I'm just going to, in the next five voicemails I send, I'm going to explain the long, sad
story about why my voicemail wasn't good.
And I'm going to be saying.
It really requires.
Please buy.
Thank you.
You know, short and sweet.
Wait.
What was that last bit?
I don't know.
OK, whatever.
It was funny.
Yeah, it was good.
You really, you know, you owe us an explanation.
We need to know the full backstory.
Like, where were you?
Like, how were you feeling at the time?
Like, you know.
Were you OK at home?
What was going on in your life?
You know.
The story.
Like, you send in a message and it's like, hey guys, I saw a girl and like, it's just
cute.
And I was like, how do we ask her out?
And we go like, what a dumb question.
Just do it, idiot.
And then it's like, you write it like a month, months go by and you write and it's like, listen.
I got that voice and I was like, listen, I was born under the Brooklyn Bridge.
Under the Blood Moon.
You don't understand.
My existence was cursed from the start.
It stopped my fault.
Guys, you don't understand.
I'm a Pisces and, you know, it's just sort of a bad week for me.
Bro, like, sure, sure, our sun signs were aligned, but our moon signs, bro.
Our moon signs were all fucked up.
Opposite.
Yeah.
It's hey, man, it happens.
It happens.
I just learned the existence of moon signs.
That's like a new frontier of astrology I just heard about.
I was talking to Michelle, who retardedly likes, you know, astronomy to some degree.
Oh, no.
Astrology.
How in high school you had like an astrology website as like your homepage?
I do.
Oh my God.
Yes, I do remember that.
You love.
I check cancer every day.
You loved it.
Bro, I did no idea why you forgot about that.
But I remember that it's true.
That holy shit.
Oh, I wonder if I could, I mean, it was like one of those shitty like, you know, 90s looking
at website with like a repeated, tiled, terrible background of like a dolphin doing a flip.
Did you like read it and be like, hmm, it says I'll have a fortunate encounter today.
Better keep my eye open for that.
You know, I was a, I was a young man at the time, so I can't really remember how like
seriously I took it.
But I remember reading it and being like, like, yeah, yeah, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, you know,
use these words and be, be into it for the day, whatever that meant.
Pretty cool.
I had a lot of personality as soon as you get out of bed.
I had a lot of personality.
I had a lot of intelligence and personality.
As you do, like every day I like check my horoscope.
I crack open my fortune cookie.
Like I scratch my Lotto tickets and then I fucking, and then I attack the day.
Bro, but you're like cancer or Pisces or whatever.
That's just your star sign, bro.
The moon sign.
It's all, this is the deep lore shit, the moon sign.
The fuck is the moon sign?
I don't even know what a moon sign is, but it's a thing.
It's just like a deeper level astrology thing.
I don't believe you.
I'll tell you what it is.
It's a, it's just your normal sign is what part of the sky the sun is in when you're
born and the moon sign is just part of the sky the moon sun, the moon is in.
Okay.
And it depends on like the time of day.
Whereas like the sun sign only changes in a few months.
Yeah, it's like what time of day you were born.
That's right.
I know what side it is.
It's up.
The sky is always up.
Yeah, it's always up.
Well, except for the whole flat air thing, but...
That's still up.
We'll tackle that another time.
Still up?
The sun is under the, the disk?
No, no, no, sorry.
No, the orbit's around.
It like goes around.
The circle.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They don't stare directly at the sun at all times.
It's always up.
The moon is a dark orb and the sun is a light orb and they kind of just kind of like twirl
around each other.
And it's pretty cool.
It is, in fact, pretty cool.
It is.
All right.
That's wrap it up right there.
We're done with our voicemails.
A speak pipe link down below.
Leave us yours.
That was a good crop.
Short and sweet boys.
Keep it up.
Keep crying and telling us your sad story by your shitty voicemail.
I can't wait to hear everyone's update on all the ones that I rejected this time for
being too long.
Oh, you know, somebody left like a long one shitting on Ben.
Listen, buddy.
Only problem with that, it was just too long.
It was just too long.
If you're one of these, like, you know, brevity is the soul of wit.
Just call in, say, fuck Ben and then that'll be it.
That's a play.
That is such an incredible, like, emotional content to, like, time wasted listening to
the ratio.
It's the ideal format.
Exactly.
Exactly right.
So do that next time.
And of course, go to patreon.com.
Hey, $5 gives you, I think, 34 coming on 35 bonus episodes, or maybe I think those numbers
are close anyway.
A whole lot of fucking bonus episodes for $5 and $1 gets you into the PCP Discord.
So do both of those.
And perhaps more importantly right now, give whatever you can to the goddamn Radcon for
Paradise Kickstarter.
Great rewards.
We're making incentives.
We're doing it.
It looks very likely we're going to get there, but now is the time where you can get your
money's worth.
Let's make more shit.
90 second day, 90 percent.
90 percent.
Feels good.
We've got $2,000 pledges.
Absolutely mad lads.
But aren't we glad we didn't limit it to one?
I know I am.
Yeah, what the fuck?
I don't know why.
We did that last time because we were like so certain no one would do it.
What if we would have gotten more than one last time?
We just don't know.
Maybe we would have.
I don't know.
We might have fucked up.
I still think that maybe we should have a $500.
I don't know.
I don't know whether we can add that in now.
I'm pretty sure we can, I don't think we can change existing rewards, but I think we
can add new ones.
Amen.
I'd brainstorm it sometime.
I feel like there might be one or two freaks out there who are not willing to go in for
the full $1,000, but maybe they'd want something, maybe they'd think it was, we'll think of
something.
I don't know.
They'd get to die first.
They'd get to die first in the apocalypse.
They'd get a smooch.
They'd get a digital smooch through the screen.
And you know, here's one little thing that I don't know if we talked about it last time,
but one thing I really want to do, I can't give any promises right now, but I would love
to arrange.
This is kind of a hope thing.
I can't promise it yet.
I would love to have one of the days during Radcon, be like, on one of the days, we'll
be at this park during this date, this time.
So if you want to just hang out as part of Radcon, like Victor can come and film somebody,
play volleyball or some shit, have a fucking picnic or something, I mean, that sounds something
like that would be real fun, I think.
The day comes.
Hopefully we can make-
Fucking snow.
Everybody's miserable.
It might.
That's why we can't promise anything.
Make no plans around this.
We can't promise anything right now, but for the area.
It would be incredible.
I mean, it's definitely going to be pretty cold and chilly on the beach.
It will not be temperate.
I mean, it'll be March.
It could be nice.
It might be way better.
The average temperatures in Virginia for March are between 60 and 70, most of the time.
So that's good.
All right.
Global warming, doing its job, making the world a lot of ice.
The water will be fucking cold, probably.
Yes.
Swimming will be a nightmare, but I will do it anyway.
Which is why I want to film the splashing scenes.
It's going to be terrible.
We will just be miserable.
I wonder if Victor's camera has slow motion, because that would be, like, you know-
Oh, we'll have to talk to them.
We got to make these plans.
Oh, I want them real bad.
Well, we're not going to even have to do that unless you guys get us to the OVA stretch,
though.
That's correct, everybody.
So we have to hit max damage, 9, 9, 9, 9, we got to get there, or none of that comes
to pass.
So hey, just take that into consideration, folks, if you're thinking about donating.
I know I've seen a few people being like, I'm giving like a hundred right now, but if
I see that we're getting close to the thing and we need a little push, several people
are there waiting to upgrade in the wings if we need it.
So we'll see if we get there.
Yeah.
Very exciting.
So push it to the limit.
Duh-duh-duh.
Please do, everybody.
And I guess that's it.
Leave more voicemails.
Leave us more money.
Follow us on Twitter, at TP Crasnators, there will be updates there.
Even if you haven't given to the Kickstarter yet, I would highly recommend.
You make a Kickstarter account and you like follow the page for any updates that we release
or something.
If you think maybe we'll release something later than I'm way into, you may want to help
push us over if we make something really cool, because it's not 100% done yet.
So hey, there's a high recommendation from me.
We got a lot of ideas.
So that's it.
Very exciting, everybody.
Radcon coming up.
Sorry to keep you waiting for too long years, baby, but it's right up the pike, like two
months, and it'll be upon us, like a month and a half.
Absolutely incredible.
All right.
We'll see you next week, everybody.
That's it.
Another PCP episode.
Another one in the can.
Locked out.
See ya, then.
Bye.
Peace out, baby.
Slime.