I want to bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Hello. It's morning in America. That's not true. It's 3pm.
It's not true.
Recordingly.
It's the one time it isn't morning in America.
Any other day, any other week, I could have said that.
Welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. We're back for some reason.
Okay. What's up?
Well, it's up for me.
Oh, oblivionful is here. Hello.
I'm back-ish. I was away for a while.
Were you?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I couldn't do anything.
Like away from the podcast or away from something else?
Away from being able to record anything, whether it be PCP or drawcast or anything else, because
I was helping Kai recover from his top surgery because he got it.
Right.
Yes.
All right, that happened.
Well, I didn't know that was happening, but makes sense. Well, how is he feeling? Good?
He's feeling okay.
Cool.
He's mostly got all those functions back. He just can't lift his arms over his head for a while.
Maybe a couple more months, he'll be a fully functional human again.
I can only imagine, but it probably hurts. I mean, I would guess.
They take a samurai sword to it and just go.
Just slice fatides right off.
One single, it's an EI motion.
Jesus.
God, I don't want to.
Yeah.
And his blood is spurred to go through everywhere.
All over the floor, out the window.
Look, I didn't get a good look at it.
I think I walked past Fatidhi Ben when the surgeon was letting me check up on him afterwards.
Are you serious?
What?
Well, there was just a bin that had like some blood stains around it.
I didn't peek inside.
What do you mean a bin?
Oh, God, no.
It's not like the kind of bin you have in your house.
I know.
It was like on wheels.
It was made out of some sturdy looking plastic.
It was like a mobile contraption.
It was just in the hallway next to the room where the surgery had taken place.
I would not.
What do you expect?
Are we going to put it in jars?
Look, I don't know.
I just wouldn't want to see that.
I don't know.
You dissolve it in acid.
Same as you do with people that assassinate presidents.
Same as you do to people on Breaking Bad when you kill them.
That was the top of last week.
Damn.
Did that happen?
Who did they dissolve in acid?
They dissolved a bunch of people.
They dissolved Crazy8 and that other guy.
Oh, in the bathtub.
Right, right, right.
In the bathtub, then they dissolved some other guy.
Oh, the Victor who was like Gus's guy.
Gus slices him across the throat and they do that.
Then there was that time the boy got shot by what's his face when they were doing the train robbery.
They had to put him in acid.
I mean, the character is called Todd.
So it goes.
Todd in the shadows.
Todd was a freak.
He was an incel.
That's the most dangerous villain of all.
He was, I mean, yes, he was not good with women.
He's very awkward, but he's scary because he's like actual psycho behavior.
He doesn't have any sense of remorse or sadness when killing happens.
He's just like, yeah, yeah, I killed him.
I mean, it's no emotion comes through.
It's like whoopsy.
It's not even whoopsy.
He just doesn't think much of it.
And then like when he like locks up Jesse as like a slave to make meth for them.
He's just like, he acts as if Jesse is one of his friends.
He's like, hey, little buddy.
But he's like still like keeping him as a slave.
Hey, little buddy, whom I tortured.
How are you doing?
How are you doing, buckle?
How was he doing?
Not good.
That's too bad.
At least he can lift his hands over his head.
At least he didn't have his chest at least severed with a samurai sword.
Alyssa is not forced to sleep on his back for a month and a half, possibly two months.
Yeah, so he should sleep on your back.
I can't.
I mean, imagine a lot of people do that.
I don't sleep on your front.
Like if you got butt surgery and you have to sleep face down.
That's fine.
I should get that because I'm already doing what you need to do to deal with it.
Sleeping face down is what you do when you're dead because you don't have to breathe.
Face down?
Yeah, sleeping on your face.
I find it very difficult to sleep face down.
I can only sleep on my side.
I can't sleep on front or back.
I used to sleep on my side.
Now I sleep face down always.
Where does your nose go?
I mean, I don't know.
I have like a pillow in my head.
Is your head turned to the side?
Are you straightening your neck?
No, no.
I keep my face directly straight forward, like directly nose pointed towards the core
of the earth into the pillow.
No, yeah.
I turn my head to the side.
I keep my arms, arms up, arms up crossed, head on the arms, head to one side.
Sometimes my neck hurts, but not usually.
What do you mean arms up?
How are you?
As in my arms, like above.
Oh, like above, yeah, yeah, I get it.
Like forward, like I'm laying on my front and arms.
I was thinking like you were crossing them backwards over your back.
No.
Like behind your back.
Arms up from my downwards sideways laying orientation.
If you understand.
But like if you're trying to say.
Where do your giant titties go?
Do you have like holes cut out in the back?
That's a secret that I will take to my grave.
Maybe we should get new.
Maybe we should get new to draw a comic about that.
Not so at all.
I mean, I would like to see a new, new comic.
True.
That would be cool.
I guess we can.
I was inspired by new.
I drew Gib with giant titties a few weeks ago.
Yeah.
When did, when was that?
It was a birthday gift.
Yeah.
Oh, I don't know if I saw that one.
Well, it turned into a birthday gift, I think.
You were planning to do it anyway, but it was great.
I started drawing it and I was like, I was like slow because, okay.
I was recovering.
He took my bed and the futon that he was sleeping on,
we just put in the closet and I've been sleeping in the living room,
I guess to give him space, but for the first week,
he couldn't like leave the bed at all except to like use a bathroom,
I guess.
So I was using his computer in our room and just changing,
like just putting on like long YouTube videos to help him sleep
because he was like, he had a lot of pain medication and he was just
kind of sleeping for like most of the first week.
And the plan was to use his Sintiq and draw a little bit,
but it was hard because the Sintiq is clunky.
Sintiqs are not as good as XP pens in my experience having used both of them now.
But yeah, I wanted to draw like for the whole like couple weeks,
I'd be looking after him.
I only got a little bit of drawing done and one of them was a drawing a gib
and it was taken a long time because I was distracted by a bunch of things.
But then, but then I found out, oh, give his birthday tomorrow.
And I'm like, oh, shit.
I can't, I don't know if I can finish that in time,
but I'll, I'll try and get it done soon.
And then I did a couple of days later.
Oh, yeah.
And I guess I can, we can't exactly, we'll have to like censor it
because there's some nudity, but I can post here.
I haven't posted it anywhere outside of big boobie mommy milkers yet.
Oh, that's the place for it.
That is the place.
That's early access to the place to be.
I want to guess my Patreon discord slot too, but I'll just drop that in the chat.
Well, there they are.
Yep.
What do you draw in?
Program.
I use clip studio paint.
I also use clip studio paint.
I got frustrated with it.
I got mad at it this week.
What did it do to you this weekend?
Uh, uh, what did I, what did I need?
I needed to, oh yeah, I was working on, I'm trying to finalize the like print files
for the slime and punishment book and I needed to adjust the greens.
I needed to adjust my colors to account to, to minimize the damage
that converting from RGB to CMYK.
Yeah, so I'm trying green.
It's very hard to print for some reason.
I remember.
So I'm trying to like, you know, reduce the harm that will be done
and to do that I'm trying to, I need, I wanted to make a layer
that would basically apply a filter only to areas that were green, right?
I wanted to, you know, maybe shift the hue into more of the yellow
to make it a little easier to print
or maybe just brighten them to account for the loss of saturation
or something like that.
Uh, and it was just impossible to do it in Clip Studio Paint.
It just doesn't have what it takes.
There's no, I couldn't even like, even though, like, oh yeah,
that's more of a Photoshop thing.
Yeah, I ended up having to use Photoshop.
I ended up having to use Photoshop and then once I gave up on Clip Studio
and I went to Photoshop, I found how to do it in like five minutes.
I was like, oh, okay.
It's literally just a button I can hit.
Well, that's as close to yours for art.
And Photoshop is for image manipulation in general.
Yeah.
I mean, it seems like a lot of people draw in Photoshop.
It's funny.
I think Photoshop, a lot of people got into Photoshop as a drawing tool,
not really thinking to use it as an image manipulation thing
because it was like, ah, this is really good for all these things,
all these tools.
But actual drawing programs are much more limited on all that extra stuff.
So you sort of, if you started with Photoshop,
it seems like all these other programs are missing something.
You know, I tried to...
It's actually not true.
I started out thinking I could do it.
I was like, okay, I'll take the layer, I'll duplicate it,
and then I will, you know, use the color curve tools
to take away all the blue and the red and leave only the green.
And that gave me a layer, but the whites still became...
It kept the whites, and I was like, okay,
but I want to get rid of the whites.
I only want to keep the things that are green and not anything else.
So then I did that, and then I did it again,
but I took away the green,
so I was left with something that was only blue and red.
And then I subtracted that purple layer from the green layer
to get one that was all the greens
and nothing that was not specifically green.
And then I had sort of a map layer of the original image,
and I was like, okay, now I want to use this sort of brightness map
as a, what's the word, a mask for a, you know,
an adjustment layer to change hue and brightness.
And you can't do it.
You can't like copy paste an image to be a mask layer
for like a color adjustment layer.
The only thing you can do to like the mask for that is like,
just draw directly, like erase areas with like an eraser tool.
And that sounds so convoluted.
Yeah.
And after effects, you could just like literally use
via the Luma key, like select the green, like a green screen,
but instead of removing it, you use that to like create like a mask
where you can like have like a more brightly saturated green
or where you could just like apply like hue, like filters and shit
to like the green parts to like make them stand out more.
You can do that with a couple layers.
In Photoshop, there's literally, I couldn't believe it.
All you had to do was make a hue adjustment layer
and there's just a button in the layer panel.
That's like, do you, you can like select where on the color spectrum
you want it to specifically apply to.
It's literally just, there's a button for it.
You don't have to do anything.
I couldn't believe it.
Yeah.
So that was neat, I guess.
I was glad to discover.
I was glad that I gave up on Clip Studio Paint quickly.
Oh, her vast specific task, yeah.
I was a little intimidated by Photoshop.
I haven't really used it that much.
I find it kind of a hassle.
And sometimes it has trouble like launching on my computer for some reason
because I have a pirated copy.
I didn't pay for it.
I have a paid for copy in it.
I can confirm it's slow as fuck.
My biggest issue with Photoshop is though.
There's funny things you can do with like caching things
and stuff to make it run quicker.
I don't know.
There's tutorials.
I've ever had similar problems.
I had to look into like how to make Photoshop boot up quicker.
And there are like some things you can do.
But it worked out fine.
It was pretty good.
If it boots up quickly, I'm still going to be annoyed.
Photoshop is just filled with a bunch of like little annoying things
that just make me pull my hair out.
Like the workflow, especially for like art,
the workflow in Clip Studio is a lot faster.
Like messing with layers and stuff like that
is just a lot quicker and easier and more intuitive, I feel.
But Photoshop has one glitch
that is the worst fucking thing in the world.
Like let's say like you click on a layer
and you click on the opacity
and you want to change it from like 100 to 50
and then you go to click out.
The opacity button will stay selected like no matter what you do.
And then I'll like try to like go to some other box
to change the brush size and I type in 20 for brush size.
Even though I clicked on the brush size box,
it'll change the opacity to 20 instead.
And I can't like deselect opacity
or if I'm trying to change the zoom.
Because in Clip Studio, you can just like,
I just have a wheel on my tablet that lets me zoom in and out.
That doesn't work on Photoshop.
So I have to type in the zoom level manually
and when I go to type it in, it just changes the opacity layer
to just font size layer or whatever.
Like any box where you type in a number,
it won't let you deselect it for some reason.
And you have to like try clicking out of it
like 20 times before it works.
And I fucking hate it.
It's been like this for the last couple of updates.
And it's annoying.
I scream when I use Photoshop.
It sucks.
I like Photoshop for doing like sweeper and hella Jeff style.
Like Photoshop fuckery.
Oh, I'm just messing things up.
And like it looks bad on purpose.
It's the perfect program for that.
It looks bad in ways you couldn't even imagine
that things could look bad.
It looks bad in ways you couldn't imagine.
New ways to ruin art.
Very nice.
Very good.
It's true.
I'm trying to look for...
I got a thing to say.
It's not that big a thing.
Is it like that misfit song?
Is there a song where the misfits that goes like
I got something to say
I raped your mother today.
I'm pretty sure that's a song.
It's not that.
It's there's heat wave time in the UK.
Today it reached like 30 degrees,
which is like 87 or 86 Fahrenheit.
Tomorrow though,
it's going to go predicted to go to 40,
41 degrees,
which is 106 Fahrenheit.
It's the highest temperature,
potentially not happened yet.
Biggest temperature ever to be recorded in the UK.
Wow, really?
Yes.
And a few summers ago,
it was like 38 point something centigrade.
And now it's 41.
It's like Mediterranean like
summer levels in the UK,
which is not very exciting.
That's very exciting for you.
No, it's no.
We don't have.
I love that for you.
We don't have the facilities.
People are definitely going to die of heat related things
like dying.
I don't know how you die from heat.
Like a water probably.
I'll show you.
Damn.
Air conditioning is not common
because we don't need it.
And it's expensive.
And the buildings are designed to keep.
That's what you think winter.
Yeah.
Because it does like big old green houses,
but they're bricks.
Well, I don't know about green.
Brown house green.
I didn't paint it.
Brick Brown.
So yeah, to today,
green, whether you can't,
you can't print those then.
You can't print the CMYK.
How the fuck did they make green paint?
It doesn't make any sense.
Green is like the anti-pain.
It would consume itself and vanish from the surface.
This is an Omega based play for an artist,
like a real physical artist.
You take green paints
and you make a really big green image.
And then when people try to like,
I don't know, sell like prints of it,
it's not going to look as good.
You got to actually go to the museum
and see it or own it.
It's a real experience sort of thing.
Paint with green.
Oh, you know, I ordered a test,
a bunch of like paper samples
from this company called
Comics Wellspring,
which has horrible pricing.
Absolute horrible.
I would never actually buy from them.
Thanks for the samples, you suckers.
But they do offer.
You can do a thing where like,
you can designate an area of the page,
but they'll put like foil in the page.
You know, you can have like a little like,
a little like reflective foil kind of poke through
some parts if you want it to be shiny.
It's like, what if I made it,
what if I made it like green foil?
What if I made the slime, you know,
reflective green?
Wouldn't that be nifty?
That would be nifty.
I think there are, okay,
there are fluorescent inks
that you could print with,
but if they're not standard,
it would have to be like a custom job.
I'm sure it would balloon the price.
And I mean, the price is fucking high enough already,
printing a whole book in full photo color.
So, you know, sorry, it's terrible.
Just terrible.
Although I did find a company on Alibaba
that seems to have some like pretty decent price.
I found one that I think I might be able to get them
for like a hundred copies for like $15 a piece,
including shipping, which is like, that's pretty good.
That's pretty good as long as the quality is not terrible.
So, yeah, I'm hoping that.
Hoping that works out.
She won't, she hasn't gotten back to me.
She's bad about responding.
I asked that lady for a template.
I was like, can I have a page template, please?
And then it was Friday.
And I think like her shift ended.
And then she didn't get back to me and I'm waiting for Monday.
I'm gonna have a goddamn page template.
I'm sending my damn files.
Damn.
That's, that's, that's what's going on.
You know, I was doing some crafts this week.
I had some ideas for things that I could potentially do
as stretch goals for the Kickstarter.
And I've been crafting.
I learned how to etch a glass.
Which is, yeah, with like chemicals.
With like a, um.
Like you put a stencil and you just spread a thing on a glass.
Yes.
I found, okay, most of the time, like stencils like that,
they're like not reusable.
But I found a company called Icon Art that sells these stencils,
or it's like a system for making stencils that are reusable.
Like they are a sort of like vinyl covering over a fine mesh.
And so you can sort of get a design into the vinyl
that will hold together and it won't fall apart when you use it.
And it's theoretically reusable.
But you have to do it.
Okay.
They sell this system for doing it that costs like two or $300.
And it comes with like these sheets of this like, you know,
this mesh and coating.
And then it comes with this stand with like a black light,
or like a UV light.
And you're supposed to put your design over it
and then shine the black light on it.
And then that will like do some reaction to the coating.
And then you rinse it off.
And like if you did it right,
the covered parts that you covered with your design
wash off the stencil and the parts that were uncovered
that got exposed to UV light,
like they harden and they stay on.
And this is how it creates this reusable design.
And so I was like, that sounds great,
but I don't want to spend $300.
So I just bought the, I bought some sheets of the stuff
and then I just bought my own little like black light
and I just fucked around with it.
I cut out a little piece and I did experiments with it.
And I found out just how to do it myself.
Didn't buy the stand,
saved like $150 because I just figured out
how do you kind of sort of shine my own little light on it
and get it to work.
Fuck you icon art.
I love your product.
And that was my, that's my story.
It's my glass etching story.
What are you etching into the glass
and what sort of glass is it?
Like is it the size of a little key chain?
It's a, it's a bottle.
It's bottles.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
You're going to put slime in a bottle with etched glass.
I won't admit that that's what I'm going to do.
That's insane.
Do you want to, yeah, do you want to see?
Oh, I can show you.
I do want to see.
I saw you post a picture of slime earlier.
All right.
Well, give me a second and I will show you what I've got.
Yeah.
That, that one pencilmation episode featuring Ben St is coming true.
Wait.
Why?
What, what happens?
Because you're going to fall into a slime.
Um, one second.
I got to take a picture.
Actually, I got to take two pictures because I'll show,
I'll show you in, in like regular light.
And I'll show you in black light because it looks really good.
Now, I don't know.
This might be like too much.
This might be too much work and impossible.
So like,
I feel like the amount of labor and materials you're putting in is unheard of.
I might, it might be going a little bit up for it.
That could be like a super high donation thing.
The etching doesn't really, it's kind of hard to see.
Ah, it's kind of hard to see on the camera.
Okay, I'll show you.
You can see it on an empty bottle.
They're all filled with slime.
Okay, here we go.
It's, it's a little bit hard to see.
All right, come on.
Yeah.
Uh, all right, give me a sec.
I got to find my, I got to find my black light.
The only thing I know black lights for is that they show semen.
Wow.
Because they use that in the, the shows where they're like, what's, let's find.
Oh, there's for blood.
They find blood as well.
But mostly I remember the semen.
I remember the semen.
Maybe it doesn't find blood actually.
I'm not sure.
I don't think it finds blood.
Luminal finds blood.
That's the different thing.
Yeah.
I remember that from Ace Attorney on DS, the secret extra thing, the lady, science lady.
I know that from Detective Conan from the other thing called Japan.
They're both from Japan.
Wow.
I'm sorry.
Detective Conan.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
Show this stupid, stupid.
Oh, Marin.
Marin's going to get excited when he sees this.
Oh.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
It looks pretty good, right?
Hang on.
Yo.
It's blowing up big.
So like product of New Los Angeles City, AKA Neo Milwaukee.
That looks, that text looks very clean.
That is kind of a big bottle.
I was thinking of like a tiny little slime thing.
It's like a smallish, like olive oil bottle.
Yeah.
It's like a shower gel.
It looks like.
It's only six or eight fluid ounces that it actually holds.
So anyway, that's what I did this week.
I mean, I didn't spend the whole week on that.
But like I bought, I think I bought this stuff like shortly after we discussed.
I think on the PCP last week, I said, haha, what if I gave people slime?
And now it's here.
And now there it is.
Be disastrously expensive to ship.
Not if I pretend that it's not in the box and I ship with media mail.
Here's the thing.
I hope that works out.
Oblivion fault.
Here's the thing.
We talked about this last week.
And the book is already going to be disastrously expensive to ship.
True.
The only way that it won't be is if I use media mail.
I'm going to just kind of, I'm going to try and like send some shit through media mail
that like technically shouldn't be sent through media mail and just like see if it works.
And like if it works, I'm just going to do that.
And like if some of them get caught, like, oh well.
Alternatively, you could just make it up the price that people have to pay for it.
So that way it works out.
I want, I will, I will have to charge for shipping.
I mean, I mean, I don't want to charge people more money.
That's bad.
Foreign shipping will be like $40.
So that's, so that's a nightmare.
That's a nightmare.
But I think if I, if I can get away with using media mail domestically, then I think I can
slightly overcharge for shipping domestically and then like undercharge for fucking, you
know, I don't want to charge people $40 shipping for international.
And because like most orders will not be international, I feel like I might be able to get away with
that margins wise.
That's my, that's my plan.
If I actually had to spend like $30 on shipping every individual order, which is like what
it is, I don't know, that's like, that almost makes me think I just shouldn't do it.
So, you know, that can't, that can't be true.
Yeah.
All right.
That would, that's my crafts.
That's my craft.
Craft corner with Ben.
Thanks.
It's edible.
It's, it's, it's edible by the way.
You can eat it.
Oh, you can eat.
Okay.
Yeah.
I mean, I probably wouldn't want to because it's so cool.
What, what is it?
Is it like, is it syrupy?
It is.
I mean, it is mostly not to, not to, not to break the illusion or anything, but it is mostly
corn.
No, no, don't say it.
It's mostly, it's mostly corn syrup.
No, the illusion shattered.
The slime is mostly corn syrup.
It's, it, you heard it here.
Yeah, true.
It's quite, it's quite tart.
It's quite sour.
It's, it's good.
You could make a slime and tonic out of it.
Oh, you could put that in a shot glass and do a little slime shot.
Yeah, you could.
You know, I mean, you could, you could make, you could make your own if you wanted to.
Well, actually, I mean, the, the only like hard to find thing in it is like the fluorescent
the fluorescent additive that stuff.
I mean, I don't know.
You have to get it yourself.
That's a work around here.
Here's a media mail, minimum eight pages.
It's a book just explaining where to buy the bottle, how to do the glass etching, how
to make the slime, just all the instructions to make yourself at home.
My, my idea was that I would send it with the book.
So, oh, oh, you mean like instead of sending the bottle, just, just send a little pamphlet
explaining it.
Yeah.
Pay for my secrets.
I ordered a bunch of rocks too.
I ordered a bunch of different kinds of greenish rocks.
And we'll see which ones look the best and which ones are the most cost effective.
What do they got?
I got floor, I got calcite.
I got the, I don't think I bought, I don't think I bought green jade because I thought
that was stuff was kind of expensive.
Calcite is pretty cool though.
I'm optimistic.
The calcite looks pretty good in the promo photos.
I'm optimistic to see how that's going to look.
You got to secure all these rocks because if they, if they crack into the glass, you
get slime all over your book.
Yeah.
And in a box, I would probably fill it with like packing peanuts or something.
I would probably wrap every individual piece with like bubble wrap or something is the
idea there.
Where did I, I got Amazonites.
I don't think I'll use Amazonites.
I think it's that shitty company.
I don't, I don't feel like that's a good one.
Yeah.
Or no, no, no, not Amazonite.
Aventureen.
Aventureen is what I was thinking.
I don't think I'll go with that.
I think it's like more like a pale, like turquoise color.
So like, I got the crazy light, which I'd never even heard of before, but it's green.
So worth a shot.
And I think that's all I just got before.
I bought like a pound of each.
I don't know.
It's going to be fun.
It's going to be fun this week waiting for the, I know, I know.
I'm just having fun with it.
I'm just having fun with it, you know.
Very whimsically.
I just, I like making, making funny little, funny little themed gifts, I guess.
I don't know.
And trinkets.
You should have a real, you should have a potion shop.
You should have like a real, you could be a traveling like trinket vendor.
Bizarre.
Yeah.
Like the guy in at the beginning of Aladdin.
He sells the thing that makes Julian fries.
Yes.
Yeah.
He sells, he sells it on Alibaba.
Alibaba is.
That's the name of the camel.
Alibaba is so good.
They just have stuff for just.
Just have everything cheap.
Yeah.
There's like a, there's a million, there's a million vendors and they all have names
that I can't pronounce or even distinguish from each other half the time.
But if I sift through them, I will always find stuff at like half the price I would
pay for something from the Western of Western vendor.
Only then the shipping costs like 10 times as much.
So it's sort of evens out.
But unlike Western vendors that have things like minimum wage and all that expensive.
The children want to work.
How dare you bar?
How dare you keep all these children unemployed against their will?
Joe Brandon dark Brandon rising.
That's crazy.
Gas prices going down.
That's the worst of dark Brandon.
Gas prices going up.
Yeah.
Oh, fucking.
That was a thing that happened a couple of days ago.
Elon Musk and Trump were having a little fight.
They were having a little.
Oh, yeah.
A little spat.
I am that that Irish accountant that Irish like a finance YouTuber that I watch.
He had a video explaining the Elon Musk situation.
And Elon is like boned.
He's like totally toast.
Yeah.
It's like he didn't know what he was doing at any step.
He 100% is like by any reasonable metric like already agreed to buy the company and
there's no backing out.
Just look at that power stance.
Oh, does he actually have to spend the what was it 40 billion?
He might be able to negotiate a there was like a backing out fee of a billion.
But or but like the agreement was to buy it for 40 billion.
But like he's passed the point where he would have been able to just pay the 1 billion to
get out of it.
So he will probably have to either.
Go through with the deal and maybe he can negotiate a lower price than the 40 billion
or he will have to back out and probably negotiate a bigger fee than the 1 billion.
But it's, you know, going to cost him a lot.
Lol.
Yeah, lol.
He totally fucked it up.
I saw him like making means like coping means.
Yeah.
Twitter.
That will definitely be that are already being used against him in court.
Like his legal team.
Just should have told him don't post memes about an ongoing legal dispute.
Sir.
Sir Musk, please.
But he couldn't help it.
Can't help it.
No one tells him what to do.
Well, I hope he can.
That's it.
He's a very distasteful man.
The very distasteful man in my opinion.
You know what it isn't a distasteful man.
The Eye of Sauron.
Hmm.
Yeah.
True.
Did you know?
He is no man at all.
In fact, he is one of the Vaynor or whatever.
The Aeneir?
Yeah.
The deities of some kind.
There's like a, I forget all of the mythology.
I saw a YouTube video about it one time and I think I know what I'm talking about.
Yes.
Who'd you be graded a fucking video?
Oh, he's one of them.
He's one of them.
Yeah.
But like I noticed.
I noticed the other day that was just drawing endless war.
Just doodling him.
As one does.
Yeah.
And I was like, I'll draw endless war.
Just doodling him.
As one does.
Yeah.
And I was like, I'll draw endless mud next to him.
And it's like, wait a minute.
Eye of Sauron is an eye on a plinth on a pillar.
He must be related.
He must be like, he must be another endless.
The resemblance is uncanny.
Oh my gosh.
It's a little racist though, don't you think?
You think they all know each other?
Yeah.
Eyes.
They're so tall.
They have eyes.
They can look.
They can see each other.
Well, we just had the last RFCK art contest was about death furnaces.
And there were a bunch of different ones.
Let's see what was there.
There was Endless Oil, Endless Mochi, Endless Entertainment.
Endless Mochi.
Endless Mochi is awesome.
Prince Annihilation drew.
It's like a big mouth.
I want to see these.
I agree.
You know what?
I'll find that one.
There was also Endless Expansion in the Big Booby Mummy Mocha one, which is a giant dome
that looks like a booby.
That one's got to count for something.
That's on a death furnace.
That's a breast furnace.
Yes.
Let's see here.
I'm going to find it.
Sauron would be called Endless Search.
Endless Orcs.
The One Ring.
Endless Pain.
Rar.
He would say Rar.
Sorry.
I'm going to be quiet for a minute while I find the thing.
That's right.
I have a small in the middle tangent speaking of racism.
Yeah.
You know how GitHub got rid of master and slave terminology?
Oh, yeah.
I did hear about that.
No, I did not.
Some people, it's like a coding thing where one code drives another code or some shit.
I don't know.
I'm not a codeman, but they're like, we're changing the terminology because it's just
tasteful, which is like, sure, whatever.
I don't care.
Some people get super mad over it, though, which is funny.
Yeah.
Because we were talking about Photoshop earlier.
Ben was talking about getting rid of the whites, which I thought was really funny.
I did say that and I almost made a joke about it.
But listen, I was on an important tangent and I didn't want to get distracted.
I know.
I understood.
I laughed.
But there's another terminology that I hear a lot when talking about color grading, which
is crushing the blacks.
Yes.
I know about crushing the blacks.
Believe me.
How long are we going to keep that around for?
I wonder.
I haven't heard anyone talk about it being problematic, but I'm like, surely, surely
someone would complain.
It's fine.
What is it describing, though?
It's when you adjust the contrast of an image so that the dark areas become pure black.
Like 00 on the RGB, basically.
Yeah.
I don't have a problem with that one.
I feel like that is just describing what it is.
It's like darkening the blacks.
Darkening.
What did I see?
There was somebody on Twitter, I think, I saw someone added Crayola because they had
a black colored pencil and it said Negro on it.
And they were like, yeah, Crayola, what the hell is this?
And they were like, yes, we're an international company.
That is the Spanish word for black.
And he was like, no, he was actually mad because they also had the French translation and he
made a joke like, why would you include French?
I hate France.
It's like, ha, ha, ha.
Very, very, how drool.
Anyway, it's like that.
I mean, it's like that, though.
It's just the word.
It's also the word for the color.
Yeah.
I think the GitHub thing makes more sense just because many words can replace this fake
thing that you made up of a thing being in charge of another thing.
I've seen parent and child be used in a monster and slave.
We wouldn't want to offend any slaves who are using the code to build any programs for
their masters.
The thing that would be annoying is the code terminology changes and now all the coders
have to learn or their code breaks and they have to fix it.
But, you know, I don't know.
Here, I found not going to be a major problem.
I found this from Prince's Death Furnace art.
That's cool.
Well, that mountain has a big fucking sideways.
It was the dark spooky one.
That's Endless Oil.
He was new.
There was Endless Mochi.
That's Endless Mochi on the bottom right there.
I like that one a lot.
Just a mountain with a sideways mouth.
It's got that, I don't know if you call it, but that like sort of like flat cloud design
thing going on.
I don't know.
What do you mean?
I mean, the way that like the smoke looks, it looks like, I don't know, it looks like
a very stylized sort of like, oh, the clouds are a flat geometric shape.
In a sort of Asian way, I don't know how to describe it.
I mean, sometimes clouds do be like that.
Oh, what?
Yeah.
Sometimes they do have a flat bottom and then like a bulb is swirly atop.
And it's like, wow, that's just like Toy Story.
It's almost like art is based on real life.
It's almost like art is based.
Oh, no, I hate art.
I hate art now.
I don't like it anymore.
So thanks for that.
Yeah.
Thanks for reminding me how bad art is.
How much it sucks.
I have to pee.
I'll be back in a minute.
I have to clean.
I have to help clean.
We'll take a break and spend his pee.
I'll be back.
I believe in fall has gone for a second.
Ow.
Okay.
Well, now that's the episode.
No.
What do we go?
I mean, we've been going for a long time, right?
We've been good.
That's an episode.
That's another one in the can.
No, no, no.
Yes.
You must die.
Yes, yes, yes.
Kill me.
End it.
End this charade.
I can't do it.
You're so cute.
Come on.
Pussy.
Nah.
Thor's gone away into boiling acid.
Fine.
World peace.
Okay.
Okay, I guess.
I don't know why we have open vats of boiling acid in world peace.
World peace?
What?
Are you describing a real phenomenon?
What are you talking about?
World peace?
I can't even comprehend this.
I just realized Elon's tie is a little short.
Elon's tie doesn't even reach to his belt.
Yeah.
You gotta have a lead lined tie and droop it low so that if you're hit with radiation,
your penis and genitals are protected with the lead in the tie.
So you can't get zapped by aliens with their radiation guns.
I continue to wonder whether I should shave my head or not.
I am continuously on the fence about whether my hair is worth keeping.
And I just can't.
Does it fill you with joy?
No.
Well, get rid of it.
Burn it.
Throw it away.
Well, that, I mean, would that make me feel even worse though?
Yes.
No, I'm already filled with that actually.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Sorry.
No more.
No vacancies.
There's no fixing that problem.
I mean, would you consider taking like chemicals to grow your hair back?
That's not something.
That's not an option.
It's not an option.
How do you know it's not an option?
Well, I know that you can't.
I mean, haven't you heard the freaking, what do you call it?
Keeps.
The keeps is the company that like advertises on YouTube.
You know, they say in their ads, you know, you can't reverse hair loss.
You can only, you can only prevent it.
Yeah.
So.
You got to get one of those Jordan Peterson hair transplants.
Your hair plugs.
You got to go that route.
Listen, I don't, I'm not going to say that I have never thought about it.
I don't know.
Certainly be a lot simpler to have a shaved head.
But yeah.
I don't know.
Wait, actually.
I don't like.
This might be true.
I hope maybe I'm misremembering.
What's that?
Does estrogen bring your hair back?
I, we just said no.
It doesn't.
Once the hair follicle is completely gone.
I don't think it does.
But.
I've, I've, I've heard.
Stop it from falling out.
I've heard the opposite.
But.
That like.
I mean, I've heard so many things about what estrogen does.
And there's no like, there's no absolute like certainty to a lot of it.
People are just hoping and like they've got a, what do you call it?
Small sample size.
What do you call that?
It's just one guy saying something.
Anecdotal evidence.
There's a lot of anecdotal evidence and not a lot of research.
My favorite kind.
It's hard to know what is true about what estrogen does.
Obviously, obvious things like boobs growing and like skin changing.
So.
Softness and various other things.
For like.
Fat goes in.
The fat goes to your hips and thighs.
Hair is unknown.
As far as I understand.
It's, it's not, it's not unknown.
It doesn't bring your hair back.
There.
Well, I mean, maybe there's magical.
Ooh.
I mean, women are magical, I guess.
So like, who knows what could happen?
Well, all right.
I don't know.
I ain't seen the stats.
I ain't seen the truth.
I'm not holding out hope for it though.
I, my hair is receded already and I can't do anything about it.
At some point I might shave my hair off and start wearing wigs.
Cause it just doesn't look that good.
I think, I don't know.
I can say this before like.
On the one hand, maybe I'm just like, uh, maybe it's just cooler.
Maybe it's, it's just a cooler look.
And by look I mean in the more general sense, not of how you look in like visually, but
just how you look to others as a human.
It might just be a better look to just say fuck it and embrace whatever nature bestows
upon me.
I respect that.
I respect that sort of thing in others.
Uh, but do I have the courage to do it myself?
I'm going to say probably no, probably no, I lack that in my heart.
Seeing guys with, with no hair doesn't make me think anything in particular.
No.
It's just like a normal guy.
Yeah.
With a really bad receding hairline.
Seeing a really old guy with a full head of hair is like, wow, lucky.
That son of a bitch.
How do you do that?
Oh, he got the right gene.
Well, fuck you.
Fuck you, Gene.
You don't deserve happiness.
Uh, I don't know.
I just, I just want to complain.
I sort of complain about being old.
So thanks for letting me, let me do that.
No, it's, it's fine.
It's old.
We're all old here, except a blue and full.
Yeah.
Only a few years ago in Gib.
Where do you like 20, you know, like 27, right?
Yeah, I'm 27.
29.
Oh, you're 27.
No, I meant, yeah.
Yeah.
Okay.
I don't know.
Man, I don't know.
I just, uh, it's starting to, you know, I got, I got, I got, I got my thing that I'm
working on, not the book.
I mean the book too, but like, I got that video thing that I was going to make.
I've sort of have been more focused on just getting the book done lately.
I haven't been focusing too hard on it, but I, but I, I, I'm excited to make it.
I'm excited to finish it and put it out.
And like, I think people like it.
And, uh, so that's cool and all, but like, uh, I feel, I don't know.
I wonder if I've really like made the most of my, uh, my internet career.
Have I, have I really like, have I really done anything worthwhile with it?
I don't know.
I've been, I've been, yeah.
I mean, that's fine.
Yeah.
That's true.
No, those were good.
Those were, those were good and they were worth making.
Like I should have, I should have done more.
I should have done more and I'm, I don't know.
Uh, you know, I guess when I think about it, it's a little bit, it's a little rough that
like, hmm, my, my most, my most important achievements, if you just go by the numbers,
are just things wherein I like discuss some shit that other people made.
That makes me depressed.
Uh, you know, I think it's funny to talk about Sonichu or whatever.
It's funny to talk about, uh, fucking unicorn jelly, but it's a bit like, it's a bit, it's
a bit shit.
But like, oh yeah.
Ben saying that guy who talked about Sonichu, that guy who talked about unicorn jelly.
Yeah, that is, that is me.
That is my legacy.
I don't know what YouTubers are, but like half of them.
I know and they suck too.
Those people are also shit and worthless.
So there, they're not worthless.
You need to learn about how like the UI has one extra pixel on the side on a remake of
a video game.
That's true.
I love that content.
I gobble it up and, but I don't respect, but I don't respect it.
I actually don't like that content.
I don't, nothing against the people who make it.
I just like, why do people care about such a tiny little detail?
I mean, I don't know.
I don't know.
I mean, when I say that content, I mean like game related, like split speed run stuff I
like, even though it's like, it's pretty vapid at the end of the day, but I still like it.
I think it's, it's just what you make of it.
I've was watching, um, this guy called settled makes RuneScape content.
Yeah.
And, um, I found him from this odd like challenge run he's doing of an Iron Man RuneScape run,
where he can only move one tile if he gets a certain amount of experience.
And then I was like, oh, that series is still ongoing.
We'll wonder what else he's done.
And he's done like this, um, leveling every stat to 99.
Well, not every step.
I'm just like doing like everything you can, but, uh, relegated to one area of the entire
map where you can't do a lot of things normally.
And it's just an extremely tedious grind.
And he loves it.
Like he loves the, like he, he grinds for like 1500 hours trying to find this one thing.
So that he can get like, he can, he can finish, uh, like, uh, I don't know.
It's hard to explain because there's so many moving parts in RuneScape.
I don't even know the first thing about RuneScape.
Uh, you get experienced by doing crafts and fighting and leveling up and stuff.
Okay.
You run around, um, MMO.
Yeah.
I mean, I know, I know that much.
Uh, but he like, he gets really, really happy and excited whenever he breaches a milestone
or like a certain item drops that there's like one in 1600 drop chance and he's killed
like hundreds of these fucking enemies trying to get it.
And he gets it and he's like, oh, Pog.
He, and it's just like, I can't imagine.
Like, carrying.
I'm so jealous.
For so long.
Like he, it's just his enthusiasm for the seemingly completely pointless, arduous, tedious task
of playing some video game.
His enthusiasm is infectious.
Yeah.
It makes me like really happy for him.
And everyone loves him and he's, he's just literally riding on cloud nine or whatever.
It's, it's, it's just great.
You know, when you're, when you're passionate about something.
Yeah.
It's like, uh, one, it's not work to, you know, do it.
And two, other people who might not even care.
Yeah.
They might just enjoy your enthusiasm for it.
And for, you know, for both of those reasons, that's like, oh, that's good content.
You know, if there's something you really care about and enjoy, it's like, hey, if you
turn that into content, you know, that's like, that's pretty good.
It's good work.
If you can get it.
Yeah.
So like, you know, yeah, I wouldn't like, I wouldn't have a problem.
I don't think there's anything wrong with like doing vapid content.
Yeah.
It's just whether you're enjoying what you're doing.
I guess Ben, did you enjoy making the lectures or, or like having the, the videos, other
videos you've made?
Um, yeah.
I guess, I guess, sure.
I mean, they only took me like, they didn't take very long.
Sure.
They were fun to make.
It's not like I've like spent that much time doing them.
They were so fleeting in the grand scheme of things.
Um, I guess, I mean, I think the reason they're, they're so like enjoyed is, is your enthusiasm
for the things you're talking about.
Yeah.
Like, I guess what I, I guess what bums me out a little bit is that I feel like it's
not that I think they were bad to make or anything, but I do feel like, uh, I don't know.
I just, I don't know where they leave me in terms of like, what, what can I, what is
my next move?
What, what is, what does Ben St. who has, you know, this list of things that he's done
and that he's somewhat known for?
Like, what does he do with that, uh, in terms of like, uh, I don't know.
Uh, I mean, you learned how to etch glass for like a potential slime bottle thing.
Yeah.
And.
Well, you could make funny, cool things on Etsy.
No, I hate it.
I hate that idea.
I hate it so much.
I don't know.
I don't know what you mean.
Like, you don't know what you mean on YouTube specifically.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Or whatever.
As a content creator or as a person who, or just as an artist, just as an artist in general,
like whatever that means.
Uh, I guess I'm just, uh, I don't know what to do with my life there.
That's it.
That's what I'm getting at.
Uh, this is, this is all part of my, this is all part of my crisis of being 34 and being like,
what have I done?
What have I done?
And now what do I do?
And, uh.
You're 34.
Yeah.
You should follow the rules.
What?
Draw porn.
Rule 34.
Oh.
Isn't it?
Rule 34, when you hit 34.
You have to just draw porn.
That's all you can do.
I'm getting a head start.
I'm cheating.
I don't, I don't want to, I'm, I'm too, um, this might speak to like a broader failing
of me as a person, but I'm too like, I'm too shy.
I'm too shy to draw porn.
I don't want to be that vulnerable.
I would feel way too vulnerable, like drawing porn that like, I'm like, yeah, this is what
I'm into.
Okay.
Now I'm, now I'm posting it on the internet.
Yeah.
No fucking way.
I felt like that.
I felt like that before.
Yeah.
But I feel that way.
I still kind of feel like that.
I feel that way.
I felt like that for a long time, but then the bandit got ripped off and that was easy.
Now, now I can't wait to share all the other crazy porn ideas, ideas I have that no one
has drawn before, but only I can draw unless I pay someone and fuck that.
I mean, yeah, I'll do it.
I should have just, I should have just paid someone, should have just paid someone to
like format my fucking book for me.
I shouldn't have spent like weeks and weeks working on my stupid book.
It seems like it's such a simple step.
Just organize it into a file, find a printer, but no, months go by and it's still not done.
You know, I got a specific complaint.
I mean, I really hate, I think it's going to be the case that the book will have to be,
you know, long, you know, like bound on the short end and it's going to be kind of long.
It might end up being like eight by 12.
And that's just too long.
I don't like that.
It's annoying.
Yeah, it's a flappy.
That's an annoying, yeah, it's an annoying flappy size for a book.
But like, that's what, that's the shape.
That's the shape of the panels, man.
I mean, in the Homestuck books, they have like the panels don't take up the entire,
like four panels don't take up the entire thing.
They're smaller and then they've obviously got the text underneath.
Yeah.
But then there's like the commentary right at the bottom.
If you had the commentary there, it would make it a taller book, I guess.
Yeah, but no, some pages have like, I have like a lot of commentary and some and like,
it just wouldn't fit.
Some pages have a lot of commentary and some have very little or none.
I could just add, I mean, I could just add space in between and at the bottom and top.
It's just like, that's a waste of space.
And that's just like making it cost more to print, like for what, like just to make it
taller, to make it less oblong.
It seems kind of stupid.
And yet I want, I kind of want to just because eight by 12 bound on the eight.
It doesn't fit on a bookshelf.
It's going to stick out.
Oh, yeah.
All the things I have on my, on my like cool comics shelf will be sticking out.
I have to put at the edge.
I could bind it on top, like I could make it so that you have to flip through it, like hold it sideways.
You know what I mean?
That would be so weird.
Yeah, it's that seems just as awkward, if not more so.
I'd have to like open it like a laptop.
Exactly.
Rest it on my knees.
So I don't know if that's a good solution.
I guess I could, I could make it really tall.
What if I had, ooh, I could have eight panels on a page.
I mean, if they don't end up being too small, that could work.
I would cut the page.
But then it would be 16 by 12, wouldn't it?
It would cut the page count in half.
It would be 16.
Yeah.
Oh no, it wouldn't be 12 then.
No, yeah, would it be?
Yeah, it would still be, it would still be 12 long.
It would be 16 by 12, or I mean, I could shrink it to eight by six.
That's too small.
It's almost like a Twitter image size sucks for books.
Almost.
What if you just squished it all so all of the images were distorted?
Ooh, yeah.
And I could like just use like the, the Morph tool and like have it set on like hard, hard
edge transform settings so that like.
Nearest neighbor.
Yeah, yeah.
Like it ends up with like all these jagged, like pixelated everywhere.
Yeah.
Thinking, that's thinking.
This is, this has been my week.
I have not, again, I have not left my house for another week has gone by.
So you know, that's where I'm at.
Just contemplating my hairline and all this stuff.
That's, that's how, that's how it's been for me for a while.
Listen, I'm not in a great place.
Listen, I'm not in a great place mentally.
All right.
It's what I'm trying to say.
It's not clear.
Okay.
If you can't pick up on, if you can't pick up on, on subtext, let me just spell it out
for you.
Okay.
All right.
Why is hairline the most important thing a human can have?
It's, why is that, why is that so like such a thing?
Yeah.
You know, scholars wonder, yeah, why is the hairline the single most important thing
about a person?
It is kind of weird how like 70% of what makes someone attractive is their hair a lot of
the time.
That's not even a joke.
God, I was gonna say, please tell me you're joking.
That's just like my estimate because like I've noticed the like.
Is that for you personally?
Well, I and I, I think other people have noticed that like the way someone wears their hair
like has such a huge effect on like how they look to other people.
Yeah.
Like having shitty hair can make you look like a gala and having good hair can make you
look fucking great.
It's, it's, it makes such a huge difference.
It does make a difference.
I would say for me, it's definitely not 70%.
I would say for me, it might make like feel like someone who is otherwise attractive,
the difference between them having like a really nice hair cut hairdo versus them being
like disheveled.
Their hair looks like shit.
Maybe like a picture of Elon Musk 25% before his hair was fixed.
Who?
Elon Musk, you've seen what it looked like before he got his hair like.
Yeah.
I mean, he looks, he looks better.
He looks better with the, with the hair.
People kept making fun of Donald Trump for his funny wig, but he would have looked worse
if he didn't have it.
That's not true.
I've seen him with his hair like combed back.
It looks fine.
Like he doesn't even have like a receding hairline.
I guess I haven't really seen him.
No, he actually looks fine with his hair normal.
Like there's no reason why he does such freak shit with it.
This is so funny.
He literally looked, literally looked older when he was like, what is he like in his 30s
in that first one?
Literally looked older with his, with his receding hairline.
I do like some of these, these comedy moments.
I miss these.
Okay.
And that one, he does look like it's like a wig or something.
Hmm.
What's that?
Weird.
Oh my God.
What a weirdo.
He truly is just a real fucking weirdo, honestly.
His wife just, or his ex-wife just died.
So we can't, we shouldn't make fun of him.
He's going through a hard, he's going through a hard time.
I forgot what I was doing.
What are we talking about?
Hair.
I mean, I feel like my hair looks all right when it's nice, but the hairline thing is a
constant like aggravator.
You know, because, because it's, it's not just that, oh, it's looks kind of bad.
It's, it's like telling of my masculinity that I have a receding hairline like that.
And it's like, oh, dysphoria on top of all that.
It's really, really gets me sometimes.
I have to wear hats whenever I go outside.
It sucks.
You know whose hair was fascinating to watch progress?
I feel like I bring this guy up like an unusual amount, but Dan Olson, his, he used.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
He used to do a thing with it where like, you could kind of tell that it was thinning,
but he sort of wore it over his forehead in a kind of like, almost like deliberately
shitty way.
And I think, I don't know, there was a period there where it was like, it doesn't look good.
Like you're, like you're, you're kind of clearly sort of trying to do something with it that
like you don't have enough there to do that with.
And then at some point he just, at some point he just made the switch, the switch flipped
and he, he went from a disheveled looking, you know, youngish guy to a pretty, pretty
like well put together a middle aged man when he shaved his head and beard went white and
you know.
Yeah.
I mean, it's a good look for him.
I would say he overall looks better.
Yeah.
Which is what makes me like, maybe I should just, maybe is it, is it time?
When will I have to take the plunge?
The day will come.
Whatever you do, don't, don't do a fucking comb over like that one voicemailer suggested
like a few weeks ago.
No.
Comb over is part of a devil.
I would, you gotta, you gotta grow your hair right at the back of your neck really long
and then come all the way over.
I would never want to like wear my hair or anything in a way that's like I'm like trying
to disguise something.
Like I brush my hair to the side now and it's just, that's just how I do it and it's not
like, I don't know.
I'm not, yeah, I wouldn't, I would never do a comb over.
That's just stupid.
I would just, just shave it at that point in my opinion.
Yeah.
In my opinion, I agree too.
I just, just when, when do I, when do I pull a Dan?
Am I there yet?
I don't know.
One of the, one day.
Is it today?
It's the sort of the sort of Damocles.
The sort of Damocles is dangling.
The sort of Danocles.
Ah, yes.
That's all, that's it.
That the scissors of Damocles or the razor of Damocles.
Yeah.
Because you're cutting your hair.
Right.
I lost.
Yeah.
You know what, you know what?
On a more, on a more exciting hair related, this is very exciting.
The stuff we talk about on this podcast is like a thrilling to our audience.
I gotta say, I have a beard again.
I have like a real beard, which like I have not had one since Radcon 2 basically.
Oh, comb the beard up over your hair.
I have like an actual like full beard again and it feels great and I feel like a more
complete human for that.
So I got that going for me.
Yeah.
Even though, even though it is, even though it is kind of white on the, on the near the
ears, but like, that's fine.
I don't really mind it.
Is it, is it like lumberjack size the same as the first TBAP Q&A?
It's not that big.
It's not, it's not that length yet, but like it's getting there.
Maybe in another two months or something.
Yeah.
I remember like I, it's bizarre, but like around TBAP time, maybe like a little before
TBAP or in the very early days of TBAP, I had like a long beard.
I had like, like it was like, it must have been like seven or eight inches long.
Uh, very strange, very strange to think that ever.
Yeah.
Uh, only time I ever did that in my life.
Uh, maybe I'll just do it again.
Maybe I'll just freaking do it again.
I have, I have managed to avoid, my, my trick or telemania has been, uh, I have managed
it, uh, in a way that has, uh, allowed my beard to be normal more or less.
Uh, uh, and that's an accomplishment for me.
It's very difficult.
So it's kind of strange that I have managed that these days when I am feeling so such despair.
Uh, uh, but I guess, you know, that's just, uh, that's life.
That's the way the beard crumbles.
That's true.
Speaking of beard crumbling, um, my, my laser hair removal thing that I've been doing.
Yeah.
To get rid of my facial hair forever.
Um, it has progressed to a point where, uh, the last session, I had a session recently,
but before that, um, there was, uh, there was a problem after I got home from America,
I had gained a bit of a tan because we went to the beach one day.
Right.
And they said, Oh, we can't do it.
Yeah.
You mentioned, uh, you mentioned that.
So.
Oh, very strange.
That's been, that was, that was a thing.
Yeah.
And now I've done it, but in the interim, I had to wait an additional six weeks and my
beard barely grew back at all in that entire time.
And I, I, I've always had like an extremely fast growing beard, um, compared to people
my age or the round the age that I started growing it.
Um, so it was really cool to see that after six weeks, it was like very faint.
Yeah.
Like if you didn't look at it, you probably didn't notice.
Is it, is it like, okay, did it grow back?
Like just, there were fewer hairs.
Like there just weren't many hairs or was it like, they were like, like, like the hair
on your arm, like they're finer and, and like softer and thinner.
No, no, no.
There were just fewer hairs.
Yeah.
Um, round my cheeks, there's nothing.
Um, on my chin is where a lot of it is and on my lips, uh, above and below my lips is
where.
On, on your lips.
Yes.
Glowing directly out of the lips.
Yeah.
The lipstick's a nightmare.
Um, but.
I gotta shave my lips before I apply lipstick every single time.
Um, but yeah, it's like, there's like a countable number of hairs, probably not actually countable,
but like it's so stark from the way it used to be.
It's, it's, it's really gratifying.
I like it.
I like looking at it.
I like, I like, I don't like looking at it because I can still see that there is hair
there, but I like knowing that it has been such a long time and I don't have a beard that
goes like, like protrude from my chin.
I don't have a moustache that goes into my mouth.
You know, you know, moustache gets too long.
Yeah.
Doesn't happen anymore.
The hairs were like the length, like about half a millimeter length maximum.
My, I, my moustache is a bit shorter than the rest of my beard because I did, I did pull
out like a part, not a lot, but like a little like section of my moustache.
And I was like, shit, shit, shit.
Uh, so I avoided plucking at it for a while and it has grown back and it's like few.
Okay.
It's complete again.
I must, I must never again.
I must never again do that.
Uh, so, uh, it's back, but it's just shorter because it started growing later, basically.
Uh, but it looks deliberate.
It doesn't look fucked up.
I swear it doesn't look fucked up.
I look normal.
I say screaming into the mirror.
Thank you.
Someone, someone finally, someone believes it.
I believe it.
You know, I went to a hairdresser for the first time in like two years.
Oh yeah.
Recently.
Since COVID.
Yeah.
When COVID started, I just said, fuck it.
I'm just going to like shave my head once every six months.
That's what I was doing.
Yeah.
I mean, um, makes sense.
The way my hair grew back looked really weird.
I look like a freaky, freakazoid.
How's, how so?
I don't know.
It's just like, it looks like I was wearing like a fucking, like a helmet, like a fucking
Minecraft helmet.
Like you just grew back as like a shapeless like orb.
Well, well, it's like, you know, like my, my fringe is, you know, was like just above
my eyes.
And then right before it hits my ears, the hair just drops down like four more inches
and then just goes around the back.
Um, so my, my face is like in this fucking square window.
Um, oh, cause it was like long on the sides.
So it like kind of, yeah.
Yeah.
Cause I have like a straight, I have a straight hairline on them by my ear as it just goes
right down.
Yeah.
And it was really weird.
I went to a hairdresser and I, and I thought, you know, I'm actually going to tell them,
I'm actually going to tell them to aim for style for the first time in my life.
Cause I would always just walk in there and be like, I don't know, just take like half
the length off, I guess.
And they would just do whatever the fuck.
And my hair slowly got like really bad.
Uh, but this time I'm like, I don't know, vaguely just shape it vaguely so that like,
if I just sort of brush it, it'll sort of sit on my face the way like emo hair from
like the late 2000s would, but without all the product.
It's a good, it's a good style.
Yeah.
And she was like, I got you a fan.
And then she, uh, shaped it.
She didn't take any line call, but she just shaped it and it looks good.
I feel like it looked good.
I feel like it looked better than I have.
Wait, that's how it looks now?
Yeah.
That's how I look now.
And I think I look better than I have in a long fucking time.
Yeah.
Um, even pre-cut.
I don't, well, I can't compare to how you looked pre haircut, but, uh, looking good.
Looking good, man.
I, I should probably find it a pre haircut image.
Actually, I definitely can.
You just re-posed the Donald Trump image.
This is what I looked like before.
Oh, I, I, let me go for my 2019 folder.
Uh, I, uh, I might go, I, I, I cut my own hair, but I might go to like, uh, a stylist
or something to get a real haircut maybe before I am ready to film that, uh, that
video project that I've put off for the book for the moment.
Uh, although I'm, I don't know.
I don't know, it makes me nervous.
Sometimes I get a haircut and I hate how it looks.
Sometimes I feel like, uh, when I just kind of let the hair do whatever it wants, I just
end up feeling like more comfortable with it.
Like I'm just like, eh, it's fine.
It is what it is.
But then if I get a haircut and it's bad, I'm like, it's, it's, it's not, it's bad,
but it's like deliberately bad.
Like it's like, it feels worse cause like, okay, but it's like, I don't like how it was
made to be.
If it, if it just looked bad by accident, I could just be like, eh, well, I didn't even
try.
Eh, it's just how it grows.
Hey, you were in the broop shirt.
Yeah, it is.
Let me see.
That was like three years ago.
That shirt is in very, very bad condition now.
It was already starting to get in bad condition then.
You should probably get a new one.
You looked fine.
It's faded.
The white is gray.
It's full of holes.
Oh, you're talking about me.
Yeah.
I mean, I, my hair was like really poofy on the front.
So like at the front of my head, above my forehead, my hair like jutted out like two inches forward
in this like weird round like bulb.
Which is not super apparent in that screenshot, but I don't know.
It was odd as I, I don't know, I look better now and I'm going to be even more better because
I'm going to keep growing it for a bit.
I'll be sexy boy, sexy oblivion is coming back.
He is.
Did I, did I mention that the last time I saw my dad, he told me he was going to grow
a ponytail.
I, I vaguely remember that.
I just think that's so funny.
He called himself an old hippie.
He's like, he was like, eh, I'm an old hippie.
I might as well grow a ponytail.
I was like, yeah, yeah, cool.
I should, I should go, I should go sailing with him.
I haven't gone sailing in like 10 years, but I think he wants me to go sailing with him
sometime and like I should do that before the summer is over, maybe sometime next month
before puts the boat away.
So you have like a sailboat.
Him, him and his friend co-own a sailboat together.
Yeah.
It's their, it's their thing.
It's their, it's their hobby.
They love it.
They love, they love that freaking boat, man.
They're just all about it.
More than you.
I don't like boating, but you know, whatever.
It's not, it's about.
The ocean will kill you.
Yeah, I know.
Yes, I know.
That's why I don't like it.
Exactly.
I'm terrified of it.
Boats are cool until you're on one.
I remember being on like, on like holiday once somewhere and it was like, oh, this wooden
like pirate ship kind of looking boat is going to like take us on a tour around the rocks.
We're going to see the rocks, but it was like a real boat.
It went up and down and I felt sick.
What?
I thought it was going to be okay, but I'm going to throw up.
I think it's probably scarier for me to contemplate than it would be to, to actually go out and
do that.
Like I'm, I feel like it'll be fine.
Just thinking about it.
I'm like, God, on the sea.
I'll drown.
Uh, you know, I'll be eaten whole by a, by a lurker fish.
Oh.
Drowning in footwear.
Yeah.
What?
No, that was a give and take.
That was a hypocrite.
Yeah.
You remember Jack and Daxter?
Yes.
That's what I was, that's what, yeah.
Yeah.
I'm going to, no, no father of you.
Don't, I don't want to be thrown into the sea.
Yes.
Classic.
I was, I was, I think I was calling like, no, I wanted, I don't want to go fishing.
Yes.
This was Jack and Daxter.
I'll be eaten whole.
God, I like some of my videos.
They're good.
I also like some of your videos.
It's a shame making videos so strange now.
Now that I have a big brain, I don't feel the compulsion to just talk about things.
I think my brain is small and stupid.
You think you have a big brain now?
You think your brain's gotten bigger?
I don't feel, I don't feel that way at all.
I feel, all right.
What I feel is that my, my, having seen so many good analysis videos, I feel like I can't
just make a video and just be happy with whatever I come up with because I need it to be worth
something to the larger gaming analysis scene.
Yeah.
Like I don't, I don't want to talk about a game that somebody's already done an amazing
video on.
Yeah.
Every other game reviewer does a retrospective on some other thing.
And even though the retrospective has been done by 70 other people, I don't feel like I
would benefit the world by doing my own, even though people would probably like it.
Cause like if the nostalgia chick reviews, reviews Good Burger, then the, then the nostalgia
critic can't review Good Burger.
So like only one of them can do it.
Ironically, yes.
And Good Burger is a classic.
And we, we, this is like highly contested.
Obviously.
The rights to Good Burger.
The rights to discuss Good Burger.
Obviously there's like, um, there's no like dibsies on, on a review.
If somebody made a review of a game, I actually, I actually would do this.
I would see if, and somebody had made a video on a game like Rayman one.
And I was like, ah, these videos suck.
I can, I, I'll do that.
And I'll do that video.
And then I did.
No.
But it's, it's just sort of like now that I've seen so many good, like really in depth
videos, I feel like I want to be smart when I make it.
I don't just, I want to be like bringing something new to the table.
I want to be a big, the big Joel of like, um, video game analysis.
I want to be saying something while I review the game.
Yeah.
I know what you mean.
And I have, I feel the same way.
Like, do you feel like if you're not, like if you're not, if you're not making something
that's like amazing, you're just like, why, why bother?
Like, is that what you're saying?
Kinda.
I mean, when it comes to videos for sure, I feel like I, I have that compulsion with
comics and drawings as well.
But I, I don't feel quite so bad about making what I currently make, which is good.
But like, I don't know, I wouldn't, I wouldn't say anything I've made so far as a masterpiece,
even though there's good parts to them.
I, um, I think I'm a little, I'm pleased to announce that my, the video thing that I'm
currently, is currently on hold is, it's, I think it's, it's the only thing, it's the
only thing like it.
There are like adjacent things about like similar topics, but there's nothing, there's
nothing like exactly the idea that I'm, that I'm working on.
So like that's good.
But that's like kind of stupid because like even if there was, like it wouldn't matter.
Like it really should be fine if there was, if someone else had already done a similar
thing.
That shouldn't stop me.
But I think it would.
Uh.
Yeah.
I've had ideas, but then I, I, for, for little things, like I kind of wanted to like understand
all of the World of Warcraft lore from the very beginning of time to presently.
Um, and I would have taken a lot of research and I would put it all in a video.
But of course, World of Warcraft is gigantic.
There are already people who have entire channels dedicated to documenting World of Warcraft
lore and they do it really in an entertaining way with animations and voiceovers and I'm
like, okay, well, I mean, why would I spend all that time researching?
But is there like something that was subpar compared to what was already around?
But maybe they're doing subpar because they're not funny.
Yeah, I guess.
They are funny.
You would need.
I mean, I guess you would need to find an angle to it that would like, it's like, okay,
but has anyone does it like this?
Like has anyone done it in this way?
Like, like I said, the thing that I'm doing, other people have made videos about similar
things, but no one has done it in the format that I am planning to do it.
So I'm like, that's, that's good.
Interpretive dance.
Yeah, exactly.
Uh, like that's, that's good enough.
You know, I mean, maybe, uh, yeah, maybe other people make like World of Warcraft lore videos,
but nobody has like organized it into like a comprehensive, uh, I don't know, uh, the
fucking eight hour long, uh, yeah, spoken word poem about it.
All right, get right on that.
Yeah.
That's, that's an untapped market.
No, nobody's just dryly spoken the lore, uh, while they play, um, Counter-Strike in the
background.
I think that that's an untapped market.
Yeah.
I want heavy interruptions.
You're like, oh, wait, wait, I gotta wait.
Hang on.
Give me a minute.
Okay.
Yes.
Double kill.
Okay.
So anyway, uh, so anyway, Thrall is green.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, I said campers, man.
Oh, bullshit.
Okay.
So anyway, uh, uh, the horde is good and the alliance is bad.
Huh?
Um, yeah.
Yeah.
So you should Thrall go to the mall.
Thrall.
Thrall plays Super Smash Bros.
Cool.
Brawl.
Uh, I don't know.
I don't know anything about anything about the World of Warcraft lore.
I didn't even know it when I was playing it.
Uh, I knew that Arthas was bad.
What, uh, race were you?
Uh, my main was a troll.
So did you, you got like the, when you made your character, there's like the cutscene
that zooms around and ends on your character.
And there's like a narrator saying stuff about your, your kind.
What, what's the trolls up to?
I mean, I, I, not, not much.
They're kind of just, you know, they sort of have their like witch doctor stuff and
like, you know, they're in the horde.
They're allied with the orcs and like, that's it.
You got it.
I'm pretty sure there's just not that much else too.
I remember the, the Draenei kind of had, the Draenei had like their own, uh, they were
like alien.
I thought the Draenei were really cool.
And then I, um, crash landed on the planet because they were fleeing the Burning Legion
who were also in space.
Yeah.
And they're like, oh man, I love the dry.
I, uh, I, how like they're, I didn't realize it at first, but like they look exactly like
demons.
And like they are demons.
Like they're the same creature.
It's just those are like the evil version of what was originally these like these peaceful
like blue people.
They're peaceful blue people.
They got like, when the Burning Legion conquers a planet, um, they enslave the race and they
turn them into demons.
And then all the different demon enemies you see in World of Warcraft are different races
of different things that have been conquered over the galaxy.
And we see the Draenei and it's like, oh, well, they're not all like.
I saw, I saw one of those demons and I was like, huh, you know, now that I think about
it, and I kind of do just sort of look like, you know, regular old like hoof footed, like
Satan demons, just blue.
Oh yeah.
Neat.
Uh.
Yes.
Kind of like.
So much richness.
There's so much layer.
Hmm.
Someone should make.
So much onion.
There's so much content to be mine for like an eight hour long YouTube video that people
post around like, oh my God, I can't believe somebody made an eight hour long video explaining
the lore.
Oh my God.
Who would do that?
Haha.
Let's make clickbait articles about it.
Do people make clickbait articles now about those?
Yeah.
Like, uh, when Quinton reviews put out the fucking like seven hour long victorious review, just
like, just the fact that he did that, like fucking news outlets were making like shitty
non-articles about like, some guy made a seven hour video discussing every episode of victorious
lull and just got a ton of exposure from that.
Just from the fact of being like a very stupid endeavor that someone like fully, fully executed.
I mean, it's playing the meta.
He knows how stupid that looks.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
It's just, it's, it's, it was objectively a smart thing to do because of how stupid it
is.
You need to make a 100 hour video talking about the lore.
Oh, but I, I'd lose my voice.
Uh, I don't know exactly how long this video project that I am working on is going to be.
I am considering ways that I could make it, ways that I could extend the length and wondering
like, can, can I make it absurdly long, like stupidly long?
And, and if so, should I do that?
Uh, I am taking it under consideration.
You should obviously not pad it because like a super long video with a lot of fluff would
make me click away.
No.
But I mean, I wouldn't want to pad it.
Don't, don't like leave things out.
If you want it to be.
No, I'm thinking, I'm thinking, like comprehensive and just allow it to be whatever length it
is.
Yeah.
I'm wondering like how long can I, can I make it by just like being as comprehensive as
possible and like how much.
Yeah.
And I don't know.
I genuinely don't know.
I think that there's two ways to approach it.
There's like the, the cliffs notes of the most interesting parts, which is going to be
like, you know, depending on what the subject is, would be a shorter video, but a longer
video people would just put on and listen to.
Yeah.
And the droning is like relaxing.
So if it's like all, if it's really interesting stuff, I would say try to make it a shorter
video.
But if it's a lot of stuff that is just sort of odd that they have all that information
about them, then you would go for a longer video because it's not like, you know, imagine
if you're like trying to sleep and you got this video playing.
You want it to be like the same sort of interestingness throughout.
I, I, I'm just going to have to, going to have to see, I'm going to have to see how long
it ends up being.
I'm, and I'm going to have, I think I'm inclined to try and like rush past things and like
keep things short and concise, but I think I'm going to like maybe try and maybe try
and like resist that urge that I have and like not like force it to be shorter than
like maybe it needs to be.
Like if it, if it's long, like let it, like if it needs to be long, let it be long is
kind of my thinking about it.
Yeah.
Because people like long videos.
The long videos do well and there's really no reason to not do that.
I wish, I wish that my lectures had been longer.
It would only be better, they would only be better for having been longer, I think.
I agree.
Yeah.
It's funny.
I saw a long video recently.
Yeah.
I'll let you finish first.
Oh, I was just going to say, I remember like people have commented on like how long they
are.
And like looking back, like, yeah, those, like the Sonata lecture came out in an era before
you know, people making seven hour retrospectives about Pokemon Ruby, 12 hour long retrospectives
about, you know, Skyrim, a seven hour long retrospectives about victorious, you know,
compared to all that, like two hours, 10 minutes is nothing.
It's funny in hindsight.
I've watched a long video.
I watched a, I think it was, I don't know.
I think it was, oh God, what was it?
I watched like an eight hour long video yesterday.
I just put it on like all day.
It was a, well, I don't remember.
And I'll think, I'm probably, it'll come to me.
Was it a no cold world travest?
No.
I don't know.
Oh, was it Pokemon?
I, listen, we, I don't, I don't remember.
I will probably remember at some point.
We don't have to dwell on it.
Were you going to say oblivion?
I was going to say, I saw, I got a video recommended to me that reminded me of a thing, a mini rant
perhaps.
But yeah, it was like a long video.
It was like the first 100 levels of the back rooms explained.
And I'm like, the back rooms, I know that mean, what do they mean levels?
I thought it was just, thought it was just yellow, yellow empty office building.
You know what the back rooms is, right?
Yeah.
No.
It's, all right, you may have seen this.
It's like based on liminal spaces.
There's like a, I think there was a video series or just a short film made of the
back rooms, which is like a, a dingy office building with uncanny architecture and like
weird hallways and it doesn't make sense.
And it goes on and on forever.
Yeah.
It's like the sense of a liminal space, but a video of it.
But then there was a monster and monsters scary.
That does sound scary.
I think that would scare me a lot.
Yeah.
Well, I think nowadays there's like at least 10 or 20 people who are making back rooms
videos that are actually, for the most part, a lot of the ones I've seen are very, very
well made.
It's not a genre video.
People really like this idea of like the, the, the sort of the feeling of being a kid
and lost in some, in your parents like office building or like in a place where there's
no people around and it's just like oppressive fluorescent lights and, and it's just sort
of unnerving that it's like, cause like the idea is that you're there and there's no,
like you just black out and you wake up there and there's no way out and you're just trapped
there forever.
Yeah.
And that's a, that's an appealing prospect.
For a horror setting.
Yeah.
For a horror setting, it's like this infinite space that just kind of looks the same, but
like, it doesn't really make sense and it just stretches on forever and you're just kind
of stuck there.
You know, so yeah, like I was watching that video and the video has to go through like
a hundred like versions of this.
So like there's like one that's an office building.
There's one that's like a basement full of pipes that goes on forever.
There's one that's like a hotel lobby that goes on forever, et cetera.
And the video was sort of like, I guess he wanted to be concise.
Like he didn't really spend a lot of time on each one.
The video was only an hour long to talk about a hundred things.
So I feel like that could have been a video that could have benefited from its length.
But the other thing that I was thinking about watching it, it's not directly related to
this conversation is I kind of, I kind of hate how like this cool idea of just like an infinite
space that goes on forever.
Like everyone's like, yeah, but where's the monster?
Where's this scary stick figure that jumps out at you and goes, blah, we need like ten
pages of lore and there has to be a bunch of monsters and they come in different types
and they have these rules.
And if you you blink three times and then like it's just all this.
Well, that's I mean, that's just that's just good horror writing.
You know, it needs you need to have like a really clear explanation of like what everything
is.
You need to be able to like put it on a spreadsheet.
They overcomplicate everything.
It's it I get the compulsion.
If you can't I mean it's a mystery.
I want to figure it out.
But like people that just would just make up an idea for like something and then people
like, oh, yeah, that's probably that's that's a good idea.
So that's now canon in our fan and world.
If there isn't a well understood explanation for what the monster is and its exact capabilities
and what sort of taxonomy and hierarchy it exists within, then like, what are we going
to make a wiki about?
Yeah.
I I didn't like the the monster.
I I didn't realize how much the monster detracts from the feeling.
I always like the liminal spaces posts.
They're like, ah, that's it's just it's an odd feeling to see something that is a liminal
space because it just it's it's like nostalgic but like I'm nerving.
And like the it's still and it's like, what do I do here?
But the the back rooms with the monsters.
It just sort of becomes like, oh, no, you're there's a minotaur in this maze and he's going
to get you.
These rooms would be so awesome to be in with like people.
Yeah.
So what I'm posting here is a offshoot of the back rooms called the pool rooms.
Actually, that descending staircase into the abyss is actually scary.
I don't like that one.
Yeah.
Yeah, these are great.
The pool rooms is like the better version of the back rooms for me.
And the main thing like some people have made videos where like spooky spooky monster jumps
out of the pool.
But like there was one animation I saw that's really well done.
I'm going to link it by what's his name like Matt something hold on.
I think the the thing that's just it's really captivating is is the the apparent stillness
like if you're standing here and you're looking at this there's nobody around you can keep
walking you can look around but like there's no like sense of urgency.
I feel like the sense of urgency is contrary to what the liminal space images like bring
to the table.
It's like if you had a doom level in a little more space back rooms level is like or a quake
level.
It'd be fun but it would just be a quake level.
Oh God.
Yeah.
Although I would like that.
Now they say it.
This is like even knowing that like there's no like jump scare and this like it's too
tense for me to watch.
I know it's really well done though.
Like this is all just an animation.
I mean you think they built all of us for real.
Oh it's animated.
Yeah.
I guess that makes sense is the camera motion.
The found footage but like the footage is so fucking weird.
I mean where are they.
I mean I yeah so I mean some of these rooms seem like they might exist in some capacity
somewhere but like not a whole complex like this yeah.
It's a feeling of like going into an abandoned building and not being sure if there's like
somebody is going to tell you to get out of here.
Yeah.
You're just like you know it's real life so real life doesn't have random encounters
so like there's no monsters going to come.
It would actually be really man I don't know.
I don't know what would scare me more like the prospect out of this.
There's like if I was here in one of these pool room places it would be scary to be
all alone and think like I'm the only one here like there's like nothing.
This just goes on forever and ever and I'm the only one and like there's nothing else.
It's just an expanse but it's also scary to think like what if someone did show up.
Like what if what if there was someone like I don't know I would feel like.
Are they going to get me or are they going to do something like.
I'm going to have sex with me or what's going to happen.
I would feel like if someone finds me if someone finds me here it's like they're going to think
I'm not supposed to be here they're going to do something to me.
Yeah.
It's the sense of that that possibility because you don't know anything about this place.
It's not like oh in 5am the janitor will come and open up.
It's like you have no idea what the hell is going on.
The fear comes from not seeing anything.
Not actually seeing a monster running after you.
And but assuming that it could could be there.
I remember good fucking atmosphere.
It's it's thick the atmosphere is thick.
By the way I remembered the long video I watched it was the new LS mark ranking every
SpongeBob SquarePants episode ever seven hours.
It's good.
Oh I think I saw that and recommended.
I had I have what I have watched the one he did it with the Simpsons he did it with family guy.
I watched both.
Oh yes that guy.
I haven't watched any of those.
It's something about.
His avatar.
No well that but also just the the idea of like ranking every episode of.
I don't know.
I I feel like I can't imagine game.
I'm down for it.
Like yeah.
All right.
Well I I mean you can you can tell me then do they get into an acceptable or satisfying
level of depth with their regards regards their opinion on each episode.
It or do they like say yeah this one was pretty good.
Next one.
He will generally give.
I mean he goes more into it like that if he doesn't like it he'll explain why if he
does like it he'll explain why they do tend the explanations tend to get shorter and
shorter but it's because like they start to fall into patterns that like you've seen already
like if a season has like a recurring theme that he finds really annoying like you know
he doesn't have to explain it multiple times he'll just be like oh it's another episode
like this only instead of this situation it's in that situation but it still does this this
and that so you know really annoying didn't like it bottom of the list anyway next episode.
Some some of them he'll have give a pretty short explanation for but you know usually
have a thing or two to say about each one.
I mean I guess I like the real gyms like season.
I love the real gyms.
Season reviews because in a smaller capsule when he's only talking about so many episodes
you can get more of a of a recommendation or like a sense of what it's like to watch
that season.
If you're doing like every episode you're gonna forget which ones are good by the end
and it's just YouTube squish.
Yeah I mean yeah you definitely forget.
He doesn't keep like a running tally of the full list.
He keeps a list of a by season like as he goes through the season he'll rank all the episodes
in the season and then only at the end does he give you the full list of like all you know
900 episodes he'll read up the names off in order like this is the full master my full
ranking for yeah I mean you definitely do not remember where every episode fell on the
list as he goes through them.
It's like many.
Like I appreciate that it's like type of like mindless content that's fun to just put on.
Yeah but I always like it when there's a bit of a point to the video.
Like Drew Gooden is a YouTuber who talks about all sorts of things.
He made a video comparing every season of Saturday Night Live to see if it actually has gotten less funny
or whatever and he had like that was the ideas like it's a question and he's gonna answer it by
watching an obscene amount of media and it's like oh yeah you know at the end he has a conclusion
and like something to talk about at the end of watching every Simpsons episodes I guess they just have
their favorites and their least favorites.
No.
Which is less engaging for me but it's fine.
I think see I feel like it's kind of the same because like I mean there sort of is an implicit
question there it's like well you know did it get as did it get bad like when did it get bad
and when did it get bad?
Yeah.
Did it get bad after season 8? Season 10?
He does come to conclusions at the end and he's like yeah so like after like this was
kind of the point where it fell off and like this this was the this was the like how I felt about it.
Like he has a different he comes to kind of different impressions of the of like Simpsons
versus Family Guy versus SpongeBob.
I think it's I think it's he gives a little bit of I guess you could call it analysis
enough that it's engaging for me anyway.
Alright.
I like them.
I have to pee again though so fuck.
BRB.
Damn.
Dang.
Eleazar put an image of Howard Hamlin smiling at the camera in the center of the screen
and slowly zoom in for 20 seconds.
And on top of that put a picture of Oyster smiling please.
Oyster smiling?
Do you know Celery Man?
I don't.
It's Tim and Eric's skit.
Oh I love Tim and Eric though.
Uh yeah it's uh yeah if you google Celery Man you'll find the clip.
Damn.
I think it's is it Paul Rudd?
Is that his name?
Guy who played Ant-Man.
Yeah Paul Rudd.
Oh my god.
His coffee spilled all over.
And he's Celery Man.
Oh he's not Celery Man but he's working.
And he's-
That is Paul Rudd.
Yeah he's got a computer.
I believe today is Sunday and tomorrow is Monday.
Better Call Saul Day.
You know Bob Odenkirk is on Tim and Eric as well.
A few people from Better Call Saul.
In fact a lot of the actors in Better Call Saul and Breaking Bad come from comedic backgrounds.
Yeah I know in Breaking Bad there was the two guys.
The big guy.
And then the little guy.
The ginger guy.
The ginger guy is um fuck I know his name.
He was in Star Wars.
I know his name.
I know there's a B in his name.
He was the guy for F is for Family and he's a great comedian as well.
Bill Burr.
And the other guy um what's his character's name?
Big fat guy.
Hewl.
Hewl Bobo.
He is I think a comedian as well.
I'm back.
What are we talking about?
I'm talking about comedic actors being in Breaking Bad and Better Call Saul.
You know I found a clip that didn't have that many views.
It was from like an older show Bob Odenkirk did way before Breaking Bad where he was like
man I had a job at a law firm and I had to quit for Chuck.
Wait you're talking about Mr. Show right?
I think so.
Yeah the law school sketch for Mr. Show.
I've seen people suggest that it's a yeah that it's the same character.
Well there's the law school sketch that has the actor for Chuck playing a law professor
with you know Bob Odenkirk.
Right.
In the background but there was like another show where he said where he said he had to
quit a law school quit like a job at a law firm for a guy named Chuck.
Oh I haven't seen that one.
That was like not Mr. Show.
That was like a separate clip.
Let me find it.
Oh weird.
The Bob Odenkirk Law Breaking Bad Mr. Show Chuck Saga Law Web is very tangly.
Here it is.
Welcome to law school.
I'm Professor Peans.
Oh that guy was on Tim and Eric as well.
No maybe.
Wait you mean David Cross?
The glasses guy.
There's two glasses guys.
The glasses guy with the no hair.
Oh my god they both have no hair.
The glasses guy with the gray hoodie.
That's David.
That's David Cross yeah.
Yeah.
Bob Odenkirk on news radio.
Wait this isn't Mr. Show.
Yeah I don't think this is Mr. Show.
This is like some other thing where he's like again pre-breaking bad.
Oh this is some other sketch comedy show that he did with David Cross.
But not Mr. Show.
I have to feel like the creators of.
And it's got all the same fucking people.
Both of these other all four of these people were in Mr. Show.
I don't know.
I recognize all of them.
There's another guy from Mr. Show who appears in like one episode of Better Call Saul in the most recent season.
I don't know if you've seen it yet.
I haven't watched, no I haven't seen the new season.
I haven't seen a single Better Call Saul.
Mr. Show has so many actors that like went on to do other things like Tom Kenny is in Mr. Show.
That's crazy.
Oh shit really.
Yeah he's really funny.
There's the girl.
I don't know some girl who was in I think in 24.
It was like Jack Bauer's assistant in like the first couple seasons of 24.
Was in Mr. Show.
There's a bunch more.
Yeah I think a bunch of people who went on to be in Tim and Eric and stuff.
Yeah this guy from this Tim and Eric skit was also a major character in Better Call Saul as well.
He played Cliff Mane.
I can't wait to watch that and be like oh the Cinco Phone Guy.
Yeah he plays a very important character.
Well maybe not super important but I think he's important.
I love Cliff Mane.
He's just an old man who's trying to be a good lawyer.
It had been a long time since the last Better Call Saul season came out right?
Yeah like a two year gap or something.
Okay then I think I was caught up because yeah I watched it a few years ago.
Did he get to the part with the Germans?
Ooh I don't know that doesn't ring a bell.
German engineers building.
Does that ring a bell?
Not really so maybe I did.
Oh my god you might not have even seen season 4 then.
You know what I don't think I did see season 4.
Shoot you gotta catch up.
And I don't remember what happened in season 3.
I'm so fucking stupid man I don't remember anything.
Oh god no.
I don't remember what happened in the show.
I almost said Mr. Show.
You gotta watch a retrospective more video.
I should watch LS Mark rank every episode of Better Call Saul and that will tell.
No just watch the show instead.
Why would I watch the show when I can watch an 8 hour long YouTube video explaining the show?
Yeah instead of watching a season for 8 hours.
Watching even longer even more time listening to a YouTuber tell me about it.
I should watch a fucking...
Oh I just watched a video.
It was explaining how react content is basically wage theft.
No.
No he's pretty much right.
No I agreed with it.
They made a really compelling case.
What was the case?
This is basically...
He used an example of some YouTuber who like his whole thing is just reacting to stuff.
It's basically just the idea that someone who does reaction content
basically it's other people invest the time and the effort and the money into making content
but that just becomes the content of a react streamer
and at the same time that person's reaction content is also taking views away from
not just the person that made the content originally but just the broader YouTube ecosystem.
Are you certain that they're taking views away?
He made a pretty compelling case that they do yeah.
I'm pretty sure that for certain things once you see somebody react to it
you don't care to go and check it out yourself because you've already seen it.
I think that's most things.
Well react channels now...
I think it really depends on the relative sizes of the audience though.
If they're like a big channel and you're like a small channel
that would probably bring more exposure than you'd have otherwise
and then you could get a lot more fans from that.
Okay, yes?
I wonder what the math is on that.
Like if you're small and a big react channel reacts to something
then yeah that's gonna bring exposure
but I think in terms of the entire ecosystem of YouTube
of like what are people watching
the general trend is like if people are watching react content
they're not watching original content and so on the whole
it does like take views away from other people who make content
and funnel it into people who merely aggregate it
in the form of reaction content.
And I think it's true, I agreed with it.
I only ever look at reaction videos for things I've already seen.
Yeah, I don't think...
I'm not sure if that's how most people do it
but I don't... how did I even get on this topic?
I guess most people are just...
I don't know, we're talking about Better Call Saul and then this happened.
Wait, fuck, why did I bring this up?
I had a point that I wanted to make.
You mentioned someone made a video about react channels being bad.
Yeah.
No, but why did I bring that video up?
Shit, what were we talking about before?
Something on the topic of watching long explanations of things instead of watching the thing.
Oh, yeah, I think I was just gonna...
I think that was all in service and I was gonna joke that I was just gonna watch
and go and react to Better Call Saul instead of watching Better Call Saul.
Yeah, that was it.
Yeah, that's it, that's all.
I do watch people react to Better Call Saul and because...
When it's like network television, I feel like...
When it's network television, I don't think it has the same.
I don't care that much.
Well, especially because to avoid copyright detection, they have to like...
They can't even show the whole episode, they just kind of have to edit it down to like...
Yeah.
Like just like half the length of the actual episode, just like the highlights.
That makes sense.
Actually, you know, what I would agree is wage theft is when channels are like...
If you want to see the unedited full reaction, sign up for my Patreon.
People who do that, I'm like, that's a little scummy.
What the fuck?
Wait, hey, I reacted to How to Train Your Dragon if you want to watch...
I only show like 30 minutes worth of highlights on YouTube.
If you want to see my full unedited reaction, go to Patreon.
I'm like, wouldn't that be more of a copyright violation since people...
It's behind a paywall?
Also, who would pay for that?
Yeah, it absolutely is.
Like, who would pay money to see that?
Like, you could buy the movie for the price of that.
I mean, reaction content has always been like a...
How legal is it, actually, sort of thing.
If you just...
I feel like if somebody is like commentating...
Like, you can do a commentary of a thing.
You're not really supposed to put the film in there.
You can have a commentary track that you can play with the film that you own.
But like a reaction YouTuber, is it a video they have of just the whole film?
Here's the video I saw.
Uh, yeah.
Reactors, the professional parasites, how everyone loses except...
I believe it, even if it was false.
Because I just don't like reaction content.
Uh, I hadn't really thought about it.
Oh, wait, I know this guy. He attacked Dream.
Wait, uh, Dark Viper or Asmongold?
Yeah, Dark Viper, he fucking confronted Dream on his cheating bullshit
and like called him out pretty hard when it happened.
And Dream was like, oh, no, no, no, no, man.
Oh, let me convince you, but I'm not cheating and he would...
Oh, well.
Pretty good.
Well, we all know how that...
Dream was a duity cheater.
Yeah, I don't think...
I've never seen or heard Dream,
but I have a strong negative opinion of him from everything that I've heard.
He makes...
He's able to pull off cool Minecraft stunts
when playing against his friends and speedrunning.
Well, they try and kill him and all that shit.
Well, over time, more and more, it feels like the videos are becoming more staged.
Yeah.
And he's also kind of a dickhead.
He's a real Ben St on that Twitter just going out attacking people
or some shit I actually don't know if he attacks people.
I don't believe for a second that he is anything like me.
You know, probably not.
That just doesn't track.
Look, I can't roll it out if I haven't checked.
I'd be okay, yeah, true.
Yeah.
Maybe.
Oh, take any chances.
Oh, there's a new Sean video.
The weirdest thing.
I'll watch that later.
The weirdest thing to come out of that was the fucking Numberphile guy making a video about Dream.
Matt Parker?
Yeah, Matt Parker.
That was crazy.
Oh, I don't know if I saw...
I mean, I heard...
I think it was Carl Yobbs.
I think I heard Carl Yobbs explain how Dream definitely cheated.
Carl Yobbs?
Or J-Jobbs?
I don't know how to say it, yeah.
I don't know how to pronounce it.
Maybe you're correct.
All I know is that this video is the best video by far on all of that stuff
because it's maths.
Yeah, I can trust Matt Parker to be somewhat good at maths.
I was convinced that, like, yeah, mathematically.
I mean, at this point, like, he's admitted to cheating, so...
Yeah.
It's not that there's any question about it, but, yeah, back then,
when it was kind of a new thing, I remember I watched...
I think it was the Carl Yobbs video.
I was like, okay, so the maths says that it's definitely...
he definitely cheated and he's just a liar.
Dream is such...
I mean, he's a product of, like, the way, like, the algorithm and luck
can elevate, like, complete who cares, nobody's into such positions of power.
He's just some kid.
And he's like, um, I think cheat.
I've hired a real physicist, astrophysicist, to prove otherwise.
And it became news.
It's just some...
Yeah.
He's just a rat.
And he's, like, a god.
The world has made it a god.
Yeah.
What's even more of a dream is Mr. Beast.
And specifically, Mr. Beast's worthless friends.
They just look like kids who sat in school and played Call of Duty and did nothing,
and now they're, like, millionaires because they're friends with a guy.
I don't know anything about them or...
All I know about Mr. Beast is just...
That's just the guy who, like, spends tons of money on stuff, right?
Well, he, like, gives, like, tens of thousands of dollars to people all the fucking time in his videos.
That's pretty cool.
I like that he gives, like, a lot of money away.
It's very clickable content to see some person get given a free car in their reaction.
And they're like, oh my god, what?
A free car?
First person to leave, last person to leave this circle wins two million dollars,
and it's like 100 people standing in a big circle,
and every day they make the circle smaller,
or they throw in little hazards to fuck with them,
or they're like, oh, if you walk outside the circle on this plank,
you can get, like, $30,000 right now,
but if you fall off the plank, you get nothing.
It's just fucking with...
Just dangling money in front of people like keys.
But, like, even when people lose, they'll still give them a couple thousand anyway,
just to be nice.
And it's like, okay.
I mean...
I mean, sure, yeah.
I guess.
I don't find the content, like, that interesting,
but, like, the fact that it's as big as it is is amusing,
and, like, interesting in that way.
It's like, ah, well, like, I saw this video where he made a chocolate factory,
like Willy Wonka,
and he had people go through the chocolate factory doing tusks,
and if they win, they get to own the factory.
But then at the end, he's like,
actually, you can sell me that factory for, like, $100,000 or something.
And so it's just, like, giving people money.
That's very funny.
He had, like, a...
That's a very funny thing to do.
Yeah, and it's like, that's kind of cool.
The actual content is kind of YouTuber, screamy, like, not really my thing.
Just the fact that he had, like, all of that, like, a huge set,
so many camera crews, like, all of these...
Like, when he built Squid Game,
that was like, huh, he actually did that.
I think it was just brown water, but, I mean, that's how it was in the movie.
Yeah.
Now, that's content.
We need a hundred Mr. Beasts,
and then there'd be so much great content.
If we had a hundred Mr. Beasts, everyone would have a...
Sorry, I was distracted by a dinosaur image.
No, that's the ending of Better Call Saul, Kim Ghost of a Dinosaurs.
It's true.
Oh, darn.
Let me spoil it.
I don't know who any of that is.
These are characters from Better Call Saul, and they're cool.
That's a guy from Mr. Show.
That was a famous guy who was on Mr. Show, just like everybody.
More like Better Cock Saul.
Am I right?
I don't...
You know, before I watched Ivor's show,
my friends were telling me about Better Call Saul,
and I'm like, Better Call Saul, more like, Better Fuck Chuck.
And they were laughing.
They were laughing real hard, because little did I know
what would actually happen when I watched the show.
I just realized that picture of Saul and Mike is in the AVGN room.
Oh, my God.
Gained some lotion. They're looking a little tan.
They're looking a little, yeah, I mean, blotchy.
They look like they could use some grafts.
Save them.
Okay.
With voicemails.
Yeah, I was actually just gonna say,
we've been going for two and a half hours.
Is it time to go to voicemails?
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, well, let's do it.
Go to speakbive.com.
Is that the voicemails?
Is that the...
Yeah, to leave a voicemail.
Okay.
Let's see here.
Did we listen to this one called Serious Question Time?
I just got to close my window in case Moth's coming.
I drew giant testicles during this recording, by the way.
I just wanted to let people know about it.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
Okay.
Is the...
Did we listen to this vocaru one called Son of a Glitch?
No, we heard this one, didn't we?
This one?
This one called Son of a Glitch, a vocaru.
Yes, we did.
What is multiple, potentially?
We'll listen just in case.
All right, let's try this vocaru one.
Wait, wasn't this you, Oblivion?
Yeah, these are me.
I know I sent one in right after you stopped recording last week,
so this is probably a new one.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, well, let's listen.
Uh, three, two, one, go.
My favorite show on the internet, Son of a Glitch.
Here's to top five video games I've put in my arsehole.
Number one, Mario.
You put them in?
Now that's content.
There is no game called Mario that's Super Mario Brothers
or Mario Brothers or Mario Go typing.
I think the full quote was Mario, all of them,
but I cut it short.
So Son of a Glitch, I should confess, right?
Me and my friend Maid, who the pilot he worked on
is coming out like tomorrow.
Pilot?
It's called Monkey Wrench.
It's a show by Zarell, big YouTube animator.
Oh, he's working on that.
He made a 22-minute long pilot episode of a show.
Maid worked on a bunch of scenes for it,
and Zarell did all the cleanup.
Imagine a 22-minute TV quality animation
where all the line work for all the animation
was done by one guy.
That's insane.
Yeah, Zarell did all the cleanup.
How long did it take to burn?
Oh, like at least three years.
But anyways, me and Maid, we played Minecraft.
We played the new update.
It was spooky, it was scary, and we were just goofing around
and I recorded it, and we were doing funny
video game reviewer voices,
and I just clipped a bunch of those
and just made them into voicemails.
So that's what all that shit is.
Okay, I'm glad we know the back story
of Son of a Glitch.
There's probably going to be even more, who knows.
Shower me with them.
The next non-worthless voicemail
is I think it's this one called Pigeon Circus in Tampa.
I just posted it there.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
Konnichiwa.
Okay.
Samurai-san.
Venno Sentosa.
You have this oneru.
Samurai Master.
True.
Shinzo Abe-san.
Conservative Nationally.
Nationally.
Icon-ness.
Faka-yu.
Practice.
Venno Sentosa.
Apo-yozo.
Boku morare.
Wiru-si.
Buu kanseru.
Until you next time.
Sayonara.
I fucking love that quote so much.
I gave the assassin his contraption.
Yeah, I found it in my basement.
Wait a minute.
That reminds me of this guy who I found on Twitter.
His name is Seth-sama or Sephiroth Sword.
And I cannot tell if he is satirizing something
or if this is like how he is.
I don't know. Check this fucking tweet out.
Just...
Man.
Okay.
And then he made a video of himself.
Okay, I got two more.
Two more of this guy's tweets.
His tribute.
He made a video montage of himself drawing his tribute to Shinzo Abe.
And the tribute is this right here.
And...
Okay, looking at this, I know you'd think this is like a parody, right?
You'd think this is like satire, but I don't know.
Because this guy...
I've checked out some of his videos and there's no artistry to them at all.
There's no sense that he's doing a bit.
There's no delivery. There's no comedy to them.
It's just...
How do you keep finding these weirdos?
I found this guy a while ago when I just followed his Twitter because he was funny.
But then I just saw this Abe tribute and I was like, whoa, this guy is delivering.
This guy is delivering?
Oh, I don't know.
If anyone wants to look more deeply into Sephiroth's Sama...
He's even got a little Sonic on the end of his buster sword.
I genuinely do not know what to think of this guy, but I am fascinated.
That's all.
The next...
I had a realization even though I just realized something.
What's up?
Yeah.
I'm just getting a screenshot here.
I cannot wait to see what you've uncovered.
Yeah, this is a little bit wild.
I don't think we were meant to see this, but...
Oh, no.
Ben Orochi, Orochi-sama.
I think I cracked the code.
Is that Mike Scully?
No, it's the other guy.
It's James P. Sullivan.
Mike Scully.
That's the green guy, right?
I've never seen Monster's Inc.
Why did I say Scully?
Because this guy is Sully.
Same energy. They're the same guy.
They're identical.
Fascinating.
Oh, my God, there's a spider so close to me.
Ew.
There was a Daddy Long Legs the other day in my room.
That's pretty rare.
There's not usually bugs in here, which is the one nice thing.
The one good thing I could say about my shitty apartment is that there's usually not bugs in my room.
On that day, that failed.
Even that...
It failed to clear even that low bar.
Anyway, what?
It's like the tiny little garden spider, the size of a piece of crumb.
I found...
And he was leisurely walking up the wall.
Oh, no, he stopped and then he's going.
Yeah, I found there was a Daddy Long Legs walking around near the end of my bed,
not on the bed, just at the floor near it.
And then on a paper plate that I had been eating a sandwich on,
I found there was a tiny, tiny, tiny little spider walking around on it.
Sucks.
Hate this.
Hate this shit.
The next voicemail, I'm posting it now.
Shit, I already posted it.
It's called Prince in the Big City.
I think I know what this is about.
Three, two, one, go.
Wow.
Boston, the Big Apple.
I finally arrived.
Amazing.
RFCKcon7 here I come.
Anyways, I guess the first thing I should do is go and kill Ben St.
Yeah, number one.
I have to figure out one thing before I can get to his location
by my preferred mode of transportation.
Where are the bike lanes?
This guy is like Danish or something,
lives in some some frugal European country where they ride bikes.
I heard Boston had great walkability and stuff,
but no bike lanes.
Yeah, not bike ability.
That fucking sucks.
Fuck Boston.
There aren't many bike lanes.
It's true.
You just got to have helis.
You just got to have roller blades.
Oh, you know, actually, you might be right.
You know, I mean, people do ride bikes around.
I don't think we don't have dedicated bike lanes.
I think you just ride on the fucking...
Oh my God.
Just ride in the breakdown lane.
You ride right in the middle of the road to avoid cars going either way.
Actually, did you see...
Yeah, right down the middle in between, yep.
Did you see that fruity...
I have a storm.
That fruity document that the Texas GOP cooked up a few weeks ago.
A fruity document from the GOP?
Nah.
Okay, the Texas GOP released a document that was full of absolutely psycho-insane shit
that they want to do if they win.
And it's textless, so they're going to.
It's...
Yeah, but this is like worse than you think if you haven't heard of it already.
Like...
I mean, I think they want to, you know, make gay marriage illegal.
That's one thing.
Outlaw, yeah, outlaw gender.
Outlaw gender, period.
Yeah.
Okay, so like...
Yeah, they want to get rid of, you know, gay marriage.
Obviously, they don't fucking do that.
Contraception.
No more contraception alone.
Yeah, they want to get rid of contraception.
They want to get rid of all-sex education at all levels and all grades.
Even a harm prevention and risk aversion.
They want to get rid of that education too.
Right.
They...
So they can more easily take advantage of them.
Preventing harm is so fucking woke.
We got to stop that.
Yeah, we can't teach kids about stranger danger.
Like, even that's got to go apparently.
Yeah, that's pretty woke.
Because they don't think we're strangers.
Yeah.
They want to like make it like super hard to get a divorce.
They want to abolish for minimum wage.
They want to abolish paid leave of all kinds, including family leave and sick leave.
They want to, you know, just normal stuff.
They want to declassify carbon dioxide as a greenhouse gas.
You know, they want to have it written into law that science is wrong apparently.
They want to ban high-speed rail.
They want to ban funding for...
What do you mean ban high-speed rail?
They want to make it illegal to build high-speed rail anywhere, even on private property.
Because they want cars instead, right?
What the fuck?
That's just insane.
They want to make it illegal to publicly fund slow rail.
They want to make it illegal to fund alternate lanes for like, you know, bike lanes and bus lanes.
And any infrastructure, even sidewalks potentially, I don't fucking know.
You know, I didn't think you were going to surprise me.
But yeah, wow.
I mean, this is like comedically evil.
But like, what are they trying to get votes from this?
I don't know.
Like, who likes this?
I mean, I know some people liking...
No gay marriage, you know, like Backwoods, Hillbillies, Losers, Bigots.
They have their social issues.
But like, who's against train?
I mean, like, illegal to make new trains?
Like, are people seething about trains existing?
I think trains are commie shit, clearly.
I think it's just one of...
I think that's probably just one that like, most people don't care about.
Yeah, but like...
That's something they want to do.
Like, that's not most people's like, top of their issues list.
And the same document also has multiple sections about, we believe in small government.
It's like, fuck off.
No, you don't.
Yeah.
This is not small government banning, building basic shit.
They also want to...
Yeah, that's a say the line, Bart.
Say the line, Bart.
Small government.
Yay!
Yeah.
Yeah, abolished environmental protection agency, repeal of the Endangered Species Act,
eliminate campaign contribution limits.
That's clearly a good idea.
That's not the...
If that doesn't just give the game away right there.
Yeah, they also want electoral collage, like the electoral college for all like,
Congress appointments from Texas, which would basically like guarantee 100% Republicans
getting in from here, which would be dumb.
Right.
And anti-democrat.
There's also a section about teachers being forced to have guns in class, among other normal shit.
I think the average conservative doesn't want to minimum wage and wants no sick leave
and family.
That's pretty normal.
It's pretty normal stuff.
I think you're appealing to the base.
I joke.
This is like insane shit.
I don't know.
Honestly, they might for all I know.
I mean, I don't know.
Kai's mom is like very conservative, but like, even she is like, this shit's like fucking
nuts.
I don't know what they're doing.
I don't know.
It really does like...
If only it would trigger some self-reflection.
Like, is this what I've been voting for all along?
Oh, actually.
I mean, I think it actually might when it gets to this.
No.
This far.
I think...
Sorry.
It won't.
I promise.
Well...
It would have already.
What I mean is that there are a lot of people who voted Republican, voted for Donald Trump,
that aren't quite as insane as all of that.
I feel like the people who love all of those things listed are not enough of a majority
to win, like, the entire presidency.
If they're going like full mask off, evil policies everywhere, the Republicans are
not going to look as good.
Right?
Yeah.
I don't think it...
They wouldn't share this information if it would hurt their electoral chances.
My favorite addition that I haven't yet mentioned is compelled speech.
Remember when Jordan Peterson lied about Bill C-16 and talked about how for governments
going to force you to use people's preferred pronouns?
They're going to force you not to use people's preferred pronouns.
They've classified social transition as abuse, and anyone facilitating it in any way is breaking
the law is another thing they want to do for anyone under the age of 21.
So if you have a friend who's 21 or younger and you call them she, and that's not what
they were assigned, you're breaking the law.
I would say, as a conservative, as a Republican voter, I would say that freedom of speech is
pretty woke and should probably be abolished, yeah.
As a small government libertarian, I do think that freedom of speech is Marxism.
I really, the long short, I want to get out of Texas.
This place is starting to fucking suck.
It's getting real bad.
Texas is bad.
Well, I mean, I like to think that human beings are not what these policies imply about humans.
There's plenty of people like what?
Yeah.
I don't think most people are like, yes, we should defund the railways.
I don't think most people are like into that, but I just don't think, I think people who
are socially conservative will continue to vote Republican, basically regardless of
all this other stuff, because that's all secondary.
Yeah.
Like the impression I get from Cairo's relatives is that they would all, if you told them about
any of the stuff they'd say, that shit's all insane and crazy and stupid, but they're
also like, well, I don't know, I'm never voting for a Democrat.
My daddy voted Republican and they just do it, and that's as far as I think about it,
which is bad.
Another reason I have to get out is because I wouldn't be able to get a US citizenship
if they pass all this shit, because another thing, if citizenship becomes impossible
unless your biological parents are US citizens, which is translation for no one can immigrate
at all.
I heard, man, I don't remember where I read this.
It might have just been an anecdote or something, but I think it was about Romney, apparently
voters, Romney could say, I plan to, I am running for governor or whatever, I'm running
for senator.
My platform is, I am going to cut taxes, basically cut taxes for the rich and for corporations
and raise taxes on the poor and middle class, and he could just say that, and people just
would not believe it.
People would just like, and then you could tell someone, yeah, this is his platform,
and people would just be like, there's no way that's his platform.
There's no way he's actually running, even though he was, right?
Maybe it wasn't about Romney.
It was something.
I think people just don't, people just don't, I don't know, they'll vote Republican even
if you tell them that, they'll just be like, nah, that can't be right, nah, they can't
really, yeah, but they're not really going to, no, that's all just, all that stuff about
defunding the rail and no minimum wage and freedom of speech is illegal.
That's not what, no, they're the party of small government, they're not actually going
to do that, so like we can still vote for them just to kill trans people and like, so
it's, yeah, it's fine, it's fine, all the other stuff is just...
No joke about killing trans people, yeah.
There's that guy, Mark Burns in South Carolina who was running for Congress, who went on
a podcast and talked openly about how he wants to execute all the LGBT people and went through
his step-by-step plan on how they would legally kill off all the fucking gay and trans people,
and he wrote about that for like two minutes, and then the people on the podcast clapped
and said, wow, this is our guy, everyone, but they literally said the our guy thing.
No, it's okay, you'd only have to kill like a few, you'd only have to do a few public
executions and then like, you know, the fear that that would create would drive all the
rest back into the closet, so like we wouldn't, we didn't actually have to kill that many,
so like it's good actually.
Let's give him a hand, let's give him a big round of applause, ladies and gentlemen.
But he got 25% of the vote even after saying that, that's like half the way to win.
I'm not surprised, yeah, because most people just don't care, yeah.
I put them all in one place and set it on fire.
I wonder, I'm starting to wonder if we're gonna balkanize.
It's kind of starting to feel that way, I know that that's probably, I'm probably jumping
the gun, but like, I don't know, we might balkanize over this shit, man.
What is balkanizing?
You know, it's when, it's like what happened in the Balkans, it's like, you know, they
split up a country into like a bunch of small like independent states.
I'm saying that the United States would like split into, split into small, several, yeah.
Then I know the people born in the wrong, that would be catastrophic for many levels.
Especially for people who are stuck living with their parents who can't get out of the
shitty part they were born into.
Oh, I mean, aside from, oh yeah, it would be, it would, living in the balkanized like,
you know, fucking, I don't know, the conservative Republic of Texas or whatever with no like
federal oversight would be like, it would be like Saudi Arabia, you know, it would be
on that level, like if you're, if you're not straight and white and probably male, like
he would not want to live there.
So I'm not saying it's good, but I, I, COVID, COVID comeback, we miss you.
No, it's still, it's still here, actually.
No, but I mean, like really come back, like, like put everyone, don't, don't, don't, don't
think we're, don't think it's gone.
They want to ban contact tracing.
So if they're trying to bring COVID back, I mean, ban, ban contact.
What does that even mean?
Contact tracing is like, if someone catches COVID, like they would like, like, okay,
like, where have you been, like for the last, like, you know, week or two, since
you were contagious, what areas have you visited so we can like keep an eye out for
cases? How would you ban that?
They want to make it illegal to ask people where they've been, I guess, because they
don't want information on where the disease is spreading, because I guess that invades
privacy, maybe, I don't know.
Well, abolish, abolish no-fault divorce.
Yeah.
And also have a six month waiting period for any divorce, regardless of the reason.
So if like, they're like beating you and trying to kill you, well, you have to wait
six months, even in like extreme situations.
They're just crazy.
They want you to die.
They want you to suffer.
They want you to have no money.
They want rich people to control everything.
They're like very transparent about it.
I don't understand.
People, people like genuinely don't believe it.
Like the average person would see this lit.
I don't, I don't think they would read this list and be like, this is bad.
I think that it was just they would read it and be like, well, you know, this is all
just this is all just talk, you know, I wrote that list myself.
I read the document.
That's all in there.
Oh, very nice.
Oh, uh, I just, um, most people got there like one or two issues and like anything
else is just not going to move them on, on whatever it is.
Uh, so.
I, I self selfishly, I feel like it would be cool to be rid of these freaks if we
balkanized and I would just, I would be safe in the, uh, in the, in the liberal,
uh, what do you call it?
I would, I would be straight in the liberal commonwealth of New England or whatever.
Uh, but then, but then, you know, uh, the, the Republicans would probably
just like declare war or something.
They would probably do some shit.
Yeah.
So it's, it's, it's, it's, it's only a fantasy.
Probably, probably shouldn't be rooting for it.
On his fucking, uh, true for a website.
He liked someone like truth, damn, I guess it's time for a civil war to deal with
these fucking gays or whatever.
I don't know the actual, well, the actual issue was about and Trump just liked
that, that fucking truth, I fucking hate that.
Truth, truth, the, uh, the, the website where instead of tweets, it's truth.
I fucking hate it's annoying.
It makes, they're destroying language.
They say we're destroying language, but they're destroying language, I swear.
Um, do you want to listen to the next voicemail?
Yes.
Yeah.
Please.
Uh, the next voicemail, I already posted it.
It's Prince in the big city too.
Uh, it's up above the list there.
All right.
Uh, three, two, one, go.
Ben, that is like the fourth cop car that I see riding around Boston.
You're not doing your fucking job.
Uh, oh, by the way, um, I'm Dutch just, uh, to explain the last voicemail.
Yeah, I'm, I'm, I'm Dutch.
I don't understand why you people think it's acceptable to, uh, to paint
fucking, uh, bike signals onto the concrete road that huge fucking cars drive
across all day.
I know.
That's just asking for bike people to get turned into God damn roadkill.
Uh, but anyways, um, looking forward to the first, uh, cyclist I see
splattered across the pavement.
I haven't seen one yet.
Anyways, Boston is nice.
Uh, see you.
Well, yeah.
There are hundreds of cyclists.
Uh, yeah, I think, um, I think he's here early.
I think RFC KCon is like this weekend.
It's just a bunch of people, just a bunch of RFC K people, uh, getting
together in a, in a house in Boston.
Uh, I'll probably go visit, uh, say hi.
So that'll be fun.
But it is the weekend.
The weekend's almost over.
I mean, I mean, next weekend.
Oh, see.
All right.
I think, I think it was, yeah, it's the 21st.
I remember we were going to judge the next art contest during it on the 21st.
So I think that's, or maybe it's all this week.
Uh, I, I don't actually know.
I should check, I should check when it's happening.
Uh, I guess Prince is here early.
Uh, okay.
And then a bunch of worthless ones that don't count.
Um, okay.
Next one is an iconic PCP character returns question mark.
Posting it now.
There it is.
Three, two, one, go.
Can you hear it?
No, I hear is the scrabbling is the joke that the iconic character is inaudible.
Wait, this is a guy from the other week who was just fucking whispering the whole
time and you couldn't understand him.
Yeah, I think so.
So that guy again, I turned it up really loud.
It's just him.
Uh, he's so funny.
Can you tell what he's saying?
Uh, yeah, he's saying, oh, I see.
Cool.
Uh, the viewers will hear it next.
Next voicemail, Prince in the big city, three, three, two, one, go.
Why are there so many flags in this country?
What are they trying to tell me?
What are they trying to say?
Why are the flags in the metro station behind glass?
Let them out.
I don't, I don't know how to answer this.
Yeah.
Why, why are they behind glass?
They just keep them clean.
Let them out.
Other flags can't be out.
They've got to be kept safe from all the dirty leftists who are going to burn them down.
They put them in a nice frame to display them so that they don't get touched by dirty fucking tourists.
Dirty communist Europeans that come here and want to touch our flags.
I just wanted to put my greasy palms on their flag and I couldn't reach them.
I know.
That's what all you non-Americans want to do.
You just want to get your fingerprints all over stars and bars.
Oh, my God, you know, setting.
I have, I have like a beautiful like New Zealand flag, right?
So sadly, the flag design, we never got the change.
I was like, if we were in a house, I want to fly the New Zealand flag and the American flag together.
And I had to be warned.
I can't fly a New Zealand flag higher than the American one.
Or someone might just fucking shoot me and also it's against the law.
But wait, it's like there's a law about putting the American flag at the top.
Is it a Texas thing?
It's against the law for other flags to be flown higher than an American flag.
That is cool.
Very normal, normal.
I love small government.
It's so small, I can barely see it.
I love small, I love small government.
And that's why I like it that the big government
isn't telling the smaller state governments that they have to not
take our rights away, letting them, letting them, letting them ban abortion if they want to.
That's small government.
Small government is when federal government lets state government
ban you from doing things.
Yes, I'd put like a bunch of flags.
The trans flag at the top and a bunch of like other like LGBT flags.
And then the American flag right at the bottom, tracking in the mud.
It's like sliding all over the mud.
That's what I would do.
I'm going to take you, I'm going to take you out.
You can't fucking do this.
Is this a date?
You can't. No, this is a war.
The next voicemail is called it was Ben's Twitter banner from when they outlawed vaping three to one go.
The first panel of that comic was inspired like you saying that was inspired by
yes, your old Twitter banner.
The one where I'm squatting next to the I have been heard a song called
Dancing is not a crime.
The fire hydrant.
Unless you do it without me by panic at the disco.
And I see from that, I had this little parody idea in my mind.
Following the song, I guess, where it's like vaping, vaping, vaping is not a crime.
Unless you do it, do it, do it, do it, do it without me.
And the melody of the song follows.
I see.
I can never manage lyrics very well.
I just have that first day, the chorus.
No, I get you, man.
But yeah, deep cuts.
So I'm just so much too deep.
I don't know if this voicemail needed to be a minute nine, but thanks for the explanation.
Next one is called Candyman Ben.
Poston.
There it is.
OK, three, two, one, go.
Hey, Ben, just wanted to say that orange slice candy fucking delicious.
I think it's a noble pursuit to try and recreate it.
I do have a theory as far as how they're made.
I think that they basically just whip a bunch of fucking air into the syrup to create that texture.
And maybe if you, I don't know, used a mixer or just took a whisk and beat
the syrup as fast as you could while you're making it, you could probably get similar results.
I don't know.
I think it's worth a shot at the very least anyway.
Good luck with your candy making endeavors.
I think baking.
So I saw I found a recipe that called for baking soda.
I never I never tried putting it in there.
I did. I did manage to make some that were solid.
They were very hard.
They were very tough, not tough, but they were very solid and they really sticky.
But they didn't quite have the consistency I was looking for.
Baking soda might have improved it.
I kind of started.
I kind of changed my focus.
I might come back to that at some point.
Next one is a God.
We got another Prince of the Big City.
The Prince of the Big City episode.
This is episode four.
There's no subtitle.
Three, two, one, go.
So Ben mentioned on the last episode that he's thinking of getting on Tinder again.
But Ben, unfortunately, I am in Boston right now.
And I am on Tinder right now.
And what I'm going to do is take all of the hot girls
and take them with me back to the Netherlands.
And I will make sure that you never get laid.
And Boston will be for virgins and not for lovers.
That's that's just that's just the status quo.
Boston is for virgins.
That's just how it that's just you're telling me more of the same is coming.
And I'm ready for it.
Next one is called.
OK, there's an image link.
But here's the voicemail.
It's called Any Way Big News, three, two, one, go.
And here's the image.
It's back. Yes, a lobster.
Oh, it's lobster is back, I see.
This is this is another one from Prince.
This is Prince.
I think he might be lobster is back.
He might be reacting to Papageno's, which is he might have heard us talk about.
Me and Nate talk about that as like our favorite New England pizza chain.
Or one that we're familiar with, anyway, I was my favorite.
Anyway, lobsters back on the menu and it's never going away, baby.
OK, next one is a Vokeru link,
which I will get soon.
Download.
Showing folder, there we go.
Here it is. OK, no subtitle.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello, friends.
I have a very important message for you.
It's one come fixer.
You go very close to the microphone.
So you can hear a very important message.
OK, OK, yeah.
Closer, OK, closer.
Oh, it's a fake, you idiot.
I bought it at the party store.
It's not one day.
I don't know what to.
OK, you got us with a SpongeBob.
Is that a SpongeBob?
I think it was a sound like Patrick and then Squidward.
No, it didn't.
I thought that was like the stalker episode of the guy who was like going to kill
SpongeBob. What?
I just did not want to party.
I thought that was Squidward.
The I don't even listen.
I just will listen to L.S.
Mark explain all the episodes and I don't know what you're talking about.
So you don't even know every good attention.
Every single bit of dialogue from every episode.
By the time I read, I really got my seven hours worth out of that experience,
I guess. Anyway, that was the last voicemail
or the last one that I'm going to play because the rest are trash.
Oh, this guy, is this the
no, this isn't the thing I was talking about his mustache being a fake
that he bought at the party store.
He's been trying to kill SpongeBob this whole time and then he keeps going
interrupted. I'm pretty sure that's the plot of that episode.
I've been seeing, you know, that clown girl from
from a fucking ace, ace attorney.
Yes. Yeah.
I've been seeing a gift going around where, you know,
she she snaps her suspenders and the boobs pop and then SpongeBob
and Patrick go, they were fake.
And then some tough biker fish goes, of course, they were fake.
So I saw I saw that exact same thing you're talking about.
I've seen it posted a couple of times.
So that that's what that reminded me of, but it wasn't the same audio.
So I think it's just a coincidence.
I think I think that was that audio was from the SpongeBob movie.
With the I guess I just know my SpongeBob.
I haven't seen SpongeBob in like ten years, but I just have.
I saw it so many so many times as a kid.
I, you know, it's funny.
I had watched. Yeah, I watched it some as a kid.
I rewatched the first couple of seasons a few years ago.
And it's really funny.
I mean, I remember thinking on my rewatch, I remember getting to the end
of season three and being like, I already kind of feel the quality declining.
Like it already, like it's not bad yet, but it feels like it's getting worse.
And we're only in season three.
And then I watched the video and I watched that that video.
And Mark is like, yeah, like right at basically after season like three or four,
it like goes way off the deep end.
Like it gets immediately worse like right after that.
It's like, huh? Well, yeah, that's like that's the thing of most shows.
I usually after they hit 64 episodes, they start fucking up.
We usually after a third season, they start fucking up.
Simpsons is kind of an outlier and then it managed to last for quite a bit longer.
I know Simpsons is an outlier, but like I feel like SpongeBob is kind of
the Simpsons of its generation in that it's like to to an extent.
So I thought it would stay good longer.
They did free seasons and then a movie and then immediately after the movie,
like it was pretty like it was like a sharp turn downhill, I remember.
I remember the movie.
I don't think I've even watched a single full episode of SpongeBob,
but I saw the movies for some reason. Really? Really?
I've seen like clips. I've seen bits.
I've seen half of an episode.
I never watched it like at normal because it wasn't on TV.
So like the channels I could access.
Oh, that's so those are like only shows we could access in New Zealand, like consistently.
Was it not on British television?
It maybe was on satellite or something.
I didn't have Cartoon Network either.
I have Nickelodeon. I didn't have any of that.
I had like different things.
I had Dick and Dominic de Bungalow, which was great.
Yeah, you didn't have a you didn't have a Mega Man on the NES,
but you had a fucking Jet Set Willy on the ZX Spectrum.
So this is just as good.
Just as good. Yeah.
Now, that was like occasional like things of SpongeBob.
I just don't remember like.
Like ever being like around when it started.
I just I caught the end of an episode a couple of times.
I remember when it started airing and I watched, you know, the premiere
because I was a kid and I, you know, I would just watch it sometimes when it was on.
I guess I liked it well enough.
And I think, you know, then I kind of stop watching cartoons for as much
like when I went to college or whatever, like I didn't watch much TV.
And then I was surprised, you know, maybe in the last
in the last maybe probably less than 10 years, but in the last like five to 10 years,
the the sort of the dice of history
landed and it's like, yeah, SpongeBob was kind of like the like the show for
like Zoomer, the Zoomer generation.
Yeah, like like they all grew up watching it.
And I was like, huh, really?
That that show.
I mean, I guess I mean, I guess it's fine.
I like it. I like it fine.
I guess I never would have suspected that that would happen when it when it premiered.
Comparing SpongeBob to The Simpsons is very appropriate
because The Simpsons and SpongeBob are the only two.
No, they would be only two cartoons that like never stopped airing in New Zealand.
Pretty much I think SpongeBob must have started right when I was a kid,
because I think like right when I was like of television watching age,
because every time I would come home from school,
you turned to Channel Two and Studio Two would be on
and the presenters would talk about a funny thing
and then they would play an episode of SpongeBob and then like an episode of Yu-Gi-Oh.
And then you switched to Channel Free and Malcolm in the middle is is on.
And then after that is The Simpsons.
And that was like that was like it for like 10 years.
And it was only the first free season of SpongeBob.
What more do you need in SpongeBob, Yu-Gi-Oh, The Simpsons and Malcolm in the middle?
Well, Yu-Gi-Oh would occasionally swap out for something else.
It would be a SpongeBob and another show.
And then Channel Free was Malcolm in the middle for a long time,
but there was always The Simpsons and they would do reruns all the time.
Like the first free seasons of SpongeBob,
I must have seen at least like eight times because I was very familiar
with the order of the episodes would be in by the end.
Like I'm like, oh, next week is going to be the fucking Shanghai episode of the,
you know, they're on the flying Dutchmanship.
And after that, they'll be like this episode.
Like I mean, my sister would figure out and we'd like get excited
for the episodes coming up that we really liked and I know SpongeBob was good.
It's funny. It holds up the first few seasons anyway.
It's good.
Yeah, like I said, I watched them a couple of years ago.
And yeah, I mean, I only watched the first three seasons and they were all good.
That's good. Yeah. That's all you need.
Yeah.
Any UK heads in the audience, remember, Mona the Vampire?
Actually, that's familiar.
Mona the Vampire.
This is like all those like funny, like Canadian puppet shows.
Yeah, except I've never heard of but only Canadians know.
Yeah, there's the story of Tracy Beaker.
These are so fucking funny.
You're just you may I know you make some of these up like these.
I've never made anything up.
Dick and Dom in the in the bungalow is probably the funniest sound in one.
I can't be real. So real program.
No, it was great.
It's like you get a bunch of rowdy, like seven year olds, seven to not seven year
olds, like 10 to like 11, nine year olds, get them in a room.
And it's like a game show variety show with two like wacky zany
comedian guys who are in their early 20s, jumping around,
throwing custard pies at each other and all the kids are screaming.
And then they watch cartoons and there's like puppet shows
and like games and it's insane.
I loved it. It was my favorite show.
It came on every Saturday from nine to eleven.
Did you guys see some I think a guy who was in Black Panther
is like making a a dark and gritty Barney reboot.
Ah, yeah, stupid.
They already did that. It was called Deltarune.
Yeah, it seems like a project that shouldn't exist and maybe it won't.
But this saw the story going around Twitter.
The quote was like.
Oh. Oh, ew.
What? Oh, ew.
I think I just had a I think I just sped up a tonsil stone.
Ew.
It's a terrible.
That's that's terrible.
Oh, God, I hope that's not a new thing that's going to start happening for me.
Oh, and Yvonne Yvonne of the Yukon.
I was going to say something.
Wait, I have to say the quote of the Barney quote.
He was like, Barney asked us, like, won't you say you love me, too?
But what if that's what if that wasn't true?
I don't love you.
No, it's horrifying.
Doesn't necessarily imply hatred.
It's just sort of I thought music is coming out of your fucking speaker.
Give when you said you don't love me.
It was like like sad music started playing on my computer
and I thought it was going for this chord.
I clip that sell it to the to the highest bidder.
I sell it to fund the next Republican gubernatorial race.
It was just like the first sound of me saying, I don't love you.
And then the Republicans marching.
No, it was just the first six seconds of that video.
It just started playing randomly on what I don't know how it happened.
Some tab open and I click this.
Yeah, yeah, that's appropriate.
Well, that they should make a Barney reboot.
He says, I love you, but you don't like me.
I'll go gets his hat.
Wouldn't get the fuck out of here, Barney.
What a that's that's going to be me when I'm on Tinder after Prince
has taken all the all the cute girls back to Deutschland or whatever.
I might as well not even try, you know what?
I might as well just give up before even give it a shot.
Spare myself the spare myself the embarrassment.
Yeah, I think that's the move.
Now, you should you should give it into doing a Barney themed Tinder.
I think I think Nancy Reagan said, you know, failure.
It's not about how many times you get knocked down.
It's about how many times people see you doing it.
It's about how many times you get up again.
You're never going to keep me down.
Uh, OK, huh?
Oh, you were doing the tub thumping, tub, tub thumping.
No, it's tub thumping.
Chumbo Womba, Womba Chumba, right?
Is that Chumbo Womba?
I don't know. Yeah, it's tub thumping.
Yeah, yeah. I get knocked down.
That damn end of the song.
I don't know.
What were we talking about?
The last voicemail and before that, nothing.
There are no more.
Yes, they just refreshed.
There are no more voicemails.
Thank God.
I want to I want to talk about a little thing, though.
OK.
I talked to my therapist about like, I'm not doing anything.
It's hard.
No, it's hard to not want to be doing stuff.
Uh-huh.
And she got me on.
I mean, can you be any more specific?
It's just like I want to get back into drawing, I guess.
I've got I've got commissions to do.
I've got stuff to draw.
OK, I need to do them by golly.
That's yeah.
And she got me on this thing
where she was telling me to get a piece of paper and a pen
and to like, like she knows I have characters.
So she told me to draw some characters, like, I mean, sure.
But like, where is this going?
OK.
And I then she asked me questions like,
so what are they doing with each other?
They just stand in there and make them interact with each other.
And I'm like, I guess this character does this.
It went on like that for a while.
I really didn't know what the point was
because it was like, it's eating into my therapy time.
But by the end,
it was like the point was that
forcing yourself to do to get work done
feels the same way as somebody just asking you to do it.
Hmm.
And it's but you have to be the one to do the asking.
And I was like, oh, cool.
Like, that's actually like good advice.
Wait, it was smart.
Someone getting work done feels the same way
as someone asking you to do.
Well, when when you don't want to do work
and it's like, I can put it off like, I don't want to do it yet, not now.
Hmm.
Having.
Having another person
shove you into it is like very useful.
And it's like so it's like you can be that person to yourself.
Yeah, I don't know how to do that yet,
but like it was a way of thinking about it.
It was like pretty good.
It's also why like writers rooms are so much more productive
than a writer sitting in by themselves with a typewriter
just trying to think of stuff.
And like you got to bounce ideas off.
That's why that that works.
Like it's like if this is like someone.
This is why for years,
I found that the best way for me to be productive is to get
to sit in a call with other creative people and just vibe,
which is why when we work, which is why it works.
It works if if you're on a good time zone thing with them.
I tried to do that.
But everyone I know is like only awake when I'm about to go to bed.
I'm only around for a call when I'm about to go to bed.
I'm like if like it's like if someone else asked you
to draw something, you would do it.
You'd be like, OK, OK, well, I guess I'll figure out.
It's yeah, I guess I'll figure out a way to do it.
Yeah, it's not as simple as that.
But like it's the it's the fact that like I hadn't drawn in such a long time
and drawing the doodles, it started with something that didn't matter at all.
Draw anything is what she said, get a piece of paper, draw anything.
Yeah.
And then it's sort of like accelerated from there into
what is essentially a series of panels of two characters interacting
or three characters.
Oh, like like like some kind of comic or so like so some kind of comic.
And I'm like, man, it really is very easy to make these things
like to sketch this stuff out.
Yeah. It's the only thing holding me back is my desire to not do it.
And it's it's such a powerful desire.
But like it's it doesn't make any sense.
Like I could I could draw that so easily.
I think that the difficulty was starting is that.
I want to plan it out and throwing myself into the work
allowed me to get it done, even though I didn't know what it was at first
because it was just like an exercise.
But like that's something I need to get better at is throwing myself into work
without a plan.
So that, yeah, so that I can get my, you know, my my momentum going.
And it's like, OK, well, now I'm working, now I've warmed up.
Now I can actually like think in terms of art
and maybe I can sketch a page or something.
That's kind of like how, you know, even if you don't know what you're going to do,
like just doing something like just opening the program or whatever is like,
OK, you just you just like I don't know what I'm going to draw,
but I'm going to open the drawing program.
And I'm not going to worry about what happens after that,
but I'm going to take that step right now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
How I've gone to work recently is I just throw myself into my Patreon server
and do the Hangout channel.
I I ping the role for my patrons who like want to be notified when I'm hanging out
and they pop in and then I work for like four hours and I get a lot done.
And I'm going to start doing that twice twice a day, starting tomorrow.
What are you working in the morning?
Four hours at night, just drawing or animating or whatever I need to get done.
I want to be productive.
And I also want to invite more friends in there, too,
because if there's not enough patrons around,
I know it's good to have access to friends who can hang if they're available.
Yeah, both of you could get in if you wanted, I could just pop you right in
if that sounds like a time or not.
Sure. I mean, I mean, so I mean, so many servers,
but I'd I'll I'll accept I'll accept an invitation.
Of course, my nighttime stream would be would typically start
about an hour or two from now and my morning stream would start
let's see, like six and a half hours ago.
I could catch a morning stream.
Yeah, I could.
Yeah, I'll take that.
Epic throw me in there.
I'll throw you right in.
I'll give you the art friend role.
I I found this tweet the other day.
I liked it.
It's like a bunch of.
You know, we got this little artist here saying like each one,
he's like he's facing a problem and he's he has an unproductive way
of thinking about it versus like a productive way of thinking about it.
Like this first one is not I need to be in a better mood before I will draw,
but I will be in a better mood if I draw.
Right. Yeah, true.
That's true. Yeah.
It's so true.
These are pretty good.
I like in your server, there's a self there's a role self assign.
And if you want the horny, there's lots of people who click yes.
They want the horny role, please.
I would do access for first posting channels, because people were first
posting everywhere and I had to contain them.
Well, well.
Mm, that's that doesn't surprise me so much.
Also, those comments you linked are unironically based.
I'm going to hold on to that.
Yeah, right. I thought they were great.
I had to go through my Twitter likes.
I need to be in a better mood.
I need to be in a better mood to draw.
That's always that's why I get like nothing done for like eight hours
after I wake up.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
I've I've been there 20 times.
Well, I'm glad you like that.
I had to go through.
I had to go back through my Twitter likes for a few days to find them,
but I did.
That's great.
I hope to be making progress
on one of my comics, probably Clarissa.
Soon ish.
I don't know when I want to hope that I also hope that I am.
I am hoping to hear back from this this printer lady.
I'm hoping to very soon be done with this stupid fucking book
formatting job and send that off.
And then as I wait for them to send me the test print,
then I can get back to working on that video that I was excited about.
That's my plan.
That's a good plan.
I know. Thank you.
Hell, yeah.
Wait a minute.
I got to share another tweet.
You got to share another one.
It's a it's this one.
He's practicing the Among Us alphabet.
And as you can see, oh, my God, all the.
Fucking volume wouldn't appear.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
Yeah, I didn't realize it had a sound.
The sound adds a lot, but I couldn't access the volume.
Yeah, I mean, I I like the Q on the S.
The S looks like a worm.
Some of these are better than the O is the best one.
I like the V. The V is just upside down.
Yeah.
A is just the boy.
You is you.
There's an upside down grade.
These are great.
Look at these. This is delightful.
Oh, what do we got here?
Plomocus.
I just don't mind because of a song.
Jesus, that's fuck.
Literally.
Yikes.
You came back from the dead.
Well, oh, it counted.
Oh, it counted down.
Counted down.
Oh, I didn't even like register that.
I just thought it was like a really distressing like
lots of people kill themselves in one word.
Just did it.
No, so it's like oh, I see.
I see. Excellent.
That this is a good reaction image
when you're sad and something cool happens.
Yeah, exactly.
Don't don't be a statistic.
Oh, shit, like turn the clock back like me when I play
that new Cuphead deal.
See, I haven't played it yet.
I should get on that.
I haven't been playing video games.
I've been I've been playing games today.
I dual played Adventure Quest and RuneScape at the same time.
Now, that's productivity.
That's shitty games in one.
Even though they're neither shitty, they just are great.
And I love them.
How are you in the early 2000s twice at the same time?
Because the technology exists late 2000s.
I've always respected Jagex for like just giving the player
base what they wanted and making old school RuneScape
a permanent thing that they will upkeep.
Yes, because they asked for it.
I like it when my character has a triangle for a face.
Yes, they're so stupid looking.
It's it's a perfect.
My name is Five Polygon Man.
And I have a Five Polygon plan.
My tonsil is sore.
I wonder if there's anything to do with that tonsil stone that just.
Yes hurts a little bit and I don't like it.
Don't like not knowing what's going on.
With stuff, especially inside of me.
Better cut your open and find out.
Or get a tiny submarine shrink shrink people down
to go inside your body and look around.
Why didn't I think of that?
Get a tiny little magic school bus and the kids can like learn about
whatever the fuck's going on and sell my body to science
while I'm still alive by swallowing a little magic school bus.
Ms. Frizzle can pay me a stipend for the use of my body.
OK, that's the end of the podcast.
Patreon.com slash the procrastinator gets you some of them bonus episodes.
There is a new one.
There is a new behind the scenes bonus episode.
Oh, my God. Last week.
Yes, I'm like 40 bonus episodes behind.
I got to catch up.
I think that's number 59.
I think there are 59 bonus episodes of which only nine of them
are behind the scenes or something like that.
Send us a voicemail.
Hey, quit spamming the PCP voicemail with like.
Nonsense, because like I'm just going to ignore it.
What do you what do you get out of it?
What do you what do you as a man
get out of posting the same YouTube link over and over.
In our voicemail.
Who? Yeah, who gain who benefits from that?
I don't know. Maybe they don't even watch the show.
Yeah, maybe. Yeah.
But then but but still the question still still who.
No.
That's all.
Patreon, speak pipe.
Uh, I don't know.
Follow the PCP Twitter, I guess.
Follow us. Oh, yeah.
Sure.
Join Big Booby Mommy Milkers or my Patron, if you want to see.
I don't even know.
I don't even know where the link to that is.
Just link it.
We'll put it in the description this one time.
This one time. Oh, my God.
And then if you scroll through my post, there'll be new people
and they'll be like, oh, shit.
Check out a blibby.
We don't want them seeing Gibbs, a big old titties.
So I drew. That'd be terrible.
The one the one person who clicked this episode,
who has not already seen previous episodes
and is familiar with Oblivion Fall,
you should check out Oblivion Fall on Twitter.
I mean, on YouTube, I mean, I guess also on Twitter.
Why not?
I mean, I guess mainly Twitter is easier to like Twitter
at Oblivion Fall underscore D, where I'm going to post
little gibbon images eventually along with other stuff,
like the booze and balls I've been drawing this episode.
I drew some giant nuts and I shaded them and they look good.
But none of you can see them.
OK, let's draw my patron.
Nice. Cool.
The nuts will blot out the sun.
That's all. That's all I got.
The leading world is nothing but come.
Good night.
Good night, everybody.
See you later.
Or good morning, everybody.
Or good day, everybody.
Good night. Thanks for listening.
Everybody.
I'm going to go swab.
I'm going to go swab the inside of my mouth
and see what develops.
I'm going to go swab the inside of his mouth as well.
OK, yeah.
I'm going to go swab the man on my.