The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Hippocrit.
Hello everyone and let's commence this episode of the PCP.
I am the best guy ever.
And the PCP is an internet show to podcast with a bunch of internet creators.
We make stuff. You might know us. You might have heard of us around the world.
We're pretty good.
We're joined today by Ben Saint.
That's me. I'm an internet boy and so are all of you folks.
Hippocrit is also with us.
YouTube.com slash not doesn't exist.
And lethal Roar Mage.
I assume this is going to go up near the holidays. So happy holidays to all.
Indeed. Well said. This will go up. Let me say I think this is out on the 24th.
It'll be Christmas Eve. This episode goes out.
Merry Christmas everyone.
Why didn't we change this to be about Christmas?
What?
Didn't we consider making a Christmas episode?
We did.
We did consider it. We did consider it.
I guess we did around but we decided to be big old gringes and not go over there.
That's right.
We were actually going to do that after this one, I think.
Oh, that's right. Yes.
I think so. I think that was the plan.
Right. Okay. So enjoy that next time after Christmas is over.
I can't wait to hear the Urban Dictionary for Christmas anyway.
Speaking of which, I was about to read or I'm getting to our topic for today.
All right. Tell me if you guys, you fair viewers, can guess what our topic today is
given this definition from our Goods Friends over at Urban Dictionary.
They should sponsor us.
Here's the top definition.
The place that will give your old poor grandma a heart attack after reading the comments.
Tumblr.
Oh.
Yeah.
So that's the definition for YouTube, everybody, for YouTube.
But our actual topic is a little bit broader.
It's about the end of YouTube.
About the distant past that lies beyond what would happen in a theoretical world.
The distant past of the future.
Oh, wait.
AKA right fucking now.
Just like the end of Ava.
Get your timelines in order, Nate.
With all the things happening this year, with all the ad apocalypses and the vicious racial slurs
being said to the poor children's ears on all manner of YouTube videos.
Don't forget about the death of net neutrality.
That's a good one.
That is a good one.
That we have a BCP all fully endorsed and are very excited about.
You know, it's actually funny, a last episode that we recorded before that vote was cast
but it's coming out after the vote was cast.
Like I defended a little bit.
I raised some issues about why it would be a decent, or like there are reasons to get rid of net neutrality.
But yeah, I don't actually share that really was a great idea guys.
So watch out for that shit.
You got a little egg on your face there now.
I feel 100% responsible for the outcome of this vote.
Well, because you are.
Is it official? I think it still needs to go to quarter something.
I mean, there are like appeals and things that are still going to happen.
But like the initial big vote thing that they wanted to happen did happen.
So we will see.
But on the left, we did it guys.
Hashtag we did it.
All these things, all these things though.
I mean, if that happened, I mean, shit, YouTube stuff couldn't even,
couldn't, might not even matter anymore.
But nonetheless, we are here.
We're all internet content creators.
All of us make videos among other things.
And we all use YouTube for that stuff.
And let's just, let's just gaze into the future and think about what it will be like when YouTube is no longer king.
And you know, that could come from YouTube like, indeed.
That could come from YouTube like going away forever.
And then like having to scramble to see whatever else there is around there.
Like vid me just died.
So there's no vid me option anymore.
Rest in peace.
The anime snob.
I think the first question we need to ask ourselves is would we continue making videos if YouTube wasn't around?
It's a good question.
It's a very good question.
Would it even be on our minds to continue with that?
Or would we go elsewhere and do other types of things?
I mean, that is a very good question.
I mean, this is open-ended.
So we can pretty much just go anywhere we want with that.
So let's just start with that.
Wait, can I pose a question that I think is important?
Okay, let's say that YouTube just dies.
Do you think that the YouTube audience will like cohere somewhere else?
Like will that audience like move to a new place and there will be some new, there will be like a new way to reach them?
Or do you think they'll just be scattered and like it will be, do you think they'll just be lost?
Like that platform will just go away?
I think what would happen is if YouTube died for some reason, companies would be scrambling to scoop up all of the talent because they know they can get like views.
But they won't be able to make a good actual thing to host their content on.
So it'll be a big mess for a very long time and most people, like most people who watch YouTube casually will just forget that it ever existed.
Yeah, like the community of YouTube is very strong at the time.
Like it's taken what, like 10 years or something, but now YouTube has a very strong, you know, like individual identity.
And it is like, I think it's like the premier viewing, obviously the biggest like viewing, you know, streaming website in the world,
but it like rivals like television.
It exist and destabilizes the hold that things like television have had on us for all these centuries and eons.
And like with it, if it, for it to crumble will absolutely shatter like that community, that community will absolutely go away.
But what I wonder is, you do agree, you agree on that?
I disagree.
Oh really?
Yeah, because I feel like with the absence of YouTube, there's going to be like a gap in our internet society and like these people will congregate somewhere else.
There's a demand now, so people will want that back.
Think about like MySpace, that used to be a huge thing, and then suddenly Facebook came along and took over.
I agree, Mage, because like people, like the people that are used to watching streaming video, like the people that are used to the things YouTube offers,
which is like, you know, creator, creator-owned, creator-driven, like personal content and, you know, streaming video, like those people can't go back to TV.
Like they're going to want-
TV is a nightmare by comparison now.
They're going to want-
Yeah, there's going to be a demand to like get that back.
Well, the thing I was getting at is that the large swath, like the large majority of people on YouTube are kids and normies, and they will not come back.
They will not go into their little cliques.
But, hey, let me ask you this though.
An individual like community, like, you know, the animation meme community, or the people who like video game reviews and analysis, or, you know, anime analysis,
like those people will find ways to host their content and their fans will follow them, but the vast majority of the viewer base of everyone will not be able to come back.
Like if you have a million subscribers now, you're going to have maybe 100,000 people following you in the future if YouTube is just gone.
There's a lot of data counts as well, so you have to account for that.
Well, sure, sure.
But I mean, that just really feeds into his point of like less people will follow you and you'll get less, you know, numbers overall.
But what I'm wondering is, like, you say that the views definitely come from the normos out there, and that's absolutely true.
But, but, are those people really indicative of the patrons of these people?
I would say absolutely not.
And that's where I think that's kind of where this question is going.
Like individual specific fan funding of these projects.
Okay, well, here's a here's a sticky quagmire of an issue.
My question is, okay, those like the hardcore fans who are, you know, incentivized enough, they're invested enough that they will like actively support a creator.
Will they feel the same way when they don't see, you know, a huge community of people commenting and like, you know, hundreds of thousands of views on the videos that this artist person is putting out?
That is a great point.
Yeah, I think that I think that without that sense of like, you know, importance and community and relevance, like, I think, I think it's going to be bad.
Like, I think there will be people that would have maybe supported if they'd gotten that same impression, but like without that, they might not be as moved.
We've been talking a lot lately and shitting on like comments in several episodes after this, you know, these last couple of months.
I you've been saying this and I totally agree that the community aspect of YouTube is absolutely one of the reasons why it was so popular and so many people like to engage with it and watch it.
In addition, in addition to like just the fact that people like to be part of something that's gone viral and they find it interesting just in its own way.
I think also part of that is that YouTube was one site and you could go from all this sorts of different content to others by clicking on, you know, recommended videos and links.
And it felt like, you know, it was a congregation, everyone would come to this site and they would be able to just switch between different creators.
If creators all move to their own websites, you'll never be able to find other people.
So it will feel like, you know, you don't know where to go.
People will try, will like go to like largely, will go to a place that is like an aggregate for interesting content, whether that's a site that exists right now.
But like that's what Reddit is.
Like you just go to Reddit and like they'll collect the links of like whatever you want to see and you could just go through something like that instead probably.
The thing I'm thinking about is like if YouTube is gone, videos will be hard because like YouTube is like an unbelievably expensive thing to run.
And who could like match that? I don't think anybody could.
And where would all these video creators make their videos? Where would they upload them?
In the absence of like some YouTube successor coming along and like picking up the slack, I guess it would mean a return to the days of like people just host their own content on their own websites.
And that's what like did you and Tom have been talking about a bunch lately? And you do this yourself, Ben. You've got your own website for your public stuff.
I do. Yeah, I mean my content is not stuff that could really be hosted anywhere else.
Like there's no like, well, I mean there are platforms, but they're not. They're not robust like YouTube is. Yeah.
So if that happened, I don't know. I have mixed feelings because I feel like that experience of like just a creator, you know, curating their own content and putting their own website together and placing their work in the context that they deem appropriate for it to be experienced in.
It's good. And I like that. But like, you know, the YouTube algorithm is really powerful. And like that's how a lot of people succeed and get noticed in the first place. And it's going to be really, I don't know.
A lot of people are going to just lose their jobs and not be able to recover and have to do something else.
I want to say something.
I have one more thing to say that the like as much as I hate the I hate like the way that the algorithm can be gamed to like to like, you know, guarantee success.
But without it, they're just like, you know, there is so much less opportunity for success.
Period. Looking at you, pedantic romantic.
I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding.
Earlier, but my engineer was dying and so I couldn't hear you guys talking up until it was kind of like over. But like when it was saying, like, you can, you know, find different creators on YouTube and stuff like that.
I kind of like the rabbit hole. You can jump down by like clicking on the.
Absolutely. Yeah.
That part of YouTube, you know,
It's like, it's like clicking links on Wikipedia. Yeah.
You don't know where you're going to end up and you find interesting stuff.
I really think this will be become an outsource thing to a site like Reddit where, but like you will have to choose what kind of content you're interested in.
And like, let's just say there was like a, maybe there could be like a YouTube revival subreddit or something that's just like, ah, we assemble all the most popular links.
So, hey, want to see the new fucking like Colbert show on whatever it is?
Yay. My favorite. No, fuck that.
I mean, the thing is really just about the fact that you need to be extremely, you will need to be extremely successful in order to maintain, you know, the amount of bandwidth at, you know, the site you would have to run to keep your videos on would have to be like, or you'd have to go to another video thing.
No, none of us, none of us are at a level to survive from this shit. It may be Digi, but maybe not even him.
Yeah. I mean, in a way, in a way, like I like YouTube. I like the fact that there's so much interesting stuff there.
But there is a lot of crap and I feel like if YouTube dies, a lot of the people who make crap will die and a lot of the absolute best people will survive like red letter media and stuff like that.
Yeah, they'll be fine.
It will be kind of good in a way, but for most people it would be terrible.
The barrier to entry will become higher, like people will have to work harder to find content and they'll be pickier about what they want to watch, which is kind of good.
And the savage part of me wants to see that happen.
That's very convenient for guys who are already like a John Tron, a big guy. I think they'll be okay in general, but I don't know.
And for guys like me, for example, I've already learned everything I need to know to become a successful YouTuber for the most part.
I understand the video editing, all that stuff, but when the barrier to entry goes up so much, like remember Ben, we even made our first video,
like the bar was so, you got to make the video and then you just put it up and you're ready to go. It's done.
And so like the opportunities to join are there and like it has a very low skill floor.
What do you actually need to do to get your foot in the door, but as an extremely high skill ceiling, having both of those things.
Yeah, I mean, I'm using the word skill, but really I just mean like success rate that you're going to climb to eventually.
And I really like that. And it seems like what we could be getting to at this point is a raising of the skill floor as in you just, you can't even get in without being more leveled up in all these skills
and possibly also lower the skill ceiling and that you can only, you know, succeed so much because like there isn't a gigantic aggregated platform that is YouTube.
And I think those both, those are both unfortunate things.
I really like in theory how YouTube is a meritocracy and how it just you succeed or fail on your own merits.
And I know that it's not really like that, you know, like, like that's that's an idealistic picture of it.
But I like that idea.
It's sort of like that, like trends come and go like a few months ago, there was that whole trend of like the hot knife cutting through things and everybody was doing it.
And that one guy got so many subscribers, so many views, completely dead, like no one cares.
Yeah, like that guy isn't building a career off that one meme, you know, it's gone.
He's lost what like foothold he had because he didn't make anything actually interesting.
Realistically, he probably made several thousand dollars and like that's it.
And that's, you know, everything. And that's fine, you know, that's not a bad amount of money to make for making a popular meme.
Like the good stuff by the good people does stick around and get rewatched.
You know what I was thinking recently? I was thinking about how like changing things in this way.
Like, okay, so for example, if YouTube dies, then everyone has to individually host their own content.
And like maybe, okay, so like this is something I was going to talk about.
It's the fact that economically speaking, YouTube has never ever made money, which is terrible, which is a disgrace.
And it's because they were planning on turning this around and they're held afloat by their, you know, parent company, Google and whatnot.
For the hope that one day they will be making money with like YouTube red or whatever.
But like economically speaking, just based on the incentive structures, if people have to like pay a certain amount of money for like the video file size that they're uploading
or the length of time that their video is, those sorts of things give an actual cost to uploading like massive amounts of content,
which makes sense because you're asking more of the person hosting that content.
It's a perfectly reasonable thing to do.
And because of that, it incentivizes making like the highest density quality content for amount of time or file size that you have uploaded,
which sort of like incentivizes things to go back to the way initial YouTube was,
where like guys like Egoraptor got famous for like big animations that they worked really hard on.
And I mean, you know that I certainly would be in favor of content going back to that sort of stuff as opposed to this kind of just like upload literally anything you want,
just keep trying forever at no cost to you and hopefully you'll eventually figure something out.
I kind of like that. I kind of like how that sounds.
Right? Isn't it great?
It makes sense.
It's especially because like a lot of long form, many, many, many episodes, let's play content is basically just like a friendship simulator.
So like if that content goes, people will actually have to try making real friends.
You're right, dude. You're absolutely right.
It's so terrifying. I don't even want to think about it.
If you just, that right there, I think is actually could potentially be a very positive thing.
Don't get me wrong, I love consuming tons of garbage content.
Like I watch tons of garbage ASMR every day that I just play forever.
But I really would prefer, more important to me than that, is increasing the quality of content overall.
And I'm sure there will still be plenty.
Nothing is more important than ASMR.
Indeed. But like by changing the, like YouTube is not making money right now, right?
And like it'd be good if they made money.
So if YouTube like asked the people uploading video to pay for what it actually costs them to host the videos to some degree,
perhaps they finally could get into the black and like, I'm willing to do it, you know?
Like I get that people at the very bottom, you know, again, this raises the quote unquote skill floor way higher
because you have to actually put in money to do this stuff anyway.
But like money is just a way to measure like effort and shit that you're willing to put into something in a way.
Like I don't know, I don't think that's a crazy idea.
The way you're saying it like suddenly asking creators to pay, like, I don't know whether that would actually make...
It's an idea.
I don't know whether that would make animation come back because animation takes a long time to do
and they need like confirmation that it's going to get big views.
What it does is de-incentivize thoughtless content or, you know, flip it.
That's the idea.
So it changes the landscape overall.
It wouldn't be that expensive, right?
No.
Like how much do you think they'd have to charge to host like an hour's worth of video?
Let's say maybe ten bucks maybe.
Whoa, that's more than I thought.
There's no way it's 200 bucks.
Like you've got a hard drive with so much space.
It's because they charge nothing right now that they're in such a hole.
It's more than just like how much it would cost to have it on a hard drive.
It's the cost of having it on a hard drive and then distributing it to people like different YouTube servers
across the world.
Right.
So whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
YouTube does not have distribution costs.
No, no, no, no.
It's just in their fucking...
They've got server farms and stuff to maintain.
It's not as simple as just having the file on a computer.
That's totally true.
You're totally right.
But like, yeah, that's the thing.
There could theoretically be a calculated cost that YouTube could come up.
In a sustainable way to actually support all this content.
I would be very curious what that figure would look like.
Yeah.
The problem, of course, that people object to.
I haven't tried myself, but I've heard, I remember hearing that hosting video files
of any size on your own website, on your own like video player, is extremely expensive
and nobody can really afford to do it ever.
Well, that is exactly why we should outsource that process to giant companies that can afford
to for some fee.
Like, what are we doing just expecting YouTube to give us stuff for free?
Like, obviously their game plan was that...
It is pretty incredible.
It is pretty incredible that they operate the service at a fucking loss.
And don't get me wrong, I understand why YouTube does it.
It's because by doing so, they have taken over the streaming market and they are a fucking
juggernaut.
I get all that.
But you do need to stay afloat economically when you're a business.
So, I'm just putting out solutions here that might be able to work to help this problem.
So, you know, I'm sure nobody wants to have to pay money for anything, me least of all.
But I recognize the economic reality here that like, what's better?
YouTube starting to charge people and changing the economy of YouTube and making it, you
know, like into an economically sustainable model or YouTube just dying or YouTube going
away.
And I don't know, seems like a good idea to try to shift things around instead of changing
them or instead of letting it die.
Yeah, I mean...
I feel like the backlash, if they actually changed it to something like that, it would
be like terrible.
Okay, but here's the thing about that backlash, it'll be from whiny entitled babies who I don't
care about.
Who don't care.
And they can make those...
They can complain.
They can say all those things.
And there is a case to be made that it disincentivizes like, uploading to YouTube, which it actually
does.
But that economically disincentivizing things is not evil and YouTube is a company that
is trying to survive and make money.
So like, everyone's...
I can hear the millennial screams already, the shrieks of woe about how upset they'll
be.
Yeah, you know, as much as I agree that it would not be wrong and I could see why they
do it and part of me is interested in that idea, I think that the backlash would be so
intense.
It would be such an upheaval that it could be the death of YouTube if they did.
That's possible too.
Kind of a bummer.
Yeah, I'm not...
I'm not...
I don't fully disagree or anything, but I feel like the animation...
The animation community would just die because a lot of them are like kids and teens and
stuff like that.
And so they wouldn't be able to cough up the money.
Now, Mage, I hear what you're saying, but here's the thing though.
If a company or if any community or business or whatever cannot sustain itself economically,
it should die.
It should die.
That's what comes down to.
I said I don't disagree with you, I'm just sad that like communities like these would
just die off because they're...
I'm just like...
People get so wrapped up in that they love how things are right now and this is not an
attack on you, Mage.
I just mean like people in general out there.
They just say like, oh, you know, I love that I get to upload videos to YouTube for free.
That's so great.
Therefore, it should always be this way and nothing must ever change and things must stay
exactly as they are.
I don't care how in the fucking red YouTube has to go, give me free video uploads forever.
Well, there's that, but like I don't think people like all of them are whining that they
just want it to stay the same.
A lot of them need it to stay the same because they have a career based around it now.
They have to pay rent now.
That's just entitlement.
It's entitlement based on the fact that it has worked for years now and suddenly if
they don't have a house, it's kind of...
They need to scream about it because like they're going to be homeless.
But that's what the market is.
YouTube is a business and it's not YouTube's job to maintain people's lives.
Okay.
Yes, go on.
If it's just about like YouTube getting money from it, what if instead of making people
pay, they just take the money from the ads because it seems to be working out for illegal
anime sites and stuff like that, you know?
They're just hosting.
Well, those are much smaller operations than YouTube.
And when you do things illegally, I don't know, like you can...
Yeah, never mind.
Never mind.
I mean, I was just like, who knows how big an operation like KissAnime actually is in
terms of how many people they have to employ, what kind of 401K they got going, what kind
of dental insurance they got for the employees of kissanime.com, my favorite website.
If YouTube is operating at a loss, I'm a little confused how they can justify like offering
ad revenue to people, like are those people making some of the money back?
Maybe that's why the ad apocalypse is happening, they're slowly taking back the months.
No, it's not that.
It's because YouTube specifically has catered its entire ecosystem around incentivizing
people to just upload as much fucking video as possible all the time.
What we're talking about is shifting the incentive structures here and that will cause problems.
Like for example, guys like Game Grumps make their living by uploading just massive amounts
of videos, like three every single day.
I guess here's my question, people who upload tons of video and are really popular, like
the Game Grumps, those people make ad revenue off of those videos.
I'm just wondering if the cost of hosting, does Game Grumps make money for YouTube or
does Game Grumps cost YouTube money to host?
I don't know for sure.
Because YouTube does take a percentage off of the ad revenue, don't they?
Yeah, but I think that the idea is like-
I wonder if the most successful channels are the ones that are not a drain on YouTube.
Like the successful ones help YouTube and the unsuccessful ones hurt YouTube.
Oh, I see your point.
Sure, sure.
I would guess that that's how it works.
I guess that the thing is like the more views, like they must have come up with a formula
so that an amount of video file space and then the amount of views it gets, like that's
how many ad bucks are generated because of the amount of people who see that, and then
they take, like, they must have thought about being able to pay for itself when they came
up with how much percentage the content creator gets.
And you know, okay, this whole discussion that we're having right now about like the
idea of expecting uploader people to contribute some amount of money to like make it sustainable
of their videos being hosted or whatever, like the thing about that, that in that idea
like hurts guys like me more than almost anyone.
Like that would be a direct attack against me economically.
But the thing is though, like I accept the reality that economics, you have to conform
yourself to the economic situation you find yourself in.
So rather than bitching and moaning about like, eh, why can't I get shit for free forever?
Like instead I will mold myself economically into whatever fucking contortionist rhombus
strip cube I need to be in in order to make this stuff work because I'm just dedicated
to making it happen.
And I understand that there is like, there is a privilege here because I have not like
founded a business upon the current model that YouTube exists in and changed that model
will definitely fuck up some people.
But also YouTube needs to go in the black and if YouTube just dies, the businesses will
be fucked up anyway.
So I'm just trying to fix these issues.
Here's an idea.
What if YouTube just very temporarily like very briefly started charging to host enough
to put it in the black because I'm sure you've heard the saying once you go in the black,
you never go back.
Business proposal to think about I feel like we've gotten far off the topic of the podcast,
which is what we would do if YouTube dies.
We're talking about YouTube possibly dying.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's say it's gone.
Would we want?
What would we do?
First of all, what would we I would try to do my like work would be pretty much unchanged
because I'm already kind of post YouTube like YouTube is already like a secondary platform
for me.
I mean, I would lose we would lose the PCP.
I would lose exposure like like my YouTube channel and the PCP are like where a bunch
of my exposure comes from and I would lose it so that I would I would be hurt in that
way.
But like I would do what I was doing and I would probably just put more focus on, you
know, like doing like running kick starters and stuff and and you know, just putting out
I don't know, just pushing pushing my stuff in other ways.
I don't think the PCP has to go because it's a podcast.
We already have it on Google Play and I do.
Oh, yeah.
But it's like I forgot we could we could survive without I mean, you're right and all and actually
that the PCP actually does already have a WordPress website that we could slightly remodel
and just like make it our hub for like all PCP content and stuff, which would not be
particularly difficult.
So like that's true.
Yeah.
Like we could shape ourselves to that.
But like the factor of the exposure that YouTube gives us, you know, like that's that
would be quite a loss, especially considering how I hope the PCP will continue to grow.
And, you know, that growth exists on YouTube where everyone is right now.
So, you know, that'd be that's certainly be challenging.
Like imagine if we were just in a in a pool competing with like literally every
podcast, like on a podcast subreddit or something.
And it's just like, yeah, listen to the PCP and they're like, why?
And we're like, we have no answer to that question.
Yeah, exactly.
As for what I would do, I think
I would be okay with saying goodbye to YouTube reviews and analysis and funny,
funny fucking videos forever.
I'd be okay with getting because like it's it's been good for me to do.
And I had fun doing it, but sometimes it is a slog.
And I have never really broken through the, you know, I'm still below the
subscribe account of my old pony channel.
It's if, you know, if it if it goes today, I'd be okay just quitting and doing
something else, maybe getting more into drawing or music.
It would be difficult, obviously.
But I also have
like actual job opportunities in like writing for for cartoons and TV.
So like I could go and do that and that be my job as a freelance.
And then I could still, you know, upload things to Bandcamp, maybe once in a
blue moon or draw some stupid comics, comics for my for, you know, for things.
Like I have very economically viable though, very skills that could work outside of YouTube.
So I feel like I'd be OK, but I wouldn't I wouldn't be too sad to say goodbye to Hippocrates.
I have.
I just had a thought like, OK, say YouTube announced today like guys were dying.
Yeah, you know, get get your shit out of here.
We're going to be dead in a week.
I would what I would like to do then is get all my YouTube content, like download
it and like host it on my website, like maybe make like a separate section for
like video and just have like a big archive of all the videos I've ever made
and just host them there.
And I just wonder how much that would cost, because that's a lot.
That's like, yeah, that's a good question.
That's like tens or hundreds of hours of the thing just from my channel.
Plus T-Bap, like, you know, like that's a lot.
I don't know.
I wonder how prohibitive I wonder how prohibitively expensive.
Well, I feel emotion or something to host your videos.
You know, I guess that's true.
Yeah, yeah, but I like with the idea that you can't host YouTube videos.
And like, I feel like, well, I know that the cost goes up depending on how many
people, you know, ask to see your video on your website.
So if you get a lot of traffic on your video, like that's a lot more than just
getting a lot of traffic on a, you know, a page with an image on it.
Yeah, yeah, I see.
Paying for people to watch your entire
Nuzlocke series and let's say a hundred people do that.
That's that's a big fucking.
How much so you pay for you pay for you pay for bandwidth rather than like storage?
So I think so.
OK, well, yeah, I don't really know much about the back end of this of the like
the hosting process.
It would make sense for both of those things to like be things that you have
to compensate someone for if they're hosting your video and like the amount of
traffic that like your content.
Oh, I'd be so sad.
I'd be so sad if all my content was just lost.
Or if it was just economically impossible to preserve it.
Right.
I think the first thing I would do,
but I mean, my videos, a lot of my videos are kind of like throw away, like they're
not that important, but there's a few pretty good ones.
And I still have all the files.
So I might kickstart a DVD Blu-ray collection, just like the idea because he's got
all of his Angry Video Game Note episodes on Blu-ray that you can get.
And it's like, yeah, like physical media, that might be the way to go.
That's because I know just watch it whenever you feel like that's just that's
just making me fantasize about the about like two Blu-ray box sets for Nuzlocke
Conquest and Nuzlocke Genocide.
Hey, that'd be pretty cool.
Oh, my God, that would be so cool.
Maybe I'll do that anyway.
Put that in your Kickstarter that you have right now.
Oh, my stretch goal.
I'm actually very curious what how much how hard that would be to do.
And if that doesn't work, yeah, like maybe as a separate.
I'll just buy one for myself.
Yeah, like all of your first
Nuzlocke series on two Blu-ray discs.
Oh, well, OK.
All right. Good.
Yes, please continue this.
But but so what about you, Mage?
What would you do if YouTube just went away?
I feel like I'm in the same boat as Hippocrates.
Like, I wouldn't be too sad about it going away.
I mean, I would be sad to lose the videos and stuff.
I probably save them if they give a proper poor warning.
But I still have my deviant art and
I am still sort of trying to work on that comic thing.
And I am actually like, do you guys know about adaptables?
Like adaptable? No, I know about it.
Oh, seas. I don't understand them.
They confuse me a lot.
But I know what is this.
Explain. OK, so very quickly.
OK, I'm glad it's not just me.
Yeah, you create like these signs of these original characters of yours.
It could be like it could be like oh.
Pokemon, because it could be just
animal people, whatever it could be.
People, angels or you can create action for example.
Yes, yes.
You create like different designs for them.
You could use the same base usually, but the design has to be different.
So they all look, you know, distinct from one another, despite being in the same pose.
And you sell them.
They're kind of like like imagine like toys, I guess, but just virtual.
And they're drawings, it's kind of like selling.
So it's it's just artwork or is there some sort of Neopets website?
Here's here's here's what I don't understand is what do people do with them
once they buy them?
They create characters out of them and usually do they have them.
All right, so why do they need to the character, right?
But why do they need to buy them to do that?
That's where I guess that's where I get confused.
Some people can't draw then.
I I understand.
But if I was just googling and I found one, why can't I just use that?
But like you buy you buy you buy you buy someone else legal issues.
You buy an adoptable.
There's no there's no legal issues about
fantasizing that you are a character.
There are no legal issues.
The art and the character design.
OK, but do you need but do you need to own the art?
Like, do you like put it on things?
Well, well, hang on.
If you like commission a new character to be drawn as you're adoptable, perhaps that
like it doesn't exist until you pay for it.
That I could understand like that makes sense to me.
The way I see it is that people are they don't know how to design characters.
Maybe they can't draw, maybe they can.
And maybe maybe somebody designs a character
and like, oh, oh, I want that to be in my furry RP.
Yes. And then and then they say,
can I buy the rights to use your character as my own?
And they say yes.
And that's how it starts.
Yeah, I guess.
I guess that makes sense.
Like it kind of really feeds into people's need to collect pretty shiny
sparkly things because a lot of the signs are really cute instead of like,
I just want to own it.
I guess here's OK.
Here's I'm just going to be a big asshole right now.
Well, like I don't see the need to purchase the artwork unless you're then
putting it into like a commercial product that you're then selling like it's not
like it's not not for people like you then.
But I don't understand people who aren't like me.
I can't say that.
Well, what I'm understanding here is the honor system, like it's there's no legal,
like you can't say, oh, I'm going to sue you because you you drew fan art of this
adoptable, you're not allowed, you didn't pay me yet.
Like there's no it's just like people decided that this is the system they're
going to use and they are I guess that system.
You kind of treat them like kind of like in digital toys, toys, let's call them.
It's just like you see a plushie.
Oh, that's a cute plushie.
I just want it.
There's no reason for me to own it.
But, you know, it's cute.
I want it. So I had to make sense.
All right. So what I'm hearing here is that the adoptable economy is booming right
now. And that's where I need to be going.
That's where all our all our ships need to be pointed in the same direction
straight towards the do I do I hear one million dollars for action.
Oh, it's a drop in the bucket for his medical fees.
But it's a start.
It's not like.
He's a big handful.
He's a fixer upper.
He needs a rich patron to keep him going.
Let me tell you, though, like some people do earn like several hundred dollars
per drawing off of these adoptables.
OK, so it can be very successful.
And I've made a few I'm not successful, not yet.
And I don't expect to be any time soon, but they're really fun.
I like I like making designs of like and I like creating species.
And it's it seems like a fun thing to do.
So I might try focus on that.
Like if you don't goes down and I might OK, don't get me wrong.
I fully understand the appeal from the creator's perspective.
Like you draw a nice thing and someone pays you for it.
Like that that that I get.
Ben, we will never penetrate these childlike minds of these people buying these things.
They simply belong in a different universe than than we we men.
We true men in the real world.
You told plus she's OK.
So that's that's interesting.
I like that I like that you're thinking economically.
But what I'm wondering is that like these are cool ideas, but are these actually
long term economically viable things to do?
Because that is all I ever think about.
And how to how to achieve that?
I mean, I don't know like the one of the more popular
or most popular, at least the one I hear about the most, like they've been doing
that for years and like each drawing gets just more expensive each time.
So OK, I guess as long as the internet stays up, it is I mean that the thing is
sure people have survived before YouTube, before even Patreon, before any sort.
Like people used to just have PayPal links and and they would do a commission work
on your website or whatever.
They would they would do commission work.
And you know, people like artists will definitely be able to survive.
I mean, at least the good ones.
Like if you're good at art, you'll you'll you'll get you'll get an audience
and you get you get people buying your stuff.
OK, here's here's where I'm at with this whole discussion.
I have now tasted the fruit of freedom that that YouTube has provided me.
And I have found it succulent.
And so I want to continue doing it to making a living like getting my opinion
out there and sharing who I am.
And and now that I know what it's like on the outside, I cannot go back in.
I when I think of a like a lifetime spent continuing like as my at my programmer job,
it would not be horrible.
But it'd be like that episode of Star Trek,
the next generation where Picard like goes back and changes something in his
past a little bit and he ends up as like a shitty, worthless, not captain.
He's like a science engineer.
It's terrible. Oh, he's just he's just like a sad.
He's just living like a depressing, sad life where he didn't achieve his
potential. And I when I think about that, I would rather die.
So I will do whatever is necessary to not only I do not want to just survive
as a artist, I want to live, I want to thrive as an artist.
I hear you.
I want to hear what Mage has to say about please, please.
You say you say YouTube is freedom.
But I say YouTube is a cage like any other, just maybe more spacious.
Oh, well, I mean, that's juicy in what terms.
It all depends on how you do it, you know, like perhaps you make an argument
based on the way that like you have it.
You have to do like Mia Mavva or we Agua.
And that's like not exactly what you want to be doing.
But you have to do it.
No, Mage, tell us more about the cage.
So long as you're reliant on the Mage cage.
So long as you're reliant on YouTube as your source of income, you are, you know,
in the cage of YouTube, you have to keep producing.
I'm about to fucking dismantle you on an atomic level.
You're you're you're you're beholden to to what the people want to see.
You have to keep delivering what the people want to see.
You need to entirely true, entirely true.
But, Mage, you have no fucking idea what it's like to be a corporate tool.
You have no idea what it's like to go into work every day and be afraid of the
people in charge of you because you're afraid you're not living up to their
expectations and to be at their mercy to do whatever the fuck they want to do with you.
Whereas when I am working on YouTube, I do both of these things.
I do both of these things.
And YouTube gives me such a sense of freedom and personal empowerment because I
am running my own ship.
It is the entrepreneurial spirit that I crave more than anything else.
It gives me purpose and rewards me in life and gives me control over succeeding by
how hard I work at things that I actually want to be doing.
And to compare those two, to say that they are the same fucking thing just proves
that you have no fucking idea what you're talking about.
I'm not saying it's the same thing.
Also, side note, I do know what you're talking about.
I have worked in the workforce before, but yeah, so noted.
I'm not saying it's the same thing.
I'm just saying it's still a cage in a way.
It might be more spacious and more grants more freedom, but in a way, it's still a cage.
Major, I will happily grant you that life is a cage.
Exactly. Life is a cage and death is the key.
We are all trapped by the crew.
We're all trapped.
Look, man, we've really come a long way today.
You've covered some real ground here.
I never stated whether or not being in a cage is bad.
By the way, Major, I wasn't actually mad at you.
I was just speaking emphatically.
I know, I know, I'm aware.
I can sense the mood.
I'm just, I wasn't saying it was bad or good or like looking down on your knee.
I was just making a statement that in a way, it's still a cage.
Yeah, OK, I'm totally with you on that.
Well, here's what I think, like the freedom of YouTube.
Like, OK, you might be some schmuck and you're like, hey,
making videos where I cut through things with a really hot knife is really popular.
So I'm going to do that and then you do it and it's really popular.
OK, well, now my living is cutting things with a hot knife.
So I'm going to do that.
I'm going to do that from from nine to five every morning and I got to keep doing it.
And, you know, I'm sure that would suck and that would be a cage.
But like, but what if you construct your own cage to your own specifications?
Like, what if you go out there and you're like, here's what I'm making
and this is what I want to make and it just, you know, and people like it.
And like, so there you like you like you are beholden to continue producing the content.
But if it's the content that you want to be making, that the people also want to see,
then yeah, it's a cage.
But it's a cage of your own.
I have a cool metaphor for this.
It's like, and you can leave when you want.
The more spacious the cage you want, the more expensive it is to maintain.
Like, like, like if you've got a huge cage, you can do whatever you want,
but you're going to have to, you know, you need a lot of money to have
like the ultimate freedom, you know, I mean, they're less money.
You have the smaller the cage there.
There is major. You're right.
I think we're speaking on slightly different scales here, but you're right.
There is no true freedom in this world.
We there are things that you will never be able to avoid doing.
You always have to work to support yourself in some way or another.
Or I mean, if you don't, then you're if you're living like a like a socialist
style life where like everyone else is supporting you, then you just like you
don't have control and that's bad in many ways as well, as well as I don't
think it's economically sustainable long term for like other people to support
people like that in a mass scale, but that doesn't matter.
I totally agree.
But like Ben was saying, it's just I'm doing both of these things right now.
And not only do I feel like I prefer one over the other, it's it's the sense
of empowerment, which leads to a much greater rate of productivity doing one
that is that is such a tangibly better way to do things.
And I can see myself growing as I do it.
And I just like my whole life, my whole life, I've been hating myself
because I would never able to like commit to doing things.
And now I finally stumbled upon the one thing that I actually don't need
to like beat myself up to keep doing, I just find myself doing it.
And so to live my life in that way will will will definitely just be a more
pleasant experience.
I totally agree.
It is not total freedom.
None of us have total freedom in the world, but it's closer and that's that's
all. But if you love your but if you love your work, if you love your work,
it might be a cage, but it doesn't feel like one.
Humans need suffering.
Humans need to suffer in order to maintain their their it's like you have
to you have to have resistance in this world or you never grow.
You have to have a challenge in your life.
I am like I totally relate to you because, you know, I'm also in the YouTube
cage, but I kind of like you here, you know, I do.
Yeah, we find it generally pleasant so far so far.
OK, all right.
So we're on the same page.
Generally, I mean, it's like like when I when I sit down to draw a page,
it's like, oh, I got to do this.
Yeah, I wouldn't say like like the work like the work is still work.
But it's just that the the the gratification of finishing it and putting
it out there is worth it.
And so that's what I've chosen other job.
I'd rather be doing other.
Yeah, right.
Yeah, and like Ben's Ben's made a physical comic now.
He's done it.
He's like that will be there forever, both online and in it's it's real.
It's in real life.
And he did it.
He put in the effort.
Now he's got something to show for it and he's going to be able to at least
make some money off of doing it.
So yeah, it just it just it's such a better feeling.
Exactly how I always wanted my life to be.
And it's it's getting there.
Any way that we can sort of structure society in a way that things are
sustainable long term and people are the happiest and doing the things that they
want to be doing with their lives.
That certainly is the direction I prefer to steer into.
Yeah.
And things like YouTube are useful tools for getting there, I think.
So I I mean, YouTube, for all these reasons of like the growth potential
that it has, like I would be very sad to say YouTube crumble, but I would be
absolutely willing to work to put in my fair share of the effort to like help
support YouTube if it's by like paying the fees that I have to to host my content.
I will find a way to make it work.
I'll do whatever it takes.
I'm I'm in this for the long haul and and if YouTube doesn't eat crumble,
I will find some other way to do it.
I'll go to daily motion.
I'll I'll do whatever else.
Maybe I'll need to totally change the kind of content I make.
If so, I will do it.
But yeah, like we we Agua and me and Maffova were created because of how
YouTube works and the way that I wanted to steer into what works on YouTube.
And I would be happy to steer out and do something else, you know,
if it if it worked better.
In I like the series, though.
I hope I hope to be last.
Me too. Me too.
So have we have we all said what we're what we do if YouTube crumbled?
I think we did.
Have we have we all have we all set our our our take on the topic?
Yeah. Now is there is there any anything else to say on the matter?
I mean, I think none of us actually want YouTube to go away.
We're all obviously happy to have it here.
Yeah, like even if even if YouTube
just decides to get rid of ad revenue entirely so that it can support itself,
I would be OK with that because I like putting a funny video up for like
just a little joke and to have people go, oh, I get it.
Yes, same as most popular video is demonetized and I don't get shit for it.
So I don't like I don't like the fact that someone else is earning money
because of it from it.
But like, if no one was earning money from it, neither me nor anyone else.
Like, yeah, sure. OK, that's misery loves company.
Do you think Patreon would?
I mean, OK, I don't think that Patreon would have started without YouTube.
But now that it's here, I wonder I wonder if YouTube dying would end Patreon
or if Patreon would just keep on going in its own.
Keep on going because a lot of artists who just like, you know,
draw comics or whatever and don't even touch YouTube are being supported on Patreon.
So they are.
Do you do you think I I feel like a lot of what people support on Patreon
is YouTube content?
I'm sure that's a large part of it. Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, now it is a large part.
But I think the majority is like weird porn shit.
So they're not for long.
Not a Jack Conti has anything to say about it.
Jack sexually repressed Conti.
Yes, my my hero, my hero.
All right, yeah, I don't know.
I think it'll continue to exist for the next while.
Let's let's just give our predictions.
What do we think is actually going to happen to YouTube?
Because guys like Digi and I think to do maybe I've been saying that like
they see it dying in like the next several years based on this shit.
What do you guys think is actually going to happen?
I see ad revenue just thinning and thinning
and getting less and less.
You know, the adpocalypse won't just the adpocalypse won't really recover.
But I feel like it'll it'll it'll be around for maybe another five years.
I don't know beyond that.
But I feel like it's just about to die right now.
Like I feel like it's got some power left.
It's just I can't see beyond five years with my mind brain.
Ben, what do you think?
What do I think is going to happen to YouTube?
Yeah, what's your prediction for actual the fate?
Oh, man, I mean, do you think it'll crumble in the end?
It's hard for me to imagine it ever going away.
But if it's operating, it'll like I don't see how it can just
continue to operate at a loss forever.
Well, I mean, if Google's other businesses just make enough money,
theoretically, YouTube could operate at a loss forever.
Yeah, but why would they?
That's a good I don't know.
I don't know.
I mean, maybe YouTube really does like work in indirect ways
to support the other businesses.
It must.
Right.
It's like it must serve some purpose.
Yeah.
YouTube Red is like if YouTube Red actually really, you know,
takes hold and everybody gets it because the stuff that you can get
with YouTube Red is so good that you can't live without it.
Then YouTube will be saved.
But I don't know whether that will actually work.
Because even though, like, you know, Vsauce has his YouTube Red series,
I kind of want to see all of those, but I also don't care enough.
Well, here's OK.
I guess here's my prediction.
I don't see YouTube ever just going away.
It'll probably continue to do what it's always done and like change
its algorithm all the time and make everyone mad and keep changing
how it works behind everyone's back with no with no announcement given.
I think that probably a successor will come along at some point
that will do right all the things that everyone hates about YouTube.
And like I because because nobody like everyone complains about YouTube
all the time. Some eventually like I think eventually
like with more and more YouTube alternate like with like I don't know
Netflix and and I feel I think you do will probably lose traction
until it becomes less enough less of a monolith that something else can can come
in and feel like the place that it once held and maybe and maybe it'll be better.
I feel like the only competitor would be Facebook.
If Facebook video actually started.
Yeah, they're working on like pushing that real real hard down our throats.
Please not.
Then everybody would go over there because.
Yeah, but that's like the huge monolithic website
that might have the money to support such an such an amount of stuff.
But is this what we want?
Just juggernaut companies like the literally the biggest in the world
to just trade hosting of like video stuff.
What else could it work?
I don't I mean, everyone pays their own way.
They pay the I made a vlog the other day.
The other the other week about like what could solve it.
And it would be science.
It would be making making really, really cheap.
Like making the ability to host and and, you know, display a video
incredibly cheap to the point where it doesn't even matter anymore,
which it does get every year, which we are, which we are marching towards steadily.
Sure, surely, but surely.
Yeah, and I was going to say like the way I see is possibly to fix this
is just YouTube, just I mean YouTube or anyone else.
There's a service that just simply does not host video.
It is simply an act.
It works exactly like YouTube, but you got to supply the connection
to your videos to whatever way it's just the comments section.
But I mean, all the algorithm stuff, all that stuff still works.
But like you you are the one who pays the weight of like supporting your content
and whatever manage in a whatever way that has to be done.
Like if people could do that, I agree.
Then that definitely way raises the like the the skill floor.
But nonetheless, it could be it's just one one idea.
I mean, sort of with what Ben said, I I I expect to maybe one day
for for some something else to take over, not any time soon.
But like I feel like the story was like, you know, my space in Facebook
is going to repeat itself with you.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
I've got it. I've got the solution.
OK, now that that worthless pilot trash net neutrality is gone,
what we can do now is we can have YouTube can host like videos for free.
And the dragon that is now that that beast is out of our sights,
that Leviathan is dead on the ocean floor.
We can now what we can do is YouTube can itself host content for free,
but that would be on the slow shitty lanes that cost a little bit of money.
Whereas everyone like everyone who wants to like do their own shit
can pay YouTube for like the faster upload speeds.
And so they can be an economic structure here where like the content
that people really want to see is on the fast lanes that they themselves contribute to.
Therefore, everyone can still have their free shitty content.
It'll just take longer to load and whatnot.
I'm just making me and hypocrite.
Thank you, Ajit Pai. Thank you.
Me and hypocrite are free from this, right?
For now. For now.
I honestly don't know. I don't even know.
I mean, I don't know anything about it, so I won't talk as if I do.
But I feel like that's that's an American problem
that won't affect us directly, but it will affect the fact
that we can't see American content creators anymore as much.
Oh, that's true.
Like doom and gloom ways, like, oh, all of America is like turned off.
And we still have like UK vloggers.
Oh, good.
Everyone knows that people only watch YouTube
so they can fantasize about living in America.
The greatest country in the world.
And then and then a PCP HQ will come to the UK at last.
You don't have to lift a fucking finger. Of course.
Of course. That's the master plan.
By the way, I am Ajit Pai.
You guys may have orchestrated this whole thing.
You're working behind the scenes like you see under Ajit Pai's robe.
There's a small diminutive, a small Hagrid on top of major shoulders
forming Ajit Pai, the flesh golem.
OK, now let's to close this discussion.
I'd like to read you one more definition from Urban Dictionary.
Oh, few. OK, here we go.
I didn't get my fix yet.
The word is actually used in the definition itself,
which is the cardinal sin.
But nonetheless, the word is at the end.
OK, here we go.
When good things about you are searched for and found
through the YouTube search engine, you are YouTube-alicious.
And here's the example.
Donald Trump is very YouTube-alicious.
Wow, that's very illustrative.
All right, I think that's it. Shall we go to questions?
I'm shell shocked by that one.
I know.
Oh, Ajit Pai, a.k.a. Mage and Gib, collectively.
You guys, you guys.
That's our Jamfusion.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
And your weapon is the giant Reese's Cup mug
that he wields with such skill and grace.
Got to do the Harlem Shake.
We've got a fidget spinner.
That's our jammed weapon.
Oh, my God. That's our attack.
Disgusting.
What a disgusting display.
OK, here's a question, a pity question,
from our friends on Twitter, using hashtag AskPCP.
This one's from at Daniellius, I believe.
And it's relevant to what we've just been discussing.
If the apocalypse happened today, how would it happen?
Or what would you like it to happen?
OK, that's the letter.
I want to answer this question
because this has been a religion for a while now
and no one has picked up on it.
I want a meteor to strike Earth and annihilate it
in one fell swoop.
Oh, dude, I love Homestuck as well.
And that's completely unrelated to Homestuck, though.
I would, OK, I would much rather
the world be destroyed than die, personally.
I would much rather the world end with me.
You know, as Christopher Hitchens so elegantly put,
the cruellest thing about death is not that you have to leave the party.
It's that the party goes on without you.
Yeah, I want I indeed want that Earth fucking destroyed.
Well, guys, I don't think it's exactly Kickstarter to end the world.
I would like to indeed.
And I would like to point out that this is, in fact,
this is, in fact, the plot of Final Fantasy Nine
and Kuja's entire motivation as a character.
So shout out to our boy, our fellow our fellow popcorn nihilist, Kuja.
Now, this is terrible.
This is terrible.
Oh, wait, wait, I just want to say,
if I want I want the apocalypse to be a little green aliens come
and just shoot us, that will be cute.
That would be cute.
OK, while you're while you're going through our questions,
I'll I'll ask a question from the patron lounge.
By sure. Sure.
Are you in favor or against the term law?
As in League of Legends or very against League of Legends.
I I. OK, I think that sometimes I really show my age
because I will just type lull into messages.
And I think that that's not cool anymore, but I've been doing it for.
No, I think lull is fine.
Saying kek is something I could I would never get into.
The cool kids are all saying kek now.
We're all doing. Sometimes I say kek.
I don't know which makes me feel dirtier.
I would prefer to stay.
It's like lull is vanilla ice cream.
You know, kek is like the new like crazy like popping candy thing
that everyone's got kek is like that guy who orders
like forbidden chocolate ice cream and then opens up several pixie sticks
and sprinkles them on top and crushes up M&M's and, you know, kek is kek is
kek is the young Ben St in the mall food court going up to the Dairy Queen
and saying, hey, make me a blizzard, but put these nerds into it instead.
Exactly.
Exactly. Personally, personally, I do test lull
and I only use it ironically when I want to be obnoxious.
I know you don't have notice.
I wish I had your courage.
I wish I had the courage to abandon lull.
Did you have you guys notice that I did you like always types lull in all caps?
Have you noticed this? I've noticed this.
I'm not just down with Digi.
Yeah, it looks like it's down to Digi.
It looks like he's really excitedly laughing,
but I don't think he's actually that excited about it.
I think it's a normal level.
It's disingenuous. It's very confusing.
Yeah, what the fuck, dude?
Get your shit together.
I never used. No, I'm defending lull.
Lull is is my thick crust pizza in this in this debate.
You'll never change my mind.
Lull is the funniest.
Oh, it makes me lull lull lull every time I do test lull.
I never used it, but recently I started using it only to be obnoxious
because I find it obnoxious.
There's nothing more obnoxious than someone saying lull at the end of your
you can't you can't spell you can't spell
with cake. That's stupid.
I guess I guess you got a point.
You got us there.
It's not a song.
Yeah, you win this round.
All right.
Hey, I've got another question that I that I like from at Luke Chef 99.
It's everyone. I know that.
Oh, you do. What is his what's his reputation on the streets?
Well, I've talked to him and he I think he just I think he just pledged to my
Kickstarter.
Well, isn't that interesting?
Because his question is, is everyone excited for Ben to finally get his
oculus rift long last?
But no, no, I will I'll be I'll be I'll you got me.
You got me. We're going.
We're going the final stretch goal will be Vapors VR, just like Munchie says.
Yeah, yeah.
Then only only on please add buying an oculus ripped to your incentives.
Maybe I will.
Maybe if I just run it, maybe if it just takes off beyond my wildest
yeah, put it like nine thousand one nine thousand one dollars and we'll buy
an oculus rift, I did I did quite like my suggestion of a stretch goal for
nine thousand one dollars, which was stretch your neck out under the guillotine
blade. That was my I think that's a good one.
All right, well, nine thousand two dollars will be that's good.
That's good.
So I can retreat to VR after death.
That's that's my plan.
My severed head will fall right into those goggles.
And here's just like the same question.
But at Monkey Away asks, also, did you expect Ben's Kickstarter to do so well?
And what did you pledge?
Did you guys pledge to Ben's Kickstarter?
I did. I was the first guy to pledge 25 bucks.
Really? The first one for the book and the pin.
You know, that pin looks great.
It's so good. I know.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Fuck yeah.
There's there's so nice.
They're shiny.
You know, what's great about PCP Kickstarter's, I just noticed, is that
they all have really such humble asks and then people just always like
shatter them immediately, which is great.
Which Ben clearly showed like exactly what needed to be like what the money
was going toward and in a totally, you know, transparent way.
And like it was just easily broken and it's just it just keeps going.
People. Yeah, I cannot like, you know, I was I was going to plug it at the end,
but I guess I'll just say it now.
Like I can't I can't fucking believe it hit the goal in 10
hours and it's well on its way to its first stretch goal.
I'm so fucking stoked about it and thank you, everyone that donated.
And I'm just I'm just going to give myself a little Christmas,
an early Christmas present.
I'll link in the description because it's going on.
It's going on now, right?
OK, it's it's cool if I link my Kickstarter in the description of this video.
Right. I got no problem with that.
I got no problem with that.
And here is just a related question.
Monkey away.
Also, Ash, what do you want for Christmas?
It is Christmas Eve.
This is coming out, everybody.
Like last week, did we?
Yeah, I think last podcast, like I said, I said I was torn between
like getting like a hoping for a switch or a PS4.
Oh, that's right. We did.
OK, well, anyone who wasn't on last time, was it with Ben?
Were you not on?
I know I was on last week.
OK, well, this is a terrible mistake.
I fucked up massively.
I want for Halloween.
I want to get fucked on Halloween.
I want paydays. I want I want paydays to the best.
They're the best part.
Yeah, paydays.
I want I want a real payday.
You know what I mean?
I'm going to be hitting up my local bank, if you know what I'm saying.
It's going to be a big payday for me with a fucking balaclava on
and and and and and it's going to be an explosive with the orange part at the end.
So it's going to be some men just want to watch the world burn.
I'm going to reenact the dark night of that.
I will reenact the dark night in this bank.
Yes, I am.
If you could do something, I would do it for free.
For Halloween, I want clowns to disappear.
Just like for the last Halloween.
This is Halloween.
Clowns will just multiply.
May the greatest gift for mage is a world without laughter.
Who laughs at clowns?
Did you did you guys see me every day by any chance?
Because I actually thought it was pretty pretty dope.
I like what?
The new it, the it remake.
No, I didn't see it.
I'd recommend it. I'd recommend it.
I liked it.
He looks like a giant baby head.
I hate it.
He I mean, he looks goofy and retarded.
He absolutely does.
But it is still pretty.
Is is the sequel to it?
It's within a post.
Monty Python's Flying Circus.
Yes, that's what it is.
I have it's like alien and aliens.
It's it and it's a question I want to answer.
It's by a G shoot or a shoot.
Not sure how to pronounce that in the patron lounge.
And they're like, what's the most efficient emoji?
And I just like for people who know about those blobs,
like there's like this really cute blob that has like the o-woe face
and it has like tiny arms going up, like grab your little arms.
And it's like the best emoji and I'm going to send it to Bennett.
Please, please edit this into the podcast.
I know I'm asking the impossible.
You are. No, no, no, I'm going to.
No, I'll do it. I'll do it.
I honor I honor the requests of my PCP comment.
It is the best emoji.
If you do not see this emoji on screen,
please remove your pledge from Ben's Kickstarter
and delete your pledge to his patron and all other, you know,
give them to me as compensation for emotional trauma
that private message private message me.
So I don't forget.
Yes, it's the best emoji.
It's the most efficient.
It's the best. It's the greatest.
I cannot live without it.
OK, I've got I've got I've got one last question here
that I that I absolutely love from our from our pity section on Twitter.
At Eskimo Bob, two asks, what is the best kind of milk?
Two percent, whole, etc.
I like chocolate, strawberry and whatnot.
Unpopular opinion.
I actually like skim milk.
I skim skim.
I find skim.
I find skim milk to be refreshing and it's still nutritious.
And I don't mind that it's not like thick.
I like that I can just drink it kind of like water.
I think a lot of people think it's disgusting, but I don't think so.
I think I think semi skimmed.
I semi skimmed one percent or something.
Or is that even more skim?
I don't know. I just buy in the UK.
There's there's whole milk skimmed milk and semi skimmed.
Yeah. OK. No.
I don't know what fucking you fucking savages.
There's there's whole skim one percent and two percent.
I don't know.
The first time I heard like one percent milk,
it becomes like wait, no, but then there's one percent.
And then 90, 99 percent water.
Wait, then there's the dark souls of milk cream top milk.
You guys know what the fuck is that cream top milk is unskimmed milk
that just has the cream that comes to the top of the bottle.
And I knew I knew I knew someone once who would just put her finger in
and scoop out the cream and just eat and just like eat the cream off the top.
Yeah, it was just like a treat for I hated it.
That goes against everything I've ever.
I don't know why.
That's all known laws of physics.
I don't know why I don't know why you would buy cream top milk.
It just seems like a waste unless you're a weirdo and you just want to love.
I just want to eat a dollop of unsweetened cream off the top.
Unbelievable milk, really hard.
Like it's it does form a little bit like that.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, the skim on top.
Yeah, it forms a bit of a skim.
And I hate that skim I detested.
I hate that I hate it on the top.
Yeah, it's so gross.
I don't know why, but it is.
I mean, I associate stuff like that with like the milk has gone off
and now you can see lumps.
Is anyone here going to chime in for strawberry milk or chocolate milk at all?
Banana milk, banana, banana milk.
I know we're increasing the complexity of this question
exponentially by introducing these these other factors.
I was I was shocked and appalled because when I was in Europe,
I realized that there are like other milks because in America in America,
it's like strawberry, chocolate and sometimes coffee.
Those are the flavors.
But in in Europe, I saw like like raspberry milk was a thing.
OK, OK. In a lot of ways.
And I remember, oh, in cookie clicker, in cookie clicker,
you can upgrade your milk and the milk turns pink.
And I assumed that it was strawberry, but I read like some some dev log or something.
And it's actually raspberry milk.
And I guess it's because or teal is French.
And I guess in France, raspberry milk is more common.
What the fuck?
Incidentally, when you evolve your your milk high enough in cookie clicker,
it becomes orange juice.
So I'm just going to say orange juice is the best milk.
Yeah, without a doubt, without a doubt.
Do you guys like the way it looked?
Cream top milk, the Dark Souls of milk.
I'm really proud of that.
And I just want to call back to that and make sure that gets.
Yes, quite quite apt.
Quite apt indeed.
And the Dark Souls, too, of milk is cheese.
Impenetrable and dense and a nightmare to deal with.
Yeah, well, I'll agree.
Question. Yes, mage. Yeah.
Having a question.
OK, but on patronage by Squidmiku,
what's a holiday tradition you have?
I thought it would be relevant considering this is on Christmas.
OK, Christmas.
I go around like a Viking and destroy everyone I see.
Well, me and me and Nate have a bunch of family traditions.
Our dad always leads us in a round of bizarre,
in a nonsensical playlist of cobbled together
show tunes and college fight songs that have no relation to the holiday.
It's specifically related to the Holy Cross University of Boston, Massachusetts.
Yeah. Yeah.
There's some some some Yankee Doodle, Dandy,
and like some other shit that I've never heard anywhere before or since.
I don't know what these songs are.
Wait, is Holy Cross actually in Boston?
I have to Google this now. I think it is, maybe.
It's around there. It's around there.
For Boston, for Boston.
The Irish one the day.
Dubzinski from Dublin.
Letch up from Galloway.
All right, that's all it does.
Lockhease of Bilski to all the try and get into Boston.
For Boston, the Irish one, the day.
What a bunch of bologna.
You know who won the day.
Boom, boom.
I don't get it. I've never understood.
It's always been like a bizarre, a bizarre, like mystery to me.
I mean, we also sing still lot,
which is just like a Polish celebration song.
That would make sense.
But then there's like show tunes and college fight songs
and just some other shit.
He just grew up, his family sung them.
I guess.
Oh, it did be fine.
Simply divine when a goon sits in the presidential chair.
I just can't wait.
Won't it be great when a goon sits in the presidential chair?
What the fuck does that song mean?
Someone fucking explain that one to me.
I've never understood why I sing it every birthday.
What's a college fight song, though?
Well, it's just like a song.
We'll give a holla in a choo-chee or a rah for Holy Cross.
They're just singing like, yeah, go Holy Cross football team.
Yeah, that's it.
Just like, it's weird.
OK, so my traditions, like other than going to visit my parents
for holidays because that's that thing.
We have this tradition in our family.
I think it's like either pagan or religious or whatever,
but it's a Christmas thing.
You have to have like 12 different meals on the table,
but it also includes bread.
So it's not like, you know, big meals.
But it can't contain meat, but it can contain fish.
So and also mushrooms.
I like mushrooms, though.
I believe this ritual is called vegetarian.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's like, there's a word, but I don't remember it in English,
that I think it has something to do with religion,
though I think we do break the religion of no meat
by adding poultry sometimes.
Is it like kosher or halal or something?
No, no.
I believe it's known as the holocaust.
No, no, no, it's no.
The original holocaust was of the dining room table.
Everyone knows this.
No, I think it's something to do with religion.
But it's like a mix of Christianity and paganism,
I think.
I mean, hey, Christianity is like, or rather Christmas
is like a pagan holiday anyway, that we like mixed
with Christianity in weird ways over the years.
Exactly, exactly.
That tradition.
It's a Lithuanian thing.
I haven't heard many other countries do that.
That's cool.
Got a lot of food.
I like that.
Well, like you said, even a plate of bread,
just sliced bread, also counts.
So we always try to have like 12.
And drinks also count as well.
OK.
So it's not as much as you think, but yeah.
Incidentally, I just looked up where
the College of the Holy Cross is,
and it's in Worcester, Massachusetts,
which is where Tom lives.
So it's probably.
Maybe he knows the song.
Maybe he could join us.
Yeah, shout out to Tom.
He should have joined us, but did.
He failed.
He's deleted for life.
My tradition, there's not really like anything
extremely special.
It's just like Christmas, family, whatever.
But we never have like a family around the dinner table
except like the immediate family, like mom, dad, and siblings.
And that's nice.
I want to ask you, because I don't know whether this
is a thing in America, because I feel like somebody's
called me out for it being weird, is a Christmas crackers.
Are those the popper things, like the poppers?
The things that you like pull.
I know those from Mr. Bean.
I know them from Mr. Bean specifically.
All right, so it is in English, or at least the European thing.
Yeah.
I mean, I've seen them in America.
I think I've done them in America, but they're not like.
I've seen them in anime.
Yeah, me too.
Me too.
Anime.
I love them.
Anime, famously taken place in England.
That's the only place I actually ever saw them.
Super wizard crackers.
Yes.
Yeah.
That's the one.
See, I was really confused reading Harry Potter for the first time.
I'm like, why are they eating all these crackers?
You're going to get so many empty calories.
Why do they hate white people so much?
Oh, Hermione was always black.
All right, everybody.
Well, shall we?
Let's wrap it up.
I think we had some good questions there.
We had a good discussion here.
Oh, it was good.
So let's go through the normal rigmarole at the end here.
Thanks for listening, everybody.
And if you like what the fuck you hear,
why not sign up at patreon.com slash theprocrastinators
for all our goddamn bonus episodes as well,
as well as just to support the show.
So Pledge $5, and he got all nine of the bonus episodes,
including the most recent one.
OK, the new one's not out yet.
Yeah, the most recent one is Inuyasha versus Charlie
Brown. It's insane. It's madman.
We've got, if you pledge as little as $1,
you'll have access to the Discord Group,
the patron, the official patron PCP Discord Group.
Everyone hangs out there.
And we ask, that's where we got a bunch of our questions
from today, so you're more likely to get your question red,
if you remember there.
And it's a great community that we all hang out in.
What else we got?
We got redbubble.com slash people slash theprocrastinators.
PCP shirts, it's Christmas time, people.
They're going to want those PCP merch.
So get in there and get mugs, get cups, get glasses,
get containers, all containers of all types.
Oh, and the stickers, of course.
To hold your cream top milk in.
And when you put your stickers on,
take a picture of them and tweet them at me,
because I want to know what you put your stickers on,
and what you use them for.
Yeah, we retweet people.
We retweet when people have PCB merch.
So if you want yourself retweeted,
tweet yourself, tweet your picture right over it.
If you want to be retweeted, buy our merch.
Pretty much, at TPGrasinators, guys.
That's the price of admission.
Basically.
If you want to play in the big leagues.
And of course, our podcast is available on iTunes and the
Google Play podcast app thing, which I think is slightly
separate, I haven't actually looked at it.
But I know we're on iTunes, so you can check us out there.
And I think that covers everything.
Well, one last time, I just want to say that my Kickstarter
for printing physical comics of the Vapors chapter one is
going on now.
We got stretch goals to go.
We got stretch goals for extra content and stuff.
They'll be added if we reach them.
We're fucking, yeah, grab yourself a copy.
Grab yourself a poobah pin.
The pins are fucking sick.
The URL is kickstarter.com slash project slash 56159055
slash the-vapors-chapter-one.
That's very unwieldy, and I'm quite disappointed in it.
Do you think that any kickstarters about porn
have, like, vagina stretch goals?
If you know what I'm, you see what I'm, you see what I'm
going with that?
I'm glad I put that image in your mind, everyone.
I don't understand.
Think about that.
Think about that while you sleep at night.
OK, well, anyway, thanks for listening, everybody.
And we'll see you next week.
Bye.
Yeah.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
But I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
My dick, I'm jerking.
Myself, I'm sucking.
I am an asshole.
I am a stupid.
I've got a deadline.
Don't want to do it.