I won't bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Uh, are you recording?
I am. I'm just trying to remember what I just had for lunch so I can put it in my calorie thing.
Oh.
It was a steak and kidney pie, which was lovely.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. This is great content. Don't waste this.
Don't waste this.
Wait. Okay. Let's sync.
Eleazar, keep this all in.
No.
Three, two, one, sync.
Sync.
Okay. Now, tell us about the steak and kidney pie, which I've never eaten one of those.
I've never had one of those.
You've never eaten a steak and kidney pie.
It's just beef chunks, kidney chunks in a beef gravy as a pie.
Kidney chunks sound so disgusting.
Well, it's a kidney. It's sort of a weird meat.
Oh, it sounds really good actually.
It's a weird meat that's not normal.
Yeah.
It's like eating beef heart, cow heart, or whatever. It's like, ah, that's odd.
But kidney's all right. It's sort of like mushrooms, but if they were more beefy.
Oh, well, that sounds all right. I've heard that beef heart is like disgusting.
I've never actually eaten it, but I can imagine it's like very, very tough because it's a muscle.
Yeah.
So lean.
There's, you know, I haven't watched it in a little while, but there was that channel I was watching for a while
called Tasting History with Max Miller.
And I think one episode he did like a themed one where he I think he might have been like doing a Game of Thrones
with Racky thing where he cooked a beef heart instead of a horse heart like Daenerys ate to become Khaleesi.
And he cooked it. He found a recipe and he cooked it according to the recipe and he ate it.
And his reaction was just like, oh, oh, God, it's so tough. It's disgusting.
Makes me respect Daenerys even more.
They probably had a really maybe they like stewed that heart for like a week.
Maybe they marinated it for like months to get it like nice and chewy.
I was wondering about I think I remember looking at like Blu-ray extras and I think the heart was a heart or
like they had a heart and it was a fake thing that looked like a heart.
In any case, one or the other.
It was either real or fake and that's what I remember.
It either was or was not. I see. Yes, excellent.
Spectacular. Anyway, yeah, I never had never had kidney.
Yeah, it's it's not everyone likes it. I didn't like it when I was younger, but in a in a steak and kidney pie,
it's very nice with the gravy.
I think I remember my dad telling me that like he went to, I don't know if it was England or maybe it was somewhere else in Europe,
but I think I remember him saying that he was a vegetarian at the time and but like some he was staying with some family
and they offered him maybe it was steak and kidney pie or maybe it was some other kind of meat pie that contained organs.
But he like found he didn't want to refuse out of like politeness.
But it like he like he like threw up at the table because he was like so it was so bizarre.
I feel like that wouldn't have been a steak and kidney pie. That's this. It's not that odd.
It's too normal. Yeah, it's like the gravy and the beef mask, the taste of the kidney.
You can have kidney and other things.
My dad's a little bit of a picky eater. He like won't eat like chicken on the bone.
I know.
Chicken drumstick like grilled like from a barbecue is great. Just hold the bone.
You just know on it.
Yeah, like wings like come on.
It's easy.
It is easy. He won't eat he won't eat like most shellfish.
He won't eat chicken on the bone and he won't eat most shellfish and that's I just I just I just don't.
I mean, I don't like oysters, but I think oysters are a bit weird because you're supposed to like slurp them up
in the most disgusting way you could possibly do anything.
You can pick them up with a fork and muscle you can eat.
Yes, I like doing that.
I've tried oysters like twice.
I've eaten them the way they've told me to eat them and I'm just like, I don't get it. Why?
Like I feel like Gollum trying to eat Noister.
I feel like I am like Goblin right then.
I am going Goblin mode as they say.
Yeah.
Anyway, speaking of baby potatoes and broccoli, I was that's it.
I think I've been actually quite a few.
I've still been tracking my calories.
A lot of my calories have been coming from pure sugar lately because I've been cooking more.
I've been cooking more gummies with my new recipe.
Actually, I put more sugar in and less fiber to see if that would make it easier to gel.
Because I made one batch that was like low sugar and it came out kind of soft.
I was like, hmm, that didn't work out so well.
But I definitely cooked it with the really low sugar and it definitely worked out a few times.
So I don't know, I would like to work out like what's the least.
I think the most expensive ingredient that I have is fiber.
So, you know, least fiber would be good.
I think the gelatin is the second most expensive.
So less gelatin would be good.
Sugar is cheaper than dirt.
So, you know, bulking it up with as much of that as I can is good.
And then water is free.
That's the best.
Try to make it almost entirely water.
You've got like a perfect product.
Imagine.
Imagine the returns.
I bought some new flavors.
I was really excited to get green apple.
But this brand of green apple that I got, it doesn't taste like a jolly rancher green apple.
It doesn't really taste like a candy green apple.
I kind of can taste like the peel.
I can kind of taste like a sort of cooked like apple pie flavor in it.
And I don't like it.
It's disappointing.
It's not what I want from a green apple flavor.
It's a bit of a bust.
But that's okay.
They can't all be winners.
Yeah.
Apple flavor things are usually quite sour, aren't they?
Like tangy almost.
Yeah.
I make all my gummies pretty sour just because I like them that way.
I made the batch that I gave to my friend for his birthday.
Everyone that tried it was like, oh, they're sour.
I was like, yep.
That's how I feel about you.
Yeah.
It would be a waste.
Actually, oh, I made a batch of peach and I forgot to add the acid and they came out not sour at all.
And they were terrible.
It was so bad.
So I popped them out of the molds and I put them in a cup and I added the acid.
And then I like melted them down in the microwave.
I reforged them into a new blade.
I did though.
And then I remolded them and they actually came out better.
Like they came out firmer.
Like I had evaporated some of the moisture off of them.
Maybe I should do that all the time.
Maybe I should always put them in the microwave and try to cook off excess moisture just to see what happens.
I really like the idea of tiny little gummy swords being forged.
Like every scene in a medieval or a fancy thing where they pour the mold,
pour the molten metal into an open thing in a way that they would never do in real life.
But with gum.
You hear the blacksmith.
Man there was a...
I saw a really funny video on Twitter.
It was a video of two Japanese guys working in like...
I think they were working in like a mochi stand or something.
And they had these...
They just stood at this table and there was like a big like wad of...
I think it was mochi.
It was some squishy green stuff.
Some kind of confection.
And the two of them just had these big wooden hammers.
These big wooden mallets.
And they just took turn like...
Beating this wad of some green shit.
Like one after the other.
Like taking turns.
I've seen references to that technique in the rabbit on the moon.
You know how Japan sees a different side of the moon than America?
They don't see a different side.
They just interpret the...
Yeah, I guess.
It's slightly different because it's a different...
I don't know.
But they see a rabbit with a hammer.
The moon is in a locked orbit.
Everyone sees the same side of the moon.
Well, why do I see a penis on the moon?
I don't because you're gay.
I don't know.
But like the rabbit has a mallet and the mallet is for squishing things.
So I've seen like in...
There's like more than one like video game or anime that like references a rabbit using a mallet to squish a squishy thing.
Well, another rabbit pushes it around.
I don't know.
I've never known what they're building.
They're creating but that's the...
I can picture it.
That's interesting.
I hadn't heard that before.
It's like that bit at the beginning of Dragon Ball where Goku...
I'm trying to think of rabbits with hammers.
There's like when Goku...
Kid Goku, he...
As a...
My headphones fell out.
I can't hear you.
Oh, you fuck.
Okay, now tell me.
Like in the beginning of Dragon Ball, there's a bit where Goku...
There's these thugs and they've got like bunny ears on and they're like,
Ha, we're so evil.
We're gonna...
We're gonna beat you up.
Beating with hammers?
They just have like bunny ears on and that's their thing.
And then Goku easily beats them and he...
As a punishment, he gets his Nyobo, his extending stick.
And he goes all the way up, pulls them up to...
Puts them on the moon as punishment.
And that's like...
It's just like that old fairy tale.
It's just like the rabbit on the moon thing.
It's me, Akira Toriyama, editor's note.
And then Goku comes back down to Earth.
That is so fucking adorable.
Yes.
They never...
Oh my God, and then they died because Master Roshi blew up the moon at the tournament.
Oh my God.
I never thought of that.
They definitely be killed.
Think about that one.
Yeah, they blew up the moon a bunch of times.
So...
Oops.
Dragon Ball Z is so annoyed by the end of Dragon Ball Z.
They have to wish it back with the Dragon Balls a few times, right?
I mean, I've never watched all of...
I've only watched bits and pieces of old Dragon Ball.
I mean, Dragon Ball Z is like that too.
I remember, yeah, Piccolo destroys the moon that one time where he notices Gohan going insane.
And he's like, wait a minute, it's the moon.
Right, that's...
He goes back to normal.
Right, that's why, because of the...
What do you call the monkey form?
Big monkey.
No.
Super Saiyan 3.
I don't know.
Whatever.
True Saiyan.
When they turn into big monkey, they have to blow up the moon sometimes.
That's right.
Well, doesn't Master Roshi just do it for no reason in the tournament?
Master Roshi does it in the tournament when his kid Goku.
No, he does it because Goku is going big.
Oh, okay.
I forgot about that then.
I think it's because his tail is cut off at the very beginning when he goes monkey for the first time.
You understand that he's a were monkey.
Yeah.
He sees the full moon.
They can't destroy the moon because it's like...
What's it?
Like that little brat guy and his two henchmen, the dog and the lady.
Pilaf, that guy?
Yeah, Pilaf.
Pilaf.
Little goblin man or whatever.
Little goblin man.
And then Goku goes big monkey.
And then I think it's Oolong or Yamcha or someone who cuts off the tail with a sword to save the day.
Yeah.
And then randomly during the tournament, Goku's tail comes back during a full moon and then he goes big monkey.
And so Master Roshi destroys the moon instead, which is a bit of a different way to solve that problem.
Wait, so why was he doing that?
Kami-sama puts the moon back together.
Kami-sama is Piccolo?
It's the good half of the great demon king Piccolo, yeah.
Right, right.
I think that's how it goes.
Why was Goku going beast mode if he had his tail cut off?
Because it grew back.
They didn't know that that happened.
It's like, oh, my tail's back.
This is great.
And then, uh-oh, he does the rest of the tournament and he's like, my tail now, this is epic.
And he uses that to his advantage.
But then later the moon comes out.
I guess that makes sense.
Yeah, okay.
That sounds familiar.
I have seen that part.
I would just catch Dragon Ball occasionally here and there.
By the time it was like airing regularly, I think by the time I got Cable as a kid and Dragon Ball was airing regularly, it was already like in the...
It was Kid Buu.
It was the Kid Buu saga.
Not Kid Buu, just Majin Buu, yeah.
So like really late, I mean pretty late, yeah.
But I watched it with my friends.
I'm remembering all the Red Ribbon Army stuff.
Dragon Ball is such a good manga.
Yeah.
So nice and so perfect and they did it.
They did it and they did it.
Yeah, yeah.
Is it better than One Piece though?
Is anything better than One Piece?
You know, for where Dragon Ball ends up going, as a kid, I liked it more than One Piece just because of it having more fun, even more than One Piece and being like more badass more quickly.
I don't know how to describe it.
I think they're kind of equivalent.
It's just that One Piece has like a longer lasting sort of sense of adventure and Dragon Ball is like a fun adventure story that it's just like great to go on.
And then Dragon Ball Z comes around and it becomes a little more serious, a little more edgy and a little less goofy and like adventure-y.
People just teleport and appear at the next battle arena and it's just like one after the other.
It's still good.
Is that like an aging up with the audience kind of thing?
I guess so.
The style definitely changes.
It becomes much more about like personal drama between characters who want to fight and less about a kid exploring the world with his magical stuff and flying cloud.
I wonder if it's like, you know, what do you call it?
Shonen Jump Executive smokes his big cigar.
Toriyama, the kids was reading Dragon Ball.
Well now they've grown up into edgy teenagers.
They want to read Sinon now.
You gotta make your guys big buff guys.
It can't be no little kids running around.
You gotta have them be aliens, Toriyama.
You gotta have alien genocide now.
It's the only way.
And he said yes, sir.
Yes, sir, Mr Jump, sir.
Right away.
It never feels like it's betraying the Toriyama style.
It still feels like him the whole way through.
It's just sort of like he's going like, well, they were kids and now they're adults and now the stakes have to be higher each time.
How high do you go when the guy is trying to destroy the earth?
It's like you can't joke around if that has to be taken seriously.
It has to be kind of a scary guy and he has to be kind of scary.
And so it's like it just sort of naturally goes in that direction, I guess.
Yeah.
I mean, when it starts, I mean, I remember seeing the beginning of Dragon Ball Z and like it does still feel like the same characters.
Like Goku still feels like Goku and he's a goofy man.
Yeah, it's not like a bad like sequel or anything.
I definitely like Dragon Ball Z.
Yeah.
There's something about the adventure feeling of Dragon Ball that I only really get from one piece and then like the Dragon Quest games and other things like that.
It's just sort of like a cute, funny, wholesome, epic quest.
I like it.
Maybe I should read Dragon Ball at some point.
It's not that long, I say, looking at 15, 16, 21, 22 volumes, lol.
Yeah, but I mean like how many chapters is that?
Because I've read a thousand chapters of one piece now.
Yeah, it's not as long as that for sure.
I don't actually know how many chapters.
I own like the physical volumes, so I think of them in terms of that.
Speaking of infinite games, I played, I didn't stream it.
I played, I beat Mega Man 8 two days ago.
I've played Mega Man's 1 through 8 now and there's actually a lot more to go.
I've only played like half, I've at this point played like half the series.
I've played Mega Man 1 through 8 and I've played X through X5.
And what do I have a list here? I've got...
Oh wait, Dragon Ball is only 194 chapters.
That's like child's play.
It's like maybe a couple days of constant reading.
Yeah, that's not even, it's not even anything. It's trash.
That's like, man.
Man, that's...
I don't know how that makes me feel to think that something so influential and important is like...
So, I mean, not small, but like...
It's definitely not small.
I mean, if you think about how difficult it is to make a single chapter of any comic and then doing 194 of them.
Yeah.
That's a big ask, that's a big task.
But also, I mean, yeah, like you said, you can read it in a couple days.
It would probably take you 20...
I mean, how long does it take to read a chapter of manga? Like half an hour, less? So...
Yeah, less than half an hour.
So, it's maybe like 20 hours of reading, which I guess is a lot.
I get 20, 30, I mean, what am I talking about?
I mean, I think it's just one of those things, like, if you draw a picture, people can look at the picture for like five minutes,
and it took you a lot longer than five minutes to make it.
It's like, well, dang, why would I ever draw anything?
Well, because it looks cool. Idiot.
Yeah.
It reminds me of...
What was it? Some show just came out on Netflix or something,
and I heard people saying, like, yeah, the fact that they dropped it all at once
in a big, like, bingeable block, like, killed it.
Like, if it had come out weekly, it would have been like a part of the conversation,
and people would have been talking about it.
But because it came out all at once, everyone just watched it and was like,
okay, it's done, and nobody talked about it.
That's definitely a thing.
Yeah. That probably has happened with many shows.
There was a recent example, but whatever.
People, like, moving on to the next thing, and...
You know how, like, weird it is?
The Elden Ring is the biggest game ever, and I see nothing anymore.
It had its heyday, and that was like, wow, it's done?
People don't talk about Elden Ring anymore?
I still haven't finished it.
I haven't even started it. It's all gone.
Yeah.
The hype is dead. It's so crazy.
I can't believe that art can exist outside of the public current hype culture.
Like, what?
Yeah.
Well, yeah, I don't...
I mean, it's been out for about a couple months now,
and that's long enough that everyone has played it.
Everyone who's played it, that was gonna mostly.
Although, Noah Caldwell-Gervais did just drop an Elden Ring.
Well, it's an Elden Ring, Bloodborne.
Yeah, I just finished watching that.
I watched it yesterday. That's good.
He's so true. He's so correct.
He's pretty right.
Man, I don't even... Okay, I shouldn't even say that.
I shouldn't even have an opinion, because I haven't played any of those games.
So, I shouldn't just be like, oh, man, this guy knows what he's talking about,
because I don't fucking know.
I just like...
As he's coming from the Souls series as a casual player,
who isn't perfect and doesn't like the whole get-good thing, like me,
he resonates very perfectly with the way I feel about the games.
But you are good.
Only because they're fun, and they are not as...
Well, that's the thing he explained in the first video he did on Dark Souls 1, 2, and 3,
where he was hesitant to get into the games because of the reputation of them being so difficult,
and you have to get really good.
He's like, well, I don't want to do that. That sounds hard.
But then when he actually started playing them, he realized that the game doesn't want you to lose.
It wants you to win, and it is actually very forgiving if you use the tools at your disposal to win the game.
It's the atmosphere of you have to do it single-player, otherwise you're a loser,
you're a scrub that pushes people away.
It is nice to hear him push back against that and be like,
he's not the only person who said it, but it really is like,
guys, they put summoning in the game so that you'd fucking use it if you want to.
It really is like the people that say no summoning.
If you summon to win, you've cheated the game and you cheated yourself.
Those people really are just going against what the game says.
They're just denying the text of the fucking game.
The reason I'm quote-unquote good at Dark Souls is because it's not difficult,
because if I use the tools that are in the game, I can do it.
That's fair. I might have told this story, I'm sure I have, but I'm very stupid.
I did beat Dark Souls 1.
I found it fairly difficult, but I worked through it because I have a lot of patience for trial and error stuff.
But I did it in a very stupid way. I did not experiment that much.
I tried to stick really rigidly to one way of playing.
I used the fucking stupid Drake Sword for the whole game, just because I thought it was cool.
Oh, I got a special drop from a dragon. It has a super wave attack.
That sucks. Yeah, I'll use that. It's a cool sword.
That's cool than any of these other normal swords.
That really gimped me.
When it comes to player comfort, Dark Souls is a little more difficult just because
if you don't know where you're putting your stats or if you don't know what you're doing,
then you can't respect at any point during the game. You have to make a new character.
I knew that I got a special dragon sword and I knew that the only way that I wanted to use it because it was neat
and I knew that the only thing that could upgrade it is Drake Scales.
I was like, well, I guess I better try to get some Drake Scales and I upgraded it twice.
I was like, that's pretty good.
I mean, I did win.
The game is not punishing. It's a little punishing in a few areas where if you are very strict with what type of damage you're putting out,
the boss that you're fighting may be strong against that and it'll just take longer.
But there's no hard cap on what is required of you because people have completed the game with no weapons just by punching.
And it's like anything is possible because of that.
It's great.
Just like in real life, anything is possible. Actually, if you try hard enough, you can punch any problem away.
Yeah. Dark Souls is more forgiving than real life because you just can't do that in real life.
That's true without the shadow.
You can't dodge roll through bad things happening.
Gib, you can't just dodge roll all your problems away.
Here's another bout of depression. Wait, frame perfect dodge roll coming up.
Oh, I missed.
Uh-oh. Taxes are due. Better take all my armor off and put on my Havels ring.
Yeah, video games. In real life, that would be silly.
Sure would.
You ever think you've seen Mario in real life?
How does Zelda keep so many items in his little bag?
Okay.
That would have been an interesting game mechanic where things physically make your pack larger if you pick them up.
And then it's like a physics-based thing.
Like in Breath of the Wild, you have a satchel on your back and it gets huge and weighs you down.
It gets huge and makes you slow. What's the Hideo Kojima game where you're walking around?
Death Stranding.
Death Stranding. You get Death Stranding wobbling mechanics like, ah, shit, my pack's so full.
I shouldn't have picked up 100,000 mushrooms that I'm never going to eat.
That's a game that looks cool and I kind of wish I had played it. I guess I still could.
Is it on Steam? I feel like everything's on Steam these days.
I think it must be. I know it's a console non-exclusive, so...
Game just looks neat, but I gotta play Mega Man and Bass.
I gotta play Mega Man and Bass, so my schedule's booked for the foreseeable future.
Man, I tried playing Mega Man Soccer. That game sucks.
Mega Man Soccer?
Mega Man Soccer. It's a real game on the Super Nintendo.
Is there lore in it?
The lore is... I think the lore is just in the manual and it's just like, hey, Wily's back and he's got his robots back
and he's trying to win a soccer tournament this time and you gotta stop him because that's not fair.
So you, Mega Man, also a robot, must join the soccer league and beat Wily's team for the sake of sportsmanship?
It's great. It might be that I kind of don't really know how to play soccer.
I know the rules of soccer. I don't know anything about the strategy of it, so maybe that's why I was failing.
I couldn't score a single goal.
Soccer in video games is so impossible.
It's just because you need a sense of...
Because when you're playing football, normal, you get the ball and then you have to think strategically about where you're going to go with the ball
and you need your teammates to be on the same page as to where you're expected to kick it to them or when.
And if you get tackled, it's hard to play the game when you're just one person.
Playing the game is everybody. It's usually just like, I press the button, I pass to this guy.
Oh, he got tackled instantly. It's gone. Ah, fuck it.
It's really disorienting. I don't know if all soccer games are like this, but I think the way it works is that at the start of the game,
you pick your team set up where your players are going to be on the field and there's a couple different default configurations.
And then the ball enters play and when a player is on screen, you gain control of them and suddenly you're controlling that character.
But if the ball moves, then the screen moves with it and suddenly whatever character is on screen, that's who you're controlling.
And you don't choose. It's automatically switching which character you control in the middle of play.
And any character that isn't on screen, I think any character that is on screen is automatically running towards the ball
and any character that isn't on screen is standing at their default position, waiting for the ball to come near them.
And having characters switch between characters is really disorienting.
I had to keep trying to look at the minimap to figure out where on the field am I? Where are my teammates at?
Where should I be kicking the ball? Just very hard and I couldn't do it.
I scored one goal in the two hours. Maybe an hour and a half or something.
It was too hard and I didn't like it. And apparently there is no ending. So whatever.
Football is a lot more strategic because the idea is the people, you put them in a formation, they are in charge of that little pocket of the pitch.
And if there's a striker, their job is to try to get close to the goal and to do the shooting.
And the rest of the team is there to back them up, to defend against attacks, to weave the ball through the defense of the enemy.
It's like a strategy game. But when you're a kid and you're playing football, you get the ball.
You know it goes in the goal and no matter where you are on the pitch, you just try to get the ball to the goal.
And if you're quicker than the other kids, you do it.
And so most football games don't have that feeling to it. They have more strategy to it.
It's like, I just want to kick it. I just want to kick it as hard as I fucking can.
Which is why the Ape Escape 2 mini game, Monkey Football, is the best football game they ever made in the world.
Because you catch monkeys in Ape Escape and you use those monkeys on your team.
And if you get a rare monkey, if you get a rare monkey like a cool ninja that's hard to catch, they have high stats in the football game.
They have high kick power, high speed.
Wait, who do you play against?
You play against a various set of computer AIs or a friend. You could have multiplayer matches.
Okay.
But there's a league and you go through the shitty teams and get into the harder teams.
But your monkeys that you catch in the game, if you get some good ones that have really good kick power, you put them on the middle of the pitch.
If you get the ball, you hold down the kick button so it's like maximum power.
And you just go all the way, it hits the monkeys in the head, knocks them out, knocks out the goalie.
And I just would do that. I would just get really strong kick power monkeys.
And I would kick the ball into all of the enemy team, knocking them out, making their fatigue go down.
So they would be really slow.
And I would just goal score for the next entire match.
It would be like 72 to 0.
And I would just keep scoring.
And the monkeys would dance about it after every goal.
That's the best football game they ever made.
Well, Mega Man Soccer does let you do trick shots.
If you're a heat man, you can do the trick shot that sets your enemies on fire.
You can set your own teammates on fire by accident too, if you want.
But you can only do it like twice per game, which is like not very many.
And the game just goes on and on because nobody's fucking scoring.
Is it on a timer?
No, no, it was just, I think it was like game two, like a certain number of goals,
which I never reached because I couldn't score it that many.
There's a YouTuber who's not too big, but big, maybe 100k, called Kim Justice.
And she makes videos about, a lot of her videos are about older computers,
specifically British computers and the British game scene in the pre-NES era.
And she talks about shit like the ZX Spectrum that didn't exist outside of the UK.
I've heard of that. I don't know what it does, but I've heard of that name.
Well, there's, oh fuck, I don't know, I've watched a bunch of videos about, like, hang on.
You know what, I gotta find this and recommend this because it's really funny.
Kim Justice, there was one, she made one, like, going over the career of some guy
who made a, like, huge hit on the ZX Spectrum.
And apparently he was like a, he was like a rock star.
He was like this famous rock star who, like, went into drugs and had like a rock star downward spiral
because he was like such a big celebrity, because he made this stupid little fucking platformer
like pre-Atari, like, console.
Hang on.
A rock star?
That, I mean, that's how she describes it.
The Commodore Amiga is another one.
What was this fucking guy's name?
Yeah, and like, now he's like a burnout.
Okay, yeah, oh my god, here's, here's, the video is called
From Manic Minor to Jet Set Willy, the story and games of Matthew Smith.
Yeah, and Matthew Smith was this like 17 year old savant who made fucking Jet Set Willy,
which was like the, like, a cultural revolution on the ZX Spectrum.
I love this video, I've watched it like three times.
78k subscribers, so medium, pre-medium.
Anyway.
Did you link it?
Oh, I should link it.
There are other, there's other good stuff.
She has a big like history of Peter Molyneux, which is pretty interesting.
Look at this guy.
Jet Set Willy.
And there he is, this little fucking, this little fucking top hat man.
Shout outs to Kim Justice.
I would never have known about the Commodore Amiga.
But anyway, I just remember she, I think it was on one of those consoles.
I don't remember exactly which one, but there's a game called like, called Sensible Soccer.
And it was like, it was like a huge hit.
And I'm like, that's like the most, the most British thing I've ever, it's just called, it's, it was like,
it was like kind of revolutionary, I guess, in that it like more, it was like so much more like realistically portrayed
like the rule, translated the rules of soccer into like a game.
It was like the first soccer game that actually felt like soccer.
But it's just called Sensible Soccer.
It's like, hmm, hmm, yes.
A very like, a very sober, a very sober and reasonable, reasonable gaming experience that I'm having.
I love reasonable gaming experience.
Love to, I would love to just have a, I'd like to play soccer, but like unlike all these other, you know,
unlike all these other like fly-by-night, you know, party boy developers,
I would like my soccer game to be sensible, please.
Just keep me grounded.
And they did.
And apparently it was a big hit.
So I don't know.
I don't even get on this.
Oh right, Soccer games, Sensible Soccer, Mega Man.
That's it.
I have no like notes this week.
I have nothing happened to me this week.
I just, I have to, I'm just rambling.
I can't believe a whole week.
I can't believe a whole week has passed since, since last Sunday.
Yeah, I don't really feel like anything happened.
No, nothing at all.
It's one, it's one of those weeks that I feel like I just blinked and it was gone.
Yep.
Same.
Yeah.
Tomorrow is.
I have been, oh yeah.
I was just gonna say tomorrow is America Day.
It's July 24th.
You mean the fourth?
Yeah.
Why did I say the 24th?
It's July 4th.
I don't know.
I don't super feel like celebrating America at the moment.
No.
But like, I mean, whatever I guess.
Not boo America.
Boo.
Yep.
Exactly.
May the 4th is funnier because of the Star Wars.
Star Wars.
Jokes that every dad makes.
Yeah.
Peter.
It's Star Wars, Peter.
Love Star Wars.
That's exactly what she says.
She says that that's her line.
That's what I know Lois for.
Anyway.
Yeah.
I was gonna say.
I have nothing else to say about the fact that it's July 4th tomorrow.
I don't care.
Go on.
Maybe I'll do something.
Probably not.
Make a little upside down American flag.
Post saying July 4th.
More like die 4th.
And then it wouldn't make that much sense.
Absolutely.
I have the past few days had like a weird itch.
A mental itch.
Not a physical itch.
This is a world building itch.
I've been playing Oblivion.
The Elder Scrolls.
And you know.
Just for the no real reason playing it without first travel.
So if I need to go from one side of the map to the other I need to buy a horse or get a horse.
And just travel along the roads or you know whatever.
Yeah.
And it's been a it's a longer journey.
It's feels more like I get a sense of like a real sense of like a gratefulness that these settlements exist.
Because like on the road there's like bandits all the time.
There's like trolls and imps shooting things at me.
And I'm like fuck my horse is going to die.
I don't want that.
I got to get to a refuge.
I got to get to an inn and stay inside and be protected.
And so it's sort of just nice.
And I'm just sort of looking at all these quests and these names and these like places and I'm like fuck.
The Elder Scrolls is such a rich world with all these things that they made up and came up with.
The Daedra and the fucking books that you can read.
I want to do that.
It's my time to do that.
It's what I want to do.
And now I'm thinking about world building all the time.
I just want to why I want to world build.
And I don't really know how to do it because it's.
Hmm.
It's so such a big task.
Well, I every time I come up to something like this is like, oh, that's so cool.
I want to be the one who have done that.
I know.
Yeah.
It's like right now I'm thinking how do I make the fucking Cyrodiil?
How do I make oblivion?
But I did it.
Isn't it?
Isn't it sort of tempting when you see something like that and it's something that you like?
Isn't it sort of tempting to think like, well, I could have thought of that.
Like if only I hadn't like seen them do it first.
Like I probably would have thought of that myself actually.
It's it's kind of like my idea.
Give her that.
I for some things, I guess so.
It's it's really just that I can see how people would come to.
To come up with these things like where the inspiration came from.
If I looked into history and like ancient theology and like things that have been like words, etymologies of words and like stuff like that stories from the past.
I use that as a base for stories of the future.
And that's basically what all these things do is they take like tropes and and ways of naming things that real people did but use funny elf words instead that they made up.
And it's like, yeah, I could have come up with that.
I mean, oblivion gates.
I mean, that's cool.
It's like a land of fire and they've got like a different kingdom.
It's like the kingdom on the other side of the portal.
Like that's not so strange.
Everybody's made a story like that.
That sounds pretty reasonable.
Yeah.
That's what I would expect to be on the other side of an oblivion portal.
Sometimes I do feel like that a lot of what I would make is just completely copied from something else.
I'm like, oh wait, no, I'm making a homestuck thing here.
This is a homestuck thing and this is an oblivion thing.
Oh, and this is a fucking, this is a Princess Mononoke thing.
I'm just copying.
Ah, fuck.
Ah, shit.
I don't have a single good idea.
I mean.
So it's hard to do.
Yeah.
I guess you kind of got a, you kind of got a, you know, great artist steel and all that.
I gotta not worry about that too much.
There definitely is some point at which it's like, okay, now you're just taking everything from such and such.
But like, you're probably not actually there.
You probably feel like you're there way earlier than you're actually there, you know?
Yeah.
I mean, I felt that a little bit about Belle Jape because it was like.
Oh yeah.
Belle Jape is exactly like everything.
I don't know.
No, no.
I mean, what happens in it is, you know, unique enough, but the method by which I was doing Belle Jape was like, I just want to have Microsoft Paint Adventures.
But I did instead.
So I had a website called APSA as Adobe Photoshop Adventures.
And I made a comic reminiscent of jailbreak and homestuck and problem sleuth and stuff.
And I'm like, haha, I did it though.
And it did turn into something that was a little different, but still having the S like flash, but and all that, the gifts.
It's, it's so obviously like a homestuck fan thing that it sort of felt like, ah, shit, I got to start being different.
I got to start being more unique.
And I guess that's why I started drawing the Lord of Ghost comic.
So I wanted to have, I want to have like a real comic that you could print on a piece of paper.
I want to have stuff that I can do that's not exactly the same as something else.
Ben?
You there?
Hey, I'm back.
Oh, you're back.
I don't know why that just happened.
My internet just went out for like a minute and now it's back, I guess.
Well, I said my bit.
The viewers at home know exactly what I said.
I'll just have to wonder.
I'll never know.
You know, one thing about world building that I was wondering.
I was looking into like the world, like Tamriel is the world of the Elder Scrolls.
Yeah.
And like the people, I just sort of thought, what are, why do people know what the planet is?
Like, did people in medieval times have a concept of the world being like a singular place that could have a name?
Or would they only think of their immediate area, their own name, their country, the kingdom that they're being like lorded over with?
Like, do they have a name for like the Earth?
And I guess they did.
But it was like Earth, like soil, like land mass.
I mean, people, I mean, what do they, the Greeks knew that the Earth was a sphere?
Did they?
Yeah.
I mean, maybe not all of them did, but some Greek.
They had gods that were like, I was looking into it a little bit.
I didn't get very far in my, because I literally thought of this just before we started recording.
It's like, what are they, what do they, like, would they have a name for the world?
Like people in medieval England.
I think.
Would they have a concept of like, oh, the Earth, the planet or the world or something like that?
Would they have a name for it?
If they just lived on the British Isle and they didn't know that there was anything like across, is it, is it the Caspian?
No, what's the, what's the channel?
Is it the English Channel that goes between English Channel and the North Sea?
If they didn't know there was anything beyond the sea, they would probably just think that, you know, that island is the world and they would be one in the same.
But then as soon as they figured out there's an even bigger land mass across the channel, they'd be like, okay,
there's actually like a, this is a world and our little island is just part of it.
And who knows what the fuck else is out there?
I mean, you can see France from the coast of England.
Oh, can you?
Oh, lol.
Okay.
But I feel like people would know countries.
They would know, they would hear tales of people going on treks and coming back and telling the stories and stuff.
People wouldn't know literally what the Earth looks like.
But like.
Yeah.
A name for like a, like, divorced from country, from kingdom, a name for the land.
It seems like an odd thing that only exists in fantasy novels.
I'm going to say, I'm going to say they probably would because like they would know that like, oh yeah, the land just kind of extends, you know, East, like, for who knows how long.
So you can't, you can't really talk about just like a landmass because like it doesn't really have like an end that you even know of.
So I guess, but like, I mean, you would say the land, you would say the sea, you know, the ocean.
And then you would say the land, which is like rocks and soil and dirt that you can stand on.
And those are like the two things that make up most of what you understand.
And you wouldn't say like, you wouldn't call the sea a name other than the sea.
It's just like a descriptive word.
Yeah.
And so you wouldn't call the Earth.
Oh, like you don't call it.
You don't call it.
It doesn't have a proper name.
I understand.
This is the world of Tamriel.
This is the world of Azeroth.
Like, why, why are these names?
They would have countries, they would have factions and they would have like landmarks.
They would just call it the world because like, what's what's the point of giving it a name to distinguish it from some other?
Like we call we call Earth the Earth because we know that there are nine planets.
Yeah.
And Earth is like derived from words that mean soil and dirt and like ground as opposed to the ocean, which is the other thing.
Yeah, you're probably.
And they're like, they're like gods of terror.
The Romans had terror and the Greeks had Gaia and they were like gods and goddesses of like the Earth.
But the Earth meaning land and like very explicitly just land, not like a metaphorical sense of like the world that we understand.
Like a human world right now is like the observable universe.
I think it's like our world that we understand.
Yeah.
Calling it calling it something like Tamriel or Azeroth is like a little bit might be a little bit like, you know, for the player to just to distinguish it from the real world.
I don't know.
I wonder if maybe some cultures did have like, oh yeah, our world is called such and such.
And maybe if they believed in, I mean, maybe if they believed in an afterlife or like a spirit world or something, they would call the real world one name and they'd have another name for that other world that they believed in, perhaps.
I could see that.
All right.
I may have misread this.
I was quickly Googling on Wikipedia.
But I did read some Middengard was like an old English term for the concept of world in that same way where like, this is what we understand as like a place that we know the edges of.
Yeah.
Middengard or Gehrd was that and that was like what Tolkien used to create Middle Earth as the term for that.
And also Midgar.
Is that like the Norse Norse mythology?
Is that like to distinguish it from like, you know, Asgard and Jotunheim and Hell and stuff?
Yeah, I guess so.
Yeah.
That's what I'm, yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
Like, if you believe there are, if you believe there are other worlds, then it might benefit you to give this one a name to distinguish it.
So I guess, you know, now I think about it, we call Earth Earth.
It is a proper noun because it's like us earth and hell and heaven and everything.
Yeah.
And we use it to describe the world.
And I guess for these fantasy worlds, Azeroth and Tamriel are like equivalent words that mean dirt.
Maybe.
But sounds like more names than we would be used to because we're used to Earth and that doesn't seem like a proper noun, even though it functionally is the same thing.
All that to say is that I don't know what to call my world.
I don't know what to call it and I don't know what to do.
Just call it, have you considered calling it space?
But what if there's space?
Just call it, I'm just trying to think of something.
What can we rip off?
Like a hot dog Leo.
Sure.
Yeah, that's what I was going to say.
Uh, barrel of laughs.
Just some stupid phrase.
How about call it, how about you call it?
Popstar.
I've got it.
Call it the Marvel Cinematic Universe.
Yeah.
Popstar.
Wait, Popstar is just one.
Popstar is a little planet.
Yeah, just set your world in the Kirby universe.
Yeah.
And then Kirby has all these different planets.
And then one day for no particular reason, fucking,
what's the giant like machine that grants wishes?
Marvin the Martian.
I know what you mean.
It's the giant clockwork cat face.
Yes.
Then one day just for no particular reason,
totally divorced from whatever else is happening in your stories.
Just fucking giant clockwork cat face just like swoops by
and like smashes the planet into smithereens and like that's the end.
Yeah.
I have my whole story.
There's like the countries of pop pop star and like all the like
Game of Thrones, but on pop star with all my characters and then
it gets destroyed and then Kirby's there at the end.
It's like, it leads into the Kirby number one.
It was all a prequel to Kirby is, is pop star the one that's
like frozen and it's like post apocalyptic earth?
I thought pop star was literally a star shaped planet.
Yellow five pointed star that Kirby lives on or goes to.
Yeah.
I think that might.
Quick.
Yes, it is.
It's the first level in Kirby 64.
Crystal shards distinguished by forest and grasslands.
Yeah.
Pop star into Google and it gives me pop stars as in music.
I didn't even think of that.
I typed in Kirby.
So I was safe from that.
Yes.
It's the star with the two rings.
What's the one that's just earth?
What's the one that's just post apocalyptic frozen earth though?
How would Kirby say earth?
He would say he would call it Azeroth because he's a big game.
I'm shiver star shiver star.
Oh, because it's frozen.
Yeah.
You know the one like you can see.
You can see like North America and the and the continents and stuff.
Is that a new ish?
No, it's a.
No, that's from that's from 64.
Yeah.
I remember this level.
I didn't think but yeah, I can see the.
It's very intentional.
Yeah.
And I think they I think they elaborate on it in forgotten land.
I think they I think you go to shiver star in forgotten land.
So in the in the Nintendo cinematic universe, Kirby 64 happens after any game that takes
place on earth.
I guess so.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Is there even a single actual Nintendo game franchise that has earth as a as a place?
Or they all fantastical.
Splatoon of things.
Splatoon.
So Splatoon is like a prequel to Kirby.
I want to think that that's true because I hope that the inklings come become real.
I hope that the inklings take over because I love them.
And then they get frozen and die.
Sure.
But you know, for a for a shining moment in history, they would they would they would
burn brightly and revel in their murder frenzy.
World building is bad.
Don't do it.
You know what?
I want to build.
I want to world build because you know what?
Any world you build is just going to freeze over and die one day.
No, but you can build over that too.
You can build over everything.
I can have, you know, Steven Universe has that giant hole cut out of the earth.
That's world building.
So does so does Adventure Time.
Yeah.
Maybe that was the adventure time I was thinking of.
Maybe they're like a bit in Steven Universe, whether they go on the moon or there's a map
of earth or you can see.
And there's just like a huge part of like the top of Russia is just missing.
Yes.
Epic.
It's fucking third impact.
Third impact happened.
Dude, what if Shinji met Steven Universe?
Oh, they both cry.
They're both big pussies that cry all the time.
They'd be best friends.
They probably would be best friends, honestly.
And then Steven would go up and kiss the Avers.
Oh, no, not the Avers.
The Angels, what are they called?
I mean, they genuinely...
Oh, the Crystal Gems.
No, Steven would kiss the enemies from Aver.
Yeah, the Angels.
Yeah.
They genuinely both have the same problem.
They both like...
Wait a minute.
They both have like, use their mom's power to like fight against like aliens.
And they both are like really fucked up about it.
So, yeah, I mean, I see no...
I see no problems here.
Yeah, maybe it's like a direct inspiration.
Honestly?
Yeah, seems like it.
It's actually...
Instead of big robots.
It's actually quite analogous now that I think about it.
It's a pink shield and a lion.
Yeah, instead of him being in a giant robot that has his mom's brain in it,
he is a giant robot that has his mom's soul jewel in him.
So, it's kind of like...
It's kind of like reverse.
Like she is piloting him.
Yes.
And he has to grapple with that.
It's like, I don't want to be the robot.
I don't want to be the robot anymore.
I didn't ask to be the robot.
Be the robot, Shinji.
Get your mom in you, Shinji.
Ah, geez.
I don't know about this.
I think this joke has happened.
That's a deja vu.
This is a joke from PCP Episode 3 or something.
There's no way.
There's no way we would have ever made a joke before on any of our 700 fucking episodes.
When one day, one day there will be more episodes of the PCP than there are chapters of One Piece,
and then who will have the last laugh?
How the hell would that happen?
One Piece chapters come out weekly and so do the PCP episodes.
Not forever.
Oda won't live forever.
And we will.
Oh, no.
There's more than a thousand chapters.
And One Piece has gone past its 25th anniversary.
I don't want to have the 25th anniversary, the Procrest News Podcast.
That would be terrible.
That would be life-ending.
Well, I'm sorry.
There's no other way.
No.
I'm sorry.
You're just going to have to do it.
You're going to have to do it.
Shit.
Or, I mean, what's the alternative?
You just die?
I guess not.
Yeah.
I guess I'll live.
Yeah, yeah.
You're stuck.
This is the only thing.
As long as you live, there must always be.
A podcast.
It's like the World of Warcraft when the Lich King got killed.
And the Bolvar Four Dragon put on the helmet.
And he's like, there must always be a Lich King for some reason.
Really, there's no reason.
We just wanted to say that was very badass.
In the writer's room, we thought that was very badass.
It doesn't make any sense.
But I am the Lich King now.
Was there a previous Lich King that passed on the crown?
The Lich King, the crown, I think it's the sword, Frostmourne, how's the undead ghost
of Ner'zhul, a warlock orc from another planet.
And he's like evil.
He corrupted Arthas into doing the bidding of the Burning Legion by doing undead magic
and raising the dead and all that.
So initially, they were Burning Legion associates.
And then I can't remember really what happened.
I think they broke off and they became their own thing.
Arthas was like, fuck you, Burning Legion.
I'm in control.
I'm evil.
And I'm going to kill everyone my way.
And then they kill the Lich King in the game.
Damn.
And then...
Didn't work out.
I don't know.
I guess they just defeated the Lich King and there's no Lich King.
Well, they defeated him.
Except there has to be.
And then he couldn't do those things.
Yeah, I feel like when they beat the Lich King, there just wasn't any more Lich King.
But some guy put on the hat and now he's the Lich King.
And he doesn't do anything until one cutscene later in another expansion
where Sylvanas Windrunner goes evil and she breaks open the Lich King's helmet
and it tears open the afterlife.
And then everyone goes into the afterlife and everyone's dead and alive at the same time.
Wasn't Sylvanas already evil?
It's so strange.
Wasn't Sylvanas already evil in Burning Crusade?
Sylvanas was evil from the very beginning.
I mean, not really.
She was an elf, right?
Yeah, but like as long as she's...
Arthas was taking over the Night Elf place.
Sylvanas was like one of the sisters.
Like, you will not take my land.
Arthas says, yes, I will.
And then you play the level and you kill her.
You turn her into a Banshee and she's like a slaved Arthas.
And she's like, fuck.
Okay, I'll do your bidding.
God.
And then she's like doing his bidding.
And then at some point she manages or is helped by someone to rest control away from Arthas
and she becomes her own person and she is so angry at Arthas that she uses her powers
of the undead to raise or to corral her own faction of the undead as the Forsaken
who then joined the Horde in an alliance of strengths so that they can kill the Lich King.
And that's her whole goal.
And she helps with that.
And they go in the wrath of the Lich King expansion, they kill him.
And then she is just sort of a faction in the Horde and she's always seemed kind of sus.
But it's mostly other people in her faction who are sus and they want to extinguish life.
And she's like, I don't want this.
I'm not evil.
I'm not like Arthas.
And so she becomes more trustworthy.
At some point she becomes the War Chief because Vol'jin dies and he trusts her based on all the adventures they've had together.
And then she becomes the War Chief and it was the most hyped moment ever because it's like, whoa.
Finally, Sylvanas is getting recognition.
She's not evil.
Her undeath does not define her.
She's not exactly as everyone thought.
And then one expansion later, oh, she is evil actually.
She's just, they changed her and now she's like a one note, I'm evil and I just hate everybody.
Relatable though.
And it sucks.
It sucks so bad.
I hated it.
You know, it's a classic story for a reason.
We can get behind it.
It's not classic.
It's stupid.
World of Warcraft is a stupid story and I can't stop playing it.
Man, I hate video games.
Man, I hate fiction.
Man, I hate, is this world not enough for you?
You have to go and invent some new ones, pathetic.
Why would I want to learn about things that already exist?
Why would I want to do that?
Listen, I just want, I just want to play soccer, but I just want it to be sensible, right?
None of this fancy, fantasy nonsense.
No, stop putting robot masters that can shoot flaming, like paralyzing kicks down the pitch in my games.
I just want to, I just want to, I just want to shoot the goal in the hoop.
I'll just, I'll make my world called sensible world and it will not have magic in it.
It'll have science only.
Yes.
Thank you.
That's a very, that's a great relief, a great relief to me.
You see, Pumpk is, she's, she's animated, she's, she comes back to life because that's just how it works, okay?
This is the physics of the world.
Are you telling-
Pumpkins can live and have fire in their brain and that's just how it is.
It's not weird.
It's sensible.
Are you telling me that if you put a string, if you put a candle inside a pumpkin,
you can illuminate it from the inside?
Like, what is, what were they smoking when they came up with that one?
They were smoking wax candles, Ben.
True.
It wasn't very tasty.
True, though.
I realized something.
I had a, I think, okay, I was struggling with the decision about whether I wanted to invest in a new camera.
And it would be like, to get it, to get it, I was like, okay, do I buy a new camera or do I try to make do with my smartphone camera?
Smartphone camera, you know, it's not amazing, but it does record in high, you know, high enough definition that it's, it's okay.
But the problem was that with the autofocus, like if you try to film something, I did not find any way to turn off the autofocus.
So if you're filming something that's moving, the thing is like autofocusing over and over again and it's bad.
But I guess you can use third-party camera apps, like you don't have to use the native camera app.
You can download third-party apps that give you more manual control over your camera.
So I might be able to record video without the autofocus ruining everything with my smartphone.
And if so, it's probably going to tip the scales and I'm probably just going to use my smartphone.
I have a stand for, I have a stand for it now. It's a cheap stand.
I might try to get like a, like a, more of like a slightly fancy like stabilizer stand.
I don't know how those work, but I could probably find a better one than just like a stick that holds it.
It's odd that your app just doesn't let you not like the autofocus.
I mean, maybe I missed something, but I could not, I could not find any way to do it.
And I looked up reviews of the phone because some people make like reviews of every camera and every phone.
I could find no, ah, moth, fuck.
I could find no mention of anyone like adjusting the autofocus.
I like specifically Googled for like turn off autofocus.
And I found, and I found people like saying where the option is, but not for my phone.
Like I found people saying how to do it on like certain iPhones and certain other Android phones, but not this one.
And so I'm like, I don't know.
I think maybe the app just doesn't have the option.
So, but it's okay because I think I can probably get some other apps that presumably will let me do that, which would be nice.
Because like if I was going to invest in a real camera, it wouldn't be worth doing unless I spent like probably at least like 250 bucks, which is like, I don't want to do that.
I don't want to spend 250 bucks if I don't have to.
So maybe I don't have.
So maybe I don't have to.
And that's nice.
And that's it.
That's it.
That's all I have.
I don't think I have anything else.
Oh, wait.
Maybe, maybe someone in the audience knows a bit about plants.
But I have a houseplant.
I got it for my birthday.
Oh, yeah.
It's a, it's a Guzmania, G-U-Z, mania, bromeliad.
And it's like a, it's a cool looking sort of jungly plant, houseplant.
Oh, I'm looking at it.
Yeah.
And I've never had a houseplant.
I want to do it right.
I looked up a lot of like videos on how to treat for a Guzmania bromeliad and they had
advice and I've tried to follow it.
I don't think I'm doing it right.
And I feel like I am going to kill it accidentally.
Help.
I can't help you with that one.
It's just, it's just a, it's a little scary, almost not scary.
It's just sort of, I don't really have like instant feedback like you do with a dog or
a cat about how they're feeling.
I just wake up one day and I notice the leaves are looking at a little something or other,
like they're a little curled up.
So like, does that mean it's lacking water?
The, the, the tutorials, tutorials, the advice guides and things, they're all saying like,
don't water it too much, but make sure to water it.
Yeah.
And like every two days during summer, keep it in bright light, but not direct sunlight.
So keep it outside of the like range of the sun coming through the window, but make sure
it gets plenty of light.
And I'm like, ah, it's enough light.
I put it sort of far enough away, but it never gets hit.
How do you know, how do you know how much is too much?
And so I'm just sort of looking at it and slowly it's sort of looking worse.
And I don't know exactly what the problem is.
I don't know if it's too wet or, or what.
So I am just sort of hoping that I didn't kill it already.
So it's, it's inside, right?
It's an inside.
It's in my room.
It's in your room.
To make a, make the room greener with greenery.
True.
So it's, I mean, I don't know.
Maybe is it, is it like near a window?
It's, it's, um, it's narrow-ish.
I mean, the window's big.
Um, and I just have it out of range for weather or when the sun is like coming straight in.
Um, it doesn't get blasted by it.
But it's, I mean, the walls are white and it's good.
And I feel like it's getting enough light.
Like if you, if you were to put it outside, you would put it in a shaded area because
it sort of lives in like a jungle.
So it's like used to like bigger trees being covering it, uh, from, from the majority of
light.
So I feel like the light level is all right.
I'm just worried about like the water amount, whether the soil is shit.
And, uh, that's, uh, that's my story.
You might have to like, I don't know, give it some like, some like fertilizer or something.
But honestly, I have no, I have no idea.
I have no idea.
I've never had a houseplant.
Yeah.
Uh, like I wanted to, I didn't specify, like I asked for one, I didn't specify what kind.
This seems like it, that keep people keep saying, oh, it's a very easy houseplant.
You don't need to, you know, worry too much about it.
But I'm worrying it's a life.
I don't want to, I don't want to be responsible for a death on the property.
Uh, think of the neighbors.
Oh, think of my reputation.
There reminds me, you know, uh, I've mentioned at my old house, my root, one of my roommates
had a plant.
Oh God, what was it called?
I'm blanking on what the name was.
It was like a sort of variant of it, like a citrus tree.
And, um, yeah, it was in a pot and it stayed inside most.
I mean, he kept it on the porch in like the summer and he would take it inside during the winter
and it was a nice tree and it, it fruited a little bit.
They didn't, they didn't become like edible or anything.
But, uh, one year it bloomed, it had flowers.
It was like, you know, a kind of high tree.
It was maybe like six, six feet tall.
It had like a nice foliage on top.
It flowered, it smelled incredible.
It smelled great.
And then the next year he, I think he accidentally left it out on the porch a little too late
and then like it got cold, like before he expected, and that like cold snap, like it didn't kill the tree,
but it like devastated it.
Like all its, like it didn't, like all its leaves fell off.
Uh, he pretty much had to like cut, he pretty much had to cut the entire tree off
and leave just a little like stick, sticking out of the pot,
from which like one little branch kind of started to grow eventually and like it grew a couple of leaves,
so it's like technically still alive and maybe it could recover, although seems like it would take a while.
Uh, so I don't, I wonder, I wonder how that plant's doing.
I wonder, I wonder if you still got it.
Hmm.
Citron just like, I don't remember.
I don't remember. What was the big fucking fruit called?
I don't know.
A lime.
A pomegranate.
No, it had a nickname.
It was called like something limes or it was called like blood limes or like like scarlet limes.
Scarlet limes, yes.
Scarlet limes.
Okay, I'm not finding anything.
It doesn't matter.
Some kind of cumquat or whatever.
Anyway, if I, if I have like a devastating update or a good news update,
I will update people on the bromeliad situation.
Bro.
That's my new corner.
That's my new like ongoing arc.
You've got to keep tuning into the Procrastinators podcast to get the latest scoop on the bromeliad situation.
I've got, I've got gummies and you've got the bro, the bromeliad.
Hmm.
Delightful.
I'll mention again, I have, I'm waiting on Nate to do this for me.
I need Nate to log in to the Kickstarter because I have, I think I have a couple of packages here
that need to go out to Kickstarter backers.
I found them in my P.O. box, uh, wrote to Radcon books, for instance.
And I think I, I just need, I didn't, it won't let me do it because Nate is the one that made the Kickstarter account.
So like they asked me to show ID, but I can't do it.
They need Nate to show his like driver's license before they'll let me access the old document,
the old records and look at people's addresses.
And like, I think I want to message some people and to ask them like, hey, is this still your address?
Because it has been like two years and it may have.
Yeah.
Oh, it's, yeah.
A couple of them are people who were living or living in like New Zealand.
And so their address, so they, and like COVID meant that I couldn't mail anything to like Australia and New Zealand for some reason.
So I don't know.
I could just send them, but I sort of want to ask these people, like, I just want, like, I just want to double check, like, is this still your address?
It's been a long time.
I feel like there's a pretty high chance that if I just sent them, they wouldn't arrive at the people.
So I just want to like check on that before I send those out.
So I'm waiting to do that.
That might be messaging on Nate though.
Hmm.
Yeah.
Well, he mess it.
He, I know.
He told me again today like, oh yeah, I'll get right to that.
Like message me later.
I'll do it.
It's like, yeah, you always, you always say that.
You always say that.
And then maybe like after like five times, you actually do it.
But I'm working on it.
You know, Kaiju had started, Kaiju was drawing the dojin.
Did I mention that?
Like he actually showed me some progress that he was making on it.
That's good.
Yeah.
I don't know how much of it he did, but I haven't heard from him in maybe like two weeks.
But he definitely was working on it.
Uh, I, I don't know.
I think I would, you know, when that gets done, my hope was that we could release the dojin at the same time as the OVA.
And then it would be all come out at once.
And then that would be the last thing.
And then the, and then the radcon curse would be lifted.
Um, but, but, uh,
I mean, whatever comes out just immediately.
I feel like there's no reason to like wait if something is finished.
Yeah.
At this point.
I mean, I, I mean, yeah, sure.
But, you know, I had hoped that Nate would, uh, because the plan was for Nate to, you know, edit the OVA together.
And he, he did edit the music video together.
Although, you know, uh, Victor was in the comments being like, why did this take so long?
Like I fit, I basically did all of this, like at the place.
So I don't know.
So I don't know about that.
Uh, I think, I don't know.
I haven't really talked to him about it, but I think I'm going to ask him like, Nate, I know.
It took me like months of asking you, like, like, like, how is the music video going for you to get it done?
Like the OVA will be that, but worse, like maybe we should just hire someone.
Maybe maybe, you know, some editors, maybe we should just hire one of your editors to do it and pay them to do it.
Because like, I don't think you're actually going to do it.
You're going to tell, you're going to tell me you're going to do it for months.
And maybe event, yeah.
Yeah.
So I'm going to, I'm going to suggest that to him.
Uh, and, uh, that will be better.
I don't know why Nate, I don't know why Nate insists on pretending that he's going to do things.
If you're not going to do it, just tell me you're not going to do it.
I guess, I guess that's not fair.
He did eventually, he did eventually make the music video.
He did eventually finish that and release it.
So it's not that he's never going to do it.
Don't understand why he'll be like, oh yeah, yeah.
This Wednesday, I'll have it done this Wednesday.
Oh, Wednesday's over.
Okay.
Definitely next Wednesday.
I will, it's not even me.
It's not even me that suggests it.
It's just him of his own volition is like, I'm going to set a deadline for myself next Wednesday for sure.
Yeah.
Oh, it's over.
It seems like he does that.
Yeah.
He likes doing that.
But then he just ignored it.
But then he just ignores it.
He just ignores it.
And like, what's the point?
I understand that like a deadline can be motivating to get things done.
Yeah.
If you don't just ignore it.
I truly do not understand.
But whatever, I'm going to try and work around.
I'm going to try and work around that.
Let's just fucking hire someone.
Let's just hire someone.
Maybe get it done in a week.
I think maybe Kaiju would do it.
Kaiju is an editor.
Oh my God.
I mean, if he wants to work.
No, no, yeah, I mean, I'm sure he would be okay to do it.
It's just sort of, you know, he's already doing the dojin and he's got his own job.
It's like, I feel like it would just continually conflict with his own like work that he's got.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, he said he was starting to draw the dojin because he had some downtime from the other editing work he had to do.
That's what he told me anyway.
You know, the thing is that I've, Kaiju's told me that editing is like a real pain.
Sure.
It's good money, but like he hates it.
I don't really want to put an OVA on him.
Oh, well, I mean, I mean, it wouldn't have to be him.
I mean.
No, no.
As a, you know, spitball suggestions, fine.
I mean, maybe, I mean, maybe I'd ask him if he wanted to.
Unless Nate had someone else that he thought would be like a better fit for like the project.
I don't know.
Nate would probably know.
Nate knows more about editing than I do.
And he knows like what would be required for that.
I think he's got like a plan.
He has a plan for like how he wanted to assemble it.
Maybe he would have someone in mind who would like do it the way he was intending it to be done.
Fucking Radcon.
Yeah, fucking, fucking Radcon.
I'm going to beat it.
I'm going to defeat Radcon.
I'm committed now to just being able to say it all got done.
This is something I would love to be able to say as well, even though I'm not really doing anything to help.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, you did, you did all the things you were obligated to do.
But then you've picked up the slack of every other thing that people were, did not do.
Yeah.
There were, there were things left.
All the things that were left is like, well, I mean, well, who's going to do the, I mean, I've basically been the guy who's been like, okay, well, how are we going to do.
The dogen.
Okay.
Well, I guess I'll reach out to these people and get that done.
Yeah.
I've been doing like all this stuff that like nobody else kind of knew how it was going to get done.
It's fine.
You know, it's a little, it's, I mean, it's mostly just a lot of waiting.
Like I've talked to, like I've had to talk to people, like I had to get Mishi to draw the cover.
I had to finish writing the road to Radcon.
I had to, I guess it actually was a bit of a project to like go to the printer and get like, and like, collude with the printer and get that whole thing set up to get the books printed, etc, etc.
But it wasn't that bad.
It's mostly waiting has been the majority of it.
It's been some work, but I don't mind.
Yeah.
I mean, originally I was going to edit the OVA, but like,
Oh, were you?
Yeah, very, like very originally, but like Nate offered, like to do it because he wanted, I don't know, he had like a vision.
And I was like, thank God, because I don't want to have this hanging over my head.
Yeah, over to him.
Yeah, I don't know.
By this point, I feel like I would have been able to do it.
It would have annoyed me a lot having that hanging over my head.
Yeah, it wouldn't.
I mean, there's no, there's no reason, there's no reason for it to have taken two years other than you just didn't want to do it.
Yeah.
So let's just, let's just look that in the face and be like, okay, we have all this Radcon money left over.
It still has not been spent.
Let's just spend some of it to get it done.
Like who cares?
Although I mean, I guess TBAP, I guess TBAP Resurrection did take a year to come out after Radcon 3, Lamal.
Which is, I mean, it's also stupid.
It is just the way of things.
We are the procrastinators.
We don't do things in a timely fashion.
That's true.
I mean.
I had this dream, well, it's not a dream, but just sort of a funny thought that like later when we, you know, when we grow up a bit and we get better at our crafts and we, you know, we speed up, we get stronger.
Yeah.
We can make, we can make these videos and comics and things faster.
We'd stop being the procrastinators.
We become the professionals.
We'd be raking it in.
Now we're called the professional podcast.
It never happened.
Yeah.
I'll never get stronger.
I'm as good as I'll ever be.
There's no more.
There's nothing more to aspire to.
No, Ben.
Think about gummies and lifting.
What if you could lift gummies?
I could.
What?
Wait a minute.
Protein gummies.
Oh, the proteins.
We could be the proteins.
Protein gummies would be, that'd be gross.
That'd be disgusting.
You'd have to eat so many of them.
Jesus Christ.
Now, you know what would be funny?
Caffeinated gummies.
I could make caffeinated gummies,
and that wouldn't even be hard.
It'd be easy, in fact.
Yeah.
That would be cool.
Instead of having a drink to start the day, you have a gummy.
Yeah.
Why not?
I could.
I think I would be.
I think I have become,
since starting Slime and Punishment,
I think I am a faster artist than I was before.
I think I am faster, more efficient, better.
Now, however,
I have nothing that I want to do with it.
I have nothing that I want to draw.
I have no comics that I'm working on,
so it's just a waste.
Just a waste of a skill that I've gained.
I must say,
thank you very much for that birthday image you drew for me.
Yes, my pleasure.
That was really cool.
Thanks.
I really liked it.
I thought it came out pretty well.
I was pretty happy with it.
I'm glad you liked it.
Yeah.
It's got everybody.
I mean,
yeah, it's got flower head.
My boy.
The flower head.
Nobody draws flower head.
Nobody draws Katie.
Forgot.
That's true.
Another dark member of the Gibbonverse.
And the Lord of Ghosts with the little sparklers.
Yeah.
Very cute.
Thanks.
I had to go and look at some Lord of Ghost pages
to figure out exactly how big Lord of Ghosts is.
And I decided he is about as big as a person's torso,
more or less.
Yeah, I would say that.
You got the proportions quite well.
Yeah, I think so.
I had kind of imagined that he was about the size of the plush,
like less than a foot tall.
But no, he's a little bigger than that.
Like when he's sitting on the couch or on the sofa seat
in Flower Head's house,
he does take up like most of the cushion.
Yeah, he could fill a beanbag chair.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So that was interesting.
I was a little unsure,
I was a little unsure how big to make Red Man
because he seems to vary in size quite a bit.
I know that you drew,
I know that the big is like nine feet tall.
Yes.
Okay, big is nine feet tall.
Katie seems like she's fairly tall
and Flower Head seems somewhat tall as well.
So I made Katie and Flower Head about the same size.
I think I made Red Man about there.
I think I should have made him maybe a little bigger than them.
And then, I don't know,
I assume that they were maybe like six feet.
And then I made Katie.
Yeah, Gun Girl is like a five foot something.
Five foot five or something like that.
Flower Head, Katie are taller,
but they're not like absurdly tall
and Red Man is kind of, he's a big boy.
Okay, well if they're,
I mean in compared to them,
I mean then she's maybe like half,
maybe I made her a bit small, I don't know.
Well, wait.
Now I'm curious.
How big did I make them relative to each other?
She comes up to about,
she comes up to about chest height.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's fine.
That's great.
That's good.
I'm trying to scroll to where it was.
Oh, here it is.
Yeah, she's a, I mean she's,
her legs are like out.
Yeah, she wouldn't be a little taller
if she was standing straight up.
That's about right.
Yeah, she comes up to about like,
Flower Heads like arm pits or so.
That would, Red Man would be a bit bigger,
but like there's no like true size for him.
I never really thought, it's just sort of like,
he's like, what's his name from kill a kill?
The guy who's like big?
Is it Katakuri?
No, from kill a kill.
That guy's from One Piece.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
He's like the big guy with the blonde hair
and he's like one of the captains of this thing.
I know who you're talking about.
He fills the screen.
See, I was close.
He fills the screen based on like the scene he's in
and he doesn't really have like a fixed size.
Yeah. Yeah, that makes sense.
He's just as big as he needs to be
to fill the entire shot.
As big as he needs to be to like,
for intimidation purposes if he's supposed to be doing that.
And like Red Man is the same.
Whatever is the funniest size for him to be,
and it airs big.
And he's like, whoa, whoa.
I'm a big guy full of blood.
He's this big.
Yeah.
Red Man can be that big.
Yes, I started drawing that in like the morning.
And then I had to do the RFCK art stream
for the Death Furnaces contest,
which was a great contest.
There was some very impressive entries in that.
But then it got late.
And so I didn't finish it until your birthday was over.
Go men.
That's fine.
No, it's not fun.
No, I'm so stupid.
No, because it's like I go to bed and it's like us.
A nice birthday.
Got some nice art.
It was cute, fun.
And then I wake up and there's more.
But guess what?
It's not over.
It's not even over.
I'm going to be this age for an entire year.
It's my birth year.
The party's just getting started.
It was fun.
I spent a while on it because I wanted to include everyone.
There's probably more I could have included.
I could have included dog.
Yeah, dog.
Dog would have been nice, but he's not invited to human parties, I guess.
I mean, it's nice you drew so many of them.
Most people, it's like on commission sheets.
It's like, oh, you can cost this much to do this thing.
But if there's an extra character, it multiplicatively increases as the number of characters goes up.
Seven characters?
Oh, that's a thousand.
That's a million.
And so you drew a bunch of them.
I wanted to get them all in there.
Dammit, I'm trying to post it in the chat and I can't...
Oh, there it is.
They saved it over on the other side of my stupid desktop.
I'll just put this in here for Ellie as our fan.
Okay.
Yeah, I wanted to get them all in there.
I wanted to have Flowerhead because he's my boy.
I wanted to have Katie because she's got lore.
Yeah.
She's got lore that I'm invested in.
I had to have the pony.
I had to have the little hippo.
I almost forgot about hippo.
I almost forgot that hippo is his own character.
I think when I was looking up the reference to figure out how big Lord of Ghosts is, I remember...
Oh, yeah, hippo's actually in comics.
Okay, well, I guess he gets the spot.
And you got the pumpkin alley doing the pose from the game that you could play right now.
Yeah, they're really doing it.
Instead of holding a party favor or a piece of cake or a drink, she's just got alley over the head.
That's the party favor she's taken home.
And you got my giraffe right at the top.
What's her name?
You know, I was thinking about it.
I was calling her my giraffe OC for a long time.
She's sort of like, oh, what if I was a furry?
What if I was a giraffe?
I never really thought of a name.
I think her name is Lizzie, though.
I think I'm going to go with Lizzie.
I feel like I saw you say that somewhere.
I couldn't remember what it was.
I feel like I remember you saying, like, what if her name is this, haha, or something?
I think I was like going with like, if I like Lizzie's a cool name and people sort of assumed that I was changing my name to Lizzie.
And they started referring to me as that.
And I was like, you know, maybe actually, no, I don't want to be.
I like it, but I don't think that's me.
I don't think Lizzie is me.
But it is a good name.
Yeah, giraffe is Lizzie.
That's my final offer.
My foot's coming down, hoof down.
Now, now I know.
I'm putting my hoof down just like that one pony episode.
Do you think red man could kill iron will?
How much slime does iron will have?
Oh, I don't think he has any.
Yeah, so that's that's rough.
With that, I think if he had no slime, I feel like iron will would win because he would just like, if like, all you have to do is get like one good hidden and red man would just be like,
a balloon and red man would just pop like a balloon.
If he, if he, if he, with his horns, I think he would just like deflate like a, like a, like a punctured water balloon.
Yeah.
And all the blood would come out.
Yeah, all the blood comes flooding out.
Yeah.
Red man is.
When you, when you, when you fight red man, when you win, it's like that scene in the shining where the elevator doors open and all the blood just comes like rushing out.
Like you do, like you do not, you do not want to get in a situation where you have to kill red man.
Oh, all right.
All right.
So we got gun girl.
I could draw this, but I just wanted to explain it.
Red man and gun girl in the elevator in that Asuka Ray pose.
Shinji.
Yeah.
Like an Evangelion pose.
Then the shining scene and then gun girls in there.
You can see what happened.
It's just her.
She's covered in blood.
And the blood comes out and it's like, oh, we know what happened.
Yeah.
Well, I drew, I drew that in slime and punishment.
There's that scene of red man is singing on the, that tower on that one bridge in Boston.
He gets gun, gun girl shoots him in the back of the head from behind and he falls down and he hits the ground with a big like plop.
And there's just a big like wave of blood just covers phantom and strawberry.
Delightful.
What else can I say?
Love red man.
Yeah.
Uh, what do you, well, I've, as I said, like an hour ago, I got nothing to say.
What do you, I mean, do you think it's time for, for voicemails or can we, or can we pad this out?
No, we can pad, we can pad.
We can pad.
We can, we can, we can, we can, uh, we can talk about, we can talk about every character you didn't draw.
Starting with Clarissa Gunsmoke.
I forgot Clarissa.
I sketch, you know what, I sketched Clarissa.
How did you?
Yeah.
No shit.
Now I remember I was, I drew the heads in and I remember I drew, I remember I drew like the hat.
I drew a little sketch of the hat on a head and then I like, I hid the layer.
Oh fuck.
Yeah.
I hid the layer and I was like, I'll come back to this and then I forgot that that layer was there.
And I told, I guess I could, I guess I completely spaced on Clarissa Gunsmoke.
Damn, I forgot until you told me just now.
Oops.
Ah, it's okay.
I don't want to like, like, like show you for a drawing that you gave me before.
No, no, you're right.
No, you're right.
It's garbage.
It's trash.
Throw it away.
Uh, delete.
Uh, that's true though.
I totally, I did, I meant, I forgot.
I meant to, but it just didn't, it just didn't happen.
If, if Clarissa was on this, she's like seven feet tall.
So she'd be taller than Flowerhead.
She's taller than Flowerhead.
Is she taller than Redman?
Like, canonically?
In this image?
Uh, not canonically.
No, no, no.
Not, not in this image.
I mean like, in your mind, Zye.
In my mind.
I think he's a little taller than her, but mostly he's like a wide figure.
You wouldn't think of him as like a tall character more so as like a large circle.
Ah, I see.
So how tall, how tall is Clarissa?
Is she like seven feet tall?
Yeah, she's seven feet tall.
She's a tall girl.
Yeah.
Okay.
Sounds about right.
It was very helpful.
I was scrolling through you.
I scrolled back through your feed to see your height chart for Lizzie.
Oh yeah.
Which very clearly was like she is about, she's 18 feet tall.
So I'm like, okay.
Yeah.
So I'll have, I'll have Big come up to you about her like her rib cage or something like that.
Very clear, concise, easy to understand.
Yes.
Portions on that.
One third for the legs, one third for the body and then one third for the neck and the head.
Yeah.
I think I looked at like giraffe, like average heights.
And I think like for female giraffes, 18 feet is kind of normal.
So I just changed it.
Like if she was a real giraffe, her legs would just be like another pair of legs and she wouldn't have arms.
And that was just be how tall she is.
Yeah.
It looks like giraffe's height, 16 to 19 for a male adult, 14 to 17 for a, for a female adult.
So big.
So big and long.
Big and long.
Big and strong.
So ripped.
Does Lizzie lift?
I don't know if she lifts.
Giraffes normally lift.
I guess they lift their big head.
Sure.
They're big men.
All members of the animal kingdom get under the bar and pump iron.
Yeah.
Imagine someone that big getting under the bar.
They'd have to like lie across the road.
I've heard it said that like if a gorilla could like understand the, like the activity of like lifting weights for strength gain, they could bench like thousands of pounds.
Like they're so much stronger than humans are.
But you just, but you can't get them to do it because they're just not, they don't, they don't understand.
They don't want to.
They just want to sit in that big fat ass.
Believe me, they've tried.
They want to like do gorilla warfare.
They need to train the gorillas for combat.
Yeah.
But like these gorillas are so like fat and lazy.
They're like, I feel only we could whip these gorillas into shape.
Get them out there in the field.
Give them a gun.
Give them a little helmet, a little med pack and send them out with a mission.
I had a.
But they just, they don't, they don't have, they're not patriotic enough.
I'd love to play like a team fortress too, but with different types of monkeys, different apes.
Would they just play exactly like the classes already play?
Yeah, no, they would be like team fortress too just means like being like different classes for different roles.
So the gorilla would be the one that charges and smashes things.
And then the Gibbon would be the climbing one and swinging around.
So you mean like a class, a class based?
Class based first person shooter or first person puncher.
Based on different eight varieties.
Yeah.
Yeah, they would.
And the baboons and they would bite, I guess.
I guess they might throw, they might throw rocks or something.
Yeah, yeah.
The gorillas would like throw tires at each other.
And then there'd be the orangutans and they'd like, they dazzle the others with their flanges.
It'd be a flange dazzle button.
Yeah, they'd be like a bard.
They'd like give passive buffs.
They'd dazzle the opponents.
Yeah, blind them.
They're just there to be a pretty face.
Apes, apes are, I gotta say it, apes are horrifying.
Apes, just generally.
Yeah, I find apes like quite disgusting.
I don't know if I've ever made that clear.
I do not like looking at them.
Huh.
I thought, I always thought they were like, I don't know, lumpy and funny looking and like relatable because you can see they have like a sort of expressions that are almost similar to humans.
I find them, I find them off-putting.
I find them off-putting and weird because of like, yeah, they're kind of like a human, but they're like dumb and like ugly and like dirty and like lumpy and gross and then like, ugh.
But like a silverback gorilla is like a peak, like peak masculinity.
I guess.
Like this is what a real man looks like with that stance.
It's actually not true.
It's actually false.
With those huge shoulders and that like arched back.
Yeah, I mean.
They got the puppy arms.
It's so fucking funny.
Sure.
I mean, listen, there's lots, there's lots to praise about apekine.
Don't get me wrong.
They're just, they're just not for me.
They're just not my cup of tea.
I don't like chimpanzees.
I think chimpanzees have too big of ears.
They're, they're listening, they're listening to me and they're listening to too much.
They got too much info.
Are, are like, um, are like lemur, are lemurs apes?
They're not.
No, they're monkeys.
I think smaller varieties are classed as monkeys.
They are monkeys.
Okay.
I mean, I like lemurs.
They're, they're, they're, they're far enough from human that they don't like.
Yeah.
They're more like squirrels.
They don't like creep me out in the way that like an ape, like an ape does.
Yeah.
They look, they do look more like a squirrel.
I guess they are sort of simian.
Yeah.
They are wet nose mammals of the super family limeroidia.
Are they monkeys?
I think the difference is the monkeys have tails and apes do not, but maybe there's more to
it.
Okay.
Lemurs share, okay.
They are primates.
Hmm.
They are not, they are neither monkeys nor apes.
They are, they evolved independently from monkeys and apes.
So like, they're kind of their own thing, you know.
This is another primate wikipedia moment.
They just looked up the Barbary macaque and the bonnet, the bonnet macaque and the Barbary
macaque.
Now they're too human.
I don't like looking at them.
I don't want to see that.
Gibbons are apes.
Oh yeah.
They don't have tails.
Right.
It's like on ape.
Do apes have tails?
Is that the defining feature of ape kind?
That's always how I've always understood it is like, you see all these primates, they
don't have tails and you think of them as apes and then the little funny ones that have
tails, they're monkeys, but I don't actually know if that's true at all.
I'm going to google that exact question.
Ape tail question mark?
Nope.
First result.
The quickest way to tell the difference between a monkey and an ape is the presence or absence
of a tail.
Almost all monkeys have tails.
Apes do not.
Well, there you go.
So I guess there are some tailless monkeys.
That's interesting.
Well, now we know.
We've learned a lot here today.
And then all of those apes, they play monkey football and apes take two and then they use
their ape strength to smash that ball.
Let's smash that like button.
Now a sensible, sober, reasonable and not too fantastical game of soccer or football
as you like between between different kinds of apes.
Now that would be something.
You know, you got your, I don't know, I think at a rangutan would make a good goalie because
he's got really long arms.
Yeah.
And do they ever do funny things with the planets of the apes movies?
Was it always like, we hate being in a cage and now we're going to fucking kill you and
beat the shit out of you?
Do they ever play like monkey football?
I don't know.
They made like three of those movies.
Wait, wait, do you mean the old ones or like the newer ones?
Any of them.
I feel like the newer ones did have like wacky stuff happen in them.
I don't know.
I only saw the first one.
I remember the first one.
I remember Draco Malfoy said the line.
He said, you damn dirty ape.
And the ape remembered and he beat the shit out of him.
And then they smashed like the, the, the, the rotine like gate fence and they used the,
the spikes on the top of the fence as like spears and they threw them as like, oh fuck.
I guess an ape could do that.
I guess they could.
Oh, they, they could do a lot of things.
You'd be, you'd be, you'd be shocked.
They could bench press a thousand pounds.
Easily.
Rip you in half.
Rip you in fucking.
The apes rose up, but just to win all the sports competitions, they didn't kill anyone.
That's the difference between other apes and humans is that apes are like, humans are,
humans are efficient.
Humans are weaker, but we're way more efficient.
Like we, like for our body mass, we have to eat a lot less than apes do, which gives
us like free time, like, because we don't have to spend like all of our time hunting.
Yeah.
It's like the, it's like the, you know, the fastest land mammal is a cheetah unless you
account for humans inventing the bicycle and then we're faster.
Well, actually a human, a human could hunt, could catch a cheetah because a cheetah can't
maintain that speed for a long time.
A human can maintain like a base speed for like hours, days, a cheetah like can run really
fast really quickly, but it gets tired and like over a long period, the human will catch
up to it because it just, it just can't, it doesn't have the stamina.
Yeah, but also a human could have like a fighter jet and like zoom and like bomb it.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
True.
Also true.
Yeah.
Fair.
And if it's, and if it's just about, I mean, if you don't care about like catching it and
like cooking it, if you, if you're okay, like blowing it to smithereens and like, yeah,
we have a lots of tools at our disposal for that sort of thing.
Did you see that image?
I don't know if I posted it anywhere.
It was something I saw on Twitter that was like nine images, you have to pick two of
these groups of animals, there's like five gorillas, seven oxen, 10,000 rats, 50 vultures,
one guy with a rifle, five alligators, three bears, and two lions or four lions.
And you had to pick two and make them fight each other.
No, pick two.
And those are the guys that are defending you and you have to fight the rest.
Let me find the image so you can, you can, you can think about it.
Mike.
I want to know, I want to know your, your, your reasoning.
I think I have an answer, although I guess I'll take a look at the image to be sure.
All right, there it is.
Hmm.
So it's not as, it's not as simple as you may think, because as soon as you pick two,
you have to think about all the other ones and how they're going to catch you.
Hmm.
My, yeah.
Okay.
My first thought, and I'm not sure if I believe it, my first thought was, um, to go as, like
as diverse as possible, like the two opposite ends of the spectrum.
So one guy with a rifle and the 10,000 rats, and the 10,000 rats can swarm anything that
might be coming at me and basically distract them for long enough for the guy with the
rifle to pick them off.
Uh, I mean, I'm not, would that work?
Like would the 10,000 rats, would three bears coming at me even notice 10,000 rats like crawling
on them?
Yeah.
It's hard to imagine 10,000 rats.
That's a lot of rats.
It's a lot of rats.
I feel like there would be enough rats to at least swarm all of the big things, like
the gorillas, the lions, the wolves, the bears, and the gators, and the ox or the bulls.
Rats can't do shit about the falcon or the 50 falcons.
And I always thought like, if there's 50 falcons or eagles or whatever, um, the only
guy that can take care of them is the guy with the gun, but he needs to hit 50 shots
and get all of them before they swarm him because if he's under attack by 50 eagles,
he's not going to be able to focus and shoot anything.
Like he's going to be swatting them away or running.
Do you, do you think you have to pick the falcons just because nothing can effectively
defend against them?
I would always pick the gorillas because I imagine the falcon coming down and then the
gorilla just slapping it out of the air.
I just, I just like that because they have opposable thumbs.
They have the ability to like slap things and grab the rest of them, like the bears,
the wolves, the lions, they, they don't have hands.
They have to bite that stuff and that's harder.
The 50, 50 falcons, I mean, I don't know how effective they are.
I know from the animorphs that such birds can like rake eyes and like pluck eyes out.
So they might be able to like blind the gorillas at which point they could no longer defend
you effectively at all.
I don't, I don't know if they would could do that.
I'm not sure if like, if they'd be able to do that before the gorillas like swatted
them all out of the air.
Okay, I'm actually going, I'm circling back to the rats though because I'm looking it
up and a rat weighs like, it kind of depends on the, on the variety of rats.
Some rats can weigh up to a pound.
And so, and like a bear, well, a, well a black bear weighs 600 pounds.
These are brown bears.
How much does a grizzly bear weigh?
A grizzly bear weighs 600 pounds.
Wait, wait, a black bear and a grizzly bear weigh the same amount?
No, that's, that can't be right.
Black bears are small, comparatively.
I thought so too, but I mean, that's, it's telling me that they both weigh about 600.
Okay, grizzly bears can weigh upward of 700.
Either way though, even if they weighed a thousand pounds, 10,000 rats is way more biomass
than, you know, three, three grizzly bears.
Like, that's by far the most animal.
So like, if they, if they're aggressive, I feel like 10,000 rats is enough that they
could swarm over a bear and like, yeah, I think the 10,000 rat, well, they could beat
one bear, they could maybe even beat three bears, but then would there be anything left
of them afterwards to deal with everything else?
Yeah, it's, it's, I feel like the question is impossible.
Like you, you're gonna die.
I don't think, I don't think any two, yeah, I don't think any two of these guys could,
could beat all the rest.
Like the, I think logically 10,000 rats and the 50 Falcons would be good to like pick
off.
Wait a minute.
The smaller numbers of more dangerous things.
Wait a minute, but then, but then there's a guy with a gun who can just shoot you.
That's true, but we don't know how close he is.
So if, if we're like in a, in a separate field, separate sides of a field and I send the Falcons
out to get the guy, he needs to shoot all of them and then the rest of the, like he'll
get a few, then the rest of them will get his eyes out and then he can't do shit.
And it's sort of, I guess the same with everything else.
If they, if the Falcons can get to their eyes and like blind them, the rats can like swarm
them, do the rest.
Probably maybe.
Yeah.
I think that's, yeah.
If the guy, I mean, if the guy with the gun has a clear shot, like you're just fucked.
Like, like nothing can, can defend you from that.
You got to pick defensively.
You got to pick on the basis of like, I'll take whatever thing I least want coming after
me.
Gun guy is a strong contender for that one, for that role.
Like lions are pretty fast, wolves are pretty fast, gorillas and bears, gorillas are pretty
fast actually when they get going.
I guess everything is pretty fast.
If it turns out to like, if I'm, if I have agency and I can do fighting, I probably would
be more able to like, agilely get away from like a bull than I would a lion or a gorilla.
But I feel like my, my abilities, I would need them to be killed in order for me to
actually survive.
So the rats would just at least over, like a war of attrition, the rats would win just
because of the sheer numbers and then they, they, they, the, the rats would pile on top
of each other and they become like a rat mech.
The rat king.
Yeah.
And then of course there would be a giant rat that makes all the rules.
So yeah, does the 10,000 include one giant one that makes the rules that might tip it
in their favor?
Ah, that's too much.
No, there's no, no two of these can stop the other seven.
It's just, it's just, it just can't, it can't be done.
The rest is coming to kill you.
Why?
Why do they want to kill me?
Why is this happening?
Yeah, there's a point when you read this and you're like, why do they defend me and
why are they trying to kill me?
Animals don't act like this.
What do I have, what do I have that two of these animals want to like get on my good
side that I'll give them and that the others want to like kill me and get?
Like what's, what's, what's so special about me?
A little dog treats.
I got Scooby Snacks.
You got, your pockets are just full of snacks.
The snacks are so good that the guy wants them as well.
Yeah, he's like, it's his favorite.
They just smell, the bears have their noses in the air like sniffing like, what's that?
Then they come across like a pack of walls, it's like, oh, you smell it too?
Let's go, let's go see what it is.
Let's team up.
Like we got to, we got to work, if we work together, you know, like all 15 of you wolves
and all three of us bears, we can each get a little morsel.
We can each get a little snack roll of whatever.
It's only a, it's only a pocket full of snacks.
But it's so good though.
It's exactly what you want.
Oh, hit the spot perfectly.
Simsie says 50 hawks and five gorillas.
I mean, yeah.
I just feel like if you don't pick the rats, how, yeah, 50 hawks could not, they could
feel like 50 rats, I don't know, every 10 seconds maybe.
Yeah, most of the swarm would get to you and like 5,000 rats, the 5,000 rats that
manage to get to you, like they're going to kill you.
You're going to get nod to death.
Maybe I choose the guy and then, I don't know, the, the, whatever, the gorilla.
And then I give the guy the snacks and I run away.
So they're coming after him.
So it's just one guy with a gun and it's 5,000 against everything else.
Yeah, that's actually, that's it.
You just disguise him and I pick the guy, disguise him as me and then I leave him and
I take his shoes so that I'm faster than him and then I run away and leave him behind
to receive the brunt of it.
Genius.
Are those, are those bulls?
Is that what those are?
Yeah, I think so.
Is it oxen or?
Yeah.
They're, they're, they're male cows and they're charging that you in a, in a, what do you call it?
Matador sort of style.
If you had a piece of red cloth, you'd be golden.
I talked, I talked, I talked last week about my favorite animal, the oryx from the bible
and, or not, no, the ream and how it might be an oryx or an ox or a bull or something.
But I don't actually, I don't really know that if, okay, I'm looking, oxen are like big fat
things.
Yeah, they're, they're lumbary bumbers.
Oxen are big lumbary bumbers.
Bulls are a little more, I guess, normal looking.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oxen are bred for pulling the, the plow and, and bulls are just there to fuck the cows.
Yeah, I mean, yeah.
And I guess you can eat them.
I guess you can eat them.
You can eat the bull at some point.
You eat them.
Oh yeah.
And you make a steak and kidney pie out of them.
You can only make two of them though.
They only got two kidneys.
They got a lot of steak, but only two kidneys.
It's a, it's a rare treat.
I will make a gummy kidney and carve it up and make a pie out of it.
Gummy pies.
Yeah, sure.
Why not?
Meat, meat substitute, little cubes of chopped up meat, little steaks, but gummy and they
flavored with beef powder or whatever the fuck.
Okay, I'll show up to my neck.
I'll show up to a fourth of July barbecue and be like, Hey guys, you know, I have a nice,
you know, vet meat substitute for you and I'll take out like chicken drumsticks and
like steaks and stuff that I just made out of gummy.
Now let's throw, I'll throw it on the grill and it will just immediately melt and just drip through.
And everyone will say then.
I'm imagining that they're like the small, like, like tiny little pellet-sized chicken wings.
Oh, like, like a tiny little, like a tiny little, you know, like.
And they just fall in between the cracks of the grill.
Like, like stay on there.
Like the SpongeBob gummy Krabby Patty, like it's tiny.
Just, just tiny, just tiny.
I'll just grab a handful.
It's like a little handful of like gummy chicken.
Just scatter them on the fire.
And everyone will say, Ben, why are you like vegetarian now or something?
And I'll say, no, no, it's made with pork gelatin.
No, no, it's an animal product.
There's no, there's no reason.
And the fire goes blue.
And gaze into it and see your future.
And it's an image of you eating.
At the barbecue.
What if you could see your future, but it was only the most uninteresting moment?
Like, like, oh, tomorrow you'll be on the toilet.
Here's what that looks like.
Nice.
Tomorrow you'll eat.
Oh, oh, what's that?
Oh, it looks like tomorrow I'm going to eat.
Oh, a ham and cheese wrap.
Oh, just like today.
Oh, cool.
Nice.
Sounds can't, I can't wait.
It's going to be delicious.
I can't wait.
This is getting me excited.
As soon as this podcast is over, I'm going to go,
I'm going to make another gummy batch.
I'm going to see, I'm going to try it again with less gelatin.
I discovered that I can reduce the gelatin and be fine.
And that's good.
I'm going to try and I'm going to try and increase the fiber
and see if the less gelatin still works.
With the increased fiber.
And if it does, I'll be like, perfect, beautiful.
Do you have like exact measurements for like grams and stuff
of how much you're putting in?
No, I don't have, I don't have like gram measurements.
I use like tablespoons.
Well, I mean, those are exact measurements
if they're like consistent.
Yeah, I mean, I do have a, I do have a specific recipe.
That is like sort of my baseline now
that I was like taking that baseline
and like making slight changes too.
And it's like seeing how it, I took that and I was like,
okay, will it work with less gelatin?
And I tried it with less gelatin.
I was like, yeah, it's still worked.
Okay, cool.
Because I would like to have, I'd like to have the,
basically the gelatin is just there to give it consistency.
So the less, the least gelatin I can get away with
while still keeping that consistency, it's like, okay, good.
Any more gelatin than that would be a waste.
And I would like to have as little water as possible
because the water doesn't taste like anything.
And you get the best consistency with the least water.
It becomes like the chewiest and I like it chewy.
So, and then the least sugar is possible
because that's calories and calories are bad.
So my goal is less gelatin, less water, less sugar, more fiber
and try and find the optimal mixture there
that gives the best consistency, the best flavor.
And it doesn't like become like, if you use too much fiber,
it kind of becomes kind of soft, sort of falls apart,
sort of becomes kind of mushy.
Like, well, that's, you know, that's not what you want.
I guess you just have to keep doing like,
all things in harmony.
I guess you have to just keep doing the scientific method
and like changing one thing at a time
to see if that makes a difference, negative or positive
and trial and error your way to the perfect gum.
Nobody told me,
ugh, nobody told me that the scientific method,
they had to do it over and over again.
Nobody, nobody told me I would have to do more than one experiment.
I thought I could just read my book and then do it immediately.
I thought, I was just like, wait, I thought, you know,
it's like rabbit said in Poo's grand adventure, you know,
if it says so, so it is.
I thought I could just, just write it down and be like, okay, I'm done.
And there would be nothing left to learn.
You're telling me I have to like gather information
and like form a hypothesis and then test the hypothesis?
Yes.
No.
Well, I will do that then.
Because I care.
Because I care about my work.
I am, I am, I'm very, I'm very happy.
You become a gummy wizard when you get the right recipe.
Until then, you're a gummy apprentice.
I have a recipe and I would consider it a success.
And now it's just like, okay, but is there other,
what marginal improvements can I make to like perfect it?
That's, that's the goal.
The frustrating thing, the frustrating thing is when I try to do it,
I always try to do like, okay, add more sugar,
add more sugar to make it like more candy-like.
But every time I do that, it becomes goo.
Like if you put too much sugar in it, it doesn't work at all.
It just comes out as goo.
It's like, there's, there's a line.
There's a, there's a threshold that I'm crossing.
I want to find like the perfect just enough
so I can get the maximum like candy nests to it without like
going over that threshold and it just becomes goo.
It's so, it's so delicate.
Such a fine, fine line, such a fine process of refinement.
It's beautiful.
Anyway, that's what I'm going to do as soon as this podcast is over.
Do you want to start voicemails?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, we have a modest amount this week.
I'm on Speakpipe.
Do you see them?
Yep.
All right.
Looks like our first one is called My Deepest Gratitude.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben, I don't know how I didn't know about DigiBro's opinion of Netflix's cuties before,
but thank you so much for bringing up on the podcast.
I'm so fucking glad that now I know for real, I have confirmation
that DigiBro is in fact not into black little girls.
And I, I don't know how I lived without having this information before.
It's amazing.
It's perfect.
Thank you so much.
I forget what that was from, but I remember the clip of maybe saying-
It's not, it's not from anything.
It just, it just is its own thing.
Was it just in like a Twitter video?
I, maybe it was on Twitter.
Yeah, I guess it wasn't on YouTube.
I remember it was during the MayisDigibro arc, which technically never ended and continues.
It's just the way she says that line.
It's the way she says it and the way that like-
I mean, there's the line itself.
I mean, there's every, there's everything that she's saying in the video,
which is, which is like vile.
I don't even remember what she says, but I can imagine.
There's, there's everything that she says.
There's the, that's bad enough.
There's the context that she lays out for it, which is like, she's, she's talking to the IBS
crowd, which I don't exactly know who that is, but I think it's like a killstream group of people.
So she's talking to the killstream people, which is also bad that she's like having this
conversation with these, with these demons.
And then on top of that, I think kind of like the thing that sticks out to me the most about it is like
the confident way that she thinks she is mimicking the mannerisms of the quote-unquote
character of DigiBro and she thinks she's nailing it, but like not even close.
She's just yelling, like she's just yelling and she thinks she's doing something with it.
And it's so amazing.
It's beautiful.
It really is just a classic that can never be topped.
And you're welcome, voicemailer.
Next one is called Did You Know?
Three, two, one, go.
Did you know that?
Did you, did you know?
I did, thanks.
I didn't thank you for the knowledge.
Next one is called Grading.
Three, two, one, go.
I give Ben St's grading system a five out of ten.
What's my grading system?
I don't know.
I remember.
Shit.
I don't remember what this is in regards to.
Sorry.
Next one is called Getting the Timelines Straight, but it's straight with an eight like Briska.
Three, two, one, go.
Also, what's the first procrastinator's forecast?
What do you mean also?
The second reticon, because you'll never mention it until one reticon until the third.
What?
Maybe this guy left a voicemail that we did last week, and then this is another one.
I'm sorry.
That's following on from it, but I can't remember what they said.
Is he asking if the first procrastinator's was after the second reticon?
You know, I'm not even sure.
If I'm not even sure at all.
We did that.
We had the horse cast.
The answer is no.
And the procrastinators had existed for a while before any such thing as radcon occurred.
Yeah.
I honestly forget the order of events.
We were the horseshoe crew.
We had the horse cast.
We went to Bronycon, or you went to Bronycon, but then I went to Bronycon at some point.
And then after that, we decided to do radcons.
That's all well.
That's all well before radcon happened.
No, I'm very confident the PCP was a thing before the first radcon, which, you know,
the first radcon, we didn't even call it radcon at the time, right?
Like, we just all went to Trixie's house for some reason, I think.
I think, no, I think we came up with the name like the rad conference.
It was a conference rather than a convention.
We kept saying that.
Were you that you were there at the first one?
Yeah, that was the first one.
Second one was when Davoo and Munchie came, and Jeff, Loll.
And Tom.
Tom was not at the first one, was he?
I don't think so.
Wait, so the second one was the one where Davoo made the shirts?
Yes.
No.
I don't remember Davoo.
No, radcon one.
I recorded Sonichu 101 was at radcon one because I didn't do a lecture at radcon two,
and I always regretted it.
Right, that was the plebe and the weeb radcon.
Yes, radcon two was the plebe and the weeb radcon.
Radcon one, but I had the shirt, but I had the shirt in the Sonichu video.
I guess Davoo was there.
So Davoo was there.
Was Davoo living there at the time?
Yes, she must have.
That's right.
Yes, that's right.
We had moved in.
We had just moved in, and so me and Davoo and Trixie were there and...
Everyone else came.
Everyone else just came just because?
Was there no like...
Well, there was no like overarching like let's do a specific thing.
It's just like we like hanging out at Bronycon,
but Bronycon only happens once a year or whatever.
Let's just do it whenever.
Let's meet up whenever.
Was it like maybe the same year after the Bronycon, in fact?
Was it just like basically the same time as the Bronycon?
Like Bronycon ended, so we all went back to that house and just hung out?
Bronycon was in the summer of that year, and I think at the winter,
like November or something, we came together.
And then January or February, the next year, was Radcon 2 or like March.
It was close to the first one.
I feel like we've rehashed this a few times,
and like this is not the first time I've like struggled to remember,
like why did Radcon even happen?
I think you're right, yeah.
Bronycon was in the summer.
Radcon was in the like winter,
or Radcon was like a little like a couple months later.
And then Radcon 2 was only like six months after that,
because they had made the plans for the plebeant.
At Radcon 1, they conceived of and planned out the plebeant and the weeb,
and then a few months later they did it,
and that was the excuse for Radcon 2, etc., etc.
And Radcon 3, I remember coming in at some point to you and Munchy
sitting in a closet conceiving endless war.
And the butt and everything.
F3? F3?
I think so.
Like before that, there was arm retrieval.
That was the thing Munchy was doing.
Yeah.
And arm retrieval con happened at the end of Radcon 3.
Yes. Yes, you're right.
Because Radcon 3 was in winter in 2018.
It was like January 2018.
And then Endless War came online in April of 2018.
So yeah, that would have been before.
Wow. Imagine that.
Wacky.
Wow.
And then Radcon 4, we created COVID and we infected the world.
We made, we sure did.
And I gotta say, things have gotten better than expected.
Anyway, but anyway, the PCP was already a thing.
The PCP was the thing, there was the horseshoe crew.
Now the PCP was already the PCP well before the first Radcon,
that's for sure.
Like the horse days, the horse days were over by then.
Next one is called Ray Tracing, more like Gay Tracing.
Three, two, one, go.
People are adding realistic lighting to N64 games.
And I just have to wonder what the fuck is the point to all this.
They're just making the games look a lot worse.
Like they were created with an art style in mind.
And they're just spitting on the faces of all the artists
who had to craft the games to look a certain way
because they were designed with that aesthetic in mind.
Do people even think this shit looks cool?
Because it doesn't.
And if you do, then I guess you're just fucking stupid.
Well, there's no reason to be so evil about it, but I...
I have not seen what this guy's talking about.
I don't know exactly either.
I guess maybe it's mods or something.
It was like Mario 64, realistic lighting.
It just makes old games look bad because they didn't have the technology to do...
How would you even add realistic lighting?
How would you even add realistic lighting to Mario?
I don't know.
Would you make everything shiny?
I mean, people have made like texture pack things in Minecraft
that completely change the way the game looks.
So I think you can mod stuff around if you have the code.
But I mean, do you mean like, I don't know,
light coming off of like torches in the castle or something?
Or like what?
I mean, even just something as simple as the sunlight being a point that casts shadows.
They didn't have that in other games.
The shadows were like objects instead of like procedurally generated
based on positioning of things.
But yeah, I generally dislike realistic lighting.
As like a default, it makes it look gooder idea.
It's an aesthetic that can look good if that's what you're going for,
but like it is not a blanket upgrade.
It's not a straight upgrade to the alternative, which is not that.
I haven't seen it, what this guy's talking about,
but I'm sure that it can't be an improvement on, you know,
just like a well considered art style.
As like a technical exercise, I can see how maybe it's like,
how what if we added ray tracing realistic lighting?
I doubt many people, I mean, unless I'm wrong and people do think this,
but I feel like people aren't going to be like, ah, finally, you know,
finally I can play the game and it looks good now
because it's got realistic lighting.
Oh, they're like the non realistic shadow physics always like bug me so much.
Like I couldn't, I just couldn't handle it.
People pog at, I don't know, technical stuff, I guess.
I guess they like it.
I've never understood.
I can't lie and say that seeing something as intricately
like detailed and well lit and beautiful as something like, I don't know,
blood borne, right?
That has realistic lighting, but it's also extremely artistically designed.
Like all of the things you would see and the way like,
like realistic shadows and stuff play well in that sort of a setting.
It doesn't make it worse or better.
It's just sort of, it works.
It's a tool.
I guess that's the main thing.
Realistic lighting is a tool, just the same as any artist's tool that you could use.
And you don't have to use it all the time.
A lot of games look good with it, but not all of them, especially not all the ones.
I just, I find it so, it seems alien.
It seems alien to me to be like, like excited about something like that,
like realistic lighting, like ray tracing, technical specs.
I don't even think people are excited about it.
I think they're just so used to video games looking that way,
that when they come across one that doesn't,
they feel like there's something missing when they're, I don't know.
Who can know the truth?
Like it's off-putting to see an older visual style,
because it's just games don't look like that anymore.
I guess so.
I mean, oblivion objectively looks quite ugly from today's standards,
but even though the textures are kind of blurry and the distance,
the pop-in draw distance is very low, and there's no anti-aliasing on like leaves of trees,
I still look around and I can see that that's like a beautiful image that I'm looking at.
It's just low fidelity in some areas.
A high AHD like crispier version wouldn't ruin it, but it wouldn't,
it's not like necessary for me to enjoy what they're going for artistically.
Some of these like, especially since I've been like riding my horse instead of first traveling,
I get to like see the scenic route and be looking and like, wow,
they thought about how the imperial city would look up on this hill,
looking down on the road towards like Shaden Hall or whatever.
It's like, yeah.
I think at the time of oblivion, it was a novel thing that the mountains in the distance
were actually physically there that you could walk up to and climb
before they would just be a skybox thing.
And it's sort of like a marvel of the time that like you could actually go to all of these
mountains that actually physically exist as 3D things.
I think you'll never, you can never make like Mario 64 or even oblivion,
like you can never make it look like a modern game.
Like you would basically have to just completely remake it to accomplish something like that.
Like you'll never be like, oh, well, it doesn't look like games look nowadays, but I have,
oh, by changing this and that about it, I have made it look like a modern game.
You just can't do it.
You're always going to have to put up with or, you know, accept some amount of,
oh, this game looks old because it is old.
And there's just nothing you can do about that.
I think there's also a thing with like remakes of games that are in a cartoony style made
in an era where things were low poly like Crash Bandicoot.
Newer versions of Crash Bandicoot don't look bad.
They are different and they're different in a way that I don't particularly like.
But I don't hate, you know, I don't think it's a worse Crash Bandicoot.
Necessarily is no like objective like, oh, more polygons made it bad because he had
less polygons when he was designed.
It's just that the less polygon Crash Bandicoot looks great still.
You don't need a HD version of him to play the game and have fun.
But the HD version of like the remastered Crash games,
I haven't actually played those particular ones.
I played the Spyro remasters.
They're still good.
There's nothing wrong with them.
And I don't mind that they did that.
But I do mind when people say that there's like a preferred like better version.
Like you have to play the one that's the remaster because it's HD.
Like there's no.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's it's just a different.
It's just it's an apples and oranges thing.
That's how I feel about that.
That's how I feel about Mega Man.
Like I just I just don't I've been starting to appreciate the like later graphical style.
Like I don't I used to hate the like higher resolution sprites
unlike the PlayStation games like X4 and Onward.
I used to hate them.
I've sort of been like, it's not so bad.
But I do think like it looked perfect on the SNES 16 bit.
It does not.
I don't think it looks better.
I definitely don't think it looks better in any of the later more high tech consoles.
Even though even though they like fucking the resolution is like 10,000 times better.
Oh, it's more detailed.
All the frame rates are like, yeah, so what?
It's it's very easy for me.
That's fine and all, I guess.
It's very easy for me to like think of the higher resolution versions of these things as worse.
Because they're not they're not original and they're just graphics over art style.
But genuinely, it's not always the case.
This is sometimes you can like keep the art style basically intact or the feeling of the art style.
And like just do it a different way with modern tools and it's it's good.
It just doesn't it should not diminish the past because the past looked good at the time.
It still does stop me if I said this exact thing before.
But like I came to appreciate the X4's graphics more because at first I'm like,
oh, like the higher res sprites, so many frames of animation, so smooth,
is this really necessary?
Who needs all this?
But then I played X5, which has the same sprites, but like much worse art direction.
Like some of the backgrounds in X5 just look wrong.
Like they took like a high resolution, well, not a high, you know,
they took like a photograph or something and they just like scanned it.
And they just put it as a background object and the lighting doesn't match.
It looks like a bad Photoshop job.
It sucks.
Like they kind of just made X5 look bad.
And then suddenly I'm like, oh, they actually they actually did fine with X4.
Like it didn't it didn't suck the way this sucks.
Like I can't I can't believe I can't believe how bad some things in X5 look like.
They were just they thought like, oh, well, we got high resolution.
We got more we got more pixels on that we can do anything we want.
Oh, we can just have the final boss be a big PNG in the background.
It's great though, because we can fit because we because because our game is in 480p now.
And it's going to look like, oh, this is going to stand the test of time.
Like that's what they thought.
Hmm. Sloppy.
You there?
Yep.
Okay, excuse me.
I have no Mega Man thoughts.
That's that's all right.
I think we've I think we're on the same page.
Next one is called Ben's Weekly Reminder play Delta Broom chapter two.
Okay.
Next one is called talk about pirates.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, did you read the new one piece from a couple weeks ago?
No, pretty crazy, right?
Yes.
Look, I just want to hear someone talk about one piece, people who I like,
people who aren't Ben's obnoxious pseudo intellectual little brother.
Thank you.
You know, I mean, I mean, you know, that's, you know, that's a valid opinion.
If that's your opinion.
Ben, Ben, I understand that's fair.
All right.
It's valid.
Yeah.
I at the, I'm not sure exactly which one they're talking about.
They made this thing yesterday.
They're saying a few weeks ago.
I think they could be referring to any, any number of different channels.
But the the the 1.0 arc is essentially over now.
Oh, I should, I should catch up then because I they are in the phase where it's like,
ah, the fighting has concluded and let's all think about what's happening next.
And like the the lull in action.
I basically now and partying and all that.
I was like one chapter past Nika, I think.
So that's that's as far as I got.
So I should catch up.
So specifically what they're talking.
Wait, we did talk about one piece.
We talked about the the gender bathroom, whatever stuff.
Oh, yeah, we did.
We did.
So, I mean, you know, that's, I mean, it's if that's what you're talking about.
Um, voice mailer.
Um, so we can talk a little bit about pirates.
We talk a little bit.
Uh, I, I don't know what else there is.
Like, uh, they did it.
They punched the guy and they won.
Oh, no, spoilers, spoilers.
God.
Um, uh, in the newspapers, the newspaper came and all the big numbers arrived with their
were there more zeros or at the very least I shunt tell did the or did the number in front
of all the zeros increment up somewhat perhaps.
Oh, who can say nobody knows.
In fact, I actually forgot I should reread it long.
Well, I'll I should catch up with that.
Next one is, oh, it's a it's a vocaru link.
So let me know.
The the the one piece is on a one month break right now, I think, and it's going to come back
with the lead into the next arc.
So I'm excited for that.
Very exciting.
Delightful.
It's now now's as good a time as any, I guess, to, uh, to pick up.
Oh, wait.
Yeah, they said they said specifically is like the final arc of one piece is
Oh, I saw that announcement.
And crazy.
That's insane.
Yeah, people are saying like what it'll be the but it'll be the longest arc.
Yeah, because I think the one hour took like six years.
Six.
Yeah, it could have.
I haven't been paying attention.
It took it took a few years at least.
It took at least two years.
Yeah.
And yeah, I think that is the one so far.
And I and I fucking thought I thought the fucking fish, not Fishman Island.
Um, what's the underwater one?
That's Fishman Island.
No.
Is it Shao Shao body?
Wait, no.
Sorry, I was thinking of our long park.
Yeah, you're right.
Fishman.
I thought Fishman Island was long.
That was the longest at the time.
Punk hazard.
No, no, no.
Dressrosa was the longest since since the Fishman Island.
Was dressrosa longer than Wano?
No.
No, but Wano is now the longest, I think.
Yeah, he just he just keeps making them longer and longer.
Yeah.
It's just the way it's act five, act six, act six, act six.
Oh, God, it is.
It's just like that.
Well, it's not just like that.
Just exactly.
Yeah, things I expect to happen in the final arc of one piece.
Elbeth, the giant island will be integral.
Usopp will tell the tale of meeting Dorian Baroggi and their pirate captains,
and then they'll be like, oh, Usopp, God, Usopp.
Giant King Usopp or something.
It'd be very funny.
I hope you're right about that.
I mean, it's it's been building up for so long.
The fact that Usopp was friends, made friends with Dorian Baroggi way back in like
the alabaster arc or like the beginning of the grand line.
And then he met the Omo and Kashi at like Impel Down, the two like Frankie guys.
Yeah.
Who are also giants.
And it's like, ah, and then he made friends with Hajrudin,
who is now part of the Straw Hat Grand Fleet.
And it's like, oh, all these giants who like Usopp,
and they've got to go to Elbeth because Big Mom wants to go there.
And Big Mom's, I don't think she's dead.
I think she's going to come back.
This is going to be like a war.
There's going to be a war about it.
And there's probably going to be a war about it.
Yeah.
Catechery's going to come back.
It's going to be some sort of big Elbeth thing leading into a race to Raftel.
Because at this point, I think the Straw Hats have all the pieces of the map they need to find,
you know, that all the road pornoglyphs are at least, I think, in their possession in some form,
either written down or like physical.
They know how to get to Raftel.
And then everyone's going to be there.
Everyone's going to go.
And everyone's going to fight.
And everyone's going to die.
I don't know what's going to happen.
There's so many moving parts.
But I think the beginning will be Elbeth because we've got to see that.
That's been like built up since giants have been like mentioned in One Piece.
Yeah.
I mean, for sure.
It's one of those things like Laboon that's like, well, you know,
that's just been an essential character moment that needs to pay off or what was even the point.
There's all the ancient weapons.
There's the history of the world that Niko Robin is piecing together.
There's Blackbeard and his plans and what he's got going on.
There's the Revolutionary Army.
Like what's happened to them?
What happened to the attack on Marine for not Marine for the marriage war?
Like what happened to like Sabo and everyone?
Are they OK?
God, there's there's God, there's so much.
Yeah, this last if this is the last arc, it is going to be like 10 fucking years long.
It's going to happen.
I mean, I feel like when they say arc, they don't mean it in the way that the fans have
interpreted the arcs because maybe they mean it doesn't necessarily mean like God,
do you think they mean like just a thing where they arrive at an island and something happens?
Yeah, that's sometimes considered an arc and sometimes it isn't.
So like, I don't know.
Could they mean it in the sense that like first there was like they were in the east blue
and then they went to the grand line and then they're in the new world.
Yes, and then there was the new world.
Yeah.
So this is the final arc is like a four hour four arc.
Yeah, act.
I don't know.
Yeah.
The new world was is that everything past Fishman Island?
I think that's including Fishman Island.
It's like post time skip.
Fishman Island.
Punk hazard.
I mean, I meant a big elephant.
Yes.
I meant geographically past Fishman Island.
They cross the red line or whatever.
You cross the red line or go under it rather and that's the part of the grand line that
a lot of people don't get to.
Yeah, right.
So exciting.
I'm getting hype.
I'm getting hype thinking about it.
Yeah.
The next voicemail is what was it called something son of a glitch?
All right.
You have a vocabulary link?
Yep.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
My favorite show on the Internet, Son of a Glitch.
Hi, welcome to Son of a Glitch.
I'm Benjamin and today's glitch is women.
Like a glitch of humanity.
Like Adam, Adam was in the garden and then he glitched and uh-oh his rib turned into a woman
suddenly.
Well, you know, it's just women just have a glitch in their genes.
They got that weird X chromosome.
They don't, they don't.
They got that weird X chromosome that makes them be shopping.
They just, they just turn out all fucked up and shit.
I don't know.
You think they're supposed to look like that?
No.
Unlike, unlike, unlike women, unlike women, I have no X chromosome and therefore have
face no such, such, such problems in my life.
What can I say?
But I agree with this guy.
Is that oblivion?
Hi oblivion.
I think it sounds, sounds like you've graced us yet again.
Next time is called popcorn nihilist.
Live to see things burn instant gratification.
Three, two, one, go.
Bro, what do you mean caco?
What do you mean?
Unicorn, your Bible unicorn?
We all know the best cow is Girafariga.
I already told you.
Girafariga.
Yeah, the best cow.
We're talking about maybe Girafs or cows.
Turns out they're not cows.
Yeah, yeah, we looked, I was wrong.
Even though Kaku ate the Ushi Ushi No Mi model giraffe,
that's just one piece taxonomy must be different.
Girafs are not actually cows, but nevertheless, Girafariga's fine.
He's okay.
Bufalant is better.
More cow.
Also, also not technically a cow,
but maybe as much a cow as a giraffe is, so I'll count it.
Bufalant's good.
Taurus is good.
I like Bufalant because he said Bufalant in the Minecraft server.
He sure did.
You know, I do like miltank just because I like Pokmon that have like healing abilities.
I just think that's a really cool thing for a Pokmon to have is like healing moves.
I thought you were going to say I really like miltank because I just like Pokmon
that have their tits out.
No, no, no, not today.
I like Chansi because it had soft boiled and, you know, Mumu or not Mumu.
It's got milk drink.
Can milk drink heal other Pokmon or can it only heal itself?
Does it like suck its own tits, but it won't let anyone else suck on them?
That would be funny if it was selfish.
Selfish.
It's like a double battle thing.
It would heal the other as well.
It'll be fun.
Actually, I'm curious.
Milk drink move.
Can it be used out of battle?
Okay, prior to generation seven, milk drink can also be used outside of battle to transfer
some of the users HP to another party member.
Each useful transfer 20% of the users HP up to the targets maximum HP.
The move will not work if the user has 20%.
Wait, but not anymore.
Does it not do that anymore?
It says it says prior to generation seven.
Weird.
Milk drink restores up to 50%.
Okay.
Oh, that's so bizarre.
It heals the user in battle, but outside of battle it gives away the users HP to other Pokmon.
Awesome.
That would be so useful in like a Nuzlocke sort of setting in like a dungeon.
That would be great.
You literally just have your fucking cow.
Given its milk, all the other Pokmon are drinking it.
They're staying healed.
They're staying topped up and healthy.
And then you go into battle and you have it heal itself.
It probably doesn't have that many PP though.
Yeah.
But that's awesome.
As with most things in life, when you run out of PP, you're fucked.
Sad, but true.
All right.
Next one is called rest in peace.
Three, two, one, go.
Dude.
You see them snakes right there?
Yeah.
I care more about them snakes than I do a human life.
Just like that, man.
Them snakes mean more to me than any human being ever born.
What the fuck?
I relate.
I don't, I don't, I don't really understand, but I mean, sure.
Why not?
Kill people, live snakes, feed people to the snakes, let them eat the people please.
Thank you very much.
Okay.
Next one is called thank you Gibbon.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey Gibbon.
Just wanted to say thank you for helping Ben St. process some of the thoughts there.
Genuinely, thank you.
Jesus.
I want him to be able to be a funny man again,
but he needs to give himself a break.
And I mean, we all can, we all can point fingers and laugh at Ben St.
But I know we are rather all point fingers and laugh with Ben St.
Thanks.
You know, you know what?
This guy's making a lot of sense.
This guy's talking a lot of sense right now.
I'm not pointing and laughing at you.
I'm pointing and laughing with you.
Yeah.
I mean, at someone or something else, perhaps.
Behind you, you see.
Or maybe just in general.
I'm not pointing.
I'm pointing and laughing.
I'm pointing at you, but I'm laughing with you.
Perhaps.
Next one is called a hot summer day with the Ralfa males.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh, God.
This baby.
He's pretty annoying as babies go.
Oh, gosh, darn hot out here.
How?
How am I supposed to get my training to kill Ben St.
if I can't hardly breathe?
Well, son, that that probably means you have asthma or something that she that kind of sucks.
But you know what?
I'll get you an iron lung and I'll get you like a sniper rifle.
So you don't have to like run.
I am.
I'm going to show you this movie called American Sniper.
It's about a guy who who shot a sniper and he was American.
It's pretty good.
Wow, Papa.
Thanks.
You need to like fucking like go inside.
Who gets you an iron lung and a sniper rifle?
I'll just pick that up for you, son.
I was picking up at the hardware store.
OK, yeah.
I mean, that sounds pretty dangerous.
All right.
I should watch out for that, I guess.
The next one is called forgive.
Please add me at Vinny Vidi Vici for hashtag one nine seven seven.
You said the whole thing.
Yeah.
Next three two one go.
Hey, you should add me on Discord so like we can conspire against Ben and like send him memes
that will brighten his day because I'm not good at like communicating all the time.
But I can send you a meme and, you know, get somebody a chocolate.
Give him give him thinking.
This guy does this guy does send me memes sometime and I generally don't respond
because I don't know what do you do when someone sends you a meme?
You laugh out uproariously, Ben.
Well, maybe you go XD.
Yeah.
Well, say I say it in real life.
But I don't type it to XD heard around the world.
We can only we can only hope we can only hope.
Next one.
Last one, perhaps is called AIDS.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh, I heard about this.
All of his aides are stored in his gun toe.
But I have not that luxury.
It is going to fucking kill me.
I do not have long for this world.
Damn.
Okay.
What seems like only yesterday you were just a baby and now you're dying of AIDS.
They grow up so fast.
Uh, I just heard, you know, I didn't look into it.
I heard that, um, you know, a while ago it came out that Ethan Ralph like date raped some girl
like while like while he was like away in Vegas, like leaving while May was like giving
birth to their kid or whatever.
And I guess that girl might have HIV.
And so maybe Ethan got HIV from from this.
I don't know.
It's just, it's just, it's just a maybe.
It's just, it's just a maybe I heard.
You know, I'm, uh, I have no idea.
Just what I heard.
I had heard about the date rape thing in Vegas before that I had heard before the
AIDS thing is like a new development.
So I don't know.
Ethan Ralph might have AIDS.
I don't know.
I'm just asking questions.
I don't want to ask questions.
Did you hear this is not about that, but did you hear some gimmick account on Twitter
when it had some kind of meltdown because they thought they think that COVID is airborne AIDS?
They think that like everyone who's in fact, who's had COVID now has AIDS.
Huh?
How could you, like, why would it, why would it now happen?
Well, it's, well, I mean, it's not, why is there no evidence of that at all?
Well, I guess, I guess it showed like, I don't know, some person had like an immune,
like some person that got COVID showed like a, like reduced immune response that was like
similar to AIDS.
And so it's like, oh shit, this person got AIDS from COVID, COVID gives you AIDS.
Everybody's got AIDS now.
Well, damn.
Well, I mean, I think it seems a little more likely that maybe, maybe they already had an
immune problem and maybe that's had something to do with them getting COVID.
I don't know.
But anyway, this fucking gimmick account, it's called like falconary finance or something.
It's, I don't know.
It's like a joke account about like, no, it's like UAE falconary finance.
It's about like Saudi Arabian finance bros who are also into like falconary.
I don't know.
I don't get it.
It's some kind of gag.
But, but the other day he had like a, he broke character to have this meltdown about
guys, COVID is airborne AIDS.
We've all got AIDS.
Everyone's going to die.
I mean, at that point, what do you do about, why would you freak out if everyone's got it?
I mean, I guess we all got AIDS now.
I see what you mean, but I probably would, if I sincerely believe that I probably would
also freak out.
I guess you'd freak out and you'd go and get medical stuff.
You go to the AIDS shop and you'd say, can I have some AIDS suppression, please?
I guess, I guess they have, I guess they have those.
I guess they have some pretty good like AIDS countermeasures.
You need to like forever live on a diet of specific pills so that you have an autoimmune
system.
Did you, did you see, oh that reminds me, did you watch Oki's videos?
Not particularly.
I think I've seen a few.
There's a new one that he just put out about, I forget the name.
What was it, hang on, what was it called?
I watched the new one.
Oki, the King of Stolen Valor, about this guy called Jack Idema, and Oki goes, he went
across the country to interview this guy's ex-wife about him, and a lot of it is kind
of just about what a fucking abusive psychopath this guy was.
One of the, one of the things that like went wrong for this woman was that like she got,
she got HIV from this guy, so you know, now she's got that, which is one problem among many
that she's had to deal with since being with this dude.
It's pretty good, it's pretty good documentary, I would say.
It's nice, recommended, but yeah.
AIDS? No, it's no joke.
You don't, you don't want, you don't want it.
It's, you gotta fucking take your, yeah, take your, take your suppression meds like every day,
and I mean you can handle it that way, but like what a bummer.
Hey kids, don't have AIDS.
Hey kids, it's-
Choose the right path, don't smoke, drug, don't drink alcohol, and don't get aid.
McGruff the crime dog here saying, saying-
Say no to AIDS, if an adult offers you AIDS, say no.
Definitely say no.
Tell an adult.
And then try to like, like hold your coat out and try to make yourself seem bigger than them,
like to intimidate them, right?
Yeah, yes.
And make a lot, move around a lot and make a lot of noise to scare them away.
Base.
That probably would scare people away if you think you're like rabid, insane.
If you're like gibber, you're holding your coat out, gibbering, making erratic movements.
Yeah, don't play dead.
With it, when it's a human, when the, when the predator is a human, don't play dead,
because they'll just, they'll call the police and they'll just bring,
they'll call it an ambulance and they'll, they'll bring more humans around.
So it's not an, it's not an effective strategy.
Acting like a lunatic is, is more effective to get left alone, in my experience.
Anyway, that's the last voicemail.
Oh, thank God.
Thank God.
We're, are we just under, we're like maybe just barely at the three hour mark,
which is honestly, doesn't even, doesn't matter.
The effects, whether Eleazar will animate the tombstones, but like, who cares?
There was some, my brother had, but Eleazar, you better still,
if we're under three hours, you've got to do it.
That doesn't mean you shouldn't do it.
My brother was like, experimenting with like, the VTuber software that I used for my streams.
Yeah.
The PNG stuff.
He's figured out that you can do, you can have, if you have like a virtual audio cable
from some, like for, hooked into like a Discord call, you can get someone else's audio
and then put that onto a separate PNG VTuber and have two different people's voices
animating two different VTubers on the same, like recording or stream.
I thought that was really cool.
Yeah.
I don't know whether, I feel like you could, you could, you could have like a, a system.
So it would be your, it would be your software animating them through this.
Animating them and myself separately.
Yeah.
In a single video file.
And you could do like a podcast like that.
We could have our little animator, animation guys.
They would just react to us talking.
It wouldn't have to be like an extremely costly rendering thing.
They would just move their mouth or shake or whatever when we have voice coming out of our mouth.
Yeah.
We could automate Ellie Azar's job away, just like, just like Yang said we could do.
Finally, we can, we can, we can lay it, we can lay off an employee and have a robot do it instead.
Would you want it?
It's the future.
Would you want to, would you want to try that sometime?
That would be funny.
I maybe, I think the virtual audio cable is very confusing and I would need to like
ask for a lot of help to like get that working because I remember using it for something else
and it fucked everything up and I didn't know how to undo it.
So I had to get rid of it at some point.
I see.
If you ever get that working, I would, I would, I would make, I would make some PNGs for myself.
It could be fun.
It could be funny.
Yeah.
Neat, nifty even.
The, okay, I guess shows over.
Alrighty.
Patreon.com, Patreon.com slash the procrastinators for our extensive, our extensive backlog of
bonus episodes.
If that's something you would be interested in filling your, filling your meaningless hours
between cradle and grave with, I know I am.
There's the, the Minecraft server as well.
Access at $5 or more.
Yes, I did not, I did not have time this week to fix my connection and test that out again.
I will work on it in the near future.
All right.
And, but I mean, but I mean, you know, but I mean, you don't need us to be, you don't need me in there.
You don't have to, you can build and stuff.
You could, you could be, you could be building stuff.
And then whenever I do fucking get around to fixing my connection and making that work,
then I'll get in there and I'll be like, oh, I see.
I've been, I've been, I've been, uh, while I was away, you, somebody, uh, Cascava Montiado'd me
into, uh, into my own, uh, slime cave.
Oops.
And then I just teleport out and I think I was really clever because I circumvented your,
your trap, but it would be funny for a second.
What else?
Anything?
Um, uh, I need to get around to, to sending off a few more load of ghosts things.
I just got another one returned.
I haven't had a lot of returns.
So I assume if, if I hear nothing that it's arrived, um, but I have gotten a return and I
would have sent some stuff out.
Kaiju, Koon, their one never arrived.
Oh, bummer.
Um, so I'm just going to send them another one.
And, uh, duh, that's, that's going to be my thing for the next 100 years is slowly
sending more of those out.
Yeah.
Again, uh, if you are, if you are, I have a few return packages for, uh, Road to Radcon,
the book and the plebe and the wee blue rays, uh, these are just the ones that I found in
my PO box before it expired.
There might have been some more that I got returned after the expiration.
So if you're listening and you have ordered something for me and you never got it, I might
have it here in which case contact me anyway so I can double check that your address hasn't changed.
Or if I don't have it, contact me anyway and I will just, you know, send you a replacement
because I would consider it lost in the mail at this point.
Uh, DM me on discord or something, uh, or twitter or whatever.
That's it.
Uh, okay.
I think that's all.
Yep.
All right.
Thanks for listening.
See you next week.
We will, uh, I don't know, we'll have something.
I'm sure we'll have something.
We'll have something to talk about probably.
I'm going to, I'm going to, all right, here's, here's what's going to, I'm going to do.
I'm going to endeavor to finally finish the commissions that I have not finished because
I've been so like about doing them.
I'm going to do those and they have like five to do.
I'll try and then that'll be a thing done.
How many did you do?
Um, uh, off the top of my head, I can't really remember.
I think it was like five or six.
A number of them were not safe for work.
So you didn't see them on my main twitter.
Indeed.
And, uh, yeah.
I think it was a pretty good set of things.
It was just an unfortunate moment for me to get really cripplingly depressed and not be
able to finish the rest of them.
But, uh, thank you for your interest and I will do it again later.
Unlike all those other times, which were great times for that.
This, this one was just a really unfortunate.
I mean, I, I, I managed to do the first ones like almost immediately
when they got them.
It's like, okay, got the thing.
I mean, I guess it was like partly because I needed the money to pay for my reimbursement
of the flight back home because I just wanted to get home.
And it was like very motivated to make sure those were done so that I could get more commissions.
But then people stopped asking about them.
So I'm like, okay, cutting it off.
Yeah.
Just got to finish these ones.
All right, let's, let's end the podcast so we can go make some gummies.
Hey, all right.