Hello, welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. It's another episode of your favorite podcast
that sucks. Hi everybody. Hi Ben. Gibbont's here. Digi's here. I'm here. And our guest this
week is Kazzy. Hey guys. I'm Kazzy. From the internet. From the internet. Hey guys. It's
Kazzy. It's Kazzy. Do you want to introduce yourself? Yeah, sure. To explain who you are.
Most of our listeners probably have heard of you. Yeah, sure. You can introduce me and
then I'll pick up whatever you like. Kazzy is an artist and a fursuit maker. Wow. That's
it. Yeah, that's it. I mean illustrator. I don't know. Yeah, illustrator. Primarily illustrator.
Yeah. Yeah, she paints. You make really good art that everybody should look at now. Thank you. Go
to Instagram and Twitter linked in the description. Yeah. Yes, based. Yeah, I do that mostly and then
I'm starting to be a fursuit maker. Just starting might do more of it. I don't know yet. Well,
you say you're just starting. Well, how much does it cost to buy a fursuit from you? That depends
on a lot of things like what like how detailed your character is and like do you want the full
thing or do you want like the head and the price range? Would you imagine the price range? Well,
um, I am working on one right now that is just a head set of paws and a tail and that was like
$750. Um, and that's almost done. It's not that bad. I guess if you wanted like the the big the big
dick one that's got like the padding in it, it's like your full body. Yeah, yeah. You know, standard
like normal complicated character design. Probably like, I mean, over over 2000,
um, somewhere around like last last year around there last year for like months and months.
Every time I saw you, you had a piece, you had like you would you would have like a hand or a
or a foot or something like in your bag and you would pull it out and be sewing on it and it took
you forever. It did. The thing about me to make it to make Colby Jack. Yeah, Colby Jack is my
show Colby Jack on screen right now. This is the thing I saw. I saw be pieced together like
Frank. I think we I think we showed this when it was completed on the PCP. Thank you. I remember
you telling Ellie Azar to show it. Yeah. And he did. Well, show it again. Yeah, show it again.
Yeah. I mean, the thing about him was that I mean, he was my second one that I had made.
My first one I made way back in high school and then the second one
um, took quite a while because I just decided to hand sew him and I really don't know why I
have a machine, but the pedal is missing for it. Um, so I don't know. I just decided I'll just take
forever on it, I guess. Hell yeah. Hand sewing is relaxing. Yeah. I would like to, I want to get
into sewing or keep convincing myself that I will, but like, this, you know, that's just another
thing to be doing. And I already didn't do too many goddamn things. I want to, well, I figure it's
probably a good thing to do while you're like watching stuff, right? Like, yeah, how mindless
is it? Like, can I, can I, is it more like I have to listen to a podcast or could I actually like
watch anime? Could I read subtitles and try to sew? It's like, um, like hundreds upon hundreds of
repetitive tasks that you could easily, like after a few thousand times, you don't even need to think
about what your hands are doing and yeah, you can listen to a lot of stuff. I'm just wondering if I
can read subtitles. Um, yeah, I mean, what would you want to make? Like clothes or, or what? Well,
yeah, I'd love to make, I don't know, everything. I would love to, I mean, ideally in my mind,
every aspect of my life would be DIY. Like it would have either be able to make everything myself
or have people around who know how to make everything and I can pay them to do it. But I would,
I want everything to be in house fashion. Yeah, if you had like, I mean, if you, if you, if you've
got a sewing machine, which is what you would use, you wouldn't hand sew clothes. Um, I have a sewing
machine. So, well, there you go. I mean, if you know how to use it and you just run the fabric
through. Yeah, I do know how to use it, but there's lots of different like types of stitching and
like ways to do it for different stuff. I guess I just gotta, you know, decide what I want to make
and then watch the video about how to make it. I guess it's probably not that different from cooking,
right? Like just follow the recipe. Yeah, it is exactly like that. It is just like, there is a way
to do it and there's plenty of resources to learn how online. And the same goes for fur suit making.
I always think about like, fucking, you know, sewing or, or, or like the,
what does it even call it, crochet that I was doing a while back and I made those little boots.
Stupid things. For, um, for Vriska, right? For Vriska. Yeah, I put this, she's still wearing
them because it is cold still. Um, um, and it's like, I think I just like the action and just
repeating the action. I don't really like following like, like having a big complicated like blueprint
and having to follow it precisely. I just want something to move my hands with while I think
or while I listen to stuff. So if, if I had like, like a big piece of fabric, I would just like,
I don't know, sew into it for no reason. Just, just put thread in it. I guess the only other
thing about me is that, um, I mean, I've, I've known you guys for, for quite a while. Um, and
that's true. Um, I guess you could say that this is Munchie's return because he is in the same
house as me. So he's technically here a little bit. Wow. That's amazing. That's incredible.
Wow. Maybe we'll hear a fart in the distance or something. Oh, that man does not fart. He does
not do it. I don't know why. I think he insists. Yeah, I think he mentioned that before that he
like insisted he does not fart or something. Yeah, no, it's true. After living with him for a while,
I can confirm it's true. It's fucked up. It's way fucked. Um, we were supposed to hang out on
Halloween. That's right. But then I canceled. We all canceled. Because of COVID, because of COVID
and snow, two, two big, two great tastes. Two of the worst things in the world, actually. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. You know what? My two least favorite things. Uh, I got exposed. I've been exposed to
COVID now. Yeah. Tell me about that. I'm, I'm a little bit worried about you. I saw on, on Twitter.
Well, it's probably okay. There's not that much to tell. It's basically just two of my roommates
work for this. Um, I guess it's a landscaping company. And I guess someone who they work with
got tested positive. And so they're, they're testing a bunch of other people from that company.
Those guys are getting tested on Wednesday. And so on Wednesday, I will know for sure whether
like, oh, did any of it get transmitted to them? Has it, has it been in my house? Right. Um,
okay. So it's not like sure if I, or anything yet. No, it's not, it's, it's not even like that
likely that either of them would have got it. Uh, and if, even if they got it doesn't, wouldn't
mean I would get it, but you know, it's, it's possible. It's quite, I mean, if you're in a
house together, it's pretty likely. I don't know what the chance is, but I feel like it would
probably happen. I've, well, I've heard that like, it's possible like within an apartment,
like with roommates and stuff, if you just have the person who is, has COVID use a separate
bathroom from everyone else, they can just keep it to themselves. That's what we did. We said,
those guys now, those guys got to use the downstairs bathroom now until, until they
get tested. Oh, the fucking, the fucking gross disgusting one. Which, which one? Well, you know,
I guess you could say the upstairs one, the upstairs one's clean now. The upstairs one
actually looks great. The upstairs one is, is fine and normal downstairs. I've seen,
I've seen some shit. Right. Well, I don't use that one. So that's, that's not on me.
You see, it feels like this, the place you would expect to see some shit is in the bathroom.
It's true. I saw some literal shit there one time and I never went back.
I thought this is unacceptable. It's a little, it's a little concerning. I mean,
before in the first wave, like I didn't know anyone that had it or like was in contact with
someone that was exposed to it. And now there's this with you, Ben. And then there was someone who
I used to be quite good friends with posted on Twitter that, you know, she's got it and her
whole family's got it. And it's scary. Yeah, the third wave is coming. It's going to be a big one.
It's a, we're fucked. We're totally fucked. I'm happy that I don't keep up with anything
that's ever going on anywhere. And I've no, I don't, didn't know there was a second wave
or a third wave on the way. What is the second wave? I thought this was the second wave.
Well, Matt, there's no third wave. We didn't have a second wave in Massachusetts yet because
we weren't into like super lockdown all through the summer. So we like didn't have the second one.
But now, yeah. I was literally unaware. It was big in March. And then they said lockdown.
And it went all the way down real low during the summer. And then it started creeping up again.
Now we're in a second lockdown. It's a second wave trying to cut that. We should probably,
we probably need a second lockdown right about now. Are we not in lockdown now? I guess not. Yeah.
You're back at school. Well, I mean, yeah, but I'm not going, I'm not going anywhere.
Like my classes are remote.
Right. Well, I don't know. I don't know if there's, I don't know what technically
constitutes lockdown versus quarantine versus whatever, whatever, just shut everything down.
Just, just, just burn it all down is what I would say. We got to start over.
You should return to monkey. Sure. Monkey.
Monkey, please hold out thine hand to me.
I don't know. COVID's pretty good. Can't wait. I will, I will, if I, if I get it,
I will buy the I Have COVID shirt from Teespring. I promise.
Why did you guys make that? The procrastinators affiliated I Have COVID shirt branded
procrastinators. Link, link in the description.
If you have COVID, you should buy it. That'd be like a monetary incentive for us to spread COVID
as far as we possibly can. I Have COVID and so can you. I mean, I can only imagine wearing that to
like a grocery store and getting subsequently kicked out of said store even if you don't have it.
It would just make, it would just make everyone avoid you and then you'd never get it.
You know, it's the best defense. No one would come near you. I don't know. If I saw someone
wearing a shirt that said I Have COVID, I would be very uncomfortable. Just because of the uncertainty.
Like, is that real? You probably assumed they were trying to warn you, right? Like,
I mean, they're doing a service. Either they were taking their warning very seriously or
they were like fucking with everyone. And, you know, that uncertainty I'd be like, I don't like this.
Uh, well, you know, you, you too listener can make everyone uncomfortable. I can't wait. I'm
looking forward to it. Um, hey guys, president of the United States of America, we got him. Here
we go. Our boy Jay Rob. We got our boy Jay Rob in there. I know now it's time. He's in there.
Kick grandpa's ass. I want corn pop for VP.
No, I'm not, I'm not gonna, I'm not gonna, I'm not gonna stand Biden ironically anymore. It's not
funny anymore. I think I'm hugely excited if Biden really is president for the fact that
hating on the president, I feel like will be an uncontroversial opinion for almost everybody.
Hmm. It's, you know, it'll be very hard to hate. So far for the Trump presidency, it's like
we either really hate this man or you don't. Yeah. And you pretty much have to be on one side
of the other. I hated him, but like only as much as a normal president. So it was kind of weird
for me. But I also hate Biden as much as a normal president. But like, I don't think anybody in the
world like is going to step up to bat for this bad. Like nobody's going to get like weird defensive
over me shitting on Biden, including liberals. Like, I mean, certainly less so than with this
past presidency. Some of them do, but yeah. I can't think of anybody who I would encounter who would
be mad that I was talking shit about Biden like ever that in real, in real life. No, I don't know
anybody. I don't know. I feel like if anybody is is like, like, like legitimately excited for
Biden, they love him right now. Like, I think it's it's very much they probably got paid by him.
No, no, no, they're just like so happy that Trump is not there. And they're just re reconstituting
that happiness into Biden's so fucking cool. And then that'll wear off when they realize,
yeah, he's just the guy. I mean, it's just what it's just one of the other presidents,
like standing Biden is just a meme. Hopefully. Yeah. Yeah. For me, it was a meme, but now it's
over. It's not a meme. The one thing that is potentially good about Biden is that he does
just kind of do whatever he gets like paid or told to do. So like, maybe we can just literally
bully him into doing whatever we want. Like, I mean, that's the hope. That's the plan. Yeah,
I wonder how well that will work. But hopefully he's not gonna be like a super reactionary like
law and order like fucking crackdown kind of guy. He's more he's like, he's a little more
conciliatory. He has his base has a little bit more expectations of him to like, not, I don't
know, like violate the Constitution. I just think like Trump's way of doing things was like,
if you told him that he was wrong about something or did something bad, he'd just be like, no,
fuck you. And then, you know, maybe he'll stop doing it. Maybe he won't. But like Biden is like,
if you were if everybody was like, fuck you, you did this, then he would try to reason with people
and fail. Yeah. And that's why he might be invincible. Yeah, I agree. He's he
Democrats actually care about criticism for better or for worse. They they their feelings can be
hurt. Right. And like, I think that Obama was just like so charismatic that it was a lot harder
for people to want to just like tear into him. But like, Joe Biden's just like an old creepy
child molester. So it'll be really easy to tear into him. Yeah. No, I think you're right. Yeah. I
think hate hating on the Prez will be just something we can all as a nation get behind.
I agree with that. I don't know if you guys saw this, but I saw a clip getting passed around on
Twitter that was John McCain's concessions concession speech from 2008. And it was really
interesting. Have you not seen it? No, I don't think so. I would take a look. It's really interesting
to compare that to now because I mean, what we see now is the the president of the United States
throwing an absolute temper tantrum. Yeah, he looks very funny. He he is just like, I don't
I don't I don't know how to describe it picture of him in the white hat, like walking into the
White House like forlorn over his shoulder. Absolutely. And I watched this. I watched this
this speech from John McCain from when he lost in 2008. And, you know, aside from, you know,
his policies or whatever, when I listen to that speech, I like the the crowd starts
booing Obama at the beginning and he he settles them down, he gets them to stop.
And he's like, No, I'm happy for the guy. Like, I know that he wants to do what's best for this
country. All I care about is the good of America and the good of the people. And so, you know,
well, we have our differences. You know, you know, you know, he he he stepped he he lost with
grace. And it's such a world of difference from what we're seeing right now. It's it's incredible.
I mean, you got to you got to lose with if you lose, you might as well lose with grace. So like,
you don't look like an asshole to the current admit you should play nice with the people who
are going to be, you know, your bosses for the next four years. Also, I won't be the case for him
because he's not a politician. So for McCain, no, for for Trump, I'm saying that's why he wouldn't
have to play. Yeah, that's that's true. That's true. Yeah, I'll just try and like make his own
country. He's going to do Trump TV. Oh, yeah, I'm going to start a media empire. It's going to be so
sick. I'm so hyped for Trump TV. I really think I really think it's going to be great. And I think
this is like it's going to split. It's already or like officially announced to like multiple sources
have better be quote unquote better and less fake news than the media. He just wants to make
his own media. Oh, that's interesting. I mean, it'll be just propaganda, but
yeah, sure. I think I think I think it could really split the Republican vote,
which would be so great. That would just be the that would be the sickest thing.
I don't know. I don't know how much of the base he'll take with him. I've never been happier
about libertarians because of the shit that happens. Oh, yeah.
They literally cost him the election. I literally really did. And honestly, my favorite thing to
come out of this so far is to watch, you know, beside aside from Trump's meltdown himself,
the meltdown of the MAGA people is hilarious because in 2016, all they were doing after the
election was going like, oh, my God, look at these look at these liberals, you know, they're so
triggered by snowflakes and they're doing the exact same thing. There's like a slightly different
tone to it. But yeah, they're doing their version of it. I mean, what we see now is like all the
coping. I know, I love the cringe comps. I want more cringe comps. I've been I've been on poll
a bunch and it's all like, it's all like, you know, it's fraud, like, oh, look, the curve has a
squiggle in it. Oh, that's fraud. And like, it's like, no, no, Trump's going to take it to court.
Like, this is all part of the plan, guys. I don't know. That's very funny.
I think it's settling down. I don't know. I wonder how long, you know, no, no, it's not
going to settle down because I don't know, do you think Trump is going to fight it like all
the way up until Inauguration Day? Yeah. I think he will posture that he's going to fight it. I
don't actually know whether he's willing to go through all of that. But it's still possible
that he could, like, disrupt things all the way up until that moment. Yeah, I guess it depends on
how much people want him to do it. From what I've seen, it seems like people are mostly just kind
of like resigning. Like, I don't see a lot of people like, I mean, people are kind of assuming
that he's going to try to push it off. Like anybody I know who's like a Trump support,
like who cares about Trump at all is like, well, it's not technically decided, but like,
it's probably over. It could be overturned in the courts, but like the way the wind is blowing,
it's like even the people that want that are like, there's really no precedent. It's just not
close enough. It had to overturn multiple states. It just doesn't seem like something that's going
to happen. I watched, oh my God, did any of you like watch the fucking count come in on Georgia?
Yeah, I was up to that one. Oh, I didn't see it. I didn't see it turn. I didn't see it turn,
but I was keeping up with like exactly how many votes, you know, like several hours. It was
Georgia Georgia was was the margin was like 4,000 and then like 3000 and then like 2500. Yeah,
it went down to like 1700 before I like went to bed.
Um, yeah, I saw I think then I think you might have retweeted it, but it was something that was
like, you know, um, it was like retweet this if if your follower account, like, yeah, I did,
you know, could flip Georgia, could flip Georgia. And I looked and I was like even mine could at
that point when I looked when you when you posted that it got down to like, I think like, like
a thousand or less, yeah, like before it was like, oh my God. And it was like the the the report
was saying like 90 like over 98% of the vote was in. So it's like, well, what does that mean? Does
that mean like there's like a couple thousand votes left to count or does that mean there's 10,000
votes left to count? You know, uh, that was exciting though. That was and then, um, people were
people were talking about Pennsylvania flipping, but I was looking at the numbers and Pennsylvania
didn't seem anywhere near as close as Georgia. I thought like Georgia Georgia might flip and
that would be the only one. I felt the same way. And I just assumed that it was people who,
you know, understood politics more than me and that just are like, no, like we've run the numbers,
like we know it's going to flip, like we know how this is going to happen. It's just like,
all right, I guess I'll trust you guys. I don't know, though. It looks pretty,
it looks, it looks pretty much like an uphill battle. I mean, I wake up and it's flipped.
I felt, um, nervous because, you know, I had watched the results come in and like the New
Hampshire primary and the Iowa caucus and stuff. And I watched it like come out with like, oh,
Bernie looks like he's ahead really early on. And then like fucking Pete Buttigieg or whatever,
like closes the gaps, like, no, no, it's all slipping through my fingers. So, you know, I was,
I was prepared for a bad, for a bad time. Wait, did you guys see the, um,
like the Trump like, I don't know if it's a concession speech, but the, the Trump address
in like the, the like landscaping or like the hardware store parking lot?
No, not yet. No, I was planning on watching that after this.
I haven't watched it yet. But like they booked it. They tried to book like this speech at the
Four Seasons Hotel, but they accidentally booked it at like a landscaping company called Four Seasons.
So they're just, I'm still looking at the picture right now of fucking Rudy Giuliani giving a speech
in this like dirty gravel like driveway. Here, um, I'll, I'll, I'll show you. I, I saw like a photo
of it or something in it. I was like, guys, what the fuck is this? It all, it all ends here.
For holding press conference of Four Seasons Garden Center.
It's like, there's like construction going on in the background. It looks like next to like
some rusty beams. There's like an orange cone there on the ground.
The paint's peeling off the wall. Oh my God. I love it.
Oh man. I still haven't seen a Borat too. I guess I am probably going to watch it at some point.
Oh, I've just seen that screenshot floating around of Giuliani. Like,
looks like he's unzipping his pants or something. Yeah. On the bed. I saw that. I do. I didn't know
what it was until yesterday, um, because Munchie was telling me about it. I had no idea and he
showed me the clip. Um, and yeah, I haven't even seen the clip. It's, I mean, I don't, he's like
lying back on the bed and like, I mean, like shoves his hand in his pants and it's like fucking,
yeah, it's pretty clear to me. Yeah. What's going on there? I mean, yeah. I saw the, um,
Red Letter Media just did a half in the bag where they talked about Borat 2
and they discussed that and they, they said that it's like that part in particular is like clearly
they edited around to make it look worse than it was. It's still bad, but like, I don't know.
There's something sort of, well, they talk about it. I haven't seen the film.
I don't, I don't really know the whole context for like what's going on there.
There's an, oh, I'm seeing an, there's an Antifa thread on poll. That's interesting.
I'll have to check that out later and have to bookmark that.
Wait, are you part of poll's transition into being a leftist board? Well, well, I checked,
I checked poll. I haven't been posting there, but I checked it like as Georgia was flipping
and like, you know, everyone's making fun of, uh, uh, the MAGA atards or the meat or the
MEGA atards as they call them there, which I assume stands for make Israel great again.
Everyone on poll thinks that Trump is like super pro Israel, which I guess he probably is,
but like that's their, that's their big beef with them. Um, I've been reading it and yeah,
there's a lot of like, a lot of, I don't know, and I might settle down. I assume that it was like,
I assume that 4chan was like very like MAGA just because it made people mad and maybe now the way
to make people mad is to, uh, is to make fun of them. I think that's part of it. I don't think
they were as MAGA as people think. I think they weren't like a unified front for sure. I think
poll is just a lot more like of a weird radical identities. Just like, I mean, you, you can,
people have their like flags on their trip codes or whatever and like even, even before like, you
know, there are people in there who are like anarchists and communists. I guess it's like the
biggest, they might be trolls too. The biggest mistake people make about 4chan is that people
always think it's like a monoculture, but like the point of it in my mind is that every position
is represented there. So like, usually if you step into a thread, like if somebody starts a thread
with a dumb title, like, uh, is this anime good or bad? The first two responses almost without
fail will be it's great and it's shit. It's just like, like, I don't even know if those two people
really believe that or if they're just trying to make sure those are the first two responses,
just to like set the bar that like the dumbest possible responses have all been said right up
front. Now let's try to talk about it, you know, like, right. And so like, there are people who
are definitely playing devil's advocate. But not because they do or don't believe the things they're
saying, they only just want to argue about shit until they understand things better. They don't
care. They're not probably not even voting, you know, like, it's like, it's a place where all
conversation and knowledge is meant to coalesce. But very, you know, that includes all the bad
things and aggressive things and fucked things. So like, reputationally, it's more known for that
stuff. But if you go to any board, like part of it is people fighting against that stuff and making
fun of those people at the same time. Yeah. Yeah, sure. See, that's interesting. I don't really
know. I mean, I'm someone who's never been on 4chan at all. I don't know. It's a very different
website from, you know, the ones that I'm what I'm doing right now would be considered
it would be considered spoon feeding and would be considered a bad thing what I'm doing right now
by explaining 4chan. But like, oh, I know that. I know that. Yeah. Like, because in the reason for
that, which I kind of agree with is that like, because it used to be that I think the number
one rule on most boards is just lurk more, like, eventually, like if you come in and you immediately
react to whatever you see, then you probably don't understand why it's there, you know, like,
it might be that somebody just like says some incredibly racist shit or something and like,
you would go like, you know, freak out, I can't believe somebody said this, but like,
there might be a lot more to it, you know, and when you've been on a board long enough,
then you start to recognize like, you can tell what is a PSYOP and what is like a new person who's
literally just reacting to things and like, you know, who is a fed, which poll has a lot of feds.
So this yeah, man, I watched this one fucking speech with it was some kind of hearing. I think
it was when they were talking to the social media people, the government people were talking to the
social media people like six months ago. And like, three of the like governors or senators or
whatever, who were like the most hard ass, you had like the most serious actual questions,
legitimately dropped four Chan memes, like three different guys in a row. And I was like,
this is the feds on poll, like this is who they are.
I see. What were the memes? I don't remember this a while ago.
I'm sure I know it somewhere.
Yeah, poll poll right now is all it's all like, you know, election fraud, COVID threads.
Have you seen that curve that people post like the Biden and versus Trump counting curve where
like at the very end, Biden's like, the blue jumps up. Yeah. And they made it into like a logo
with an with an F for fraud. Yeah, the one you're talking about.
Yeah, that's the one. There's like, people post like other images, like there's other
counts in like other states where like, the voting is similarly like, you know, has like
weird jumps and gaps in it. And like, you know, the the the the MAGA guy is like furious about
this one where Biden jumps ahead. But then like, there's other ones that jump, they do all kinds
of weird shit. And he's got the NPC face like, yeah, no reaction. That's that's what it's all
about. That's what polls like right now. So, you know, I've been scoping it out. You know,
maybe I'll become a maybe I'll become a big, a big four chain guy again, now that it's been made
a safe space for me. Yeah, right. Probably not. It's just like, it's, you know, deciding times.
Everybody feels good when they feel like they're on the winning team. And I've been in a weird
superposition for for most of Trump's presidency. I feel like I was on the losing team, but not
being upset about it, like everybody else was. And now I get to be now I get to be on the team
that like, it's like everybody wins for me. Everybody who every like, I feel like a Biden's
presidency can somehow only mean positive things for me specifically, but not because
of the fact that it's going to be good. Like, in fact, the worse it is, the more fun it will be
for me. What do you care to elaborate? Well, because like, so, I mean, it's kind of like,
we already see on Twitter, like liberals immediately turning to bully on on Biden,
you and I have been doing it. Yeah, because I've been making I've been making some angry,
I've been making some nasty tweets at some shit libs. Yeah, it's true. It's just like,
it'll be so much easier to root out the problems in the liberal party when they're not all like
for the last four years, if you said anything negative about liberals, then you were like,
oh, you're going to make it so Trump can win again. Like, nobody can nobody can raise this
argument anymore. You know, we have, I don't know if Trump's going to try to run again.
Next election, I doubt it. Like, he might, he already got the big come of being president.
Like, I don't know what he got the big come of being president. He might got like, Don Jr.
something someone could run. Everyone's saying Tucker Carlson is going to run in 2024. That's
not going to happen. You don't think so? No. Why would he? I mean, he's got a regular normal job.
People always forget like being president fucking sucks. And like, most of the people who do it
are like raised from birth with the expectation that they're going to do it and like, you know,
live like a completely different lifestyle. Trump's like the only person I think who has been like,
I just want to do it to do it because I want to have done I want to have my name on everything,
including America, you know, like, so you just don't think that like, there's anything in it for
Tucker to do that. Right. I just don't think that like, I think most people who people are,
oh, you should be president or like, no, that sounds fucking awful. Like you have to kill people,
you know, you have to make like terrible fucking decisions all the time with like,
and everybody expects everything of you and everyone has an opinion on you about you on
planet Earth, you know, like, yeah, sounds kind of shit. So yeah, I don't know. I don't know.
I probably wouldn't enjoy it. But who knows, like rapid ages years. Well, yeah. Well,
who do we? Yeah, if I guess that's kind of an optimistic for me to think like, okay, well,
now that now that liberals are in power, it's easier. It's it's yeah, it's safer to criticize
liberals. Right. Well, and we can bring them you can criticize them from an even more leftist
standpoint of being like, Oh, well, like, let's take it even further. Like y'all aren't doing
enough, you know, and I think the Trump presidency radicalized more people to the left
than a Biden presidency will. But yeah, I think rhetorically, it makes it easier for those people
to yeah, I'm just saying if we if if somehow liberals can like talk Biden into instituting
UBI, then it'll have been worth it. Oh, that's a but Biden is like Biden is pro a couple of
things that are good. Like, I think he's pro $15 minimum wage, and he's pro like,
maybe student student debt forgiveness of UBI. Yeah. It's it's not it's not as good.
So like, he's he's good on a couple of things, and then shit on other things.
Like, he doesn't, he doesn't, he's like, oh, no, we should expand the Affordable Care Act.
No, government health care. But I don't know. I lost my train of thought. Fuck Biden.
Yeah. Fuck, I'm all fuck them all.
How how likely do you think it is that as soon as Biden does his inauguration speech, he trips
and falls down the stairs and dies and Kamala Harris. Oh, my God, it's like a lot more likely
believe it. It sounds Kamala. I saw a post that was like it's just going to be like four
years of like Mr. Magoo like like a Kamala is just going to be like setting like traps
for him and he's just going to be like Mr. Magoo. It's going to be shenanigans. You know,
I've seen a couple of things where like she's like mistakenly says when I'm president, meaning
when I'm vice president. Wait, has she really? Yeah, it's like, I don't know that she's thinking
about it, but she probably has like entertained the idea that because Joe Biden's so old,
I could get it. Did y'all see the pictures of Kamala Harris' family, the second black family to
be in the White House? Yeah, I did. Oh, actually, I didn't see that. Really? Wait, are those her kids?
No, that's like, I think she's like half white. Well, yeah, but like, are those like her stepkids?
Well, it looks like her dad, right? Or maybe those are maybe that is her family. Okay, I didn't
somehow I just assumed this was like, like her family as in her parents, but maybe that's her
husband and kids. I yeah. Can't we just click on this link? No, no, no, those those have got to
be those are her kids. I mean, those kids have to be her step kids. They have to be your step kids.
Hold on. Wait, right. It says, wait, wait, I have to make sure I'm looking at the right person,
because it says something about the Brooklyn born attorney has two children, Colin Ella named after
jazz legends, John Coltrane and Ella Fitzgerald. And I'm just like, are we talking about these
two white kids named after these legendary black musicians? Wait, wait a fuck, wait, just a goddamn
second here. What's what's going on? I got I got to get to the bottom of this. Maybe it's just
overexposed. That's what it is. Yeah, Kamala Harris have no, no, no, they're her stepkids.
Yeah, I was right. Okay. Yeah. She I don't think she has any like, you know, real children.
Lamal. That's a funny image, though, with that context. The second black. Wait, wait,
but so wait, so they're not they're her stepchildren. So they're his children. But they are white kids
named after John Coltrane and Ella Fitzgerald, which is still white people can like jazz. Did
you don't be racist? It's just funny to me. Okay. So I have an uncle who is like myself white,
who married a black woman. They have mixed children who similarly were named after Quincy Adams
and Langston Hughes, Quincy and Langston. But it's just funny to me, because these kids are fully
white and are named after specifically like black legends, which I'm just wondering what was the
inspiration and impetus? Are they actually fully white as they look in this picture? What do you
mean they're fully white? I thought you said they were have black. They are they are. I can
all they're not her children. So I can all the dad must just be a be a big fan of music history.
You know, I guess good for him. I'm just thinking about the episode of Atlanta. Have any of you
seen Atlanta? No, really good show. But there's an episode about the main characters going to this
rich white guy's house where he's just like really obsessed with black culture and Africa and stuff
and like, but it's portrayed as like extra bizarre and cringe worthy. And it's really funny. And that
just this guy naming his kids that reminded me of that. Like like the like that professor
in Harambe. Yeah, like Harambe. Like taken to the extreme because he's a rich guy with a mansion
who's like having a like a whole soiree there. So like his whole house is just decked out with
like all this Africa shit. And it's pretty funny. Good show. Highly recommended. Donald Glover's
TV show, if you know him. Kamala is such a fucking cop. Yeah, it's really a Kamala. So I call them
by Don and Kamala like Godzilla monsters. Because there was there was something where like when
she was announced as the VP, they had misspelled her name is Kamala on something. And Mooncult
on Twitter had pointed out that like she also got like a massive facelift between when she was
like in between. If you look at pictures of her back during the back during the whole fucking
what's it called the tryouts for president. What the fuck am I thinking of primary primary.
The primary. If you look at the pictures of her back during the primaries and then like leading
up to when she was announced like a month or so maybe before she was actually announced as the VP.
She had a major like facelift. So her face looks totally different. And so Mooncult was already
predicting that she was going to be the VP. But it was not Kamala anymore. It's Kamala. It's Kamala.
The one with an E. She is now like Gamera. She is now Kamala.
Everyone I knew when we saw her in the primary we we said Kamala. And then I had I had to relearn
because there was a little bit of a kerfuffle. It's like no. Everyone's saying her name wrong.
Kamala. Kamala. Kamala. It's now Kamala. By Don and Kamala. By Don versus Godzilla.
I like to call I like to call Biden J Robb short for Joseph Robinette. That's that's my
that's my image. Is this. This isn't true. It is. It's totally different. That just
no that just looks like a smear frame or something. Yeah. This is just like a it's
like a fucking low res screen. It's just like weird like in the middle.
I'm looking for for comparisons. I'm looking at I don't know like I'm looking at the before
and after pictures and like I can kind of see a difference but it could look at her cheeks man.
Look at her cheeks. They look different. I mean she is making a different facial expression. So
I really like people are definitely going out of their way to find the ugliest
little sort of screenshots to take. She's not a pretty woman. I mean let's be honest.
She's fine. I think she's actually older than she looks. I was going to say I think she looks
pretty good for her age like like you like you thought that that picture of her and her kids
was like her dad and her siblings. Right. Well I hadn't like looked at her. She's 56 years old.
So yeah she looks. She's pretty good. She looks pretty good. 56 yeah. Not that it really matters
for anything but you know it really doesn't. These fucking pictures are hilarious though.
I'm sure they will all scroll in. I'm scrolling. One of them looks like she's about to sneeze.
Oh we got we got an imposter. We got a fake.
Fake Kamala Harris. There she is. It's proof. She's wearing someone else's skin. What do you mean?
What do you mean fake? Fake what? Fake body? Fake face. Fake face. It's her face on someone
else's body. They swapped her. They pulled the switcheroo. That's makeup. That's just
what? What are they circling? I don't know what they're circling. Scooby-Doo.
I really yeah I don't. It seems like it feels like they just took a photo and then drew circles on.
But I think it is makeup. Yeah. Of course it's makeup. It wouldn't actually be a skin thing. Face.
Stop trying to cover it up. Stop trying to cover it up. Stop shilling for mainstream media.
Stop trying to cover it up like people try to cover up your mouth with the COVID
masks that are fake and it's all fake. Stop trying to cover it up like you want all of our all of
our white women to cover up with the uh with the uh oh what's the with the hijab you fucking Marxist.
Yeah. Is that what people are thinking? You haven't seen the like the meme that's like oh 2020
everyone has to wear a mask 2021. Like forced feminization. Everyone will like everyone will
no no it's forced Islamization. Everyone will have to wear the hijab.
Yeah that's where that's where it's going. That's where it's going.
Soon. Or wait is the hijab the head wrap or which one's like the full body? It's like
it's like it's gonna progress. It's gonna progress. The burqa is the full body. Yeah.
Yeah it's mask 2020 2021 hijab 2022 burqa. It's it's interesting that like this kind of stuff
globalism progresses to where people will say things like like the fact that we make it okay
for people to choose what they want to do somehow translates to people are going to be forced to
do X like yeah like I mean it's it's been like that with uh I mean I guess I guess if people are
really saying this about the hijab like do people think that? I mean I'm sure some people I'm sure
fucking like you believers yeah I think it would be like gay marriage stuff like that yeah yeah like
people would make it up as a meme and then like an old guy being like oh look what I saw on 4chan
oh it's true they're gonna do it they're gonna do it yeah they did it with like gay marriage they
said like oh well if we legalize it it'll normalize it and everyone will turn gay come out and they
do it with trans people too yeah it's like oh well you know they're they're gonna they're if we make
you know if we normalize it they're gonna give all our kids hormones whatever they're gonna there's
a lot of using kids to um to pretend like they're looking out for yeah they're looking out for people's
uh well that's how that's how it is that's how it is with everything like this it's like oh well
it's a it's a slippery slope they just know what it actually thinks they find things to be gross
yeah it is I mean don't expose our kids it's it's child it's child abuse to uh to have a kids
watch Steven Universe and see a lesbian marriage because then they're gonna grow up thinking that's
okay I mean do you turn them gay do people really think that like you know people are going to um
like performs like like there's gonna be surgery done on like five-year-olds like they know I think
as long as somebody doesn't see critically at all no that's not how it works like it seems like
that's a pretty easy fix well that that's that's the scare that's the scare uh and it doesn't
it doesn't matter that it doesn't really happen when people like hear about something and they
find it scary they'll they'll you know it'll their imagination will run away with them and they
won't think critically and they'll just keep that fact quote unquote in their head and whenever it
comes up again they'll be like oh but did you know they're gonna this is gonna lead to like
they're gonna do surgery on babies and it's just not right and it's like they have nothing they
have not thought about it for even one second well there's people who think that's already
happened the fear keeps it locked in there it's not even I mean there's that it's gonna happen that
it's already happening you because that's what they think puberty blockers are you can find reports
you can find reports of like that's like seem to corrupt I mean you can find evidence that
seems to corroborate like any any crazy position you want to take like there are like there are
stories there are horror stories of like oh you know some some therapist with an agenda like you
know brainwashed my kid into thinking he's a girl now or something and or like oh they want to give
they want to give my kid fucking like hormone therapy when they're like two years old and like
I don't know I think generally those are like either extreme outlier cases or like you know
the truth has been spun a little bit and if you dig in it's like it's really not as it's really
not as black and white as maybe the headline made it sound I see that all the time yeah I mean what
I mean by what I said is like the fringe cases will will let people assume that it is the only
thing that's happening and that it's always happening and then there's no there's no like
nuance to it if it's scary it's all scary all the way if there's no there's no chance that it could
be somewhat okay if it's scary and you don't like it you can always find evidence to point to
and be like look look this happened somewhere and you know this is this is what they want to do this
is what the the whatever the left or something wants uh uh the globalists who you can you
find evidence to uh uh bolster any any position any arbitrarily chosen position you you might have
if you want get a look at the data you're gonna follow the data so I said about circumcision show
me the data Ben you could have just seen the data by now I know people have mentioned but I didn't
you've you've had weeks and weeks I just don't care that much it's just I don't I don't understand
why we keep getting circumcision voicemails what are you talking about I don't think it's a big deal
I don't think it's that big a deal I'm not that interested in it but people seem to get
people seem pretty invested in it oh like the the whether you should circumcise babies
yeah okay oh I've we we've literally had this conversation before you and me I have I have I
think I have come off I have come off more pro circumcision in my arguments than I think I really
am I I'm not like really like strongly like pro we should do it don't do it don't and I would say
I would I would I would agree with what you said last time Gib I think it was you about like
you know if if there's no like need for it it's probably best to default to not doing it
yeah or give or give the kid the choice give the kid the choice if if possible I think I think
that's probably like if I was born with a penis and I had been circumcised I don't know other people
feel different but I would be pissed I would be mad but not everyone feels that way well I mean
but why I mean why would you be pissed if it didn't cause you any problems oh I just think
it's cool why why would like it just seems like a weird thing for someone else to decide for you
yeah exactly I'll give you I'll give you I'll agree with that we should we should have a surgery
to add extra for skin yeah like why would you default to taking an action specifically to remove
something rather than just let it be and then yeah take the action later I don't know I mean
I mean we should do every surgery you can on a baby you would make it like as strong as possible
there would need to be like I don't know if like um if there were like a really high incidence of
like I don't know some kind of medical problem happening in lots of people if like you didn't
circumcise babies I'd be like maybe it's for the best if we circumcise their babies it doesn't
really it doesn't really seem to be the case though so dude what if what if you could do a
surgery at a baby that would like make them not like die of old age like that's the biggest killer
do you that'd be pretty sick actually do you think do you think people will be like ah that's not
fair I'm gonna die in this baby give them a choice yeah no like what if they what if they want to
die like I want to die says the person who's going to die oh you mean like they just even
though it's like just an objectively good thing people would say no don't do it because it's not
fair because like I didn't get the chance yeah no that's where I was going to go with it it's like
well I didn't get the surgery so you know I'm gonna be better about it and not give my kid the surgery
hmm uh I I would I mean I would be better about it yeah but I mean I have no argument
I haven't I have no argument against you oh yeah Ben you fear death more than anyone that I know
nice nice oh pussy that's a great that's a great that's a great uh uh uh distinction
to have I'm proud I'm proud to wear that it's a nice little tidbit that Ben is the most death
fearing like the superlatives most likely to thank you sad when he died most likely to be
said I will most likely to be said in the grave I'll be down it's like darn I'll be down there
like punch the tail we'll shit fuck I can't believe this happened how could I have been so foolish
as to die it's fucked up man you know we should do it's fucked up we should talk about um art
stuff we should talk about art shit because we're art people yeah this is for art this is art podcast
Kazi you're art you're an artist what is your art inspiration what do you you draw you've been
you've been recently I say recently but like for a while now I've been getting into a more of a
a child child ish drawing esque sort of way of drawing that's really cool yeah free and like
unrestricted mmm then how to describe exactly um little little space yeah the word is that you're
looking for you're like noggin core like like you know nick jr noggin that shit noggin super noggin
core um yeah um I don't know I I just am drawn to that style of work I don't know I I mean I I've
had people say that my work looks like I don't know different from shit that they've seen
but I really think it's just a matter of perspective because I mean like I don't know
I I am ripping plenty of people off as all good artists do I think I'm just ripping off a
different pool of artists than people normally look at that's perfect that's exactly how to become
someone who everybody thinks is good is that either they haven't seen what you're ripping
off or you're ripping off so many things that it no longer looks like anything else
yeah I think I finally I've made it to that point in my career where like I was ripping off
just like I was always ripping somebody off at every given time until I couldn't tell who I was
ripping off anymore now I'm like oh I must just be ripping off myself is that for like music or
videos or everything mostly videos or just writing in general um yeah for sure I mean I am I'm
strongly of the belief that to be a good artist you need to study good artists intensely
I think that you really need to look at some masterful work and really break it down and just
hard it's hard to look at it intensely wait why it's hard I just I like I look at things I love
and I'm like oh this is so good I enjoy watching or reading this this thing and then to study
intensely to understand it is like I gotta go back and look closer zoom in like what are they doing
bore this isn't the same as watching or reading the thing um I I don't I don't like look at a lot
of art but like I do if I see something that is very striking I do like to like look and be like
oh how'd they do that oh like what's the what try and try and like reverse engineer what the technique
was no I think I definitely don't do enough of stuff like that I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm stagnating in
my art skill it's hard it's hard yummy too it's hard to differentiate between the art that you like
to look at and the art that you like to make um I don't know if you guys have done this before but
I've had points where I will look at an artist and be like oh like I really love their stuff and I
really like to look at it and so like I want to make stuff that is more like this and then when I
try to um try to do that it it doesn't feel right it doesn't yeah I'm not inclined to do it that way
and so you I don't know it's a hard thing to to navigate and to figure out like what
do I actually like to do rather than what do I like to look at
that's yeah like sometimes like I will draw something like this and I will be very happy
with it even though it's like extremely low quality yet like low effort but like
you know there's not a lot of thought put into where things go it just sort of feels right
and then I think and then I think of like all of the other things I want to do and that
they don't look like this they look like other artists they like and they're better than me
and I'm like I don't know how to I tried to I tried to doodle something I tried like I just
like was like I haven't drawn anything in a while I'm gonna just draw something and I like
put down a piece of paper and I picked up a pen I was like okay here we go and I like drew a face
and I put a hat on it and I was like I hate this this is the worst thing I've ever done
how do people how do people do this and I ripped it up and I went to sleep that's a classic tale
that's a classic artist's tale thank you it's all this time yes um I mean with with Gib like
I don't know I guess something that I've been unlearning is I've been going through
college because I go to school for illustration right now and I'm in my senior year is like
I like basically learning all of the the fundamentals and stuff so that I can undo them
and I'm sort of like I mean I was I was going through sort of a phase in early college where
I was trying to use these techniques and you know anatomy and stuff like that and like
I think I don't I don't really know if you have to have a strong understanding of the fundamentals
to like get to this point but I think for a lot of people and for me it's sort of like you learn
how to do things properly and then you you sort of undo that like I'm very much going towards
a simplified like very scribbly sort of style and like the stuff you draw looks very easy to do
to an untrained eye but like it's it's it's clear that there's a lot of skill that goes into deciding
how exactly to draw the script you know I've um so doing the doing the like um art on like the
inside doodles for the vapors I've been using Copics which is a lot like watercolor basically
so I've been actually like doing color which is weird for me but it's fun and I like it and I found
this that is good at colors you should do it it comes out kind of good it actually comes out
kind of good sometimes I'm like oh wow thank you um I like yeah I like it and I found this
artist on Twitter they're called corn um Magna Galina as they're at and they do like fairly
elaborate not not like super elaborate like at their cartoony but they do um watercolor or Copic
or something art and I sometimes they will post like a little like work in progress shots where
they'll have like they'll have the line work and then they'll show like just the shading
like what they do is like they they go in with like a light color and they shade in like the
shaded parts and then they color over it and like the shading like kind of carries over into the
final I think it's really cool to look at those sometimes the ones with just shading kind of
have their own kind of cool like they're very mono color and like and and I don't know they're
nice in their own way and so I've been I don't know I've been uh interested in that kind of thing
oh I'm looking at some right now uh uh uh let me find let me find a good one no that would
sucks I think they're all sometimes I just I don't have enough of um the the sort of
constant artist drive to improve that I need in order to improve correctly like I I don't know
like a lot of the time it just goes like I I don't care about all of this stuff for a very long time
and um I'm paying for it because I'm not improving and that's just it sucks
I think you are by default improving I've got all of these like like fucking anatomy books
uh like out on tabs and I'm looking through and I don't care I just like I leaves too easily I mean
like personally I don't necessarily get better by way of like necessarily practicing if I'm already
as good as I can be at what I'm doing it's like you gotta learn something new to want to do you
know like yeah like it's not a matter of like linearly improving in the direction you're going
so much as like okay well what can I add to this now so I think you might need to find something
that you want to imitate again like something that newly makes you think like oh well fuck
if I could incorporate some of that in here like that would be perfect you know maybe you need to
be doing more searching than practicing I heard this advice somewhere I don't remember where it
might have been a professor that said it to me but um it was it was like I think the a lot of the
moments where you sort of make these breakthroughs with your work are usually when you're just fucking
around and not when you're like consciously trying to do something yeah like if you're trying to like
I'm going to sit down and practice or I'm going to do this rather than just um I'm like I mean as
though like like practice is important but I mean those moments when you're sort of like when something
just happens when you just sort of make something and you're not really intending to um those are
a lot of moments where I've this is like oh I can do this it's like that John Cleese thing again
sort of reminds me of the John Cleese uh creativity lecture yeah it's about playing yeah
oh I've never seen that I mean I the other day it's really good the other day I randomly was
drawing and I came up with this and I think this is like pretty good compared to what I usually do
doodle I like yeah I love this the shadow on the underside of the hair looks really good
and it's like how cool but uh I I don't know it it's frustrating that I just can't keep
it like yeah it happens by these things happen by accident they happen by accident and they don't
stick around and I'm like I don't know I know that like the upward the the more you do stuff
it doesn't really matter whether you're doing it right as much as you know just continually doing
it the upward trend quality of your work will increase over time um so like the like I wouldn't
have been able to do this a couple of years ago um casually because I since then I learned
little bits here and there but like I don't know there's there's always this pressure because I see
good art all the time I'm always looking at Instagram and Twitter and it's like great art just by
people and it's you know I know not to compare myself to them but there's this underlying
sort of pressure that like if I practice more rigorously or or like just do more drawing generally
more often than like this would improve better and faster and I don't know I I mean I I've been
in the same position it's really hard to not compare yourself I think I've gotten I don't know
if I would say as good as I can be at it but I I've gotten pretty good at developing a mentality
where I look at art that I really like and go this is fucking amazing I can't do this right now but
like I can see a path to getting there and that's really motivating to think of it that way and I
I don't know because I know for a lot of people it's hard you you can't just sort of snap your
fingers and have that mentality about it but if you can try to get yourself to a place where you're
looking at someone that you really look up to and you say you know I like I can do that I can see
a way to getting there for me honestly I've kind of left the mentality that like I have any control
over what I'm going to create like I just see it as like it's one thing to fantasize about like I'm
going to go in this direction I'm going to like my art's going to end up like this but like it's
just not like it's going to end up being whatever it ends up being by way of like you can push it
in a way you want it to go but like you can't predict what your hand is actually going to do
like with by thinking about it you know so it's just like at the end of the day I've kind of given
up on trying to like scheme out like okay here's my path forward or like I'm gonna do this kind of
thing and this kind of thing I'm just like I'm just gonna do whatever it happens that I end up wanting
to do when I happen to want to do it and hope it works out somehow what about my plans plans
the best laid plans of mice and men are always shitty gay garbage that's what the sense right
I read I love that book uh they my problem my problem is uh is a motivation uh I think I feel
like I could do anything yeah but I just don't I don't want to I'm more along those lines there's
nothing there's nothing that I actually want to do well I've learned I mean there's there's some
I've there's some things that are fun to do most of them are drugs and the main reason to work is to
have money so you can buy them um I I I I don't know I feel like I don't know I can look at this
like this this artist is really good and I feel like I can see kind of how he does this thing and
like if I were like man I really want I really feel like drawing a picture of fucking Gabriel
with some skulls and some and a chalice and a sword and a cross and some scale I could be like
fuck yeah and then I could put some work in and it would take me a while but I could plan it out
put it in uh do this like I know how to do all this stuff it none of this looks like impossible
to me but it's like why what what would possibly possess me yeah of the desire to do that's more
the way I have tend to find myself it's like I look at things and I'm like okay I see how this
could happen but like they already did it like yeah do I need to do this or it is like do I just
what like can I I guess on some level it's like experiencing the ego death of just like being happy
that it exists and not like and not feeling like I had to be involved you know like like sometimes
you see something you like and you feel like oh I have to find some way to replicate this so I can
like show that I get it you know but it's like oh you don't have to like that person got it they
made it you know right yeah I feel like there's I don't know the the um because you post things
online and the whole world everyone in the world is watching that you know the the career of of
Gibb and take what is what is it what are they gonna do next um and I feel like I don't know if if
if it turns out that I'm only doing this to perpetuate what I've already been doing and I
don't actually care about doing it that would suck you know so I feel like I gotta like oh I
want to improve it out and I want to make comics because I said that I want to make comics and
want to improve art many times and so it feels like it's it's written in stone and I'm just
that's where you're continuing to do it that's where your compulsion is taking you and follow it
always follow it I mean it's just it's just hard to know because like I've been taking a break for a
while and I was just getting back into it like yeah maybe yeah I've been just kind of like
nickel and diming my way around making stuff like not really committing myself to trying to make
something with a lot of intentionality but just like letting things like I have a documentary
I'm gonna edit that's like I just took two weeks around the US and filmed whatever happened you
know so it's like that kind of incidental work it's more appealing to me now where you just kind of
look at it in the editing bay and say well what can I make this into as opposed to like going in with
a plan you know I I'm a little fucked uh my tablet not my tablet my my cintiq broke oh shit really
there is a thing that I yeah like it still works but like the screen yeah it does but the screen is
just black and I don't know I'm yeah so like without the screen uh a couple years okay um it's
like it's not that because mine's a couple years old too and I'm like I'm really it's a big investment
I really don't want to have to replace it it still works except at the screen except the screen just
doesn't show anything the screen is black so I'm hoping that maybe if I can bring it to some kind of
like repair shop or something they'll like there's something they can do about it and I have no idea
uh if that's true or not I will just have to uh uh see but like there yeah there is um after the
after all the vapor's kickstarter stuff there is some stuff I was gonna start working on but um
it I really I really don't want to draw it with a mouse I don't want to do that so
would you be able to use um the tablet without a screen because I can't I can't do it uh no
yeah I can like I used to use I had a lock on bamboo that I use like 50 bucks on ebay and like I
use that for years and years and years um and uh only like relative only like in the last like
maybe two years or so did I switch to the cintiq and I did come to like it and now that I don't
have it I'm like yeah fuck but I now use I use the bamboo forever I I bought a bamboo when I was
like 12 because I wanted to draw um warrior cats fan art on I want to draw on the computer um
and I could not do it I did not have the hand-eye coordination to do it and I to this very day I'm
still a little bit perplexed at people that can do it so well I can only barely I mean it's just
you just gotta you just like learn and it's just about like muscle memory to like know
where the where your hand will go and where the mouse will go it I don't know I feel like there's
just something that I just can't but that's just not clicking with me I mean I used a um I used
like an iPad to draw in my teenage years for digital and um when I was 16 I got the cintiq
that I still use today and it's my favorite thing that I have ever owned and I was just like
yeah I need to get this because if I don't then I have no other way of making digital art
Cassie can you type while not looking at the keyboard um
kind of a little bit um I never learned how to type properly I type I don't type the way you're
supposed to but I can type like at a normal speed what with your fingers on home row no yeah no I
does anybody type does anybody type like they tried to teach me and I didn't like it was too late
for me like I had already taught myself to just home row the home row is when you have your your
fingers on the ASD and the Jkl and like you know it's like oh to hit F you use your index finger
from the D and then to hit I it's your middle finger from the K and and you know yeah I don't
formula I don't know how to do that anybody does that I have my own system and I know people
who didn't learn that way and they do type way faster surely I well I didn't I thought everyone
did it that way I don't know I assumed that I was one of you who like didn't learn how to type right
they tried to teach me yeah I mostly default to having like my fingers on um AWD because of
video games they'll be watched yeah and then from there I can type lots real quick but I actually
don't know that I look at the keyboard when I type now that I think about I like glance down in it
I like mostly use muscle memory but like I do look down at it so I'm like half and half uh
what are we talking about talking about tablets tablets I'm just still scrolling through
magna galina's feed he's so good yeah I wasn't sure what you meant when you're talking about the
shadows um but when you posted this yeah these two like but you see yeah no I see now what you're
talking about yeah was that like a physical drawing or yeah it's water yeah oh cool yeah water color
water color for the yeah it's cool there's a oh man I just I just passed one I just passed a really
good one uh I'm gonna make you watch it I'm gonna make you look at this one where was it oh oh oh
oh yeah here we go yeah here we go watercolors watercolors are so fucking cool they are I'm
in a watercolor color class right now I'm watching it there was a there was a better one before where
like he starts in from scratch and like he's putting the shadow layer down over like the eyes uh
I don't know it's cool it's cool how like watercolor is like you like you put down the color
but like that's not it's not done you you have to like kind of like pull it and push it around
with the brush yeah it's it's it's water bending is what it is it is yeah yeah yeah it's like you
look at it and you're like I think my my instinct is like oh my god they're so like that's so scary
right like they're putting the brush down and like what if they what if they fuck it up like if they
fuck it up the drawing is ruined but no no no that's the trick that's what that's what the that's the
mind game you gotta be bold in fact yeah you be bold and if it works it looks great and if it
doesn't work you can push and pull it around no if it doesn't work you get and it'll be okay
if you really fuck it up um we had uh yeah if you if you're not bold you don't get anything
in my watercolor class we had um an artist come in to talk with us um he does a lot of
paintings of of boston he's local and um he showed us um sort of a time lapse video of
him doing some paintings and like I mean he he has like a you know a rough sketch underneath
and then he just sort of puts a wash of color over the whole thing and just like blocks in
these huge shapes um and I I feel like I don't know I'm trying to get over that um being like oh
but what if you know there's like a little part that I want to have in front of this part like
what if I ruin it by putting this big block of color down because you can't go over dark parts
with white parts yeah I don't know the way he did it it's very much like you you need to just be
confident just put that shit down yeah slap it on there yeah the art advice I keep giving getting
given is just like just draw sure lines stop trying to go back over your lines oh yeah everything's
gotta be done sure yeah it's the same it's the same idea if you do like bold lines then you get
then you get bold results and it and it looks more striking if you pet your lines in you just
look like a fucking cow I don't know yeah soft weak same with watercolor like it looks so good
when you're doing watercolor and you have like a section where you just have like one bold brush stroke
and it works yeah that's what it's like it's really impactful yeah well you know it kind of yeah it
kind of ties me into something I was saying um I don't remember if this is in pcp chat or where
earlier about how like I'm trying to think less in general as a human being because I don't think
that people make good decisions necessarily by thinking about them I think usually people just
know like like if they're if they're capable of making a good decision they will know relatively
quickly and it won't take that much thought like if you have to think about something a whole lot
you're probably not even fit to be like thinking about it you know what I mean you mean yeah I
think I know what you mean like like if I have to if I have to like finically like do my lines
it's because I'm like I don't know what I'm doing I don't like you know maybe I will eventually
do practice of doing this over and over again but like ultimately the way I will get good at drawing
lines is not by practicing about them shitty lines until they're good it's by just keep keep
trying to make good lines until you can do it you know like shitty lines don't build to good lines
is what I'm trying to say you have to be trying to make good lines and failing not like making
shittier lines on purpose I guess so it's like that's true so I think that applies to a lot of
different aspects of learning where it's like if if like when I write write a video I don't think
about it I just like have a general idea of what it's going to be about and like probably the first
sentence and then I just write it you know it just comes out of me and like it used to take
more thinking but now it takes less thinking and it's getting better but requiring less thinking
because it's just something I've practiced so much that like it is second nature it doesn't
take thought you know and like I think that's the ideal state you want to be in as a human
is that nothing you're doing takes thought at all like you you're just confident that you know what
you're doing and you just do it you know for sure there's a lot of value in having confidence in
general that's where I want to be there's a lot of value I think in having I mean if you're a visual
artist um a sketchbook that you know that you will never show anyone that's shit it can be like a
stack of printer paper and just like bang out really crappy drawings like in pen oh yeah all over
I do that all the time with like I don't know I'm I'm in a call and I'm just sort of fucking around
I open a photoshop document and I just draw in some crap that I will never show anyone unless
there's something funny and I'll post it just bang out like 51 minute sketches on a big page yeah
and then trash it like that's helpful um I haven't I've been doing a lot of digital stuff um
but you know I'm I'm recently getting back into some traditional art with the with the
watercolor and even back into um oil painting and I'm working on a project I don't think I
I should can say what it is yet but I'm very excited because um there's a guy it's really cool
he worked on homestuck stuff and I'm working with him on an orc it's not Andrew Hussie
and that's almost done I'm just doing the last bit of it can you not say the guy he didn't tell
me not to but I don't know but I mean like it it it might be like up by the time this episode is up
anyway so like you know um but the oil painting what'd you say look at these colors
look at these fucking colors I'm gonna die I'm gonna die just thinking about them
I like that pink that pink armor I like the blue like the shaggy body on that guy with the red head
yeah the all of those colors they're just really good mix with each other Greg's Greg's no Wayne's
cheekbones the yellow guy there's something about physical media it's just there's there's something
about media you can have it can if you do it if you lean into it it can bestow a certain texture
work that you just can't get with a brush yeah absolutely I mean this this oil painting that
I'm doing I'm I'm I find you've seen I named my oil paintings before um there's a painter named
Wayne Tebow you spell his last name thiebaud I think he's like fucking old the shit he's like
turning 100 um okay but he's really inspired how I go about painting um by like really packing on
the paint and using um the palette knife instead of a brush no not gouache yeah yeah yeah okay yeah
and just like really packing on the paint and it's just having it be really thick and sort of um
it's it's like it's like frosting a cake instead of painting a painting is what it feels like
it's like you're sculpting with the paint um that's what I'm doing for this project and it's really fun
hmm how do you decide what you want to paint or draw that's that's where I get that's where
I'm hung up if I if I was like if I had I feel like if I just had like boy I know exactly
what I want to like draw here I could it could it would be a masterpiece we tried drawing without
thinking about it beforehand and just see what happened yeah that's what I did I did I spent
five minutes doodling a face the other day and I was like no I'll never draw again this is a mistake
well I mean that's your problem I think you know that's your problem is that you stop yeah maybe
I mean it's like what did you said just um sort of banging shit out until you until it sticks I
guess I don't know but I also struggle with that like like knowing what like techniques I want to
use and like what colors I want to use and stuff but not having like a clear idea of what
it is that I want to make um yeah I've been there a bunch I guess I would just say doodle until
you come up until you're like oh I want to expand on this and I hate I hate doodling it's so embarrassing
embarrassing it's so yeah it's so embarrassing to like draw something and look at it and be like
what's the fan what's the point what's the point that's amazing that you can be embarrassed by your
own judgment yeah well I am easily easily fair enough uh yeah well you know it's it's just like
you you have in your head something that you you imagine when you start doodling usually
like you start drawing a figure and you're like I wonder if they're gonna be like posing like this
and you think of things like that then you look at what you're doing and it sucks yeah because it's
a doodle and you weren't really trying it makes me angry not so much embarrassed it's just angry
that's one of the stages is fury is white hot rage
yeah I mean I don't get angry quite so much anymore I just sort of like
I don't think I don't feel anything I'm just like drawing on like that sucks I haven't felt
that sense of like blockage only because of the fact that I again have not been holding myself
accountable to to do anything lately because I don't want to feel that blockage of like if I find
myself in a position where like nothing is coming out then my my stance was just do something else
like because otherwise I'm just gonna wallow in it like if I wallow in a feeling for more than five
minutes it's definitely a waste of time and I should definitely go do something else so like
you know if it that means I don't end up making anything for a while then it just means nothing
was going to be made you know I know the best thing is is to have characters that are so simple
that doodling them is you know you don't have to do very much for it to be correct
value such as a red man and yeah like there's a good way so just some stupid shit like this
where it's just like I'm just drawing a circle now it's red man he's talking about himself
Gib you have like the best character designs and like I just want like Gib I just want you
to like do these like funny like stupid little doodles that are you just like banging out really
fast and they're just like I don't know your stuff is hilarious I want you to like just make like a
book just of like drawings of this over and over again thankfully game that's what I wanted from
you I love that shit that's twitter well it was at least you were doing a lot of these on twitter
for a while uh yeah like the red man comics and an occasional doodle of things yeah I could maybe
I mean right now I'm working on making uh the bell shape book in in style of of like the the
homestuck books where they take the things and they take all of the good parts out of it as it you
know bees is it's like it's gifts it's animations it's stuff um and then ruin it by putting it on
paper and that's what I'm doing and so I want I want that to be fun that that's kind of fun in it in
like an art way in itself just figuring out how to lay out all these pages and making it look
professional and being like yeah these these terrible terrible drawings that were never meant
to be anything I am putting into like a book that's almost a joke in and of itself no it's awesome
but yeah I could definitely do another book of like just stupid doodle things I like yeah I like
physical media I like I like printing I like printing shitty ms paint drawings I think a book
of like really like stuff like particularly this red man one um would be a great like coffee table
book just like have on your table that people flip it open it's just ridiculous shit like what the
yeah that's what I was like it would be a great time I want that shit hardcover
or I mean even like I don't know I uh I had this I had a goal for a while that I did not
accomplish until recently which was um fill up an entire sketchbook with drawings that I think
look good scan the whole thing and put it on gumroad and I finally did it and it's great and I
I feel like you could do something like that um yeah that could be doable yeah I've gotten good
response from the gumroad book and I'm really happy and I'm gonna do another one that's quite easy
I know drawing's hard no no no like it's quite easy to just like scan it and put it up I mean
and then just like oh sure right as a like a pdf yeah just a pdf and every once in a while it's like
oh someone bought your thing just you know some some little passive how much is it um it's it's
minimum three bucks and um but a lot of people have been tipping very generously which I'm very
thankful for mm whales yeah yeah sims um I don't know I just figured it would be a good idea to be
like look it's like almost no money so you know yeah yeah you can't afford not to do it I bought I bought
um I should go buy it I bought I bought uh I bought the Six Tens album the other day
mm was it songs for songs for nice guys for nice guys beats for nice guys what a great
I bought it I haven't listened to it yet it's a great album well you did you could you two
both did like cover art right yeah I did yeah yeah yeah I didn't LaMau yeah and Anthony did
went to the art munchie um did one as well that's that's right um forgot forgot about that yeah it
was great I did I was like oh I'm gonna try you know sticking with the physical media kick I'm
just like I'm gonna do colored pencil and I did and I was like this looks great and then I scanned
it and I looked at it on my screen it looked like shit so I did a lot of editing in Photoshop
mm what did just the scan like didn't like read it well or I don't know something about
what was it on the screen there was just some areas that looked like I don't I don't explain
there was just areas that needed a lot of touching up um probably unnecessarily I think there's a lot
of um I don't know I do this as an artist I don't know if you guys do but there's a lot of
moments where you're looking at something you've made and you're like oh I gotta fix this
fucking thing it looks stupid and like you fix it and you notice the difference but no one else
would like you're just wasting your time yep truthfully I do that way too much like there's a
pixel out of out of the way like I should I should delete that pixel that's the wrong pixel
that wasn't intended by me the artist mm-hmm yeah and there and therefore therefore it is a problem
oh dang I didn't intend for this watercolor stroke to like blend with the other color and
like create a gradient like oh fuck I gotta delete it it's ruined that's the good shit when it blends
yeah yeah when when it that that face when it that face wait wait wait here we go this is this is
this is mfw it blends whoa that's what I look like good face good blend good good look good look
oh man fuck alright it's for losers well all right
yeah do we have do we want to go to voicemails then
how we've been good what oh we've been going for almost two hours haven't we
an hour and a half yeah okay yeah um kazzie you want to stick around for voicemails yeah sure
I forgot about those okay we do them there's there's there's like an average amount uh today
uh let me see how much is an average amount like seven maybe 20 oh we get a lot I had
there was one day where munchie we wrap it we wrap it fire him he was in charge of picking
which ones went on the show and so we were listening to them together so you had a dream
wait did you say you had a dream no not a dream it was not a dream it was it was real and it was
it was that munchie was in charge of picking the voicemails for an episode and so we listened to
all of them and I could not believe the level of quality how fucking bad they all were like the
ones that got in wait just like okay but the ones that don't get it on the pcp yeah wait oh that
must have been an old episode that oh it was I mean it was when munchie was on so it was quite a while
ago um oh okay there are some really um yeah no they're smells no they're they're bad yeah they're
really bad but it's okay um this one is called um ha ha bread you guys okay yeah yeah we're
three two one listen click play it all at the same time all right three two one go
hey so I found this really weird channel it's called rotating bread studios it's just a bunch of
videos of pictures of png's of bread rotating check it out it's prey based content I'm there
I'm there I can already picture it on my mind I don't feel like I even need to go see get out
this is uh like I get shocked I mean there's I mean my there's a little more to space no
oh just like just in it just an image yeah it's just a piece that it was just like a flat
I've seen the whole thing in my mind now although this one is my I didn't expect the Mike Myers in
the background of the bread 43 subscribers on a rotating bread studios okay it should be
rotating the other way I don't know why that's your critique the thing yeah the thing that's
wrong with rotating bread studios the bread rotates clockwise and I just it's too predictable it's just
everything rotates clockwise I want to shake it up it's just like the flat side should be like
pushing down it doesn't matter if we move on okay okay okay next next one is called a message from
our troops three two one go okay so I'm in the navy and I just returned from a six month deployment
and what do I find when I get back Gib and Digi have drank so much soy that they are now women
Ben has stolen Nate's soul and banished him to the shadow realm that's right has gone full
cuck and enacted communism on the podcast man imagine coming to her now for some reason
as I understand it once she has transcended from the virtual world into the real world and can now
come to my house and beat me up in real life which is truly scary I've done that in the first place
Tom is the only normal one left for the love of God Tom just save this train wreck of a podcast
oh is this what you were I can't tell if that was serious or a joke it feels like a joke
Tom is this what you were talking about yeah I like that Tom is the most I think it was a
joke with just kind of a weak punchline Tom who was going to like live in his car and make like
CG in a car it was like the most normal this this is a this is a thing it's true Tom you
I think a lot of people say I think some people say Tom is the is the is the normal
one but I think he Tom is just Tom is just the one that nobody has the voice of reason
that does not make him the normal one none of us are the normal one there's no such thing as
a normal pcp member Tom Tom is Tom is safe apple check and uncontroversial Tom is the apple jack
yeah so the hot wand the yeah that's right that's right he wears he wears the the boots the
really you know the boots he looks great the next one is called just kill them three two one go
hey guys I live in Utah and every day when I'm driving to school I see mega flags everywhere
and it's a big problem it's really cringe so guy who predicted that the next mass shooting
should be in Utah uh yeah yes please um please uh let's get rid of these guys if there's a mass
shooting in Utah they're the ones that are going to do it so I would be careful what I wish yeah
like I just called for a mass shooting yeah yeah oh god he did yeah
uh I'm gonna well I'm gonna have to respectfully respectfully disagree with you was the word that
you use uh disavowed that's the word I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm gonna vote no I'm gonna vote no
on the mass shooting but I respect my political opponents no I have mass conversations instead
uh next one is called agent e three two one go hello Ben this is agent e our organization hopes
that you have had a great week no I don't not not really Mr. T fuck off mr go outside
use me classic yes ma'am I trust you've taken the time to consider our last message
we still have the summarized body but what we intend to do with it is strictly confident
you're gonna do sticky to it although our purpose for you Ben we want your brain
boo unique no your special Ben no thanks you see only you have the ability to both be an insufferable
bleeding heart liberal cuck yeah but also a utilitarian fascist dictator of the fictitious
voice jail only you thought you freed everybody from could argue the medical merit no not everybody
without actually knowing any of the science behind it Ben if you give us your brain we will
tell you the truth about the implanted samurai memories the secret origin consider the offer
we'll speak to you again next week Ben is this a recurring thing all right people or who's this
person there's a lot uh there's a lot of lore there's like a lot of backstory it looks uh
does it not matter it it matters to me um i hope you can work that out with yourself
how can i how can i how can i is there a way to make it matter to the audience as well
positive no okay that's all i would hope that they're all i would hope that they're already
invested um um you would help wait i'll give my brain in exchange for the samurai secret how
how would i how would i know the secrets then no i'm i this seems like bad deal bad deal
bad deal back to the drawing book you're fired you have a you have a counter offer
um nah i just not fuck it uh the samurai memories ah who needs them
yeah fuck you scroll scrolls gone i don't need to know about my tragic past it's it's
from probably better off not knowing next one next one is called uh milk main i don't know what
that means three two one go yeah so uh just listen to the latest episode i mean i wouldn't
have looked up that shoplifting comment for myself and uh i don't know i think i think the main issue
i see with it at least comes down to the tone like it doesn't really come across as a poor kid you
steal because they can't order so much as a spoiled fridge cube you just steal it no well it's not
that thing that was going on facebook no no no i don't understand what this guy's saying he sounds
i cannot hear a word he's saying i had to turn i had to turn up my headphones as high as they
would go i could make it out no he this is a vein this is a vein of of complaining this is a vein
of complaining about mallory what did he say uh you say like he said like uh the reason i didn't
like the comic where the shoplifting is because it comes off more as a spoiled rich kid instead of
a poor kid and like you you listen to the podcast she explained that no that's not what's going on
so shut up shut the fuck up i'm sick of it no more i will not fucking we had an entire podcast
talking about it there's no more discussion to be had no never again all right no more
voicemails about mallory it's over i'm with you based on this alone i don't know the whole context
but i know the comic you're talking about yeah uh we literally talked about it for hours there's
nothing more to be said did you really you talked about that one comic for hours well okay no not
no no you got it when was that uh is it worth listening two weeks ago there's a few yeah a few
episodes ago we had mallory on she made the comic and we talked about it with her okay yeah i didn't
know yeah we're high rollers we we have pull we have big pull in the industry we get we get the big
names we get big guests like kezi snap yeah next week i'm sure john tron john tron we're gonna convert
him back to john tron or away from i don't know we're gonna convert him to the opposite of whatever
he is in every aspect we gotta we just gotta we just gotta get him to say i don't know we go you
gotta get him to say um uh trans right yeah yeah get him to say trans right that that'll put us on
the map i i gotta know did you did you uh was was having me on like a last minute decision of like
oh shit we don't have any guests today let's just get some bullshit was that it no no i since
well i had not asked anyone i had not like asked anyone about guesting and i don't know give you
just said like i i wanted to ask kazi i think i don't i don't remember you explain it because you
did it uh well yeah kazi said why don't i get on the pcb uh and i was like yeah why not i guess
and then i then from then on i was like let's get kazi on at some point
okay i mean yeah uh yeah i mean i did mean i guess i i never actually asked about i did i did
kind of intend that she would come on at some point and now here we are well now that um
let's see if craig now that now that munchie isn't on the podcast anymore uh now that munchie's not
anymore now i'm not breaking the no girlfriends rule so i guess that's why we this is like um
this it's like uh you're like um you know like legend of dragoon when you well your your green
party member dies but then like a new green party member dies who's basically just like a model swap
you're like that no munchie you're just like munchie munchie died but was like immediately
replaced by kazi which is basically just basically just munchie wearing a bow um yeah
yeah exactly well i mean i i mean i don't know i knew all of you guys anyway so it's true just like
uh okay next one next one is called uh sheva's guard three two one go
all right i've got a math problem i need your help with so if an anime being bad is a negative
and an anime's english dub is a negative and if a negative times a negative is a positive
does that mean the dub of a bad anime becomes a good anime because it's adding not multiplying
no you because you don't times them to you don't multiply it's it's a it's additive yeah
unfortunately so you can't uh you can't logic your way out of this one get rekt by math get rekt
get rekt fucker uh next one we're rapid firing next one is called make mary pcp three two one go
imagine the next pcp episode starts and everyone's introducing themselves like
i'm ben saint and i'm fucking gay yep my name's tom oliver my spine is broken and i want to kill
myself my name's gibb and nobody wants to believe that i'm british and i'm mary the newest member of
the procrastinated podcast like whoa wouldn't that be sick if mary was the newest member of the
procrastinated podcast guys you need to make mary the newest member of the procrastinated podcast
that would be still sick just saying you should message mary on twitter or wherever and be like hey
join you should you should you should you should be the newest member of the pcp i thought i was
gonna be the new mage after mage left i was gonna be like the girl replacement yeah but now but now
but now mary's the new mage mary's the new mage kazi's the new munchie um who else died um i don't
know cyber shell is the new nate yeah that makes sense uh what about fit mc oh no fit mc would be
the new nate uh cyber shell would be the new divu obviously obviously who's the new monkey and jeff
um uh aria can be the new monkey and did she can be the new jeff aria aria aria can be the new
endless jeff uh and uh uh uh gym storm dancer is the new jeff i i guess yeah sure that's that's
your speed so mean right now i know why would you do that for gym storm dancer i don't know um
what's wrong with being jeff because i'm cruel and capricious jeff's my favorite member jeff's my
favorite member too frankly the show really went down i don't know why i'm mean i literally know
zero about jeff uh okay everyone shut the fuck up next voicemail is called random pc prisoner
three two one go oh no fuck margar escaped and wasn't dead oh well that oh well at least they're
not gonna send message anymore because they escaped and their character is over and when i say at least
i mean drats that's so sad oh holy shit that timmy the taught small person whatever the fuck oh
drats they're not gonna send messages leaving an update about their voicemail holy shit is that
Liam uh my real personal friend in real life who i have to now talk to knowing they're bad at
leaving pcp voicemail oh shit they're dead too but i see them just outside the pcp grades um well
drats uh this is all so sad but um i suppose it must be the case so fuck oh golly gee oh it's so
sad oh i'm crying i'm crying so hard that all these deaths and escapes and all these people who
won't won't send voicemails anymore unless they're specifically funny or good um it's that margar
who uh who has escaped and their character is over so who will never try to send voicemails from
beyond the grave that has cracked the code so oh geez this is all so sad uh time to go
being spirited somewhere she's realized that you can you can you can literally just make pcp
canon pcp prison canon whatever you want just by saying it uh uh all that's canon now bev i can't
make it five there's nothing there's nothing you could do about it um no not all makes sense it
all makes sense uh if you're if you're up on the lore which of course uh all of our true listeners
will be so uh wink wink and a nod to all you at home uh next up uh
uh speaking of liam real life friend who now bev has to speak to uh we've got like three
we've got like three from liam so let's okay three two one go uh yikes that uh last uh that last
when i was on that was fucking terrible uh i sounded like i was acting like i was high uh please
forgive me for like the honor of my entire like dead extended family yeah uh got shit no more uh
chow follow liam liam overdrive on twitter no my fingers
like this is this is the time i like to see what happened here is like liam like did the voicemail
was like oh that was great and then bev was like that was fucking terrible liam was like oh really
like shit well i better apologize and then apologize was like that was great now i'm gonna
chill my twitter like i think i'm not sure if liam was responding to bev's call or just to our
reaction to his last mail last time i don't i don't remember i feel like we criticized him
i take it you grilled this this this call i probably yeah i mean we grill basically all of them
well let's see if there's anything left to grill in the other two calls that they
said or no there's only one there's just one more okay three two one go let us all take a second
to talk about how fucking based and cool transformers are all right yes fucking Gundam fans fucking
god damn uh anime robot mech fans fucking gay blown the fuck out get out of here your robot people
don't turn into cars i'm gonna give this like 30 seconds saying dude your shit doesn't it just
walks around and flies that's fucking gay oh god the crime dog the greatest robot future space
that of all time no no it's over it's over no and the voicemail transformers fucking amazing liam
thanks thanks for letting me make a video just make a video about how cool the transformers are
yeah sure yeah you got a whole essay here there are you could you could do better you could there
are better visuals there are better mediums than pcp voicemails i've been watching a mecha anime
recently and it it turns into jet planes and cars and it's not transformers well i supposed to
pause the badmobile no it's a space runaway idion or something oh idion i don't know that one good
it's the one that gundam boy made right uh after gundam oh what's the gundam guy's name i know it
tomi no tomi no yeah okay yeah yoshi yuki tomi no robots are stupid robots are bad they're all
right you drew a pretty cool robot one time i did i did draw i know i know exactly the one
you're talking about for for inktober oh yeah i don't remember what it looks like but i remember
it being good uh it looks like that pokemon that looks like a big ant the ultra beast oh yeah a
little bit like the yeah it looks kind of like that but as a robot i will you know what i will try
and scroll back through twitter and see if i can find the one you're talking about i think it posted
somewhere um okay next next up we got uh ben i get it you're a penis centrist three two one go
so uh you suggested say one out of a million people get their dicks fucked up from circumcision
where one out of a million people gets their dick fucked up from not washing it enough
if they are uncircumcised uh in the former group you can't control what happens to you
in the latter group you can it's your own failing to not wash it yeah so i'd rather be a part of
that latter group even still yes uh additionally yes the comparison to vaccines uh vaccines have
a very very tangible benefit and have far less pain than the circumcision and i know i know the
pain doesn't really matter it's ephemeral like who really cares this is the pain is just like an
addendum to the fact that it is still otherwise neutral the point is oh well if it doesn't matter
then uh why bother with this thing that just has basically no benefit uh has a very slight risk of
of things going worse and like kind of sucks for a couple seconds like there's no point in
bothering if circumcision didn't already exist we wouldn't like create it there was there would
be no need to create it like if i could say oh uh suppose that your armpits uh could could never
get stinky if you skinned them as a baby uh and it's ephemeral pain that you won't remember uh
and you won't have to put deodorant on but it's like we wouldn't do that if it were possible
because that's stupid just wear deodorant okay isn't this this just seems like the most obvious
arguing like he's right no like i don't even know why you guys had this argument his first
argument is wrong his first argument is wrong but i like yeah i agree that if it didn't exist we
probably wouldn't invent it in most cases it's like yeah true you're right about that but i really
hate the first part where you're like oh like i lay out this hypothetical where oh what if one in a
million people who circumcised gets lose their dick versus one in a million people who isn't
circumcised you know loses their dick for a different reason like i know that's not necessarily the
case i just but in this hypothetical situation it's like oh well i would rather be the second one
because it's my choice like no like if that doesn't that doesn't matter like if you fucking lose your
dick for whatever reason you you you currently would not rather to have made the choice that led
you to lose your dick you would be talking about how much of a fucking moron you had been your whole
life like it doesn't matter whether it was your choice or not i'm positing that for whatever reason
in each scenario one person loses their dick and it's equally bad the whole point of that scenario
is that it's equally bad and i won't do this oh well at least then it would have been my choice
like who gives a how do you hate that how do you lose your dick how do you lose your dick
in the second like it doesn't it doesn't it literally doesn't matter the details don't matter
it's like uh i don't know uh someone's one person in a million like doesn't wash their
dick and it gets infected and they have to have it amputated it's it what i like the details are
important take care of your dick or lose it oh you shut the fuck up oh god no that's that's
horseshit that's terrible that was a terrible that was a joke argument i don't care i don't know
what's a joke and what's not this fucking penis arc of the pcp is going on way too long i agree guys
the fact is the fact is that foreskin is cool it's cool it's just cool i don't i don't like it that
much well you don't have it yeah well if you had it you'd be like how wow i don't i don't i don't
no you're wrong you know i don't i don't think that's true uh i don't particularly i don't know
what it would be paulgan constantly bro that's disgusting that's so disgusting you look down
your paulgar's face that's really gross actually next in your own crotch and you make the paulgar's
face on your dick next voicemail thanks and good night uh oh link link to their okay this comes
with a link but whatever uh three two one go okay so there's like this one actor from
home alone two he played a really mining character in it but he's like got a job right now which he's
about to get fired from he's trying to sue sue to keep his job but it seems like it might not go through
so i'm thinking maybe use could try and get him onto the podcast and help build up support for him
and stuff you know that'd be pretty cool yeah i get it i get it uh it's donald it's donald j trump
uh 45th president of the united states of america famous famous for his appearance in
home alone two lost to new york amazing oh unfortunately he's been fired
tragically yeah we could have him on yeah he's gonna you know we could we could promote trump tv
you know pcp will be the only channel on trump tv he's maybe oh god we could we could become
media moguls this is it this is our big break this is gonna create so many new jobs and we're
gonna fill all of them we can take all of the fake non-existent people who who work um artificially
created um to to make fraudulent um biden votes and then funnel that into your subscriber count
so that trump will have to notice you and he will come on the show donald
donald j yeah donald j trump like his entire audience will be all those like fake and dead
people who voted for biden the phantom audience uh i'll just be competing over these fake numbers
uh that's that's how it's gonna be uh okay next one is called um what what it's called uh
where dat bts nibba's law three two one go uh this is pancakes with craters here listen i'm not here
to question the validity of circumcision right you know whether it's like oh oh it's like mutilation
baby but you know all that could be benefits to it no i'm here to ask ask the real questions that
questions that actually matter and that is what is more aesthetic circumcised or uncircumcised
penis circumcised frankly you know i might be biased but i'm gonna say circumcised because when i see
an uncircumcised penis i'm like oh like what am i supposed to supposed to do this extra skin on here
when i see a circumcised an uncircumcised penis i go whoo i go pog you go i don't i don't like
pogging so i would really rather not my stance is that it doesn't matter they're all penises are
beautiful if you wash them that's it that's yeah um i think yeah i mean i i don't really have a
preference for like like an aesthetic preference um i mean i don't think it's yeah they're both
yeah hell yeah i support both
i'm down with both you're the real you're the real centrist i'm the yeah i know i'm the hero take a
position the hero uh next next one is called pancakes the aesthetic of the male genitalia
we wait did i miss one i did i totally missed one uh yeah that one was not where my bts at
nibba's yeah i was wondering where the bts would come in here go three two one go yo quick question
for y'all where is like the other like radcon for bts like vlog type stuff like are you guys still
waiting for brad stuff to come out or what's going on with scenes you know all that other footage like
can you like press digi to like for that stuff or no or what's up with that thanks yeah i probably
have it um if there's anything that hasn't been released i probably have it um you you had like a
like a big you you collected all of our like phone videos that we were putting and you made
like part one or something oh i did make it well i mean like during radcon i had made
like some parts and then i think that i just ran out of time to continue doing that so
i probably still have a bunch of footage that i haven't cut together into anything because
i probably completely forgot i didn't know there was more immediately um i don't even know that
there is but if there is i will find out okay um pretty pretty cool pretty cool i think if there's
more shit i yeah i'm not sure that there is that much behind the scenes there will be for i guess
the ova one once that gets put out um but i want to wait until that's edited before i think i had
some like i had planned to release a final behind the scenes that included all the stuff
that i didn't want to spoil like stuff that was not out yet which is still not out yeah where's
the brodie lecture oh yeah i'm excited about that well that doesn't have any behind the scenes
footage okay it'll come out when it comes where's the brodie lecture though i edited like i will be
excited to watch some of it like six months ago god no i'm like the same way with the the the
sonichu two lecture is like three quarters done and i just haven't finished it and it's just been
like that for ever i i start like i went into it and i like thought of a way to edit it that would
be exciting and then i started doing that and it was two time consuming so i got like 15 minutes in
and i'm like well i don't want to undo all this editing but it'll be really weird if it's like
starts off heavily edited and then just disappears so just put a note on screen just be like i gave
up after this point i might do that and i also have considered adding bits into it where like
like i already had to add in a whole bit on derpy hooves because i just like completely
forgotten to talk about her like so like there's i'm sure there'll be other stuff i have to add
it you added you added in a segment on derpy hooves that's awesome yeah like a two minute
little bit about her yeah i just totally forgotten to mention her i think just the extrapolation of
so much out of like a character design you know i think that uh i don't know when i rewatching
this on a show i feel like there's more i could have said uh i feel like i didn't i definitely
didn't like you know say everything added in post i guess i could add it in post maybe i'd rather
just like leave it for a number like a hypothetical number three at some point could be done yeah
you should do what nate does and put your face over like like a like footage of you speaking and
then put your face over the face of you in the in the actual lecture and pause the lecture while you
do it wait put my face no whenever nate has something that he forgot to say during his like
but where he's speaking to the camera he'll pause the video and then put a bit of him with a shitty
webcam camera speaking footage and put that over his own head oh okay okay in like in a lecture
i don't know maybe just in general and in weagos and stuff okay okay well
maybe maybe if there's something i would do that if i felt like there was something that like
the audience really needs to know about to like understand the context of what i'm about to say
right yeah you know i thought about it for a couple minutes i think there's a few more i think
uncircumcised might actually be a little bit cooler i thought about it i might be leaning
towards that highly highly agree i don't know what the difference is what do you mean more
when they're erect they look exactly the same there's nothing there's there's no difference
it's pretty it's pretty similar yeah it's the only important part you're you're forgetting the magic
of erect by the time it's out of the pants then there's no it's not even happening that's not
true what about a half hard dick they just look cool what aesthetically that's it the half hard dick
is is is often forgotten the half the half job is pretty cool yeah yeah i i will agree with that uh
okay with their next one is called phallic person redux amazing wait wait i gotta upload it uh there
it is okay three two one go
hey i heard you got a big cock
i'm sick i wonder what this guy thinks about the circumcision you know what voice grail
i think should we put should we put phallic person in the voice grail i think yeah yeah i agree they
put in so much my work they've made multiple uh voicemails of just saying hey heard you had a nice
or a big penis cock nice yeah it's always such a treat such a boost to my morale yeah so let's
phallic phallic person you're in you're in the grail you ascend ah the light shines down and you
ascend uh uh into fucking the the realms beyond very congratulations you have done good work
congratulations good job uh next up is uh timisaurus uh here we go three two one go
hello i've just listened to the gloomy cast and if you have depression what helps a lot of people
is taking mag magic mushrooms specifically high doses um studies have shown that it helps
quite a lot it also makes you more creative by a lot and it doesn't make you it's very safe
to consume also um cancer patients approve okay everything he said is true i was just talking
to this guy uh 17 on twitter i've never heard of anyone i've never heard of anyone odying on
magic mushrooms yeah there's no there's nothing unsafe about mushrooms other than if you happen
to be tripping balls and do something retarded because you're already insane okay i've never
done a drug but i've always wondered though uh well they're fine i i tried i do them every day
i got mushrooms from a guy one time and i ate them but like they didn't work i think they were old
and like had like lost their power yeah well that's well i mean i guess i i drank some i only drank
with ben they are they're good for depression supposedly the mushroom well that sounds like
a recipe for just constantly needing more of them and not actually fixing depression it's like it's
the way that like doing major psychedelics will like open your mind is such a way that you might
be like decompressing about it for like fucking forever afterwards so it could be like a more
long-term solution than than that you know well i see all kinds of crazy shit then if it's if it's
super safe then i guess i wouldn't be averse to the idea of doing it at some point i would only
do it with something just to give it a try really i did a weed i smoked a bit come to america do some
acid and no the acid that's different isn't it shrooms and i don't think i ever you tell me you
tell me if i do it all the time you tell me how safe it is i don't know it's fucking it's fun to do
i'll tell you that much no i've heard acid is is the thing that killed well not killed well maybe
it did kill but like it made the the the original pink floyd guy loses mind what's acid like i mean
he was in pink floyd how like i guess they must have done a lot of acid but i think it was acid but
it's yeah i don't know acids are not usually known for i mean it can't i it can't make you insane
it might activate the fact that you're did you what drugs don't make you crazy uh basically
your brain stops sorting between what data is or isn't important and so everything start like
because you you cannot like if you're trying to look at something it's going to look like
it's moving because of the fact that uh your brain can't like ignore enough things to make
it look solid anymore you know what i mean like like just every piece of data is constantly going
through your brain and so depending on how you interpret this like if you if you're thinking
of it the way i'm thinking of it like i'm explaining it then you can get a pretty good handle on it
and just be like okay i'm just taking in more information than normal what do i do with that
the more acid you do the more you can parse that and not feel like you're tripping or anything
but if you are if you take enough of it that you can no longer keep track of everything that it will
feel like you're just seeing shit and losing your fucking mind so it really depends on like
how much dosage you do how much you let yourself go are you trying to you know create horrifying
visions or are you just trying to think a little harder see that that feels like it would give me
a headache is that is that accurate it does not give you a headache it puts you in a totally
different mind state from norm like doing acid is pretty like it's not extreme as like the effect
it has on you as a drug like oh your physical health it's extreme in terms of the psychological
effect of like you're not going to feel the way you normally do at all you know like the world
is going to feel like a kind of a different place um it's like everything is fractaling all the time
like if you stare at anything it will just endlessly frack and you'll be like wow i did not know i
could actually see this much like i did not know that you won't realize how much information your
brain is normally ignoring until you start not ignoring it you know what i mean that's intriguing
okay i'm looking at i'm looking at it as of as of 2008 there are no documented fatalities attributed
directly to an lsd overdose despite the several behavioral fatalities and suicides have occurred
due to lsd so it makes you yeah it makes you do things that would kill you just if you're somebody
who are who is suicidal then you and like you you know doing acid by yourself near a gun
like yeah you know who knows what could happen i think alcohol probably is more likely to lead
to suicide than acid like i can handle it then i would i just need a baby center i'm scared of
the it sounds like it burns you though it's acid it burns you know they call it that's let's do it
together it's more the effect it has on your perception because it feels like stuff's melting
like when you look at shit it looks like it's melting a lot of the time that's why i feel
like i would freak out before i do it i would have a bad trip before i get the acid in me
and i'd be all right probably i feel the same way i feel like i would have a have an oh god moment
and then take it and be like okay i understand what it is now because the fear of like not knowing
what it's gonna feel like is scarier than what it probably actually is yeah i was a little even scared
of of weed before i had tried it not too scared like i didn't think anything was gonna happen um
but i was i don't know i did it i was smoking it drugs are cool i mean i was scared of alcohol
i knew a lot of drugs and i was like i was scared of alcohol until i learned that it just made you
it's or at least for me it just made me like feel dizzy and just laugh at more things
it the that's good i have like that's pretty much the basis i have i can be like a happy drunk
or i can be like an angry then your your drunken state is unbelievable you i got some i got pretty
drunk i got pretty drunk uh on discord yesterday and i was very i was very i was feeling very grim
i was feeling very dour i basically told everyone on my discord that uh your problems don't matter
the apocalypse that sounds about right for you yeah you always say that you like hey you know
this is how you felt after winning the election well i was thinking about i would you say you say
winning um uh i was thinking about cove it i was like sure like sure sure my man j rob might be
might be repping me in the white house now but you know what's what's that gonna do he's gonna
get cove it too we're all gonna get it we're all fucked ben drunken third wave baby ben really drunk
is the kind of guy who will be like i fuck like to say to someone he does not hate say like i
fucking hate you like you are the worst person and then as long as you press him on it and go like
ben you don't think that i'll just be like yeah i don't think that i love you every single time you
do that that's true that's true uh okay let's uh next next one wait no no there's a bunch of like
duplicate emails here timisora sent like three that are all the same uh so the next one is
called um oh god it's another fucking circumcision one it's called ben just do
ben just do your research let's give it a chance let's give it a chance three two
fifty whole one go we probably won't listen been through a lot of gosh up the arguments against
circumcision is the use of they are shown as benefits are negligible and are statistically
insignificant yes i know yeah okay okay yes i know yes i know okay you're right yes circumcision
it's bad it's probably bad yeah probably don't probably don't do it unless a doctor's like hmm
if you don't circumcise this kid their dick's gonna fall off then then do it if they don't say that
yeah fine fine fine you got me i don't like circumcision there are you happy that's my
whole personality gone next one is called uh pancakes how do you do it um wait there it is okay
three two one go uh pancakes with creators here listen i was wondering what are you guys
more inclined to do when creating a story do you create cool characters and like create a world
around them or do you create a world and then like just start writing with characters just start
writing is this is is this like an architect versus gardener sort of sort of quandary i think digi
would have more of a yeah i usually build characters first like i am i will i have the bleach
method of like if i don't know what to do create 20 characters and then unlike bleach though i do
not then create a story i just have 20 characters and i don't know what to do with them um i think i
i think i based i think i do like an events based like it's not so much that i have like a character
or a setting i just have like an event that i build a story around like a like a climactic
moment then like and i see that better way and i see that moment and i'm like okay how can i
build a story that that builds to that that's how they wrote the entire third series where
whether the blocks that i'm starting with yeah personally i feel like i'm not anywhere near
good enough at making stories to like offer advice um i disagree because i've i've i don't know i've
done so much planning and world building on things that don't exist yet and probably never will well
that's not even like when i think storytelling like i don't think about like building an entire
fucking world and all that like you you've you've told tons of stories like you do tell stories good
yeah i mean when it comes to those they definitely start with a character and a point a and point b
um like uh lord of ghosts is i know what the whole thing is going to be like very movement
based like it's always about like a character moving through an environment i've noticed like
almost always yeah i i don't know why that is i think maybe it's just adventure adventure like
you don't want to stand around talking about a physical a philosophical idea because i'm stupid
i can't think of things things like that i want to run around shoot i want to be a cowboy go it's
like at the beginning of um spirited away vibes like that kind of like moving through the environment
sort of oh but the few times i've written stories i've also done the exact same thing
uh that's good i mean if you're in a visual medium that is the best way to tell a story in my
mind is like through you know environment and not through dialogue dialogue is is is useful for
certain types of information i guess i would say given that you draw comics like an animator
which is to say like it's focused on movement even though it's not moving um i guess i do i
think that um the only story the only stories worth telling are about the human heart in conflict
with itself georgia martin i think he stole that quote from someone else so no no no the way to
tell a story is to just have a bunch of like faces and have them expressing like very complicated
emotions that that's fuck environments environments are for losers you can't relate to an environment
yeah you can no that's i i tend to my excitement when i go to a city is to like look at it and
think about the shape of it and like why it's all laid out the way it is and how that affects people
i'll say the fucking uh seeing the the gigantic seagates in in uh one piece the you know the
architecture the the the all of the places in one piece are like really good at adding to the
story in the narrative of what's happening there when i see a really good environment it's like
a big cum it literally feels like oh my god like fuck yeah dude like look at this i want to be in
that place dude i get that feeling yeah same it's like i want to build it in minecraft i get i get
that specific feeling a whole lot reading one piece like if only i had the time to build this in
minecraft yeah i feel that way building my animal crossing island
so there you go um okay well yeah fuck me uh next one is called ben so about you playing
all the voicemails every episode uh i don't know what he this three two one go
one day jesus will punish you for your sins
well not today okay next one is called plague the stage uv uh three two wait three two one go
so how do you do pro crestinators that's me this is um a request from plague from
new melanchi yeah um please send all excess testosterone to that one shopping cart in the
alleyway it would be much appreciated thank you i can do that for you i can give you the
testosterone i don't need anymore i will uninject it out of me and then inject it into that
channel i think there's even a a gram of testosterone between the four of us yeah
i have i have a condition where i don't believe it i can like cough that up for you if you want
cough it into um just cough it into a bucket let's all just pass the bucket around
and spit it out i also have a condition where i have a little bit of extra tea further
i don't i don't know what what you're talking about uh i've deleted my tea it's gone um
uh i can i'll i'll take it uh i could i could use i could be i could be running do you want it i
have i have like a spec that i can give you a spec yeah of of tea that's not gonna be enough for
a drop of tea please it's it's not huh how much do i need a lot okay okay okay uh next one is mozilla
fennekin uh upload three two one go wake up pcp it's been it's been fun i've been listening for
like all um it's been like five years leaving the fandom for context that's um it's about how
long it's gonna be until we see each other again because now that sleepy joe biden has won we all
get to go to sleep for the next four years i'm so i'm i'm excited i get to finally catch up on my rest
rest my old achy breaky bones you know i'm i'm 24 years old i'm an old man you know i i really
could use the rest so yep i'm happy good night pcp i'll see you in the morning in like four years
you're the new dawn at the dawn of the carlson presidency imagine if joe biden was like america
we're gonna all like go into hibernation for a while like we're gonna pause everything we're all
just gonna sleep until like coronavirus is over or something you know i would be you know i mean
the political project of the pcp getting joe biden elected uh has been accomplished so like this the
podcast has served its purpose we don't need it anymore um this was the plan all along and now
it's over uh take take take five everybody we did it uh next one we got two two more voicemails
and then we can call it a fucking day uh they're both from james so three two one go so you missed
the good parts on that circumcision shit so i looked up the numbers it's four and ten thousand
people have like problems so that could be anything you know but a non zero number of those problems
are uh one of them is degloving where the incision line separates so like all the ways you can
fuck up your dick the dick me and then i love they have like stitched that back together there's
not counting the kids that just straight up die from it or like have like weird
remember epstein's egg dick i think it's because of circumcision like i don't remember
ever kind of scrunch it all right i don't know yet a weird i mean that makes sense yeah
circumcision videos are fucking terrifying and then also the traditional jewish way to circumcise
a kid is to uh cut the foreskin off then uh the moille sucks the blood out
hell yeah and kids get herpes and die from that shit too blood libel baby she's fucking wild
um okay and then five seconds of silence um okay you know what i mean if the number is four
and ten thousand then that's probably too high so uh that sounds pretty bad maybe circumcision bad
after all whoopsie daisy you came around uh there's the more you know there's another one
there's one more from james more circumcision talk we we're almost there three two one go
i've been thinking about this one for a minute and just got the chance so fucking um listen
utilitarianism there's the most mathematically pure and simple way to describe it it's collecting
slime yeah yeah so like you want to do the things that make good slime people's brains and not do
the things that make bad slime like the example you gave was like what if you're gay and everyone
in the room is mad about it thinking of slides they kill you that gets rid of all their bad slime
what so you think that's good right wrong now every time they see their friends the ass and the
gym they have to worry about getting killed it says way more bad slime so if you just think about it
as a fraction of the good slimes like get that dopamine get that serotonin get the oxytocin
all those good slimes compare it to like the bad slimes like the cortisol yeah adrenaline the
norepinephrine all those slimes fuck those fucking slimes yeah keep those cop killer slimes come in
and fuck those ridey boy slimes yeah okay all right so so maximize the good maximize the good
slimes maximize the the the testosterone minimize the estrogen is what he's saying what a great
note to end on right i don't fucking know dude nice um well uh uh fuck yeah uh we did it we listened
to them all and just in time because i'm pretty sure i'm pretty sure i've got some brute cuve sparkling
wine waiting for me downstairs so i can get mad at my discord again dude i've got some drugs waiting
for me so i'm excited to i've got a bottle of red cooking wine cheers i'm gonna down that
and then munchies making carbonara right now that's hi that's his favorite it is his favorite
that fucker's always making carbonara i think i'm having biscuits and gravy for dinner i made fried
chicken yesterday it was so good it was super good i got nothing we gotta wrap this up so we
can all go fucking hell yeah okay uh leave us a voicemail leave us a voicemail at speakbike.com
slash pzb voicemail uh check out the um patreon bonus episode bonus episode i was on the most recent
one wow what do we call it the commentary track check out the commentary track episode uh want to
know if people enjoyed that even if we even if we should do more um and um anything else oh and uh
get covid and then buy the shirt uh please and go to my twitter oh and check kazi snap oh yeah
check out kazi on twitter and instagram uh links links in the description if you don't know already
but uh yeah check out her fucking art i'm sure we'll have shown some some of your art on the
fucking screen and if you didn't ellie azar you you fucked up oh and yeah and the yeah the
vapors they'll they'll know they'll know i was in the vapors oh right i actually you know what
i gotta fucking make that uh i make my post i gotta make that thank you twitter post i gotta
make that post yeah gotta make that kazi post i'm kazi posting okay end end of the show
sweet dreams everybody sleepy joe baby sleepy joe four more years
you