Hey everyone, welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm here to
talk about a big problem, hegemonic masculinity. Here to weigh in, we've got Nate Best Guy
Ever-Bestman. Yeah, I'm like Edward Scissorhands. I hate hedge cutting masculinity, you know?
Fuck, okay, cancelled. We've got Tom Oliver. Look, I just do what my dick tells me to do.
It's good, it's bad, it doesn't matter. It's the boss and I know where I stand in the packing
order. Arrest this man. The pecker order, you might say. And finally, we've got Lethal Aurora
Mage. Completely unrelated to the topic, Pokemon. I'm glad to hear you're an ally. I'm going to poke
your mom, Mage, because I'm a bad toxic male. Pokemon is gay coded, I'd say. Queer coded. Hey guys,
I have an announcement. I have a big announcement to make right now. All right, go, go, go. My
Kickstarter is launching right now. Hooray! Maple is two physical copies available right now on
Kickstarter. Link in the description. I don't have, as I record, I have not actually made the
website, so I can't say it out loud, but it's real. Damn it, it's real. It's real in the future
when they're listening to this, not right now, correct? I can't go right now, but I can when this
is live in the future. Yes, on Friday at 2 p.m. or whatever, release these. Yes, at that point,
the page will be up and the suffering will begin. Deb, Deb, Deb. Now, I'd very much like to have
physical copies of all the vapor chapters, but what can I expect as a fan for new content? Is it
vaporettes? Here's the thing. There's going to be like, there's going to be, unless any of my,
the artist that got lined up, drop out, I'm going to, it's going to have, this is going to have six new,
six new, fully new vaporettes. They are canon. I wrote them. They're being drawn by guest
artists, but I wrote them. They're canon. We're probably actually going to be more new content
than old content, actually. And we're going, we're going deep. We're going deep diving. Guess what?
You're going to meet, you're going to meet Vincent and Magda's parents. You fuckers. Oh my god.
That's exciting. Yeah, they're in there. Yeah, they're in there. We can find out who's responsible
for these fucking delinquents. Yeah, there's some fucking shit in there. Okay. There's some
fucking shit. You're going to, you're going to feel real fucking bad when you read this
shit. You piece of, you fucker. Don't see that. That's actually pretty interesting because that's
like an important part of your character's kind of like development is like reveal these characters
and, and you're not even drawing it. You know, you've outsourced a very big kind of like,
I would say plot point, but that's kind of cool. Well, I made, um, well, I did some like concept
sketches, not just for parents. Like there's other things like, like if a particular thing
factors into a story, I'll draw it out and be like, here's what this looks like or something. So
like I did like design stuff, but like, I mean, I don't really care. I don't feel any less like,
I don't feel like divorced from it at all. If like someone else draws, I think that's cool. I think
that's cool that I can get my ideas represented in another person's style. And I'm, and I, and by
the way, um, I'm giving all the guest artists a cut. I'm giving, like, you know, I got six of them.
So I'm giving everyone as a cut. Every, my deal is with them all that every chapter, every copy
of Vapors two that sells, I'm going to give them 50 cents. So last time I moved about 200 copies.
So that would be like a hundred bucks. If I did really well, it would be even more. So Ben, Ben
same, putting his money where his mouth is and giving his artists the Vapors dividend.
Yeah. Yeah. Dab. Yeah. Uh, uh, uh, workers, workers of the workers of the world tonight.
Everyone's, we got, you got mutual ownership here. Right. We got a worker, a little workers co-op
going on right here. We got to mutually, we mutually own the means of production.
But you know, whenever I work with anybody, I make sure that they are financially compensated
or else I wouldn't possibly expect them to do it. I didn't, uh, funny, funny thing. All these guys,
like they're not all, all these guys like just asked me if they could do it and said they wanted
to do it like for free. And I was like, yeah, okay. And I was like, wait a minute, I should probably
pay them. I should probably also pay them something. You know, I, from a purely, that's just an art
me too waiting to happen. If it gets out, you don't have any of these artists being paid because
there's nothing that an artist gets mad about more than unpaid work. I mean, how many times have,
you know, we like shit on like guys like Dr. Wolf and KP for, you know, exactly. I didn't want to
be, I did not want to be a Dr. Wolf. Like I, I guaranteed those people came to them and were
like, Hey man, can we edit for you? They develop a rhythm. And then at a certain point they're
like, Hey, shouldn't I be getting paid for this? Even though I, I mean it, I can't imagine that
Dr. Wolf, for example, would willingly take advantage of anyone's labor. I'm sure he just
bumbles into it due to, you know, whatever free shit that people just offer to him. This is my
guess anyway. Maybe he's a master manipulator. Who can say he's a wily one? You know, I gotta say,
I was going over, like I was deciding on how much I was going to set the goal at this, this time. I
was going over the expenses from last time and they were like, they were like almost double what I
thought. Like it cost almost twice as much to do. Like I, my initial goal was like 1750. I think
the actual amount of just like, you know, initial Kickstarter fees plus like postage plus initial
printing plus like making the pay. It all came to like, like 2,800 or something. So like almost
half like the whole thing. Well, it was Ben. It was a real, it was a real, oh, and shipping,
God, international shipping fucking killed me. This time I am going to have to add like an
international shipping charge just because last time international shipping was so fucking bad.
With Digi about shipping shirts and stuff. And he was recommending stamps.com where you can get
highly discounted shipping through there instead of going through local traditional channels. So
that might be something to look into. I'll check it out. Is it really cheaper than just sending
with the he was able to ship the shirts that he's been doing for half the price that he was before.
So well, yeah, it seems like it might be worth looking into. I'll, I'll, I'll look into it and
see if that, if that, if that cuts any, any costs anywhere.
If you want to know more, watch that episode with me, me, Tom and Digi where half more than half
of the episode is about Digi talking about shipping. Oh, I didn't watch the Baronecon one.
Yeah. But maybe before the people are split on that, whether being it was a nice, cool,
calm reprieve from the normal PCP. The other half the audience like this is the most boring
shit I've ever heard in my life. Well, so you know what, at least it was, at least they can't
variety, you know, at least it was different. People aren't spoiled for choice at this point.
Thanks to me. Indeed, indeed. Speaking of, of financial curves and trying to get ahead of things,
this is very much on my mind as I'm embarking on my, my year long quest to be financially viable
long term and whatnot doing YouTube stuff. And I got to tell you guys, this, this last, I don't
know, couple of weeks or whatever, I have been like an animal with a taste of blood in its mouth.
I have been on the hunt. I have been the hunter in the field. Remember that guy in Jumanji that
like sick, like South African hunter guy who was chasing Robin Williams? Like that's me. That's me.
And, and my prey, and my prey is the most elusive prey, the most dangerous prey of all that I've
been pursuing. And it is a, a Huel sponsorship. Oh, my God. Okay. Right now. Are you,
bitch, are you for real? Well, okay. So tragically, I'm not for real.
As far as I know, I've been doing some research. I don't think that Huel has really done anything
like this before. So I've taken on myself to reach out to them and just say, Hey guys, talk to me.
I love your product. I would be, I would absolutely love to shill your shit online,
because I think it's so great and so good for the future of humanity. Let's make a
fucking deal where I can make a little pittance, shill your product and whatever, more people buy
your stuff. You have to do a we Agua on like Starfleet or something and then integrate your
Huel into that. Because what is more Starfleet than Huel? Well, that's, that's couldn't be more
accurate. But I mean, at the beginning of my last we Agua about the Tarantino movie,
once upon a time in Hollywood, I do like a little gag where I actually say like Huel,
sponsor me. I'm wearing Huel merch, drinking a Huel, saying Huel, I love your product,
please let me show for you. I need more Huel. I haven't gotten Huel in a fucking forever.
I just got my second batch of the, of like the bottle, you know, whatever bottle Huel. I just
had one for breakfast. The chocolate Huel bottles are so fucking good. I have not done the bottles
at all yet. Because they are, they're so much better than the powder. They are delicious. The
thing about the powder is it's annoying to make and honestly doesn't taste that great. The bottles
are so good. They are so good. But isn't it like a lot more expensive to get bottles? It is. That's
the doubt. It is more expensive. That's definitely true. But the question is, is it overall for life
still a better use of your money than like buying a sandwich, which I think the answer is yes. That's
what that's what I've said. I've worked at like between three and four dollars a bottle, which is
like 400 calories. Not cheap. By the way, how do I get to use my EBT on Huel? I'm making a healthy
choice. I have to go contact the government and be like, in a perfect world we'll be there. Maybe
you can find it in like a convenience store or something. I don't think they sell in retail
because they only sell direct to consumers right now. No, no. I swear I've seen like boxed like
Huel. Oh yeah? Maybe. I think so. It was in the same place that we saw the boxed water.
You know? Well, okay. Boxed water. That sounds great. Maybe I'm getting confused. I don't know.
Well, in any case, look, I just want to let people know that I'm not asking anybody to do
anything. But like if anyone knows about ways to get at this point, I have sent two salvos. I've
reached out twice to their support staff just saying, Hey guys, I make YouTube videos, look at
for a sponsorship with you guys. I think you're great. I think we'd be a great fit.
Work with it. Just let me know if you're even interested. So far, I've had no communication
back from them whatsoever, which is not a no. You're going about this the entirely wrong way.
This is what you need to do. You need to make a video on YouTube talking about this exact thing
you're saying right now. You want to get a sponsorship. And then you have to make a hashtag.
You have to put it on Twitter and you have to add Huel and get everyone to jump on the
hashtag. Get it trending and they'll have to acknowledge you. What do we got? What's a what's
a good hashtag? Hashtag. Heal it up. Hashtag. Hashtag. Huel Nate's heart. I don't know something
like that. You have to workshop that a bit, but we'll get there. I'm gonna like that one. That
was cute. Huel Nate's heart. Like I'm going for like a fuel Nate's heart kind of thing, but it's
Huel. Yeah. All right. Yeah. Okay. There you go. Hashtag. Huel Nate's heart. That's the one.
You're starting a social media campaign. Tell Huel you want me to sponsor their product
for reasonable compensation. That's what I'm all about. That's it. Hashtag. Fuck Huel. There you go.
They're doing God's work. So we mentioned Twitter briefly. I'm gonna go slightly off topic. Does
anyone know if Twitter still verifies people because I've heard it doesn't verify people anymore
or something? You know, I've looked into this a bit, Mage. And what I found at my last check was
that there used to be a process through which they would, in fact, like you could submit a form to
be verified. When I was interested in this a while back, when I looked into it, they said they have
shut down the application thing. So they're not like accepting applications or whatever. But when
they, they will still give out the badge to people that like they just like journalists to
like people who just are known and are recognized. And journalists is like the number one kind of
people who that just happens to when they're known and they do stuff, even people who don't have a
lot of followers or anything. So for us pleads, there's basically no hope. No, I wasn't, I was
giving it for me. I don't care about the take, but I'm following like this one Twitter account
that's been wanting to be verified for a while. We're talking about Satan. Are you talking about
Verify Satan? Yes, I am talking about Satan. How did you know? Because I saw this on the
Twitter. Is it just at Satan? Hashtag verify Satan. That's young Venus's dream is to get
verified on Twitter, but I guess it'll never happen. What a shit. Well, I like how Tom knows me enough.
I mean, what's their, what's their reason for not verifying people? I mean, I think it's because
like there, it seems like their standards for verification were like way inconsistent. Or
maybe they, like there are tiny accounts that are verified and there are like big accounts that
are not verified. It seems like verification is more at this point, not to be this is who you are,
but it's like you're involved with like the traditional media or something like that. It seems
like it's, it's like, yeah, it's not about this is who you are. It's about like, it's Twitter giving
you sort of like an endorsement. Yeah, it's our tacit pad on the head for everything. I mean,
the one, the biggest one was when they simply de-verified Miloianopolis and like we know that's
Milo's account. Like that's verified, but they just were like, no, we don't want to, we don't want
to be with this guy. So obviously that's not what it means. Yeah, anymore. That's true. Later on,
he did get banned. So yeah, that was, that was a separate incident though. Yeah, well, I don't know.
Good luck, Satan. I wish you all the luck on your quest to get verified. Shout out to Satan for
giving us the knowledge of good and evil. It's really enabled everything. It was kind of a good
thing. It was kind of a help. In any other story, Satan would be the hero. Think about it. You're
in this post post apocalyptic dystopia and some heroes. This is my story.
Satan is punishing the sinners. He's not evil himself. He's like, he's being the jailer.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He's just running a for-profit private prison. What could possibly be wrong
with that? That's why we need Bernie. That's why we need Bernie to get in there and bust that
cell. But we're already feeling the burn. Satan's got fire and brimstone. We don't need Bernie.
It's the wrong kind of burn, okay? It's the wrong kind, all right? It's not exactly what I was thinking.
It's just, it's just too slow of a burn. Eternity is too slow of a burn. We need something quicker
and faster. We change now. That's why we need Bernie. God, this just makes me think. I've been
watching this YouTube channel. I think Jesse might have complained about this YouTube channel
called Renegade Cuts the other week, and I didn't know what it was talking about.
I didn't know what he was talking about, so I couldn't comment. But I started watching it,
and it's great. It's great. It's just my shit. It's my vaguely lefty media analysis in the
vein of Big Joel or whatever. It's one of those. It's really good. But in particular,
what this guy Renegade Cuts is good at is, I think he was raised very Catholic. He was an
altar boy and stuff. He's got insight. He's got insight into the evangelical mindset. He has one
video that I particularly recommend on the, oh fuck, what's it called? That movie in books
left behind. The ones about the rapture people living in the post-rapture thing.
He goes into a deep dive. I knew about some of this rapture mythology stuff, but I didn't know.
He throws out terms like post-millennial dispensationalism and stuff to describe what's
going on here in terms of the philosophy at play. It's great shit. It's great shit.
What is dispensationalism? Okay. Oh, I didn't know this, but apparently
a dispensation in some... It's a payment, right?
In this context, what it means is a period of time, is a dispensation. The time when Adam and
Eve lived in the garden before the fall was a dispensation, and then the time before the flood
was another dispensation. Currently, we are living in a particular dispensation that has been going
on since the resurrection of Jesus, and then what is... An era, an age, something like that.
Yeah, an era and age. Not all of them are specific to this, but a lot of rapture theology
evangelicals have a particular view of eschatology called post-millennial dispensationalism,
which says that we are currently living in a long dispensation, but there will be the rapture,
and then there will be the millennia, which is a thousand-year reign of Jesus Christ, followed
by the judgment, and the return of heaven on earth, which is the post-millennial dispensation
that is when the judgment happens. It's something along those lines, and anyway, Renegade cuts
this really good, and he talks about that kind of stuff, and I love that shit. Well, all right,
cool. He doesn't only talk about that, but a significant chunk of his videos are about
movies left behind and other Christian propaganda kind of things. I forget the name of the guy,
but Michelle was Mormon for a while when she was young, which is basically a cult. It's just a cult.
It's weird. There are some YouTubers that pop up. There's a little sub-genre of former religious
people. It sounds like this guy is one, and there's these former Mormon guys. I can't remember the
guy's name specifically, but there's one guy. I think it was actually Mr. Atheist. I think that was
his name, and Michelle was saying for a while that she was watching his stuff, but after a while,
it just became like, here I am, not still not Mormon, still wishing I hadn't done that back in
the day. That can't be your whole thing. Well, it's got to change at some point. You don't want
to be a springboard or something with more meat on its bones.
Michelle was telling me about, there are these channels that get huge off of specifically
like Acne. They're like Acne channels, and they're about someone's journey to get rid of their Acne,
so they start off looking pretty rough, and they try, I forget, like Accutane or some of the
procedures. Because people are like, oh, I've got Acne. Would this work for me?
Well, they do this for weight loss, right? They do weight loss journey channels too.
Yes, that kind of shit too. And the thing is, oftentimes they can succeed, but in doing so,
they develop a pretty sizable following. I saw some people with over like 150,000 subs just off
of an Acne journey, but then it's like, well now what? You're done. The quest is over. You lost the
weight. Yeah. Good job. I think there was something like that, like a channel about a woman trying to
lose her weight, but she ended up like binge eating and just becoming. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's
right. I know. I don't know what I know. Well, there's, oh God, I saw a video about this, and it was
like people, it was talking about how people love to hate on these people and to like, and to like
law, like if someone, yeah, there's one, there's one particular channel that is like well known
for this, but it's not the only one, but it's like a weight loss journey where like, based on what
the video contents, you can tell that like they're not doing it. They're failing, right? And they're
like making excuses for themselves and people like, and people like to watch these and do reaction
videos pointing out like, oh, look, like, look how dishonest this person is being. Like, look how
this person's fucking up. You know, it's kind of like a there, but for the grace of God. That's
the internet for you, I guess. Yeah. I know the channel you're talking about, but I don't remember
its name. Yeah, I only heard about it like. Like how long, how long can you milk the idea
that you are on a weight loss journey when like it's been years and like you weigh the same?
I think at this point, it might be like some sort of psychological dependency on the attention
for the female, I think. It's not, it's not quite the same. Well, it reminds me of Boogie,
right? Like Boogie had that like gastric bypass surgery and he went down from like 500 to like
300 pounds and then. That's pretty good. Well, yeah. I mean, it's, it could be better, right?
Sure, of course. But he's like, he's still, man. I mean, 40% weight loss is pretty damn good.
Yeah, well, when you have gastric bypass, of course you're going to have that, right? But then
he's still, he's still morbidly obese, right? But like, I don't know, I saw a video, there's this
one pretty, pretty well known video about like, what's, what the fuck's wrong with Boogie? Just
like what an asshole he is. And he does seem like a big asshole. But in particular, there's people
that have made like really good faith attempts to be like, hey, Boogie, here's what I think is
going wrong on your weight loss journey. And here's how I think you can fix it. And he's responded
with like great hostility, like a totally inappropriate sense of like, I'm being victimized.
Well, well, look, after, I mean, you know me, Nate is hardcore hashtag kill the fats. But,
but aside from that, when you've like, obviously people have been telling Boogie like, I'm sure
great advice for like years and years. And it's absolutely sure true that he should have taken
most or all of that advice and fix his problem, which is fixable. But there's like, I mean,
he's got like, like mental like abuse, any like comfort eats, because he's so traumatized,
but like his fucked up childhood, I just don't know. I mean, I'm not impressed, but I mean,
we've all got our reasons why we fuck up.
He's been like, like for years on the internet, known a person like, and imagine like,
constantly getting this unsolicited advice, it would probably great on your nerves too.
Okay, all right. God damn it. All right, I know you guys are all you guys are all
we love Boogie. And we love the idea. I know the defense of this guy. Let me tell you this.
Okay, I wouldn't complain except that Boogie has like, he sort of like has made part, he too kind
of made part of his appeal, this like weight loss journey thing. And he's like, he's very cagey about
it. He'll make, he'll make promises. And then he'll like, I know that like, I know that like, to a
certain extent, it's none of his, it wouldn't be his audience's business. If he didn't talk publicly
about it. Yeah, yeah, I mean, I kind of wish he wouldn't make it his audiences. It seems like a bad
incentive structure to make it your audience's business. Your, your especially when you say,
I've got psychological issues. This is not going to be easy for me. You know, blah, blah, blah,
my whole that that just that's like a private thing, man. I don't know why you'd
to be fair. I like, I don't know much about Boogie like at all. Yeah. I've known people say that
he's a nice person in general. That's all I've heard of him. And now I'm hearing this, you know,
I'm not believing either side, honestly. So I don't know. I don't care. Well, this video,
this video, there's a video called the fall of Boogie 2988, why he's losing subscribers that
has 2 million, 2.5 million views right now. Is that by that guy, Tom, something? Oliver? Yes.
2.5 million Tom, congratulations. Yeah, you know, that's, that's pretty good. I finally came.
It was like, I got to get into the blood sports is the only way to make this world.
You must be raking in the dough. Oh, yeah, I have like seven whole dollars in my AdSense.
I'm so stuck. Have we talked about how the Sonichu lecture is closing in on 100,000,
not 100,000, closing in on a million. It's about 100,000 away from hitting a million.
It's up here and there, but that should be noted. That's that's pretty amazing. Do you think it's
going to see like, well, let's see like a second wind, right? Like, I think back in the day,
Digi said that like, when his, when his old anime videos hit like a million views,
they would sometimes get like a second wind and get like a new wave of like people watching.
I would be surprised. I mean, that's like an algorithm question. I don't know, man,
I am no fucking expert on this shit. I have no idea what made like my Galco video. My Galco
video had like waves. I think that was just because people would like post it on Tumblr and
they'd be like, oh, let's go watch the video. It wasn't a huge wave, but like the past like two
weeks or so, I don't know why. Like viewership on the Sonichu lecture was like double what it usually
is. I don't know. Just just happened. And then it went kind of just drifted back down against
a normal and yeah, I don't know, man. Let me see. Let me see. How's it doing right now? How's this
shit doing right now? Um, YouTube YouTube studio beta. Show me show me the analytics. Show me.
Beta. Okay. Yeah, I went back. It went it's gone back down to about normal. The typical like 1200
views a day or so. Yeah, for a while it was doing like 1900, 1800 a day. I think I think just just
for a very distinct little period there. If Sonichu does something, you know, that that makes them
trend, your video will probably get some. Yeah, Sonichu goes out there. You gotta dig deep. You
gotta go to your last 30 days and then you gotta see where external traffic's coming from. See if
like maybe go post it on Reddit or something. Some traffic increase source. It sounds crazy.
And yet there is a Sonichu currently living among us in the real world, right? Yeah. No. Yeah. Yeah.
One has crossed over the dimension. One has torn through the dimensional veil and is currently
has come over from C197 and has come over to one to two dimension one two one eight specifically
Well, because well, because you said if Sonichu does something and the thing is there currently is
a Sonichu in our domain. They're not supposed to exist in our dimension. They're from
they're from university one nine seven. But one of them has crossed. Magi Chan Sonichu has crossed
the dimensional barrier guys. Magi Chan Sonichu has come but not bodily mentally has entered
the body of Christine Weston Chandler and is currently living. He's possessed right now.
And tweet. Yes. Currently living and tweeting in our dimension. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
And Sonichu himself. Right now. Is this a possession or is this like a head made multiple
system kind of deal? I believe that they have swapped bodies. Yeah, that's right. Whoa. That's
what I heard. Jesus Christ. Well, tomato tomato. It's not the same thing. The result is the same.
If you swap body, that means your mind. Two minds have swapped between bodies.
Okay, we understand the idea as in as in Christine is currently in 1218 and and Magi Chan Sonichu
is currently here. And the thing that's scary thing about that is that Magi Chan Sonichu is
all powerful, right? We should we should all be fucking terrified right now because Magi Chan
Sonichu contains within him the ability to bait the fuck up everything. I had heard that
completely obliterate our entire time. But does magic magic and retain that ability in the body
of I heard Magi Chan is having difficulties using his psychic powers in Christine's body.
This is what I heard. You know what? It's it's not out of the realm of possibility that maybe Magi
Chan's power only one of us was a fucking Christian and could dig into this deep for us and do an
addendum to a almost million viewed video. I mean, there's there's no there's no precedent.
There's no precedent for this, right? We are in a bold new era, right? The dimensional merge is
happening and this is its harbinger. It's happening. You know, this is like remember those guys,
those like, uh, yeah, I mean, you know, end times, judgment day guys are like, guys, I'm telling you
like August 8th, 2012, it's happening. That's the date of the apocalypse. I really would. Did you
see did you see the internet historian video because I saw the internet historian? I certainly
did, man. I certainly did. And I was one of my favorite YouTubers in the historian.
Just make such high quality stuff. But in any case, hey, my alarms shout out to internet historian
if he's listening. A big old fat shout out to historian. Give us give us give us a give us a
plug. Give us a plug lads. Give us a subscribe to like patron $5 for bonus episodes, you know.
Hey, speaking, speaking of these devil tongues and these devilish activities.
I've got some shit I'm going to write down so I don't forget to mention it.
Okay, go ahead. Write it down. Okay. Well, I've got, I've got a truly devilish
point I wish to raise at some point. Speaking of, we were talking about Satan. We're talking about
hell. We're talking about the dimensional merge and all of these things culminate recently in,
in just, uh, let me say in four simple notes. Da, da, da, da. Yeah.
It's in Smash Bros. I saw it. I saw it live. It's really, it's pretty fun. It's so funny
because me and my friend were watching direct together. Well, not together. She was watching
in her house me and we were talking to each other on Discord and you know, I said, you know,
wouldn't it be funny if like sans got announced in Smash? This is as much
I mean people have been nemen about it for over a year now. Yeah. I just like, I was like, imagine
the pandemonium of the internet of sans got announced. I didn't, I said it in the tongue that
I didn't expect it to have Terry Bogart that apparently like South Americans or Mexicans
like love obsessively love King of Fighters totally overshadowed by sans and one song mega
Louvania getting into, into the new game. It's, uh, I mean, I don't really know much about Terry,
so I can't really speak on that. He just seems like another kind of boring fighter character.
And that's right. Roast me in the comments. Yeah. I literally don't know anything about
Terry, but where can I marry him? He is a very handsome man. Did you hear the cool, the cool,
the interesting thing? All the Japanese fans of Smash are saying that Terry's just a jacked
Pokemon trainer. Oh, I saw, I saw the meme. I saw the meme and I'm like, Ness is like the
base form than the, the Pokemon trainer is the middle evolution and then Terry is like the
final evolution. Do you think that, that Pokemon trainer and Terry walk down, they see each other
and they point and they go, same hat. Have you seen, have you seen the, the fatal cutie
fem swapped Terry Bogart? No. Is that a thing? You're about to. So get ready for that. Oh,
is it in the show notes? I'm posting it right now. This is like official art from like one of the
recent games or something. Okay. In gross discussing audio links. Okay. There you go. Okay. That is
awesome. Yeah. Oh, supposed to devolution. All right. It's about what I expected. Yeah. I mean,
it is what it is, but this is, I mean, this should be the one of the, one of the character
model swaps for Terry. That's his echo fighter. Oh, that'd be great. That'd be great.
And Terry's fucking cool though. I hope they do. I hope if you fight, if you fight,
fucking Ken, they bring back that SNK toss, fucking legendary. It's so cool. It's so cool.
I heard other people, they're just saying Terry is just Ken with hat and that's, you know,
pretty accurate. Since we were talking about sounds, Toby Fox was like made music for Game
Freak's game. Yeah. Toby Fox is a chat now. Yeah. For Game Freak. What game for Game Freak?
Their new game Town or was it Little Town Hero or the fuck it's called? Yeah, that's the one.
He's making the music for it, which means the music is going to be pretty great. Yeah. And also,
this was another one of the big things. Did you guys fucking hear, you brought me to,
probably did you watch it, that he went to Sakurai's house and he played Smash Bros.
Like he's just become, let's just, let's not forget people. Fucking Undertale Man,
fucking Toby Fox has made one fucking video game. He's made one video game. He made two games.
And as a result, Delta Rune is a demo. It is a demo for a game. It does not count. It's basically
a chapter release of it. Well, then I guess we should count his fucking ROM hack for Earthbound
2, but the point is it's not a complete game. No, that's sort of, that's great. Exactly. He's
okay. I'd say his total games add up to maybe like 1.85 games. Okay, fine. I'm rounding a hard
down to one. This fucking guy made one fucking video game. And he's literally like the prince
of the game industry, like Kojima and Sakurai and I don't know. When's he going to get me too?
It's only a matter of time. Toby, he's too private. He doesn't do anything. I don't know. Maybe he
is out there smashing Japanese puts right now. It's, he's just, he's living like the literal
drip. He was making Undertale in fucking Andrew Hussie's basement, literally, and was just living
like a fucking cockroach parasite piece of shit. He makes his fucking demos like the best game
demo ever. There's hope for us yet. I just, I can't believe the meteoric rise that this one guy has
had. It's inspiring, honestly. All right. And fucking Hussie has got to be on Suicide Watch right
now. Seeing how Huss out just makes me roll my eyes. This is bullshit. What's bullshit? It's
bullshit. It's all bullshit. Toby Fox? Toby Fox, you know, whatever. So he likes to do a really good
video game idea that everyone loved. Oh, great. Is he so much better than the rest of us? No.
No one's saying he's better. It's just incredible. He's fine. He's fine. Yeah. The dude made a
fucking sick product and he's, yeah, he made a pretty big product. All the accolades for it.
He made a pretty good product. He's living the way you do. Good for him. Good for him.
Like, Toby did not, Toby did not predict the mimetic rise of Undertale. It's almost baffling
to me to realize that, like, wow, a lot of these guys have not actually put in the amount of time
or, like, even played Undertale, but they just love the Saiyans' memes and they love, you know,
megalovania and those are crazy popular memes and stuff. It's weird for me to think that these
people don't actually appreciate the actual game as much as they should, but it is like one of the
better. It's still. Normies don't appreciate art. It do be like that sometimes. It do. It truly do,
but the megalovania is in Smash Bros. I cannot fucking believe it. Its original usage was in
the ROM hack as the final boss theme of his, like, Halloween earthbound fucking thing. It's all, like,
all comes back. It started with Nintendo, ended with Nintendo. It's incredible. It's fucking
incredible. What a journey. What a legend. What a god. What an inspiration. I feel supreme jealousy
and I also feel. I'm happy for him. I'm genuinely happy for him. Let's end Nintendo. Let's get,
like, Sakurai and Kojima. Let's put them in Toby's shoes and see what they can make in his
shoes, right? Like, let's take our big developers that have, like, a big corporate backing behind
them, you know, obliterate them and put them in Andrew Hussie's basement and say, all right,
what can you do? Huh? Well, you just gotta go back to their early career. That's a fair question.
Toby, I mean, look at the, like, everything in Undertale is extremely simple. Like, the gameplay,
it's just like moving around a keyboard. It obviously doesn't look amazing. I mean, the art's good
for what it is, but it's a very, obviously, you know, the product of a couple of people. It was
styled back and scaled to be appropriate for the man. It's just that the ideas that he did work
with, like the whole resetting, remembering things that happen, like the different timelines, the
amazing way that you can write with genocide or pacifist or whatever. That's all you need. Like,
that's the good shit. That's that's the shit that makes it. It had a great hook that the rest of the
game never quite lived up to. I disagree. But the time the time shenanigans were never quite as good
as they were in the Toriel fight. I agree. That was the purest concentration. Is this a hot take
that I feel like the Toriel fight promised more to, like, sort of implied that there would be more
to the timelines thing later on and it never really even got as good as that ever again?
You know, Ben, I would totally agree that within within like the demo, the Toriel demo,
like it is like basically it's the perfect packaged way to show off how that mechanic works.
And like so it's true, like the game is so much longer. It's the single best instance of it.
It's because like you're not that far in a game that you wouldn't feel sorry about resetting the
game. You know, like once you're further in the game, I might as well stick with what I have.
Well, it just takes more commitment. Well, another thing I played that game like five times.
Another thing to keep in mind with this is that like the Toriel fight was the demo and that was
like what like a year removed from the full game. So you play through the demo and you have like
365 days of being excited for this game and imagining all the ways it could make you could
play with this concept. But I feel like if there was no undertale demo, I don't think the Toriel
fight would be as impact not as impactful, but like it wouldn't be such a huge like schism,
you know, it would just be another part of the game. I think giving that year to just kind of
ruminate on what that implied for the rest of the game makes it stand out for that.
If you if we'd been given the whole game, we would not appreciate the Toriel bit as much.
I never played the demo despite vents and systems at that point.
I did. Yeah, I had that. My friend showed me the demo a couple months, a couple months before
the game itself came out, and I was pretty excited about it. Yeah, like,
yeah, that bit like, I mean, maybe, maybe it is, I think it did because because it was just a demo,
like you had the chance to like play it through a couple times and it was short. And like, yeah,
you got to experience like, oh my god, this this, it like it under it knows what's going on
of it, like adjust and like it knows what you're going to do. And it is like dynamic, dynamically
responds to your fucking around with the save states. That's pretty neat. And then in the real
game, it's like, yeah, we did it once. Well, okay, that that's where you're exaggerating a bit,
because I don't think I am. Well, well, a little bit late. Like, there are a couple of moments
when the game will be aware that like you previously saved and had a game over and restarted.
Well, I totally agree. That's the same gimmick again. Basically, everything that happens between
the toriel thing and the very end, when you do all the finale stuff, kind of doesn't really matter
towards this particular point of the resetting stuff. And it's all funny and humor, blah, blah,
blah. But on this point, which we all know is the best part of Undertale, mechanically and like
story wise and whatnot and game design wise. The it's the fact that you can do these pacifist
and genocide endings. And like that only in very specific ones do you get the ultimate super epic
boss fight against sans. And then that's doing the genocide ending. That's not that innovative.
That's not the end of my point, though, because the end of the point is that even after doing
the genocide ending, and you literally destroy the world and whatnot, you can't I mean, I talk
about this in my in my undertale video. But I'm just restating the point from that. But it's that
you can do that ending. We know the game is teaching us there have been consequences to our
actions and everything, including the toriel thing at the beginning. And you do genocide,
you destroy the world. But then the game gives you the ability to reset. It's that whole thing.
And then you play through the game again, you can do a pacifist ending. But your but that's when
you get the true final thing is after that extra play through, when it turns out the char is still
evil. It's like, oh, it's making a larger point. I get yes. Okay, okay, I guess I guess it's true
that that is sort of the same thing on the scale of the entire game. And that is pretty cool.
But I agree. That's over like a 20 30 hour experience as opposed to like a one hour experience.
But I mean, it's the amount of content what you're just you're what you're describing is literally
like the addition of like a two second moment. I don't think it's a good moment. It's a really
good moment. I think that's the point though. It's it takes that entire slow burn of playing
the game multiple times to like have that hit home. You're like, oh, okay, I mean, I don't think
that that's how I mean, that is a great thing. It is a great moment in the game. And it talked to you
when you did when you were recording the game, you did you were recording or it's like, haha,
look at those fools watching your recording. You're no better than playing the game. Yeah.
There were those bits about like, even the people who watch let's plays and stuff, they're just as
bad. They're just for years to the side. Yeah, okay. I mean, that's not cool. That's a different
point. Yeah. And it's funny. And it's but it's not like it doesn't blow my mind or anything like that
point. I haven't seen it done before. And I like when I think it's fair to say that Undertale,
the whole game, the tutorial, it's I absolutely agree. Ben, everyone should have played the
tutorial. The peak experience is I think what you and I had playing the playing the tutorial
ruminating on it for months, then playing the full game with that in mind, because people who
just play the game now, they like almost nobody is going to actually do the reset stuff with Toriel
when they first play the tutorial, the tutorial. Oh, my God. Oh, fucking. Are you fucking seething
me right now? I can't believe I never saw this connection. Okay, guys, you're joking, right?
Yeah. No, no, no, no, I never joke. All right. Well, in any case, I think that it like
homestuck back in the day. God, it was a pun. God, it was a pun all along. Oh, my God.
I think time travel did currently as I exist now time travel did more with or sorry,
homestuck did more with time travel than I've ever seen in any other medium. And so it's the
pinnacle of like time travel stories. And I think that Undertale, I'm sure someone could do it better,
you know, eventually, I think it's the pinnacle of like meta narrative in video games using like
mechanics and stuff. It's that's my I think it's the best example so far. Yeah, that's all I'm saying.
I'm not saying it's the best that could ever be. But I mean, best I know I haven't read House of
Leaves. I do want to do that. That could be it. I could maybe I don't know. It looks pretty good.
I guess you could cheat and say that we're only talking about video games, but fuck that.
Let's talk about all mediums. All mediums. I never played the Doki Doki leadership glove,
but it has that sort of shenanigans, doesn't it? One day I'll do that maybe. It's supposed to be
pretty amazing. Like you edit like the actual data files. I mean, that's just programming. But
if they make it part of the gameplay, that's that's pretty cool. That's pretty impressive.
Well, there you go. Sans is in Undertale and also in Smash Brothers. What do you know?
Dimensional Merge is upon us, ladies and gentlemen. This is evidence.
Have you guys heard like a really stupid, not even a theory, but a comparison,
how Sans just looks like Steven Universe without the skin?
I mean, he also looks like Ness. I've seen the thing that's like actually
Steven with his new pink jacket from the movie. If you just make that blue,
he looks even more like Sans now, who's been wearing a jacket the whole time.
Speaking of Steven and Sam. The time lines are slowly coming together.
Yeah, speaking of Steven. New movie, new movie. I want to discuss the new movie.
Sure. Me and Tom have seen it, so I'm happy to talk about it.
Sorry, sorry, Ben. You just had to watch it. Ben, just go download the movie,
watch it on like seven X speed and like half like three you can jump in.
I've got my own shit to say. You fucking cowards.
We'll go on, Mage. What did you think?
I didn't know what to expect when I went into the movie. All I knew about the movie
and when I went in was like, Steven has a neck. That's all. That's all the spoilers I got.
Indeed. That's some real character development right there.
Yeah. And then like when I saw, I saw immediately like, you know,
those pastel colors on Steven, I was like, oh, I wonder, I wonder how long is it going to take
Yeah, excuse me.
How long is it going to take for Internet to be like, oh, look at the trans colors on Steven.
Steven does say trans rights. This is his only line in the film.
Well, now I got a fucking watch.
I'm not against the idea or anything. It's just like, oh, those are pretty good.
For people who hate trans, I'll just give you an out. It's also a fact that the four colors
he's wearing do reflect the colors of the diamond authority. So there's your out if you want.
Like, no, no, no, it's not trans. It's, uh, yeah.
That just means the diamond authority is trans.
Thanks, God.
But yeah, so and I watched it. It was a musical and but they were like,
Sure was talking.
I did like a few of the again, like the villain song is one of the best songs and any
Which one? Which one? There's several.
Both all of them.
I mean, you could mean other friends or you could mean drift away, etc, etc.
I like both of them. Those are the way two songs that I really like. I guess I like
Okay, no, I'm a little bit torn on that song that he sang at the beginning and at the end with the
We adore you. You're not hurt. We know you're not hurt.
Whatever comes my way because as long as I can say here I am in the future with my friends.
Yeah, I completely forgot that song.
And I mean, like all of them are pretty okay songs. They're not they're not bad or anything.
I remember some of them better than others.
Just with a lot of Steven songs. I'm probably going to get fly for this, but I don't like
most of the Steven Universe songs. I agree. I like one or two of them that were more like
better sang, but like most of them are just like what like Steven on a ukulele or something. I don't
know. That's interesting. I didn't like most of the songs, but like in this in this in this movie,
they're pretty good. I like them. They're nice. I like I like Pearl's explanation song. I don't
know what it's called, but it's kind of fun. It's got like a long like pearl boot.exe name or something.
It's pretty funny. Yeah. It's just it was it was quite cute. Something is clearly wrong. I love the
animation at that time. Yeah. Yeah. It was really fun. When I saw a spinel with how with her rubber
hose animation. I bet you love. I bet you nutted instantly when you saw a spinel. Why is the air
going crazy for some spinel? Okay, that's that's the thing because as soon as I saw a spinel,
I was like, Oh, the internet is going to eat her up. She has that she has that, you know,
Oh, she could be your angle or your devil. We like we like old animations. We like rubber
hose. We like Cuphead and stuff like that. I knew I knew the internet is going to eat her up.
And it did. And like, I don't have a problem with it. But it's just like,
I don't want to say it's better because but it like it felt weird to see her so animated in
comparison to everyone else being all a rubber hosie and stretchy and stuff. And I know that's
her shtick, but it's just so weird to see her like that. Like, so she's in, you know, that sort
of job and just like, are all spinels meant to be like rubber hosie little psychic character
things. Presumably, presumably, we don't see any others. But yeah, it's yeah, it's just I just
I just like spinel because I'm like, Oh, the Steven Universe staff can actually animate good.
I mean, I'm sure you guys heard, I loved the balloon inflating and deflating sound effects
as she stretched. There was so much soul so much soul in that animation. I did I did end up liking
her. I thought I wasn't going to like her initially. When I saw her, I thought she was going to be
super annoying. But no, she's fine. I liked her. And she had her I mean, even to the characters,
she was rather annoying to I mean, intentionally sell. Yeah, but there's a but there's like
annoying for a purpose like within within reason in the show and like just being so annoying that
you feel the annoyed rather than like you understand that never really. Yeah, she never
did. She she's good. I like her. And then like her backstory and the song just like, Oh, that's
sad. I like I like this. This is really sad. But yeah, well, hey, if I can give my yeah, go ahead.
I'm done. I this was one of my favorite movies I've seen in a million years. This was like a
nine to a 10 for me. I fucking loved this movie. Not every song was like a perfect 10 or anything.
I love this movie so I watched this movie like maybe four or five times all in all. I spent like
a day in meditation at my deep feelings about the the issues at play in this children's cartoon,
which are incredibly poignant to the issues of today. And I recorded a we Agua that is currently
being edited about this exact movie and will be out by the time people hear this. I love this
fucking movie. I love spinel. I love the usage of I mean pink diamond piece of shit, but like
great usage of her character. Because if I can just spoil just one of the themes of the movie,
the theme here is about family. Okay, it's about family. It's about family. What happens when
okay, like Steve, this movie takes place. It's Steven and it's all the kids like the song is
about like happily ever after never ends. That's like the opening. They're in there happily ever
after they've solved all problems. A racism has dropped to zero. We did it, you guys. And all
of a sudden, so life is perfect. But spinel spinel was an old friend of pink diamonds who got left
behind. I won't go into how you should go watch the fucking movie and watch all of Steven Universe,
which is unequivocally gone down in history as one of my favorite shows of all time. I just
I love everything about okay, I don't love everything about it, but it just overall it is
one of the greatest shows I've ever seen and I go back to watch it all the time. But okay, back
on the point. The theme here happily ever after happened, but spinel was literally not included
in everyone else's happiness. Everyone in the world got a happy ever after, but spinel was
forgotten and left behind. And so she comes back full school shooter. And this to me is exactly
like one of the most important issues. Just like when Sonichu didn't accept the CPU goddesses and
decided to shoot up the mall, the Charlottesville mall. Did that happen recently? Yes, Sonichu did
that. Listen, wait for my lecture. Okay, okay, I'll get into it. I mean, everything about it,
like to me, it felt very obvious that this movie was kind of about the exact, it's not literally
about a school shooter, but it's about those feelings that those people have, like when you
don't fit in, when you're bullied, when you're not appreciated by the people around you, when
everyone else seems happy, but you're left behind. And spinel is quite clear. She's like,
I came here to do violence against strangers because I hate the world now. This is just exactly
the kind of thing that we're seeing. And I thought it was packaged so poignantly, so beautifully.
And the song Drift Away, I feel like the song Drift Away is the kind of song I could feel myself
committing suicide to. I want to make a suicide playlist. I think I've said this before. But this
100% qualifies as a song that you want. I almost felt like it was taking me to like a dark place
because the movie has, I'm not joking, the movie has a happy ending. But for whatever reason,
the strongest feelings in the movie are the lowest point where we learn spinel's backstory
and she sings the song. I listened to that song over and over and over again. And I felt myself
like drifting into a dark place with the character. And this is why I spent like a whole day like
meditating on it. And then like I kind of had to force myself like, no, Nate, like it's okay,
like things are good. It's not all bad. Like I wanted to say like- Were you getting radicalized?
I was getting hardcore radicalized against Pink Diamond and I wanted to murder her and her whole
family. But then I kind of had to jolt myself out of it like, no, the world is not an all bad place.
Pink Diamond, you know, there are actually kind of reasons that aren't just pure malignancy
in what resulted in basically a torturous life for spinel. There are reasons that are just maybe
more carelessness or immaturity. You shouldn't say that like everything's bad, because one person
did something that ended up hurting you really, really bad. And it really affected me in a deep,
deep way. And it kind of was a little bit too strong for me and I couldn't handle it. So I had to just-
Okay, I guess I gotta watch this movie now. I feel bad even over hyping it.
I guess I gotta go get my own opinion, huh? I had zero hype going into this movie and I saw
Spinal and I thought like, oh, this is going to be shit. I was so blown away by how much I love
this fucking movie and, frankly, how much I love Steven Universe overall. Right now, it's making
me emotional just thinking about like taking a journey with these characters and seeing how happy
things end up and how they bring up issues like this. Like, Steven, at the end, he's like,
nah, happily ever after, like, it's a lie was kind of his point. Like, there will always be more work
to do. We've always got to help people. All this time you were pretending so much for my happy ending.
Exactly it. But I, you know, I don't want to go on too long. It just, it made me feel so many things.
It's interesting because like, I'm curious to see your, uh, your Viagra you're going to do on this
because the movie for me was like a seven, maybe? A seven. Well, I think that like, I mean, if you
look at like the kind of thing, this appeals, some things just hit your strike zone, you know?
Yeah. And like having a movie like this, which it's, it's almost like, it's like a, a movie about
like the kid who was bullied in school who like didn't find happiness and like decided to do
terrible things. But instead of like painting that guy is like purely evil, it like tries to
understand why they feel that way. And even the people who made them feel that way, they have
some reasons for what they did. A lot of people are saying Pink Diamond's like pure evil. I think
that's an exaggeration. No, I don't think Pink Diamond is evil. I think the great thing about
the movie, I think the themes are the strongest part for sure. And like Steven Universe has always
been pretty good at painting everybody in shades of gray. Like there's no like hardcore villain,
you know, that's why everybody can get redeemed pretty much because there's possibly too much so.
But yeah, yeah, possibly to its detriment at some degree, but like it's, it's, it's playing,
it's playing to its thematic messaging and it sticks to it, you know, through hell or high
water is that everybody has like some nuance to them. And that's cool. Spinell was great.
I really liked Spinell's like arc and like what they did with her and all that kind of stuff.
And like, it was a good way of like leveraging more of like getting to know Pink Diamond and
I guess maybe it's like a personal thing for me because the movie does like one of the things
that I just is like a personal pet peeve and fiction is when like they do something to the
characters that you know is temporary and is definitely going to be reverse. So you have
to sit there and wait for it to go back to normal because like, I mean, that, that is the plot of
the movie. 100%. It's like the plot of the first half of the movie. They cut because like I was
afraid that it was going to do it the entire movie because like spoilers for anybody who hasn't
watched like go watch it. It is worth watching. But in the beginning of the movie, Spinell has
this weapon that resets a gem to factory settings, essentially. She hard resets everybody. So Steven
loses all of his control of his powers and all the gems go back to like stock versions of the
gems without any of their character development. Like they don't know who each other is and shit.
And like, you know, immediately this isn't going to stick. And like that's like, I don't know,
for some reason, when when movies do that or narratives do that, I'm like, now I just got
to slog through like shenanigans until we get back to the inevitable end state of like, you know,
like there's so many songs. There's only so many songs I can take about how much Ruby and Sapphire
love each other. Right. Like I when when that was initially revealed during the season three
finale or whatever, that was like the highlight of the show. What was it stronger than you?
Yeah, it took the internet by storm. It was a huge big fucking deal because it was as fuck.
But how many times do we need to have an episode about yeah. So and like so that section, honestly,
their thing was kind of the most boring. Seeing Pearl reverted to factory settings settings
was was kind of more interesting because we haven't seen her that way right really before.
I mean, that was probably the coolest part of that section. But I just feel like that whole
section didn't do a lot for the overall narrative because like we're talking about this like whole
arc with Spinell and everything. I mean, I totally agree. And I think even her just being there and
trying to like fuck up the planet again was enough to be like, Yeah, my happy endings ruined. We
didn't need to kill all this. Here's my case for that. On the one hand, I totally agree with your
points. That makes makes perfect sense. And I agree. Like they absolutely retreaded old ground
for the sake of like, I mean, okay, this is a movie. It's been like, I don't know,
maybe like a year since there's been Steven Universe stuff. I felt like it was like they did
it to kind of establish the characters for people. Yeah, I think especially if people are probably
going to jump into a movie before watching like five seasons of a show, that's something that I'm
sure a decent number of people could do. And if you haven't watched any Steven Universe, I would
recommend you don't do that. And instead, you just watch the whole show, then watch the movie.
But if you only got two hours and you're going to die, okay, then go watch the movie. That's,
that's fine. Don't make peace with your family or anything. Just watch Steven. Yeah, just watch
this movie. There was a utility though, even has a suicide song in there. If you want to end it,
like it does have a suicide song. No doubt. Here's here's the reason why I think that was a good
usage in part because I still agree with your point. It was redundant for a lot of it. And we
got to see fresh things like Amethyst being reverted. We never seen her when she was first born.
She does this like gimmick where she just repeats things. She's got like a blank brain basically.
And I mean, that was that amazing payoff to that where like they do a song that's based on the
gimmick of repeating after me, which is like that was like, I loved that touch. I thought that was
so clever and such a genius way to like do that little progression for her. And then like Pearl
is like a robot. She's just being like a servant. She gets like a new master with Greg. All great.
Okay, but the utility in like going over the love, because like the way that they get their memories
back is they relive their experiences together. So like Steven needs to, you know, show Amethyst
a fun time. They need to go do the activities they like to do. And that'll like help her remember.
They do their secret handshake. That helps her. Pearl, they need to like show, they need to like
reproduce Pearl's plot development. So she realized she can be free and be her own person.
Doesn't need to just be a slave or whatever. Like her turning point sort of wasn't Rose Quartz.
It was her own freedom, so to speak. Yeah, that's true. The absence of a master ultimately what
did it. But and then like Garnett is the same thing. But like what the point I see to this,
the reason why I like all of that was because in all these scenes, in every single scene where we
see Pearl doing things and like Amethyst doing things with Steven, like reliving the moment,
it's like we feel how much love Steven has for Amethyst and Pearl and Garnett and you know Ruby
and Sapphire. That's so apparent to us. And it makes me reflect thinking back I did not like
Amethyst very much at first. I love Amethyst now. I've become such a fan of all these characters.
Okay, but the point of this is we as the viewer and Steven himself love and have a huge attachment
to these characters. So we feel that viscerally when we're trying to restore them to their memories.
But that entire time, Spinell, who's been reverted to her like happy go lucky, you know,
retarded, mildly annoying self, she is in she's literally third wheeling the entire time and
you can feel Steven doesn't really want her around. The contrast is so clear between how much Steven
cares about like Amethyst, for example, versus not wanting to have to bother with Spinell. It's
just a story about that annoying kid who's not terrible, but is hanging out with you anyway and
you don't really want them around. And this comes to like the final though the head during the the
song or whatever, where Spinell really recognized like, Oh, wow, Steven likes them way more than me,
which is exactly the problem that she had with pink, pink diamond. So like there was a utility.
No, definitely that I thought was enjoyable on its own anyway. Totally. And that that that definitely
it served a purpose and like for Splinell setting up like the fact like, Oh, I don't, I'm not cared
for in the way that these people are. And like, it's just like, I'm history is essentially repeating
itself, you know, exactly. I could see people. I just personally because that that certain plot
element drives me up a wall, I would rather they've done it a different way. Well, that's
understandable. So the other thing that I kind of, I don't want to say had an issue with it,
but it's kind of confused, not even confused about, but just like kind of shrugging at was the end of
the movie, the way the way they resolved the conflict with Spinell is that like, like, like
super big spoiler, this is the end of the movie is that she goes back with the diamonds and goes
back to homeworld and hangs out with them. And the diamonds are like, Oh, like you remind us of
pink, because the whole reason the movie starts with them wanting Steven to stay on homeworld,
because you're pink and we miss pink and we fetishize pink, I guess, and stay with us. And
the end of the movie is that Spinell serves that same purpose. So she goes back and like,
they are guests are going to fetishize her. And so she can have friends now. And it's just like,
not only the diamonds, like, like, that's not really healthy, you know, like fetishizing someone
who's dead like that. Because like, the whole point of the movie is talking about how like,
there is no happily ever after and like, things are always changing and you have to move on.
And like the diamonds don't move on, they never have and they assumedly now never will,
because they're just going to project all of their musings and desires for pink.
In their own song, they repeat as if they're trying to convince themselves the line like,
Yes, we know that you're not her. But like, it's fucking weird to convince us that they think that.
But I'm a little skeptical if they really believe. So that's the thing. I agree. The ending and a
lot a lot of the movie, honestly, like was it it was this easy to heal Spinell's wound and like
make or not a school shooter anymore? Like, I mean, there's some logic to that. But the overall
thing that a lot of people are criticized Steven Universe for and me too, is that it's it is a
supremely optimistic version of everything. This movie sounds really strange. It is interesting.
And I love it personally. But you should definitely watch it. I wish I watched this movie.
Well, it's not too late, even though you know everything that happens.
If you want to link, I got one. I'm so confused. Okay, I'll figure it out. I'll have to go figure
it out. What can I do? What can I do about this problem of having? I think I think it's I think
we need I think Ben needs to watch this movie and we need to have Steven Fornevers.
Oh, well, this is kind of it right now. I don't know if we should do another one.
I mean, then make a separate episode next episode. I have some opinions about your guys
opinions about this movie. Ben, just just watch the movie as soon as we're done and then send
me like a five minute take of your thoughts and I'll splice it in right here. All right. Future
Ben here. I watched it. I watched Steven Universe movie at 1.2 times speed. I guess I liked it.
The music was pretty good. Didn't like that one song, the truth, the garnet song,
didn't like basically anything to do with like the gems reverting and coming back,
getting them back. Oh, we got to we got to make them remember. Garnet remembering doesn't make
any sense. It doesn't make any sense. That part's terrible. I wish that weren't like half the movie.
Whatever. Teen Steven's cool. Fusing with his dad. Yeah, it's weird, but it's true that the
messaging about fusion has been inconsistent. So whatever. I don't know why I don't know why
Steven Greg fusion is like ripped because like they're both fat. So why is a fusion of them ripped?
I don't know. Whatever. Best part of the movie hands down. I mean, I mean, it's all about
Spinal. Spinal? Fuck, how do they say it? It's all about Spinal. It's all about evil Spinal
chewing the scenery, mugging for the camera, doing cool poses and looking awesome and doing
cool fights and those like those like two scenes that you can tell are animated by like an anime
studio that look fucking awesome. They're so fucking cool. Holy shit. And the ending's the
ending's dumb. The ending about they take they take pink they take Spinal back and they like,
oh, we'll love you instead. It's dumb. But I mean, the diamonds are all dumb. They've always been
terrible. Nobody likes the diamonds. So whatever. Nothing is ruined. It's contrived in the end.
Whatever. Is the earth fucked? Seems like the earth's like fuck. I don't know. She injected
the whole thing of poison. It was supposed to kill the entire earth. I don't know why they're so
fucking calm that whole time. It's just about Spinal. It's just about her cool faces. So fucking
evil. So fucking sick. All right. Yeah, go watch it. Fuck. Maybe I will. Maybe I just fucking will.
Hey, last point though about the the the other thing that seems okay. Like they once there was
one thought I had about the ending too, which is just like, so as you said, at the beginning,
they want Steven. Okay, Steven, at the end of season five, they're like, Steven, you're pink. We want
you back because you're pink. Like sure, you're weird now and you're a little fat boy. It doesn't
matter. You're pink. It's like they they were it's understood to be that like they understand at
the end because like some crazy shit happens. Pink is gone. Steven is here to stay that like
Steven is not pink anymore. But he kind of is. I mean, it's her son. It's at the very least,
it's pink son. So that's a pretty big connection. So you can see why they'd want Steven around.
I think I think more to the point is that like diamonds don't reproduce like humans do. So from
their perspective, this is still pink. Like that was the whole point in the beginning. And I you
know, sure, like you can't really reframe their understanding. That's pinks diamond. That's pinks
gem. Like you can't change who you are from their entire cultural perspective. Like that is still
pink. And so and that's totally understandable. Right. But like so like my point is like, once
they accept, even if they accept that Steven isn't pink anymore, and that he's like different,
there's still a very strong connection there. Spinell, on the other hand, is just like a friend
of pinks, basically. But they're and yes, she's very simple. Like she's designed to look like pink
with like the poofy pants. And she's fun. And it seems like they're almost too willing to accept
this as a replacement for Steven. And they just like leave as soon as they've got Spinell. That
seems okay, again, especially considering they showed up to stay with Steven on earth. Yeah,
but then they were like, well, I guess we have this facsimile of pink now. So they were willing
to stay in a place where they really didn't like just everyone wants to suck Steven's cock. So
this is literally like that that way. Wait, speaking of Steven sucking cock, can we talk
about how we gem fucked his dad in this episode? Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. You know that he had two
dicks. You know, yeah, yeah, yeah. So Steven and Greg fuse and become a four armed pompadour
guitar wielding madman to guitar wielding. Yeah, who seduces Pearl essentially and wakes her up
from her, her reset status. And it was very fucking strange. It was pretty sick. Because like,
because like, again, the show has like, made it pretty clear that that fusion is a metaphor for
like relationships and possibly sex. They're just going back and forth on this. There's no
consistency. So some people say he's just love and they could be like, I don't know paternal.
All right, all right, that's that's a slippery slope argument right there. I don't know how to
they code it so hard in some episodes, but then they don't at all. And when's when's Connie,
Steven and Greg going to fuse into a crazy monster? I mean, now we I mean, we've long
known you could fuse every being in existence, you know, all of the city fuses into the ultimate
life form. Yeah, go for it. Why not? That's what God is. I don't know. Oh, it's like, oh, it's like
a Madoka Magica moment where like, it turns out that what God is is all life form fused into one
being who then go like does things retroactively through time to control things from the future.
I'm just saying it's possible. That's what Madoka Magica. There's enough anime influence
in Steven Universe to make that possible. That's true. That's true. Okay, well, here's the thing.
Is this the end of Steven Universe? Like season six is I believe confirmed. And it is one more
season. I think it should have ended it with this movie. It would have been a perfect ending. I think
you're right because I anything more at this point does seem it's downhill. Redone baby 100%.
Speaking of season's ending, just quickly question. Have you guys seen My Little Pony ended?
Is it over? Did the final episode actually air? Yeah, I saw the I saw some gifts of the of the final
Nate spoiled it like a week ago in the chat. I didn't mean to. I thought it well. I thought I was
scrolling through the chat and you're like, Oh, this is the ending. And you put in a spoiler
tag. I'm like, that's considerate. And they're like, actually, fuck it. Here we go. I'm like,
because I thought no one cared. I can't box. Twilight looks so I have seven seasons to go. God
damn it. Not really. Like five. I got a ways to go. You know what? I do want to watch it. I might
skip every episode up to that point. But I do want to watch it. It seems to be very similar like
one episode like the very final episode. It's like it is a time to get forward. So you might as
well just watch that one. Is it really? That's exactly it. Like the kind of the story,
spoilers, by the way, for MLP for the seven people who care.
I mean, I kind of care. I just I, I spoil, I stumbled upon them and I was like, yeah,
all right, that's fine. I was doing so good. I dodged everything on Twitter. And I was like,
all right, I can watch some point of my leisure. But no, Nate comes in, ruins. So sorry.
Twilight is fucked. Twilight is a fucking Celestia sized horse with a big glowy mane,
but it looks like shit because she still has like the same kind of haircut. And it doesn't
look very good. It doesn't look very good. She was not designed to be this way. Implication,
that, uh, Rainbow Dash and Applejack are gay together. That does seem to be the implication.
What? It kind of seems, it kind of, it's kind of implied. It kind of seems like maybe Fluttershy
and Discord. Oh yeah. Which I hate that. Definitely. They tell me Rare Jack's not canon. I hate this
show. It's not canon, dude. It's not canon. No, no, I'm done. I'm done. There's too, there's too
many hints dropped throughout the entire show. Pinkie Pie and Cheesy Jean Sandwich. Oh yeah,
that's such a show. They're fucking, they had a kid. Oh my God. They had a kid and it just looks
like fucking curly hair Fluttershy. Yeah, I was going to say like the, like the one image I saw was
like a fucking nightmare. I don't want to watch it at all. No, it's fine. The image I got spoiled
was like with all of them together. And I saw the little curly hair Fluttershy thing. And I was
like either either Pinkie Pie got together with Cheese or Pinkie Pie got together with Fluttershy.
I guess Rarity just dies alone. Okay, that's, that's fine. They saved Rarity for me. She has a
Prodigy now. Rarity gets old and her hair turns gray. They're all old. They're all fucking old.
They're all, they're all gonna die. It's, it's happening. They're all gonna die and Twilight's
gonna be, remember how they said, wait, they're confirmed on Twitter saying Twilight wouldn't
outlive everybody else and they blatantly lie. Because she's gonna kill herself when they all
die. That's why. Maybe she's gonna. And Discord just rides from the ashes. It's like my long game
plan has finally paid off. Oh my goodness. Maybe, maybe she's gonna make everyone look forever.
You should find the magical. I mean, well, that's kind of fun. She's the Prince of Magic. So, you
know, she could. There's a, there was another thing. Shit, what was it? It's bullshit, I tells you.
Oh, I don't know. It's, it's complicated. Oh, apparently Luna and Celestia just retired. Yep.
Just retired. They just retired. They're done. They're just done doing a good run and it's over
now. The one to the Pony version of Florida. This is the stupidest shit I've ever heard in my life.
You know, look, we, I feel like all this thing is kind of like with Steven Universe. I feel like
you can talk shit and you can roast it. I bet if I watched this episode, I bet I would love it.
That's my contention. And I bet I would literally cry if I watched the final song. I bet it's got
that emotional sting to it. It's got those good songs. It's probably a musical and it'll make
you feel good, but then you'll think about it three days and you're like, wait a minute. Well,
fuck, I guess. You get to see what most, if not all of the cast is doing right now. You get to see
the cutie microseed is all grown up and stuff and excuse me for my cat. Whoa. Child. Okay. There was
just like the Steven Universe movie. The end of my little pony is bad. That's what I'm hearing right
now. Sure. It reminds me very much of the last episode of Star Trek The Next Generation is All
Good Things, part one and part two. And it's not quite this, but it's kind of a vision of the future
where there's time travel involved in it, but it's very well done as most is in Star Trek.
Not all the time, but it's like we see what each of them get up to in the future. And here's an
interesting thing. In that episode, Minor Spoiler. Well, actually, these are kind of major spoilers
for Next Generation. But I'm just going to say that data, we see him, he's like a, he retires
from Starfleet and he becomes like a professor. And he has like these distinguished white like
lines on the sides of his head. And he's like, he's in this giant library and just seems to be
consuming knowledge and he's become way more human. And it's just having a great life. Until a little
movie called Star Trek Nemesis came out like 10 years later, where they literally just kill data
despite the just just forget all the Star Trek movies. They're not real. Data becomes a wonderful
professor from like Oxford or something. He's got a beautiful, sexy robot daughter or something.
And life is great. Speaking of that great ending to Star Trek, the next generation,
are you ready for Star Trek Picard to steamroll all of it even more? Oh, I forgot about that.
I mean, I'm just not like I gave up on Star Trek discovery because it sucked. So I'm just not,
I just don't care anymore. I'm just over. I mean, I still got to get through Voyager and
Enterprise. So that's, that's, yeah, but Picard's going straight for the juggler,
they're going to fucking bring back Picard and they're going to do a bunch of dumb bullshit
because it's written by the same people who do discovery. So I'm not, yeah, I'm not expecting
anything great. I mean, I've been watching the, the red letter media guys are my go to boys to
talk about what to expect from Star Trek. And I've got zero expectations. So not watching,
don't care. Picard's dead. I'd love to be wrong, but you know, these things,
but he's so fucking old, man. He's so fucking old. Patrick Stewart. I don't know. He's still
making it happen. I mean, that's not the major issue because at the end of the end of all good
things, we see Picard retired to his family's vineyard where he makes wine, which he's
passionate about and is totally sick. But whatever. Anyway, everyone go watch Star Trek,
the next generation is really good or Steven Universe. These are all good choices. Now that
we've spoiled the endings for all of them. Go watch them. You know, you know, the thing is by,
look, unironically, by the time, if you said, said like, Oh man, they spoiled, I didn't even
really spoil, but let's say I spoiled the next generation ending. If you sit down, you're like,
fuck it, I'm going to go watch. By the time you get through seven seasons of the next generation,
you will have forgotten what we've said here today. So you know what you should do? If any of
these sound good, go start at the beginning and watch all the way through. I can vouch for Steven
Universe and next generation though. So go watch them. They're, they're worth your time. Okay,
anyway, um, that's it. I have some, I have some recent events. Sure. Discuss. Okay. On this show.
Okay. We would like to get on. Um, see, guys, the contra points deleted or Twitter.
No, I heard, I heard some vague ramblings about this, that something happened.
Point of order real quick. Everyone says this always, this is just a pet pee. People say
deleted Twitter, but I believe that the appearance of this is equivalent to one who has
like privatized or like, like made it so no one can see it. You've deactivated your Twitter. You
can reactivate it whenever you deactivate it. Possibly. Well, you can, can you only deactivate
it for a certain amount of time? I don't know. Don't know. Ben, you're gonna have to deactivate
your Twitter. It's possible it's deactivation, maybe not, whatever, whatever. Um, well, uh, yeah.
Um, so I don't know if you guys know why this happened, but I don't know who this person is.
Well, they're a, they're a Lefty Tuber. Well, they're a, they're a Trans Lefty Tuber.
What's their, what's their name again? Well, they're like, they're like the
contra points, contra points mage. Never heard of them. Okay, go ahead. Yeah, go on.
Um, uh, she, she said some, she said some stuff on Twitter that some people didn't like and it was
about, um, it was like saying that like older trans people are like more, they want to, they
want to like pass as binary basically. Right. They want to like just, just live as a woman,
live as a man or whatever. And like the younger generation is more, more like non-binary stuff.
And it's just, I don't know. She just like acknowledged that difference. And there was a lot
of very terrible on its face. Pretty factual. I haven't seen all the tweet. I haven't seen all
the tweets. Apparently there was more to it. I don't know. There might be more to it than that,
but like my understanding of what I've heard people saying is that basically that was the gist
of it, but people said that this was not woke enough, that she was erasing non-binary people
was stuff and, and, you know, and I mean, genocide right there. That's what that is. That's genocide.
Uh, people say, you know, people said that like, oh, contra points got canceled. She didn't get
canceled. She deleted her own Twitter, but like, what's annoying to me about it? Well, that one
guy just committed suicide. So he just did it himself. Was that a canceling? Oh, I want, that
was my other thing. But let's talk about that in a minute. Let's talk about that in a minute.
I don't know. The annoying thing about contra points is that these are, these are like,
these are trans people, non-binary people that contra points is like a huge advocate for. Yeah.
But then, and then they will fucking rip her apart and abuse her and tear into her and like,
distance themselves from her and say that, oh, we need to do better. We don't want this person
representing us because she's like, because they disagree on this one, like relatively minor
point of contention. That's been the entire problem with the, the, the lefty tube kind of, or that
sphere is that you step out of line a little bit. And it's not even stepping on the line. It's like,
you have a minor disagreement on the general kind of talking points and you're immediately
excommunicated. It's ridiculous. I mean, it is a huge win. It is a huge win. And like, if you can
show, if you're more woke than contra points, if you can be like, contra points is problematic.
Here's why she needs to do better. Here's why I actually am more progressive than, than, than the
legendary contra points. That's huge. You can, she's, she, you can take, if you take her down,
you can springboard yourself. You're the wokest. I mean, I guess that's true. You're even better
than contra points, dude. Cause you killed her. You slew her and you took her and you absorbed
her all her, all this. Think how much slime she dropped. It's a lot. She's very slime based.
Now you're the biggest boy in New Los Angeles city, baby. You know, man, the take, when I
examine the take itself, it doesn't even, I, I, are you looking at the take? No, well, did you say
am I a fan? No, I said, are you looking at the take? Oh, sorry. Not, not right now, not right now,
but I'm just going off of my general understanding. It seemed very strange to me because all it seemed
to say was that contra points was kind of voicing an opinion of herself and people who share her
opinion that did not seem like it was saying like other people can't feel a different way.
They were just kind of expressing a personal desire to kind of just blend in as a woman,
which I mean, how could anyone object to their feelings about how they want to be. It operates
as a hive mind. Twitter is like a hive mind. It's fucking terrifying. I'm looking at the tweets.
I'm looking at the tweets. I mean, I don't get why people are so mad. It sure it's not,
her position itself is not itself advocating non-binary-ness, but it also doesn't seem to
be criticizing it. So I don't get the point. Okay, well, here, I'll just I'll just read what she said.
Okay, give us the actual some of the offending tweets quote. This has happened to me before
in hyperwoke spaces like it's me and a bunch of cis women and we all go in a circle. We all have to
go in a circle saying she her because I'm there. Okay, there's this paradox where I can go to a
sports bar in North Carolina and be mismammed all night no question. But in self consciously
trans inclusive spaces, I have to explain my pronouns and watch woke people awkwardly correct
themselves every time they say you guys. I guess it's good for trans people who use they them only
and want only gender neutral language. But it comes at the minor expense of semi-passable
trans is like me. And that's super fucking hard for us. Okay, I find very so I see. Yeah, so I see
why I see the conflict here. I see that like, sure, sure, she is saying yes, there is sort of a
conflict of interest in that like about your fucking milk toast neutral takes on something
though. I mean, yeah, there's nothing incendiary there. It's just a literal statement of fact
and something it's just the fact that she's I guess not on the team enough of one group. It's
not even that it's just a statement that like the language it's being used here is at a crossroads
and that you're you got to lean one way or the other and it's going to cause I mean, why aren't
we mad at these people just as an example for denying contra points is desire to live in a
specific is punching up, dude. They're punching up so it doesn't count. Oh, our dynamics. I mean,
look, I think punching up at the person who's fucking like doing them more favors than like
anyone else on the internet. You know, you're done. It's maybe this is silly. Maybe this is
silly, but especially now I wish I'd gotten a chance to meet contra points at before they died.
They're dead now. Their Twitter is gone. They might as well be where they were
suicided. Yeah, they were listening to that spinel song. They're like screw it.
Contra points. Don't listen to Steven Universe movie. Don't do it. Now that's actually not funny
because I don't want this person to hurt themselves in any way and that has happened kind of recently
to make it clear because everyone was talking over me. I said deleted their Twitter not deleted
themselves. Oh, whoops. Okay, I took it a different way.
Contra points makes an insane amount of money, by the way. I believe that doesn't surprise me in the
slightest. Okay, I mean, look, they make extremely high. Ben, when you're gonna start dipping into
that pool and start ringing in those big victim box, I can't victim. But I mean, I can't do a
contra point stuff. You can you can you can lack the little experience to just make it happen.
I mean, I want to I mean, I'll actually you know what I was thinking. I take it back. Don't do that
because if you do that, it'll take you three months to start building up some momentum and then
they'll find out you're on this podcast and you'll get canceled. So don't even know. Oh, God, they'll
find out that I associate with people who say the n-word. They probably would not be fans of that.
You're fucked before you even began. You know, you know, you know what I think? I was, you guys
heard of this webcom called Stone Toss? I have heard of Stone Toss. I think I could be the lefty Stone Toss.
Big fan.
Okay, I mean, for anyone who doesn't know, Stone Toss is made by a Nazi and well, okay. I mean,
he said he's a Nazi. Are you sure that was like a serious point, though? Because people say those
things as jokes. Um, look, we know he's super right wing. We can all agree on that. Here's what I
think. Here's what I know. Okay, I know that he has said he's a Nazi and that everything he espouses
in his comic is consistent with the ideology of a Nazi. So I'm going to go ahead and say he's a
Nazi. Okay, fine. I feel like this is a pretty open shut case. All right, whatever. Um, I mean,
but okay, at the very least, he's a far right leaning. Yes, we all agree on that. And I feel
like I feel like I could be I feel like I could be lefty Stone Toss. You gotta make Rock Throw
have it be like with a Pokemon angle. Ben used Rock Throw. That's the name. How about Rock Smash?
Right? True. Yeah, I don't know. I mean, we got like Matt Bors, the guy who made the I am very
smart, like you live in a society and let you critique it comic now. I've seen a couple of
comics dissecting how effective how effective Stone Toss is as propaganda and like the way
that it's like punchy and like really easy to understand and like true and like in like funny
and ways that are not necessarily like bigoted, even if they carry like some like dog whistles in
them, like, like you can laugh at them for other reasons, even if you don't really know what they're
saying. Sounds to me, Ben, like you are looking to to as a wise man once said Ben Saint is obsessed
with branding and here he goes again branding himself using his lefty brand. Listen, listen, listen.
I saw I've I've seen a couple of people discussing I've seen a couple of people discussing and I've
and I've heard people say like we need a leftist equivalent like like the left needs a Stone
Toss we don't have anyone who's like but I was the left can't meme as they say I was like well
maybe I don't know like maybe I could maybe I could I mean hey wait a minute I just remembered
that I draw sometimes and I know how to do that these takes a hard left turn in more ways than one
I don't know this is something I was thinking about well you know what I'll say Ben I'll say
about this what I what I I mean look if you want to do it hey that's up to you man that's fine
but uh in terms of like what kind of it's just an idea it's okay okay around my old noggin
in terms of I'm just but then you'll have to post it under a different under a pen name or a pseudonym
because again as soon as they find out you're on the Nazi podcast you're fucked the Nazi podcast
all right podcast piece of in terms of when I think about well the things that I want to extract
from Ben's existence as Kant and I like because I I'm a big fan of the stuff you make um it's uh
like I think about something like Steven Universe look it is unequivocally true it has been stated
by the developers over and over again that like Steven Universe among other things like is is very
clearly intended to promote through art like progressive values and uh like one thing is that
all the gems are nine are non-binary Rebecca Universe is non-binary I suspect this is not a
coincidence and you know what it's probably made me as a person like more just being like oh a
non-binary person oh like a Steven Universe yeah that's oh man you know I get it I get it that's
well you're a non-binary person where's your gem where's your gem I'm gonna find that gem boy let me
look at your body uh uh oh my okay dark twist on the Steven Universe like there are gem hunters who
just rip the gems out of uh gem people and they harvest them and they use it for currency oh if
they meet like the Ferengi in space at some point from Star Trek cross over okay my point
time to write a fanfiction again uh it reminds me uh how much of latinum is a gem worth go yeah
who's like you know that's a good question by the way did you guys know that the currency uh they use
in Star Trek latinum is in fact a liquid encased in worthless worthless gold tablets because gold
I have heard that gold is replicable latinum is not so uh that's why it has value but my point was
Ben if I could have an ideal world uh I want you to make art and everyone in the world to make art
that slowly indoctrinates me into your beliefs and coming along for the ride through subtle and great
characters as opposed to you know outright political message I feel like all art does that that's what
I'm thinking because it's sure my spreading my ideas through this podcast sure aren't working
because everyone in the comments fucking hates me well it's a bit you're going you're going
hard without lube on a Nazi podcast what do you expect is gonna happen it's funny how the last
episode had like particular levels of like bile towards wait even though I was like specifically
less like like like aggressive about stuff like I specifically didn't talk well look I mean the
the commenters don't matter I can tell you that I appreciate I feel like you've been trying to be
you know not not antagonistic I'm trying to be a good boy you know I'm trying to have a good time
that is my prime virtue I want to hang out with everybody here you're all my friends
I just want to have a good time and talk about things that are reasonably interesting
and you know I'm not interested in getting like overly if there's something we strongly disagree on
and it's like an important debate then the PCB theoretically might not be the ideal place to
discuss it you know like if it isn't entertaining anymore but like in general I mean I'll tell
everybody I think Ben's being perfectly reasonable he's got different beliefs from me and several
others that's fine you know he's not being obnoxious about it I'm so reasonable you guys yeah
even though I'm fucking crazy on the inside I'm totally reasonable on the outside and that's
what it's all about I don't know yeah let's oh wait well no sorry I made my point so that's
all right whatever yeah contra points oh what about the suicide guy though that that guy yeah
that's another thing Alex Holoka or Holoka or Holoka okay do you guys do you guys know about
this oh yeah so you heard about this a little bit I did a whole I did a whole bonus podcast on my
patreon.com slash pod station too weekly bonus podcast oh okay there's 15 bonus podcast people
you're missing out on all of them maybe we can hit some highlights there's like okay all right I mean
there's there's developments right so like really first first Zoe Zoe comes out wait sorry Ben can
you tell us who this guy is just to begin okay so Alex Holoka and I try to okay I'm actually
there's more developments I've missed them so I'm fascinated there are there are there are okay I'm
curious how much you guys know about it this is like this is like pro this is like pro Jared again
and that like just more and more information keeps coming out it just keeps deepening the
scandal only like way more important okay um the so Zoe Zoe Quinn comes out with their accusations
they say that this guy Alec so okay do people know who Zoe Quinn is that they're they were the they
were the the by the way the five guys burgers and fries Zoe Quinn today now that's why I'm saying
they they're non-binary now okay yes okay I found this out I found this out it's on whatever it's
on Wikipedia um uh they were the person that's kicked off Gamergate because of like a sex scandal
involving like one of their exes like then reviewed their game and it was like oh that they they had
they oh they exchanged sex for uh for uh sex for free review and also they're a bad person and they
cheat on people and they're a bad girlfriend or they're a bad partner and so everyone hated Zoe
Quinn and then that spawned into Gamergate and then the new circadian and the game was like more
about like the integrity of the journalist or something okay well well it depends on who you
ask Zoe was involved at the beginning for sure I have another bonus podcast on Gamergate
a liar I'll tell you that yeah yeah okay so keep going keep going keep going get everybody up to
speed okay so that so so the so Gamergate just hates Zoe Quinn right but whatever Zoe comes out
with Alec accusations that like 10 years ago this guy Alec Holoka who is one of the two okay there's
a three person team that works on Night in the Woods which is an indie game it's very popular
indie game which I personally have not played but I know Night in the Woods okay okay and there's a
three person team but it seems like the two main it's it's Scott Benson is like the writer and the
artist Scott Benson's wife does I think she also co-writes it I'm not sure and then this other
guy Alec Holoka it was the made mainly the programmer and Alec Holoka had sort of like
gotten in touch with Alec based on Twitter they like Alec had worked on previous games before he
had known like sort of gaming industry inside people like Zoe Quinn okay and he was sort of in
this like weird indie game scene he'd been very successful and he got rich at a young age doing
this and he was kind of like an industry an established industry guy like before Scott got
involved with him so she accuses him of basically being like a fucking physically and sexually
abusive guy to her back when she to her to her yeah specifically to her okay and he and then
Scott Benson and the the Night in the Woods team take Alec off their twitter profile and like they
like distance themselves from him and they like remove reference to him and like it seems like
he's not on the Night in the Woods team anymore and then Alec Holoka kills himself he shoots
himself in the head what was the timeline there was that fast like 48 hours it was like a couple
days oh my god that's fucked up okay all right it was fast um and then and then his sister comes out
his sister comes out with a statement oh how'd you like this one you've you've read this I I saw
bits and pieces of it yeah his sister comes out with a statement that is like you know I knew out
she says she says I knew Alec I believe Zoey Alec didn't want Zoey harassed over this
doesn't help people go after Zoey people call Zoey a murderer like these accusations that you
accused a mentally unstable person of this and you know you're you're a murderer you killed him
you're you're a lie oh she's at it again the Zoey Quinn body count is racking up
um the sister saying that people are accusing Zoey she's not accusing Zoey well she says
she says don't harass Zoey over this and that he wouldn't have wanted that she says that he
specifically said that he wished no ill on Zoey gotcha that's what she says gotcha um let's do
that his own sister she says she believes Zoey okay okay and then Zoey deletes their twitter
and then uh Alec is the other guy Scott Benson doesn't delete his twitter but he's he's like
the co-writer he releases a blog post talking about his life with like the time that he knew Alec
and like based it is my take this this is the last thing based on everything Scott said like
Alec Holokos a piece of shit and he's better off dead he's a fucking scumbag okay sorry did you
say that's a hard take? Zoey deleted her twitter? Zoey deleted Zoey deleted her twitter? Well she
deactivated and reactivated it now it's private okay fair enough okay from what I understand at
least it could have changed again like people like people okay everyone was really mad at Zoey
and at first I was like man this is terrible a man died but then the reports roll in people
corroborate Zoey's story Scott corroborates Zoey's story Scott describes a whole culture of people
around Alec that he treated in exactly this way Alec's sister says yeah this is pretty much what
Alex was like Scott says like like my whole the whole time that I knew Alec he was like a
horribly abusive person he like you know he was always really secretive and cagey about stuff
he literally gave him PTSD from the fucking shit he put it yeah Scott has Scott has PTSD
but kind of makes you wonder why he worked with the guy if this is all well it's because Alec had
clout okay it's literally because Alec had clout and uh I don't know he used it to fucking
he uh you should you should read Scott's art Scott's I've not read Scott's post which might
recontextualize a lot of my understanding of the issue so far um okay if you if you were initially
on the side of like the cancel culture gone too far I get it I don't know shit that was my that was
my take two but like after reading after reading Scott's post no I mean no this is good this is
great thank you thank you Zoey I will not I will not go as far as saying I'm glad anybody's dead
is that just kind of like a hard and fast like I don't want anybody to die um okay I okay I wish
we I wish we could have rehabilitated him right that would have been better but I think it's pretty
clear that that wasn't gonna happen sure okay just in light of and he was a bad guy I mean look I mean
it sounds like we're I'm not saying she's lying or anything I'm definitely not implying I don't know
anything about the situation I all I know is mostly what you said but yeah it's kind of like easy to
throw shade at a person when they're dead and they're not there to defend themselves I mean it's
kind of I mean it's almost admitting to your guilt when you you kill yourself because I guess you
assume you there's no way to defend yourself but at the same time but the same time you could you
could have just felt like you know there was no way out there maybe some mental issues or whatever
it's not necessarily his guilt and maybe just some people had it out for him and you know they're
talking about the mob the mob I've seen so many people talk trash about Stanley after he died I
don't believe that that shit but I mean that's a whole other point just recently she also I mean
I mean I don't think anybody can deny the fact that like Twitter is enabling a lot of bullshit
you know the fact that like they're you just you can sick the mob on whoever you want without
any evidence or anything like that and that's kind of the really creepy thing Zoe in their
post Zoe said in their post that this was that they forgave Alex right for all the stuff that they
said interesting isn't that fuck but isn't that weird well here's the thing but why I have always
I assume from the get-go with the statement from Alex sister that this did happen to some degree
whether it was as extreme as Zoe was saying who knows Zoe has a history of coloring the truth
to her benefit but it sounded if your own sister is not coming out playing defense hard there's
probably some grounds for like legitimacy there but the thing this is this is an example of a
piece of shit being a piece of shit to another piece of shit because Zoe Quinn has a history of
doing fucking ridiculous shit and the whole reason that this even happened in my opinion is that she
was getting a bunch of flak for not delivering on the Kickstarter and this was a smoke screen
especially when it was 10 years removed and she said in the very statement that I forgive this
person and I don't want gave him and I don't want anything I don't want anybody to go after him I
just needed to get this off my chest it was a way of deflecting before it even took off
I don't want to defend Zoe Quinn because Zoe Quinn doesn't seem like a particularly great person
either but like even if you ignore what she said like the fact that the fact that like lots of other
people and women and Scott Benson came out and said like yeah I want to I want to look this this
is I just want to quickly say everything this person says yeah I just want to quickly say I'm
not saying that everything said about him was a lie no I don't believe that like he he does sound
like he might have you know done something to upset people and maybe you know harm them and what
not maybe he definitely did well we don't know he's not here to tell his side of the story that's
my point it's kind of remember when we were all convinced about allegedly the torrents and torrents
of people coming out to allege the abuses done by one pro Jared right that all of which fell away
and the only two substantiated ones were basically revealed to be at the one very likely just made
up and the other totally like we can't verify it at all so look I'm not saying that they're not true
I'm saying we should just wait for the fucking facts and like that's what are these actual
accounts that people are making look no what what like the thing you just said Scott's account
that's a very biased source in this whole affair what do you mean that's a biased source I that's
exactly what I mean he's a very biased source if he was given everyone's a biased source well
that doesn't mean the facts don't exist literally no one point to even one person that has come out
and said I knew Scott he was not like this nobody look my point is very uncontroversial nobody says
that my point is I mean given our recent events shouldn't we just every every everyone is like
yep I knew Scott he sure was weird around women we kind of had this thing that we all said like
don't be in a room then I would challenge you actually present me a list of the people doing
that and show me the evidence here's a problem maybe I will do here's here's the problem I have
with that you know everybody the the narrative with these stories is always someone comes out
and makes an accusation and then all of a sudden there's a torrent of people coming out and saying
yeah me too this happened to me too and like why wait this is exactly what happened to projaret
why are we waiting so long for this like like if we all knew that this guy was a monster for this
long why did we wait so long for it to happen do something about it like at this point it is
partially your fault for sitting on it for x amount of years and just letting it continue to happen
when is personal responsibility coming to the equation what do you mean personal okay I mean
distance yourself from the psychopath she's not responsible don't work with him I'm not talking
about Zoe I'm saying like if you're if you're a three person team and one of those people is
mentally unstable don't wait until some random person brings up baggage from 10 years ago to
finally pull the plug on him do it immediately okay well Scott I mean Scott the only reason that you
have lived in like a different country from alex right Scott didn't know about like alex personal
but you just said that he has PTSD from him well that's well yeah then not not from not from his
experience maybe stop working for him maybe stop working with him before you get PTSD this is such a
okay this is okay what he describes is a whole pattern of behavior whereby alex uses his clout
to like get people working for him like get people dependent on him and then abuse them look Ben
like this is that strategy I'm not even saying I don't believe you or I don't believe any of these
people I haven't reviewed most of the documents I don't know anything about who's made what claims
but I just think my position is simply I should probably find out as much information how many
of these accounts seem you know and I just want to know if they're credible or not I'm not saying
they're not I definitely just don't have enough and considering what just happened with projared
shouldn't we just I mean at the very least for me I'm speaking just for myself I should probably
wait before I'm like yep it seems all right all right you can wait listen I've heard I've heard
I've heard enough multiple independent sources also the same thing I'm just gonna say ala caloka
fuck you it's it's you know wish you could have been reformed you weren't gonna be reformed I'm glad
you're dead and I'm 100 positive that we will not be hearing anything that indicates to the contrary
it was a scumbag everyone in the industry knew it and that okay it's already it's already it's
everybody in the industry who knew pairs bears partial responsibility for not acting out sooner
is all I mean fucking weird victim blaming it's not victim blaming at all it's just stating effect
I just find it weird that everyone if Zoe Quinn is a hero for stepping forward then everyone else who
did it is a valet because he killed himself as instead of defend himself because like what are we
supposed to make about like oh boy I what I bet he would have had a great fucking defense he would
have had like a great like projared level like here's how I can disprove all my acute if only
he hadn't killed himself then we would know the truth no bullshit that doesn't mean he was completely
guilty of everything just because he did that it's just a it's part of the story I agree it's also
the court of public opinion has too much power something because of social media and it's dangerous
the court of public opinion what did the court of public opinion did not kill alex haloka no but
we really don't know the court of public opinion made made its judgment without and without a
public opinion and the court of public opinion didn't and the court of public
no stop this is ridiculous the court of public opinion literally did nothing to him
scott scott brought him up for he didn't fire him because alex was not an employee they were a team
and and alex had not been working on the project already for a while he'd been distant from the
project for a while and scott didn't even like him because he was like person like on a personal
level alex was like not good to scott so like the court of public opinion didn't fire alex
didn't kill alex didn't do anything to him he fucking killed himself so if if me and all my
he's the soul of my classmates at school we bully one kid we don't like and we all do it a little
bit but it's just enough that collectively he kills himself we all bear zero responsibility
across the board are you calling this bullying yes
i mean i think that seems one one word among others that could be used to describe it
i mean i don't obviously there's a there's a there's a morality attached to the term bullying
that the people doing it must be all evil and the people being okay must be all good well like
how if someone kills so if someone kills themselves like are you gonna like you what
there's a it just makes sense to examine the facts when someone kills themselves and determine why
they did it and you know maybe there was some fucked up situation going on there i have a
people deserve accountability i have a small story i want to that'd be bad so i mean it's
probably not all made up so good okay let's find out exactly where it all is like i don't even feel
like i should be commenting because i don't have anything to say i haven't done any research i'm
simply stating facts are good i will make up my decision once i get more facts and i want to
i want to quickly i want to share a story right okay i want to quickly i got a lot of them and
i've made up my mind and i think it's very well substantiated okay well i mean your problem what
what opinion you have like a bead nates or bead bends it doesn't really matter the things are the
way things are and whatever you think isn't going to change anything however um i want to quickly
say a story like with the situation it's very complicated it's hard to tell what what's the
truth and what's not and uh you know like i'm a bit with a date i would prefer to you know more
know more facts than you know make up my mind or whatever remember pro jared yeah i know it's not
the same from the very beginning there were conflicting reports about pro jared you all
just weren't paying attention that's possible i i'm still not paying attention to pro jared i'm
avoiding that as much as as i can anywho uh there was this story about this one girl that you might
have heard uh in uh not saying this is like the same it's definitely not the same it's a lot
clear more clear cut i suppose of the situation but um she drew fanard of rose quartz and she was too
thin and she got so bullied by everyone she was such an evil person and her way out was to try and
commit suicide thankfully she survived but if she had went through it and died would have that made
her guilty i mean i mean no like what's what's the what's the parallel the parallel is that
there's a calculus that i think everyone's doing here that's how much of a crime how much of a
moral crime did the person commit versus what's an appropriate i don't know social backlash and
obviously yeah there's different degrees you're illustrating the point the difference is that
alex actually was like a really bad guy and like lots whereas this person didn't fucking do nothing
these are like opposites i mean these are not people have claimed that this person was awful
in our eyes they weren't wrong well yeah and maybe like some of some of the people who are claiming
that this guy was awful are wrong that's my point i mean i don't know if they're wrong they might they
don't seem to be wrong yeah and they might not be wrong they might they might actually be honest
but it's just i don't like the way the situation has panned out i suppose that's my point and i can't
really trust them in this situation necessarily so i reserve my opinion on this whole situation
well who are you who are you choose who exactly are you choosing not to believe
no one i don't it's just i don't like the way it's such a big mess you don't like the
you hadn't even heard about this since then you're so fucking weird ben you're like oh my god
you haven't looked into the facts and haven't formed an opinion yet that's fucked up man like
you haven't looked into the facts and you're formulating an objection her objection is she
doesn't know yeah that's not her objection what is your objection is let's your rejection is let's not
jump to conclusions without the information and i'm saying i actually have a lot of really good
information yeah but yeah but you're leaning one way and i have your story i have but i haven't
heard the other part of the story therefore i don't want to make an assumption or you know
make us a solid opinion about the situation just yet i think they could be wrong they might
that's i mean that's fair there might more information i feel attacked i feel attacked for
my opinion okay then listen i don't i'm saying it's it's fine the way you you think i'm just i'm
not agreeing with you but i'm not exactly disagreeing with you either i just think there might be more
facts that might come out there might not be more facts you might be right you might be wrong i don't
know that's my point there's there's okay i i also felt i also felt sympathy i i guess my final word
on the subject i also felt sympathy for alex and i thought boy what if what if zoe was lying like
that would be so bad like that would be a really terrible thing that happened and then i read scott's
article and i was like wow fuck me dude i don't i don't even feel sympathy i reserve all feelings
until i have facts one way or the other and so yeah i'm just i'm saying this for the benefit of
the viewer if you're listening to me and you're like wow wow ben how dare you like good better off
dead that's a yikes statement go read alex's go read alex's article and then tell me what you
think to me to me is always like the boy who cried wolf i can't and like scott scott's article not alex
i keep confusing scott is the one that wrote the article yeah with like like i was saying like
zoe the boy who cried wolf i can't really believe her other people i might actually you know look
into it and see what they're saying and then reserve my judgment um yeah zoe seems kind of
questionable scott's a scott's a good boy i mean if committing yourself if committing suicide is
sign of a guilty conscience what is do you know privating your twitter or whatever is that all
suicide in the gill i i don't i don't know what does well does that mean that contra points is
guilty you tell me i don't know it's also private i mean i don't think so but other people seem to
what is what i mean that was the point you made like he killed himself isn't that suspicious i don't
understand i don't understand this because you're you're taking two things that you have the opposite
yes ben because one is the depiction of your point that i'm making for the sake of to show the
fallacy in the argument that that does not necessarily imply anything high i mean killing
yourself doesn't prove you're guilty i agree no part of your you're you're saying that oh killing
yourself seems like an admission of guilt but isn't deleting your twitter also that but it's not
if it's but if it is for zoe then it is for contra points it's it's you know what it doesn't
matter it's not retreating away from you know the public eye isn't necessarily admission of guilt
some people might say but i mean that's what pro jarid did pro jarid retreated from the public
guy for a while and then he came back and he made a video and everyone's like oh i get like i'll get
i'll give zoe that i don't think it's an admission of guilt like being bombarded by a lot of people
who you probably say kill yourself and other awful things you know that that's not fun so you know
just just uh you can private your twitter and that's what you probably did and that's you know
that's fine i don't know that i don't think that makes her guilty of anything that specific moment
of course anyway hey how about those voice mails uh
it's getting fantastic i raise this game okay this is the inception point for gamer gay too
all right it's coming i specifically asked not to make this podcast three hours and we're almost
two hours and then like the voice mails are probably gonna be like i don't know one hour so
well i mean how many of us bitch and complain when the episode goes long mage huh it's almost like
the episodes do that sometimes yeah i'm not i'm not complaining i just i really hope was hoping to
make it a bit shorter this time i was too but i fucked it up well it doesn't matter in any case
we've have the voice mails i fucked i fucked up and gave our listeners even more of the great
content they crave those poor bastards i was really hoping that this episode we could avoid
politics but no ben was here oh wine wine wine wine wine get go well go back to last episode
and get in the comments and say uh thank goodness thank goodness that they shut ben down from talking
about politics oh whenever he says any whenever he has an opinion about anything i just get so
fucking mad because he doesn't agree with me about anything that's politics is things that
don't agree with me i saw that i saw that one comment like somebody i saw you i think you
responded to or something this some guy was like thank god nate shut bet down when when did i shut
ben down i don't remember i don't okay it didn't happen i went really mad at i got really mad at
that guy yeah i don't even think he was the worst one i feel i was really mad at him yeah i don't
know i don't it's true i did not i i tried to avoid escalating in like a negative way i did you
know that's true i guess there was another yeah okay so that guy i'm a little sorry that i got so
mad at you but not really like fuck you man like get fucked right and then there was another guy
fidelio i don't know what fidelio fidel i don't know what your problem is because you see him like
a comrade right you seem like a comrade who just doesn't give a shit about like identity politics
yeah and this and this guy and this guy is like he's like a purely an economic driven he doesn't
care about the social aspect like that's the sense i get that this is a guy who's like steeped in
economic theory or something and he doesn't give a shit about anything else and so he's down there
in the comments like uh the fact that ben went to protest the straight pride parade just proves
that he's just a larper and he's not and he's not for real like he's like it's like he didn't even
pull a gun on them ben you fucking pussy you could make you like oh wait he went out and he went out
and actually did a thing well that just proves that he doesn't actually he's not actually doing
so much for the tolerant left am i right for the tolerant left why don't you read chomsky you
fuck okay i should probably read chomsky listen hey you know what i got i read conquest of bread
i just read the i just read the the communist manifesto it was really short uh maybe i'll
read chomsky next i don't know i'd be interested to hear i want to read bakunin i i just got a
book of my own i don't have a lot of these but i got a book um it's the vision of the anointed
by tomas soul you know tomas soul i know the name i forget he's a he's a libertarian guy and this is
a book as i understand it about how like top down governance is uh is in his view suboptimal
subideal and so i'm curious to see uh what he has to say i've i've read like one page so far
but uh he seems like a smart guy he's not like a smart guy so i'm gonna give him one page seems
like a smart guy can write some i mean from the other experience i have tom come on i'm gonna fucking
cut me oh boy i don't know you said the l you said the l word oh boy no no no no no no no no no no
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah all right well uh all right let's do the voicemail
last it's time it's time you still have to endure the voicemail whoa whoa whoa they could be good
this time we don't know yet no no no no no i'm saying nape okay before the episode nape you said
that the voicemails this time were of a higher caliber than usual do you stand do you stand by
that i i said are you gonna are you backpedaling the question was are like nape did you prepare
another bunch of shit voicemails because we don't want to deal with the pain if there's i said like
they're good i stand by they're good i stand by that is this what i said endure the voicemails i
meant the fact that our our like uh bot rhythm bot isn't working and we all have to click separately
oh god that's right okay that's that's what i meant short saga people so to get these voicemails we
had to do extra work because i looked into it i went to discord's chat or whatever discord is
currently not working with soundcloud for some reason we don't know since yesterday so we have to
manually play this in rn so forgive us if it fucking fucks up it's not our fault blame discord uh
okay in any case all right if you guys are ready we can click on number one yeah are you guys ready
to go yeah ready ready okay voicemail one is from riddle my ass batman and i'm gonna count three two
one go okay so here we go three two one go um shit did it did not work it's not work it's
shit it's not i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i only try let me try okay all right take a
sec no problem uh open with okay yeah i got it sorry okay all right all right here we go uh all
right click play go back to the start or whatever okay here we start on the count three two one go
so i'm out for a run in the middle of the park being a good fit boy like a dick good work so i'm
on the top of the hill feeling real good about myself when suddenly i hear a yell from the guy below
it's a one oh no so i don't know what's going on i don't know what's happening but i know someone
needs my help so i start spreading down the hill and halfway down the hill i hear a second screen
from another someone it's a guy this time oh i feel like some of you are beating me to the
do not steal my joke okay i get to the screaming and i find there's two young kids just going in
and i mean young like 15 or 16 young oh no so she comes up in in embarrassment in reverse
camera position and he's on the floor having a time his life drawing it right
good just i'm just in shock here like utter shock okay so the only thing i can think to say
in this particular situation is have fun use protection so i say i just sprint off so that's
my story i hope you enjoyed it from riddle my ass batman same pcp time same pcp channel
maybe was that was that a true story i i would like to imagine that he was shocking was out for
his run in full batman attire yeah and so these guys are just fucking and they just see batman
right up to them tell them to use protection and then fly off into the distance hey yours protection
sprints batman grappling hooks okay i mean a message for the people i guess that's riddle
my ass batman thanks riddle my ass batman i feel as a great start to my day all right let's go to
number two this one's from scumbag chris okay here we go three two one go three two one go
go there is no such thing as human core i thought about this two podcasts ago it was
two chickens hit to make a reaction however after hearing the absolutely worthless voicemails of
most recent pcp i knew i had to set the record straight thank munchy what you said was wrong
humans did not invent agriculture ants have been cultivating fungus for millions of years
and many even keep aphids as a sort of insect cattle and it was while i was sticky pre-nap
wank come at the peak of my kenja taimu or postnat clarity i realized there is nothing humans have
invented that wasn't done by animals long before us clothing bagworms war ants again art birds even
what i had at one time believed to be the most human core activity suicide bombing is a tactic
employed by ants humans aren't special we're just another animal and i am frankly disgusted by the
lack of creativity or genuine achievements we've had as a whole it is for that reason that i have
decided to give up my dreams of being an artist renounce my humanity and begin living life as an
ant along with the colony aren't aren't we all just ants living in the ant hill known as society
i i think he's saying he's going to suicide bomb pcph that's fair probably that's fair uh at least
we haven't wouldn't have to listen to you terrible voicemails anymore speaking of which uh we got
another call from human human core human core is human core are things that humans humans humans
must sabotage themselves humans sabotage themselves in specific way i feel like they're
i feel like they're they're a particular failings that humans are are subject to space uh no whether
or not they would if they could there are water bears on the moon that have been living there for
like fucking bajillion years what are you talking about oh wait a minute that's like a tv show ha ha
no that's that's a real fucking thing wait all right it's obviously a lie no there's no there's
little animals like fucking weird little creatures that are co-weekly known as water bears and they're
the most like resilient animal of all time they can resist like nuclear explosions and
shit and can survive in the depths of space and they found them on the moon because like they've
just been flung out into the fucking void and they're just on the moon now look at look at this uh uh
audio links audio links look at this shit i've seen so we don't even get that we don't even get
space travel they they're already forming starfleet without us damn it well if they were already on
the moon to begin with it's not like they traveled through space they hitched a ride on the moon or
something we're hitching a ride on a fucking rocket yeah yeah yeah it was a like a rocket
that crashed on the moon like had it's god's rocket hmm okay well all right pretty cool water
bears pretty cool all right we can't do anything we suck as a species uh but they're just so
fucking resilient they can survive in the vacuum these are the things that live for like millennia
and just like don't they must be like completely they're not parasites yeah i'm just saying if
we're gonna start doing some dna splicing i think water bears a good place to start you know
probably true they're not they don't look like bears i don't have you guys ever uh
have you ever heard a manga called terraformars you know you know what i'm talking about i've
heard of it yes it's okay it's a great series i mean it's it's interesting i like it and it's about
um basically they they colonize they're trying to colonize mars humanity i i believe it's mars
and they get there and um they they were trying to terraform the planet and the way they were like
testing it to see if it could sustain life or something like that was to use cockroaches
so they left a ton of cockroaches there but when like humans come back to like check on the progress
of the terraforming the cockroaches have mutated and it is big hulking freakish like black monsters
that are super strong in fact let me let me get a picture uh terraformars attack on cockroach
that's basically what it is that's basically when there's a there's a there's a show now too um okay
look at this guy this is what i'm talking about first episode of this back when it was airing
i i never watched it but i like the anime and they are yeah yeah they are um spooky yucky boys
damn seeing these they uh so the point was like the human beings however who go to colonize the
planet they're they're pretty scary they are absolutely terrifying and uh look at the look
at this happy guy he's having a fun time this cockroach man yeah they're not fun right okay okay
point no thank you the humans uh who come to fight them each of those humans
are given like a specific bug power to like fight against them like what like the main character
guy he gets like sick like wasp butt punching gloves or he can like sting ya and he's got bug
superpowers and everybody gets like a different bug power and it's pretty cool shonen stuff um
but uh what if we gave water bear powers that would be a pretty sick one that's just becoming god
you'd you'd literally be indestructible invincible it's literally just like curvy rock power you know
that's a pretty good power but then you can get grabbed in smash and thrown so that maybe it's not
so good after all uh well regardless let's check in voicemail number three all right we're gonna
count it down mage why did you send me this pad on the head uh because you said you were feeling
attacked and i didn't say that that's true that's true i feel i feel a little bad i feel a little
bad i feel like maybe i went a little too far to say that like it's good that he died it's not
good that he died it's sad but i also feel like humanity is better off without people like him
is there is that i mean i feel both of these things at the same time hey you feel how you feel
and i understand that position like i don't i'm not exactly thrilled when like murderer i mean it's
sad when like a murderer exists because like sure wish he was not like it is like it's tragic right
like it is tragic when anyone dies right like it's a tear it's a terrible thing not everybody
i mean some people i'm glad that not everyone but yeah i mean some less than others you know
alex is okay i i don't know there's a spectrum of how sad my scott's account he just seemed really
bad just seemed really bad and i don't you know i don't want to i haven't looked into the sky like
i i've known i've known people i've known people that he reminds me of and i just think they suck
all right fair enough that's what i think i think it's a fair enough uh feeling to feel like uh world
would be better off with it without certain people but it's always a tragedy when someone has to die
yeah yeah that's how i feel yeah that's how that's exactly how i feel okay next voicemail we got a
mouse ghost is calling in and i cannot wait to hear from him so uh okay here we go three two one go
oh fuck i i didn't start it i'm sorry i wasn't paying attention we'll restart all right sorry
okay this is on me okay you ready okay i'm ready count of three three two one go
hello this is the chairman mao curing from a communist hero comrades starin have informed me
of this podcast i've become a very big pcp fan however i recently reached into episode 173
and become a very sad ben saint only went to turkey bird politics and ruin her podcast
please take pager from a communist pain book in her stage glorious revolution overthrow ben
saint community people in china but even i know this misguided naive is ben saint
oh here's an error ship pcp t-shirts to communist hero you and comrades starin
are going to rip your merchandise oh yeah thank you there's going to be saying global communist
utopia of china it's all these those ones are bad i great we got to get some merch down to hell
right away uh this teespring ship to hell i feel like that's our target market i feel like that's
our demographic yeah yeah we're missing out like there's so much there's a lot of untapped
that's an untapped market we could we could really make some headway there i hope this uh this cadre
of uh it's what's the opposite of a rogues gallery um it's like uh like we're obtaining a group of
allies in communist hell and i hope this continues to grow who else have we got is polpot communist
no he was just like a murderer uh i don't know when we other people when we uh well there's solid um
um i mean we get marx pho marx or something uh castro mal maybe maybe the color maybe the car
marx was correct wasn't he like mean to his maid or something and like impregnated and kicked her
out so well he's probably in communist hell you know yeah i don't know that's pretty fucked up i'm
just he was an atheist god damn atheist that's the real i'm just saying if we can help satan get
verified maybe he'll hook us up with oh yeah yeah yeah yeah okay hashtag verify satan we gotta make
this happen now um okay only if he's also communist only if he's also an atheist i don't
want no you know religious satan is satan an atheist i guess we'll never i guess we'll never
know i think he'd be better he'd be happy until he gets verified we can't be sure that's true uh okay
next up all right get ready to click lads we got tongue twist me daddy he's calling in uh okay here
we go three two one go
oh god damn it no wait one more try then what the fuck are you doing all right okay i realized that
i'm bleeding i'm bleeding goodwill from the audience right now and from all the revolution
was upon us but now the will is fading yeah i i didn't hear that i was i was hoping i could try it
but now i don't know what it what it is okay well let's try one more time okay no no no it's okay i
didn't even hear it bended up bended here okay okay three sorry man here we go three two one go
here's a german tongue twister fish up rich fish fish fish fish fish fish fish fish fish
fish up rich fuck here's a russian tongue twister
that's it what what just happened what was that okay so the first one was a german one and the
second one was a what one russian that was a russian one oh okay i mean i can't the the german
one was just like it's fish up fish up fish up fish up fish up fish up no no she she was messing
up i think that's the that yeah any that makes sense to me i don't know how uh something about fresh
fish but she kept messing up so she i don't think she got to finish it oh i couldn't even tell if
she was making mistakes or not because you know no ear what about no she was definitely do you
pick up any russian there was there any russian uh the the second one i couldn't tell it was russian
well yeah i was wondering if you knew any okay well fair enough honestly the second one sounded
like she had like was playing something backwards i'd have to be i had i'd have to listen again
listen back again and just increase my volume a little bit to to to tell if it was russian hold
on okay fair enough i'm just taking her word the pronunciation seemed pretty good though for
someone who sounded american uh well whatever tongue twisted okay let's move on uh number five
let's go megalo smash i wonder what this could be about okay three hold on okay okay okay ready
good okay three two one go just in case there's small chance that this didn't come up on the
podcast i'm giving you the opportunity now all right all right that's that's okay ladies and gentlemen
thank you for uh reminding us we did in fact discuss sand he's a good boy i left that in as a fail
safe he does say some stuff oh what do you say he says i missed it i think he just said ladies and
gentlemen he's oh yeah okay all right good good good i mean true true and it feels good it feels
damn good it is a weird i feel like sands is the only assist trophy in history to be celebrated
i think every the other one is not an assist trophy he's not an assist trophy he's a fighter
costume actually an assist trophy would kind of be better i mean sort of g gino is pretty excited
he's he's a as a as a me costume i mean guys like me that that's what sands is too right yeah
yeah that's true but i mean i'm saying that like when when gino gino got in at the same time that
cloud was announced in smash four and i actually don't think gino is a me costume and smash ultimate
currently which i think is why people keep alive the hope that he could uh he could really get in
yeah so i mean that's by the way i i you know what i'm glad this came out because i almost forgot
to say did you guys know that this is actually by far the most important announcement except
maybe for sands but in that direct it's that they they stated you know it was a it was a they were
gonna make five dlc playable characters for smash they just blew the door up they're like nah
fuck that we're gonna make more dlc we're not stopping at five we'll go as long as we like we
like money so i mean yeah doors open boys we it's no longer just one and done we don't have to fight
between the steve idiots uh the the doom guy bros the the ramu fags you know it could be anybody
it could be a doom guy like what what if it's one of the demons like the dude the dude one
like like the beholder with just the one eye he just floats around i would love bolder
which cacodemon trophy or something i want i want the dude skeleton cacodemon trophy
trumpet guys uh oh man so many possible i found i found i found the tongue twister
you did yeah the german one can you pronounce it uh hold on i'm good i i can i can try okay uh this
is what it's written um fishers oh god uh fishes fritz fish frishe fish frishe fish fish fish
frishe fritz oh that's terrible wow what does it mean like fresh fish yeah what's it mean it's uh
hold on um the fisherman fritz fishes for fresh fish uh fresh fish is what the fisherman fritz
fishes okay okay okay yeah pretty good i like it it's good i wonder what the russian one is well
one one day maybe it sounds like a lapino one i'd like to be similar but it's definitely not the
feeling but uh there's one tank just a lot i like showing off because no one can pronounce it yeah
yeah it is a rare thing uh by the way this just reminds me did you guys you probably haven't
seen this it was like on my trending tab on youtube or something i saw a fascinating video it was um
it was by what's his face is it tom scott that guy with like the blonde hair the british guy who
always wears like a red t-shirt is that you know what i'm talking about yeah he does oh wait is he
like a math guy yes primarily yes but yeah i think i know who he's just like a genius guy he's just
like a knowledge information guy yeah okay he did a video he did a video this was fascinating
where like there is a chart it's about languages there's there's a chart that exists about i'll
try to find this later it's about like do you have the video about all possible that's the one
language sounds that could exist but don't because if you like the human mouth has only so many
positions that we can move our tongue and like mandibles and fucking our palates to to make
different sound effects and like across all languages if you look at the chart there are
blank spots where like sounds could exist but like nobody uses them there are blacked out ones that
can't exist or whatever i'm confusing it there there's marks for symbols that do exist because
someone's trying to make an alphabet of like every human language so that every sound would be
accounted for but there are theoretical ones that could be used in languages based on position of
mouths but in no way have been in any languages yet and i just thought this was the most fascinating
concept that's neat that's neat as right right you should check it out made just my guess to watch
it it wasn't in my list to watch i'm subscribed to good tom scott i mean honestly i wasn't that
impressed by this guy this video blew me away i just thought it was so cool but uh there is
he always makes such beautiful videos but he does make cool stuff he does the video about the
youtube i think i saw his video about the youtube algorithm right i'd like to watch that i don't
know i think he's got a big popular one about the youtube algorithm maybe i've seen him i've seen
him in other ones too i like his videos about the tree that owns itself and there's another tree
that owns it yeah how's that is it is it fluttershy get it no wait the tree that owns itself yeah
how does that work i'm not owned i'm not owned i scream i'm shrinking into a small corn cup
how does that work mage if you if you can break it down i'm just curious it's a very short video
you should really look it up but it's like uh it's something a while ago some some landowner like
you gave the rights to the tree to own itself and like that's fascinating and like and like
people are honoring it but like a few a few like like kilometers or something i don't know how
but like a little bit ways away there's another tree that also owns itself but it's not as popular
as the first one so no one knows about that one lol overshadowed by his big bro that's hilarious
by the way i'm just i mean i'll just throw this out there while we're just discussing smash quickly
some guy a komodo komodo enesis two just tweeted at me is like what if we had a swordsman me hollow
night oh that'd be cool oh i would love that oh that'd be so sick wait digi's not here correct
or else i would rip him into him yeah for his video that he made about me on the radicalization
of ben i thought that was a hilarious video i did not agree with everything he was saying okay
i didn't agree yeah it's honestly it was pretty funny yeah there were some things i would have
objected to it wasn't all bad i guess but it wasn't all bad i wasn't really that mad with
anything did you say even though i disagreed with a couple of his characterizations but the the
question whoever did you get the feeling that whoever asked that question like hates my guts
um i did feel that they were definitely not a big fan yeah i definitely thought that like he said
i think the kind of questions like i love ben and i love his comics but and then he but i just
think that he's like the scum of the air he did not go back and he's clearly just okay okay he he
brings up like he brings up like some specific shit like he specifically talks about like the house
that i live in and this is like stuff that i don't know why this is relevant to anyone and i wonder
if i know this person personally because i have someone in mind it's hargadine it's hargadine
no no no there's another there's another person i know in real life who has been to my house and
who i know is a fan of digi and i and someone said huh what if it was that guy and i was what it
could be it could be you know that that's possible i don't i don't know i feel like someone uh could
have not not to not to quash the dream just the way the tone was asked was strange to me and i was
like this feels like weirdly personal i think it's theoretically possible someone and i personally
think it's the more likely thing that someone just from hearing what you said about like living in
like a big house with like trying to you know keep the rent low because you split it with a
bunch of people like that in my house i like living with my friends with this question asks
it's like oh ben's just mad because he has to squat in the house with a bunch of guys and a bunch of
dirty you know i got he lives in squalor maybe maybe someone who's christ maybe someone who doesn't
agree with you on everything i i saw perhaps more of what i thought his point was which was kind of
like like given the way you choose to live your life that more aligns with like you know more like
leftist mentality on like i mean i don't know maybe maybe it does maybe it does i don't know i felt
that i felt the question was really hostile well i mean did you answer i don't completely agree with
it but i don't it's like whatever it's fine you should ask that person though i mean i'd be
fascinated here if it's actually he didn't say who it was i mean you should you should you should
grill them maybe suddenly try what conversations i'm out and suddenly like oh did you sure made
a funny video about me haha don't you think so friend no he's not he's not talking to me he thinks
he thinks i'll murder him real is it good he thinks you're gonna revolution on his ass so he
thinks socialism will literally kill him um he thinks he thinks that i want to personally execute
well it sounds like he's just misinformed about your particular beliefs he's i told like that's
not he's just he's just one listen you know it sounds this sounds to me like a guy not i don't
i don't know him but uh it sounds like he's a little bit too like he thinks that you know he's
heard the memes of socialism death that count or whatever and he's like oh that means me i'm gonna
be death counted or something by i don't know that's that's my guess this this was a this was a guy
i don't know if i really i don't want to i don't want to talk about this guy specifically whatever
but that's that's that is amusing regardless um yes so i mean did anyone else get the feeling
probably not him odds are it's not him but wouldn't it be funny if it was and i was like ah now i
understand everything the context is all that you know about the video though like about the digits
video like i thought it was i really feel like look we all see the world and we see the things that
like we are most attracted to and like yes you've done like interesting marketing things by occasionally
throwing a few dollars to like advertise your your things somewhere but like did you whole thing
about like marketing i feel was him being like this is how i see the world ben must be this way too
so this is my i think it was a little bit of projection yeah that's the right like okay the
fact like it's not like in a way it's true that like everything you do in public is marketing yeah
right like in a certain sense it's unavoidably true that that ever that i am marketing myself
but that's like a really broad like the part that i object to is that he said
there's a part where he sort of implies that i like i saw people succeeding on the left and
i saw that there was money to be made i mean yeah he did kind of like that's not like i have i don't
know like i mean you'd have yeah i guess i guess there are some people like that but like i don't
think it's like a huge like money mill i don't think there's like and i certainly haven't like
done anything to make money in that way so i don't know that's that that's the one thing that
i'd be like no that's just wrong everything else whatever it's yeah i don't think you said anything
particularly me i just i just thought like i mean me knowing you i was like ben seems pretty sincere
i mean i don't think he's you know i don't know yeah did you didn't did you didn't say like oh ben's
not sincere but i feel like a lot of the comments like read like heard him as saying like ben's not
sincere a lot of the comments are your typical stupid you crit you you criticize capitalism
even though i mean ever considered the fact that not all of them are like that but a lot of them
are unironically that's silly because to go back to what we were saying earlier is like if you're
trying to like score lefty points to get more money the last thing you want to do is come on a
podcast like this like that's just putting it i mean well i mean to be fair ben is making money
by being here so there is a resistance to just no but i mean if you're trying to make money off
like the left narrative and like being a lefty guy to make that long-term transition yeah you're
just setting yourself up to like like do i want to just tag tie this huge ball and chain around
my left leg right now you know like it's not a good idea but if there's a space for like a
hardcore like kind of free speech also very lefty person that seems i don't know if that market
really exists though uh they're just what about uh what about look well there's a lot of slovoi slovoi
zizek yo well yeah yeah okay there you go slovoi zizeks like that there's um you know the dirt the
dirtbag left the dirtbag left is all the dirtbag left there's there's lefties that say retarded
and stuff you know they exist yeah that's fair uh okay all right i've seen some of them in the wild
so we've got one last voicemail now this one isn't like a normal voicemail it's more of a someone
was kind enough to make a public service announcement for us on our behalf so let's play this pcpsos
okay i won't okay we all set lads okay all right the count of three three go okay here we go one
two three go this is a fucking emergency okay listen to me the pcp needs more voicemails man
they didn't even notice maybe they did i don't know two of them were me last week
two of them were the same guy oh no ah we need more voicemails it's fucking hell out here we
need some more content he can't wake up mom and dad in the next room over i know that's what i was
thinking it's his fake whispery oh i love that that's i remember doing that the neighbors will
complain when i started making youtube videos i had to be quiet and i would do that but now i've
got a office and stuff what's what's his point what his point is two of the voicemails are from the
same guy well that just means you're a great voicemail man congratulations that's true but
we do need more voicemails send them people pile them in sure but also make them good because
they don't want to make them trash yeah yeah quality more importantly make them good exactly
tom exactly let this be a what's the word a buyer's market on our hands not a not a seller's market
where we'll take whatever we can get we don't want that compete with each other and and what's the
where i want to like lower the not the bar to get over i'm trying to raise that look to lower the
you want to lower the floor i don't want to lower the floor i want to want to raise the skill ceiling
and also raise the floor i guess and also yeah everything goes up that's you want to you want
to raise these people up out of the depths of their own mediocrity to create something it's not it's
not left or right it's there i just want to hashtag raise these bros that's all there is to it all
right that's it for the episode everybody uh speak pipe click down below to leave those voicemails
on uh the website where we get them it's a big fun time please do so make them good uh patreon.com
slash the procrastinators one dollar patreon discord five dollars twenty nine bonus episodes and we
just before starting had a great idea for the next one which i think you will be interested in but i
won't tell you yet in case it doesn't work out but we'll we'll get to that soon uh what was the last
what was our last bonus episode again that was uh doom playing uh uh no i would create quake three
the arena yes we re-entered the arena the rematch we re-entered the arena just like i re-entered
the birth canal to be unbirthed and frankly it was the best choice i ever made in my life
i disavow i disavow all right uh so give us money much appreciated thanks everybody for
supporting thanks for donating at tpcrastinators updates twitter stuff there you go hey hey my
kickstarter check out my kickstarter it's boy i'm scared saying this right now because i only
have like five days to actually make it happen and make sure that it's up but if i didn't
fuck it up link in the description papers to buy a book put it on yourself get up get some pins
excellent have fuck yeah that sounds great now's the time is there a new pin for this uh for this
upcoming one there is a new one i want to know i want the pins i love my poobah pin i want a new
there is the okay so i there is the poobah pin which you have you okay because i have like
because i sold most of them the first time to get the poobah pin you gotta buy like you gotta buy
it in like a bundle the new pin is infinite jest you can now have infinite jest on your person
at all times and did i mention how many fucking guest chapters there are there's like six
okay ben it's gonna be like it's like new content that's that's excellent question ben if you had
to make a pin if you have any ideas what would potentially be a pin for chapter three
maybe like crippling depression you know uh um magda god i don't hmm i don't know a hospital
ivy or something uh the ivy uh boy a shoe a slipper a magda slipper perhaps oh you know
the slipper is a good wait but that's just a poobah damn it you're right i forgot what okay if you
put two of them next to each other you could get the poobah slipper effect you know yodels yodels
did she yodels i can't remember she she steals the box oh yeah ha ha fuck the man that's that's i
think that's the best i can okay all right well i as a completionist minded guy this this is what
i think about when i think of these things and i look forward to it one day uh i hope you get
sued by the guy who makes infinite jest for all your money for using his like this don't you know
he's dead oh shit but he's a but he's he fucking a la colloquium so but his greedy estate surely
exists and will demand their their devious compensation lawyers or children or relatives
you hope so yeah let's let's hope so like no no you don't understand i i curned the s and the t
just a little bit to the right so it's infinite g street yeah it's fine it's not the same book
you don't yeah you don't own that phrase because it's a shakespeare reference so it could be a
totally different book it's very that's fair use yeah okay fair use you don't own the concept of a book
so get fucked all right sounds good we'll do chief uh all right we'll see you next time everybody
patreon give us money twitter at tbcrasnairs speak pipe for voicemails that's all you need to know
thanks see you next week peace
oh