We're recording, and maybe this will be in the episode, or maybe not.
Yeah, who the fuck knows?
Who knows?
It's a mystery.
I mean, if we sync later, you can still sync this all up too, so it's all good.
If we sync like the Titanic later, this will be our lifeboat.
That's every episode since Nate's left, am I right?
It was Nate's show.
I mean, it's not the same.
The Titanic is a happy ending, though, because the old lady got a locket or something.
No, she threw it into the ocean like an idiot.
Did she get it again?
They found it at the end, and they gave it to her, and she throws it into the ocean a
second time?
Is that how it goes?
No, she throws it into the ocean and dies.
Oh, well, I approve that.
I've never seen it.
That is not what happens at all.
I mean, I don't remember.
That could be what happens for all I know.
No.
I just remember that Leo died.
Yeah.
Leo!
My beautiful bull.
I saw a tweet, and it just got me.
I don't know why.
It's just a picture of Trump yelling.
Just Trump yelling, and the text is, I've abandoned my child.
I've abandoned my bull.
It's like, yeah.
OK.
We've all been there.
My child.
Dude, I'm watching, I watched like the town hall with Trump.
Oh, man, that was, that was hard to get through.
Oh, was that the one at the same time that Biden was doing one?
Yeah.
The what?
I didn't check out either.
Yeah, I watched them both.
I'm a fucking scrub.
I mean, give me the highlights.
It's really hard to just highlight it.
The man is just so dumb, so fucking dumb.
It's really hard.
Somebody said, did you see the thing about like Hunter Biden this week?
You know, I heard about it, but I haven't like watched anything.
I saw that image of him being like, I want to go to the anime realm.
And then Joe Biden gives him a bong and he smokes it and he sees anime.
Is that what happened?
Whoa, I'm voting for Biden now.
That sounds awesome.
That's what happened.
Well, it's like, I guess Hunter is on the one hand some sort of like oil company
executive, but also like a complete fuck up crack head, like a literal crack head.
Sounds about right.
Like pictures of him smoking crack.
And, and I guess I didn't read them, but I guess some texts leaked of like Hunter.
Like, you know, I get maybe check himself into rehab.
It is, you know, having a fucking crisis or whatever.
And it's like text between like Joe and Hunter.
And I guess Joe is like, you know, very much like, I love you no matter what, you know,
I'll always love you son or whatever.
It's that kind of thing.
And it's like, I guess Rudy Giuliani leaked these thinking that they were like going
to be damning to him because, oh, your son's a crack head.
But like everyone I've seen is like, this is like really humanizing and, and is like,
even like the people that I follow that all hate Biden are like, even I felt something
for Biden in this, in this read in this shit.
Right.
Oh God, the man loves his son.
That's that.
Yeah.
That's going to go really well.
Like, yeah, what a piece of shit loving his son despite his faults.
Treating him like a human being.
Wow.
Amazing.
Incredible.
That's almost like, like it wasn't leaked by someone who's trying to, you know, fuck
him up.
It was leaked.
It's Joe and Hunter Biden making fake, making fake text messages that then leaked to Rudy
Giuliani so he can leak them.
Like it was all a ploy.
It was a 40 chess move.
Hey, some pretend that I love you for a minute.
Okay.
Yeah.
Secretly by Joe got his own, his son addicted to crack intentionally so that stage this
whole, this whole long play and he, and he arranged for Bo to die of brain cancer too
so that he could have a humanizing, a tragic backstory.
Oh my God.
And then when the cameras on Joe will kick his son like a puppy.
Me.
Meanwhile, like there's a, there's a thing from, from Trump.
There's like some, I guess, like when his first son was being born, I think Baron, that's
Baron's his first son, right?
They're like, no, we're like, Baron's his youngest son.
Oh, no, no, no.
Don.
Don Jr.
Is that?
Or who?
No, he's not the oldest one.
I don't know who the oldest one is, but I guess when his first son was being born, his
wife wanted to, his wife wanted to name him Don Jr. and Trump said like, no, I don't name
him Don Jr.
What if he's a loser?
That's kind of based.
A little bit.
Someone said like, you know, I don't like Biden, but this shit is really endearing.
And I, I responded like, Trump says stuff that endears me to him all the time, in that
it's like funny and it makes me laugh.
Like that gift of him making all the funny faces like, this is a funny man, this orange
man's still bad, but like, you know, anyway, this is all in like, you know, you can, we
can, we can, we can all, we can all be like, oh, oh, yeah, pretty, pretty good that Joe
loves his son, but also support Medicare for all, please.
Yeah.
He may care for his son, but that doesn't mean he'll care for us, the sons of America.
No.
Or we.
No, indeed.
What do you mean us?
Yeah.
Fucking British man.
Yeah, who are you?
Nothing.
Give his, give his trans America.
Trans American.
Yeah, yeah.
The trans Atlantic Railroad.
Man, if you really want to like, fucking oppress yourself, become trans Atlantic, become an
American, you have to get, you have to, you have to give yourself COVID.
Like, sorry, that's just, that's just part of the process.
Just the way it is.
Oh, look who's in the chat.
Look who finally is.
Who's in the chat?
Finally decided to show up.
Hey.
This is it.
This is epic.
Oh my.
Our guest is here.
We did it.
Everything good.
Fashionably late.
Well, 50 minutes.
What, what a bougie fucking.
50 minutes late, but it's okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So who are you guys?
Which one is, are you the did your bro guy?
No, he's not here right now.
We're the less important people.
Oh.
No, the better people.
No.
Is it me?
Which one's the, which one's the guy who did the, the, what's it called?
The guy with the gun and the pizza on his pants.
Oh.
Munchie.
That's Munchie.
Munchie is, Munchie is dead.
You know, you know, guys, I've watched all of your things, all of your lectures, like
multiple times.
Excellent.
That's so based.
Oh, it's a bad one.
Even the one I did.
Which one was that?
The brisco one.
What?
No, don't worry about that.
No.
Is that one I haven't watched yet?
I thought I watched all of them.
I guess.
It's relatively recently.
There was a couple of ones that came out a few months ago.
Like, I gave dude one on, on, on brisco.
I did one on Animorphs, which went over pretty well.
Ben did a.
I did Chris Chan 102, which is.
Oh yeah.
You haven't done that one yet.
Still in my fucking editing bay.
You haven't?
A family year later.
You better do it soon.
I know.
Yeah.
It's time.
It's, it's well, it's long past time.
So there's the, the Deagle Nation one, the hottest guys in the universe one, and the
360 Sonata 101.
I can't believe that 360 one exists.
What a, what a bizarre artifact.
It's pretty great.
It's pretty interesting.
All right.
Let's.
Hey, okay.
On the count of three is go one, two, three, and then we all say sync.
And just for our editor's sake, could you, when you sit, when you say sync, could you
like maybe wiggle your ears up?
I guess.
So our editor can, can, can sync the footage with the audio.
So when, when we say sync, I raise my eyebrows like this.
Yeah.
Yes.
Okay.
Cool.
We'll do it twice.
Yeah.
One, two, three.
Sync.
Very, very nice.
Okay.
I think, I think I have everything positioned so that it won't fuck up.
Let me just close my other windows here.
Yeah.
Okay.
Hello, everyone, and welcome to another episode of the pro crass snators podcast.
It's me.
It's me, Ben St.
We got Tom Oliver.
Hello.
We got Gibb and take.
And we got, and we got our guests today.
My friend, Mary weather, who is a, is a cat boy was like a big, a big deal famous guy.
It's like a, he's like a internet content.
He's like an internet, internet fucking mogul over here.
No.
Yes.
And also he's a Vtuber now.
That's correct.
And there he is.
Look at, look at him go.
Yes.
He's like looking at that cat boy move.
It's, it's so sweet.
It's a dog boy.
I'm a dog.
I know.
I knew he was a dog.
Wolf.
What the fuck's a dog?
That's very much for having me on everyone.
I'm a big fan.
I'm glad you're here.
I'm a big fan of the pro crass to pay us boys.
Same.
That's its name.
The perspirated boys podcast radio show.
I enjoy when you, I enjoyed when you did the lecture on that guy.
What's his name again?
Paul Western, Paul Western Chandler, that one.
Yes.
Yeah.
Paul Joseph.
Paul Joseph Westerns.
Yeah.
Chris, Chris Chan.
I think that's, I think that was probably the first thing we talked about, Mary.
I don't even remember.
I think, I think it was.
I think, I think it must, it must have been, we had, because I think around the time that
we started talking, you had not too recent, had not too long ago done an interview with
Chris on your other channel.
That's correct.
That's right.
And it was, I pride myself on that interview because what I was told afterwards is that
we didn't try to troll him.
Oh, sorry.
Yeah.
Um, trolling.
There's, there's a certain strain.
There's a certain strain of a, have you, you've, you've interacted with, with Christine
on the, like on Twitter.
Yeah.
Right.
A few times.
Do you, do you notice, do you notice like the tone of the replies that always happen?
Yeah.
Uh, whenever she does anything on Twitter is so negative and gross.
It feels like very, um, it's so overdone honestly.
I don't think, I don't think anyone's really trolled Christine in a funny or creative way
for many years.
Yeah.
Uh, the, the, the like, it's, it's, it's, it's sad.
Like you, I don't know.
She'll just like do, says anything and like, everyone's just immediately jumping on it,
even if it's something unremarkable.
Fifteen, like teenagers or something.
I don't know.
We'll, we'll just be in there like, uh, Chris, shut up.
You're delusional.
Like nobody, nobody likes you.
Nobody believes in the dimensional merge to get a job.
Yeah.
She'll just say like, I'm having a good day and everyone will go, no, you're not.
Oh, you, everyone hates you.
You're a terrible person.
It's very, it's very crazy.
All of the personal stuff.
The epitome of your reputation precedes you.
They always bring up like extremely personal stuff that only a complete lunatic would
know about.
Like this, like stuff about his mother and stuff.
Like, why do you care so much?
You're just trying to be an asshole.
Yeah.
That's right.
That's true.
Sad, but true.
Um, Mary, um, you, uh, do you want to, I don't know, I, I make comics sometimes and you've
made like a million, I also do comics sometimes.
You've made like a million fucking comics.
You have like, I, I don't think I can list them all.
Honestly.
I'm sorry.
That's okay.
That's all for you.
If you'd like me to.
Yeah, sure.
Go for it.
Winter moon, internet explore, everywhere and nowhere, stalker, stalker, my succubus
girlfriend, one million gold, fox girls are better, uh, console girls, meme girls and
spook man.
Nice.
I think I've seen the, I didn't know about seven was the internet explorer one.
I think I've read that.
You might have.
Yeah.
Posted it everywhere.
I've read, I've read that one.
And I read, um, I read most of, wait, you did.
Did you say crawling dreams?
Yeah.
I read most of crawling dreams because I like the girl with the big boobs.
You guys know it's illustrated by a girl.
Uh, no.
And, and she refuses.
She absolutely refuses to draw anything that does not have giant boobs.
Can you introduce me?
I can.
I'll send you a link afterwards.
So her name is, her name is Ushimi and she, uh, I have offered her to attempt to draw
a girl with a slightly less gigantic boobs.
Uh, and she has refused.
So yes.
If you, if I will, I will actually send her, I will, I will message her and I will say
I'm a big fan of your.
I think you should.
I think that will make her very happy.
I will.
Absolutely.
100%.
Nothing would, nothing would make me.
It's funny.
Everyone thinks I'm the one asking for those characters to have gigantic boobs, but no.
In fact, I would prefer it if they didn't, every single one of them have gigantic boobs.
But, uh, yeah, every character that is not, that does not have giant boobs in that series
is drawn by the second artist we have on that series.
You're kidding.
I'm not even kidding.
No, she's, she's that serious about it.
She does not do the backgrounds.
She does not do the male characters.
She does not do anything that is not a giant titted female.
I respect the dedication to the craft.
Yeah.
Perfect.
Real goals right there.
Nobody else.
Nobody else fucking.
No, no, no, I'm going to do it.
Nobody else fucking talks to you.
Yeah.
Um, actually I remember that lecture you did on the girl, the girl who did the, uh, the
coconut wish girl.
What, what was her name again?
Yeah.
Jennifer Diane right.
She's fantastic.
I had no idea about any of the things.
All I'd ever seen of us was that one coconut wish comic.
Um, yeah.
Yeah.
And introduced me to this whole world.
I had no clue about.
I was so amazed.
Honestly.
So I left a comment on that video.
I said, why?
Mm hmm.
I was so amazed.
I was so flabbergasted.
Honestly.
How?
Uh huh.
I, I said in my comment, very specifically, why is the coconut wish girl better at writing
webcomics than me?
And I've been doing it for like nine years now.
And all of your viewers completely just dog piled me because you saw your awful, maybe
try putting some effort in, maybe you'll beat her then.
Oh, was it, was it that bad?
Wait, let me, let's, let's find, let's find, I deleted the comment though.
You did.
I kept, I kept getting, I kept getting replies.
They kept being like in my notifications for months later.
No.
What the fuck?
It was so amazing.
They just all owned me.
They kept doing it.
Your view is just, just like ganged up on me and bullied me too.
It was amazing.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, I, I, I, I see, I see the comment.
Oh, I didn't delete it.
I see, let's, no, I'm, I'm glad though.
I might have just.
What was the one?
I talked myself out of believing it.
The one that I said I thought was the funniest was, oh wait, you, you were, you were too afraid
to go on.
That's, that's the difference between you and JDR is that JDR goes all in and you, you
just, you just lacked the, the, the, the moral fiber.
Yeah, I really am.
Apparently.
It's so difficult writing such a robust world building thing.
You know, I've tried so many times and I just frazzled my brain trying to come up with everything.
Yeah.
I, I was thinking about, I was, I was thinking about, I was thinking about that.
I was thinking about like, man, building like a big like comic.
I was thinking about the champion specifically.
I was like, man, expanding on that world is like any idea that I have for that just seems
like stupid.
It just seems like, what's even the point of doing that?
Like why even bother making a comic, building a world, creating fiction?
It's so lame.
But then I was like, you know what, actually, you know what?
It's, isn't it actually about, isn't it actually about the characters?
Like if I focus on that, I don't feel that cringy about it.
I don't feel that like intimidated like, oh, how would I even begin to like create a setting
that is not stupid?
The best things usually have a robust world that the characters like use to their advantage
in telling the story that they're about.
Like the, the interestingness of the world is useful in the story that the character is
in, you know what I mean?
I feel like if you, if you have a character and a white void, they're not going to have
much to do.
I feel like, like she actually took the hard route with all of it, with all of her world
building.
Because when you look at the world, like when you look at the, see, based on your lecture,
I haven't actually gotten around to reading the webcomic yet, although I really want to.
Based on what you were telling me, the interesting part was, in fact, not the characters.
It was the world they were in.
Oh yeah.
And that takes a lot of skill to do.
Like usually it's the other way around.
I think that she was a lot more interested in Bill.
And I'm sure she likes the characters, especially like, you know, a couple of standouts.
Yes.
But I think she's much more interested in the, in thinking of, thinking about universe,
parallel universes and like timelines and like, ooh, how does, how did, what an alternate
physics work?
Like that, I think that's what fascinates her.
Yeah.
On this, on, on that subject though, I did something this week or maybe it was last week,
I don't know.
A little wacky, a little weird, a little crazy.
Well, I went and I read one of her, a, a film fiction, her My Little Pony fan fiction.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
She has, I'm looking at her, her biography, Chatoyance on a, a film fiction.
She has written a total of 1.4 million words.
Whoa.
I guess that's a lot.
And they are set in, they're set in a whole bunch of, I think I explained this a little
bit in the lecture that like, her, her pony stories are all set in these like, kind of
like sub universes of film fiction.
You know what I mean?
Right.
These, these like fan, these fan like, constructions wherein like, oh, this is like a, an AU.
Yeah.
An AU.
So she did a Marvel film?
She, she didn't start these like, like the, the big one is conversion bureau conversion
bureau is an AU in which basically equestria has appeared in the real world as like a magical
bubble that is expanding and humans and it is going to take over the entire world.
Humans cannot enter the bubble into equestria.
So in order for them not to be, you know, killed, destroyed by this, they have to become
converted into ponies.
So they, yeah, they have to undergo punification in order to, you know, to enter into this,
this.
Yeah.
So I read the first, I read the first story she ever posted on film fiction.
It was called the big, the big respawn and it's okay.
It's kind of short, actually.
It's, it's, it's fine.
Sounds like another lecture.
I had that idea.
I was like, what if I just did a whole thing about my little pony fan fiction?
Film fiction.net.
I think I could do one specifically on the conversion bureau.
I mean, there's so much, you know, I've watched, I've watched all of your lectures like six
times minimum.
Yeah, I've rewatched, I've rewatched them a bunch, especially the, especially the first
one.
But the second one.
I think my favorite one must be, yeah, Tails gets trolled.
Really?
Yes.
Most.
That one has a lot of like, whoa, from the audience, although the first one has that
as well.
Yeah.
I'm noticing.
I haven't watched the first one in a while, actually.
I'm noticing just now the Kokura Wish Lecture just passed a hundred thousand views.
It's pretty.
Wow.
It's pretty cool.
Oh, wait, I completely forgot about that one.
Yeah, that one's really good too.
Kokura, yeah.
We're just talking about it.
How did I forget you did a lecture on it?
It's weird.
Yeah, the Tails gets trolled when it's like, did you, do you know Cybershell?
No.
Do you know who that is?
Okay, he's a YouTuber, he's a Sonic YouTuber who was gone for a couple years and he just
made a big comeback on YouTube, he just posted a whole bunch of videos, and in one of them
he talks about Tails gets trolled, and in that video he mentions my lecture, but he
says, even this is a good video and it's a good lecture, but if you're going to read
Tails gets trolled, don't watch it, because it basically is just recounting the story.
And it's true.
The pleasure of the Tails gets trolled lecture is just that listening to it, you hear about
the story of Tails gets trolled, which is from cool and funny and amazing in its own
place.
It's the revelation of such a story that when you tell somebody in a sentence, that's the
dumbest thing I've ever heard.
But then when you go into more detail, you're like, oh my god, this is incredible.
I really liked your lecture because it feels like I get put into the mind of a person discovering,
more like the mind of a community discovering this thing that happened way back that I would
not be able to go into with a fresh mind anymore.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
It's, I wish, I wish I could read Tails gets trolled for the first time again.
I wish I could read, I guess I feel that way about a lot of things.
You know, actually, he did just start making pages again.
There is like, yeah, we talked about this with Cybershell, but the series ended on a
cliffhanger and then he tried, he decided he was going to go back and remake the entire
series and everyone was like, no, please, please don't do that, please just continue.
And then I guess he was gone for a while, but he has, yeah, laser bought the author.
He got a bunch of like artists, a bunch of like volunteer artists, like agreed to like
draw the rest of that chapter for him.
So the cliffhanger has been resolved.
And now I think he is like supposedly back to posting what I think is, no, it's not like
everyone, it seems like the story was almost over, but according to Cybershell and according
to, I know the guy who runs the website, the talesgetstroll.org website and runs the
Twitter account and does like all the promotion for it now.
He says that apparently laser bought says the story is only like half done or something.
So he did a one piece of web comics over here.
It's going to go on, it's going to last, it's going to outlive all of us fucking, yeah.
So you said he wanted to redo the entire story.
Yes.
I didn't know this, but apparently he started the story, it was called talesgetstroll polished.
And it was just like the story again, but with like more stuff, like more like just
like a longer way of telling it and like it was supposed to be have like a better art
style, but laser bought's not that good at art.
So it just kind of like and looked muddy, he tried to shade it, he tried to shade it,
but it just kind of ended up looking like sort of muddy, it wasn't, it wasn't helping.
I'm glad he didn't redo it.
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, it's just kind of entertaining.
It's kind of funny actually because generally webcomic artists.
It gets I'm sure you know about this too, Ben.
It gets very tempting to like redo the first few chapters.
You know, I have never really had that problem.
But I know, I know it's common so good.
It's so perfect every time.
No, it's not.
It's not that it's not that.
I think I just, I think I had seen other artists try that kind of thing and I knew, I always
knew that that's an artist trap that you can fall into.
And I feel like when I look back at my old stuff it's like, I can't remake it, it would
just be a new thing if I tried, I don't know, I never have that urge, I mean I do look back
at my old stuff and I cringe and I think, wow this sucks, but I don't think like, oh
I should do it again and make it good this time, it was like, no, I can't, it's too late,
it sucks forever.
Something I did, which is on one of my comics that I wrote, it's probably the comic I have
with the most subscribers, it's called Winter Moon, it's got 2.5 million subs, which is a
lot for a comic.
So with that one, I actually really didn't like the first 100 episodes because they
were all, the artist was not very familiar with typesetting and also it was before I
had like fully an idea of what was going to happen, I was just like making things up
as I was going along, so lines of dialogue in that story will appear that reference
potential future villains that never ever appear.
So there's like one, one episode that I always think back to when I think about this, which
is like, the main character is like sitting and chilling and then these two guys just
pop out of nowhere to attack him and they have this like long bubble of dialogue that's
like way too long and they just go, because I only had four parents to work with, but
I had to like get some sort of foreshadowing in because I thought I was going to do this
like one story arc about how it takes place in an MMO and the idea is that the main characters
hated by all the big guild masters because of something he did, which never ended up
happening.
And so the dialogue of these two guys was just like, they just jump out of nowhere and
they go like, haha, we're going to kill you because the main guild masters union all hate
you and they're going to pay us to do it and this never gets brought up again and like
three seasons later, we never hear about this.
So I just hated that episode so very badly and all of the early episodes, they have this
problem with the typesetting and like the way you typeset things is really important.
I only learned this later and all of the dialogue is like very weirdly phrased.
So what I did instead of us like going back and redrawing all of it, I just hired two
professional typesetters to like just re-typeset the first 150 episodes and I feel way better
about it now.
That's like, yeah, it's the same, but just like with the jank sort of smooth, I guess.
Yeah, and the rewritten dialogue and stuff.
Yeah.
I mean, I think that like, I think probably there's a lot of like long form works of art
that probably start on like a totally, they say, you know, they have all these loose threads
at the beginning and then it kind of has to like find its footing and like figure out
what it actually wants to be as it goes along.
I mean, the thing that jumps to mind is like Seribus, Tom, you know what I'm talking about.
Yeah.
Seribus, like, you know, it starts out as like a fantasy.
It's like a parody of like Conan the Barbarian and then at some point along the way he starts
going to these alternate realities and it's like.
It becomes a very different thing.
It's like Dave Sim was just like, eh, I kind of don't want to do a fantasy parody anymore.
I kind of just want to talk about like what I think about politics.
Real shit.
Yeah, what I think about how like, you know, how like women suck and stuff.
The first like arc of the story after this parodies is like high society.
It's all about classism.
And then the second arc is church and state, which is all about commenting on theocracy.
It's like, this started as a Conan parody.
What is happening?
This is all like through the character of like an anthropomorphic art bark and it's very,
it's like tonal whiplash, but like that's when the comic really gets interesting.
Oh, you know, I was, I was going to say Seribus lecture, but I've seen, I have watched at least
one YouTube video that basically just summarizes the story of Seribus.
So it wouldn't be beaten to the punch, I guess.
Ben, if I ever become schizophrenic, please promise me one thing.
Yes.
Anything.
Make a lecture about me.
Oh, like if you just go off the rails and start like putting out like really wacky shit.
If I, if I let go of the rails, become insane, start doing all of this weird stuff.
Everyone starts hating me.
Well, now make a lecture and make me seem so very pleased.
This Mary guy, like he's such a fucking train wreck.
Like, oh, I hate this guy so much, but why, but why is he such a fucking idiot?
And I'll say, aha.
And then you do it.
I know.
Now that you've said, now that you've said that though, how are we ever going to know
if it's a legit breakdown or if you're just trying to bait Ben into making a lecture about
me?
You'll never know.
I guess you'll never know.
You can always go back to this and play it and add to the mystery of that.
Is he just pretending?
Did you, did you see, did you, you seen Tom's Animorph lecture?
Not yet.
No, that's, I actually, I didn't know you guys had new lectures.
Yeah.
They came out.
They could be getting an April.
Yeah.
We recorded all of them in like March and yeah, that one came out in like April.
That one's pretty good.
I would say Animorph's one is pretty highly regarded, which I'm surprised that.
I see it's, it's a 200.
It's a good, it's a good big talk about and a very strange thing.
I think you would like it.
Yeah.
Mary.
Um, it's, um, it's been, uh, I think I was looking at the analytics and I think it's
been the biggest, uh, I think it's been the biggest, uh, ad rev earner on the channel
for, uh, for a while, which, uh, did pretty well.
That reminds me of, this is a funny, funny anecdote from this week, um, some, some one
on Twitter who I don't know made a joke about like podcasts with too many people on them
and, uh, and, uh, Bev, who I know, an RFCK person and who was on the, the 40 person,
you know, all guest podcasts, tweeted a reply like I was on a podcast with 40 people Lamau.
And I guess maybe this person retweeted it and it got like, uh, I don't know, it got
a few thousand like views from this.
And I was, yeah, it made, it made about like, it made like $10 in ad rev.
Sick.
Yeah.
It was like, fuck yeah.
Cool.
What's the animal flexor up to?
It made like a couple hundred dollars last time I checked, right?
Uh, you know, I mean, I can, I'm not logged in, but let me, let me log in and we can,
uh, uh, I don't know if I care that much to get to log in and it's unbelievable.
Logging is just such a hassle.
Wait, what?
It totally is.
What are we talking about?
Uh, stuff.
Okay.
Comics.
Nice.
Uh, YouTube.
Like with, with the thing with, with, with, uh, cause I've been making comics for a little
while now and I am.
Oh, you do?
I do.
Uh.
Give makes.
Uh, yeah.
Give makes comics.
That's true.
Let me get an image.
Sad but true.
The most recent one shot that I submitted to the Tezuka award, um, contest thing.
Oh yeah.
When do you find out?
Do you read that?
When do you find out about that?
I, I just checked today.
It still isn't closed yet.
They're still, no, it's, it's closed, but they're judging it and I've been judging it
for a while.
Um, let me get a good page for all the pages.
Um, but yeah, I've been doing comics for a little while and I'm like in my head, there's
like so many over, like over the top ridiculous big stories that I could tell with all these
characters that I have.
And I'm like, I got to get started somewhere.
I'll make a short, small story and then, uh, eventually I'll, I'll foreshadow everything.
Everything that I say will become something later.
It'll all be so fucking based and so cool and people will go back and be like, oh my
God, it's like Oda is just, it's just genius.
Um, but I don't, I feel like it's not going to happen like that.
I think it's just going to be a little fun thing and then I'll actually start being good
later.
I can't find a good image.
Every attempt at like making a comic that I've tried to do has always collapsed under
the world building weight because I'm so obsessed with like crazy high concept fantasy stories,
which is why with the character I'm doing now as Umi, it's just like, there's no story.
The story is she does something cool and, uh, it's takes a lot of pressure off and kind
of allows me to be more freeform with the stuff I end up making and, uh, I like it.
It works for me.
I'm not a craze.
I'm not George R. R. Martin.
I'm, uh, Michael Bay, I guess, and I just have to own that at some point.
You just have to accept Michael Bay, you just have to let go and embrace what you've become
based Adam Jensen.
These are some things, the Clarissa gun smoke and the bandit king as I submitted it to the
Tezuka thing.
Are you putting it in discord?
Yeah, I put it in the general chat.
Right.
Oh, that's like a shit.
You know, I have that panel is so good.
I haven't actually gotten around to reading it yet.
It's it's it's not fully out yet.
I still need to do the second half and then I'm going to put it on my site.
Right.
That that's why that's why I was waiting for him.
Yeah.
I'm so I'm so I'm so you know what this reminds me of?
What?
It reminds me of you guys have seen Giorgio's bizarre adventure.
I've heard of such a.
Yeah.
A bit.
So there's these characters in Giorgio's bizarre adventure.
They have a they have a stand that can allow them to see the future, but it's drawn in a
bizarrely illustrated manga and they're called Oingo Boingo.
One of them is called Oingo.
The other is called Boingo and and and this art style kind of reminds me of them.
Boingo Boingo.
I'm not familiar.
Oh, wait, I wait.
Oh, well, I can't.
I can't post anything.
Oh, no, I just realized I'm going to have to.
I'm going to have to I'm going to have to fuck with the V with the VTuber recording
in order to post the voicemail links later, but that's OK.
That's fine.
It'll it'll it'll be fine.
Oingo Boingo looks yikes.
Yeah, you should you should you should Google it.
Yeah, it's it's odd.
It looks a little bit like more grats.
Oh, God. Yeah.
Is that little like sun thing floating under the brother's adventure?
Is that like is that the sweet bro and hella Jeff?
The turn. Wait, what?
It's sweet bro.
Well, you see when I when I Google Oingo Boingo, I see the purple book cover.
And there's like a little like
flower sun thing.
I don't know, it's got like a sweet bro and hella Jeff mouth.
I've got the Oingo Boingo band that is based off.
No, wrong.
False. OK.
Do you guys want to know?
Do you do you want to know?
Should I make it public information?
How much money?
How much ad revenue all of our all of our top videos have made?
I'm looking. Yeah, why not?
It makes us sound like we're established and cool.
I'm I'm looking at the data right now.
This is this is interesting.
I'm some of these surprised me a little bit.
Number one, Animorphs 101
has made in its lifetime eight hundred and seventy dollars.
Damn.
Hottest goss in the universe has made eight hundred and twenty four dollars.
Guilty Gear 101.
Seven hundred and sixty two dollars.
I'm bringing in all the big bucks, baby.
Deagle Nation, five hundred and nine dollars.
Voice Bale Fund, four hundred and eleven dollars.
But that doesn't count.
That's not ad revenue.
That was donations.
And then OK, then the next one was Radcon for Paradise Opening Ceremony.
That was donations again.
After that, it's Things We Can't Get Into, which has made two hundred and forty seven dollars.
And then Sonichu 360 classroom has made two hundred and forty six.
And then it's a whole bunch of bullshit after that.
That's those are the interesting ones.
So now join them.
So now you know, what's that?
Can I join? Can you join?
What? Oh, you want to flex on us with your crazy numbers?
Oh, yeah, please. Yeah. Yeah.
I love data. The funny thing is I actually think you guys have made
like your individual videos have made more than mine.
Wait, really? How's that?
How does it even work? I would I would believe it because my videos are less.
Most of my videos are less than ten minutes.
That's true. Multiple ad breaks.
You you think? Yeah.
You upload a lot of the highest.
They're like, well, then would you call them motion comics?
Yeah, motion comics.
I I had a theory a while ago that you could basically get.
Seventy percent of the way to the feel of getting an anime.
If you look like without any animation,
if you just get Japanese voice actors and custom music, I think you are a hundred
percent correct in that in that apparently it works.
Estimated. Yeah.
Um, I think people I think people
people overvalue polish and like in the same way.
This was laser bots. Great failing.
This is why he wanted to make tails get strolled polished because he was like,
oh, I got to make it perfect.
I got to make it high quality.
I got to have like high fidelity renderings.
I have to render every individual bit of stubble on the Space Marine's cheek.
You know, in my triple a video game and it's all it's all bullshit.
No, I'm even now that I'm looking at my my Clarissa drawings here.
I'm like, God, this was so bad.
It needs to be redone, but of course it doesn't.
It's fine. It'll do. It's cool.
I I look at I look at like my worst.
I look at my worst panels in like
slime and punishment, which like some of them are just straight up bad
because like I would crank them out in like five minutes sometimes.
And I look at the really bad ones and I'm just like, well, that's funny.
I like it.
I don't know. I don't know.
Well, when you when you rush something or like you just do it real quick
and it comes out sloppy, that's understandable and thus OK.
And you can be like, how low when you try really hard.
And then it turns out that you're, you know, your best is lame.
And it's like, oh, it feels it hurts a little more.
I guess.
Yeah, I guess so.
I guess it's easy to look at that because I know, like, yeah,
I slapped this out in like five minutes. Don't worry about it.
Hmm. Hmm.
I think my biggest earning video was a Minecraft anime one.
Was it the the the Creeper girl?
Yeah. Yeah.
And I looked at your channel the other day and just to see, like,
you know, what you had on there.
And I think that one was like it's got like it's got millions of views, right?
Must. Yeah. Yeah.
I think the biggest one we've got is two point two million views.
Yeah.
But even that one, they don't really make that much money.
I think, like, yeah, it's about watch time.
Yeah. Watch time and average.
Most of my videos don't really go above a few hundred dollars.
Yeah. Wow. Yeah.
Do you?
Well, that really is terrible.
Like, I've heard the way that the YouTube
changed to watch time, destroyed animation on YouTube forever.
And it never really recovered.
And the idea that you can do one thing that kind of saves us
is that we don't do animation. Yeah.
It's like multiple millions of views
and you can't get more than the sort of stuff we make.
The lectures are obviously like good quality content,
but their length like both like we've only got a few.
Well, actually, how many how many views is the top viewed thing on our
Scott? The top viewed.
Yeah. What's the view?
Most of our most viewed video is.
It's the guilty gear lecture with almost just shy of 300 K.
Really? Yeah.
And then the second one is the animorphs with two point 15 K.
Then I thought it would be the.
The son of two lecture or something.
That's not that's not that's not my channel.
That's on a different channel.
So that's actually.
And I mean, Nate's lectures, Nate's one piece lecture,
I think has half a million and the the Kingdom Hearts lecture.
I'm not sure if that's hit a million, but it's got a lot.
I really like the Deagle Nation one.
I, you know, I had I remember being there in hearing it live.
And it was a ton of fun.
I don't know if I've gone back and rewatched it.
But maybe I should.
I've rewatched a bunch of the other ones.
One time in Japan, I decided to.
So this is this is a PCP lecture story from me about one of the one
of one of the ways I used one of your lectures to get through some work.
OK. So in Japan, I don't know if you guys know this,
but they have a very strict recycling thing.
You have to get like these colored bags and put everything in the exact right
thing. And if you don't do it right, you get this like pink slip of shame
that they put on your thing and say that they're going to refuse taking your trash.
So one time I had to reorganize all of my trash like five days after I put it there.
Yeah.
And I had to do it all on my tiny balcony.
So I put on the Deagle Nation lecture and I did it then.
Well, you're rifling through trash.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's pretty comfy.
Good. That's that's good.
That's what it's for. You. Yeah.
Do you still live in Japan?
No, I I I usually do.
But the problem is the coronavirus pandemic hit.
And then I got afraid because I was it was back in back in like February
when it really got crazy. Yeah.
I I.
I I got I got scared because Japan's close to China.
And back then we didn't really know much about what the coronavirus like truly was.
All we did was like we heard like news from Wuhan about how they were
were like forcefully closing apartments down and stuff.
And and we had no clue if they were even reporting the right numbers and stuff.
So I got scared.
So I went back to Denmark.
Yeah.
And like stayed with my mom for a bit.
And unfortunately,
the borders closed like a week or two after.
And then I was stuck and I've been stuck here since.
And the thing is, it's not even much better here.
I was I don't even have much better numbers in Japan.
Yeah, I was going to say like, I don't know exactly how the numbers are.
I know like Vietnam and like South Korea, I think, are doing really well
with coronavirus America not doing so great.
Europe overall doing pretty bad right now.
I don't know how I don't have Denmark and Japan are doing in the grand scheme of things.
I would. Well, Japan Japan has pretty good set up for the entire thing.
Because they have they are all used to using masks already and used to like washing
their hands and not touching too many things in public.
Yeah. Yeah.
So they were good from the outset.
This is the first time I've ever seen people using masks in Denmark.
Oh, yeah. Same.
Same over here in Massachusetts.
It's pretty cool, honestly.
It's pretty pumped. I was so upset.
I was meant to go to America this year and do conventions.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, I'm I'm sure all the convention circuits are closed this year, right?
Yeah, every every convention.
I mean, like me and me and like Saber and Paylor.
And then we all used to go to conventions like MomoCon and stuff.
And every year since they started going to MomoCon, I've missed it for some reason.
And this year I finally could.
And of course, MomoCon is canceled along with every other convention.
I was going to be I was going to be like a VIP guest at so many different
conventions this year, and all of them got canceled.
Yeah. The one year I was some of them canceled next year as well.
Already, it's fucking crazy.
It was my first year going to conventions.
It's it always sucks like hearing that.
Oh, I was I was waiting.
And this was the year I was going to do a whole bunch of stuff.
It's the new decade.
No. No, I I kept I kept, you know, yeah, I kept saying like,
I'm going to I'm going to start tabling at conventions.
I meant to do it last year at Mice, the.
Oh, God, some Massachusetts indie comic expo.
I meant to do it last year, but I like was too late to sign up and I missed it.
So this year I went to it and I didn't table again.
I was like, no, fuck it.
Next year, I'm going to do it for real.
It's going to it's going to happen.
And then, yeah, no, not anymore.
There's no mice anymore.
Yeah, so same.
Yes, another like was my school because I wanted to go, but I never did
because I suck.
Honestly, no, I don't like it.
Damn, I don't I don't I don't like it as an attendee, but I wanted to table at it.
I think that would I would have felt differently about it.
Interesting. Yeah.
Because there's there's nothing there, except like you walk through a series
of hallways and rooms where people have tables and are selling stuff.
And I don't want and I don't want to buy shit.
It sounds like Mocha, which I went to once during college, which was pretty cool
because I met a bunch of people from a podcast I was listening to.
But yeah, it was just indie comics.
It's like, that's all it was, just a big room for the dude selling indie books.
You've just described why I decided to start doing comics.
What do you mean?
I went to the convention in Denmark and I had nothing to do.
And all of it was just walking through hallways.
All the things people did was either cosplay or selling things.
Yeah. I.
So that's when I decided back in 2012 that I wanted to write comics.
I when I yeah, at my side, I was like, I would be.
Like it's it sounds cool.
Like, oh, it's a gathering of all these.
Like it's like a lot of them are completely unknown.
A lot of them are have no like name, recognition.
There's some guy and or whatever.
And it would be cool to go and like meet those people.
But at mice, I didn't meet those people.
Like there's just like you go in front of their table
and you look at their shit and either you buy it or you don't.
And you just make, I don't know.
You might make a little small to I'm not interested in the in the buying shit.
I would like to meet other comics people, but it just I went to mice twice
and neither time, neither time did it scratch that edge for me.
Then here's a question because here's something I've been thinking about a lot,
like going to conventions and like why I never went to conventions until like 2013.
Do you think that being where we were in the pony thing
and going to pony conventions, like changed our perspective
on what a convention should be?
Because like every time I've gone to a con before
and after like being prominent in that community,
it feels like a very empty consumerist action.
Whereas when it was like the pony thing and I was like a known entity
in that small bubble, like it was a much more dynamic experience.
And I feel like that was what I really enjoyed about going to cons
and not just going and like talking to people and buying things.
I am going to say kind of.
But no, I think that I think I do think that, yeah, being being,
you know, even a little bit horse famous at a at a pony convention.
Yeah, like obviously that lent a certain energy to it.
And, you know, sort of propelled the experience, I guess, because like,
you know, you were always like we were like we were we were always
like making appearances and stuff like people were like people would see us
and they and it would like cause a minor, you know, stare or whatever.
It would be a little bit of an event wherever we went.
It was very exciting. It sounds nice.
It was it was pretty cool. It was pretty bad.
But like not to say I guess what I'm trying to say is that.
But my but my but I don't think that's entirely.
I think that Brony Khan specifically is like a specifically
like high energy event.
I guess I guess what I'm trying to say is I think it's a little calm.
A little bit like when you're saying like I want to go to convention
to meet people like because of like the the certain degree of clout
and that people knew who you were to a degree, it made approaching
and talking and meeting and interacting with people much easier.
Because like you again, you had like a reputation that preceded you.
Whereas like if I went to mice, I would feel like a fucking moron trying
to just go up and talk to somebody because like it's a much it's a cold
experience versus a warm interaction.
Yeah, definitely. I've tried both.
I went to I actually went to a convention like last month
in Germany. They did one convention, one test to see if it could be possible
during Corona virus. Oh my God.
I did test negative afterwards.
So that was pretty good.
It was pretty good. Congratulations.
The convention was a success.
It was very good.
I was I sold out of all my comics, which is amazing.
So many people compared to Copenhagen comics, where no one knew who I was.
You sell you sell like physical comics, too?
Yeah, only at conventions.
Oh, sure. Yeah.
So I met so I went to a convention
and they called Copenhagen comics another time that was like two years ago.
And I thought that I would it was probably one of the first time I really did
a convention. But the thing is, no one knew who I was because it was like a
traditional comic convention.
And they put me over in the corner with the like the youth corner.
Oh, this is the webcomic guy.
Yeah, just just put him over in the corner with all the kids, right?
And and front stage, I was probably
a follower wise.
I was probably the biggest one there if you're thinking like social media following.
But the front and center, they had one of the artists of Garfield.
And I was just put off all the way in the corner.
Oh, you can't you can't compete with that Garfield clout.
There's no touch in there.
And they also did the same thing to to another artist.
He's called Toshio Maida, and he's the guy who did La Blue Girl,
which is like a really old hentai.
Yeah, yeah.
He's the guy who like he's the guy who like popularized the whole tentacle thing
in Hentai. Yeah, well, that's doing work over there.
Yeah, well, he was really cool.
He told me about how I said hi to him.
And the first thing he told me because we had like one mutual friend,
which is Jacob, the CEO of Faku.
And the first thing he told me is that that guy's girlfriend is hot.
So that was pretty funny.
Just this old Japanese guy.
He's really cool. Yeah.
I yeah, I think that Tom, where you were saying, OK, about about like.
I don't expect to go to something and like have clout.
Like, obviously, yeah, if you go and you've got clout, that's good.
And people will respond in a way that's good.
And yeah, like, obviously, that's ideal.
I guess. But like, I think that's a little bit of the difference.
I think would be between like tabling at one of these and as an attendee.
Because as an attendee, you're just there.
You're you're a sheep, you know, you're there to consume.
If you're a tabler, I feel like if you're a tabling,
you would at least have. Oh, my God, someone.
Someone just someone just subscribed to the YouTube channel.
And it like made the like funny gift happen over Mary's face.
So that's that. Don't don't worry about it.
Don't worry about it, viewers.
It's it's good.
I'm glad it didn't make the sound.
But yeah, like if you're tabling, I feel like that's
that would be how you would like get to like
converse with your fellow creatives or whatever.
That's like gets you on the inside.
You're there with a purpose.
You show up early. You're setting up.
You're all like, you know, I don't know, making small talk with the people
tabling around you or whatever.
Maybe there's like a lounge or something. I don't fucking know.
I mean, I've I've gone to like one small convention
before I had any clout in the pony thing.
And I was trying to table there and I was trying to sell prints and stuff.
And it was miserable because nobody knew who I was.
Nobody wanted to talk to me.
I literally just sat there for two days, but just staring at a wall.
But surely surely you weren't the only person tabling who nobody knew, right?
Yeah, nobody. I don't think anybody there was like particularly like well known.
But like nobody wanted to talk to each other either.
It was just like you were just sitting there like waiting for death and it sucked.
Well, how does it? Yeah, I know that feel.
OK, it's all thanks for thanks for disillusioning me.
I just want to say my dream mice could very well end up that way as well.
Everyone just like kind of awkwardly hoping that someone
because like it's an awkward position where you have no clout
and like the little bubble you're in.
So you're just you're just there hoping like someone will come over
and they'll look at your stuff and they'll look at you and you'll be like,
what's going to happen? And then they just walk away.
And you're just like, well, OK, that was awkward.
And that was just that 48 hours was like, OK, cool.
Oh, I tried that in January.
I was at a Finnish convention and Finnish people are very a social.
So if you if you make icons, sounds like my kind of way and walk away.
I feel like if it was like like
if it was me, you and Gib, I went to mice together and had a table
like we could like vibe off of each other while trying to do things.
That would be a totally different experience.
Oh, it's like me by myself sitting at mice.
I love that. A big old cut.
Let's do it, buddy.
But next time America reopens, let's do it.
All right, we'll see you in 2037 when the virus is finally contained.
I was going to fuck.
Oh, that makes me sad, because I kind of had a plan to do that last time.
I was when I when I failed to sign up to table at mice, me and me and Kazi.
We're going to we said we were going to like table together.
And then I fucking blew it.
It didn't happen.
And now it'll never happen.
Did Kazi table by herself?
No, she didn't. I'm going.
No, she didn't either.
Nobody did. Yes.
It all came tumbling down.
God, I've got to I've got to finish some of my comics.
I've got to I've got to finish the Lord of Ghosts
so I can print it out and do something.
I want I want to finish a comic just so I can print it.
I just want comics on the shelf.
Yeah, I like be erect for months if I can make that happen.
Yeah, you know, hey, I think we should all do a booth together.
Yeah, that would be pretty cool.
That would be so sick. Yeah, please, please.
But did I have I talked about what a fucking nightmare
it was trying to peddle my comics in like stores?
Yeah, I think you have talked about it, but it's been a while.
I remember I remember during years ago during RFCK.
No, I'm retrieval con.
We walked around one of the shops where you had put in
like you had given the owner of the store
the vapors chapter one or something
and Munchie and everyone like conspired to like ask the guy
like one at a time like, hey, have you seen the Vapors by Ben St.
to just try and give him the idea to intercept the idea
that Ben St. is a big deal and that you should buy more comics from him.
You get this one guy to be like, hmm, who is this Ben St.
fellow? Yeah, the I don't know.
The thing about, man, I would go from store to store.
I would I would like look up like comic stores.
They sell comic books in in Boston.
OK, and I would go into the city and I'm OK.
I'm going to hit this place, hit this place, at this place.
And each time they'd be like, hmm, I don't know who you are.
But if you want to give me like three copies,
I'll give you like three dollars a piece for them.
And I was like, yes, but I'm legit now.
I'm published. I'm in stores, baby.
It was a giant waste of time.
I will never do it again.
The only the only way it's the only way it's worth it is if you have
a distributor who will like, you know, yeah, lobby these people for you,
put you in a fucking catalog or something.
There's like the rewards.
They're just not they're not willing to like
stock your comic in bulk if they don't know who you are.
And why would they?
And it's just not worth it's not worth the fucking
bus ticket to go into town and like, yeah,
sell like twelve dollars worth of shit.
Spend it on lunch and then come home in the red.
So it was a bit of a bug.
You know, I tried to do that with the comic store in my city.
Yeah. How to go?
They didn't know who I was and they just basically told me like,
maybe if you send us something in an email,
I tried to explain to them that I have the many subs,
but they did not really care.
And do you know who I am?
I mean, these kind of guys who run like comic book shops and stuff,
like their their brain is just like diamond numbers and that's it.
They don't give a shit about like the Internet.
So I mean, they're not going to understand the language we're talking.
They're no like incident.
They're in they're in the physical.
They're in the physical media business.
I imagine I mean, like I imagine that they are
right because like their sales in store are not going to be dependent on like
how well known someone is elsewhere or on the Internet.
I mean, there's going to be some people who come in looking for a specific thing.
And those are going to be either like the classics or they're going to be like some
something from like a new like up and comer, right?
And there's probably only so many of those in like a year.
And then other than that, their sales are just going to be
people that come in, don't know what they want
and see something that looks appealing on the shelf, right?
And they're just going to make like a I guess I'll buy that
because why not?
So, you know, that's like a whole like mindset.
That's like that I don't understand.
Imagine selling things in a store.
I don't it's so removed.
It's so removed from from what it's kind of antiquated with the Internet.
But like, you know, we just it's the digital market is still there, I guess.
I mean, if people are still making their living, I guess it's not the fuck.
If people if it still works, then it's the conclusion.
Yeah, boomers bad.
Yeah. Well, no, no, it's all bad new good.
What? What?
That's like the opposite of the marching orders of this podcast.
I'm going to disagree.
I'm going to I disagree.
I I think I I even though I don't do it,
I think that the idea of like a physical store is nice.
And, you know, I don't know.
There's surely there's a surely there's room.
There's room in this world for brick and mortar retail.
Like it fulfills some some need like community that that that, you know,
you know, we're all just old right now.
I feel like anyone under the age of twenty four is probably listening to this,
like being what the fuck are you talking about?
Just Amazon it.
I mean, Amazon. No, no.
Give us give the zoomers more more credit.
You can't Amazon a sense of community, Tom.
You can't you can't or you can't call up Jeff Bezos and say,
I'd like ten slices of hot, cheesy belonging.
It just it just doesn't happen.
The text isn't there yet.
I don't think there's any of us.
They haven't built it.
They haven't built a drone for it yet.
We have a minute.
We have a vtuber in our very presence right now.
We are looking in the eye, the community online being built in real time in front of us.
It's only a matter of time before what you're talking about is a relic of the past.
No, no.
The future is not old man.
No, no, it's not.
No, we're thirty.
We're thirty one, Ben.
We're thirty one.
We don't matter.
I'm thirty two, fucker.
Oh, well, okay.
I'm just making my case for me, bro.
Have you guys heard of Project Melody?
What's that?
Yeah.
Yes, that sounds familiar.
Vtuber porn.
It's the first Vtuber camera.
Yeah.
And all the all the all the regular cam girls got mad because like
Project Melody immediately crushed their numbers and revenue.
It's amazing.
She debuted and on Chatterbait,
she hit number one immediately and everyone got really mad
because all the all the cam girls were going to get replaced by robots.
Basically, the automation is here, except it's it's with an animated character.
This is why we needed Yang.
And we spurned him.
You're beyond for cam girls.
This is why would you?
OK, I don't know.
Like you're making you're making this lady.
You're like, this is going to be my little my little puppet,
my little my little internet fuck puppet.
I'm going to whore her out.
I'm going to prostitute her on the internet.
And she I mean, that's what it is.
I mean, you're not wrong.
I don't I don't want to come on.
I don't want to come on.
That's not me. That's not me being anti sex worker or anything.
But like that is what that is.
What's going on? I'm just saying, why would you do this?
And why? Why would you?
I don't understand why her bust size is so modest is what I'm saying.
Like you could look like anything and you and you went and you went modest with it.
I think I think it's because it might actually be.
Why wouldn't you go hand?
To appeal to the most amount of people, a lot of people get really upset
when there's big badonka donkers,
when there's big badonkas.
Oh, oh, my God, her back.
Oh, no, that's that's not healthy, bro.
That's fucked up. This is torture.
That's all you know.
The girl I told you about, the female artist I work with,
we see me, she gets so many comments like that.
That's oh, my God, her back.
Like, like, like this is anatomically impossible or something.
Like, shut up.
An anime face is anatomically impossible.
Nobody complains about that.
Did you know? Yeah, the eyes wouldn't even.
The eyes are so big, there's no brain.
There's no space for the brain.
I think they should just why not just consider them.
Yeah, aliens with giant tits. Yeah.
But where's that image of like a photo of like a grainy picture of an alien
and then they overlay and anime girl is the exact same proportions.
Yeah, that's the thing I'm talking about.
Yeah, I have not.
Literally true.
I have not seen that, but I was I was on the cutting edge
of all that stuff when I made the the punk only fans,
the the cartoon character, stick figure, pumpkin girl.
And I made money off of it.
You still any any any.
That's criminal.
It's quite interesting.
Do you do you guys think that VTubing
like VTuber characters might replace real streamers?
Well, I think there's always going to be a place for a real face.
But for everybody, I think what it's it's doing is the people who otherwise
wouldn't want to be seen on camera are now able to easily have a character
that is like attractive looking in some fashion.
Like it's they can make it look exactly however you like.
So the amount of streamers doing that will just flood the market.
And the people with real faces will be overshadowed.
Just by quantity, I think.
I mean, I feel like even Pokemon did it.
Yeah, I mean, I think it will probably take up some of the current
of like the non VTube streamer market.
But, you know, it won't.
I mean, the the the the there's too many.
There's always going to be space for German 985 always.
Right.
Yeah, it's it'll split.
It'll split the market, but it won't, you know.
Yeah, I don't think it'll outright replace it, but it'll definitely become
a significant portion of I mean, it already is.
Yeah, I think it'll just become more and more mainstream.
Guys, I have an answer for you.
I think they're getting.
I think I think VTubers are going to replace everyone.
All humans.
You know why?
You know what?
I have proof.
All right.
What's the proof?
Ben's lecture.
What?
In the ending of Pastel Defender Heliotrope, the whole world is virtual and everyone's
using a virtual avatar.
They.
Oh God.
Yeah.
Well, that's pastel.
This is this is Mundus Mundus.
Okay.
We've got we've got we don't have to be condemned to the same to the same fate.
I for one, accept it.
I guess they are kind of using they're like, yeah, they're like raw data.
They're like like these like abstract like data structures just kind of floating in
some sort of like information information void.
I don't know.
It's it's yeah.
I guess I guess on the way towards that perfect like future of leaving our bodies.
VTubing.
It's just like Oscar brain.
You just know what that is.
Intermediate step.
A metro is like the the nesting dolls.
Yeah.
So there's this concept in sci-fi called a matrioshka brain.
The idea is we build a megastructure around a sun that powers computers that just run
our brains.
And then we all have fun and VR forever.
What happens when the sun explodes?
I guess we all explode.
I mean, that would happen whether you're virtual or not.
We're already kind of fucked when the sun explodes.
We just zooshes up to another star.
I mean, it's a few billion years or something.
Right.
Yeah.
Wait, I don't.
Okay.
I understand.
Imagine being in the digital realm for a billion years.
Based.
Was there like that thing where they're trying to like do time dilation.
So like time in a virtual space goes by slower than real life.
So you can do like years and like an hour or something in real in the real world.
That's what we need.
That's the close.
That's the hyperbolic time chamber.
Right.
But you would flex your digital muscles and therefore gain.
So cool.
I understand.
So like gain and tell.
Imagine going into the time chamber for 10 years doing nothing but drawing and then come
out in five minutes of pass and you go in a child at drawing and come out a fucking god.
They have that in Dragon Ball.
Yeah.
Hyperbolic time chamber.
But then you still spent five years like you're still five years older.
No.
Because like your brain is just processing time differently.
So like when you come back out into the physical world only a couple hours have passed like
your perception of time in the virtual space is different.
And that's that's there even a physical world at that point.
Are we always why would you why would you even bother with the physical world then.
Right.
I mean at that point you wouldn't have to like you could argue at that point to take
it like that would be if that would be assuming the physical reality is still prominent but
like the eventual end game to that be everybody exists in virtual world and your lifespan is
now like hundreds if not thousands of years which would be fucking sick.
You know the thing I always get scared about like just thinking about this this putting
a brain in the digital realm so it can do anything at once forever is like from the
perspective of someone on the outside you know like all right the person in queue to
be brain digitized is in front of me and then they go into the thing and then they
decide to do nothing because they have no you know they can do anything they want and
they decide to do nothing forever.
Well I mean people do nothing for their oh all of all of the all of the the ideas they
had all of the plans they had there's no real reason to do any of them anymore so they just
they just don't.
I mean people do nothing with their entire life as it stands now I feel like it would
still be a net positive like you'll still have people who aren't motivated but that
just gives them more time to possibly find some sort of motivation and if you're in
a virtual world you wouldn't have to worry about your body decaying and breaking down
on you which makes that endeavor more difficult as you gain more experience like wouldn't
it suck to be like 50 something finally like want to like oh man I really want to do like
a physical activity like that's what like my passion life always was I was just too afraid
to do it but now you're 50 something and you're just broken and you can't do it anymore like
that blows like being organic sucks kill physical bodies virtual reality.
Yeah that's that's why I that's why I would like prefer to like to go halfway and be like
cyborg so that you can augment your physical body I don't think rather than computing your
entire consciousness.
Oh I don't think we should ever digitize our consciousness I think the proper way to
do it would be like the brain and nervous system still exist we would just like have
that connect directly to a virtual reality and hopefully we'd have some sort of nanomachines
or artificial stem cells that could continually repair the like necessary organic components
that keep our bodies going while our minds exist entirely in a virtual space or entirely
within like a machine body because as soon as you digitize your brain it's an artificial
copy and you are technically dead like you are your brain and nervous system yeah I can
I can one up you you don't even need a virtual space you know what you need you just need
a you just need your brain to get taken out put into some sort of like containment unit
that'll keep the brain alive for as long as possible then you just get your brain to through
some sort of artificial means just pump dopamine you experience nothing but you experience
fulfillment forever I mean that's so fucking scary I've seen I've seen I've seen that that's
like the prototype for the matrix right that was what they said in that movie that they
first tried to make utopia but it didn't work because humans like necessarily need suffering
anything which I think is probably bullshit but like for the rules of that world that's
what their initial idea was it's not a utopia it's just a the brain is just it's dormant
it's just got it's just got its fulfillment glands activated or whatever it is it is as
equivalent to death in my eyes I've seen things like that yeah I'm like it really it really
forces you to grapple with what is the per you know what is life if you are perfectly
content and do nothing forever so in one of my comedy really be called life in one of
my comics which is like an anarcho-capitalistic utopia I wrote yeah so in that one everything's
run by this one guy called the director who's basically just Jeff Bezos except he actually
owns all business which comic is that Crawling Dreams I thought so okay yeah I was gonna say
it but I didn't want to embarrass myself his name is Jeff Barzo very thinly veiled Jeff
Bizarro he's just called the director because he's the director of all businesses so basically
and also all the police are just private security for this one company because the company owns
everything anyway so in this world basically the way the plot is going is that everyone is going
to be just working themselves to death so that at the moment they hit 60 they can become part of
this like big tower that just like feeds their brain dopamine keeps them artificially alive and
that's why everyone's working yeah gross that's retirement in this world that's retired that's
pretty funny actually yeah it's like why bother with like yeah why bother with your normal
mortal terrestrial retirement let's just skip to the good part just skip to the part yeah where you
go on a dope event then you need a terrorist organization with cloud strife to blow up the
brain tower hell yeah I don't know I guess I mean I'm obviously speaking supremely biased
because like I'm living in like a physical body and like having to deal with all the struggles of
modernity but it feels like to me that just like getting a fucking dopamine ivy and definitely
seems like you're almost not even alive at that point like when you lose your autonomy right like
the whole purpose of like being alive I feel isn't so much like pleasure but like accomplishing
something or like setting goals and trying to accomplish them I feel the same way even though
I logically know it makes no sense to feel that way because all the reason we're doing anything
is because of dopamine releases right yeah I guess on like an instinctual level that's true
I don't want to be brand the broken I want to be like that is just brand the broken yeah
like I feel nothing oh you're your shit fuck you brand stupid when when when we're all
dopamine soaked brains in a big tower then we'll say oh man uh new bad old good remember having
physical bodies guys remember back when we did things remember death death was so cool that was
so base like what a great motivation remember pain you know I don't remember pain I kind of feel
nostalgic about it I want to I want to cause pain let's let's go back yeah yeah super villains are
born everyone tries to kill each other everything just keeps going in cycles
idea for a comic it's just it's just the day-to-day lives of a bunch of brains floating in a
van that's all kind of be like hmm how will I stimulate my neurons today it's like uh uh rich
richard you stimulated my fucking my my my pain center ah he quit that he knocked it off like
ha ha I have I fucking jacked into the to the control center I can give you a little zap
and it's uh it's very funny it's very goofy you know there's a bunch of can they be a girl so I'll
have that done by tomorrow yeah no anime anime girl versions their eyes are too big there's no
brain it's true we did anime girl versions of emotions it's just inside out but they're all
girls this time no no thank you to fucking uh kitchen after this podcast apparently we're
gonna get pressured into it by our viewers I I don't know when I will have the time but I am
I mean I have the software I asked mage about it because mage made a made a well he's made two
actually I was gonna say like there's 3d versus 2d vtubers right like you can do a 3d model or you
can do like a live 2d rig I'm assuming Mary you're using the live 2d one right now yeah all right
I I've got a questions to ask um for the setup with the webcam and lighting how how important is
that to be like high quality video feed the guy at the store told me that 4k is best but I don't
really believe him anymore do you I mean do you have like I don't yeah do you worry about like
do you have to like keep your face well lit and stuff so that it like tracks or do you just
like not that big of a deal you want to try I'm gonna I can try turning off the light oh and then
we see you okay oh I mean yeah I'm sorry okay but like you don't have any like you don't have any
like track lighting or like spotlighting or whatever okay is that enough yeah because I I'm
think that my webcam I have is really a terrible old piece of shit and I'm not sure because I I got
this this one program which is not the program that people use when I was looking into it and it
didn't work at all um I will get live 2d at some point nice I'm gonna have to build all of the pieces
and look at tutorial videos so like I use I use face rig face rig yeah well face live 2d is the
one for like making the puppet and face rig is for like doing yeah tracking like something I haven't
yeah I don't know that much about it I just I may just told me a little bit about how it works so
there's all these like really creepy characters on face right what yeah oh god oh no what has happened
oh yes I think oh there's isn't there a wolf with a gamer headset do you have that one
whoa that one seems super good we eat things traveling I like I like the cheeseburger
oh no oh my god okay I don't remember I don't remember these that's scary all right well
terrifying we don't have to we don't have to do all that come back for all the cherub next time
I looked I looked at um yeah the 3d I guess the one that the 3d one is called vroid is for making
your 3d model yeah I looked at that and it's really neat how it's like a sort of user friendly art
program that is like specifically designed for like 3d sculpting like an anime character
oh I tried to make one I just didn't want an anime character is the annoying thing I wanted to make
like a like a one of my characters in my style yeah I would I would want a 2d one for sure
I feel like if you're trying to do a custom like art style the 2d one makes more sense
I I think it just looks like the program looks like a lot of fun to just like fuck around with
and like try to push the limits of and see like what happens if I make it like this what if I
like fuck around with it like this like how how much can I get away with in terms of like
what it will accept as like a face you know what I mean uh uh uh oh the way live 2d works
see like you you separate out each uh each part of the drawing right and that's how it
kind of maps everything so as long as you have like some sort of shape for the eye it will animate
it and treat it like an eye I would assume I don't think the aesthetic matters too much but I haven't
looked into it I'm just kind of making baseless assumptions I suppose yeah I don't know uh uh I
assume you tell it like okay I assume that like live uh uh or face rig probably has a bunch of like
preset with like nose like where to place like your eyebrows like your corners of your eyes you
know your nose your nostrils corners of your mouth chin lips whatever I think you like put
tracking points on there to define like where those are relative to a normal face yeah yeah and then
it's like maybe you have like the mouth layer and it like you know that one's controlled like on top
of it or something and uh you know the whatever yeah I don't fucking yeah you're uh Mary you're um
dog boy excuse me um is is that oh it's a social faux pas uh yeah is that like a
like a pre-built thing because it looks very slick very professional and and custom oh custom so
who drew it uh Japanese artist named Kirito cool Kirito how many layers does that need
because I noticed when you move your torso a bit there's like a like a fake 3d-ness
to to the the a lot of a lot of layers yeah yeah let me let me let me let me give you an expression
that shows a lot of layers oh my god I don't even I really I like I like how you you can I don't know
I I like when the hair moves I like how the hair kind of you I think you can tell the hair like
how to behave like how flowy to be and stuff like how to like follow the character or something
yeah there's a lot to it there's a lot to it that I really want to dig into just because I think it
looks interesting I have a I have a rigor for it who like makes edits to it and plays around with
like the the different moods you can get on this character so the most recent addition has been
um my ears yeah I I saw I saw and I was shocked I saw it wait who's who's the girl that you do
streams with Lumi Lumi yeah yeah I saw her uh uh I think she put a video on Twitter the other day
and I noticed her she has a hand yeah and I'm like how how how the fuck does she how the
fuck does it know where her hand is yeah the in that 3d we had to thing yeah there I think
there was a thing where you could like have a button to have a hand motion or maybe use your
hands wave them in front and like the 3d model would also wave its hand um in the same way we're
doing it is a the way we're doing it is a special glove oh like okay I was I thought maybe because
like it it would have to know it has to know like if you if you didn't have like a glove with sensors
or something it would have to like be able to know like when the hand comes on screen versus
when it goes off screen and then to like recalibrate like which finger is which finger and yeah so is
it kind of like a VR sort of glove yeah yeah okay a lot of the equipment is also used for VR
games and stuff yeah yeah yeah I had I had thought about it I had thought about like I wonder if they
can have hands I would like to make one with hands and I was like I haven't seen any with hands and
then I saw I saw Lumi moving her hand around I was like oh my god what technology has gone too far
uh you should see like some of the some of the vtubers actually they like they can do dances
and stuff with their characters like full body dancing yeah they have a full body VR suits
like in like in ready say ready player go just is that what project melody has I think so yeah she
must be fully functional if you know what I'm saying the funny thing when I when I like wave
my hand in front of my model it goes crazy look whoa whoa whoa it's like interrupting the tracking
of your face yeah so it doesn't know what to do yeah when I when I fucked around with face rig I
was using some of those those hideous 3d default models and I think it it was either the lighting
or just the crappiness of my webcam that it like it had a little bit of trouble like it had a little
bit of trouble like following me like where like wherever I moved sometimes it would kind of like
lose track of where my face was and just kind of jump back to like default position yeah and I was
like I assume I have to like really have a nice like clear like camera setup that's like very easy
for the computer to understand or I would need to maybe like go in and do some like custom fiddling
with the like the rigging to like I don't know so it like matches like the shape of my face better
or something like that I don't know uh yeah it's very it's very neat it's very cool uh I'm not afraid
of technology I welcome it uh uh damn
so uh how you guys you know if we are all yeah if we are if we all become anime girls and all
donate to each other it'll basically be like what yang not wanted yang the automation is to take our
job it's gonna take our streaming jobs next wait if we all donate to each other then wouldn't just
paypal get loads of money oh it will go up to Elon musk no no is he not the paypal man anymore
I don't know I don't think but he's the one he likes anime too so maybe he'll be he'll be willing
but this is long con he's the one who's secretly financing face rig so he'll be like the next
fucking tesla rocket a launch will have like an elon musk anime girl vtuber narrating it nice
ah elon musk would have a fucking you know he liked one of my comics ones
no shit which one the one where I turned him into an anime girl oh okay I don't know if I've seen
that one but someone someone must have brought it to his attention I almost considered because
there's like a tesla store nearby I almost considered going there asking them for a free tesla
because elon liked me on twitter elon liked my tweet I think I believe in your company policy
it says uh one elon like is worth one tesla three tesla yes yes i think that could work if you just
kept badgering them about it yeah just keep harassing them it's the twitter guy again it's
two likes now there's two likes that's fucking twitter guy how's everyone's uh how's it how's
everyone's week going how how's you how's your personal life oh it's great yeah it's a 10 out of
same same same it I'm living the peak quarantine life I want to throw peanuts at crows today nice
yeah save those I want those actually send them in the send them in the mail and I heard that
that crows can recognize your face if you feed them for long enough and then they'll bring you
trinkets yep no shit yeah crows are very smart they I think I remember a story of like a girl who
fed the crows a lot and the crows all knew her in the community like the crows talked to each
other about this is the girl she was she had a lot of cloud in the crow she did she literally had a
lot of crow clouds ironically yeah and they would protect her from bullies that's I don't think that
part happened no they're like now you when you say that I imagine that like some bullies are coming
and the crows like all like flock to her and like form like a big suit around no all the crows all
the crows like show up behind like behind her and like eye down this bully they're like do you want
to learn why we're called a murder of crows and then just beat the fuck out of them you know you
know in Naruto how how like gara had like the sand that would like always protect him from any
attack it's like that but like a flock of crows yeah she carries a stream of water bottle of
filled with crows on our back this gourd of crows she has like a giant a big like I don't know a big
like like bird feeder like a maybe a big like log with like seed like glued to it with peanut butter
or something it's just covered with crows the crows like seeds they must birds like seeds
yeah that's the one thing I know about birds they like seeds seems fair uh yeah my my weeks my
multiple days of of stuff have been mostly just fucking around playing video games and
thinking so hard thinking every day about um the bell jpeg book of my first comic it's all part of
the process that I that I made the first page in photoshop I was like ah I see I could I could
put the the text here and then I could put the page number up here and I could be exactly the same
as the the homestuck physical versions where it has the little author comments at the bottom
and I was like I'm gonna write author comments I tried to write one I'm like oh no I'm stupid
though I can't write this is this is not gonna work I think yeah I was thinking of doing I was
considering doing something similar with slime and punishment and I think that I could I think I would
find it pretty not a brag or anything but I could probably write them very well I feel like I know
exactly what I an egg yeah maybe um I boys I'm back at it I'm lifting again I'm fucking ripped
I'm jacked uh two weeks in and I'm stronger than anyone has ever been
Ben's getting ready for if Trump wins again he's gonna take it to the streets
he's gonna help jump over the buildings they they're not gonna they're not gonna fucking throw me
out of a helicopter all right we're not going down without a fight uh I've been drinking my almond milk
uh almond milk is based it's so based yeah I love almond milk I've I've discovered it in this past
year uh uh people people talking about oat milk being the new hotness oat milk has carbs
unacceptable on acceptable it's all about the all costco the big like I buy and buy the crates
I'll buy like 24 cartons of uh of Kirkland almond milk at a time holy shit you get it you gotta buy
in bulk all right you're on a totally different level than me then oh my god no I'm drinking
it I'm drinking like I need to start hitting up cost so Aldi is closed right now so this entire month
I've had like no access to Aldi and I'm like going broke from like buying regularly priced
groceries I need to go down to Costco I swear to god I swear to god my instacart subscription
has paid for itself because with instacart subscription I can send other people to go
and shop at Costco for me I do not have to buy a Costco membership to benefit from their incredibly
low low prices I want to go to Costco and use my ebt cards and then I pay like literally nothing
yeah well that's you know that's true but I'm not that worried about it I'm not that worried I
get you like I don't know the ebt point I can use them later I'll use them later it's pretty sounds
pretty bougie to me not having to worry about your fucking money oh worry I'm worried about the
they reduce my benefits like they cut me but it's okay I'm gonna I'm gonna make it I'm gonna make
it just fine um but yeah super powerful super strong uh sucks to be you guys uh well I get on
my level I've started trading as well is that true yeah do you lift
dude what but Mary what's one of us you oh uh no uh I lift myself
well oh okay what do you what do you do what do you what's your what's your uh routine like
so twice a week I walk 10 kilometers and then I go to my friend's house uh we who lives like
five kilometers away and then I walk the other five back um and then we do uh we do calisthenics
cardio kills your gains you'll never get huge like that I'll never you'll never you'll never
swell I drink warm and milk with protein uh powder yes hell yeah hell yeah I haven't got
into the protein it's pretty good supplement stuff at all I've just been eating meat or whatever
are you a little beta boy
oh my god a little beta girl actually she's a she's a little beta girl now
uh sad I've been I've been doing the squats imagine eating meat cringe
imagine not crafting your own keto gummies imagine having like normal food how sad
I've perfected a new recipe by the way hell yeah I I have utilized I have utilized the power
of pectin and mono calcium phosphate that's all I have to say about that the pectin the pectin
really really brings out the flavor really imparts a little bit more of that candy consistency
so it doesn't just taste like hard jello uh and it helps the flavors shine a lot more it's very
really on to something one of these days I have to partake in your science experiments they've
they've evolved the ones I'm making now are like nothing like the old ones I feel like
I'm gonna have there I'm gonna have like I'm gonna have to make like mark one mark two mark three
Mary oh my god he's he's huge he's so cute oh no what is happening ah scary oh Jesus Christ
it's too it's too big frankly it's just a little bit too big for my day that really is I take it
all back v-tubers were mistakes in advanced strength he's just fucking zooming he's zooming
all over the damn place is this what a zoomer is he's got no legs it's like oh my god he's got he's
got a torso I can't that's so weird that's wild I didn't know I you know what I I didn't know I was
curious how far down it extended but now I'm soul now I'm yeah now I'm glad that I know
neat yeah I've been doing I've been doing fucking anyway yeah I've been doing squats I've been doing
this and that moving my legs and they hurt now and that's good it's good it's good to feel pain
it's a good pain it's pretty good we've spoken like a flesh bag oh pain's good
my weak physical body I have to train with fucking resistance trading oh I have to break
it so I can build it back up instead of just like buying the better model of body oh how pathetic
we're all sad flesh bags the worst I don't know I don't know I something about the the the feeling
of like you know like I sat down the other day I was like wow my butt's bigger than it used to be
that I can feel it and that's good is that good it's it's is that what you want yeah okay that's
what I was so what you want it's it's always been like really bony and terrible and now it feels
like an actual thing are you are you eating big I don't think I'm really eating enough to make a
lot of progress I'm not doing it very efficiently well there's your fucking problem I have I have I
mean I have such a small brain I can't remember anything yeah so the only thing I'm you know that
is your problem it's all I'm doing is working out doing my routine every other day and I eat
whatever I eat when I'm hungry and it's it's it's making some progress and I that's fine by me
hell yeah I was just me being working out and being based is awesome it's not enough
it's never enough I mean it'll never be enough but like I don't know there's already too many
things in my life where I say oh it's never enough I don't need to add like fitness to that that's
doing something is better than nothing exactly I'll like this two weeks into two weeks into
getting back on the wagon and already already I can feel my whole worldview shifting just the other
day I thought like hey what if I like wore clothes that fit oh I saw that tweet yeah that was terrifying
I was like I was like should I like call Ben and see if he's okay this is like a tweet you would
put out you know that you know that meme where it's just like what would you tweet to let people
know that like you were in trouble like that's that's what I think you're like a nice outfit
what if I was dressed like in a fucking suit and tie or something and I was tempted to just be like
tweet out something like horseshoe theories real because like you've gone so far left you like
want to dress like a fucking like super like alt rider guy now but it's like that won't that won't
fit all right they're just expensive and those yeah all the all the all right they've reclaimed
suits they really have nobody can nobody can wear suits anymore they've they've got the market
cornered yeah we everyone else has to dye their pink and and wear like mesh vests and I don't know
rainbow uh I don't know tattoos whatever the fuck what about Sanji who from one piece he's a Nazi
give Sanji Sanji he is out of the germa clan
have you been keeping up with one piece who me well I guess you I do you read one piece Mary
I um I did until the fish people and then I kind of fell out of it I which which fish I have read
a little further than you but I'm like I'm like a while behind I'm like a few months behind
anything I almost caught up at radcon when you say everyone's underwater and there's this giant lady
oh okay yeah that's quite far in and this guy who doesn't wash his hand throws axes at her
doesn't wash his hand yeah he doesn't wash his hand um because he wears a gloves vandodecken
his power is to throw something and it will always meet its mark and he's touched shirahoshi
so he doesn't touch anything on that hand again so that he can throw things at it forever oh right
that's his secret plan you forgot about that you're such a one piece idiot Ben
shirahoshi is the best uh girl design she's the same as all of the others she's just bigger
she isn't wait wait wait no no no I'm not thinking who was her mom the queen otohime
otohime is my favorite that's what I meant yeah she was great she's sick she's sick as
is she big too no she's small I think the next you along is the big one she's she's
otohime is kind of big but not like big big she's like one piece small aka like eight feet tall
saw a tweet the other day uh that was like well it was a visual diagram but the long
and short of it was what if all the big people in one piece like uh uh um like uh donky hote and uh
who's the fucking nightmare guy the shadow guy shadow guy yeah on on thriller bark
oh gecko moria the shishibukai yeah like what if all the big people like donky hote and gecko moria
are actually just normal sized people and people like zoro and luffy are just tiny they're just like
three feet tall that's funny makes makes you think can't disprove it that's just well you can't
disprove it because he said how tall they are um maybe maybe the the planet is lying like like
like this is people like the gravity is different maybe the plant's quite small so like people grow
really big because the gravity doesn't squish them that much and the the yeah the luffy maybe the
maybe the planet in one piece is flat how what do you think about that why would they sail around the
grand line makes a lot of sense actually yeah you know i don't know it makes no sense there is there
is no red line it's just there's just the there's just the dirt wall there's where's the car there's
just the car you see the curve the whole time no oda has never drawn the curve oh water finds
it's impossible he refuses to draw the curve because he knows he knows one of my uh one of
my favorite things recently is watching like flatter of his own videos on youtube oh i i
it sounds like folding ideas really big it's a whole genre of like videos and it's got its own
like youtube creators and it's got its own keemstar figure it's really funny oh my god yeah okay that's
that's pretty funny the anti-flatter scene i didn't know about that so there's this one guy called
si man dan and um so some of the flat earth is called him satan man dan okay okay oh because he
is a heretic i guess yeah and one of them has this like obsession with walt disney
for the flatters or the anti-flatter the the flat earth is they have this obsession
with walt disney because they think he's like part of the worldwide conspiracy so they call him walt
hitler yeah okay donald duck uh it's all in that one cartoon
i um you know the last flat earth thing i watched was the uh uh the one the new the newest video
from uh in you and not any i always confuse them folding yeah i watched that one and he went further
than just like how it's for earth is round idiot it was like it was like the whole reason that people
fall into these types of ideas and the the sort of desire of of wanting to make sense of the world
and all of the dangers that come with that i wish the earth was flat yeah then i could throw
like a rock wouldn't it wouldn't make a difference i mean the and if if some of their theory is to
be believed the Antarctic would be like um would be all surrounding us like a giant ice wall to just
kept us out and maybe there would be maybe there would be more worlds with more what if what if
the real world is like minecraft and if you get past that point it starts like the the world's
generation starts fucking up yeah you go into the far lands of real life but nobody's ever
made it that far because it's too cold and they always turn around all i know the earth is flat
nobody's proven otherwise no one can convince me i don't know that's not true that's not true
because in that video i mentioned he literally proves that the earth is round so never mind
now the the earth is the game of thrones intro it's upside inside out earth
it's inside out it's like halo but a sphere it's sphero
it's like it's like a hey it's like a ring but if the ring was like yeah
toward yeah yeah rotated 360 degrees extended in a polar sort of fashion i would be interested to
see how that would look rendered like i've always loved the way halo looks when you see the the ring
in the distance going all the way up do you um do you guys have any more questions for
oh i have a question here's an interview type question um you you say you write comics uh
do how did you get your start we look in in in terms of like getting people to draw them for you
i did you just have the money to do it or i have a follow-up question i have a follow-up
question do you want me to answer first or yeah i wrote a i wrote a message that basically said
i want to do a comic i have this and this budget and then i copy pasted it to 600 people on dvn
die wow so i mean that's how you do it was your budget yeah um what what was your budget for the
first one like 200 dollars for like uh for like uh for like i don't know what the first one like
what a yeah what did 200 dollars pay for basically nothing but it got you started and and now look
at you i i was gonna say um um did you have like a did you have like a big break moment or something
when like you went from like just doing this as a hobby to like was there like a moment when
like you got like exposed and you were like uh hey i've sort of broken out into the into the
it um industry i say in quotes it came in three waves yeah uh the first wave was after i'd gotten
my job as a sales guy at a company uh i started having a lot more money to throw at comics so i
could hire a much better artist and i did a comic with him and that comic was drawn really well and
so i just marketed it like crazy on twitter and it gave me a lot of followers um the second wave
came when i got Ushimi the girl who draws big tits um and nice yeah that that came that that is
just that that's just why that i don't need to explain yeah and then the third wave was the
third wave was when i started um doing uh internet exploratory and just like the meme characters
yeah that was the first time i really did like a comic that was made just for twitter not like
with a longer plot like it turned it turned into a series later but that was the first time i did
like uh yeah when i i remember reading it and being surprised when it kind of like yeah it does
it does develop a plot eventually and i was like oh oh shit okay yeah uh hmm so for the uh for the
anniversary we got like a really good artist to come in and do like 180 panels worth of action
for for a thing so that was really tough yeah yeah um i didn't realize we've been going for
almost two hours now yeah time flies when you are talking about dopamine and flat earthers
yeah boy the topics that really matter yeah uh well um uh we could move on to voicemails if you
guys uh want to i might have to go unfortunately sure sure you've been uh yeah yeah i uh i think
my eyes swelling uh might have to go to the doctor ooh ah sorry about that oh that's my bad uh yeah
it's your fault ban it's your fault my bad uh hey introduce me to um uh sashimi chan or whatever
i will thank you uh you it's i'm i'm glad i'm glad we got the chance to have you on mary appreciate
you i appreciate you have to co-write a comic with me someday ben i think it would be fantastic i
think you're better than me i boy i don't know i have like i have no confidence in my ability to
appraise my own writing skills so i'm just gonna assume you're correct um yeah um yeah um all right
excellent i want to be in on this i just i'm i'm i want clout too can i have some
yes oh sure uh yeah i need um okay ellie is our cut this part out before you go mary let's let's
do a second sink up okay okay all right uh uh three two one sink three two one sink can we do a
third one because i didn't say sink would you guys just dip the ear thing oh yeah yeah right sure uh
three two one sink okay uh all right any any last words any last words i love gold
baby yeah fuck yeah give me the gold all right epic nice thank you very much
take it easy catch you catch you later see you later gamer boy bye bye everyone check check out
mary's stuff links in the description bye everyone bye thank you thank you very much for having me on
uh i love the pcp uh i hope you do more lectures uh please do the uliliya one soon uh yeah oh yeah
okay yeah face bye right take it easy
all right so voicemails right that's what we're doing now oh oh yeah we gotta go to the ellie is
our cut all this bullshit out make this less awkward nah just double the pauses in fact ellie
ellie is our use your editing skills to make this not awkward please that's what we pay you for
no no no don't put the whole podcast in the trash no that's not what we meant no it's too much that's
that's too you're making it too based now all right so um okay ellie is our sent in a voicemail
so let's start with his um let's do that he gets priority so ellie is our what what what's your
fucking problem three two one go hey it's me ellie is our your favorite ethnic pcb hater you might
know me for it's time to shit or other classics such as this is the stupid ilian corner anyways
i've released an album in fact you're listening to it right now oh ellie is our link in the show notes
all the songs are instrumentals and they're copyright free so you can use them in whatever
projects you like the only requirement is to keep great for the music i will now go back to my
eating layer and keep acting the pcb i haven't seen the sun in so long and i'm hungry ben only gives
me what he calls keto crumbs which is just a plate with nothing in ellie is our hey wake up ellie is
here they come okay i remember oh i remember cracking that whip good times good times i don't
remember saying wake up wake up ellie is you only dreamed you were editor for the pcb you've been
in pcb jail the whole time uh okay well uh check out ellie is our as a fucking album yeah link in
the description uh cool cool next up we've got uh maxed out three two one go so i was listening
to tom's patreon bonus podcast at patreon.com slash polystation two and here's some of how maybe he'd
want to make a fighting game one day and it got me thinking a lot of times this kind of thing will
come up and the chat or comments will be like yeah i'd love to see a fighting game where i'm playing
as my favorite pcb member and that'd be cool i guess but really i'd love to see a fighting game
with your ocs as the playable characters especially if they were in their original art styles i would
love to see a 3d a zoomy fighting a very simplistic 2d pump i want to see a black and white sophia
having a zoning battle against saraya that's what i would love to see out of a pcb fighting game
it'd be the most eclectic thing since angel i've actually thought about this and i would be all
in for it i don't have making of making like a smash clone with all of our characters but i
would just i don't dare i don't dare to imagine such a thing uh i do all the time it'll be so
based i would run around i mean that's not even the first project i've thought about i thought
about make doing like a deck building game based on uh all of our oc characters and like print out
like a deck of cards with them a deck building game there's a lot of like floating around in my
magic that sounds like sounds like some real nerd shit oh super nerd shit just make top trumps
i have like the the you know top trumps no uh it's this very simplistic card game where uh there
was all the rage back in the playground where it's just a list of things and there's a bunch of
stats and the person just puts down and says i'm using this stat um like if it's like about
cars it's like oh the acceleration number and then the person who goes next if they have a higher
acceleration number they win and they take the cards and the winner is the one who takes all the
cards it's a weird it's it's what the wait what the fuck so you just you is it it's hard to explain
and so so okay so so the card has it has a list of arbitrary numbers that are related to whatever
the theme of the deck is like that they made so many of these things um there was one about dinosaurs
one about cars harry potter fucking everything lord of the rings but but so the ultimate goal
is just to have the yeah you have to put down your card and say which thing you're you're most
confident in winning um it's like uh i put down this dinosaur and it's like i don't know height
or whatever do you put it do you put it down not knowing what your yeah yeah it's a gamble whether
you have the bigger card and sometimes you get a dinosaur that is really good at something and
really bad at something else and if the other so okay so the you win by having the biggest number
so i imagine that the goal then is to like save your big numbers for like when it really matters
like when no i think you just have to use whatever is the at the top of your deck because you split
the deck in half oh so it's like war yeah war what's war yeah war is basically you split a
deck of cards in half and then you just like flip cards at each other and like whoever's
higher wins i guess so but um unlike a deck of cars they have multiple numbers you can choose on
each card but wouldn't you always just choose the biggest one no because because because like um
let's say it changes for every uh deck every themed card deck but like um sometimes like a
thing that's really like if we're talking about cars something has really high top speed
will have a really low something else and um you might have a car that has a low top speed but
a really high of that something else i can't think of an example because i haven't looked at these
acceleration or something something like that um and so you could strategically well actually
it's not really strategy so much as luck and then strategy it sounds like oh okay okay so so when
you're flipping these card decks like you're both gonna have cards that are like themed about like
cars yeah they're all cars in the whole day i was imagining that like you might have one guy flips
like a you know Toyota Corolla with like acceleration 50 and like you know armor 10 or whatever and
then the other guy flips over like uh uh you know mothra you know maximum flight flight speed you
know 50 miles per hour yeah it doesn't special move uh sleep powder it doesn't work like that because
the there are different numbers of stats in in different things yeah like cars have a lot of
different numbers associated with them and some cars just really based i i learned about the
McLaren i learned about all these these car of manufacturers names through this this stupid game
interesting anyway that was a bigger side and meant nothing yeah i mean i was thinking something
more along the lines of star realms but that's an interesting concept as well but anyways we're
talking about a fighting game uh it would be cool it would be like the most titanic endeavor ever
undertaken by all of us to buy i think buddy i was talking about man i was talking about uh
a pcp not not pcp well yeah rom hacks pokemon rom hacks on the stream this week and about how like
it's the kind of thing that i think about like oh what if someone made like a pcp pokemon rom
hack or what if someone made like an rfck pokemon rom hack and it seems it seems just doable enough
but then i know that like if if i were to try to do it it would be like oh this is actually a
lot harder than i thought in all these different ways and it would probably end up taking like
weeks months definitely years even yeah yeah that's everything yeah and like it's like what a what a
shame if it were like to be half made and just like you really need a nightmare that that a
youngster energy where you can spend the entirety of your waking hours working on something and then
not having to think about like eating because your parents will make it for you i mean i mean when i
was in like college i like got rpg maker and i started working on i've probably talked about
this right i started working on the christian weston chandler's adult chronicles i was trying
to like make my own version of it and i put like a lot of time into that i made like sprites and
stuff i made started making maps it was not even close to like a finished product and yet it was
still like a pretty significant effort that i made towards it and like the shit takes a long time
it really really does oof i mean just to make that one room of venezuelan game took like the better
part of a year of just like working it just it takes so that was you building the game mechanics
at the same time right oh yeah there's a lot i mean there's a lot going on which is why it took so
long yeah but like you could if you have mechanics and like an entire game if you were to make another
room it wouldn't take as long for just that room no but like every time you enter you build like
because like i started building a level on top of that and it's like okay i want this level to like
because like the whole thing was supposed to take place in like a like an old factory or
something and like all right so there's gonna be a little thing so you have to dodge it like we'll
like crush you if you stand under them but like that has to be built out custom on top of like
everything else it's like okay so i know how to build a room but now i have to build like the
sequence of like uh like uh variables that cause these objects to go up and down in a certain pattern
and like i have to make sure the collision box follows that sprite that moves up and down and
how it controls everything so like it's just it's a lot video games are complicated as shit
video games are complicated and like a fighting game i've always like in the back of my mind
because i love fighting games Guilty Gear is my favorite thing in the entire fucking world
and i'm like i'd love to make a fighting game the problem with making a fighting game is that like
it's so simple on the surface because it's like well there's like two characters there's basically
no level design it's just making a pretty background but like the game balance is so
fucking hard because you have to make multiple characters you don't need to make game balance
and you have to make sure the balance is there and everything yeah you do if you want to make it
fun and like yeah yeah making a shitty fighting game is probably like i mean it's probably still
hard but it's probably like doable you could you could right you're just doing making a character
estate machine over and over and over and you just all you need to do is make punk op and i'll then
that'll be all i suppose that's true i suppose i could just do that to use our fire breath
um so what we're saying is uh yeah uh uh make it somebody else somebody else make it please i think
i think what we need to do is we need to get two hundred dollars we have to message six hundred
people on dvnart until somebody will make our game for us i think that's where all the games are
on dvnart yeah yeah exactly just go on itch.io and go to like right user page after user page like
hi i'm looking for someone to uh code me you go to fiverr.com yeah um i use fiverr to make a video
i have two i no i paid someone on fiverr to convert uh to convert a a png image that i had
into a a vector uh it was for the rc game the kickstarter thing how how are those pins going
by the way how's all that stuff have i not mentioned um i have uh the the lady has been like
sort of like hard to get a hold of lately but like i have all the pins except for one pin
and the coin and when i'm missing one of the pins i'm missing the coins but i have settled on the
final design and i just i literally i literally just have to give her the money and then it will
probably be another like whenever i she lets me do that it will probably be another like two weeks
or so until i have the product and then it will be done and i will have everything and i will start
chipping sick that has just kind of been going on in the background i'm so excited to have the
coins uh they i have the test coins here i i'm like made like a slight change to them but uh i'm
confident that they're going to look sick they're gonna look almost like these ones that i have
like a little different a little bit better um anyway anything else anything else about fighting
games or whatever the fuck what are we even talking about uh fighting games are sick i want to make a
shitty fighting game yeah i guess they're kind of sick i just started playing uh power rangers
battle for the grid actually good pretty cool worth twenty dollars what system is that on it's on
everything how i want to see it i want to see it is it new uh it's like a couple years old it was
like a budget game that came out it was like a small company made it so it's like kind of rough
around the edges but like the actual fighting system is really fun i mean i'm a little surprised
that like a power rangers game would come out in modern era yeah it's it's strange but it was
really fucking cool and i enjoyed it immensely weird yeah weird cool okay next one is from
uh konichi konichi wag dot flv uh okay three two one ago hello pcp thank you for listening to my
voicemail you're welcome this is the um end of an era guy um i was drunk last time i am drunk
this time uh and i just listened to you guys talk about my little voicemail thank you thank you for
spending so much time on it um a couple points um i don't really have any um i think y'all went over
it pretty well this is great um and all i do is listen to you guys talk all day it's either you
guys dick masterson or the radio so continue doing all your uh pcp um and yeah no i mean
like guys please just fucking please
it's it's something endearing about that guy
simp simp guys i gotta say that that voicemail has made me reconsider whether i want to be a part
of the show i kind of think that maybe it's time to wrap it up pack it in let me begin i'll take
your cut going forward no no no you have to quit too no no no no if i quit you all have to go down
with me it all burns i forgot it all i'll be the gift show i have to do exactly what you say it's
contractually obligated i think that's somewhere in the we think we had a meeting i think we voted
on that actually and it's in the it's in the right yeah we ratified it so i see it next up is yes
and three two one go
guys help me out here what am i missing
yes if you're missing something
that's not that's oh this is this must be this must be this must be like some other member of the
Kawasaki clan some like beast some like beast guy who's just like fucking sound like you're
like dogs or whatever fucking is ninja dogs sexy ass ninja dogs really getting into it
oh oh animals can't consent but ninja animals can did you know that i do now yeah
next up is more yelling about digimon yeah i'm into this three two one go
i sent in that first digimon rural rumble voicemail since an huge influx of
similar voicemails proud of y'all anyway it's been i think in washington they try doing so in
japanese the english dub is full of character assassination there's a reason why people generally
like daisuke and taiki and absolutely hate davis and mikey yes i know worst of all is mimi
who in the original show is one of the best characters especially in japanese but the english
dub absolutely ruins her character for the sake of just valley girl generally making her dumb
it's actually kind of sexist and gross and it's not very good watch it in japanese
start with either the original mamora hisota short film or with tamers or
either work i didn't uh tom tamers is base but recently there's been one just as base
digimon universe aptly monster i know it sounds like some cringe emoji movie stuff it is not it's
a lot of social commentary about like the internet and youtube and how it's affected how
the youth see their future koreas etc very interesting it is on country roll in america
lastly digimon story cyber salute bundle both the original cyber salute and the spinoff hackers
memory 250 hour rpgs only $50 on pc and steam i meant pc and switch uh often on sale for half off
two very good deal digimon survive look space that first trailer was amazing but it keeps getting
delayed i hear a good thing about the manga so maybe check those out but i haven't read well
that's your uh sounds good that's your digimon uh content update uh for this for this week every
time someone talks about digimon i'm like oh digimon so fucking cool maybe i'll do a lecture
but that'd be a nightmare we should have should we get digital dream on as a guest
i i don't i maybe i don't know like that'd be fun probably for me i'd just get out of a digimon
i'd have a good time no honestly i wouldn't have that much to say about it i just think digital
dream is a very funny person i wouldn't i'll i'll get digital dream we'll do a podcast together
yeah yeah okay all right um next up is next up is that's how'd you how'd you know
i was gonna do for the intro it's i gotta figure out a new one now your name required
i have a great idea listen to me america i have important very important ideas this is what we
need to do every infant that's born every infant male we need to take them and cut their ear lobes
why number one it's unsightly number two uh greater chance of cancer more flesh equals
more cancer chance number three they can't get earrings therefore they can't be gay okay there
you go so we need to cut infants ear lobes off because it's it's worthless flesh it does nothing
it's completely functionless um it's great great idea let's do it roll it out it's the default
you have to opt out this is the future people cut away that which is unnecessary we don't need
appendixes we don't need pinky fingers we just need arms and legs no fingers no hands
just head and jar yeah just a head just brain and the dopamine column yeah i mean we already
you're a little late to the party we are way you're miles ahead of you
and the appendix i want to i'm gonna cut all of the the good parts out and just leave the ear lobes
and the friend your finger that's all i'm gonna be yeah just all the the worst parts the back of
the knee isn't there isn't there another like useless the front of the the front of the knees
lean what do we have two front of the knees so we can bend them no no no no no no no no um
that's the only useful organ that i've got um the penis uh maybe i don't know um so tonsils
yeah fuck tonsils yeah pretty much yo fuck tonsils all right that's all i'm saying uh so yeah hard
hard agree uh next up we got is this okay no three two one go i just want to sing i just want to
dance i just want to live my life i want to be happy stop i want to express the joy i feel in my
heart would you guys be okay with it if i sang in the voicemails the thing about that is that we
i've run a really tight ship here and like voicemails have to pass a very strict strict
range and quality control uh criteria so um sing at your own peril my dude um next one is uh it was
just called like a cat face like the ascii cat face character um so okay so three two one go
so i think uh ben you need to start your own podcast and i think that's those amazing
and you need to uh just keep doing that thank you wait what could you guys make that out uh
uh
let me let me i think you said ben you need to start your own podcast he did it's called the
progress starting with episode 200 whatever why does ben need to start his own podcast what is why
yeah i
i mean you have the patreon one yeah we all have our secret you all have that uh and they're great i
mean maybe he means like maybe he means because i mentioned uh uh like you know when you were talking
about uh squad zilla i said like i'd love to be on like a on like some kind of like very specifically
themed podcast like that maybe he means something like that i mean i don't know i don't know it's
all well and good you just
huh you just need to make out find the just got to start keto confections the the new
confections that's fucking awesome yeah you know what just talk about like damn so what's new in the
world of keto confections this week oh boy really having great results with this uh mono calcium
phosphate uh it's like a perfecto why not this is good as it's as good as anything else
um next one is called samurai the musical uh so uh three
a lot of fucking pretenders to the throne
but then you but then you stab them with a kunai and a puff of smoke you realize they were a simple
log the whole time this is uh three two one go
i think that was uh i think that was the genuine article
shows shows what i know
samurai the way the samurai she's sure must must be doing things such a multi talented character
such a robust character uh uh uh full of uh uh you can feel any niche really yeah next is
margar this fucker all right three two one go margar here in light of the recent uh
anti police and anti prison episode of the pcp i would like to uh send a formal application
for you to reconsider my place within voice prison i think that i've more than served my time and
been a uh good contributing member of society um you know just just just be cool man i'm just
being cool in prison how is he not uh i don't want to be here anymore how did we let this happen
how did we allow him
why do we let him have a phone he keeps sending he's not allowed to petition light him up and
they just don't finish the job has to be illegal somehow right this has this um the uh the uh the
the uh some no who who do we just make voice grail who do we just make voice grail appeal to
that guy appeal to that gut i don't remember the guy it doesn't matter it doesn't don't care he's
whoever that guy was his voice grail appeal to him because the only way to get out of voice jail
is to have someone is to have is to mutually annihilate in a burst of pure energy with the pot
the negatively charged uh the oppositely charged a voice grail i don't make the rules uh i accept
i kind of did but i don't so that's just i i yeah that's right i do in fact make the rules but i
have already made them and i'm not willing to reconsider i do make the rules i just won't
change them next up is bob story three three two one go hey so yeah uh quick follow-up to my story
from last week yes i took all of the pictures for her um oh this is the it was all her idea
i also put the pictures on fourchan a while later um like because she wanted you to right
but yeah the horror of it was that i had a christian video on like a playlist
playing while i was fingering her so i'm like having chris look at me from the corner of my
eye and he freaked me the fuck out it was also the first time i fingered a girl so is that too
gross uh everything about this is bad okay okay so this this really makes me think though this
really confirms my suspicion that the girl kind of just wanted to get fingered and maybe was using
the let's take pictures as just sort of a sort of a pretense to to sexualize the encounter
i don't know i don't know that's just my that's just my opinion man
yeah but there's there don't worry there's more there's more in bob story four we get the follow
home god three two one go uh to follow up then um the girl and i we kind of went on a couple
dates and i fingered her a few more times and like made out a couple times and then i found out
she was engaged and i was not okay okay okay okay these are like two very key facts that making this
story as terrifying as you're implying it to be and you let it kept us waiting a whole week you
know what you know what i think my theory holds i just kind of think she was just on the prowl
yeah no that definitely solidifies that yeah yeah and just uh i can imagine i can imagine
no maybe i'm being unfair here but but my mind goes to like
your guys are talking about chris chan or whatever and she's like why don't why won't this
why won't this homo just just finger me already
like she she came up to you the first time she saw your hands just like this is like hands i know
she complimented the only language the only language you understand the language of
chan is the language of sonichu i know i'll i can i can pretend that these pictures are for
maybe maybe if i fuck with chan he'll care and then i won't and that's the reason why i can
get naked and i won't look like a slaughter and as as we're posting my my my uh nudes for
weston chan layer onto four uh it doesn't doesn't it i understand more but at the same time i don't
um good story though good story next up it's tale as old as time next up is pro
master just like toy story three two one go hey pcp so gib is a girl now i i don't i don't
understand that there are no girls on the internet right like that's not a thing that's right so
that's true what's up with that jk uh trans rights hey well
you gotta cover your back i gotta be sorry i think maybe make sure there's no way maybe this guy
called in to be like ha ha sarcastic about like uh but then he felt like oh this kind of actually
just sounds like i'm like stupid so i gotta like i gotta dial back i gotta dial it back
can be like and be like no but actually no but actually don't don't say these things
it it is the unfortunateness because it ruins the punchline everything i am about to say is not
sincerely believed like anyway by the way a lot onto my voicemail um okay next up cross fan art is
based three two one go i recently got my first piece of fan art and it got me thinking about how
fucking based fan art is feel like you need to draw but you got artist block whoever your favorite
content creator is is probably a great source of inspiration make fan art want senpai to notice you
but they won't respond to the hundreds of comments you've left on their youtube videos tweet fan
art at them you want to support your favorite content creator patreon.com slash ben saint yeah
what you're broke well then fucking fan art this guy knows everything how is how is this guy just
the smartest person alive how did he do it mm-hmm i drew it's it's every every a zumi fan art i get
makes the projects i'm going to especially for someone who draws be complete five minutes earlier
than they otherwise would be because it's like an extra boost of energy yeah yeah yeah yeah that's
that's the whole point i can't i can't say it's too far only five minutes though i'll get two more
fan art and the project will be done so it's got you gotta you gotta taper that out a little bit
yeah yeah i need a like a few gigabytes of
pump i got a piece of coming in got a cop killer fan art the other day it was a it was the first
one i've gotten in a while but i was like hell yeah let literally amazing uh next yeah
i would like people to draw the the gib sonar that i have the the female looking one the one
i haven't drawn her that like yeah properly but i've drawn her a bunch
like i'm a dress it's just it's just basically me but with tits just do that
yeah and or just wearing clothing yeah i agree um next one is called
astro astrogen is a hell of a drug oh three two yes true jen
konnichiwa it is samurai here to explain to ben no sun this is a cold situation no but friend
explain because samurai voice not good
hi i'm the samurai's friend um so he found your discord through an old tweet that you made in like
2018 maybe after you said that he was in the discord which he wasn't he went to your discord server
there was somebody there called actual samurai guy so the samurai sent him a dm and said hey
why don't you get fucked you posted a cringy picture fuck you the samurai is my character not yours
so that guy fucked off and now samurai committed in the discord now is the actual summer
i don't know why he wanted this clarified but he wanted me to do it so i'm gonna hand you back
we're pure now
make voice hard to do so samurai go forever probably but until whenever sayonara erogid
ah sucker he fucking he fucking forgave me for all my betrayals ah you nerd this is what i was waiting
for i tricked you into it i waited you out and it paid dividends i'm gonna be i'm gonna be rolling
in it i'm gonna i'm gonna use the power of the scroll what did they make me uh make me a millionaire
it's fucking nerd
i missed that too about something about the voice makes it difficult
i i some yeah i didn't hear that word he said something uh uh uh i get fucked i get fucked
thinking i'll return the scroll thinking i'll use doesn't even have a fucking he doesn't even
have a fucking prayer okay okay okay good fucking oh okay oh he said he said hormone make voice hard
to do oh does that samurai trans never knew jesus
wait but that's not how estrogen works it doesn't change your voice you have to do that yourself
uh you have to do that with rigorous trace
maybe that's what's on the scroll is how to change that shit i don't give a fuck
uh swipe my ass with it when i need to let the cats hang on my toilet paper roll
just emergency tp you know in case of emergency a great glass kind of deal
no just reusable toilet paper you know it's like it's like drill drill said recently they
should invent toilet paper that you put in the trash instead of in the toilet i did it it's called
the Kawasaki clan scroll um okay so glad we've sorted that situation out uh riddle my next one
is from riddle my ass batman well three two one go batman here for his first weekly report
disney drew the body the back cave for the new amusement park they only offered five trillion
dollars batman was insulted so the bat took the mouse his ears took him off shut him down and
stroked and replaced him with bad ears such concludes the weekly report do it next time
same bat time same bad channel batman's a fucking psychopath
was it was it disney the mouse wanted to um yeah that it seemed like a little low ball
for price oh i thought they were gonna make that correct a bat cave attraction and they're
no they probably were no they were gonna have they had to buy it from batman yeah oh yeah in
the authentic bat cave yeah sure yeah yeah yeah yeah i probably i probably would have handled it
the same exact way honestly yeah completely justified it sends a message hey now's a riddle
my ass batman is one of the many many people who has not completed uh uh uh their uh fucking uh
Kickstarter uh survey uh so i can send the fucking shit in the mail incredible uh
uh yeah yeah for the vapors too um the uh i um it's coming up on a point because i did because
i did the Kickstarter so long ago um like the surveys are only available for a year and we're
coming up on the year and the surveys are only going to be available until the 31st so after
the 31st i will not be able to see anyone's like uh surveys if they want to like fill them out late
they will have to like message me instead of doing it via the survey which is a little inconvenient
but i guess what can you do so i don't know if anyone's listening and you haven't fucking done that
get that in uh pretty soon because the end of the month is coming up and it'll be it'll be less
convenient after that um okay just thought that just put just putting that out there um next one
is called pancakes shit gay uh three two one go hey pancakes with creators here listen i just
got back from taking a big fat piece of dump in my toilet just a piece and i was wondering you know
how sometimes like taking a shit sometimes feels even better than sex well is that gay because
taking a shit is like technically anal penetration yeah i mean it's not gay it's pretty gay adjacent
frankly it's only gay and i won't stand for it it's only gay if your your shit is the same gender
that you are so what so you need to know what the gender is that you ate yeah i guess that's uh
it's the only way to do it
well my shit is non-binary so i don't know what to do better not better not better not come while
you're shitting then or else you're else will never fucking understand uh i mean uh i don't think
i don't know about listen then what do you do when you go to next time you're taking a shit and
you just fucking come while it's happening because it just feels so good just you know just be aware
that yeah if you if your shit is male and so are you then it's gay and there's nothing wrong with
that but it's the fact of life so you know careful um three next up is pancakes physics degree problem
uh three two one go hey pancakes with craters here listen i know some people at pcp
technically have physics quote unquote degrees and i was wondering can you solve this problem
can an object have unlimited surface area but a limited volume why or why not and please explain
uh yeah there's um
yeah i know i know exactly i think what he might be talking about is the idea that it would it
it you you can always find you can always uh measure the surface area of like a an irregular
shape more and more finely and it would never you would never get a super completely accurate
measurement but you can't have it be literally infinite yeah well like um right
it would just take an infinite amount of time to get the next your accurate measurement wait under
what circumstance um like if you're going around a country and you're trying to find the exact
perimeter of the country um yeah it's like you could go like to the atomic level yeah i
suppose well by what you define as the coast and eventually you will find there's um you you can
infinitely like refine your measurements uh okay you guys know what a mobius strip is right
would you say that that is has infinite surface area
because like um no because you can you can't overlap the part before you measured right
like you can't measure the part because there's a there's a 3d thing called the Klein bottle
which is basically which is basically a three-dimensional mobius strip it's similarly
like it's it's its surface area is recursive and it does have a fixed volume it's like it's a it's
a finite 3d shape with a yeah a recursive mobius like surface area but no i wouldn't actually say
that that has infinite surface area so um i'm gonna say it has one side that's the fun part um
i'm gonna say no i'm gonna say no
you can't you can't have infinite surface area and limited volume right am i missing anything guys
brain teaser have i failed yeah i don't know you're though you're more physics than i am i just
watch fucking youtube videos i watch smart every day
wait wait a minute wait a minute and v source no that's stupid because what i just described like
an object with like a continuous surface area that wraps around a sphere does that i'm a fucking
moron um all right all right mr. fucking pancakes with prayers if you've got some smart ass answer
then i guess call in next week and we'll see if i've failed uh and if not then get the fuck out of
here um next up pancakes only play this if you're weak-minded you know wait wait wait i got an answer
unlimited surface area and uh got him oh obliterated uh okay three two one go
jesus christ even a two-year-old with ass burgers could know this and answer this question
what are you some kind of moron it's obviously gabriel's horn look it up basically
shit i don't want to fucking explain it just look it up um oh oh yeah i get it yeah i get it
it is a a 3d a three-dimensional okay well
yeah the the point is that like it widened it's a it's a horn that widens at the base
but it widens like two at a rate the asymptotically approaches
like bottoming out but never quite gets there oh yeah yep yep that would do it
yeah but how could it have limited volume if it never quite gets there just keeps going the volume
also keeps going right it does but it but it keeps going at a diminishing rate that um
what's the word what's the word that converges that converges to a finite number it doesn't
it doesn't approach infinity well all right yeah i've heard of it um
but i would i would i would ask for a robust explanation here because because because to
my thought process if something is going to infinity um the volume inside it there's a bunch
of youtube videos about it so i'm sure um you could find the answer here we go that me and you
could understand i've heard here we go here we go um so yeah the recipe okay imagine this um
i don't i don't know what a triangular number is but um the oh okay okay three the reciprocal
the reciprocal of powers of two right this is an infinite series of of sums you start with
one it's a series of fractions that you add on top of each other right you start with one over
one is the fraction so that has a value of one and then you add to that one over two half you add
to that one over four quarter add to that one eight add one sixteenth add one thirty two
add one sixty fourth etc etc etc and you keep going to infinity um the numbers get smaller
as the series goes on such that even though the series is infinite it you it does not even
if you continue it infinitely you don't get infinity uh uh the series continued infinitely
becomes two uh it converges to two so yeah the the the idea with gabriel's horn is similar in that
like you know the surface the the area that it is enclosing you know yeah at the wide base of it
that like goes out and out and out and out infinitely uh it it like moves like the the space
between it and the bottom it and the the asymptote is so becomes diminishes at such a rate that's
similarly it converges to a non-infinite number i don't i don't know if i clarify anything uh
i'll go to youtube maybe find some smart alec yeah oh because you're sure you're sure is
fuck not gonna find one here um all right uh next one a disgruntled fan three two one go
you know ben for being such a proud leftist icon you platform a lot of hate speech on your
shell it's disappointing wish you'd be a little better about vetting these things no elaboration
all right cool uh a couple um a couple people a couple people complained about some of the
voicemails last week i didn't think any of the voicemails last week were that bad honestly um
well they which ones i can't think exactly because i can't remember because i
block all of the episodes out of my mind uh um i well you know i don't know i i talked i think
i talked to the person that sent this voicemail afterwards and she said that like she didn't think
it was that big a deal so maybe i should i just kind of want to just move on from it um yeah i'm
not interested not interested uh next up is called sorry for those shitty ones
three two one go hey there pc proud boys uh just wanted to be like sorry about those
really shitty voicemails uh it's uh it's the ones with the metal gear stuff
i'm just uh this is just a preamble for my next voicemail which is gonna blow your socks off
it i swear it's not a meme i it's it's a genuine voice uh
uh fucking performance genuine voice and it's a story it's got a beginning middle and end you
don't need to do a preamble blow your your fucking uh decks off why is this a whole minute long
and this the next voicemails come guys and uh we've never we've never had a good voicemail
before but i think this might be this might be for real the next one's gonna be good i swear
okay here we go sense here we go this one's called the good one
three two one go baby
you fucking fools you idiots who could have seen this coming god damn reapered you
cook so boy you fucking fell for it are you fucking voice gel voice gel uh i don't know if
this is even worthy of voice gel this is too it was just pathetic let's move on uh yeah terrible
terrible um bad uh honestly i'm on the fence i'm on the fence about voice gel
i'm thinking about it um next up why does the quality decline sharply several seconds in
three two one go a few moments later this guy sucks should we just cut this voicemail it sucks
really bad yeah i don't want it all right yeah i i'm okay with that ellie is our uh ellie is our
cut that voicemail but leave in this part where i'm saying cut that voicemail fuck that last guy
all right uh yeah um next one is called not worthy of a response frankly disgusting quit
watching our show um next one is called communism from someone who experienced it
oh boy three two one go okay so i cringe every fucking time you fucking dumb americans think
oh communism this i'm gonna suck the dick of communism it's so good it's so fair when we
here in eastern europe we've lived under communism for like almost a hundred years and it was the
worst thing ever it killed everyone and it's fucking yeah it killed everyone in the ass okay yeah he's
right and it slowed down our progress like a hundred years we still have medieval villages
until fucking now it's stupid it's like okay maybe america's brand of communism would be better now
with the power of handsight of we even have a brand of communism not really a tiny it's just a tiny
subset of people we're like really far left i love the other one but god fucking damn i always
always cringe when you guys like invoke oh i love the russian national anthem the so who
hate them i hope i that's that are still alive that have a heart attack right now
they are literally i wait who who's who's hitler i i i it's always the same like the people who
don't know what they're fucking talking about have in their head the idea of what a leftist is and
what they believe and they think that is what they're talking to whenever any one of us has any some
like they don't think about what we're saying they think of what the the the label of leftist means
to them and what they've heard and they ascribe it to it like nobody has ever talked about the
fucking russian national anthem maybe yeah i feel like he doesn't know anything about what
communism would actually mean i think i mean not to uh boy i i i i feel like you really need to go
into this i feel like this is like an open up a whole can of words i feel like maybe i i don't
want to go into the specifics but i want to address this the mindset and i i feel like i might be
accused of um i don't know west explaining this or something to uh you know this guy is like hey i was
i'm in a fucking eastern country uh we experienced communism this guy is probably like 20 so
probably not but whatever um uh is it what what does it mean what does it mean that like
communism like fucked up our development and no the what would probably fucked up the development
of whatever country this guy is in um was probably the ussr the ussr like supported its
surrounding you know eastern bloc countries but it was beset at the same time by the rest of the
world the capitalist world which you know sought to destroy it at every turn and i don't know i
kind of feel like maybe that might have had something to do with it i don't think this guy
has really considered uh all the possibilities here uh for the reasons behind what he describes
as the ills of communism uh i don't know this guy just kind of seems like he's being dogmatic
i think i think it's it's it's like there's you could say that a capitalist um surge is good for
like getting a good strong foothold and then you're the most powerful country in the world um
and then from that you can become communist and then give your people what they need but it comes
down a lot to like just having the right resources in the country like america had a lot of stuff you
know it's really it's really hard it's i mean it's hard to like put any of us there like
neat bow on really educated enough right about the political theory to make a like educated
response to this in terms of the effects and causal links between communism and like capitalist
pushback it's true eastern europe it's true but at the same time i don't think any of us are
fucking tanky yeah we're here singing the praises of communist russia just because you want social
reform in america and are not exactly pleased with what capitalism is doing like i don't think
anyone here is saying we need hardcore need like Stalinist socialism you know like i would be perfectly
happy with some tax reforms uh to fucking bring the rich back in line yeah like close some loopholes
and shit so people i i don't know if this guy is is like this but some people get yeah some people
get offended get uppity get like weird about it when you even suggest like what if we tax the rich
more and they act like that's Stalin style siege socialism in and of itself uh i mean there's a
discussion yeah there doesn't need to be a fucking jumping down everybody else's throat you know like
there are pros and cons to doing that i i just have to weigh them against each other and just have
a discussion and figure it out i just want to say i think i think that you know the the legacy the
legacy of communism it's so i feel like there's a very difficult web of like causations there and
i think it's probably really hard to entangle like you know which what what misfortunes were you
know the fault of communism itself versus what was the what was caused by like deprivation created
by like you know sanctions and or military action from the disapproving you know capitalist rest of
the world and to just you know to just blanketly say like oh yeah communism ruined everything it's
like no it's never that simple even if that's that's and that's me being charitable uh to this
interpretation of history which i'm willing to i'm willing to be charitable uh fuck man uh um
hail hail Stalin uh uh uh hail the ussr uh disavow disavow disavow um uh um what's a what's a
communist thing to say um guillotines i don't know just i just i just want people to fucking
listen to the things we say and then respond to that instead of the things to be fair i think
that the line about um the russian he might have been talking about like maybe the left
generally and not us specifically because surely none of us have ever been like i love the russian
but like like the left generally is such a the the left generally is not general there's so many
different things i'm not saying that it's a group yeah i'm not saying it's it's fair but yeah uh yeah
okay have we be specific for fuck's sake have we have we have we have we successfully obliterated
capitalism once and for all uh nice shut up no no it's still too powerful no no no we're gonna
we got it we got it it's gone now um next one is troll jester mgs this is stupid i'm sorry
okay three two one go miller what's gotten into you snake they aren't real what they aren't real
poor people aren't real i've never seen one you've never seen one i can't be i'm blind snake
get it i'm blind the sunglasses i you're not blind what master miller isn't blind you
are fucking moron have you even played the games you lost your arm i knew that snake look
that was a test i wanted to make sure you were the real snake what are you even talking about
i've never uh felt the poor they aren't real snake uh snake it's me a parole throat i'm in this too
it's you it's me yes hello what are you doing snake listen don't listen to him he's a liar snake
don't listen to him he's also a liar like me i can tell what other liars are around
that's bullshit fuck you listen i've got some keycard bullshit to deal with i'll get in contact
with you later okay it's like i'm there say it's the last second it's like i'm there
it's like a it's like a proto it's like a proto one but later
uh
it's good excellent uh okay all right all right simmer down uh next next one we've got is called
canned tent uh three two one ago hey everybody and welcome to another episode of canned tan
canned tan we just watched a fucking terrible anime it's a really bad anime and i don't care
about it at all listen to me talk about how much i don't care for 45 minutes there's just way too
much going on in the plot there's a lot of talking and there are more than two things happening at
once that's too much that bores me and because it's boring i don't care at all and because i don't
care i'm not going to pay attention which will cause me to miss extremely obvious plot details
i'm not misunderstanding because i'm stupid or anything it's just that the show is not good
if it was just a good show i would understand it very well because i am a smart person it's hard
to understand and the author made it that way because the author is autistic i don't understand
the story at all but i completely understand the kind of person the author is and their creative
process well that's going to do it for this week's episode of canned tan
i believe i believe this was uh uh
now now i'm now i'm not i'm not i don't watch i don't watch canton but uh i heard people saying
that the re-zero episode made a lot of people angry did you guys hear anything about this
i heard nothing i i haven't heard i i don't watch because i don't care about the anime but like
i i totally believe that this is what's happening because it seems it seems very realistic yeah
yeah it does in particular it's like it's like i was there in in particular it was i i heard people
saying that the re-zero episode they just kind of like didn't understand the plot and like
people were like why are you talking about the show you're criticizing the show i mean
but you like didn't understand it and you are like factually wrong about some things i mean
that's the biggest nightmare for any person who talks about media is is to be stupid live on screen
is to is to is to have missed something obvious and talked with authority i i i have nightmares
of doing that myself i've probably done it hundreds of times because i i just i'm not aware it would
be it would be pretty embarrassing that's that much i i can uh i can agree with uh well uh canned
thanks for your thanks for your voicemail uh fuck yeah next one is called ben is racist
uh oh oh oh boy three it's about time this was brought to life three two one go say it say it
say white lives matter if you're not a racist say it say it now oh god i mean i mean i mean i mean
i mean i mean white lives do matter got got right a little bit right like i mean yeah they
matter too right but ben you just have to say all lives matter you cover everybody i mean i mean
all lives all lives don't matter you don't live still matter though it's right yeah you come on
you know it's like uh fuck no it's all right he's right i'm racist i'll i feel like i should
just say the thing the black lives matter is not about black lives matter more is because society
does not generally deem them to matter in western society it feels it feels the need to be said
therefore it is a thing that people say do you ever do you ever feel like the left has a language
problem do you ever feel like the left makes up makes a lot of terms that are seems to be inherently
difficult for people to understand it's not inherently difficult for people to understand
they're just not trying to understand i feel like i mean it's not like is sloganable but if
like it had been if the movement had been called black lives matter too we wouldn't have this
conversation because it would have been implied in this yeah then now that would have saved would
have saved us all collectively hundreds of hours that one is fair enough i have always thought that
but i also don't think that at this point people can can be allowed to just still not get it it's
been so all over but i'm just saying if only if only we had known and could have
proactively corrected this problem from the very beginning um i don't know i i i wonder if like
would would like tweaking the phrasing a little bit like really have made that much of a difference
or would i think the people i think the people with the people with the problem with it had just
have a problem anyway they just wouldn't i think they would have found another problem but i think
there are probably a significant amount of people who don't understand who probably once
explained like oh i get it now and those people would have been saved yeah or the very least the
people who are on the fence who were convinced by the people who acting in bad faith would never
have had that that avenue to be swayed in the first place i think it's just sort of like if if
someone were to say the statement black lives matter and your responses like not yeah of course
if your response is defensive then there's something up i mean i know i know a lot of white
people myself included initially was like what about white people um but that's because i yeah i
don't have the i don't have this perspective i do now that's that's that's entirely that's entirely
my point but like i don't know i learned i learned this here's wasn't that difficult here's but
you know what i'm gonna i'm gonna go i'm gonna move past that honestly yeah i think those sure
like out and out racists who are like uh don't say black lives matter that's uh why you why you
politicize why you gotta bring race into it or whatever like yeah fuck that um but i think i
think there is a more insidious the more insidious problem is the is the guy who's like you're like
okay black lives matter and he's like yeah yeah sure yeah black lives matter yeah yeah of course
yeah equality black people and then you're like okay okay uh you know therefore outlines a bunch
of like progressive policy ideas like you know defunding the police uh or whatever uh you know
funding social welfare programs instead of over policing uh you know decriminalizing marijuana
so on and so forth and then they're like whoa whoa whoa i thought this was just about black lives
you know being equal now you're trying to do well now you're trying to sneak in all this Marxist
shit on me i think that's the real sticking point i i think that's the that's the thing yeah it does
come from the same place that's like a bigger hump where it's just they don't have the perspective
to understand that in order to make sure black lives are treated equally these things need to change
like like a like a conservative will agree like they'll say like yeah yeah yeah black people are
just as invaluable as white people black lives matter just as much and then you're like okay well
here's how you know on the whole you know people of color and such are you know disadvantaged
you know the you know wealth and equality is a big problem over policing is a big problem crime
criminality is you know is not a uniformly enforced and then they'll be like okay okay okay yeah but
i mean that's just kind of like uh human nature or something like uh like yeah but you can't like
do anything about that right like share black lives matter but like you can't like do anything
about that's just like the way the world works that's just like uh and you know maybe they
shouldn't commit those crimes that you know we convict them for more more vigorously than
than other other people you know what i'm saying i do yeah um i think is there's a there's a there's
i don't know it's what you say insidious i say that it is it's it's for people who have like more
insidious um goals they act like that and then there are people who just act like that because
they don't think about it at all which is an unfortunate double those people that i just
described are convinced that they are the real not racists right that like redistributive wealth
is like a racist thing like that's the real racism or something and that makes me so bad
it's like you know that that like affirmative action is like the real racism or whatever i don't
know it's very it's i'm getting mad just thinking about it um uh i feel like i was gonna say oh i was
gonna say uh you say you know think about the left having a language problem i think that to a certain
extent i would agree the black lives matter like yeah i guess i see how like it's a little like
maybe if you don't think about it it's like well that's kind of a weird you know
another thing is like only black lives oh no you don't mean that okay uh i misunderstood another
example would be like um what is it private property versus personal property yeah that's a
whole that's a big fucking problem like imagine all the memes that could have been avoided if we
didn't use language like that yeah with me i mean mark said i didn't use that language at all but
you know what i mean like there's just there's tons of small little examples like that um throughout
like like like language on the left that i feel like when you went if you're not into politics at all
if you're like completely apolitical yeah uh and you stumble upon a lot of this phrasing like abolish
private property like what the fuck that sounds stupid but like you'd have to have like someone
who's like knowledge sit down and explain all this like preamble to you and like we we just had a
very bad reaction at preamble so i'm sure people who have had to live politics feel similarly it
just seems like really poor language choices on a lot of key issues fucked a lot of this shit up
yeah i i think that i agree but on the same time i wonder like to what extent was it like
poor phrasing versus like to what extent has it been like to what extent has the phrasing like
been poisons on purpose well i mean it took me forever to realize that private property and
personal property were different among people who are talking about like marks yeah i didn't know that
forever yeah because as someone who just listened to it i'm like abolish private property that seems
like it would cause a lot of issues i i feel like if like maybe uh i don't know just um just
thinking that lab maybe not capitalism's biggest fan so it's not like i was like pulling for the
other team or anything it just like on the face of it based on like casual vernacular that sounds
really bad i just i maybe if maybe if like i don't know the educational system were more
because like you know i grew the orthodoxy that i was taught growing up was that you know the free
market corrects for itself and and all that stuff all this neoliberal like a voodoo and um
someone just fucking subscribed or something i don't know um and uh so that but then you know what
one wonders if maybe one wonders if maybe the the we were taught a more like a more genuinely like
neutral perspective or a more balanced perspective maybe we would know the different because a lot
of people don't know the difference but like you know that we have a public education system
is supposed to educate us and make sure we know things i mean i feel like that's one thing that
maybe could be you know that's i mean i would agree with that to to a point but like i would
also say that like this entire like group of people on the left are operating under the assumption
that we live in a system that is very skewed so if you're making an excuse for like well the system
should be better so we're gonna explain how the system is bad like it just seems like self-defeating
but you have to be operating with language using the the kind of like framework that we're already
established in otherwise you're kind of just tacking on like understanding our problem to
the list of problems you're trying to fix which seems like circular i think that's a fair point
i agree you have to you have to meet people where they are but like i don't know there's a lot of
very i don't know whether they're easy to get into but there's plenty of videos now that explain
these things that people can link to i think on some level people just need to be open to different
ideas on the whole i mean yeah like if you want if you want to dive down a rabbit hole of learning
about this stuff like it's it's very easy to do but um you know i'm getting someone getting someone to
to accept like thinking about it for a little bit is the hardest part and i guess yeah the language
problem is is you know it's it exists i guess i i guess i i can't disagree um next voicemail
let's do it next how many more do we have only like four only three more three more only 46 only 14
no no we're almost done uh uh this one's called fuck them three two one go look the circumcision
is an operation carried out on infants it's done without their consent it's done without
anesthetic it's unnecessary it's a cosmetic operation that's what it is you shouldn't
need to do such a thing routinely to an infant and there is no reason it was invented by this guy
who wanted to stop people from masturbating how fucked up is that yeah it sure will be hard to
jack off when your dick is fucking dry yeah it's fine actually it works so sad it's sad that people
defend it oh yeah like my dick works fine sure sure but your rights were violated dude what the
fuck stop defending it i'm you know i'm religious reasons call me the fucking circumcision defender
i'm circumcision biggest fan now dude it's my belief i think we should just cut our heads off at birth
you know it doesn't make it okay your stupid backwards bullshit doesn't justify your crimes
your violations of people's rights fuck you uh fuck circumcision fuck people who defend it
and fuck doctors who perform it is this that same guy who made wait is this the guy who did
the voicemail that we cut because it was terrible no it was a different guy this guy that's a different
okay okay i mean i agree i don't think circumcision is defendable um you can argue that it's like
good or bad but i don't think it's it's good that you can you can do that to a child because there's
no way they could possibly consent to such a thing i'm gonna play devil's advocate here for a second
whoa holy fuck the tables have turned um i mean i mean i think that um it's not look i i don't know
i don't know everything but like i've seen the arguments that i've seen are like that it's not
just a cosmetic operation it's like a sanitary operation and like circum if you're circumcised
you have like a reduced chance of like uh you know uh various diseases developing and also
it like it lowers the transmission rate of of various stds and uh things like that
and i don't know maybe maybe that if that's true maybe it would convince you and maybe it wouldn't
but like i don't know if well here's the thing if in fact if let me finish if there is like a if
there is like a sanitary or like a medical reason to do it i don't think that like the oh they didn't
consent argument holds water because like you give a kid a vaccine without their consent you know
because like the benefits outweigh the drawbacks and it's because if this kid didn't have the vaccine
then not only would it hurt not only is it best for the kid it's best for all of society if you
know everyone's getting the vaccine it's good for everyone and i think that you could probably make
a similar argument if in fact there are medical benefits to circumcision as i have heard argue
that there are right but nobody someone would argue in response that like a vaccine isn't like
permanently disfiguring and yeah anyone like vaccines do not have a drawback in the same way
that circumcision does i mean does it though dude they give you autism that's the drawback
circumcision does fuck i mean that explains well obviously i can't i can't speak to someone who is
circumcised circumcised because i'm not but there is no sanitary bullshit it's very very easy to
keep it clean it's never made any sense like i really hate the the people who talk about that
when they don't you know they don't have one they don't know it's not a problem that you just wash
it like you wash any part of your body okay uh ben from the future here so i am a fool and i fucked
up and my audacity i ran out of disk space so it stopped recording right in the middle of this
conversation this conversation made me pretty mad uh because nobody fucking uh it's all it's all
gib being like oh but but oh the baby didn't have a choice or the the the what why would you cut a
baby and i'm just i'm i just think that we should follow the science and if i'm just i'm merely open
to the possibility that if you know we're widely practicing circumcision were to significantly cause
some sort of significant societal benefit like say a reduction in the transmission of std's for
instance uh uh you know without any with that without significance or with without you know
a commensurate negative thing because like you know everyone says oh you mutilated oh it's a party
because like okay well so is your appendix uh but you know sometimes you got to cut that out
sometimes you're better off without it uh it doesn't necessarily do anything uh let's not let's not
fall into the trap of the naturalistic fallacy here um so sorry you won't get to hear any of that
but i've summarized it for you i was right i'm always i'm on top of it um okay back sorry goodbye
back to the show all right well let's let's finish this episode as soon as possible right now um
go patreon.com slash the procrastinators if you want to give us money we have tons of bonus episodes
we have possibly more things going to be adding in the future uh leave us a voicemail uh follow us
on twitter at tpcrastinators keep updated on all the random shit we talk about that isn't fit for
an episode and that's it till next time have a good day uh bye yeah go go check out maryweather as well
ben you there you're gonna say bye or you're not recording okay well