I want to bless that guy. That's on above!
OK, I'm gonna sync with myself. One, two, three, sync!
Hello everyone. Welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
It's me, the Gibbontake.
I, it's a solo Gipcast, at least for the beginning, um, I've waited, I've waited for an hour and
a half for Ben's internet to work suddenly and it's not suddenly working.
So I'm doing it, I'm doing the solo Gipcast, I don't know if this has happened before,
I know I've uploaded like a solo, like a vlogcast or something a long time ago just talking
about what I do, but that wasn't a PCP episode.
I think this is maybe the first Procrastinator's podcast where only I have appeared.
So, uh, what you, what you doing, um, I should start with, I think, the Lord of Ghosts, uh,
thank you for people who have, uh, since the last episode sent me their addresses, there's
only seven people left who haven't responded in any way, uh, to emails, to, uh, public
callouts, uh, uh, so I'm gonna read those names one more time and I'll probably be sending
these at the end of April and if there's anyone left, I'll just deal with it, uh, when it,
when it comes.
So, the last people, and I may have spoken to these people, but I still haven't got the
addresses in my, like, spreadsheet, so, uh, if you have responded, uh, this may not apply
anymore, but as of recording, uh, Mimi Menzies, Oren, O-R-I-N, James Gottwig, Adam O'Donnell,
D.S., James Dollar, and Milo Rocks.
James Dollar and Milo Rocks are actually, like, high pledge people, they, they give
a big pledge, I have to draw a doodle for them, I think, maybe they get in the plush,
uh, so, you know, Jed, give the address, go to the, go to the Kickstarter, if you can't
remember your Kickstarter account, then just message me somewhere, uh, so that I know,
and that's that, that's my little thing, but yeah, that's, that's been fun, the Lord of
Ghosts, it's almost completely finished in terms of the Kickstarter thing, and I think,
I think I've learned quite a lot, I've learned, um, that I should, like, very thoroughly figure
out exactly how heavy all of the items I'm going to make will be, I think I did ballpark
figures for, like, the number of pages I would probably, I would have, and then, like, the
page thickness, and, like, how much that would probably weigh, and I got, like, a rough estimate,
but it was very far off, uh, correct, and it wasn't enough, uh, so, luckily, the Kickstarter
made enough money that I'm not, like, losing money, overall, um, I may, like, not, I may,
like, break just even because of, like, all the customs bullshit, which is, uh, unavoidable,
but, uh, what are you going to do? Um, yeah, I've learned a lot about how to do that,
and it was, it really just comes down to, like, make sure to, to know exactly what the
costs are before you set the price for, for, um, for shipping to various countries. I thought,
like, oh, America, and, like, Australia, they'll be similar, and no, Australia's far more expensive.
And, uh, it's Farmerx, but, oh, is that Ben St. Yeah, yeah, yeah. You appeared. I messaged
you a minute ago. Oh, and there's, there's oblivion fall as well. Oh, hey. The episode
has already begun. I just, I basically just gave my spiel. Uh, give, give, give, give,
give, give, give, gimme five, five minutes, since you messaged me. I was waiting for a
whole extra half hour after the hour, you initially said. Let's wait.
I s- I, I said like an hour. I said like an hour and, uh-
Look, I, all I did was I said the Lord of Ghosts, like, people who still haven't given
their addresses and that's it. So that's fine. You can just leave that in.
Okay, I'm sorry. Okay, you're right. It's fine. I'm in a, I'm in a, I'm in a rotten
mood this morning why so rotten I don't know if I even want to talk about it to
be honest sorry and wow I'm being a real downer how are you guys I'm fine I was
just I was I was I was just speaking I guess I don't know I'm sorry I ruined it
I show up and I ruined it it's gonna be a gift cast it's gonna be the first ever
gift cast only I know well I I just my internet's down I don't like that my
internet's down no I don't want to but I don't want to pay for data I don't want
to pay for data on my hotspot my Wi-Fi hotspot on my phone is it isn't working
are you on hotspot right now no I'm on I'm on the hotspot right now well if you
don't want to pay for it what why why are you paying for it it's gonna it's good
if we go on for a while it's gonna be a lot yeah I don't know I'm just doing it
patreon.com slash the procrastinators to pay yes for Ben's hotspot also let me
let me let me whine about how let me just remind everyone that we did not
charge any patrons any money all last month we lost like a thousand dollars
so please take pity oh please take pity on us yes we you got last month for free
please take pity on us and pledge us some money just to make us feel better
about that that boner of ours we uploaded I uploaded four I thought it was
gonna be two but there are in fact four bone new bonus episodes that I went put
up this week so that's like six hours of stuff so I don't know check it out give
me some money that would make me feel a little better yeah okay and what's up
oblivion I'm doing yeah I've just been for the past week plus a couple days I've
just been watching my patreon explode yeah explode I saw it the day after that
video went up I haven't checked it in a little while let me take a look at it
I'll just show what it's at today oh wow it's insane it doubled like a whole thing it
doubled again yeah it's fucking I saw it like doubled the day the video went up
and then it did it like again okay yeah it was at 400 and now it's at 3500 wow
that's which that congrats that's a lot yeah I'm just I'm just speechless I'm
speechless I've been making animations on YouTube for up close to 15 years and
this is the first time I can officially say it's it's me I've done it I've made
it I'm independent boy not having to rely on doing animation forever people it's
the power of the big booby and so I'm very happy yes I guess damn well not to
demean not to diminish the fact that it was a very good animation that got all
that attention because it was very nice what can I say 900 it's a big number what's
what's your next like animation then what's what's what are all these patrons
gonna gonna be waiting for the next project is come zone for I have I mean
I've been working on the instrumental since the beginning of last year I've
just writer's block is bad and also I've had so much other things to focus on that
I haven't really been able to properly sit down and you know dedicate a lot of
time to it until now but yeah like it's going well I'm making my own music
instead of stealing from infected mushroom that's nice I actually really
really like how it's sounding so far and once it's done I'll be like storyboarding
and figuring stuff out the plan is to work on the shots one at a time and a lot
of a shots I know it's gonna be at least one part of the video where it's just a
whole bunch of sex happening but for the YouTube version it'll just be like
silhouettes with like you know like quickly cutting in and out with like
the music and it'll just be like a you know a black silhouette with like a red
or white thing around that or something but I'll basically be working on those
shots and releasing them for patreon so that way they can get like as they're
as you're as they're getting you're gonna release the pieces of the video as
you finish the pieces yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah and then eventually you know
the whole all of bits will be done and I can combine it all and there'll be like
obviously non-sexo shots as well and maybe some art in between though like
considering how much people respond to the animation like I was planning to do a
lot more art but people seem to really care about the animation mostly so I
guess that's where I'll focus I'm still gonna spend next month mostly drawing
but I do have some content I can release that like I'm gonna make a I'm
probably gonna make like an NSFW version of come zone free I'm just gonna you
know take the After Effects file that I had take the Photoshop file for all the
layers and shit and just we got no put take your titties out I guess is that
not something I thought that's I thought you already had that I thought that was
what was on patreon no that's like sitting in a chair it's like the first
one oh three that's three yeah okay gotcha yeah the yeah come zone free was
for one that blew up like in 2020 yeah the new animation is on Kazonex come
zone and then comes on for the thing I'm doing next what what qualifies what
disqualifies on Kazonex come zone from being number four is it that it's a is
it that it's a meme crossover it's that it's short probably that it's short it
doesn't have lyrics okay the musical style is very different from the over
free whereas the fourth one will be more in line with that and way better I think
what I have so far is way better like it's musically some of the best stuff I've
made ever in my life and I don't know I think mainly it's like the lyrics being
a thing because that's what cracks everyone up gets everyone giggling me I
see me I see could we get Craig in here sure oh yeah also we should say oh
right yes maybe I just maybe I just like being on the show you know maybe I
just like to be here you think about that what maybe that's why I'm on
even though I'm paying for data well yeah I mean maybe I just enjoy it
I appreciate your company same to you Ben
I'm losing it I'm losing it this morning all right let's let's sync quickly and
so we can get that out of the way yes yeah okay one two three sink sink let's
go let's keep going that was the coldest open ever what were we talking
about comes on for yeah it's gonna be a thing did you you how I mean you didn't
you didn't expect it to like quit quintuple but do you expect it to quintuple
again after it comes on for there's a chance look I did my research right yeah
because I'm like I like doing animation there's a lot of different kinds of
animation I'd like to do but I am like primarily a degenerate I feel okay and
that tends to like succeed so that that's good for me but I don't know like
how well it'll do so I did like see like whatever people have done in order to
um you know make a living like I looked at some of the page like the most highest
earning patrons the patreon people and there's people like Sakimichan who
like $60,000 a month and they just do art like they like people like that have
like such an insane reach like their art just gets posted a million times on
every website everywhere like do people yeah like outside of like you know like
like mainstream like I look at hentai porn circles like for some reason has
like reached beyond that I don't know they make like a ridiculous amount of
money and they always have and I'm like okay but that seems to be like a fluke
though like most NSFW artists like will make a couple hundred or maybe a couple
thousand but never like a crazy amount like it seems to be a fluke in that case
Sakimichan is a weird anomaly yeah for sure yeah um and like they're a good
artist but like this better artist definitely they definitely have I don't
know if it's still a problem they had same face for a very long time who's
Sakimi yes Sakimichan yeah I mean Sakimi is like a good painter whatever yeah
they're not like 20 times better than everyone else and you know like she
has very good rendering her anatomy can definitely be noticeably off frequently
but yeah but like it's not like not to like a terrible degree it's just like yeah
the people who like I don't know how Sakimichan got to where they are are
never seeing their shit like posted by like news articles hey this person drew
Disney princesses is hot men and you just see like fucking BuzzFeed articles and shit like
that kind of attention yeah so like I yeah not gonna happen to me and also I
can't like that that semi-realism that gets people wet is not something I'm
into anyway but what I have seen as I've seen animators like fucking go from
small number to ridiculously huge number that's like the tens of thousands
very fast and it seems to mostly happen with animators it happens with yeah
there has to be exclusive content yeah just be an animator have exclusive
content and like be good right the primary thing like some I see like some
really like big artists who you're talking about NSFW specifically yeah
like yeah porn mainly yeah like and they're they're animators who you know
don't do NSFW who are just as talented or more talented than me who get like not
even a hundred a month it's sad I just just how though just how things be but
yeah like I looked at I forgot the website's called it's like a it's like
social blade but for patreon you can track how much people have earned over
time I looked at some high-earning animators you're talking about graph
trian graph trian yeah that was it I know I'm gonna see on that graph trian
actually I wanted to look at um Trixie's graph trian it's great I know I want to
know what was fair maximum earnings and almost 5k almost 5k okay so I've got a
while ago before I beat that record actually let me let me uh actually let
me look at your graph here oh wow oh wow yeah I actually haven't looked at my own
graph it's really funny wait I'll post it don't look don't look it's gonna be
in the crowd I can't find myself that's weird lol oh my god it's like a
waterfall in reverse that is mad oh my god and the trajectory is still going up
that's probably am I it's probably gonna skim close to 4k I mean
depends how long this this gravy train keeps chugging along I'm pying to just
keep the output good yeah that that that puts things into perspective yeah
apparently number one in the adult music rank there's an adult music rank see
that does seem like a pretty a pretty small niche oh yeah I didn't even know
those thing like how is this cataclysm wait rock candies in here I know who
that person is candy they're they're they're like an they're like an ad they
do like flash animations um let's see this person well yeah you you became
number one in adult music on April 22nd or no April yeah or April yep yep wow
huh that's interesting like I'm looking at some of these like the rankings for
top-patreon adult music not ever not I know all of these people like seem to
have like music listed as like a thing they do at least in there like you know
very little description like I guess mindgasm creates audio guides I don't
know what an audio guide is is that music Orion the Orion person says they
create music videos huh yeah audio guides for meditation
oh maybe it includes music the people at the bottom like have music but the
people never top don't mention music that's interesting except me I'm
authentic Lamau yeah yeah you're the best sex music person that they've ever
seen cunt and the gang creating silly music and other content for enlightened
ear holes I'm interested jinx monsoon creating gorgeous little things I don't
even know what some of these are but cosplay music videos okay it's a real a
real a real but what do you call it mishmash a real melting pot this this
category hmm number one though pretty good you beat you just barely beat out
golden tar who is creating sketches and stories also does not sound like music
but oh well interesting the money and the money you show me the money the money
though that's pretty good hmm I'm gonna be able to at this rate we're gonna be
able to afford kai's top surgery in a couple months and then all so we're just
saving up for that right now and after that I'm just gonna have a lot of extra
money I'm just gonna use it to hire people I guess hire help hire animators
and you know be able to get more good plug-ins for my music hire a
professional mixer that sort of thing hmm I'm gonna put it on yeah you know I'll
be curious yeah I I guess I would be curious to hear like what you how you
do that I don't know like what like what would you yeah outsource like that
mixing maybe like what do you call it like a fit finish finishing like a what
would you call it when like you have the rough sketches of an animation and you
send it off to a Korean studio and they and they send it back and usually you
send the key frames key yeah yeah in-betweening in-betweening it's not
quite the best analogy like with mixing it's like you know I'm no no I'm not
saying they're the same I'm just wondering if I don't know you would do
something like that oh if I would do something like that for animation I mean
way round I would get someone I would pay people to do rough animation for
I'd really them to do like a sketchy version and then I would clean it up
because that's my area of stress really are you serious yeah it's you use that's
crazy I'm bad at the fundamentals but I'm extremely doing micro adjustments
like I'd probably at this point I can probably like I can do like rough
storyboards and then I maybe I can find like so an artist you can like really
push him like get more like intense perspective and things to make it just
look really cool sort of thing so like better storyboarding rough animations I
there's a couple people I've talked to who said they would be interested who are
really good and now I can like pay like here I'll give you like like 150 bucks
to do like like like a shot that's like five seconds or something and if just
roughs you know which I think is pretty good rates you know that's that's kind
of what I'm thinking and hopefully hopefully comes before be really good
but it's still gonna take a while to get done sure I mean you laugh about like it
being oblivion is not good at the fundamentals then but I think like people
have their skills sometimes that just is how it is where you're like I don't know
I look at a blank page and I like some people can just sketch out like a rough
idea really easy and really quickly and other people like they they just can't
and they can only like refine something that already exists with with like a
like a fine-toothed comb yeah skill sets it's all it's all depending on because
like I was trying for like pumpkin alley stuff to like to like do concept art I've
never really done concept art in my head I know what the game looks like roughly
enough I'm like yeah this is this kind of level and it's like this and I have to
like I can't just say it I have to make images so that it can be like so that
when I give it to Charlie he knows like what sort of models to make and what
color they need to be and stuff like that and concept art sucks I don't know how
to do it I don't know how to like just bring something out in like a in like a
quick and quick and dirty like just because if because in my head it seems
so obvious like what it looks like I was like why would I need to draw it I just
say it's like it looks like this I have to draw it and it's like it's difficult
it's weird Ryan some sometimes things be difficult sometimes they true yeah yeah
like with me I on occasion when I go to sketch something it'll just turn out
pretty good the first try most of a time it's bad I have to fight I have to fight
my sketch after fight my sketch for hours and get a bunch of opinions and
then I can sort of coax it in a direction that's good and then maybe I'll
polish it up but they'll still it'll still have a lot of problems and the more
I work and the more I just hate it yeah I'm definitely not great at drawing
still like I can get a good drawing eventually but it takes way too much
fighting at the moment compared to other artists I see who and then like five
minutes I'll just have something that looks great something out yeah I'm like
what the fuck how did you do that a lot of people in the draw cast server are
like like phenomenal and they just like yeah they're just like making like
masterpiece sketches within the time limit of a draw cast I'm like fuck I
also feel that the longer I work on something usually the less good I
think it is yeah it's funny cuz cuz the reason it takes a long time is cuz
you're like you're I mean usually it's cuz like your sketch was your sketch was
was not great and then you're building on a you're building on like a an incomplete
or an unpolished foundation and then you just kind of got a like well the face
kind of like is it supposed to be here no that's not right this pose I'm getting
if I move the arm will it look a little bit no it still sucks that's what it
takes long long time that's it's bad there's been a few people who have seen
throughout my life who are like born illustrators and like doesn't matter how
old they are they just sort of are really good at like making an image really
well but they always hate their work and they're always talking about how it
sucks I'm like this you yeah insult me by saying that it's so annoying yeah
cuz I feel bad than what am I yeah yeah yeah I yeah some people some people some
people just can't take a compliment some people you'll tell them like oh this is
a really good drawing and they'll be like no it's bad it sucks you you have
shitty taste if you think my stuff is good you idiot yeah for forays is always
like fat a little bit not not to not in the annoying way like he'll just let's
kill him he'll just sit down like just throw some lines down and like it'll be
these really nice like shapes that have like really good like appeal and look
really good I'm like whoa that's really cool and he's like what the fuck you
talk about I just this is just some garbage I made I'm like it's good you
know yeah I do that as well sometimes it's not I don't I'm not proud of that I
do sometimes like draw and it's like yeah I can see that this has you know
potential this has some good stuff you've done some really but I'm not yeah I
don't I don't know how to judge my own work and so when I'm in a bad mood or if
I feel like a futile today oh it's all it's never gonna work out doesn't matter
how good I'm actually drawing and how much people are saying oh wow Pog it's
like just another day of being Gib being like the not good one just another
day being Gib so tragic just a little Gib in a big wide terrifying world
you know twi-pi drew just to twi-pi drew that that Virginia and then they they
they sent it as a voicemail on the last episode and it was great they didn't
tweeted at me so I could retweet it though those those and it's those those
Virginia having sex paintings they were so good the crutch tip it wasn't sent as
a voicemail I sent it in voice chat for oh right that's that's right but the
point is we did show it yeah yeah I I censored it so that LA's are could have
something to put on screen I don't know if you saw the censored version I did I
did went back and looked at the episode of that part you know if they're on if
they're even on Twitter maybe they're not I'll I'll ask Twi if she'll post them
at the time she said like I don't know if I'll post them actually and I'm like
okay but like maybe you should I thought they were worthy they were good they're
on a family trip when they get back I'll bully them I see oh wait maybe maybe
over time this episode's out did you you did you ever post that that video I
think it was a you would four eyes reacting to the yes I didn't see that
but I'll I I want to find your server I'm sorry I must have missed it but it's
okay yeah it is funny I I I know at some point I had over recordings that I guess
at some point I deleted for space but um because I was very intent on clearing
space on my computer at a certain point but yeah I'll put it there there it is
who drew that me that was so comic from a while ago I forget who drew it it was
like the artist was someone you it was drinking moth you linked them in the
last episode I think oh yeah oh yes yes yes I realized that drinking moth has
drawn a bunch of things that I remember over the over the years drinking moth
is a very cool PCP fan I like yeah yeah I am I realized as we were talking with
you I said wait I know wait I remember this person did the the what do you
call it the league of the the league of Nate fuckers is the one that jumps to
mind yeah it's gonna focus one that that's for panel the the thing I use in
the YouTube thumbnail was for panel where you were freaking out about the pig
the pig the pig is coming the pig is coming yeah yeah so scary shit man yeah
you know I had I don't I'm not gonna go in any detail about this I'm keeping this
a secret I have decided I have decided to stop being fucking stupid what yeah
that's your whole character I know not anymore I'm turning off turning on I'm
decided to stop being stupid and do something that might actually succeed in
the free market and I'm not gonna go and I'm not gonna say what that is porn but
I'm no it's not I'm sorry good guess good reasonable guess nah not
interested something even better if you can believe it I'm nice give I talk to
you about it I'm gonna do it oh I'm gonna try I'm gonna try to do it kind of
soon I'm just it needs a little it needs I I shouldn't dwell on it because I'm
not giving details and this is gonna be really annoying to be so vague but it's
gonna take set yeah what you told me was like there was a thing that I didn't I
didn't pry about I'm wondering like okay yeah we can't talk about it cuz it's
secretive I'll just say it's gonna take it's gonna take set up and it's gonna
take some money I'm gonna have to invest some money in getting it done and my
hope is to be I'm trying to figure out how to do it for little enough money that
I don't think that I think it will be turn up turn a profit is the is the is
the difficult thing I've been I've been making phone calls they have not led
anywhere yet but I'll keep I'll keep at it because I would kind of random phone
calls to random because I would like to do that when you are in in town when
you're visiting so I have that's in like a month so I'm just gonna try and get it
set up by then and we'll see how that works out but I'm excited to maybe not
be such a fucking failure maybe I don't know that's my goal that would be wild
if that happened I don't know the Ben Saints success arc but we'll but we'll
see we'll see one and maybe in a couple weeks I can tell you what I'm talking
about listeners let me not let me not dwell on this anymore let me not keep
us from the important topics at hand this week I've mostly just been like
trying to figure out pumpkin alley concept art for the pre-production phase
yeah how's that going and it's yeah I mean I've had these this this this level
that comes after the first level in my head and I'm like alright this is this
part and this is the next part and this is an enemy and I'll just draw down a
design for an enemy oh this enemy will block you a fun thing about pumpkin alley
is like thinking of ways that the enemies and and all the things can be like
designed around the ability that punk has which is burning stuff mm-hmm so yeah
this is like a sandy level they're sand so you use your fire breath to turn sand
into glass so you can you can heat up like sandy enemies turn them into glass
and then smash them hmm so it's like freezing them with fire yeah that's
neat that's very that's very neat so there's all sorts of like like thinking
of like a type of enemy that is just unique from all other types of enemies
and you have to deal with it in a certain way and just making it fit with the
location saying lower I will do this and that I haven't got I think the next thing
I need to do is like draw a literal like level plan layout of like the floor yeah
and stuff I don't really know anything about pre-production I'm just sort of
like doing things I assume will be helpful to refer to later and that's
it is that like I'm I just I just don't know what I'm doing it's the stupidest
thing ever yeah making a game making a game doesn't make any sense you just you
fuck around and then suddenly you're playing something like I don't understand
that is fucked up it's really fucked up when that happens that's really messed
up it's bad it's bad stop stop it oh my god I'm I'm I'm happy you
when when people I occasionally check if people like are playing pumpkin alley
the demo and I watch everything I can it's just nice seeing people enjoy it yeah
I have seen a slow a slow a continual slow trickle of a few more people downloading
phantoms revenge you know a couple people a day maybe here and there and that's
that's nice that's not what is this I wonder I wonder how high the number
will eventually go maybe a billion on a long enough time scale maybe I mean
extrapolated to infinity every human being on earth will eventually play the
game so for the last few days it's mostly been that and then occasionally
Elden Ring streaming and nothing nothing nothing is happening that's okay
that's fine I've been I've been doing the book I've been doing more I'm almost
done converting the phantoms revenge story beats to book pages it is so
tedious I hate doing it it's just like oh take screenshots and then arrange them
and then cut them up and post them on the page and it's like the most boring
thing and I hate it but I have like I'm almost done with it and then I can
actually pick paper and then I can actually maybe order a fucking test copy
and then I should really just buckle down and finish that because once that's
done I really can like start to get that book Kickstarter underway which is a big
kind of a big deal this I should probably try and try and finish that like
this week it shouldn't really take me that long but that's what I was doing
like this weekend yesterday I'm getting so close to having a hundred
Hades I got the I got the epilogue I got the basically true ending I'm a bit sad
because um you have the you get the true ending and then all of the gods set they
start saying different things to you because like your relationship to them
has changed a little bit and now I'm like oh well now I'll never hear every now
I'll never hear every scrap of voice dialogue in the entire game now now
won't yeah now like like the it's forever like your safe ball is like it
seems like it because start over what if you because because before I mean this
is a bit of a spoiler if you care about such things before all the gods think
you're trying to think you're trying well they think I don't know whatever
it's the point is they have a big party you have a big part you have a big
party and everyone makes friends and forgives each other and you're a big
happy family and it's nice so instead of like befuddlement and confusion that
like why are you still why are like why are you still not like broken out yet
Zagreus now they switch to be in like oh hey no hard feelings man hey love you
guys so it's like how many more times could I hear them say like hey man your
dad sucks fuck that guy here's a here's a gun that shoots lightning now they're
like oh hey no hard feelings have a gun nephew I'll never know yeah there's so
many lines there's so much there's so much dialogue I mean my family never gives
me guns yeah they give you like here hey hey nephew hey if you now you'll shoot
now you shoot tidal waves haha fuck your dad bye my dad is fucked up is that
true I would never if I mentioned on the PCP that my my birth father is a
conspiracy crazy man oh god yeah a lot of that what going around these days like
QAnon or these days probably but like way wilder shit than that if you can
believe it like flat earth I mean it's possible I yeah maybe maybe he's
secretive about that one I don't know when I was growing up I didn't see my
birth father much I was very little when my stepdad came in and he was a good
guy very cool guy yeah my birth father I would see him very occasionally you know
you know when he decided to visit or decided to be at his house when we tried
to visit him wasn't too great but I know I was a dumb kid I thought I liked him
a lot when I was really little because he would take us to McDonald's and buy
me an ice cream and my my parents wouldn't do that what more do you need and he
would run out of movie and would watch it and I'm like whoa time with him is so
good it's amazing it's like almost as if he only has to make an effort once a
year or less yeah yeah yeah yeah but uh yeah so I was I was unaware of the
conspiracy shit until I think in 2007 we moved into his well we were basically
spending a lot of time in his city because my grandmother the one extended
relative who I have any or I had any sort of close relationship with got
cancer because all my all my other relatives I feel pretty like I don't
feel like an oven that well but but my Nana I really liked her she always
used to make pancakes and so that was sad but whereas I was seeing my I see my
father a lot more because we were in his town that was your your your your
birth father's mom was your Nana no no no Nana was stepdad's mom I don't know
any of the family on my birth's father's side I okay I don't know what any of them
look like I I know one of them is called Nana 80 I think we call her I don't
even I don't think I've even spoken to her since I was like maybe five I have no
idea but um the they just in the same town by coincidence at Hamilton New
Zealand Hamilton so it's been a lot more time around him and then and then at
this point I'm like a 12 and I'm noticing he has fucking vision boards all
over his house that have like like borderline porn in them because he just
wants sex I guess and he just has always an appropriate posters yeah the
secret he was into the secret he tried it's like it's like I'm imagining like
the Charlie Charlie from Always Sunny with like you know strings like
conspiracy strings attached no no no a vision board is like it has to do with
the secret and the law of attraction all that that oh so it's like it's like a
collage of stuff that you want in your life yes and if you just stare at it
real hard it'll just fucking happen I guess I stare I stare at pornography a
lot so I was like noticing oh this man's a little bit of a sleaze ball this
I was the first inkling and then he's he tried to show us for secret and then he
tried showing us zeitgeist and then he tried show it which was all about like
9-11 conspiracies and then he tried showing us like footage of like like
it's just like gray like it just looks like gray like satellite footage looking
at clouds and there's like a dark spot in the cloud that like moves and
occasionally there's lights flashing and he's like you see that's the
mothership for us is in war with the aliens right now and then showing us
audio of a woman who is clearly fucking she's she's on some fucking drugs she's
on some fucking drugs who's like yeah and then princess Diana she didn't die in
a car crash those were dummies they um it was a ritual blood sacrifice from the
lizards for shape-shifting lizards um and yeah and I'm like how do you know I'm
on board how do you know that like where's her evidence you're just taking
the word of some random girl how does she know this he's like you sure she
didn't just fucking imagine it she sounds high as fuck and he's like nah nah
she just sounds so sure
cool and then my parents somebody who believes it then it has to be true
that's exactly and then my parents like I told my parents like he's I've been
seeing him more he's been saying a lot of weird shit and my parents like oh yeah
dude like so like after 9-11 we go to phone call from him saying the Jews the
Jews were behind this the Ark of the Covenant was on the plane you know oh
my god wow okay um but but then I guess later so yeah Ark of the Covenant on
the 9-11 planes that's that was his original conspiracy for that and then
it was they weren't planes they were missiles and the wings were edited in
using a you know Hollywood movie magic you know I've never heard I've never
heard either of those before so wait wait is it the Ark of the Covenant opened
and that's what melted the steel beams like I like it melted the the Nazi's
faces yeah yeah like like first it's the Ark of the Covenant was on the plane
then it's there were no planes there were missiles you know despite the fact
that thousands of people witnessed it no at everyone in New York was paid and
all every video footage they took they edited they did movie Hollywood movie
magic on it and faked it to make the missiles look like planes missiles are
not the size of planes I don't think he realizes how small missiles are they're
really not that big not technology you just put a PNG on it and you have a
big old plane and then it's oh the work the planes are real but there was a
controlled demolition at the base which is not what the video footage shows the
building collapses from the top down not from the bottom like into itself but
whatever so it's so bizarre that people like decide like it's it's like thinking
about it as like a coping mechanism it's so obvious why they decide that things
that could be distressing have to have been like controlled demolitions and not
like just the world being chaotic yeah they don't want to like they never get
conspiratorial about something that isn't like a serious problem or like a
big chaotic thing I mean there are conspiracies there are conspiracies like
that but my lot of things these people care about it's always to explain like
horrible things happening tragedies and like shootings all fake never happened
that kind of thing yeah it can't it can't possibly be that the world is is it's
just crazy sometimes it has to have been a secret person involved in it and if
only I beat them up the world will be safe and nice yeah it's true he's
earned to aliens as well yeah the best one though this is the best one I'll
never I actually forgot about this for like 10 years until I remembered so it's
years like maybe 2007 or 2008 we're visiting them we put on Pirates of a
Caribbean free he's never seen it and the Pirates of a Caribbean free it opens
you know you have a bunch of pirates you know being executed they're being
taken to the gallows and they're seeing a sea shanty and like they're just being
like executing like five at a time and then the next lot goes up executed next
lot goes up executed they're just hanging a bunch of them and my dad's
watching this and he's like oh my god oh my god this is this is what they did
to the victims of 9-11 they weren't on the planes that there are no people on
those planes the real victims were flown to Mars where they were executed just
like this that's like that that is like crazier than I would have expected
like what how would you say that how would you say that every time you see
every time you watch Pirates of a Caribbean free just remember this
happened on Mars they flew the planes there to kill the people it's like the
plot of Adventure Time basically I want to know where to happen if we showed
him spirit science he probably believes the moon is fake never asked me about
that it really it really does sound like yeah sound like they're just any any
he'll just he'll just believe show him show anything that sounds a little weird
and like the the moon explodes and it's like Eggman's robot and it's like that's
true probably it is true there it is true that they just believe anything
because they believe contradictory shit too like well they're a hundred percent
like all wars fake all wars manufactured there's a one-world government the 12
fat the 12 Jewish families the Rothschilds and the blah blah blah who
control everything the 12 banks they rule the world and all politics is just a
distraction I'll say that but at the same time they'll be like yeah we have to
kill bin Laden you we we got to get them over fucker
even though 9-11 was fake to justify the war that would be fake but no it's
actually real it's just okay yeah it's like it's like just like whatever I
don't know it really is just just whatever it makes them feel better to
think about anything as it seems to be the through line and and generally it
makes them feel better to think that someone's in control even if like
nominally it's bad people that's probably why they say fuck bin Laden
because bin Laden is like a known person that is like oh it's the bad guy to get
the bad guy I gotta get the bad guy and it's like that's kind of true if there's
someone you can point to be like this is the guy that caused that problem yeah we
can get him just want to have someone to get make sense they should play call
duty you should play video games I agree oh my god I agree there's always a bad
guy in a video game I just remembered another thing he told me he's like you
know you know why in movies I've been studying film you know why in movies
like darkness is associated with evil it's because two thousand years ago back
in the time of Jesus at night there were monsters there were monsters roaming
around like giant like jackals and in creatures of a night that would eat
people and eat babies every day and we learn to associate these these these
these satanic forces with the darkness and all this shit they just used to be
monsters everywhere the truth is that in the dark sometimes you stub your toe
because you can't see it and so people thought we shouldn't walk around at night
and then the dark became became avoidable you must avoid the night in the
dark there's a wolf and it goes oh and it bites you sometimes it goes awoo
sometimes you fall off a cliff sometimes you get cold and there's no fire
actually every time so I'm sorry he said that there used to be like real like
darkness demons in the world and that's yeah like every RPG ever well like eco
yeah I just every RPG ever just like RPG monsters just used to roam they would
just like appear at night and yeah well where do you think all the idea for all
those RPGs came from that's that's like um what is it I I'd heard about it
elsewhere but Dan Olson talked a little about it in I think it was the I think
it was the Flat Earth video yeah how like the the the cons like the conspiracy
mindset like the Flat Earth and the QAnon stuff is all like it all just kind
of like pulls it all just kind of pulls stuff including from like fiction
including like they'll take some tidbit of esoteric like mythology and use
that to explain like oh yeah this explains like the story of Jack and the
Beanstalk or something where did Jack and the Beanstalk come from oh well
it's because Giants the Nephilim and you know the the world tree was the Beanstalk
and stuff like it's like it's like it's literally just a fairy tale but
sometimes they'll sometimes they'll use that as evidence for something they do
they do get obsessed with fiction though don't they like they'll read like
fiction books and say though this is real like my dad like the Da Vinci code was
like a documentary yeah I think so they're just looking for for something
to latch on to that was me that was me as like a kid that was me like only I
didn't think it was real but I would think like I don't know this but he did
I think it's is real I would I would think I would think oh this character is
described as wearing like a long red coat with a high collar I should get a
long red coat with a high collar that's real that would look cool in real life
and it was true it worked that's it's uh it's uh it's pretty pretty wacky
there's some real wackiness in the world today these days think about how
like everything all the stories was was written by cowards who couldn't take
shit they go out into the dark they go out into the dark and they're like oh
somebody died because they fell into a bog well they didn't just trip and fall
into a bog you see it was a bog demon monster and they'll grab you and pull
you under oh yeah and that's the story and the kids they gather around they
believe it and only the cowards tell these stories because those are the
only guys who survive and then they invent all this mythology and then
thousands of years later people make video game monsters in real life about
those stories and then thousands of years later JK Rowling took all those
monsters and made them a parable about why slavery is good put them all in that
book oh yeah sold a billion copies my my dad my dad is pretty smart pretty
educated guy but he is he has shown a bit of susceptibility to pretty pretty
normal widespread you know boomer like moral panic stuff like he thought he
thought video games would rot your brain he thought D&D was like a little he
thought D&D was a little bit satanic just a little bit I was gonna say it
sounds a little like my stepdad but not quite he played a lot of games no my my
dad my dad probably played D&D at some point I feel like he must have maybe
maybe he was a little bit too old there was a point in my childhood where
parents my parents were like magic school bus witchcraft but then they got
over it cuz they went to university and then they were like my dad was a
little bit like my dad was a little bit like I this seems a little satanic but
he didn't really didn't really do anything about it he just kind of
vaguely guilted you like yeah you shouldn't hmm you might go to hell well
that's the free market you didn't feel that strongly about weird actually I
always thought like man if you really think the devil is at work here like I
would I would really want to do something about that but I mean that's
that's just me maybe the maybe the devil ain't so bad yeah my parents go over
that stuff eventually or at least they did with me like they were very strict
on my sister if my sister listened to like gothic music like like metal music
or whatever they would like freak out and moral panic at her and tell her she
needs to go see Jesus and shit but I would listen to the same music and they
would just be like oh that's cool yeah listen to metal music you will turn into
metal you will become magnetic yeah you turn a metal Mario it's and that song
will play like it'll play forever if you if you play if you play if you play
cradle of filth backwards it sounds like yeah I bought a cradle of filth
album and my dad I think I think I've had a cradle of filth album we were
listening to it in my basement with my friends we were over for D&D and my dad
just made just made just a sarcastic look comments like hmm you guys listening
to devil worship music down there and I was like no dad it's it's it's art dad
you understand honey and sulfur is a banger though at least the opening of
that song is a banger I don't even remember what that is I'll be honest I
was just I was just I was just into that stuff to look cool for my friends I was
I was I don't think I was I think I like some of it I like some music that I my
friends got me into genuinely other stuff I was like oh my friends are all
goth I should get into goth stuff too I didn't pose enough I was too into like
the one band I mean I was I was I was too like dad rock focus because like I
like Led Zeppelin and the Beatles and and and like David Bowie and Elton John
and all that and everyone was listening to contemporary bands that were coming
out right now with the hot new 90s tracks of what 2000s music and they were like
yeah look at this listen to this what do you like Gibb they didn't say Gibb and I
would say um you know stuff cuz they didn't they didn't know the Beatles but
I didn't want to be like um you don't know the Beatles I didn't want to be like
I don't want to be like a freak who likes the Beatles I was like the Beatles
that's like bug that's stupid what the fuck that was me that's a bug that's like
a glitch in the system why would you name yourself the Beatles is it because
beat like music has a beat are you dumb are you trying to be clever get out took
me a long time to realize that the name had an a in it and that it and that it
was a joke look at these bowl cut boys they're not for me I said they were not
for you they were for young girls in the 60s 50s it's crazy it's crazy listening
to live performances from like Elvis or the Beatles back then and understanding
oh this is where the term fangirl came from yeah like just like they were
screams so fucking loud it's nothing like today people faint in it's like they'd
never seen a boy before basically maybe they hadn't maybe they weren't allowed I
guess I would have been you're so is it is it is it nothing like today does that
do they not the like the way they scream is like it sounds like they're being
murdered it's like blood curling like where today it's just like people
cheering like like and they chair a lot but like it's some of the clips I've
seen it's like like they're shrieking that's very they're shrieking it was
loudest shrieking they're like fainting they're crying and shitting and coming
you know all of that at the same time ironically in the front row but you can't
you know like you can't hear like the music over it like almost that that's
why they started doing studio albums more is because they couldn't like
literally couldn't do live performances because they couldn't hear
themselves it was just like a big like screaming thing it's like okay well I
don't like this I liked the music I want to do music and then they stopped they
stopped appearing live forever exactly until they didn't until they appeared dead
as we all must I do remember like a couple times would say what's your
favorite band say oh Led Zeppelin oh the Beatles and they would say oh cool
because they knew what that was they didn't care and I didn't follow up with
anything because I didn't know what to say and that was it I should have posed
more I should have been like yeah I'm into whatever you're into you know what
are you into I'm like I'm into as I lay dying and they're like as I laid as I lay
crying more like haha and then yeah yeah I would have to and then I will
literally be laying there dying because of being beaten to a pulp you don't like
cannibal corpse you don't like amazing songs such as I come blood get out
cannibal corpse I'm gonna cannibalize your corpse kills you eats you oh no
very war yeah hard that's hard for to as hard like with blood hard blood with
blood bones nice I don't I don't like murder I disavow murder and cannibalism
you're brave you're so brave thank you more people should do it why have why
why I'm the nostalgia critic why why has the nostalgia critic why has the
nostalgia critic not formerly disavowed murder and Nazism why has he not
released a statement why has he not formally condemned the Russian invasion
of Ukraine yeah he can review smiling friends but he can't review Putin's
actions you took the word every every reviewer has to has to review every
political every every newspaper live react to like it's it's like it's like
wait a minute nostalgia chick what are you doing talking about the the current
day climate of the of Russia that led to the invasion of Ukraine I already
reviewed this this war but the forces have overtaken Mario pole the Azov
battalion well I guess we'll have to collab about it hello I'm the
nostalgia critic live in Moscow Linkara what are you doing here what are you
what are you doing in my doing here what am I doing in this and this act of
minefield what am I doing in the Azov battalion can I be in this war they do
like the what was it like that first like channel awesome like reviewer huge
collab was it called kick ass here where they got everyone flew them out they
should do that but they should fly everyone out to Ukraine to fight in the
war to kick and then like film it just and just bring like a like the
journalists like not like a film but like bring like reporters to just follow
yeah the cast of kick assia and and whatever just like fighting as training
as recruits and like you know taking points or whatever they're like costumes
and their plastic guns yeah underneath they're like you know helmets and like
body armor and stuff the stakes the stakes would be so high oh yeah did you
see that um Andrew Callahan formerly known as all gas no breaks just fucking
went to Ukraine oh I don't know that which I'm not sure which guy I've heard
that name all gas no breaks before it's a guy who would just show up to random
events usually like events like flatter of conferences and like or just like you
know just just any place where he would expect he would find crazy people and he
would just walk up to randoms in the street point a microphone at them and
just let them say whatever the fuck and wait is that the guy from channel five oh yeah channel
five of Andrew Callahan yeah yeah that's yeah yeah I I have seen him he made a video in
car key no not car key in Ukraine is in Ukraine somewhere yeah it was like a like an air siren
went off and they went to hide and there's a cat the family was bringing their cat and it was good
yeah this this guy this guy is cool um he he's met some fucking weird people
he just goes where the where stuff happens and just interviews random people and it's interesting
yeah proper journalism that's that's that's real
it is it's very well I guess Gonzo journalism what does Gonzo mean I think if you go and you
join the war and you report on it yeah I think I would call that Gonzo journalism
I don't know if he joined the war he just kind of showed up and just with a microphone yeah I
don't think he's killing anyone I think he's just on the scene oh well then I'm not sure
not sure if that counts then
damn war is bad it is no I like it more war please can we invade I respect another country
I don't I may not agree but I respect your opinion maybe it's good to some people
I think we should invade Wales and finally like kill that dragon slay that dragon somebody's
got to do it yeah St George was like the the the the the patron saint of England and he is like
the guy who slayed a dragon but Wales is right there and the dragon is alive I think we gotta
we gotta solve this problem we gotta end this all all of the people in Elden Ring are Welsh
so that's what I'm basically doing and what by playing Elden Ring I'm killing the Welsh
you're redistributing the Welsh like like cutting them up into pieces and distributed
in like redistributing their arms and legs all around
it's true they got some great accents in in Elden Ring I wouldn't know I've not really seen any of
the game still I think they're they're largely all Welsh Welsh accents and a few like the British
ones not sure there was that a fucking voicemail this was a long time ago I only remember it because
I used to in the pig fucker thing the pig fucker the interrupting deaf pig there there's a guy who's
like I really want a Welsh speaking family oh and I don't even know what I remember that voicemail
like what the point of it was I just remember that I had the pig come in but I remember it it's weird
wasn't there that one guy in I think the original Dark Souls there's like a guy who uses like a
like a Welsh or Scottish greeting Aishimai that guy yes the Aishimai guy who I never even found
in my no maybe I did I think maybe I found him later you you find him either he's on that bridge
in yeah he's under the bridge in Firelink Shrine or earlier you can see him just before you enter
Blighttown from the depths right down that that weird guy that weird little tinker mask dude
he's from Elden Ring they're all connected there's that one guy from Bloodborne in the DLC of Dark
Souls one that's what I'm thinking and there's that Samurai looking guy in the uh in the old uh
what do you call it Darkroot Garden bit you can talk to he's from Sekiro wait Samurai looking guy
Samurai looking guy in Darkroot Garden I don't remember yeah um when you talk to you know the
place where there's like all those NPC like people and the ghosts in the forest that attack you
it's like the the fighter the cleric the the ranger oh yeah yeah yeah with the cat yeah if you join
the cat covenant a samurai and a ninja will like appear just outside the building and you can go
talk to him and then later you can find him down in the bottom of Blighttown and like you can buy
his weapon I think oh huh don't remember that yeah he's a cool guy nifty nifty um it's been yeah
been a while since I uh since I played in these souls the only thing I've really seen I've seen
bits and pieces of Elden Ring and I've seen um is it is it named Radon I've seen Radon
yeah Radon I I I haven't beaten him yet but I have fought him he's an interesting
interesting battle yeah oh I've seen um oh and of course I've seen uh let me solo her
oh yeah that yeah I've heard of that I haven't seen I I haven't looked at like the boss because I
don't know what boss it is it's probably like one of the hardest ones I know what that that that boss
I've seen art of that boss I have not actually seen the that boss looks like the fucking um digimon
yeah angel looks like angel woman angel angel woman yeah yeah she does millennia got the valkyrie
helmet yeah she looks great looks awesome uh yeah I'm um Elden Ring sounds really good uh
you said on twitter the other day that it makes it's like the feeling of exploring
world of warcraft yeah I that that was like oh that sounds cool that's a good way this that
that's an appealing way it it really does feel like because like I mean like old school world
of warcraft specifically because like in newer versions of world of warcraft the quests are
very railroad-y and like take you on a very specific path and there are lots of cutscenes and
and like like you feel like you're going through a theme park or a tour and it doesn't feel like a
big world that you're exploring but older world of warcraft quests they're just sort of like
it go here and do this and so for a lot of a lot of the gameplay of early world of warcraft you're
just sort of walking around and killing things and moving and killing things and looking around
and killing things and being like oh look at that building look at castle look at this it feels very
similar in Elden Ring because that's basically what you're doing you just you kill things because
they would kill you otherwise and you're just got you got a horse and you're just going
I watched um I think it was kind of an older video I watched the never knows best video
about a Final Fantasy uh which one's the online one is it 14 14 yeah yeah and then I think I
watched an older video of his about it's just about MMOs like in general and um I think it was older
and uh he pointed something out that I hadn't really thought about but it's like um old like
if you were playing like playing MMOs now like people know how to play them like people have
there are guides you can read that will just explain to you like the the optimal way to level
up your character like if you were playing like when World of Warcraft came out like nobody
knew that and no guides existed and everyone was just figuring it out and fucking around
and I got it that sounds so much more fun than like look look up a guide that like tells you
like the optimum spell rotation I mean yeah that's definitely what happened with World of Warcraft
Classic when they brought that out because you got like thousands upon thousands of super veteran
players who couldn't wait to get back to reliving their early days in World of Warcraft but yeah
but you can never really do it again yeah the player base has changed so much that even if
all of the content is the same the way the game is played is completely different yeah like everybody
min-maxed everything like the the old game used to be unbalanced and so everybody was choosing the
correct like class and like spec thing to do the maximum damage and if you weren't if you didn't want
to play as that you would just die because the game was just not balanced for every class
back in the day so it would just suck if you didn't want to play like the optimal thing and
everybody was playing the optimal thing because they wanted to get all of the stuff as fast as
possible because they knew how and it's just like a lot of people didn't like it but I didn't mind
because I never was good at World of Warcraft in terms of like high level rating or pvp I just
like the place so I was just walking around and I would I played for like a couple months with my
brother we had two torrents and we were just like I was a shaman and he was a warrior and we would just
like do little quests in little places and be like oh we're backing each other up it sounds
really fun I played I played I played a few months in the summer of Wrath of the Lich King
and I leveled up my character and I explored the world and I and I fucked around I didn't
play it that optimally I was just I was just fucking around that was just some way to do it
yeah I was just getting like I would get a staff and I would be like oh this staff looks really cool
it's not as good as that other staff but like I just really like how this one looks I'm gonna keep it
uh and uh uh and then I got to the end and I got a max level and I was like oh time to raid
and then I did a couple raids I was like oh this isn't fun at all I'm done game over by uh yeah
it's really weird how the raids like they step up the the skill floor requirements so high
from just playing the game solo or with a small group or just like casually going through it and
suddenly all of a sudden I'm getting yelled at for playing wrong yeah all of a sudden it's like
like the game hadn't really like set you up to do a raid no by the time you're able to do them
and it's like it's so I always remember like raiding being like a surefire way to feel like
shit and know that you need to do a lot of work before you're even close to being ready
and I'm like you know what I don't want to do a lot of work I'm not gonna do the raids and I never
did yeah that was like um when I when I played League of Legends I played Warwick and I kind of
figured out how to play Warwick I was like yeah all right I'm sort of getting it and then my my
friends who I was playing with were like yeah good okay now you now you have to do that with
like every character because like uh you need you need to know how all your enemies are gonna
play too so you have to know every character you don't you don't have to do that with every
character that's ridiculous I mean they didn't I you know the point is they were saying like
I realized that like there was too much work to be done to be good at the game and you just
to have fun like if you want to like be like real good that's not fun fun is just
having like two or three characters who you're good at who you just specialize in and like yeah
you'll get to know how to do with other characters just by playing against them you don't have to
play a character to understand them like to like to play against them necessarily um I liked
I was the fucking I was like the the tentacle thing um I was Velcaz uh the hentai one whoa
Velcaz I remember uh this this fucking so to show it I always use this skin because it looks
real fucking sick I don't remember this guy at all uh he wasn't played very often um but like
you have to like do geometry and shit because he shoots out a thing and then it splits and
shoots off at a right angle so you have to like shoot your abilities diagonally to like
hit people um and stuff like that I I just had a lot of fun with him um all my like um I forget
what they're fucking called the the little the little things you do that give you a little
outside the game where you can like speck like for extra points of damage or whatever the fuck
forget what they're called your your skill tree or whatever the fuck I called that hentai supreme
um I was I just I was just always joking about tentakling people and they gave him a rework
that just made him really strong and then he was way overpowered and then they just kept
buffing him for years and years they just kept buffing him they never nerfed him ever because
for some reason he was unpopular but I I was fucking great at him and I would always be really
well um that's funny that sounds fun it is fun um I have like I don't know why I picked warwick
I didn't like think he looked cool or anything I think he just seemed simple I think someone
just told me he was like simple I was like okay well I'll do that then yeah yeah my best experience
I had with League of Legends was an experience I recorded it was the first time I played IRF
which is ultra rapid fire it's that April Fool's game mode where you can just all your
your cooldowns are basically nothing you can just spam everything and you have infinite mana
and it's just a clusterfuck my first round of that I fucking destroyed everything it was so much fun
and I never topped that again and then eventually I just stopped playing League unless it was IRF
and then even then I stopped playing after a while and then Kai sold his account that was worth like
$10,000 and only got like 2k for it wow we both like hard quit about a year ago
yeah well I hadn't really been playing for a few years but um he still was but yeah he even
sold his account finally and we're fucking done with that shit no more League of Legends
yeah I realized it wasn't something I really wanted to sink a lot of time into it's just not
worth it it's just it's just frustrating it is just a frustrating experience most of the time
I had League of Legends and Clash of Clans are exactly the same thing I don't I don't have no idea
what Clash of Clans even is I've never seen it or played it or seen anything I just think of it
as like oh it's like vaguely medieval fantasy wacky to kill each people and it's like you play
on your phone and keep thinking of League of Legends as the one of those mobile games
I've just seen the little blonde viking guy yeah Clash of Clans is the screaming viking man whose
head is like somewhat square shaped I imagine it's like some kind of RTS sort of thing like you
control your your troops on a little field or something there's a lot of like RTS mobile games
and they could be a tower defense it's just sort of like I'll never play them yeah I'm offended
by the art style gives me the same vibes even though I have seen footage of it and I know that
it's like a game that has more to it it's just so like oh god you is that his hair or a helmet
it's his hair that doesn't look like that's just how hair looks in Clash of Clans Clash of Clans
is offensively unappealing that's a fucking playmobil hair that's fucking clip on playmobil
that's exactly right yeah something's weird it's his it's his eyebrows too his hair just becomes
his eyebrows I feel like it's deliberately I feel like it's yeah I feel like it's deliberately meant
to look like a helmet and hair at once I think we're falling for its trap they're trying to trip
you up speaking of marzipan uh I made I'm making gummies again I tried yeah I started
that again and I I had tried this before and the results had not been good but I gave it another
shot and it actually worked out pretty well it was using a corn fiber instead of isomolto
ligosaccharide oh my god isomolto licoficorica I'm also isomolgo ligosaccharide I think I think my
old approach was like stupid um because what I would do is I would take the fiber before it was
imo sometimes I would I would try I tried corn fiber and didn't work and I would take the fiber and
I would put it in water and I would cook it and I would reduce it down into a syrup and then I would
use the syrup to make gummies and I think that's just an unnecessary step and a step that can can
go wrong and that it like introduces like more uncertainty into the outcome this week I've
just been making little tiny batches and it's not even bothering to make the syrup I just put it all
in one I just put the water in the pan and then I just combine the ingredients right in the pan
make it all in one go and like it's fine it works fine and I'm taking notes I have a piece of paper
on my wall here that has all the different batch it has all the ingredient amounts scroll and there's
little red notes that like comparing like okay to make this one like I reduced the corn syrup like
this one I increased the gelatin or whatever um so I'm getting there I feel like I'm already like
pretty close to a to a to a pretty a pretty successful recipe I'm doing a little more
formulaic than I was last time uh and you know what the corn fiber corn fiber is way cheaper than
isomaltoligosaccharide ever was so if it works out with corn fiber then that's just it's just
better so fuck you china for not importing anymore that stuff yeah that's china's biggest mistake
I wouldn't say so yeah and I'm making and they're paying for it now they'll never get
so these are these are no longer keto gummies they're just gummies they're not keto well yeah
they're not keto I'm not focusing on the keto because I'm making them with I'm including
corn syrup and pectin but and pectin contains dextrose but my goal is to get them tasting good
and then I'm gonna try and like adjust the recipe as much as I can to get the sugar content down as
low as I can so like how can I do it with the least corn syrup and the least pectin
so they will hopefully be they will hopefully be low sugar they will probably not be no sugar
but we'll see I made a batch yesterday that was cherry flavor and I put too much of the
cherry flavoring in and it kind of burns my mouth when I eat it um but that's fine the consistency
is great it's it's awesome uh do you have like molds that you're pouring them into yeah well didn't
you didn't you ever see those pictures of the worms that I used to make oh yeah no I forgot that you
made yeah I have the worm molds I also have square molds but like those those make the squares that
they make or they're too big like I don't like biting into like a big rectangle of it and I also
have gummy bear molds but those are too small and they're too annoying like it's really gummy bears
though yeah it's just I don't I don't like how small they are I like to bite off the the tip of a
worm uh and they're also just hard to clean and like they're hard it's hard to like get the liquid
into the bear and you gotta put you gotta take a little eyedropper and put it in a one bear two
bear three bear and you gotta do that like like 40 times yeah yeah I guess if it's like yeah there's
a lot of them make it it's the making the because you've got to do it by hand the bears are annoying
the worms are like okay just do it like 12 just make like pouring it into 12 molds takes like
two minutes it's fine uh so I'm sticking sticking with worms uh for the time for the time being
uh so that's exciting that's very exciting I can't wait to potentially taste one I guess maybe
by the time you come visit I will have a recipe and maybe uh yeah well that's that's exciting
um I'll give I'll give everyone some at that thing that I'm not gonna say what it is
oh everyone who attends uh now I'm talking about attendance I feel like maybe I'm giving the game
away but I'm not gonna it's a wedding wedding if you are at a I'm gonna have a wedding at a bowling
alley um sure my my new project yeah my new you're gonna marry the bowling pin the sexy
bowling pin the new the new the new direction for my career I've decided to stop fucking up
I've decided to actually do what the cuss what the consumer wants I'm gonna get married that'll
make me much more electable as president of the United States statistically speaking we've never
had an unmarried president um yeah I guess so and think of and think of the tax breaks you know
imagine if you're filing filing jointly that's where the real money's at
imagine if your president had a dry penis couldn't possibly be my America I'm gonna vomit just
thinking about it mr president sir mr president sir the american people demand that you wet that
dick
oh it needs to be well laid well laid it's why ben Shapiro it's about ben Shapiro will never be
president because you know his wife his wife's pussy is dry we all know that's true he thinks
having a wet pussy is a medical condition Jesus yeah did you have you uh seen uh you know that
movie don't look up nope you know I've heard I know all that I've heard my sister gave it a glowing
review and then I saw your movie sucks shit all over it and I'm like I don't know this could go
ever way I didn't see any I had I had heard people talking about it on twitter my my dad
thought it was great and he got me to watch it uh over um I think it was a I think it was on my
birthday yeah it was one of my birthday when I went to give them he was like let's watch
don't look up it's great and I was like yeah all right sure and it was uh it was it's about um okay
it's about uh it's it's basically about what if a meteor was gonna hit the earth and the
what what would happen and the answer they come up with is we would all die because the Trump
administration is incompetent and they would they would bungle it and maybe that's true maybe
that's true but it's very it's very it's very like lib it's a very liberal movie and I mean that with
a capital L I mean that in the pejorative sense um it's very but I don't know there's a part where
up just look at your phones Pokemon go to the polls uh it's it's very it's very like
zoomers these days are just zoom into the grave their speed running life that's a bit true it's
very much about like we just we need to we need to trust the scientists and like it's true it's
science is good science is good I kind of I kind of agree it's very smug about it um
but uh the the uh there's a part where the the who might my dad took a careful note to point out
to me like oh yeah this this is the Trump parallel this character is the done and I'm like yes I
understand I get it but Trump is a woman in this movie and there's a part where she like
starts smoking in the oval office and she's like you know they told me on the campaign trail I had
to quit smoking for my image but then you know there was like a candid some candid photos leaked
of me smoking so I just started smoking in public guess what happened my my ratings went up 53%
people love that I kept it real haha and it's and and I guess and I guess you you the viewer
are supposed to shake your head and go uh no decorum this administration has no decorum at all
it's true it is true it's it's hard it's it's rough because I I had to I had to agree with a lot of
of the points the movie was trying to make I had to be like yep that's true but it's it did have that
it did have this at the attitude of like if only like a 40 like a bit a bit hardy and a bit like
darn if only if only if only we didn't have this clown in the White House then we'd be we don't
we don't we trust the science and then we'd we'd all be we'd all be coming up put we'd all be
pushing up daisies no that's not what I meant um you know coming up millhouse it's all very much
like it's just because one singular bad actor is the president that's why we have all these problems
we need to unelect trump that was like half I mean you know it's also about like you know
capitalism bad you know fucking rich inventor weirdo elon musk bezos guy is also a problem
uh you know it was fine it was fine but yeah the I saw it got the movie got like glowing reviews
but then everyone I saw on twitter was like bitching about it and I saw like Ben you have to watch this
movie I'm like oh god I saw those the the title mean like don't look up is in like don't look up the
science like don't look it up on your it means it means it means don't look up at the sky because
there's a meteor that's gonna hit us for like double meaning like don't look it up like don't
don't bother because you don't do that you don't look up the science these days I think it's just
I don't know I think you're reading more into it than is actually I think it just means don't
look at the sky I I saw like my sister talked to me about the movie at length in a call and
gave gave it she gave it a really good sell and I'm like but in the back of mind I'm like yeah my
sister very different like taste in movies these days so I don't know um I saw your movie sucks
talk about and he was like like yeah like don't necessarily disagree with the message or anything
there's just a way it's it's very heavy-handed like very heavy-handed yeah and he showed off
some of the editing in the movie like the way they like show like wow ha ha internet ha ha memes
I'm out and like just shoving like shit in your face it's very boomer-esque oh yeah this is how
boomers see the internet like kind of thing yeah it was it was there's a yeah there's a whole part
it's like oh this the lady goes on a talk show and like freaks out about the meteor and it goes
viral and people make memes about her yeah it's very much like and it's just like draw a fucking
mustache on her whatever it's like well this is what memes are like right kids yeah yeah I'm cool
it was it was it was a boomer's idea of like oh something went viral and became a meme on the
internet that's for sure uh it's I I overlooked that I just I just was like yeah I get it yeah I get
it I get what it's trying I get what it's trying to convey to me I'll probably watch this on point
I'm curious because it's I am interested in BA's um so it's fine it's fine and it remind I mean the
first part where they were like doing astrophysics brought me back to my old college days in the
astronomy laboratory uh those those those and I thought damn I should have fucking I should have
stayed in academia and got my master's degree I should have fucking made something of myself
now just watch 60 symbols and deep sky videos and sigh and think this could have been me
I don't even know what that is oh it's um it's youtube channels um
have you have you seen those there's a lot of youtube channels that do this um number file
does this um like a lot there's that blonde guy brady harrin or harrish harrish something
that's the number guy of file guy yeah he he's just this he's just this he's like oh like he just
like he just interviews professors and asks them questions and like it goes on number file or it
goes on 60 symbols or it goes on deep sky or um there's the professor the chemistry professor guy
who has like the funny like white curly hair um but yeah um I'll just I'll just have a quick look
I'm not not super familiar they um they're just videos where they just go to a university
and they'll find like a cool professor and they'll just ask them a bunch of questions about like
a specific galaxy or a specific star or a specific black hole or something and they'll
just talk about it it's just interesting cool stuff and like they'll they'll show off like some
of the science that they personally did sometimes um and it's just I don't know I I like this content
this is my nerdy shit that I meant to um that's interesting no I haven't seen what what is the
M number stand for is that like a Messier Messier Messier Messier objects that's yeah Messier was a
guy who had a telescope 100 years maybe 200 years ago who just pointed at the sky and it's like these
are stars but this thing's blurry I don't know what the fuck this is is it a cloud is it a shroud
we'll never know and then some of those things turned out to be nebulous some of them turned out
to be galaxies um yeah or other stuff so did he number them yeah yes he he just made note he made
note of just a whole bunch of things in the sky that he didn't know what they were and then they
were the Messier objects and then people eventually figured out them and so now they're called like
oh m m 72 m 88 or whatever yeah oh yeah one is the the bode's galaxy or something such and said
the the kiwi fruit galaxy I've never seen that before yeah I guess I guess I have a neighbor I
guess if there's been oh wow like some of these videos are quite old yeah I don't upload super
frequently which is good I like subscribing to channels there's only so many Messier objects
Messier objects I'm not actually maybe you're maybe I'm saying it wrong Messier Messier
I don't know I I enjoy channels that make good content and upload not too frequently
because then my sub box is clear but there's only good stuff yeah I like I like a good channel
that uploads uh you know four times a year but each time it's like a big good video that I want to
watch yeah these videos are very chill they're like just comfy space is freaky I was a little
disappointed to look at my uh analytics I looked at my youtube analytics just yesterday
and I looked at the I looked at the the money I looked at the money that my videos make and I
I I compared them all and I figured out like a roughly they do all make about the same amount
of money like per view like give or take and it was way less than I thought it was like
less it was like less than a dollar per like 2000 views is what it worked out to
huh that's that's low I thought that was low I thought it was more like a dollar per thousand
no not so yeah your cpm is like around 50 cents or lower than
yeah I guess so my cpm when I was doing the my little pony animations on nightfall studios was
like 20 cents it was really bad like 5000 views would be a dollar um it wasn't great I remember
looking at my thing like not too long ago and it was higher than that it's different for everyone
but why does it change what what does it mean a huge portion is watch time um yeah channels that
like are advertiser friendly and have good watch time will get as high as five cpm like 10 times
what I had so like they could get like five dollars per thousand views rather than like 50 cents or
less um like so channels like mystery beast for example get ridiculously high cpm so they don't
not only do I get like tens of millions of views per video but they also get like really high money
per view more than other people it's fucked how dare they okay so I'm I'm looking at my
hypocrite channel and it says 645 6.45 dollars cpm your playback base cpm wait 6.4 it's not point
six dollars is your cpm six is that super high whoa my i don't know okay my playback based cpm
it's telling me it's like seven or eight yeah seven or eight dollars
that's wait well that's that's really high then that's not that's not right if I feel like the
number is like a different type of number that it's showing us and not the one you were talking
about like it looks like maybe yeah like playback based cpm what is playback based I mean what is
excluding I'll hover over that thing it says playback based cpm means effective playback
based cost per mile and tells you how much advertisers paid per thousand monetized playbacks
oh for monetized playbacks so it doesn't count playbacks if it weren't monetized
to calculate your playback based cpm the total revenue from ads is divided by estimated monetized
playbacks an estimated monetized playback happens when a viewer sees at least one ad
impression when watching one of your videos okay so that's like when you have an ad how
much you get but so like for all the people using ad blocker that number goes down a lot oh okay so
it's seven or eight dollars per thousand times the ad was shown not times the video was viewed
okay yeah I usually think of um so is that what rpm is okay so yeah yeah rpm oh yeah damn rpm means
revenue per per mil and tells you how much you earned per thousand views which for me is still
four dollars and ninety three cents which still is not right because uh I mean let me just uh pick
out uh okay uh so literally ad blocker taking two ferd of my right two ferds of my revenue
that's what this shows me that's uh son sonichu 102 advanced christary has almost 200 k views it has
192 k views estimated revenue is just a little over a thousand dollars so that's did I do the math
wrong am I stupid uh that's a certainty oh yeah I'm asking the wrong questions okay a thousand
dollars divided by 200 that's by 200 000 is five point is zero point zero zero five so isn't it saying
is it saying oh yeah did you divide the wrong number by the wrong number oh I should I should have been
oh because it because it's because it's cost per mil revenue per mil so it should it should
have been just divided by 200 no it says no it says mile it says mile not million yeah
yeah but it means yeah but it means that means a thousand yeah okay so instead of dividing by 200
thousand I should divide by 200 which gives me five dollars what am I wrong do I make five
dollars per thousand views am I a genius of revenue I mean the it's a long video so the watch time is
probably good huh right yeah looking at my my given gaming channel where I've been like posting streams
playback based cpm is huge I guess because it's like a really long video yeah watch yeah I know
watch time is wow okay I guess I miscalculated I guess I miscalculated and actually uh yeah for
two 200 000 views I made a thousand dollars so that's actually for every for every 200 views
for every 100 views I make half of yeah make fun yeah okay I guess it's five dollars per million
cool uh it's still not it's still not enough I want more thanks
I was actually looking at my my twitch um revenue uh recently and apparently I made like 70 bucks
from just bit donations just people throwing bits I mean that's enough to pay for Elden Ring
so I think that's a that's a good thing that's money well spent that's time well spent streaming that
yeah I I don't really it seems like people be streaming these days what I mean it's true what I
mean is that I see it feels like I see lots of people that are streamers and are making money at it
like I that number has gone up and it makes me wonder if maybe I should have streamed more
maybe I should have not quit streaming so much
uh sure I mean why not why not just go back and do some why not do some right now I don't know it
sounds hard and I feel like I've got stuff to do I mean I also have stuff to do but I I
dedicate like time to it but I think did I talk about like trying to schedule things last time
I think I did like trying to schedule working on Pumpkin Alley Elden Ring streams and like Clarissa
Gunsmoke stuff did I talk about that uh I think you did I think I remember I never a big talk
about closer Gunsmoke on the last episode yeah and like I've I've cordoned off my my weekdays
and like okay I'm gonna spend this day this amount of hours uh and this with this many breaks doing
like work either Clarissa or Pumpkin Alley and then one day a week I can stream Elden Ring for like
as long as I feel like I did the other day for like almost eight hours well I feel like eight
hours is too long because I got very irritable near the end when I last and I said the game sucked
and then I got really angry again and uh but yeah it's it's possible to do streams regularly
and still make progress on other things it's just I'm sure I'm not sure it is not letting
not letting your week get away from you if you if you keep track of like the time you're spending
on any given thing and just like saying okay this is the day I try this and that so that every week
you're getting a little bit of all of your projects done yeah I'm I just um it always feels like it
eats up my whole day whenever I stream I guess there's probably things ways I could mitigate that
if I had discipline I mean I have I was just streaming for a while like whenever I felt like
I have a few hours in a row I'll just stream now sometimes it was early in the morning sometimes
it was late and uh it's not a smart idea if I want like viewers because people are awake
at certain times and it's better if I stream at certain times I just couldn't be bothered to figure
that out so I just turned it on I streamed for a bit and people who showed up had a fun time
and I stopped and it's like it's not the way to build a streaming empire exactly I maxed out at
like nine viewers and it's like not a big thing but you know it's fun so and it's it's basically
the same as if I was not streaming because I'm just playing the game and occasionally speaking
I'm saying funny jokes and it's fun hanging out with the chat it's like it's not like a tedious
work sort of thing maybe I should have maybe I should have streamed more of the time I was playing
Noida or playing Hades maybe I should stream some Hades sometime yeah you could do that I could do
that I feel like I always say maybe I should do such and such and then I never do it I feel stupid
even suggesting that I might do something because of course I won't I mean maybe you feel more
pressure to like perform as a streamer than I do yeah maybe I don't know maybe I feel like sometimes
I'm a little too lax and I don't try to make it like a show and so like people often say that my
streams are like really like chill and comforting in a way that they can just sort of have it in
the background which is nice but it definitely means that I'm not like exciting I'm not like an
exciting streamer what I know how I am I haven't streamed enough to figure out what I'm like
generally yeah I think I saw your one where you played our games I think that's the only
live stream of yours that I've that I've caught I've barely live streamed in my life so that
makes sense okay nice for me like I need people with me on my own I feel like I would just be
boring as fuck having people with you to like like one person playing the game and one person
respond to chat is a is a good it's not always feasible but it's a good formula it's yeah it's
it's I feel I feel very at ease when we're doing like a heckles for shackles shackles for heckles
thing yeah yeah or it's just sort of like we're just hanging out in the minecraft server and sort
of kind of I'm kind of mining but I'm not on screen so I don't have to worry about my screen
being like entertaining I just talk for sure jokes for sure yeah it is you it is it is a good time
I just just getting myself in the I have a big it's real it's real work for me to like psych
myself up and like get myself in the the attitude of like I'm going to stream I'm going to do something
even though it's like stupid and like what is what I'm actually doing is something that is not
difficult at all
yeah I don't know I feel like I have had that before I think I I just sort of I get over it or have
gotten over it because it doesn't really happen anymore by just like setting getting it live
before I really think about it it's like okay I'm live uh well I'm doing it now
and then I just do it that's right it's the same way like sending emails like if I look at the email
and it's like this isn't good they're gonna think I'm an idiot
I won't send it but if I just send it before it's ready then it was ready the whole time
it's not a problem I know what you mean
and yet I don't it's it's it's it's it's it's it's jumping into like a Dark Souls boss
before you've considered whether it was a good idea to do that it's it's it's just it's the do it
the fucking do it thing bad idea or not like the no brain head empty sort of approach
because it's it's a good way to get started on something
I like the approach I do it often as much as I can because I often overthink things to
ridiculous degrees it's a very uh paralyzing mindset where I'm like well I'm not ready yet so
but then if I just fucking do something without thinking no knowing that it is probably a bad
idea just head empty do it um it works out because I was underestimating myself usually
yep
I haven't learned anything I didn't learn anything you just got to utilize your
COVID brain fog he's gonna make it work for me yeah yeah hmm uh I I just um
whoa excuse me the cat the cat has been screaming it's probably picked up on the audio
the discord won't be picking it up but it'll be in the recording probably
I think good is for it's her food time I'm going to feed the cat and be right back wow okay
excellent um uh hold on I'm messaging a guy about I'm messaging a guy about the dojin
and uh I think he seems too expensive
oh right yeah you you had that list of potential other people I found three
dudes I think they're dudes on uh on uh tapas and I thought maybe one of these guys could do
the rest because I think it's been waiting a while for kaiju I think that's that's probably not
gonna happen so uh I just I just got a response back from this one guy and he he gave me his
rates page and uh the rates page seems to imply that he might want to charge like $100 per page
and that's a lot and I don't know if I am willing to pay that much honestly how many pages is this
the thing um there are 13 pages and a cover to be to be drawn I think it's something like that
that's more than the other guys wanted so I mean I feel like a hundred bucks a pay I mean if it's
really good like I I glanced at the people you you you posted I didn't really look too close
yeah 100 bucks for a whole page it's not insane no I don't think it's like a terrible
option but I I don't know what we budget we have all the other guys that I asked
said they would who do we ask that we asked um michi and uh kaiju and ed and they all said
that their rates were significantly below that so I don't know what what makes this guy think he's
so fucking special that's mean um but I don't know it's just uh it doesn't seem like a very cost
effective option none of these guys were a perfect match I was disappointed that I just can't it's
it's I can't find I can't find anyone who draws quite in this particular way
it's I guess that's normal I guess no no two are like uh yeah but it's like it's sort of a popular
ish I look at it yeah sort of thing like it doesn't look people would want to try like that it doesn't
look too unusual like it doesn't look like something that I've never seen before and yet
I cannot find anyone who whom who matches it and I I don't know what's I don't know what's going on
with that well give me a give me a few years I'll go to anime school and I'll figure out how to draw
like that I just uh you know I got I got I got half of it drawn by that guy curse him
and now it's like well I can't just I can't just throw these out and not use them and just like
pay someone else to do it from scratch like I I can't I can't bring myself to do that
can I can I see like what the art looks like a little bit yeah I want to show
sure sure sure please a brilliant full heck I'll post it you have you have the connections you're
you're the art like I spider I can't think of what what the art like you got all of the lines
connecting all the people I did not I did not ask Mary whether I forgot to do that I instead
I went on tapas and just tried to like look through like recent posts to like see oh that's
gonna be harder I know but I wanted to here these are what these are what the existing pages look
like whoa yeah it's so kawaii it's pretty kawaii damn I like it I guess it's pretty good paint
no this was not drawn by never paint this was written by never paint okay I see I was gonna say
that everything's already written yeah and and it's just the drawing yeah it was never paint
aura barista and chip wiseman I yeah we're the three they wrote the scripts for it for these
chip is a wiseman it's true yeah so so this is what I'm looking for and I just it's it's proved
surprisingly hard to find some of the draws quite like it there was one I found one a furry comic
artist who was a little bit similar but I they're like they have like a kind of big patron and I
was like this person is not gonna yeah this person is going to charge too much this person's
gonna cost this is gonna be expensive because they're like an edgy they're like an edgy
artist and I'm sure they charge out the wazoo for that shit I follow like I don't want artists who
sort of has a manga-ish style it's not the same as visfo yeah they also draw boobs
well they link to a capacitive page with the links broken so oh bummer
I don't know what's up with that at this point I'm like I'm not gonna find a perfect match
so I don't know I'm just trying to do the best I can find something find somebody
man whatever
yeah this artist is like the closest I got out of the people I follow and yeah I don't know how
well it would work I mean they're not like they don't let me I don't get the impression they're
making mega monies but I don't see a patreon okay they have 30,000 followers which is in a crazy
amount it's a lot though and this is good this is like it could fit very well into what we already
have this is it's it's yeah I mean it's not exactly the same but it's not much further off than the
ones that I had picked out on tapas so I might actually might actually ask this this person
are they on twitter yeah I leave my twitter was their twitter as well I have a lot more art on
twitter I think the question is can you convince them to draw something other than massive tits
yeah these are these are not these are not what we're looking for for this particular
project
I mean we all have to make sacrifices the boobs did just get bigger in the second half
and explicitly yeah yeah I'm not I'm not sure turn the page completely different I'm not I'm not
sure if they'd be interested in uh in what I'm asking them to do here also yeah they're tapas link
oh it's it cuts off into a dot dot dot and the link it's just like it's just broken that blows
you should uh would it not work to google their name or search in tapas it probably it probably would
oh I found it right I I found the link I use google I assume what's w I'm assuming it said
what's up and the character's called marina and from that I was able to find it yeah well they
they should fix their link what's the fuck up they should fix their link for real
I think I think I have a feeling that this person probably has more lucrative things to be doing
but maybe I'll ask but maybe I'll ask I don't see a patreon maybe if you maybe money if you just
wave it at them couldn't hurt hmm yeah I couldn't hurt to ask yeah this is pretty I would say this
is close enough but it's worth asking uh this other guy this other guy mo I don't know if I want to
pay a hundred dollars a page that's just yeah okay well that's uh that's one thing I was uh
that's yet another struggle I've been having this week add it to the pile
um all right I don't know just like in pokemon when you struggle you hurt yourself exactly
uh I think I'm out I'm out of things to say and voice voice fail time voice
voice fail time if you're if you're ready uh well I guess I don't really have anything to say
I just wanted to mention Clarissa Gunsmoke because I just like her dude she's so cute
I gotta draw her big old teddies one day oh my god wait please do and a big fucking hat
I don't think she has big fucking hat does she have she's not big old teddies does she
no no she she's moderately sized that's what I thought that's what I thought we'll explain
it she shoots her gun too hard and it makes her boobs just get bigger like inexplicably sure
that makes why not she just gets so shocked her tits go boinga that makes that makes sense to me
there's an argument in big booby mommy milkers over something like that I posted an image where
that happened someone it was I just found some abreast expansion comic where someone fired a gun
and their boobs just became huge instantly yeah I didn't understand the context the context of like
how it worked it seemed like they were so surprised the loud sound that their boobs got expanded yeah
sure just whatever just startle if if if your woman's too small just startle her
uh that's all it takes
uh okay as far as I know that's true a bunch of ghosts up in your house give
a little little cardboard cutouts of ghosts you'll never see it coming you'll
but but you'll achieve your dreams true yes I'll I'll draw more load of ghosts and be scared at every
panel I wish like freak myself out
the arguments that happen in big booby mommy milkers are really funny
because they're never like serious it's just like it's it's almost always entirely cosme because
we're just is like is a is a is a stick in the mud a grump who's always moaning about whatever
image people are excited about it's like that doesn't make sense oh it's like samus with big boobs
samus doesn't have big boobs you can't do that it's like right you can't you can't and it's true you
can't you can't we love them though that's pretty funny um but but they'll they'll also like contradict
themselves because like later on they'll be like an image what they do like I never I can't read
them I can't understand them I hope they're having a good time though uh you know what
you know what yeah glad they're having a good time glad everybody's having fun keeping it funny
um we're just being funny do you want to do the do the first voicemail sure
okay let me let me let me get it here there is not an unreasonable amount uh this week there's a
normal amount um finally finally uh let me see here
where uh which where was the first one oh my god uh yes uploaded today
oh they're all out of order no you know I I found myself saying oh my god with like that accent
once and I'm like oh shit this is too much I'm losing all my britishisms I'm losing my accent
like like entirely I should not ever say god is that an american thing well it's just like to
to say god but with an ah instead of an oh oh I guess I just don't even think about it oh yeah
this is it oh my god oh my oh my god oh my god e-gads e-gads it's uh professor e-gads like I just
felt so I felt so dirty hearing an american come out of my mouth uh you'd rather have an american
come in your mouth oh i was saying only if she's got only if she's got big balls and it has to be a woman
okay true all right the first voicemail I posted it there it's called Gib should do a page two
three two one go hello I just read the ben sink drawn tales gets troll page and I just want to
call in to say it is really cool really good very awesome a lot of great arts thank you I especially
love the piece of art of the devil sitting on his like a rocky throne and like fire all around him
yeah fucking sick that was that was the piece job and the resistance uh yeah I uh put a lot of work
put a lot of work on the page and I liked how it came out uh well the title is linked in the last
episode I think they put it in the description all right I I assumed it was I thought it was I mean
maybe it was on twitter you tweeted about it wait I'm sure now now I'm gonna hold on hold on maybe
you did I might I didn't finish listening to that episode yet I got like most of the way through
I think I put it in the show notes hold on in any event now I gotta in any event the uh I I don't
know whether I would be good for drawing uh tales gets trolled mostly because I'm not caught up
I had to I had to catch up yeah I have to catch up oh yeah it's the first link and I feel I mean
I I wouldn't be I wouldn't say no but I feel like the I don't know I think me being friends with Ben
is not necessarily a way in to that um I don't know I think I think it went live without the link
and then I quickly added it um maybe give I'll be honest they didn't I knew going in that they
weren't gonna pay me that much like frankly they they didn't they didn't pay me uh enough to compensate
for the amount of work that I put into that page but caveat is that I didn't really expect them to
like oh yeah it's not a money thing I knew what I would be cool to do it I guess I just I guess I
don't really put myself out there for these sorts of things too often oh if you I would I would feel
weird to be like oh what if I draw like um de-whelmingly well if you wanted to you could ask Cece and uh
I suppose I could um but that's but that's up to you oh oh you know actually on that subject uh
funny drama happened in the tales gets trolled server oh yeah I saw a tweet from Cece on the
the tales gets trolled thing I didn't know what it was about somebody had left it's um
it's but yeah okay so laserbot is the guy but also embergram embergram is laserbots older brother
and they basically wrote the story together and their younger brother shomo is also involved
but so they have us an outline they have an outline that the two the two of them came up with
an embergram's job has been to go through the outline and make actually write out like the
individual scripts for each page like I was given a craig like I was given a script that was written
by embergram and told like make this into a page please um and so embergram had I don't know he got
upset about something I guess someone was criticizing his like the way that he lays
fucking fuck off craig I guess the the way that he the way that he lays his his scripts out because
he does like format them very weirdly I was able to figure it out but he got mad at someone maybe
laserbot like criticizing the way that he lays out his scripts he wanted to be able to kick people
from the server for talking back to him or whatever CC would not give him permission to do that
and so embergram like quit in a huff he's like I'm out I'm leaving the project and uh which is a
bummer uh because he did have a bunch of there were a bunch of like plot ideas that he had come up with
that he hadn't told anyone so no yeah so this it might affect the story a bit which is sad
he might you know laser bothers though they are brothers laserbot left before and then he came
back so I mean maybe embergram can be convinced to come back but I think for now uh laserbot and
maybe shomo are doing the scripts now I'm not really sure what they're gonna do but someone's
gotta have to do that but so yeah there was this whole stupid like fallout thing embergram
I think laser embergram left and then laserbot left but I think laserbot he's not really gone
he just left the server like in solidarity or something I don't know um those guys are pretty
funny well definitely cool reading this page as I'm as I'm scrolling down towards for satan but
the embers are rising up and it feels almost animated as I read it thank you very much
yeah I thought it was an animation for a second they're like whoa the embers are going up
and I know that's just me scrolling oh I see yeah yeah you kind of descend you kind of descend
down into the darkness and as you scroll down with more embers kind of start yeah that's cool
wafting upwards good yeah thank you um I liked uh I liked I liked uh drawing it I had fun with it
and then um yeah maybe maybe I'll do another one at some point it was a lot of work so I wouldn't
do one all the time but uh they gave me they gave me a little more than they usually pay
because I they gave they they gave um they gave me a little extra like apparently they also gave
some extra to uh what are the guy the guy Rocco and uh Robonod I think the other some two other
artists who like did like really fancy work they gave me the fancy the fancy rate so I
appreciated that oh that's nice yeah um you're a fancy boy cc thank thank you cc appreciate it
okay anyway let's uh let's get the next one here uh
the next voicemail is called uh killer prints 9 30 there it is okay three two one go
so I've been watching the layer half of the body cast on the top land the arc and it's
been kind of frustrating as I disagree with most of what Gib and Nate say as you will read weekly
and fan subs fan subs yeah it's kind of retired I mean still the please don't cancel me
well what's the disagree he didn't even say what the disagreement was
yeah it was what did you mention about one piece he said he said the something land arc
he said he disagreed with a lot of what you were saying as he was reading
scan lations maybe he was just disagreeing with the reading of scan lations instead of the official
he just said he disagreed with you but he didn't he didn't elaborate uh all right the next one is
a question top 10 voicemail characters um uh I think there's conflict of interest with me I won't
give my answers I mean I'll wait wait wait no this is this is not uh this is not don't listen to that
one that's the next voicemail um top 10 voicemail I mean I would have to give it to them I'd have
to give it to them I'd have to give it to them snakes yeah okay cringis bingus I guess I would say
the samurai is a classic of course um that's three I'm not really putting them in order I was just
trying to think of 10 because like uh there's a lot but like I don't remember oh yeah my ass batman
oh yeah oh sure yeah riddle my ass batman haven't heard from him in a while um ever ever since I saw
him in real life yeah he's he's changed from a voicemail into a person yeah that's true um
I'm trying to I'm trying I feel there's probably I probably feel bad later someone will point out
to me a bunch of really obvious choices that didn't jump to mine immediately I mean uh I guess I could
like give my top five that aren't me and then my own like five that I enjoyed the most that I made
to avoid bias spotting I do yeah please whoever the fuck I don't even know if this counts as a
character the guy who sends in like fucking songs every other week that guy fucking rules yeah I
consider him I consider him like just a person I wasn't thinking of him as a character but yeah yeah
riddle my ass batman was pretty funny I'm trying the samurai definitely I like the samurai yeah
at all the whole arc yeah um it's hard for me to think of characters because most of the ones I
think I made yeah um uh were you the entire league of night fuckers or was that multiple
I was most of them um initially like I started sending them in less and I eventually I stopped
but other people kept sending them in I like stopped right before you started skipping them um
so that worked out for me none of mine got skipped wait we started skipping them
yeah the joke was just they were just they were just loud and they were just like loud and like
breathing and like yeah like people would just call in and like hello I'm the the butt wizard uh I
have riddles free which PCP do I want to pee or in or some shit and you're just like to be like
yeah this is a night fucker I don't fucking care you just turn it off that's right that's right
that's right I mean me and far as like created like a formula that was too easy to emulate
and everyone was just no one was innovating um that's right you gotta you gotta iterate right
progress it's about progress um I guess I'm glad you mentioned Ben snakes if he were alive he would
be very grateful fuck I'm a standard him a shit uh Ben snakes is my top number one for sure there's
no there's no question um I'm gonna put the voice filter on for that uh audience will hear it
all right well guess what if I didn't name you then your character sucks and I don't even remember
it so fuck you my favorite characters I've done uh aside I guess like I like them snakes obviously
I like close to my kitchen I does it count if it's like a character I made that I had someone else
voice like I wrote a script and directed them I don't know well sure it still counts as a thing
you can choose lost tapes archive is my favorite thing in general I've done because I just like
how surreal it is and like those were so weird I was so like confused and they felt so mysterious
because I had no idea who was doing it and they were so like sporadic it would just be suddenly
a new tape and I guess I guess that is like what the fuck is that I guess that is a character
yeah I mean like the tapekeeper is the character so like he was played by four eyes but like I
you know scripted him sort of how did you do all of them like all of the PCP members I didn't get
to I wanted to but like um I my work was fucking me up after a while um of pencilmation and then
people really ruined everything and then people started leaving the podcast so I had I had one
planned for you Gib I had one for Jesse I was waiting for mine yeah I I had a few different ideas for
you um uh I don't know it's maybe maybe I would have um I probably maybe I would have gone with the
the Ann Moon Anions thing that I ended up doing into a Nate fucker maybe it would have been something
like that um mainly Moon Anions and the Moon Anions I fucking love that video so much um
ah what was I what was it Moon Anions are the mainly Moon Anions are the main aliens we finding
shall be yeah woasts uh great that was that was fun I love the classic Gib content um rare characters
ones that I don't think I've mentioned uh double double Satan Satan um that almost became like a
series um I I don't I have the vaguest recollection it's like hello hello I I am am double double
Satan Satan he just says every word twice um and then he likes he says fuck you Ben because
every voicemail character hates Ben that's like that's just the meta I guess um yeah sure and I
was gonna continue it to where he like interviews triple Satan and then um Infinity Jesus um and
like triple Joker would like be in the background and like just a bunch of like characters or like
1.5 um like Buddha or something that's a pretty good that's a pretty good bit I would have been
pretty yeah yeah I had a bunch of ideas um I do I do recall but I think you just made like one
double satan email yeah there was only yeah there's only ever one I'm gonna do just an anomaly
yeah so like there's gonna be the Vemsnakes compilation the Lost Tapes compilation cluster
pun kitchen compilation then there'll be a general Nate fucker compilation which I'm gonna
include other people's as well or at least the ones I think are good but mostly or maybe maybe
I'll do all of mine and then like other people's or something I don't know and then maybe a
miscellaneous there was one I wanted to do Morph as well which was the audio demon I think I did
one of those in 2019 back when I was editing the podcast it's the the goal for that one
is that I would like put a voice effect on a random pcp member um so I cursed Ben St with
flanger and your voice was like for like a minute after the voicemail ended
uh I see I see uh wait did I not listen back to that one so I never heard that
possibly it was it was oh no it was in 2019 I'm sure I could find it um I mean if I do a compilation
I'm with the compilation I'm debating do I just have the raw audio or do I have like
from the pcp everyone's reactions um maybe I'll do both I don't know that's more work
yeah maybe for that one I'll do it since like that like your everyone's reaction was part of
the voicemail like that was like the point um but yeah I was gonna do a bunch like I'd call in
someone gets incomprehensible reverb where I put reverb on their voice and then I delete the dry
track so you just hear like faint echoing and shit um you can't understand that I was gonna
do like a bunch but then um I was close to when I stopped editing so I'm like well if I I'm not
the editor of this bit doesn't really work you can't do anything yeah I mean like I could trust
I could maybe hope that the person editing does a good job but like they probably wouldn't do it
the way I think would be funniest because I'm very picky right right true yeah it's tough uh it's
tough one it's tough bit I guess the best if I had to pick requires a true the touch of a true
artist I think to make it if I narrowing it all down if I had to pick the one voicemail out of
all the things I've done that I think on its own is the best it's really tough but I think this the
smeagle Nate fucker voicemail really it it's just so yeah I mean it's yeah it's just so
comfortable and the impression that 4a's did was too fucking good it was variant yeah that's
that's the word I can't really remember like this I can I remember like I remember being
Nate fucker's generally viscerally uncomfortable no I remember the smeagle one as being like viscerally
unsettling describes in in great detail what he's gonna do yeah it just it just sounds like it's
straight out of the fucking movie because I put like ambience and like I found like soundtrack
from the film to like work of it and everything could you could you put like could you edit like
clips of the film so that it's that it looks like he's saying it oh god uh oh maybe geez like maybe
it could as like a standalone thing for any figure compilation I'm probably gonna like commission
unless I drop myself like an artist to show like Nate like like running away from like this this
this like army of like unspeakable creatures and he's just running like with fear in his eyes
or in his sunglasses I love that those were those were some that was some fucked up some fucked up
shit once the compilations out I'm gonna force Nate to do a video where he listens to it
you should force Nate to do that absolutely uh he needs to be he needs to be whipped into shape
and he needs to be held accountable uh okay uh yeah I'm sorry I can't I can't even think of 10
I can't think of 10 maybe between us even with my own I can't think of 10 I can think of like
yeah five or six uh turns out that there's not that many good voicemailers oh no voicemails
were bad all maybe just not memorable enough yeah um my individual voicemails can be good
not one character is not as as frequent yeah what ones that I can like pick out and remember
and name them and be like oh yeah that that guy I remember that specific character oh Tommy Jay
I love that character Tommy Jay baby oh that guy who wouldn't stop voicemailing and I
went in the voice jail everyone in the voice jail is my favorite uh favorite character
next voicemail is called uh wait sorry did we skip this one no yeah we sorry yeah play the one
before um it's called garlic dis three two one go yeah well and I just changed your name to sewer
chats and they have like mixed song rules man except for all the verses thanks man I agree
Tom got all the non-rap parts and everyone's like oh wow Tom can actually sing I could
song they made me rap they forced me to rap it's not fair oh yours was like the 90s rap
sort of section mine it was funny mine mine sucked I knew it sucked it was fine uh it's okay I didn't
write it and if I did I would have made it bad on purpose so it would still be okay I don't remember
the lyrics but my heart tells me it was hello Brad you are bad and or so wait wait oh okay
I saw a comment on Kiwi Farms the other day that actually made me really laugh
it the guy he was he was mocking my verse he said that I sucked and like yeah true but he
but he he he was to make fun of to make fun of my rapping style he he like made up like oh
Ben St sounds like this and then he he he wrote a line and the line was like um wait it was uh
uh my name is Ben St and I'm here to say property is theft and traps aren't gay
like yeah true I wish I wish I could write that myself
but I can't because I'm too stupid uh so loved it well liking liking men is straight okay I mean
if if if that's you know I agree I uh if you read this you're a woman now
property property is theft uh it's a theft from the commons it's just belongs private property
belongs to to is the is should be exist for the benefit of all and that's distinct from personal
property by the way uh but we can we can get into that later oh people people don't know
but there's a distinction I didn't know there was a distinction yeah yeah I didn't realize um and
then I I don't know so I saw someone explain it and I was like oh okay yeah when when Mark
talks about private property he's talking about like factories farmland so on not like clothes
your house it's like my microwave right uh but it's easy to dunk it's easy to dunk if you pretend
if you don't know that there's a distinction or you pretend that there isn't so it's always a thing
I've said of leftists having some good ideas and then not explaining them to me in a way that I
understand and then no wonder I don't think they're good for a long time I I yeah and it's like well
if you well if you read marks like it's all there and that's true but I've been taught that it is
all there mark was to mark mark just wants to murder people that's what I was told he did yeah
yeah he uh he he you know he did the uh he did the holodomir and he killed uh you know
he killed all the kulaks uh in the russian revolution carl marx terrible dictator yeah
carl was a terrible terrible dictator carl barks woof he's a dog i'm a campus carl carl marx is in
assassins creed syndicate you can do many quests for him wait really that's probably very silly
i forget what it was it was something something like liberate this bit liberate this bitch do you
have to go and liberate this bit of london because he's in he was in london and it's like the london
assassins creed maybe do you have to go and like help protect like a union leader as they're like
striking against the factory or something like that the the bad guys are trying to crack down on
this union you got to go and assassinate everyone hell yeah damn good the that was a good game the
rights the rights of the proletariat's the arms must not be surrendered under any pretext
it was there was carl marx there was charles darwin there was some other guy charwin darwin
they were all there i saw i saw some i saw some dumb thing some dumb like anti leftist thing on
twitter it was a meme it was like you know the chad face or whatever and it was like one guy says
you know uh the workers have a right to anything they produce and then some smug the smug guy you're
supposed to agree with says like what if they produce at a net negative what if they produce
at a net negative what if they are unproductive then you know actually capital owners protect the
workers against you know uh business losses or something and i don't know uh that was like it's
like okay and every i saw a bunch of people that i follow were like god this is all in marx like
like like uh uh like make a critique of communism that isn't already addressed in the formative
challenge difficulty impossible if you just read marx like it's literally in there and it's like
yes no if i read marx i'm gonna take an axe and crack open jeff bezis's head like an egg and the
yolk's gonna spill out and then i'm gonna go to prison and i don't want that and on the one hand
i'm sure it is i'm sure it is in there i'm sure he probably did address that question somewhere
on the other hand i haven't read it i haven't read all of capital so like i couldn't i couldn't
have made that point i couldn't be like well actually marx has a rebuttal for exactly this uh
this thing uh but there is one apparently uh so i get it it's hard to explain simple things sometimes
i mean i mean the look like me in my brain if if like all the excess like earnings you have
aren't being siphoned off to some one guy at the top right then those earnings would be
with the workers and then they wouldn't need a person at top to like take a temporary loss for
you you'd have more money to tank it yourself right right they would have they would have it
in the first place yeah you would just already have like the means because you'd be earning more
so that it just seems like that would automatically correct for itself
it's not like magically like the person being having a ceo doesn't mean like more money magically
appears like i don't think so yeah somebody somebody's tank someone's got the money and
they're tanking the loss so it's just like well who someone so yeah so it's like oh well well but
this yeah it's kind of like saying oh but you see the fact oh the workers don't have the money
they didn't get the profit but that means they can't take the loss so actually it's good for them
it's like well it's like it's like i don't know about that i mean you can also just look i forget
which country it is that does have a decent number of worker cooperatives um their survival rate
like a typical business like i i i'm not gonna remember the exact number someone like 30 something
percent of typical businesses will last more than three years and the rest close down but with worker
co-ops it's like 87 survive the first three years wow they're way they're so much more resilient
that's very interesting yeah so that probably tells me that they're probably very good at
you know tanking those losses because it probably incentivizes the workers to like
because like if i know whether the risk is just the risk is distributed yeah and it's exactly like
i i haven't worked many normal jobs but i know people who do and they'll tell me like
like my partner used to work at starbucks my partner follows the book my partner tries to
do everything correctly and other people are just lazy but just sit around do nothing like their
whole shift do the bare minimum work don't care leave messes behind and just don't really try
and i hear it from other people i have another friend who works at a casino somewhere and they
have similar things like half the employees just don't give a shit they do the bare minimum
not to get fired and they don't care but like i feel like in a co-op everyone's incentivized
to do well because it means you get paid more because like your payments i assume it's more
like a percentage of earnings rather than just a flat rate i don't exactly i think maybe that's
how it works i don't know exactly but the point is like the business like the better the business
does the better you do it seems to be like the situation there so it makes sense that people
would actually give a shit and probably feel better about their work because they actually have
some control over it or something like that i feel like what would make you feel better about
your work is just getting a bigger paycheck i feel like just the fact that there's no big guy at
the top taking a lot of the money out of the company means that everybody gets more money which
means you're just happier in general and can work harder when you're a grunt you're like i mean
maybe there's like the possibility that you might if you do well you might get a promotion might get
a raise or something but like there's never any guarantee of that and for a lot of in a lot of
positions it's probably just not gonna happen so like yeah why try hard what's what's the reward
in that uh nothing most of the time a lot of the time um there are there are a lot of jobs that i
i would be like you might as well do the bare minimum you're like you're not getting anything
anything out of doing more so like why would it be expected of you oh my god i had to fucking
double take it's actually here 36 minutes ago your movie sucks the lion king part one holy
shit it's actually here no how how many hours is part one uh two hours 40 minutes and i think
there's gonna be free parts lemma maybe there'll be two that's great i can't wait to watch i've
been seeing the live stream clips for this for like for years for literally over two years
maybe coming closer for years same like and the stuff i've seen so far like i have not
watched 2019 lanking but holy fuck some of that shit that movie just fucks up like basic competence
like people's microphones clipping and like like bad like autotune on the singing like or like
audio being time stretched and having like noticeable artifacts and pops and shit it's
it's it was always amusing seeing those things because like i'm sure the movie is like
like fine well like not fine but like it's just it's just it's a series of images and
people like the lion king the original so they just say hey it's good and then everyone forgot
about it um and adam going through and finding endless like supplies of like things that are
wrong with it the more he dug it was like nobody would have ever like like it's it's i mean i
obviously haven't seen this video yet i don't know exactly what he's gonna talk about but like
like lion king 2019 is like not like the worst film in like the world in terms of like what it does
it's sort of like a trend that sucks of like just making like a like an old property but like new
and like just getting a bunch of money for it or just lazily putting it together returning
animation into live action yeah like a weird thing like that it's a stupid gimmick it's dumb
it's like hollywood's stupid and people are just dumb droves they go into the droves the thing but
like to deep dive on it you find so much more to hate and it's like nobody would have gotten this
mad about this if they hadn't been trying to make a review about it i can't wait to see how
upsetting it is i can't wait to see in front of the mouth by the end i haven't really been following
those live streams for like a year i only looked at like some of the highlight clips but there was
like actually like comical it's just comical like seeing like especially like seeing like the behind
the scenes interviews with john favreau being like yeah you know wanted to look like a nature
documentary um you know we don't want the characters to be expressive animators will
send me like a scene and it's like expressive and i'm like tell them no animals don't express
themselves you can't have the character emote you gotta tone it back and have their face look stiff
oh this person sent me a character and they made the sunset look beautiful and i spent all this
time putting these nice clouds in the sky and it was really aesthetic but in real life a cloud
the sky's boring you can't do that oh my god things like that it's like so funny in real life the
sky can be nice sometimes like like no nothing nothing can be idealized like pure realism is
what we need like no idealism at all nothing none of that it's just like in video games we want
everything brown like shit brown like poo um i guess that trend is not quite so strong these
days but for a while it was our friend of the show sigh commented on this video 10 minutes ago
sigh is watching the lion king review by yms are you are you i will have to watch i don't i won't
be able to watch this today i'll probably watch it tomorrow i'm probably i'm gonna i really want to
watch it with um my husband but he's been so busy with the new final fantasy 14 patch i don't know
if i can get him uh two hours two and two hours and 40 minutes i was thinking of like oh movie night
but like that's a long movie in two hours and 40 minutes dude the fucking the fucking kimber review
like a reminder about the kimber video that's a good video i like the kimber video was like
a section of this video yeah it was yeah it would have been insane this this guy just this
videos he just keeps making videos what the fuck is wrong with him the kimber review is
incredible though it is one of the best youtube videos i've seen still yeah it's it's really nice
the i learned a lot from it the the the the how would you describe it like the exhaustive
thoroughness of debunking yeah the like he didn't need to go on for quite as long as he did
but the fact that he did made it absolutely like airtight like you can't argue against it i came
i came away from it feeling like i had a thorough understanding of the subject and that i had learned
some things that i did not know before and i mean what more can you what more can you ask for
like this man single-handedly flipped the entire narrative and it worked yeah and everyone was
like oh yeah we were all wrong about this topic that's true it's kind of amazing it's kind of amazing
that the misconception was so widespread for him to debunk yeah i i i fully believe that like
disney like ripped it off you know i fully believe that until seeing his video oh yeah i just i mean
i don't know it's just what i heard just everyone said oh yeah kimba was a was a a jab a tezuka manga
and they kind of like took took it for the line king i was like yeah okay that tracks because like
you know all their other movies are like adaptations of a thing so why not um
yeah did not know did not know there was so many different versions of kimba did not know there
was so much of it did not know that all the all the comparisons of shots that line yeah ripped off
kimba were actually from kimber properties released after the line king that's funny that's really funny
it's like oh that's how they fucking get you like oh of course it's so they were they're being sneaky
this whole time that it's it's it's funny they tricked me through that whole thing you've you
figure out why the con the misconceptions exist and then there's like like it's really down to just
a few people's blogs there's some there's some paint in the picture there's some in that specific
way to make it look like that and everyone just picked it up and ran with that there's some people
that really should have known better that like should have done the research and maybe they did
and and yet and yet they they told the this this twisted version of the story they they literally
did like the soy jack we very female moves weak and very female like the they did the thing where
they look at a thing like lion america and then lion japan and they're like oh line from japan
that's way better yeah yeah well well kimba's kimba is better because he's from a long line of
great leaders because he's white and he's gotta he wants to be like his ancestors as well as look
like them oh yeah that was a that was a recent pcp you just quoted all that shit at the start it was
funny oh that sounds right i love i love that i love that it's funny yeah just oh god that the
fucking racism too you have no rights you have no right to bully him just because he was white
i just can't believe that when they bring up like the african tribes and they the the the
void the dubbers literally just go because like like i remember like south park doing
shit like that and that's obviously like taking that's obviously like trying to take the piss
but this is like unironic this is just them doing it unironically this is this is how african
speak they they yeah sometimes sometimes uh they don't always do it like that one that one with
the the tribesmen with the grenades was not like that but like a lot of a lot of the other ones are
that was a such a bizarre one yeah like kimba sides with the the hunter with the grenades just
throwing grenades at leopards for revenge where are they getting them from blowing the fucking
smithereens yeah it's just uh that's it so it's good good video just stuff just fucking happens
stuff just happens yeah yeah whatever they wanted to do that day
that's um it's it's kind of neat it's kind of neat that they gave them grenades you know they
didn't just go with the old that old chestnut of like a spear it's kind of you did have a spear
okay but he had grenades too and that's and that's something um okay uh i wonder if that was
literally just because it's easy to animate an explosion instead of like a stab oh god like
oh but you just get like a thing like oh like a still image flies across the screen and there's
a flash of like two frames of an explosion easier to do yeah maybe maybe that makes sense uh next
next voicemail is called praising lord of ghosts plus lore question three two one go so i finally
got my physical uh copy of lord of ghosts based and uh i had read act one before but this is my
first time reading act two and i must say this comic is extremely based great amazing so much fun
thank you uh some amazing pieces of art inherent uh so my favorites are the very osamu tezuka-esque
page where flower heads just like chops the entire page in half um i also really like the
haunting montage where it's the two pages of wacky characters haunting yeah like denizens and
i also love the two page spread of the n-word slime that's for the ghost stories my favorite is
probably writing lesson by nico it's very funny and cute my second favorite is probably uh flower
journey by uh the one ben saint hell yeah i feel really bad for that poor uh cow town denizen who
got a cactus shove in his mouth he didn't deserve that oh no he's a he's a really bad guy he just
didn't see anyway i got a lore question real quick so uh it's clear that the denizens of
new big and by the sea aka new york aka real actual london are supposed to all have like
british and english accents but what about the lord of ghosts is he american that's a good question
the lord of ghosts is not from a country necessarily it's the the the world is like
just because um endless war takes place in like a funny version of of boston that is on the shore
of like the grand canyon which is filled with slime nevada or arizona or whatever yeah yeah
so like that necessarily is like oh that's kind of a real place sorry um and then and then like
endless mods in like london like it's the funny version of that but with mud instead so it's also
a real place um i love the origin of endless but i don't i love the art sorry i just i remembered
that the top 10 mods in video games that was good video oh thanks um like the lord of ghosts
the those locations are like built around like real places but the globe that they are in
is not the real world there is no america um there is no like countries of it's not the real world but
stuff um it's different and lord of ghosts is from somewhere else
gotcha it's it's it's very it's hard to like say right now because like it involves things i haven't
quite written yet um and i it doesn't necessarily like line up with the lore as just like decided by
whoever is in charge of endless war not that it's really in anyone's in really in charge of that
but i like to think it's on like a planet that isn't quite earth and it's different
fascinating can't wait i understand it's not from any real world parallel location
yeah yeah i can't wait for my copy to arrive at some point
same it should be in the fucking air it should be flying around whoa there's
you have to wait for mother-in-law to say that a package arrived at their place and then i'll go
pick it up whenever that happens i gotta check my p.o box i think i probably have a bunch of
returned return to sender packages waiting for me in there then every single time mail
comes up you say i gotta check my p.o box it's too far away it takes me like an hour and a half to
get to medford whoa why so far because i i moved my my p.o box is where my old house used to be
so now it's on the other side of the city uh so it's very annoying i'm more like a p.u box
exactly that is exactly what i'm saying um next voicemail is two seconds long three two one go
very good uh but it has a link it has an image to go with it uh oh yes
the king of personal responsibility prevails and it only took him over two years to edit this video
that's what i called based and then vixx says this guy t and then vixx says in response for the
record i edited 99% of this on the spot of retcon right after filming i remember that this is why
i thought this was weird it was taking so long because i remember i thought victor was going to
to edit the the thing and then nate said he was going to right but i remember victor nearly
completing it at radcon really how embarrassing for nate i didn't watch it i didn't watch it at
radcon but i saw it was like okay we finished filming for the day victor was just on his laptop
working on it it's like but yeah and he's i remember like i i could get this done at least uh
you know a few days after but i guess he didn't complete it well i don't really remember what
happened that i wasn't really involved in discussing that i don't remember seeing vik edit it
and i don't remember seeing him edit it i just don't know why and i don't know and i don't know
why it took nate i mean he just he just wasn't doing it for like two years and then recently
i i egged him on to do it and it took him like two months after he started after he said he was
gonna start doing it to finally do it i don't know what he was doing i don't know what what he
actually did with it that took him along i have no idea what does nate do what does nate do i don't
understand does he does he spend all of his time making youtube videos and they're like really big
and expensive and like snazzy i'm gonna say no wow i'm gonna say he used to make videos fast when
it wasn't full time and then it was full time and then they start making videos yeah funny how that
works well he made a um on his side channel he made a uh a little like meme video about wil smith
slapping chris rock oh i didn't i guess i'm not on that yeah it's best i saw that i don't remember
seeing it i think it's on bestie boy uh someone linked it someone linked it it came out like like
maybe a week ago uh it's a little fanfare timely yeah uh and i guess he's like i wonder was it was
it was like it was actually like right after or maybe right before the uh the the grad garling
house diss track video came out i was like were you doing that instead is this what you were working
on yeah it's bestie boy it looks like i haven't seen this okay i'm subscribed i don't know why
didn't show up for me yeah i don't know i don't know i don't i i don't know why it took nate this
long to uh to do that video i just who knows is he streaming all the time i just really just
don't know what he's doing i don't think he streams all the time does he stream like once a week or
something i'm not actually sure um i don't know man uh i believe vik when he says that he edited
99 of it it checks out i don't know what i don't have a like a comparison to be like oh what did
nate do to that footage to make it the final what did that last one percent entail i just don't know
i just don't know maybe maybe leaving the pcp is as well is is the problem because like you know
when you're on the pcp you talk about what you've been up to you talk about what you've been working
i guess yeah he's not is he just not talking about it because he's not doing anything i don't
understand um if he came on if he had to talk about what he did every week maybe he'd feel
more motivation to do things i'm that's not it's not a crazy idea that's not the craziest thing
i've ever heard someone said actually someone left a comment on the last episode that said
i'm i'm gonna paraphrase it but it was something along the lines of like nate left the podcast
and he nate thinks it's been the topicless podcast for years but actually every episode is the like
motivation like career discussion episode and that's actually exactly what nate needed
and it's i think it's kind of similar to what you're saying now like maybe
yeah like less conspiratorial if you're similar at vain yeah well well just the idea that like uh
you know what if you talked about what you were working on might be good i'm i've been animating
nipples this entire time that's what i've been working on because the nsfw version of my animation
is pretty much done it'll be out by the time this episode airs on my patreon if people want to see
if you're talking about yeah on kazanics comes on with titties out oh that's not out already
oh they're still working on it the the version with the the booba being all on full display isn't
quite done i oh because there's a lot of animations that need to be touched up like some of them are
already done one i had to work on which i'll send you guys um because you're cool but there's like
other shots but i'm still working on i've been working on one today it's the shot of her butt
swinging back and forth and you can see her boobs from behind um because we're just that i just
just gotta say just gotta say in general that's an angle i like i really like that yeah from behind
but you can see the boobs around that's just a good angle here's a good angle yeah um there you go
both of it sending you're away oh my god no this is gonna get me in jail oh actually i don't think
that's true woe there gibbentake has requested that discord block any messages uh that could be
explicit the fuck what are you a square i haven't done that i have to add is it a new setting maybe is
it because we're not added as friends i swear we fucking added each other at some point yeah
discord like unfriends me before discord like unfriends me from people sometimes i swear this
happens okay that's weird because like you sent me the thing that's in the chat in our dms that's
also like file yeah okay there we go okay whatever but yes we're working on that at patreon.com
slash living fall but you gotta support the pcp uh they they you guys missed out we didn't charge
from you missed out we didn't charge for march we didn't charge for march you all owe us all if
you're subscribed you owe us more you you are contractually obligated to send us some more to
make up for it you are otherwise we'll call the police exactly we're gonna we're gonna find you
freeloaders freeloaders criminals criminal scum
okay uh next voicemail is called oh it's a youtube link uh here
all right well is this yeah it's a 11 minute video man we're not watching when we don't watch
videos do you ever watch do you ever watch the company man i don't know never heard of this guy
oh i know this guy he makes videos basically he tells the story of a company usually it's
like a restaurant chain or something uh and he'll be like he'll tell how it started usually it'll be
a company that has sort of like fallen out of favor and like you don't see them anymore and he'll tell
like how it started how it got popular and then like why it ended up like you know eventually
failing or or being reduced in scope or whatever so that's kind of interesting actually i was talking
to munchy about it one time just in private and he said that he watched the channel but he got kind
of fed up with it because basically every like restaurant or every like store or whatever has
the same origin story which is like two rich guys got friends with each other and decided we should
make a store and then they did um and it's true uh but uh i don't know anyone twitter and i we're
all gonna make it though we're all gonna we are right all you need is two rich guys um that's
that's that's the beauty of capitalism everyone's gonna be a millionaire everyone's gonna create
a chain like that and it's all you have to do all you have to do is just work hard at
creating a restaurant chain that then you know opens up you know 30 locations nationwide what if
you had like a ramen like restaurant called the old bowl bowl and chain i'd rather have a
rum and coke if you know what i mean wait the bowl and oh i get it the bowl and chain yeah
that's clever i don't know what the gimmick is i i guess it's an idiom it's like it's like it's like
marriage but there's a bowl involved and it's got ramen in it it's it's next to it's next to a
bowling alley and your plate is connected to a bowling ball by a chain if you don't finish your
meal someone's gonna throw that bowling ball and your plate's gonna go out the window ah
yes a bowling themed restaurant where they they bowl you like your drink in a bowling bowl you
have to suck it out of the holes there's a little cork a little cork in there
uh sounds good to me in a bowling bowl uh so i don't know i know this twitter thing is probably
about that stupid uh elon musk isn't gonna buy it for four hundred and twenty dollars or whatever
haha i really i really don't i'm really unsettled by the whole hmm we need to create real free speech
i'm like what is this about is this about you're just gonna unban donald trump you're just you're
gonna allow vaccine misinformation what's your angle what's your angle he's well he's gonna
crack down on the woke mind virus it is a virus if your trans die and he shoots you with a gun
yeah probably that's it probably unfortunately uh maybe actually that he'll he'll he'll unban
donald trump and he will ban like the trans flag emoji and that's the only things that will change
right because it's that's stifling my free speech we need more free speech trans people existing
can't speak i think um i don't know elon musk is an idiot he probably doesn't even know what he's
gonna do i don't think i don't think they're gonna let him buy it uh i mean it would be terrible
it'd be it'd be terrible for the world like a stupid idea i feel like i'm i'm i'm almost positive
that twitter would just break and just like disintegrate if they actually sold it to elon musk
yeah i don't think it would be good for it um uh yeah i think it would probably go south
not necessarily because like enough people hate elon musk that there'd be a boycott of it but just
sort of i don't know if i can only see bad things happening i think he would do stupid things with
it like they all they already do stupid changes to the platform all the time that everyone hates
i think it would only accelerate um i don't know that it has like fawn like i don't know if its
stock price is down or whatever and that's why this guy made a video about it i know that netflix
is cratering really hard and that's pretty funny it's first people aren't chilling anymore they're
all riled up that's that's true no one's chilling i'm never hearing like back in like 2016 and i
don't think it's changed but like twitter operates at a loss that's why i remember i and that's
probably been like that for a very long time it was youtube that was operating i mean youtube too
yeah i heard like twitter was also like in that boat just not as bad
i don't know how and why do they do it like i could be incorrect i mean i'm gonna double check
oh man if elon musk for instance buys twitter and then he decides i'm gonna turn this ship around
i'm gonna change it so we're operating at a profit that's gonna that's gonna ruin it that would be
oh my god imagine imagine what he would do if that was his goal hold on and twitter gold in 2021
twitter's annual net loss amounted to two hundred and twenty one million dollars overall this is a
significant decrease from the previous year that's good losing two hundred million dollars
that's good actually we're we're getting better that's better what the trend is in like as in the
loss was decreased they were losing more but now we're losing less losing less money is good
that means maybe next year you'll lose even even less and good for them honestly
what if he changes the twitter tweet birds into an ego icon no he can't touch the bird
that's all i have left oh my gosh i'm trying to turn off i'm trying to disable this website from
oh my god this is a fucking nightmare this is a fucking nightmare this website that i'm trying
to like look at the twitter graph is like um if you want to look at this page you have we have to
get your consent to look at our cookies you know and of course it just gets worse as it goes so i
i'm not clicking it allow all so i'm going to click cookie consent manager and then
i can't i still haven't disabled them i have to like click on the sub menus um and that doesn't
work i have to click on see more details and then when i do that which is like one out of like five
menus i have to go through i can't even disable them i have to like then click on another drop
down list and i have to oh my god scrolling scrolling i this is like seven pages deep this is
this is cookie wait i still i still can't disable it um this is this is cookie clicker okay so i want
you to compare these two images and i'm putting one in the little scroll bar on the right side
look how much it shrunk just for me clicking on one of the cookie details i have to scroll through
like 10 pages and at the bottom there's no button that says disable this cookie how do i disable it
i'm so confused it just says allow all or that's it that's nothing else oh god
sometimes there's a there's this thing and it's like they do like a tricksy thing they a little
tricky little ooh you think you're clicking on uh no but it's actually no to the yes to the
it's a reverse and we got you we make the button look good to click and now we have all your cookie
data um and i sometimes take the like five minutes it takes to just say no save it's like yeah like
but sometimes it's just like it's just dreadful and it just ruins the web the internet sucks
right now because of the you don't want us tracking you well complete our fucking 10 minute
like a hundred page survey and you have to like play spot the difference to find the little tiny
button that says don't track me please and then you can do it's like because they know no one's
going to do it but oh we got around the legal loophole it's just fuck off man piece of shit
i love piece of shit i hope i love legal loopholes i hope john oliver just fucking leaks all of
congress's data that he paid bought did he do that yeah um john oliver did something based
actually he um he he did a segment like a pretty long segment talking about data and how easily
they can track you and how it doesn't matter how anonymized for data is they they have your location
they have your workplace where you go where your phone is um at all times um what things you look at
and like they only need like a fraction of information to like narrow it down to one person
but they have like 10 times the amount of information that need to narrow it down reliably
like 90 of a time so basically they can find you easy you can't fucking avoid it um and you like
gave like talked about a whole bunch of like notable cases where people had been tracked down
times um a new studio went and bought some data from because you can just buy it for like 20 bucks
you can buy someone's data if you want it like serial like killers or stalkers or rapists or
whatever the fuck can just buy the data of the people they want to victimize and then figure
out where they live and their whole schedule and everything you could just fucking do it you just
chuck money at it it's fucked up um some news crew went to someone's house and we're just like
you're pregnant right and the and the woman was like yeah how do you know and they they just
fucking figured that out because the computer you know based on their browsing habits was able
to compute that shit so that was like the segment and then John all was like okay so you know you
can get a lot of really personal information you can also find out what websites people look at and
like to some extent their internet history and other shit so he basically figured out like
everyone in congress bought all of their data all of it he has dirt on every single one of him and
he's like if you don't want me to release this you better make it illegal for me to release it
because right now there's nothing legally stopping me wow um huh he's like blackmail uh nifty pretty
cool it's kind of neat but it's legal because he's allowed he's allowed to play funny they haven't
made it illegal to do that huh this is like when did that happen um i'll link the segment it's
pretty cool John Oliver little bass today um it's a little bit bass sounds a little bit
bass let's yeah it's 25 minutes but most of the cool shit is like closer to the end i think
like the last five minutes or so is where the funny stuff starts happening
yeah that blocked in the uk blocked in the uk
that's why that yes i remember this last week tonight i've never been able to watch them
only through people reacting to them in different videos all over is british
but he's in america currently trader he's a he's a he's a he's a what would you call it not a
class trader a nat nation trader i guess that's just a regular regular old run of the washes and
blocks i don't know there's probably other people who've looked at it the vosh pitch on all of her
blackmail's congress lol uh all right all right next voicemail uh is called i am scared uh here we go
there it is there we go three two one go so i've been listening to the podcast
seeing you react to my voicemails when suddenly a chill ran down my spine i've heard a voice
just like my own but it wasn't me i never said anything like that did i forget is someone copying
me how am i going insane is there an imposter amada imposter that's clever my own guess like
they're posting um there's uh two i'm seeing double ah i'm seeing double oh which which one do i shoot
yeah which twilight sparkle do i shoot uh you know sometimes there's just an imposter
among us and uh you just gotta that's just life you understand you know about life twilight
you're a smart cookie um what if my little pony played among us what would they do
i'm sure there's there's a thing out there about that i guarantee i guarantee there's probably a
pinky rose video where she's like fluttershy plays amalgas and she used my fucking vectors for it
fluttershy would be really scared the whole time but then the twist at the end would be that she
was the imposter she was so fucking sus it's so obvious let's see this fluttershy plays roblox
fluttershy plays minecraft you know that's a million view video right there the fucking mysterious
meadow well is basically among us because they all like like wear a secret disguise that's right
it is and they're all pretty sus against rainbow dash just trying to just trying to live her life
rainbow dash plays minecraft 20 cooler let's play oh yeah five years ago it's really been
that long since i talked to this person oh well of course it has i've been out of the
fucking my little pony community for years i just was pinky rose she was a voice person i i think
you've mentioned i vaguely recall seeing a youtube channel of a person doing a fluttershy voice
and playing games and then recently they had like a vtuber fluttershy oh boo kill him gotta kill him
they must be punished this person hasn't uploaded in four years apart from like two song covers
they did maybe someone else so maybe it wasn't this person fluttershy there's probably someone else
plays of something all right oh unless we made like a never channel for it oh vanamelon vanamelon
yeah that's that's the one i also have worked with vanamelon in the past who who it's i i wasn't
like a subscriber i just had seen that person before and i was like ha ha that's funny you're
doing a voice of a pony and you're playing let's plays vanamelon was someone who auditioned for our
anthropology thick reading in like 2013 and she did a pretty good job um and after that i mean
she was working a bunch of other things but like we worked with her in 2014 and then after that she
went off and somehow got a million subscribers good for her yeah very nice there what did she do
hold on i'll check seems like a lot of gaming content while playing as characters oh yeah
she's she's got a video yeah isabel google's anchor oh she's an animator
yeah i think she likes what she does maybe she gets people to animate i mean some of these like
her most popular video is an animation uh i'm clicking on a random video
yeah like i collected this random one this is like a vtuber puppet in like the top left corner
it's not there the whole time and it's just like this her it's basically just her doing like
reaction content when she just like reacts to like a bunch of little things um and like has a character
she plays while doing it i guess is the content the second most popular has pinkie pie streamer
video picture in picture but it's not animated it's just like still frames of her uh making faces and
stuff so i see okay i think i see it's a t-bap ripoff is what it is it's exactly exactly png's moving
that's they that's copyrighted uh okay next voicemail is a youtube link here it is ready
okay it's the it's a yeek studio i feel like this one whatever yeah i simply have no nothing
where do people just send yig videos without saying anything like say something about it
pretty clear last time that we don't have anything to say about if you just send a
yeek studio video or any video really we're gonna spend 28 minutes watching this obviously i did
have something to say about the company man yeah i don't know um okay anyway uh next voicemail is
oh god it's sorry it's a it's a vocaru oh boy there yeah here we go um i have it ready okay
three two one go music hello everyone this is the old man you might have heard me on youtube
channel limit breakers yes you'll see it came to my attention that my granddaughter twilight
sparkle is sending you voicemails i am truly sorry for how bad they are she is young and immature
and i am apologizing on her behalf don't worry i will make sure she will not send any more voicemails
instead she will play dark souls three and make a miracle video grandpa what are you doing wait is
that speak pi are you sending a voicemail yes i've been forced to do it due to your inappropriate
behavior online but i've just been having some fun wait internet is no place for kids broadcasting
yourself at such a young age is too dangerous ah come on what can possibly happen someone will
force you to say the n word and nobody will employ you ever again or worse some creep will
gain your trust and groom your main now get back to your room young lady
i'm sorry that you had to listen to this you will never hear her again no i want to groom
twilight and make her say the n word how did they get it a cry with the ai they probably just got
a clip from the show probably because i heard like a there was like some funny noise in the
background maybe it was some sound effect from the show that was playing it's pretty sad that
twilight sparkle is gone and will never leave another voicemail on the other hand i am really
looking forward to that dark souls three miracle it's a good thing it's a good thing i'll just
talk to twilight i'll have her just come back and start only fans and start sucking dicks no
she's a pony she's just a pony yeah ponies don't have dicks idiot she's just a pony and she likes
baronies great off-screen grandpa and her just argue all the time about like whether like pyromancy
is better than miracle that's like a whole side i can't believe the limit breakers old man
it's twilight grandpa how did that happen did he fuck a horse he must have somebody must have
he must it's it's it's it's as simple as that it's as simple as that he fucked a horse or maybe
he married into the family who knows well then somebody fucked a horse someone did it was virginia
and it was me thunder thunder blue virginia i must reiterate virginia is not technically a
horse virginia is a homunculous is a horse like homunculus but it's okay she doesn't mind she
doesn't mind being called a horse she's fine with it she's fine with a lot of things she's horse if
you know if you know what i mean what is this video oh this is i just quoted it earlier i was
thinking about it for some reason i'm just a bro it's a really bad song covered by a really
really weird guy it's a story i might tell on the pcp someday it was it involves saberspark and
a bunch of other people actually interesting is this is this a parody of something
it's like a parody i'm just a kid and life is a nightmare is that what it is i think so yeah
but it says i'm just a brony and i like paoni that's great i'm glad you kept the rhyme scheme
dude these ponies go on magical adventures the next voicemail just says ben your page is really
good you should do a comic hahaha slime punishment kickstarter coming soon ish um next one is called
the deep symbolism of the egg uh there posting it okay three two one go you see the graveyard in
the procrastinator's podcast symbolizes death and decay the fact that everything comes to an
end eventually just like this podcast the egg in the workaholics podcast is a symbol of rebirth
and a beginning hope i see by inviting twilight sparkle their podcast grew in size this is what
eggs mean subscribe to vaude vidya for more lore well i get it the the opposite of a graveyard is an egg
dude makes it looks like an egg yeah it's i guess what if you stuck a tiny little straw
into an egg wow don't just suck and just suck the yoke out and just drank the yoke out of no
and like you didn't break the membrane you just kind of drained the yoke so all that's left
is just a thin little empty like yoke membrane inside of well if you did that then i would think
you're an insane person and i wouldn't talk to you the yoke tastes good you gotta put your
toast in it not not through a fucking slipper through a straw i need it pure i don't want to
dilute that that yoke with disgusting toast i just want the straight i want the straight dope
i want to have eggs on toast i've never done it i've never done it what do you mean you've
what do you mean you've never had eggs on toast i just never had it i've never really had eggs
growing up i hated eggs when i was a kid and i only started like them like as an adult and even
then only sometimes get a get a frank pan throw an egg at it i eat eggs all day eggs all the time
i eat egg wraps actually i'm all out of tortillas i have no more tortillas i have egg toast bacon
for breakfast every other day very nice eggs make me feel we're not like eggs make me feel a little
sick on their own like i have to like have them yeah they're good squished into a bread sounds
like it would be good maybe we should get some bread so i can make toast i've never had never
had toast before whoa wait really no i was just doing a thing oh okay yeah
what is this spaghetti right i had to you talk of spaghetti on toast is good
you're what you're you're less than human i've heard of people eating spaghetti sandwiches
i've never really done it i know people do it i've never heard of spaghetti on toast
do you mean like like spaghetti with a like a sauce mixed in yeah like like like tin spaghetti
you know um not not like spaghetti spaghetti but spagetti owes a gross they taste like water
came to america heard so much chocolate spaghetti owes were disgusting they're terrible they're not
good no no but like there there is some like good tin spaghetti it's good with like some cheese
mixed in actually and yeah like i've never i've never had canned spaghetti actually i just um
make it cook pasta in a in a pot yeah um wadis was like the good brand in new Zealand at least
i'm pretty sure they make pretty good tin spaghetti you just put it in a bowl uh microwave it mixing
some cheese and um yeah like you have it on toast and it's fucking delicious and it's like in
new zealand like sort of breakfast thing um that's so messed up our places do like things
really are upside down and backwards down there i guess it's not too different from also a thing
i guess it's not too weird like different from like beans on toast in tomato sauce it's just like
the spaghetti is a carbohydrate you're eating it on top of another carbohydrate
that's too many beans on toast i think beans on toast is something that americans think is weird
but i i've had it and i think it's all right i kind of like it yeah it's just like a protein and
tomato flavor with a bread yeah we also make um spaghetti pizzas they're also very common like
it's like a homemade thing you do in new zealand she just put spaghetti on everything
like like tin spaghetti you just make a pizza you make make make some dough put
spaghetti as the base and you can add like other toppings and stuff to it and you just
all right i guess like i guess i get that because it's tomatoes they're both tomato sauce based
like mac and cheese pizza is a thing in america i mean how much of a stretch is it well i've never
had this i have a thought that much it's not that much of a thing i have a thought new zealand
is close to like asia and for some reason sort of asian thing like i've heard of like asian
mcdonald's having spaghetti could it be that that's like a that's like a thing that's what
trixie said about no well they she said it about the philippines there was that philippines restaurant
that had spaghetti right that chain ocean and i think no i think you're right i think maybe i have
seen maybe i've seen pictures of spaghetti at like asian mcdonald's i think you're right so like maybe
that is just that quadrant of the world has spaghetti as a as a topping or like as a more of
a thing you i don't know because they got noodles maybe i don't think new zealand's like close to
asia though new zealand's pretty like just far away from everything i mean it's pretty far away
for everything but like i mean i mean would you describe australia as being close to asia
it's closer but it like oh that's actually even further i mean it's a long way from italy it's
this thing i'm thinking of i think new zealand's one of the most remote one of the more remote
quote unquote western countries because if i try and think of like how many like italian like
like authentic italian restaurants there are in new zealand there's probably not that many because
like it's a long trip italian food is not common in new zealand um and when you find it it's not
great i i usually think of new zealand as being basically like right off the coast of australia
but no it's actually like really far yeah yeah it's like the entire like length of mexico away
it's like it's like flying to australia is like three and a half hours by plane
oh wow that's a decent distance yeah that's like that's what i know it's like traveling to
fucking uh grease from where i am maybe a bit further i lived near the top of the north island
and i've lived near the bottom of the south island i've lived all over new zealand i miss a lot of
things about it like a hundred percent completed new zealand would you say not entirely i haven't
been to stewart island stewart island is like the furred island that's like small off the bottom
it's like really small there's like a town there but i haven't been that far down oh i can see the
tiny tiny tiny little island like way down below on the map i can't i can't even
wait is it the Auckland's oh i was looking at the i was looking at the Auckland's that's different
i mean there's a lot of islands in Auckland but that they're at the top of the Auckland islands yeah
okay yeah this this is fucking stewart island and in the in the bottom left corner it like
shows you like where it is it's a little box yeah i was i was looking at the wrong thing but i see it
now yeah it's like it's a lot of islands too massachusetts has marthas vineyard which is like
our own little stewart island well mason bay is such a curve it's so circular how did they do that
probably the fancy probably like the waves would erode the ground and in a circle fashion
but why why only there everywhere else's jagged well ocean currents they go in funny lines
they go in swirls and swelps and splashes on the grand on the grand line mysterious ocean currents
exists that will take you like send you to the next island like like it would be like the rock
there was very soft very easy to erode and so it's like a very like smooth beach probably over
there and then the other places are like hard rocks so they're like crumbly
damn geography or geometry now i know geology probably
geologist geography geometry all of these things and more on the pro
procrastinator's podcast uh next next voicemail is uh was my samurai fan art wrong all along
three two one go in that video where oblivion fall reacts to interrupting death pig he said
then they fuckers have canon designs but where why did i never saw these where are they um
the canon designs have been shown on the pcp um the only i remember drinking by the way this is
from drinking moth i remember i'm drinking moth oh yeah i remember drinking moth drawings i
considered those to be the closest thing to canon i love drinking moth drawings i mean like
for for some of the nade fuckers like didn't have can designs i'm i'm mainly talking
clusterpunk kitchen wait wait no i'm i'm stupid i'm stupid that was not from drinking moth this is
the wrong one this voicemail was called where are canon designs of nade fuckers i will grab
the canon designs if i can remember what fucking folder it is and i'm pretty sure i know where to
find it uh when i was editing episode 295 i'm pretty sure i grabbed them all in the show notes so
this is uh i'll post clusterpunk kitchen uh that's his canon design okay
um vem snakes change your life yeah that's that canon design and uh tapekeeper you know
so so ben yeah the vem sexes design kind of came from you two oh yeah i i drew this
yeah because gib gib was so i think you designed it that specific image was four eyes maybe
or no maybe it wasn't actually our number i think i drew this i think four eyes might have
drawn something that i based this on i feel yeah i think you drew something for the episode where
vem snakes appeared and then four eyes drew fan art and this is the fan art maybe but yeah so like
vem snakes was originally i think i yeah vem snakes was originally green maybe it is vem
snakes which like when when vem snakes first appeared on the podcast i remember like devoo
was even there um when you're like we showed the patreon.com slash vm snakes which does exist it
had a picture of a green snake and then gib was like oh i like to think of it as like the you know
pump uh not only run away from snakes but were the red and black and i liked that idea so i took
i took that oh that's why did i say that back then yeah you suggested it um yeah you did and then
ben drew the snakes like weren't like in a shirt in a beanie looking like ben and that was great
and i'm like yeah this is just yeah this is canon now yeah so i remember canon designs
i had forgotten but yeah i remember that the tapekeeper is this guy from lesbian horse rpg
and i don't that's not his obviously that's not his canon his name in that game
javis javis javis yeah yeah yeah uh there he is the man himself
i mean if i want to be a little shit i could like like keep the same design and like maybe
change the color scheme but i am too lazy it looks fine yeah fuck it it's all good give the shit
yes those are the those are the canon those are the canon designs for vows free as for
large nose man fouls and lung man i never made canon designs as far as i'm concerned
all the fan art i've seen is equally valid i've seen a few different interpretations and they're
all fun so okay so the next one is actually was my samurai fan art wait what is this that's the
first ever appearance of them first that's the first ever appearance of them snakes
whoa was that's in in bail jade yeah like when back when punk didn't even have fingers
oh shit oh i don't hmm
i should read i should reread bail jade it's been a while then there was all these snakes from that
fucking webcomic sorry that choose your own adventure thing that four eyes did that were also
based on bail jade right i haven't i haven't actually read this i've seen this panel before
the next voicemail is was my samurai fan art wrong all along from drinking moth so let's give
that a listen uh three two one go hi drinking moth here so i guess i got confused wasn't samurai
samurai incarnated as mage's baby girl and mage lives in lythuania that was the idea behind the
image that's good that's good that's good no it's ma- maize baby uh ma- ma- ma- ma- ma- ma- ma-
and ethan ralf's baby uh uh rosanne or whatever rosanna ralf yeah may aka pantsu party aka used
to be in a relationship with trixie slash digi aka the real digi bro because the the the title was
transferred officially at one point and never reclaimed so may is walking around out there
right now just being the real digi bro and nobody knows yeah even she doesn't know
mage is different but uh that art you drew is extremely fucking cute and good and great
from last episode but i get it but now i understand why she's lythuanian and that's
extremely funny uh i guess there's two i guess there's two
you can't it's it's canon everything's canon um shoot me with it please
next uh voicemail is called um did i did i post it uh ben versus vtuber three two one go
you know ben you're free to express your opinions and shit you don't have to explain yourself to
anyone either but when you go out of your way to target people with your ire and then not explain
yourself you come off like a real inconsiderate asshole then you go on to badmouth people for
being unthoughtful like what's his face patent manning or whatever patent manning what kind of
hypocrisy is that who the fuck are you to tell people what they should and shouldn't be liking or
doing and you find to hate it but when you bring that to their attention unprovoked uh you're just
starting a fight you're making the world a worse place shut up shut up pussy fight me i mean i do
kind of agree with it though in just the sense that it's like it's totally meaningless that it
like is has become a thing and it's entirely because you decided to like poke the bear i guess
like that there was that one the one twitter thing if someone makes a bad post that you don't
like the reasonable reaction is to reply and say i don't like this now that part is fine but like
it's the it's the like acting them with the episode where we talk about it like well that was
because she screen she did the screenshot pity thing so i feel like she opened i feel like she
was the aggressor i mean i guess i i made the i made the replies for look who cares whatever
this is the biggest fucking non issue that's ever happened i i don't like this post and then
they're like like i i agree ben comes across as a fucking villain all the time it's what it's
what he does it's what you're good at but like all all this shit is so inconsequential at the end
of the day because it's like cool i don't like i don't like a post by vtuber and then the vtuber
in character is like what are you doing and it's like i don't i don't have to answer to you like
imagine saying that i'm making that i made the world a worse place that part isn't like whatever
but yeah like like i can understand thinking it's a bad look or whatever but like sure whatever
bends no stranger to that like that's not new like who cares just like like like do you do you
think that i didn't know that like by telling this ooh i am a little baby on twitter like
fuck yourself do you think i didn't know that i kind of look like the asshole sure of course
yes it's fine though actually it's good sometimes whatever i don't i don't trust any vtuber who like
like plays off the ooh i'm a baby fang it's it's it's it's a little little suss little i just don't
i don't like the tone of it i don't like seeing it uh you know she can do what she wants i can't
stop her and i wouldn't i wouldn't stop her if i could like whatever i just but i don't have but
i don't have to like it sure sure i just feel and you know i would not have like tried to like
instigate anything further because it's not important yeah well and and indeed and indeed it
it's uh i don't know you know i just she like because she was making posts about it like she
was using it for attention so like what's so like why not why not make a post about it
and add her with it like she doesn't mind she she likes it she it was good for her like she's
welcome i literally did her a favor and idiots like this are like oh ben you're such a demon
ben how could you that's a child ben that's a child you're attacking you bully put yourself
in her shoes for a second if someone if i made a post and so i'm quote retweeted she she unblocked
me she's she unblocked me after a while she screenshotted that she had blocked me and then
she unblocked me and then i added her again and she screenshotted me and said i'm blocking him again
he's like why would you why would you unblock me it's because you fucking want it you dumb idiot
it's because you like to play the victim you're welcome imagine for a second and i i can imagine
that's easily because i am a content creator imagine i post a thing post a little meme for
my followers and some person gets mad like screen quote retweets and be like oh this is dumb am i
going to like what what is the appropriate action from there i would probably just fucking ignore
it and move on but they decided to screenshot it and make a thing out of it and knowing that it
would probably get more responses from you but it's like it's like the transaction they signed up for
like i'm gonna yeah more attention to this and that person's probably gonna also bring more
yeah they they chose to bring more attention to it they made a decision that is what they want it's
clearly what they i think i think people that say stuff like this just don't understand like they
don't understand that this is that this is a content creator who is doing this to like manage
their fucking public profile right and i and if you maybe if you don't get that maybe you think i
you think i'm just bullying a baby and then okay whatever like many it's it's it's almost manufactured
drama that is it's like it feels like a transaction of like all right i'm gonna we're gonna we're gonna
have this little beef and get some attention for ourselves that's how it seems to me and like
right or whatever like i know i know with you you're just fucking having fun you always seem
like you're having fun when you do this shit so sometimes the you're you're always crowing like
ooh we talked about this on this pcp whoo-hoo and i'm like oh no yeah funny ben's at it again
being i i i i did that to be like i did that just to see what what kind of reaction it would get
and it and it got it it got the same one again like uh ben is the mean this ben saint character
i try i tried to be reasonable but you're just too evil just too evil and vicious
it is amusing think about the the because like it really does seem like some people
aren't aware it's like it's not it's not actually a little baby you know they're they're not they're
not they're not responding as if this is like two adults like making decisions about how to handle
an interaction this is they're responding as though i kicked over a little kid saying castle
and he's crying and i'm laughing at him yeah like i i wouldn't do that i don't like conflict on
my page i like to keep my page conflict free but that's i get that's for me that's for me i get
i totally understand why a person wouldn't do this yeah you can handle it you're a big boy
and very wherever they admit it or not they're a big girl um yeah it's fine that's right um
my my headphones broke so i was gone for a bit there i'm using my earbuds now
glad glad you're back uh yeah we're we're like we're actually wait are we almost done
no there's no way there's no way it's impossible um okay next one is ben's weekly reminder play
delta rune chapter two okay next one is an image there it is yeah oh yeah i i kept
fucking seeing this on google every time i'm like oh yeah phantom's revenge i need to get the image
i i get like ten times to find this there is not your game this has been pointed out to me before
there is a roller coaster called the phantom's revenge uh very unfortunate for for search engine
optimization perhaps perhaps uh actually yeah i think it well you can find it easily on itch
if you google the phantom's revenge yeah you can't find it so that's too bad
there's google slime and punishment instead uh next one is called ben just turn off tweet
recommendations vtuber problem solved can i do that though i feel like i still get
topic recommendations all the time i think there are like maybe there are options i have
browser extensions to do that for for twitter if not the settings themselves
oh browser extensions uh there's ways i assume maybe there maybe there are ways maybe there
are ways to avoid it that i haven't looked into the next one is a question or it says it says you
did kick jeff off i don't first of all you spelled jeff wrong jeff second of all no it's
spelled geoff geoff second of all no as we explained last week that's not accurate we didn't kick
jeff off we we and jeff all mutually agreed you're not really active on the show so maybe you should
maybe this is not the place for you and he was like yeah so no next one is called the pcp rap
let me get it here v pcp rap v pcp rap okay three two one go big bad brat more like big fat slur
suck my cock and dance while i'm in that ass are you just gonna sing it great great flow
too bad i can never sing it out loud in public also shout out to the best line in the entire rap
ball toy what a boy thanks uh he's just a he's just a burnt burnt little cigarette he's fine
i should have uh i should man i should have said that slur i want i wanted those non-rap lines
damn damn next one is called another cyborg ben saint sex doll
any more big booby ben saint yet another okay three two one go
hello there ben saint or can i call you benji or benny boy benji benji boo boo boy no benny boo
wedgie boo honey bunny benny bunny my little tater tot you little rascal you what a sauce pot
potty bot a hot bob in a pot okay finished task to weird out ben saint completed
no fuck i'm stuck going
that laugh that laughter half half of those nicknames are from fucking veggie tails
by the way oh yeah the the chocolate easter bunny um fiery furnace with the fuck
yes yes where they're like shadrack me shack at a bendigo a benny boo a benny band like half of
those it's like a fucking joke and a bendigo yeah or or i'm probably not saying it correctly but
and veggie tells you it's like a part was like i'm benny a benny boo a bunny benny benny and
like it's like a fucking joke and i swear this voicemail use like half of those yeah i i i i don't
know if i ever i know the one yeah i know the one you talked about i don't know if i ever saw
that episode but shadrack and a bendigo huh yeah is it a bendigo when i hear ben yes i swear
bendigo i think of oh more than going to bendigo to get me cube yeah yeah shadrack and a bendigo
sounds right to my ear some some people did something one time oh it is a crazy it's a bed
nago oh a bed nigo a bed nago oh you can't say that yeah i mean there's no r
a bed nigo shad shadrack shadrack mashach and abed a bed nigo abed nigo figures from the
biblical book daniel they throw yeah they're thrown at the furnace and then the angel protects them
got it got it because you need a big furnace to make chocolate i do i i need a bigger i need a
bigger kitchen i need a bigger kitchen to make my worms and now i can i can make these tiny
little micro batches and like that's fine but what a waste of time i'll never forgive veggie
tails for like changing that episode because there's the bunny song where they're singing about who
i'm a i'm a villain i'm not gonna go to church i'm not gonna go to school i just want to eat
fucking bunnies all day what the fuck yeah and they were like um um you're not going to church um
you better change those lyrics and then it's like okay i i won't eat tofu it's a new lyric it sucks
wait like in the episode they tell him to change the song no no no no like the episode got re-released
with the lyrics change because parents complained instead of i won't go to school it's i won't eat
tofu yeah it's it's it sucks but he's a villain he's a villain and now it's now it's now it's about
eating healthy instead of like like the original the original like theme was like cancel culture gone
too far it's so it's just a weaker theme because the original theme is like being like too obsessed
with material things where it distracts you from jesus and now it's about i just eat healthy like
that's a that's a weaker message for what i think they would want i don't know
yeah uh i didn't i did not know that but that's odd that's really weird like why would they have a
problem with why would it be a problem that the villain says he's not going to go to church
i don't understand i don't know villains can understand the motivation because then it's
encouraging us to be bad you see but but he gets punished i think in the end maybe somehow
or he has to change her heart or something you see at the end there's like oh it changed my
ways because it was bad okay okay okay next voicemail uh there's two with the same name
for some reason the next one is called ethan ralph lore might be a little loud three two one
go it's you know volume warning here we go
it's quiet so far
dinosaur sister rosaline ralph look dinosaur
oh i want to take ride the dinosaur and crush bin said if my name isn't ethan ralph junior
named after my father ethan ralph senior
uh yep okay
there's this very quiet noise in the background oh you can't hi man look at that the babies are
like it likes the dinosaur movie hopefully this will keep them fucking quiet for like
for like 10 minutes god damn
ethan ralph is a gentle they do seem like dinosaurs so says i may that's the wife of me from ralph
what is yeah this is this is a true american family
yeah yep hell yeah whoo usa usa okay there's a shorter one with a with the same title i assume
it's it's the sequel uh three two one go
my where's my cell phone
oh i think the babies that's lying with asin
i can't tell what they're saying oh yeah i say i'm with it their accent's too thick
look the father what are you doing
oh the baby just
the fuck is we're calling
found out twilight sparkle is no longer allowed to voicemail she's got to make a miracle build
in the dark souls three rosa and rossan the samurai ralph is no longer uh he's been taken away
from uh the phone that's toad's this is tragic turn of events what will we do without all these
voicemails in the future i don't know the episode of quicker next one no next one is called bendy
you play yugioh answer no i don't even think there's a voicemail with this one uh wait no
okay that's not the right this one is called forklift man the one we just posted okay three
two one go oh i'm currently a man in a forklift so at 50 feet in the air i'm going to use the
clairvoyance to this position gives me to talk down to you specifically ben seni i do not understand
the position you have uh not being somebody earthy uh explaining your position and assuming them
to just clairvoyantly assume your position and what is directly on our own uh about their their
shit uh you just just explain yourself like you did in the podcast to make no more sense i already
agreed to see but i grew through more and better after i listened to you explain the fucking vtuber
thing uh please on twitter.com slash it's also ugly or abitual no whatever the fuck explain
yourself instead of just like posting funny ha ha dunks uh i just i twitter points uh i don't
want to talk to that person i don't want i don't care if they understand i don't want to talk to
them there's also like you can't convey tone in a tweet it's going to be misread like trying to
explain yourself on twitter is the biggest mistake you can ever make when yeah like if you generally
want people to understand you that's not how you get people to understand you they're going to twist
something you've said i yeah i i agree it sounds just the thought of trying to like explain what i
mean in a tweet thread on twitter just makes me like sick like i i i i i just i'm not willing to do
it it's it's a nightmare i mean i agree with that that's why i wouldn't like say anything
i wouldn't just i just i wouldn't make the point if i wasn't ready to explain it i'm willing to
make the point i'm just not willing to explain it and i guess the fault and i guess the consequences
people like this yeah i once was asked for voice acting hot takes someone said post your
voice acting hot takes and i'm like well i think the quality of dubbing of any kind regardless
of whether it's anime or not just tends to be worse quality performance compared to the original
and there's also like you know i just prefer to watch things in their original form because
it's going to be closer to the original vision of the people making it and that's just better
especially cross-cultural cultural where certain things get localized and it just
takes away from the original intent and at the same time and it goes both ways because people who
you know i all i think it's cringe when people watch my little pony in japanese because they
want it to be like an anime like that's also cringe like watch english things in english
watch japanese things in japanese i made that tweet i got yeah screenshot it by a fucking person
who i won't name but she has she had like a decent following calling me ableist saying that
i was attacking dyslexic people who can't read subtitles when i never mentioned anything about
subtitles at all i just talked about the quality of the voice acting and she like this this horrible
person like like is is ableist and all this shit and she made this huge friend and a bunch of her
followers came after me and i'm like i never said yeah even in the screenshot i didn't say anything
like that i don't even see the connection so like that can happen and that and that was when
i kind of realized i'm just never gonna post an opinion on twitter ever again no matter how innocuous
it's just not worth it because i had to spend like two whole days that's fair dealing with that
shit and somehow a bunch of my friends got convinced by it i had to like explain to them
that's not what i said please actually read my tweets and then they will eventually like
after fighting with them over huge friends they were eventually like oh i see i guess you never
said that yeah it's so weird that like oops it's like what sort of people would hear on the grape
find that oh oblivion fall is ableist now and just immediately agree with that and just assume it's
true oh damn instead of like checking i hate that like that's my my my hate that for oblivion fall
my husband fucking hates dubbing of all kinds he's dyslexic too he can fucking read it
fine yeah like i don't know yeah like even if that was something i said i don't even think it's
accurate i think this was the is the i've been told dyslexia is mostly an issue with like paragraphs
more than single lines is it is the idea that because you said you prefer uh dub subs to dubs
that yeah i prefer so well well well dyslexic people need need dubs so you are attacking us
yeah it's like and i i immediately my response was you can do you do you i'm just saying what i
prefer um and what i think sounds better but like it's up to you what you do and like they
are like oh so you're saying people can't watch from me saying we should stop and we're saying we
should boycott him it's like yeah i did i didn't say that and when i tell them i didn't say that
oh so now you're backpedaling it's like i never said it in the fucking first place like yeah this
isn't backpedaling what the fuck that was so horrible i was i was um okay i mentioned i mentioned
last week some some people some people that were my friends that decided they didn't like me and then
decided to go and spread lies not even about me so much about other people i guess out of spite
or in retaliation or something and i was talking to some people about the some people had heard
some of that stuff and i was talking to them trying to explain what that was all about and it was
really frustrating to hear to see a lot some people's response was i'm i'm trying to convince them
these these things that they said so and so did are are simply fabricated it's not it's not true
like it's just made up and and some people's response was to be like well okay but like
it's not like they technically said it was a crime or anything like they just like they're just saying
that they did they're just saying they think it's fucked up that they did it not that it's like a
crime or anything and i'm like you you dense fuck the point is it's not true in the first place
it doesn't matter whether like what like what the like what the what these are details that are missing
the entire point right yeah these are these are these are things have i said too much have i gone
to have i explained too much about the situation oh you're fine i hope i hope not okay i don't want
to get into details about it but it's like these are these are it's and suddenly it's like well now
you know i i don't i they're trying to make me split hairs trying to make me split hairs on a
subject that is not even not even really germane to the point because it's like well they've
we've already assumed that this thing we heard is true because we heard it and now the onus is on
you to well well you know if you're gonna make these extraordinary claims that that thing we heard
wasn't true you know you've got to supply evidence of that but like we just believed the initial
claim with no evidence at all just because i know just because someone said it just because
someone said i wonder why that is is it just sort of like a general predisposition to like
believe bad news i think so i think i think it's just i hear that somebody is like a bad person
now and then yeah the evidence comes out that it was a lie and it's still hard for them to like
like accept that because they were so ready to it just to believe that the bad news was real
i think it's it's just a cognitive thing like when you hear something and and you
you know it doesn't conflict with any previous information you have you're inclined to just
be like oh okay i've learned something i guess but then when you hear some new information that
does conflict with the old information you're like huh well that's that's a conflict there's
some there's some conflicting information here well we gotta i can't just i can't just believe this
because i had thought something else i don't know it's just what the jargon was called out for
basically with like the vaccine like someone's like oh did you hear that the vaccine has this
crazy side effect makes your eyeballs fall out and he's like whoa that's crazy and then if you
that's not the case he's like um i'm gonna need some evidence that that doesn't happen yeah yeah
but somebody but somebody else told me but some yeah it is yeah but somebody else told me that it is
and like yeah didn't didn't require any evidence for the initial claim but if you try to dispute it
it's like well prove it prove it motherfucker yeah it should never believe anything like honestly
true i'm sure it comes i'm sure the evolutionary reason is caution is generally good in a lot of
situations better better safe than sorry like works oh there might be a tiger i i heard something in
that in that cave there might be something in there a tiger or a fucking bear or some
shit um uh better to be cautious than to just be like oh well you know like maybe maybe some
person person goes into caves says hey there's no tiger it's like um well i don't know i heard
noise i'm uneasy you can't prove that there's no tiger because the tiger could just be hiding
but i think it's a combination of those things people are more cautious they want to agree they
want to believe the bad news because if it if it turns out that they're correct that the bad news
is true um then they can save themselves from it or whatever they can they can survive longer
from the tiger in the cave what if a tiger what what was that cave like that parable of the people
in the cave with the shadows on the wall plateaus yeah plateaus came what if a tiger just came in
there and they killed them off i then i guess they'd be 10 they'd see the shadow of the tiger on
the wall as it was coming towards them and they'd be like oh whoa a tiger and then but unlike all
the previous tigers they'd seen this one eats them yeah damn that's a really makes you think
that's a real heads maybe a little
the next voicemail is an image
yeah i i don't know what this dog is but i can infer
is it like is it is it like um the inspiration for that future rama dog
sort of sort of that waits for his master forever yes there was a japanese dog who
he would follow his master to the train every day and then he would wait for him at the train at the
end of the day and meet him there and one day the master died at work and uh the dog just kept
coming to the train every day for the rest of his life oh no watch yeah shcw videos he's you're
just you're you're keeping you're keeping it real you're keeping on you're carrying the torch
and i have deep respect for it same big ups next big ups big ups to shcw videos
whose channel has no videos by the way but that's all right
next one is called spin dash spiral three two one go okay listen to you guys talk about sonic
in the last episode caused me actual pain so here's the real rundown of the fucking sonic robots
and whatever gamma is introduced in e102 gamma is introduced in sonic adventure and he defects
from egg man to free the little rope the free the little animals powering him and his and the
other egg man robots and he's destroyed at the end of the story so he's dead uh yes and two
after sonic adventure two e123 omega is introduced in sonic heroes i knew as a guardian for shadow
who had been locked away by egg man in secret after his supposed death at the end of sonic
adventure two he rebels against egg man for locking him away and vows to destroy all egg
man robots to prove his superiority adventure two takes place between sonic adventure and sonic
heroes so there will be no egg man robots defecting from him in this movie and his name is vector the
crocodile not vex the alligator sorry you got me both things wrong i finally i was here i'm an
expert on vectors but is there am i thinking of a different am i thinking of geck's the gecko
someone's name is someone's name is vex i swear uh maybe i like vex the alligator better i'm
gonna call him that from now on i found fan art vex the wolf oh there's a lot there's a lot of art
of this i of what i'm assuming is a fang character because i don't fucking know anything a fang character
keep it oh that way a good one oh this looks pretty sexy damn vex the wolf it's like it's like
starfox but tails wait wait what the fuck this is funny he's literally of a do not steal
character stop stealing me he's just unironically doing it doesn't look like much of a wolf he's
got barely any snout at all well i mean that's that's uh that's sonic characters
there really not that much of animals there's there's that one there's that one uh he's like a
sniper he's like a fox and he's got a snout so this not uh they don't all have to be like this
there's like yeah i forget who it is he was in that fighting game there's dingo the dingo boy
he might be a dingo i don't know uh okay next one is called uh it's another from killer prince
930 uh it's loading there we go three two one go ben stop reading my name as the name of the
message it literally says tells me just but oh my name not the name of the message and what's your
favorite the best do you think the gen two pokemon is okay look
like look what am i what am i supposed to call this message
you can just put type in like a the message name instead of your name even though it asks
for that that's what everyone i don't know i don't see anything else here there's no message
geobelinda 940 i don't know i won't call him that anyway my favorite gen two pokemon um
i like sudo wuto he's not my favorite what am i talking about uh is shuckle from gen two
gen two yes i think so i like shuckle because i in my head i always say fuckel and that's funny
haha hell yeah uh i'm just gonna scroll through a list oh crowbat might be it actually crowbat
might be my favorite gen two he's really good uh i like ampharos a lot i like umbrion done sparse
of course yeah those are some good ones there are some good ones for maryl
yeah it's fine it'll it'll do right like it was from the pokemon pikachu movie
pikachu's day out vacation we called it we called it pikablu back in the day and we liked it
god damn it next one is called burying the hatchet no sorry actually this one is called
good night three two one go i skipped one that's fine all right you know it's it's been a long day
that i've had a long hard day of work it's time to go to bed sweet dreams good night pcp
good night then saying yeah i'll see you in the morning uh that might be a follow-up to this
previous one which was called burying the hatchet uh three two one go hey pcp i just want to thank
you for having such a good laugh at my voicemails i really appreciated it really brightened up my
week sure man you know i've been saying i don't hate your guts anymore thanks you're okay i
disagree with a lot of things you say but at the end of the day it's just you know it happens you know
people disagree on the internet you may have fights on twitter.com but it's just it's all it's all
that worth it's all and good fun all enjoy each other's company yeah man i'm sure you're a stand-up
gentleman and realize i'm burying the hatchet with you ben said thanks just unblock me on twitter
at riley tweets r i e l y tweets just unblock me on twitter and everything will be okay well
we'll we'll turn over a new fleece oh i don't know i don't know about that i don't know oh i don't
know about that one actually not so sure if i'm gonna do that uh riley next
uh it's not related to that other riley riley tweets is some guy i don't know i think he's
got a podcast i think one of the other people on that podcast asked me to be on one time and i
said yes sure i would and then i got really mad because i one of the right riley or that other
person was like simping for trixie in some comments and i was like fuck you i won't be on your stupid
podcast so these people are trixie heads as far as i'm concerned so they're they're they're dogs
so i'm not unblocking immediately unburying the hatchet yeah no he can bury his hatchet if he
wants mine is saying out and ready ready for action next one is called vtuber more like ppooper
three two one go i think i understand what ben was saying last week about small vtuber
communities so it's kind of hard to articulate so let me know if i'm not quite right here it
reminds me of the phenomenon of shout-out channels on youtube that just turn out video
spotlighting random let's players who don't have a following of course if you look at the
comments of those videos they're just filled with people begging for shout-outs nobody there was
actually in the market to find new let's players to watch it's just a promotional theater where the
only one getting anything out of it is the channel owner exploiting gullible people yeah i think the
thing that makes this feel so despicable is that said gullible people don't understand that they
don't know the first thing about developing a social media presence so instead they shamelessly
latch onto this idea that the only thing between them and the youtube career of their dreams is
just the right shout-out it's a pathetic waste of time from people who want success but refuse to
reckon with the fact that it's just out of their reach here and this sort of thing is all over the
place in every form of content creation when it comes to small vtubers it's perfectly fine if
you actually do just have a tiny community of people you enjoy but i've gotten the sense myself
that most of them are just there to use each other despite the fact that it's a zero-sum game
where there's no growth potential but since they never admit to any of that themselves they just
pretend that everything is going great and all they need to do is support each other they made a
comparison to the crypto we're all going to make it mentality and i feel like that's extremely apt
it's simply crafting a mass delusion for each other but i could be wrong i don't really follow
vtubers what do i know that is a much i think you said it better than i did but i agree with
everything see ben if you just said if you typed that out in a tweet it would have been so much
better yeah it's just that easy yeah i mean i i can definitely save like shout-outs absolutely
can make a career for you if you're already doing like good high quality shit well of course you know
like yeah when i mean something when it's when it's yeah when it's to an audience of people
who are not looking for shout-outs themselves it means something if it's just a regular audience
of normal people wanting to see things yeah yeah like the audience has to be people who are interested
in the in the in what you actually have so like when i get a retweet from krakow unlike a work in
progress my patreon would jump up $50 that day like that that would happen um just a retweet
from one guy um you know big twitter artist retweeting small artists you know just just like
cheesy said like it can have an effect but it's because he predicted everything but it's because
the stuff i'm making is pretty good i think um if i was just like not making anything that interesting
i probably wouldn't get a boost like that so like it could definitely help but like yeah like these
communities it's like everyone's just fair for a shout-out yeah like the people the the the
number of like people who are actually like consuming their stuff is like small unless the
shout-out comes from like one of the big hollow life people it's not really going to do much
of anything yeah it reminds me of like um it reminds me of like uh a big big joel made a video
about small youtube reddit where like there was that one guy or something like that where there was
a guy who was just making i don't know there was a there was a specifically it was about one guy a
case study in like but it was talking about like on reddit there'd be like subreddits of people
that are just there to like ask like how do i grow my channel like how do i grow my channel
like just talking to each other just guys talking to each other about like how they're going to
grow their channel like i'm caring guy who doesn't have a large channel responds yes yes exactly it's
like oh no you got to do this you got to be doing that you got to be doing such and such and so and
so i like i read about it or like another guy i know did that and it worked or something
and it's and and it's like you know uh like like nobody goes or or on like the the
topastic forums like i feel like people comic creators would be there like posting about their
comics like hoping that people would find them and read them but the only other people on those
forums were other comic creators that were there to they were there to either discuss making comics
or to shill their own stuff so nobody was there to find yeah stuff to read i think it's a skill in
itself to like to know where to advertise it's like i i remember this this um there was this uh
reddit that i would occasionally put my hypocrite game reviews on is a game reviewer uh subreddit
where game reviewers would put their game reviews and there was no upvotes there was no nothing
no discussion nobody cared but it was just like yeah like oh yeah i guess i got to post
things but like this doesn't i there's no there's no one here no one is going to see this and like
find me so i stopped doing it it's just there's there's too many places like that too many people
trying to make art more people need to stop trying and just watch my content instead
yeah it's i think this this guy said it pretty well yeah like this voicemail better than colabbing
is sorry better than shout outs is collabing the problem is like not everyone's down for that
um yeah like some some good advice i've heard is like and again these things the stuff only
works if you're good at what you do because if you suck no one's going to come over yeah just be
really good like yeah i mean it's as simple as that no that's not the only thing but like if if if
you think that you're good and promise a lot of people who are bad think they are good but
getting getting around that hurdle like find people of a similar size to you to collab with
and then both of you might get a little bit bigger in fact the smaller you are the more
effective it is because the less chance your audience overlaps um and then that'll make you a
little bigger and then find someone else who's closer to your new size a little bigger and you
can sort of like hop back and forth up the ladder and eventually go big like that's a strategy i've
heard of that can work but you have to like be able to bring something to the table because just
messaging a guy being like hey we have similar subscriber counts want to collab it's like she's
not necessarily gonna work like um like what like what do you mean like what do you want
exactly well i want to steal something that you have in exchange for nearly nothing well if you
have similar subscriber counts when you'd both mutually benefit is the idea but like you have
to like also be somewhat good at what you do or have someone to bring to the table that they would
actually care about um never like message to collab someone and not without like having an idea
already as well like you always have to like absolutely it's like let's collab it's like okay
on what it's like oh i shit i didn't think about that oh i don't know i thought you'd tell me
vocaru yeah next one is is a vocaru link uh let's get it let's get it uh three two one go
who is ben jim and chendol kimski this is a question asked by every few people ben german
ken kemsley is a video essayist famous for his winnie the pooh video lecture series ben jerald
chiller minski is a retrospective of a human a man and a bear in that order ben jimmy skinny
is incapable of living a normal life he lives in a perpetual state of being angry at internet humans
there has never been a week and ben soldering iran's life where he hasn't gone on an angry tirade
attacking some random person a group for an imagined slight ben child finder chimney cannot
find his keys he is locked forever outside his own brain let him in let him in let him in
ben chokehold wokes cold is not your friend do not trust him do not let him in do not let him in
do not let him in
ben chokes chokehold chokehold wokes cold that's a great wrestle man kill ben saint before he kills
you yes yes chokehold wokes cold yeah my favorite ben child finder chimney
yeah guilty as char that was great i think i know who left that one and i liked
next one is okay next one is just a question i think it was spork i think that was spork it
sounds like her voice uh who is gibb answer in the email address and the email address is
gibbon is cute as a ribbon at silly dot com and there's no voicemail
there the next one we're getting down there the next one is okay it's the most important question
and there's also a link attached this is in the voicemail three two one go what is the hottest
metal gear design and why is it metal gear uh what metal gear re i think he said metal gear
ray okay right oh is that image attached i yes they want to have sex with a weapon i think this is
me too i think this is roxy that sounds like what it wasn't it like the metal gear rex or
something in metal gear solid four they had like the thick legs the weird like smooth legs
i don't know i don't know anything let me type it in middle gear smooth legs
metal gear smooth legs what what what is this thing it's like okay yeah it's got like a
it's a tank but it's on like a sort of futuristic smooth like frog leg leg thing
oh those are some womanly fies oh these are from four right yeah so it's like in the future yeah
they've discovered that frogs have the best legs for weapons on the battlefield or something
absolutely i always knew it it's what i always said no one believe you uh the the hottest one i don't
know i don't know what they look like uh this one like yeah frog leg frog leg hang on there's a hot
hot leg hot hot leg hot look hey look leg what fuck yeah yeah leg so hot you fry an egg okay that's
all right there we go log so hit you fry an egg that's that's pretty good okay next one it is uh
wait no that's just the same sorry i i reposted never mind the next one is notorious rox
three two one go also congrats on the 311th episode of my comfort podcast
damn
so we got we got rip uh i guess that's rip munchie rip munchie rip jesse
yeah it's gotta be jesse the long hair and then the monkey tiny little one yeah
then that's must be digi bro and with slicked back hair wait oh no it's it's garlic house that's
garlic no no digi bro is the there's the beast down below yeah the the giant eyes beard and eyebrows
no i thought it was slicked back hair nate but it was it that's the garlic house
like no you dingus below that i know i'm look i know that i can see that i was when i said
slicked back hair i was talking about the nate but it's not nate hey it's got the emojis it's
got the emoji i think it is also supposed to be nate i mean nate got the red red garlic house
he played him in the live action adaptation pretty much i like i like this uh this drawing
i like this gleam the gleam remember when we used to have the gleam and the thumbnail
yeah good time i put it there i can't believe that's right it was a nice little thing because i
just finished the gurren lagoon oh yeah that's funny that's a funny
inspired we were inspired the pcp was inspired by gurren lagoon pcp is inspired it's true
can't believe her we're over fur of the way to episode 9 11 oh my god we gotta do 9 11
we have we have to re-enact it dude red con 9.11 we have to build a world trade center and knock
it down for sport just like in uh slime and punishment they they just did every every other
week every other week there's a new 9 11 when will it end uh the next one is called i'm back
3 2 1 go
i have traveled very far met very many people i have met a drunk Russian a man who claimed to be
funny and most important a samurai and through my travel i have learned a very very important thing
what are you band saint hello everybody it is wang chan here long time no see
yes i went traveling not that long and i've learned very much and where i learned from samurai
he says to kill low band saint for stealing scroll so band says you watch out because they had to
long time is coming for you i go train in mountain now i see you later wang chan oh you
should uh you should train in a mountain go you should you should bring that baby to go and
train with you yeah just like uh go gohan and piccolo yeah just like him long time i'm so glad
i'm so relieved you're alive what would we be without where would we be without you
damn okay um next one is we're i think we're almost done they got like two left next one is an image
oh it's long whoa thing what is this the whole thing oh wait we it's more bend boobies why is
their resolution so low this is like it's so small it's a bitch they fucked up i can barely read it
you stupid punk oh bitch ass i zoomed in i can't really read the text but i can see that i am there
and i also have big boobies that's pretty i think it says all right next voicemail it's so
fucking small it sucks by new we gotta get we gotta get a high res we gotta get a blue
rave at least at this one all right next voicemail please listen all the way through from
sssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssss something asshole dot com lol okay free to uh i can i can like
vaguely make out the words it's difficult bend looking sexo low oh and pigs at the end
nice i wish i really it looks really good this is a this is a this is a great little
piece of art here that i can't read the dialogue on because this fucking
the resolution's too bad, but it looks great.
I think this is the same person that drew you
with the big boobs getting the award.
Oh yeah, yeah, it might be.
I think this is that same person.
Give him an inch and they'll take my splinch.
It's true.
That is what you say.
That I said it, now it's gotta be like a catchphrase.
There's no shut your fuck Gib is what I'm saying.
Oh, I want to read it.
No, send it again, please.
Try again next week, I hope.
I hope to read.
Also, who are you?
Do you do art elsewhere?
I would like to follow you.
Also, who are you?
Well, at the very top, it says by new.
By new.
Well, I'm sure that'll be easy to track down.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's very helpful.
New artist.
Yeah, that's not gonna get me anywhere.
Next one is an image, this is the last one.
It's giraffe rig.
Psychic and normal, friendly looking, quirky, funny, cute,
the only fucking giraffe Pokemon, the gayest IRL animal.
You can search it.
Oh, horse Pokemon equals cool moves, stump, ground, fight
type abilities, horse cock, horse cock.
Looks like it's wearing pants.
One piece taught us that a giraffe is a type of cow,
not a type of horse.
So get that checks out with the little weird bubbles
on its head.
Ethically diverse coloring because it has white and brown
because it's a white and black.
Yeah, and yellow like those guys and it's like those guys
in Star Trek with the white and black face,
easily fan artable, easily anthropomorphizable.
No, there's that one old episode from the original series
where the guys whose faces are literally splitting black
and white like half down their face.
Like that Zetsu from Naruto.
Probably.
He's like a plant man and he's black and white and a plant.
Freakish chimera creature with two heads,
360 lookout view, never lonely,
self-masterbutory capabilities.
Guess what, buddy?
I too have self-masterbutory capabilities
and I can tell you they're a huge evolutionary advantage.
So I agree.
This one has no evolution,
even weird or doesn't lose its identity.
Yeah, I can see the appeal of giraffe rig.
I've never really looked too hard at it
because it's like, ah, it's just sort of an animal
but it does have a very odd tail.
Psychic normal is a good type combo.
I think normal nullifies both of psychics,
or two out of psychics, three weaknesses.
Psychic nullifies normal's only weakness.
Like that's pretty good.
You can't, it's undeniable.
Why does it say wrong at the top?
Were we talking about giraffe rig?
Did I say something?
Did I cast dispersions on giraffe rig?
If so, I was wrong to do so.
Or maybe this is the voicemailer
who asked what your favorite gen two Pokemon is.
And this is a response, whatever we said.
Oh yes, it was.
Actually, it is that guy, something killer 930.
It's the same guy, so you're right.
Honestly, giraffe rig is pretty good.
Yeah, you've sold me with the same age.
Yeah.
All right, that's it, that's the last voicemail.
We're done.
Finally, it's been four and a half hours.
My God.
It's been almost five hours, actually.
Oh, really?
Well, no, no, four and a half.
Four, four 40 for me.
Damn.
Yeah.
Well,
any last words, gentlemen?
Gentlemen.
General people.
I'm looking at gen two Pokemon.
Which one do I wanna smash?
That's gonna be my favorite.
Is low-pony gen two?
No, that's beyond an Umbreon are in there.
They're decent.
It's really an Umbreon a lot.
Is that a lot in gen two that I wanna smash, to be honest?
I know it's a legendary and that's lame,
but I do kinda like Lugia.
I think Lugia is pretty cool.
Is Lugia the one with the baseball hands?
Baseball mitt hands, yeah.
Big catcher mitt hands.
They can catch any ball.
Damn, any ball, really?
Could even Lugia make a ball so big
that even he couldn't catch it?
Ah, it doesn't exist.
Oh, you know, I'm not very familiar with generation two.
I keep mixing up a bunch of them for being in generation three
because I hadn't played two when I played generation three.
So I assumed like Natu was generation three and stuff.
I didn't realize Corsola was gen two.
I thought he was newer than that.
Heracross is cool, I like Heracross a lot.
I like Foratress because he's a spear.
I do like Foratress a lot.
Foratress is awesome.
You know what?
I'm gonna actually gonna definitively say it's Crobat.
Crobat is my favorite gen two Pokemon.
This size or octelary is an odd one, isn't he?
Doesn't he evolve from just a fish?
Yeah, he evolves from Remorade.
Yeah, such a weird...
Did you know like Remorade is supposed to be like a gun?
No, you can sort of see it now,
but like Remorade's original design,
they did that gen two leak.
Remember all those unused sprites leaked?
Oh, yeah.
From like a previous very...
Yeah, the older version of Remorade just looked like a gun.
And I think the idea was that Remorade and octelary
were supposed to be like a gun evolves into like a tank.
A Gatling gun?
Oh.
An artillery platform, which is why it's called octelary.
Even though there's basically nothing octelary about it,
other than that it can shoot things out of its little mouth.
Yeah, it's such a like a just an octopus thing.
And then Remorade is just a fish
and they're not even the same color.
It's such a weird evolution.
Never understood it, but I guess now I get it.
They were going for something
and then they like chickened out.
Yeah.
Oh, Skarmory's really good.
Ooh, Skarmory's...
I thought Skarmory was gen three.
Skarmory's good.
I like Fan-P.
Oh, no, wait.
Is it says Fanny here?
Is it?
It's Fan-P, right?
Fan-P?
I thought it was Fan-P.
Well, Fan-P.
Oh, I don't know.
Bliss, I have a love-hate relationship with Blissie.
I wouldn't say it's my favorite.
No, Blissie ruined Pokemon Go for like months and months.
That's true.
That's true, but you gotta respect it.
I gotta destroy it.
Okay.
So we've settled on Crobat.
Crobat is the best.
Well, you like Crobat.
I kind of like Spinnerak.
Spiny Spinnerak.
Everybody loves Crobat.
I'm gonna go for Spinnerak
because it's a funny little squidgy spider.
I would buy a plush of Spinnerak.
I don't know if I'd buy a plush of Crobat,
although that would be funny.
Fair.
Fair enough.
All right.
That's it.
It's time to end this charade.
Yes.
So, hey, guys, remember,
we forgot to charge you for March.
Please give us some money.
Get in the Minecraft server for $5.
Get in the Minecraft server.
Build a cool thing
and we will look at it on stream.
We will...
Let's do a Minecraft soon.
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, we'll do that soon.
And I will probably be streaming Undertale right now
and this video comes out
playing it for the first time
with some people. Check out.
Check out Oblivion's...
Oh, right, right.
You'd not play...
Right.
You've never played Undertale.
Never played Undertale.
You've never played the best game ever.
Exactly.
The first PCP episode,
I actually skipped the first PCP episode.
I've never listened to it.
It's the one episode I never listened to it
when I got into it
because I'm like, I don't want to disclose
so we'll play this one game.
I know.
Crazy.
I always started with episode two.
Finally, go back and see where it all began.
Oh, God.
What was episode two?
It was like waifus.
Why, I think so.
I don't remember.
I think I listened to like half the first episode
and then like stopped because I'm like,
they talk about...
I wonder if I said Ryska even back then.
I can't even remember.
I'm sure you would have.
Sounds right to me.
You would have said Diamond Tiara back then.
Would I?
I feel like at that point,
I may have got into Homestuck.
You were talking?
I don't...
I remember...
No, you didn't get into Homestuck
until the PCP had been going for a while.
Are you sure?
Maybe.
I remember you got into Homestuck
because I was telling you about it.
Yeah.
And I'm pretty sure that was after
the PCP had already started.
I, well, I remember you telling me
but I don't remember when it was.
So...
I guess it could have been
when we were just the horseshoe crew.
I feel like it would have been in that time period.
But everyone, go back to the second episode
and find out.
All I remember is there was a conversation
where you talked about,
I'd like to get art with my waifus,
Diamond Tiara, Pacifica, et cetera,
but that I'll just be making fun of me
and call me a loser and it would be sad.
Is that what I said?
Yeah.
I ended up doing that though.
Yeah, I remember.
I had a little commission thing.
It's still on my background for my Gibb and Take channel
of me with Barger from Fire Emblem,
Diamond Tiara and Vriska.
And yeah, there they are.
Background for Gibb and Gaming.
Is it only visible in the full screen television view?
Oh, no, no, it's not Gibb and Gaming.
It's Gibb and Take, it's just the...
Oh, okay, yeah.
I was gonna say, because I know the image
you're talking about, I've seen it.
Yeah, I mean, that one's just cute, so.
Barger is good.
I've seen her around.
She's got a good look.
She's funny.
She's like sexually, what do you call it?
Forward to the player characters avatar,
regardless of your gender choice, which is very funny.
He just really likes you.
She's just gonna eat Foxip and Lyra.
Barger from Fire Emblem.
Oh, okay.
Not a player.
Did we even end the episode?
Goodbye.
No, yeah, okay, that's it.
Yeah, it's over.