Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast, the PCP, an
internet show with internet boys on an internet sphere. Just being themselves, creating things,
and loving life. I'm the best guy ever, and today we're joined by Hippocrit.
I'm embarrassed to be here. Excellent. Munchy wears tiny hats.
I'm so, so sorry. Tom Oliver?
I, I got nothing, just go. How embarrassing. And Ben Saint.
Nothing, nothing wrong with that. Ben Saint famed for making the PCP late today.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. The famous performance of that excellent live action play.
Yeah, I'm not the first, but I'll definitely be the last.
Ben Saint with this embarrassing track record.
Everything that just happened was really embarrassing and I won.
Well, how great way to start us off. And let's check in, because the folks at home don't know what the fuck we're talking about.
They don't even know the definition of the word embarrassment. So they've never heard this in their lives.
I know that embarrasada in Spanish means pregnant. So let's just go with that. That'll be our working definition here.
Embra.
Oh, right. Urban Dictionary, though, says embarrassment is the way people feel when they realize they've been spelling embarrassed wrong their whole lives.
How do you spell it? Put it on screen, actually.
You spell it with two R's and two S's and two T's. And two E's and two I's.
Oh, oh, actually. And two feet, two hands.
Wait a minute. He felt embarrassment that he had been spelling embarrassed with only one R.
Obviously, he left an extremely interesting life. Wait, but embarrassment only has one R.
Uh-oh.
Like, on the screen before me, I'm looking at it.
What the fuck?
Oh, God, this is a nightmare.
Oh, it has two R's, right?
I'm looking at it on Urban Dictionary as one.
They just misspelled it and got the wrong definition here. I'm going to save the fucking day.
No, no, look at this. Look at this.
And save the podcast for you.
Okay, seriously, I don't know. Edit this in or something. I think this should be there. Look at the thing here.
That has one fucking R, even though in the example, it has two, wait.
The hashtag embarrassment has two R's, but the example there has one.
The top thing has one.
Top definition.
You spelled it wrong.
And that's when it comes up, because you spelled it wrong.
Embarrassment.
An extremely sucky feeling that happens to adolescence, much too often, where your cheeks get all red, red like links to a new page,
and you just, just links to a new page, want to curl up under a dark bed links to a new page for all of eternity and slash or die in a hole.
Oh, no, I get it. It gave me the shitty definition because I spelled it wrong.
That's extremely embarrassing for you.
Oh, God.
That's pretty great. That's pretty web 2.0. That's pretty advanced storytelling.
These definitions have a real narrative arc to them.
They really do. They really do.
What are we going to do when the dot com bubble bursts and Urban Dictionary goes under and gets bought out by Al Gore and Hillary Clinton's, you know, Harpy's?
What are we going to do? Where are we going to get our top definitions from?
Well, the currency of the world is going to shift to the dot com bubble when everyone's just going to trade porn all the time, and that's going to be the most lucrative.
The currency is going to shift to the dogecoin, the most premier currency on the base of the planet.
The only altcoin that matters, the dogecoin.
Let's get into the fucking episode, please.
Yeah, please. Let's talk about embarrassment, guys. We, we, embarrassing, everything is humiliating and disgraceful.
What even is embarrassment? I don't know.
It's the worst.
I'm going to personally destroy this topic and shift it not only to be embarrassment, but shame, because I think that's incredibly intro-ly.
They are definitely relating.
For sure.
Sure thing in my mind.
And to start this episode off with a roaring start, a complete psychological thriller.
I'm going to reveal a homesuck-esque tier plot twist reveal here.
It may in fact rattle your cerebellum to discover art and PCB fans, but I was not always through a pollucid kosher display of an unadulterate esteem and respectable behavior.
You see towering before you today.
Oh, no.
In my young, informative years, a.k.a. yesterday, I was actually an extremely, easily embarrassed, anxiety suckling.
How did I make such a vivid transformation?
I'm just going to wait for my arm retrieval-esque, embarrassingly genuine, long speech at the end, or halfway through this episode, and then you'll know.
Very exciting.
So there was a definitive moment for you when you no longer cared about anything? Is that what happened?
Basically, yes.
Okay, okay.
Good.
All right, well, okay, go.
I thought you were going to do a whole...
Okay, Gib, what does it mean to you to be embarrassed?
I mean, it feels like you want to go away from people and you're like, oh, I sure wish I didn't do that.
I mean, what do you want me to say?
I'm able to tell me why you are a shame boy.
I'm always embarrassed.
I think I kind of like it, in fact.
I think I'm Stockholm syndromeed to embarrassment.
If I'm not embarrassed, it seems I'm not trying hard enough to try too hard.
Like, if I'm not embarrassed about how hard I'm trying, then something's wrong.
You know, I should never be comfortable in my skin.
Gib, how does it feel for us to be embarrassed by you?
How does that feel on your shoulders?
Correct and appreciated.
I don't know. We're not doing any specifics here.
Somebody's got to have a specific humiliating story.
That's the juxtaposition.
Is that where we're taking this?
Eventually.
Absolutely.
In the meantime, Tom, what do you think about this?
You seem like a deeply shameful boy.
What do you think about this?
I'm fucking horribly disgusting.
Munchie brought up the point of shame.
I think shame does play a huge part in the embarrassment kind of role of everything.
I think embarrassment is something you feel yourself and then shame is something society kind of projects.
Shame is the social focused aiming of embarrassment.
I don't know what that is, but I'm embarrassed that it's happening.
Oh, how embarrassing.
Oh, God.
You should feel ashamed.
We can just do that the whole time.
Every time you flub or anyone flubs anything in this whole podcast, it's like, oh, how embarrassing.
How high is the title?
Maybe if you should stop treating Doecoin.
I got to treat my Doecoin.
This fucking Bitcoin bubble is about to burst.
That's a lot to let me know that Doecoin is going up and surging right now.
Munchie's over there mining Doecoin with that thing right now, right now.
He just mined a new block and all the dogs just burst forth into his room and he has to go to jail right now.
Dude, it's just like...
He left, but he didn't mute himself.
Oh, it's just like Undertale with the dogs.
All right, shut up.
Shut up right now.
I have a tangential story about coins and bitcoins and cryptocurrencies and embarrassment.
Bitcoin, obviously, it had a big old boom.
Everyone was like, oh my God, Bitcoin, I'm a fucking millionaire.
And I was like, can you trade that back for money?
Because if you can, that's cool.
And somebody said yes.
So I was like, okay, I'll get a bit.
And then I went on to a thing and I got an account and I bought 0.01% of one Bitcoin, which is still like, you know, like 45 pounds or something.
And I was thinking, all right, I'll come back and maybe this will be 50 pounds and I'll just cash it in and it'll be a nice little thing I did.
Immediately, from that point, and I haven't checked, but I've checked like a couple times, it has done nothing but go down since then.
When was this?
It's the last few weeks or months.
It was up at a certain point and it has just gone down since then.
It may go back up, but it's very embarrassing that I bought it at the very point.
The reason it's gone down the last couple of weeks is because there is like some legislation in China and South Korea about trading and mining.
They're like the two biggest places, respectively, for trading and mining.
So it's been kind of like really fluctuating the last couple of weeks.
They've got rich Bitcoin reserves under China's soil and you got to get down there.
South Korea just said that they're actually not banning trading in South Korea, so it probably should stabilize relatively soon.
So hold on to it.
Okay. Well, I'm not going to get rid of it until it has more money than I put in.
My embarrassing story with Bitcoin, actually, I do have an embarrassing story with Bitcoin, is that I was really into like getting into cryptocurrency back when there was only Bitcoin.
And Litecoin, that was pretty much the only altcoin in circulation.
And Bitcoin was worth about $483 for one Bitcoin.
And I was interested in getting some Bitcoin, but at the time, I naively was not aware that you could purchase fractions of a Bitcoin.
I had like $100, but I thought you had to buy one whole Bitcoin.
So I don't have $500 to buy a Bitcoin with, so I didn't.
And if I had just spent that $100, if I had done the research, I would have thousands of dollars right now because it's multiplied by what, like 400 times in value.
So I could have gotten like $4,000 for my $100 investment if I had just done a little bit more research.
So that's really embarrassing.
Kind of hit myself.
Guys, this is important.
Wait, Munchy, Ben was going to say something.
I just have to let you all know that I'm on coinmarketcap.com right now, and Dogecoin is actually skyrocketing.
Oh, hell yes!
Dogecoin is like fucking peaking.
Yeah, if you were in the call the whole time, you'd have known that Dogecoin passed $2 billion in market worth, like the entire market of Dogecoin worth like $2 billion a couple days ago.
Yeah, it's like doubly embarrassing for me.
Not only did the one I pick immediately go down, but it was the wrong one that I picked.
Did you get Bitcoin Cash instead of Bitcoin whatever the wrong one is?
I don't know fucking anything.
Just of relevance, I just want to point out again that my friend Colin did in fact run a marathon.
His first marathon wearing a Dogecoin onesie.
Just putting that out there.
It's a fact.
Dogecoins, as of this time last year, Dogecoins were worth like $0.1500.
They're now worth a whopping like $0.1.
Not bad.
Almost as much as a lucrative PC penny, which is on the rise.
I need to leave for one second to beat my parents and I come back and talk about World of Warcraft.
No, you went to fucking farm Dogecoin by beating the shit out of that dog and wringing the currency from him.
He's just, when you defeat a dog, he just spews the experience of doing some Dogecoin.
Okay, this has nothing to do with the topic of this.
This is very embarrassing, our lack of professionalism.
Save it for the cryptocurrency episode, guys.
Save it for the cryptocurrency episode.
It's sort of hard to just think of like an embarrassing, because like embarrassing stories of things I've blocked from my memory and I just sort of, I know they exist.
I just don't know.
Well, I wanted to talk about embarrassment and shame.
But I shat myself.
That's what the people want.
Tell me what were you saying.
We can talk about, I want to talk about like the concept of embarrassment, the concept of shame.
Yes.
Is it good?
This is weird.
Is it bad? How should you react to it?
I feel like you guys are, we've swapped.
I feel like we've swapped roles for this episode, because I always want to talk about the theory behind it and stuff, but now I want to talk about specific humiliating stories.
You just want dirt on everybody in this call right now.
I see how this is.
No, because I've got mine.
I prepared mine before any of this.
I know exactly, let me tell you about how humiliating and embarrassing a person I am.
So what I was...
No.
What?
What's interesting about shame and embarrassment is that they're so integral to all of human culture that's ever existed.
And so it's interesting.
I don't care about whatever fucking...
Shame is how social boundaries are set.
That's the boundary between acceptable and unacceptable.
And the way that new things come...
I don't know what Nate says.
I want to see what dirt you have on you.
I want to hear it.
We couldn't have the legendary Digi Brony line on the fringe of acceptable and cringe without the concept of cringe.
So you have shame to think of all of Digi's records.
Incidentally, fat shaming is good.
That's my favorite bit.
But yeah, we can do both, as I hope to do.
And I will ring the...
Like Munchy goes to beat the bitcoins out of his dog.
I will beat the embarrassment coins out of all of you today.
Okay, let me just tell you this story real quick and then we can get to whatever the fuck you guys want to talk about.
Listen to how embarrassing a person I am.
Okay, so when I was a kid, I thought it was the shit.
I thought it was so cool and so rad that I decided to enter the...
It was like the middle school...
Fuck, what was it called?
A talent show.
The talent show.
And so I did, in fact, enter the talent show.
And we practiced for like weeks and it was real crazy and stuff.
And I did a rendition of Another One Bites the Dust by one queen.
By one queen.
I did this alone.
It was just me.
I choreographed all my own dance moves as they played just like the song with Freddie Mercury's vocals.
That was just like saying over it.
Oh, no.
And so, I mean, let's just say it went off without a fucking hitch.
I nailed every pirouette, every backflip.
It was a 10 out of 10 performance.
No question.
But after I finished it, there are tapes of this performance out there in the world.
And just now that time has passed, I live in fear.
Just all my waking days are consumed with fear that this illicit videotape will surface one day.
And the world will see me just popping and locking my life away.
You know, one step at a time.
I'm officially opening a PCP monthly.
Exactly.
We gotta go on the hunt.
I will personally, unironically give you 33% of my PCP wage the month you send me a video of Nate singing Another One Bites the Dust.
Unironically officially.
That is true.
Give that to me.
Ramp oil, rope, bombs, it's yours.
But only if you have a video of Nate singing.
I just want to let you know, everybody, so your expectations are set correctly.
I thought I'd be like the coolest kid in town.
I bought a fedora.
I bought this sick ass bomber leather jacket that was way too big for me, but I wore it anyway.
Holy shit.
And no one at any point even suggested that what I was doing was a mistake in any way.
Which is really the worst part, because that's where shame is so important.
Exactly.
When you push against those boundaries, other people can be like, yo, you're on the fringe, dude, you gotta be careful.
It was only years later as everyone, you know, was aware that I had done this.
They're like, man, what were you thinking, dude?
And I was like, well, I don't know.
I guess I was thinking that that was okay.
I didn't know that you guys would be this mean about it to me later on.
I actually have an incredibly similar story.
I think I might have told you before about how I, again, in middle school at a talent show in sixth grade,
I attended a sixth grade camp where we just, you know, went up to some woods near where I live and we camped out for like a week.
Anyway, at the end, there was a talent show and, you know, you have rehearsals of the week leading up to it.
And I listened to the talent show, did not know what I was going to do.
I actually just had that as an excuse to not do anything and just hang out in the center where people were doing things.
That's kind of fucked around.
And then eventually, once it got closer, I just, you know, quit because I didn't have anything to do.
And then while the show was going on halfway through, like the stage is set, everything is scheduled.
I said, you know what, I have something I want to do.
So I just like walk up to the stage and say, like, hey, can I be in the show?
Like, it's going on.
Halfway, it's almost over.
And they're like, yeah, okay, sure.
I don't care.
Yeah.
Hell yeah.
So I get up and I do.
I sing as a sixth grader in front of my entire school.
I sing the portal one and two ending songs.
This was a triumph.
Hell yeah.
This was a triumph, Monty.
A triumph.
Yeah, literally.
I do that.
And the thing is, I get off.
I don't know how well I did because I forgot some of the words during it.
And then I get off and then like when we're going back to our house, everyone is like
cheering me and saying how good of a job it was and how much they love video games and
how much I understood what I was referencing.
And the one guy told me the cake was a lie and this was the only time in my entire life
I felt validated by the people around me in school.
And I was so happy that I did it.
It was the best experience of my fucking life.
I completely nailed those songs.
Yeah.
That's how I felt.
I felt like everyone knew you loved video games.
The only thing I couldn't believe was that I didn't win first place.
I was dumbfounded by the fact that anyone could be chosen over my performance.
Such as life.
I have a story.
I have a story that's kind of similar to that, Nate, about there was a play.
It was like a school play that I was trying out for.
I don't remember what it's called, but it's some play about the like it's like a court
case about like a science teacher in the deep south who wants to teach evolution or something.
Right.
I remember.
Yeah.
And I thought that I would I thought I would try out for the like fire and brimstone preacher
guy who like is like prosecuting the dude.
I thought that would be really cool.
So his name is like, you know, Mr. Mr. Black, whatever.
So I try to try out for Mr. Black and I go and I like, I'm like, yeah, I think I did pretty good.
And then a couple of weeks later, I see the results and I go and I'm like, oh, Ben got
Mr. Black.
Yes, I fucking did it.
But I show up to but I show up to the first rehearsal and I realized that what has actually
happened is they've gender swapped the role of Mr. Black into Mrs. Black and I'm actually
seeing his his her her spouse.
Oh, that's right.
The totally like throw away one line side character.
That's the spouse of the guy.
And I'm like, shit.
So I just turn around and walked away and never came back.
That's that's that's how you do it.
That's that was Dick move and they deserve that.
Yeah, I agree.
It was probably listed that that was the case and you just did not realize.
Yes.
So it's.
I just didn't.
I didn't look.
I could have found out, but I didn't.
But I just wasn't going to suffer that.
I showed up expecting to be like a main character.
Yeah.
And I'm like, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's the thing.
I would like to ask you guys, do you feel more self conscious or do you feel like you
are shamed more, which is more proportional?
Do you do awkward or cringy things and think, oh God, I'm I'm such a shitter.
I'm such a bad guy.
I'm such a villain.
I'm such an antagonist.
Or do you do bad things and you just don't realize and then people make fun of you for
it?
What happens more to you guys?
It's self criticism a thousand million times more.
I don't know because I because I don't know because if other people are just making fun
of me behind my back, I don't know about it.
Yeah, I guess that's also.
I don't have enough real life like interactions at this point.
I'm doing something bad.
So it's all it's all internal.
Like there's so many things that I've done for so long that we're embarrassing and I
never knew.
But I was too busy like contemplating other things like internally like, oh God, is this
art that I'm posting like really embarrassing?
Oh God, it probably is not realizing that like I'm acting and looking like a total spur
glord and I don't know until it's too late.
It's not like you're the worst guy ever or anything.
Maybe you want to give that a Google fair viewer images and see what you get.
I know it's unreal.
Unreal.
Yeah.
That's probably the most embarrassing thing for me.
It's not even my goddamn fault.
Yeah, it's not.
It's not.
I don't know.
I guess we'll just tell people if you Google worst guy ever, the literally the first thing
I'm up is Tom's face with like old video.
What happened is I used to I used to wear fedora unironically and this is what I'm talking
about in terms of I did things cringy without knowing.
And the reason that I had this stupid hat is that my girlfriend bought it for herself
and she didn't like it and gave it to me and she likes me in it.
So I was like, I don't know.
I literally don't ever buy clothes.
I don't know anything about anything.
And like this was back in college and when I was in college, I literally I never went
on the Internet other than like trying to post art.
I didn't have any social contact or anything like that.
So I had no context for any of this.
So I'm just like, whatever.
She gave me a hat.
She likes you in the hat.
I'm going to wear the hat.
And that that was as simple as it was.
And then I just wore that for whatever because like that just became part of my thing.
And then I just started making videos on YouTube and then someone screen capped it and made
a fake.
Okay.
Cupid profile.
Yeah.
And it's since become a meme.
The original like 4chan it was, it was the image was called Mexican Christian bale dot
B.
Yeah.
That's right.
Mexican Christian bale.
Yeah.
So.
You know, this is why, this is why literally everyone on the Internet needs a meme consultant
to make sure they're not making any massive boners that will, that will get them memed
hardcore.
It's important.
Like all those innocent young men who just want to take pictures with their katanas that
their moms are taking pictures of and can be seen in the reflection in the mirror.
And then their mom posted to Facebook and it's all over, you know, like you're fucked
at that point.
These need to go through a review process.
It's important.
So I was like worried about my artwork being too embarrassing, not realizing that I'd set
this huge fucking trap card for myself.
Yeah.
And, and you know, it's just one of those things.
And like to this day, every now and then I just get tweets.
Is this you?
And I'm like, I used to respond to them, but now I'm just like, uh, I'm so tired of saying
it's trying to explain this over and over again.
Cause now it's on the record.
Everybody can know, uh, give me, give me money at patreon.com slash save me so I can change
my identity, get some facial reconstruction surgery and just dodge this whole thing forever.
I think that's pretty great.
I'd be pretty proud of this.
I'm a little jealous, frankly.
I pray that one day I'll be a meme in some faster or another.
I long for that day with all, with all my fucking heart.
One day.
I'm not making, I'm not making any money off of this, so it's not all it's cracked up
to be.
Let me tell you.
That's true.
I don't care a thing about coins.
I care about fame.
I care about eyeballs looking at me.
I have an embarrassing story and it's, um, it was in school.
I was a kid and I wasn't a child's genius, projecty golden kid boy.
I wasn't good.
Like us.
That is so embarrassing.
This haunted me my whole life that I wasn't Mozart or David Bowie.
I wondered at least one of those would have been great, but no, there.
That's it.
I don't feel shame.
I don't really understand the feeling of shame, even though, like, well, I do, but
like, it doesn't affect me in a way that, like, I know when I do something that's cringy
and it's like, oh, well, it doesn't affect me.
That's actually really important, that factor, because like, shame, because of much of you,
like shame.
I think you'll agree with me.
Shame is kind of like where the boundaries of society are set, right?
Exactly.
Yeah.
Kind of embarrassment is you being cognizant of the fact that you're doing something shameful.
Like, so that's, that's what it is.
And then the way that society changes and things become less, like, like become acceptable
is when people know they're doing something shameful and choose to enjoy what they're
doing more than, uh, being held down by the embarrassment.
And then that's how things become socially acceptable and things move more.
I understand what I do that is shameful, but I am never embarrassed by it.
So you're a cultural pioneer, basically, is what I'm saying.
By not being a child prodigy.
You may not be a Mozart, but you're sure as hell a Steve Jobs.
A singular Steve Jobs.
Um, I...
That's okay.
I...
So what...
Yeah, go on.
Okay.
I'd like to, uh, elaborate on my, my seemingly, uh, incongruent, I think is the word, uh,
like, like, incredibly easily embarrassed self and my, uh, munchy self.
While it's true, I often parade around my town in fully, in, like, full pizza jumpsuit.
I actually do that.
I'm also paradoxically very concerned with what people think about me.
I don't have, like, an on or off switch, really.
Yeah, most of the time, like this, in real life, within reason.
The main point that separates embarrassment in the jumpsuit and out is what my intention
is.
When I'm in the jumpsuit, I'm the star of the show.
I'm intentionally poking fun at myself and acting generally silly, specifically at my
own dismay.
He's breaking every social norm at once.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
It's on your own terms.
I am the clown.
It's me.
I'm trying to make people happy and get them to laugh at me for entertainment's sake.
But when I'm not intentionally acting foolish and some part of my personality or, like,
quirk of habit shows, I'm not prepared for the public to see, that's far more terrifying
than an entire crowd of people laughing at me.
It's the old phenomenon of a girl being embarrassed in my anime, the only media I understand,
or thing I understand.
Uh, when you walk in on them changing, they're in their underwear.
Ah, so has Kashi, so embarrassed, a blush and punch.
But if you see him in a bathing suit, it's no big deal, even though it's, like, literally
the exact same thing, just because they're expecting people to view them in this situation.
So, uh, yeah, you know, it's an interesting distinction.
I think, maybe I was wrong about, like, the embarrassment, because I have that anime
Deku Makura pillow now, like, I got it for a sponsored video.
Welcome to the club.
The best video of the year so far.
Uh, yes, I like it.
And it was like, oh, I was making fun of, like, oh, I'm a freak, oh, ha ha, and I pushed
on Twitter, like, oh, look at, look at how degenerate I am or whatever.
But posting it online is, is fine.
I don't actually feel embarrassed about that, otherwise I would not post it.
But it's a couple times when my parents knock on the door and they come in, I have to, like,
oh, I look over and it's like, the face is there, I have to cover up the whole thing.
I have to cover up the whole thing with the duvet, so they don't see that I'm sleeping
with a cartoon character.
They don't know I'm meming.
Oh, God, I can't explain it.
That's exactly it.
They don't understand the irony of the situation.
They don't understand that I'm joking.
They don't understand that it's all, it's all ironic and a joke.
He says, intensely hugging the documentary while he sleeps every night.
No, no, it's, I mean, it's not even ironic in that way.
It is like, it's nice to have a big old pillow like that to hug.
The image on it is like, oh, that's cute.
But they don't know anything.
Like they don't even know the first thing.
They might think it's very weird.
They might think they should die.
They haven't seen it yet.
They don't know, they don't know it's there.
I keep it covered at all times.
So I'm definitely embarrassed about that.
And how do you bring that up?
Yeah, I mean, how do you just like, it'd be good to like,
just to let them know the information about, like,
I have one that is in my closet right now
because they don't want anyone to see it and embarrass me
because they'll think that I like, I don't know, like,
that's my life or something.
Yeah, I can't look like that.
But like, how do you bring it up in a graceful way?
Even bringing it up at all is embarrassing.
So the only thing you can do is just simply not bring it up.
And then you always know if somebody were to see it,
it would be embarrassing because you're not gonna bring it up.
I mean, really, what the best thing to do is just to,
you know, if they come in and they see it
and it's not covered and they say, oh, what's that?
It's just like, it's a pillow, you know,
like just nonchalant, like, yes, nothing big deal about it.
Don't, you know, it's nothing.
And then they're like, okay.
Man, this is the real shit.
This is the real shit because I think about this a lot.
I mean, I also have one of those opai mouse pads
with the boob on it and they've definitely been able
to see that because it is on my desk
and they come in and it's like,
but like, they've never mentioned it.
They've never said what's that or, oh, they've never made it.
Oh, you know they're thinking weird shit.
You know it.
If they haven't said anything for sure.
That's the worst part, dude,
when your head makes it 10 times worse
than it probably actually is.
Yeah, but I prefer it like that
when like, I don't prefer them.
Well, I do prefer them to never mention it
because it means they don't care and it's okay.
Like if they think in the back of their head,
oh, well, I guess he likes boobs.
Like that doesn't mean too much.
It's kind of okay in fact.
Okay, well, here's where my mind goes
because I'm twisted like this.
I don't want one of those
because like I would think if I was in a situation
like yours, what I would think that you should not think,
but what I might think is like, oh God,
they think I'm a freak.
They don't want to bring it up
because they don't want to make it real.
What a freak I am.
So they're just going to like ignore this
and pretend it's not there.
All right.
And we'll all just move on from this.
Here's a head thing.
That happens a lot or it used to happen a lot with me.
Like I would think, you know,
it's very easy to conspire in your mind.
Like they're not bringing it up,
which means that, you know, they know about it
and they're thinking about it
and people are thinking it's conspiracy theory.
You're thinking everybody has some sort of
like nasty thought about you
that they're hiding for their, you know,
to be seem polite and stuff.
And at some point I just thought it's really,
it's just a bad idea all around
to ever entertain those ideas
that somebody thinks something and they don't say it.
Like what would, it's,
it's just-
You know what's an interesting,
sorry, you know what's an interesting trajectory
that's like relevant to what you're saying right now?
It's like, it's been my relationship with anime
over the years growing up.
Cause I've been, I've been paying attention
to like how my, how my thoughts have been going
for, I don't know, the last many years.
But it's like when I was a kid,
I unabashedly was into like Power Rangers and Transformers.
And then I just sort of like Dragon Ball Z
and it turned me on like, I don't know,
TUNAMI and like all this stuff.
And then I just got sucked into it over the years.
But like in like my early college years
and my high school years,
I was definitely like embarrassed of it.
Even though paradoxically at the same time,
I was like exclusively wearing anime t-shirts to school
and like wearing Kingdom Hearts wristbands literally every day.
And you know, like this is, it was like,
I was both simultaneously humiliated
when it would come up in any way.
And also like displaying it to all the world.
So like what, I don't really know why my,
what the deal was with that.
But like at this point in my, in my life,
I've like completely swung the other way.
And like I don't like shove it in anybody's face really.
I still do wear anime shirts like almost every day.
But like I don't think about it.
And it's not like really part of my identity
to like shove it in people's face,
except how I like, I utilize it specifically
like for my online stuff.
Cause like of course I still like and I still do it.
And I've turned it into like a product,
basically my, my passion for anime.
It's something that I have, you know,
found an effective thing to like talk about online
and people enjoy listening to it.
So-
It's probably just because you have an outlet for that
now you don't feel you have to like-
Yeah, I never had an outlet.
That's absolutely true.
Me and Ben would talk sometimes,
but like there was no anime club in high school.
There was nobody to like-
But then was the anime master like you?
It's true, it's true.
I was more into these things.
And it's just like now I like,
the pendulum has really swung.
At this point I'm like totally comfortable
with the fact that I like these things.
Like even in like the T-Bap days,
like, you know, I would like make fun of myself
for liking anime and stuff.
But now like I don't even get the point.
Like there's nothing to be embarrassed about
with like liking anime.
And now it just-
But at the same time-
Are you more comfortable with it?
Or has it just become more common and more acceptable?
Well, I actually think that because I've become more
of an adult, I am questioning myself less.
And as a result of that, I think to myself,
yeah, it's just normal for me to like anime.
Why should I feel embarrassed?
That's just who I am.
Whereas when you're a kid,
the only difference is that you're less sure of yourself.
Like nothing makes-
Kids get embarrassed about stupid shit.
That doesn't matter.
They sure do.
Oh, they sure do.
It's really funny.
Like Lars in Steven Universe.
Yeah, I can-
The Lars in Steven Universe is like the exact right example.
Like he just is humiliated by things
that are not embarrassing in any way.
And just let's like consume his thoughts
and he just makes up these narratives.
Cause I don't know,
he probably just hates himself or something.
I think it's because when you're younger,
you don't have like,
you haven't like completely figured out your identity yet.
Exactly.
So everything kind of is an act that you're doing
cause you're trying to kind of figure out
what your actual genuine persona is.
But once you have that lockdown,
it's just like, well, this is who I am.
And I'm not going to change it cause fuck you.
And you know what?
In a certain lens, that's kind of a negative thing.
And this says that you're kind of solidified in who you are.
And you can't like grow and change as much.
It's like when an oak tree grows.
Like when it's young,
you can shape it and make it grow a certain way.
Once it gets too old,
if you try to reshape it,
like snap or it just like won't go that way anymore.
Yeah.
People's personalities are like that.
That's how like, you know, like older generations
get locked into ways of thinking
and your brain becomes less malleable.
And that's, you know, that's,
it's like a good with the bad thing.
Like you're young, you're malleable,
but you're also very vulnerable.
Which is why it's super important that people keep dying
so that ideas can continue to grow
cause people with solid minds,
they need to go away and die like like religion.
Religion is not going away
with like the people who are alive right now.
Those people need to die
and their kids need to get more and more secular
so we can get off the side.
They need to die.
Right up until me.
And I need to be the first one to not die.
Unlimited life.
I mean, I hear you, but honestly,
we should all die too at some point.
Like nobody brings that,
but the one negative about if we had immortality
would be that as far as we understand it,
our minds do kind of, you know,
settle into one frame of reference
in one way of perceiving the world
where new generation, I mean, hell, hell.
Maybe if we-
I'll settle my fist into your face best guy ever.
Fair enough, but I don't know.
Maybe that would be a way to like protect humanity
from proceeding to degeneracy.
Nate, what if we have an unlimited lifespan?
What if the whole idea of like solidifying a persona
in our minds and living that way
is just a consequence of our finite lifespan
and it's like a social kind of construction.
What if we had unlimited lifespan
and we'd never had to worry about getting older
and like how these like crazy responsibilities-
Hey, if that happens-
Our minds were ultimately malleable forever
and we were always open to new ideas,
always evolving, always changing-
If that happened, there'd be no problem.
That'd be you, that'd be-
People can still change their minds,
like even when they're old.
I think that probably like the mind is still plastic
and like if people were living a thousand years,
I mean, then they'd have a thousand years
for their minds to change, you know?
I don't know if they changed that much though.
I mean, I'm seriously, I wonder about that.
Like how much the mind of like-
Here's the thing, Nate, everybody who,
once everybody has unlimited like lifespans
and is immortal or undying or whatever,
then all those people will be accepting of new ideas
and everybody who wouldn't,
who would have their closed minds
isn't gonna accept immortality anyways
because they're gonna be like,
I need to go to heaven and die.
So they're all gonna die.
We don't have to worry about that anymore.
That's only one issue though.
They're gone.
Maybe they're more accepting, but that doesn't necessarily,
okay, well, here's the weird utilitarianism point
of this particular thing.
We could make it one episode.
It's, well, we're already on it basically,
but it's just, okay, if, is it right?
Well, okay, let's say we had a pill
that gives you immortality,
like your cells just stop aging.
But let's say I really believe,
and I have a good scientific basis for thinking that
it is actually good for people to keep dying
so as to keep this like refreshing cycle going
so people like keep evolving and changing
and through their kids who gain new ideas
and they're not as malleable, et cetera, et cetera.
If that process is helped of like ideas being furthered
by new people being born,
should we then not let people become immortal?
What do we need new ideas for if we don't die?
That's a silly thing to say.
You're so wrong.
I think, I just think that if we have immortality
and I don't think new ideas are gonna stop
just cause people are immortal.
Yeah.
I think, I think.
It's a degree though.
Society would change at a slower pace,
but because everybody lives much longer,
it's gonna change slower regardless.
That's inefficient.
That is inefficient.
People dying is a more efficient system,
and I like that.
I'm coming over to your house to kill you, Nate.
It's for the sake of efficiency.
Once we think you're at it.
You can make it argument.
We do not die.
We don't need to make any more progress.
That's it.
That's the end game.
That's not true because the finite has,
the universe has a finite time span.
You've got a finite time span.
Our planet will only be around
a few billion years and we wanna get this shit rolling.
Get what rolling?
Get progress rolling.
Starfleet.
Progress towards what?
Interstellar travel.
Interdimensional travel.
Starfleet didn't have immortality.
That's true.
Starfleet wanted it.
We'd be better than Starfleet by then.
We would need Starfleet.
Exactly why.
We should keep killing people.
The thing I was trying to say earlier.
I'm not even arguing for this, by the way.
When.
Yes, go ahead, get please.
The thing I was trying to say earlier
when I embarrassingly, embarrassingly
choked on my own throat
and Nate stole the whole podcast away from me,
was that if people don't,
if people have like a problem with you
and they don't air their grievances,
it either means,
well one, it means that you should just assume
that your good qualities outweigh the bad ones
and that people like you and it's not a problem.
Cause like, there was always this feeling that you know,
things could like,
things you do that are wrong
or like issues that people have with you.
If they never bring them up,
then that just means that it's not really a big deal
and you should stop worrying about it.
But if they do have big problems with you
and they don't outweigh,
like the good parts don't outweigh the negative parts,
it is on them to tell you,
otherwise it's their fault for getting so bent out of shape
about it and maybe exploding.
And so I just, I just like to live my life
like assuming that people like me
unless they say otherwise.
My class pecked is the thief of podcasts.
Nice one.
Got him.
I completely zoned out throughout that whole
like immortality thing.
I have no idea what it has to do with the podcast at large.
So. A little bit.
A little bit.
While it's nice to not be concerned
with what other people think about you
and it is comfortable to have that peace of mind.
Well, not peace of mind,
but you know, not have to think about
how you are affecting the people around you.
I would say it's kind of dangerous, maybe.
I don't think in your instance necessarily.
Well, I'm very observant of,
like I'm not using that as a crutch
because I'm bad at understanding people's emotions.
Like I can pick up on things.
I just, if I'm not sure,
I lean towards the side of,
well, they don't actually have a problem
because they're not saying anything.
But how do you know that?
How do you know that's actually the case?
Well, I don't, well, I mean,
maybe they have problems,
but like the point is overall as a person,
if they don't want me in their life,
it's up to them to tell me, right?
In one way or another,
not like directly like, hello, goodbye.
Like they don't have to like type it out.
But if there's no indication
that anything I'm doing is wrong at any point,
what am I supposed to do?
Am I supposed to feel in fear at all times?
I think there's a balance to be found between the two,
but yeah.
Well, isn't that like the purpose of shame
is like social shaming to show you
that the behaviors and things you're doing are unacceptable?
Yeah, and like, and sometimes it's appropriate
to push through shame to like do it anyway.
Cause like it's a dumb idea.
That's the question I wanted to present.
Is that, is shame a good thing or a bad thing?
And is the erosion of shame detrimental to society?
Because like, I feel like we're at a point right now,
like with culture that like there is,
there is a lot of like social shifting going on.
And there's a lot of things that were taboo,
like even 10 years ago, like totally out in the open
and everything's happening now.
And like, is that a good thing or a bad thing?
Cause like if we keep going in that direction soon,
like like doesn't society inevitably break down
if there's no more boundaries?
There is a limit.
There's no underlying values
that all of society adheres to.
Yeah, I get it.
Here's what I think about that.
I think the way that most people like say if they,
everybody tried to do what I like,
I generally do by assuming that the best of people
and then assuming there's no problem
if people don't speak up.
A lot of people would not like be self-critical enough
to change if so, if it's, it turns out that someone like,
that what, what, Munchie?
No.
Munchie, stop, stop mining Bitcoin over there.
You're stealing my speech.
I wrote a whole speech.
Oh, okay, go on edge.
I'm bad at speaking.
The most embarrassing thing I do is PCP.
I'm terribly alive.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Arm retrieval mode activated.
Embarrassment, more specifically shame,
is not only good for you,
but actively beneficial to society.
Eternal shame is a built in natural repellent
of bad or unhealthy thoughts.
It is your body's way of telling you that you've fucked up,
but not with the carnage of the flesh.
If you're like me, your mind will literally torment you
day in, day out of your past sins and the evils
you've committed to yourself and your loved ones.
You will never escape your misdeeds.
You could be having the time of your life at a party
or falling asleep in bed
when suddenly that one on-court conversation
with your home road teacher back in sixth grade
telling her that she looked like Tina Fey,
but way, way older.
Or worse, the awful, awful porn you've drawn of Tina Fey,
Then your thought process is hijacked.
And all you can think about for the next 20 minutes
to your sixth grade teachers,
all in variously poorly constructed sexual positions
with no concept of anatomy or what sex actually is.
This is your personal nightmare.
It's all your fault.
Now, clearly this is not a desirable situation to be in.
You're probably almost moved to tears or an anxiety attack.
You've started your suggestion of your math room teacher
sprawled out on what appears to be her knees,
though due to the complete failure of perspective,
it looks like her back.
And you're probably cursing me for the mere suggestion
that you deserve this fate.
And to that, I'd say it's your own fucking fault, buddy.
In scenarios such as this and much less comedic ones
where you've genuinely hurt the people in your lives,
you only have yourself to blame.
And you have hurt and lied to the people you care about
or alternatively drawn Steve Neve or Storyboard
to your point of them.
You yourself have committed social pause
or done something you promised someone you wouldn't,
something such as that.
No one is allowed to hold that burden but you.
Only you may inherit the she things you have done.
Just because they're in your past
doesn't mean they aren't you.
You are defined in the ways you,
that you probably couldn't even articulate
by your past sins.
And I think in good ways.
Now, just because I say the past still matters.
I'm also now currently, right now, next sentence,
next word, right next thing I'm about to say currently,
okay, here it goes.
Saying that the present and future are wide open,
like wide, wide open.
Like you, hold on, I lost track of my notes.
Like so many hot moms looking like Tina Fey
only way, way older.
Exactly.
Wide open, like my voluptuous reading teacher.
Actually, no, no, no, I don't want to, no more.
Oh no.
No.
But the point is you have done she things
and you've been sung by them, probably hard.
And that does matter.
But what matters more is what you do now.
It's easy to commit a sin and then curl up into a ball
and cry your eyes out, cursing yourself for mistakes.
It's almost comforting to throw yourself
into the pity party, rejecting your actions
with the same time in the back of your head,
trying to rationalize them.
It's so, so easy to do that.
I've done that for most of my life.
But if all you do is toil and regret your mistakes,
that's all you're ever going to be defined by.
You have to make that next step, the harder step.
You have to get fucking action and snatch your wrong
from the baby playhouse of self-defeatism
and throw that slimy fuck directly into the middle
of accountability junction, motherfucker.
You must move on from your life
and start to specifically be a better person.
Most of the time this will not mean
many of them you've done because most of the time
you have to let certain things go
because you've probably destroyed them
more than you can ever repair them
in most embarrassing situations.
And you know, it's in the past you can't rewind time
to make sure that you don't envision
your homeroom teacher naked during class.
What you can always do regardless of circumstance
or background is just remember.
Live your life and remember what you've done
and look out for the signs that lead you down the path
towards treachery.
Look for ways to remove yourself
from temptations and obstructions.
Remember how and why you did the thing
so you can specifically eradicate all chances
of it happening again.
Learn from your fucking mistakes, you slippery slut.
You fucking cheap dog food nigger.
You after you snap your life back into place.
Understand what you did and can do.
Think for a moment to thank the friend
that made this all possible.
Because let's be honest, no way you would have found
the initiative or power to change your life.
Even aside the most rousing of speeches,
if you didn't feel absolutely awful at the low point,
the original pit of despair and agony
you felt deep inside your testes
was the primordial soup for your ascension
to repair your fucking life.
People can tell you and tell you what to do
and how to fix things.
But if you don't feel bad and you don't feel regret
for what you did and you feel absolutely ashamed
of what you did, then you're not going to get better.
You're not.
The pain was your trusty, biological suicide of feeling
that turned your life around.
Are we anywhere close to the end here?
Yes, yes.
Okay, okay.
So next time you let a conversation
awkwardly linger for a second or two,
you cheat on your husband
or you draw terrible porn to the 13 year old
that you post on the internet,
know that the very pain that courses through your soul
is your ticket to redemption.
And that's the only way you can let shame
positively impact you.
You have to just, you have to take it
and remember what you've done.
That's why shame is good
and it will never go away ever.
And that's just a clear blueprint
to be better at everything.
Yeah, I would say that that is exactly
what I think about shame.
The only thing is I only take shame
from sources that I trust, you know?
If a friend that I trust the opinion of
tells me that I'm doing something wrong,
I will think, oh, oh, I gotta think about this.
But if it's just a bunch of people that I know are stupid,
then I'm not gonna feel shame.
Like if it's like a societal thing
that is like generally, oh, you shouldn't say swears.
Like, well, fuck off, you know?
Like I don't need to change because of things like that.
But, you know, that's why like trying to get rid of shame
of societal shame isn't good
because some people choose the wrong things
to like not change.
Like you shouldn't fuck children.
Ah, get out of here.
Like that, those guys, those guys should
try and change themselves.
They just, you know, they're crazy.
You need to pick and choose your battles, dude.
You have to always, you know,
try and evaluate things yourself.
And it's gonna be hard.
You just have to figure out what the people around you think
because that's what really matters most to us.
A lot of people will hear you guys talking about how like
it's what the people around you say
and it's all the societal stuff.
And they will use that, like, okay,
all these positivity movements
think that like shame is bullshit.
And like a lot of people want to escape shame
because it feels completely arbitrary
and like it doesn't mean anything.
That's also abdicating responsibility
and that infuriates me.
Yeah, like for the body positivity movement, for example.
Okay, let's say you're a big, fat, fatty piece of shit
and you want to, and people are giving you shit for it.
You're getting shit for being fat.
People are calling you a fatty.
They're making fun of you.
Okay, let's say that's happening.
Okay, so you are experiencing shame.
I totally get why your reaction to that could be,
well, this is bullshit.
Like what's even the problem with me being fat?
I am who I am.
They need to fucking live with these curves.
It's their problem, not mine.
Like why, what is the problem here?
Okay, what you need to do is
you can't just say I should not feel bad.
It is wrong that I feel bad about X.
Let's, that's it.
What you need to do is sit down and be honest
and analyze the facts on the ground.
Is there actually a good case
for why things are the way they are?
Fat shaming comes from a long history
of people generally being skinnier
and now all of a sudden we've got a big fat obesity crisis
and lots of people are literally as fat.
Like half of the American population is as fat
as like the carnival show Fat Freaks
at carnivals of like the 20s and shit.
It's insane and it's disgusting
and people need to fucking fix their shit.
But like, so there is a real reason why people say
like, hey, you should lose weight.
Whether they do it in a mean way or a nice way.
I'm sorry, I'm not trying to call anybody shit.
I'm not actually trying to insult anybody.
But there is a real reason why people experience,
you know, blowback when they are extremely obese
because it is bad for them.
There are real studies about this.
It's real, it's real.
You can't run up the fucking hill.
There's two different like aspects to this as well
because like there's the people who like,
I don't care, I'm gonna eat what I want.
I know it's unhealthy.
I know I'm gonna die young, but I don't care.
Oh, okay, okay.
Yeah, there's those people
which I wouldn't necessarily like,
I think you're gross if you eat.
That is degeneracy, that is degeneracy.
But then there's the people with the body positivity
who say it's healthy to be obese.
It's healthy to be whatever weight you want,
which is the dangerous stuff that you should,
like that is bad.
You should know at least what you're doing.
Like you can do what you like.
You can die young and fat if you really want to,
but as long as you know that's what you're doing.
You know?
The problem is the spreading of misinformation.
But see, that's, I think you're touching on exactly
what I was saying earlier about how eroding shame
is bad for society because in this quest to erode shame,
we're now misconstruing facts and lying to people
in order to make everybody feel better, and that's bad.
And to go back to what you were saying, Nate,
with like the fat shaming thing,
because like I don't want to pick on fat people,
but this is a great example
because it's very tangible and easy to understand
to kind of explain this more of like a wider context
is that if you, I think for me,
the shame thing has always been my internal,
like just enjoyment of something versus the external shame.
So like if I enjoy myself enough
that the shame isn't a problem anymore,
then I'm just gonna do it.
No matter, you know, like as long as I'm not hurting
anybody else, like that's usually, you know,
if you're hurting other people,
there's the, you have a whole different story.
But if it's just like affecting you
and you're having fun more than the negative impact of it,
then just do you.
So like if you're someone who just is like super fat,
eats tons of food, doesn't want to exercise,
and you're just like, you know what?
I enjoy my life.
This is what I want to do with it.
Like go ham.
But then there's people who are going to like
the fat acceptance movement and things like that.
They're doing that not because they are actually proud
of what they're doing.
It's because they're ashamed and they're afraid
and they hurt and they're trying to get rid of that hurt
and they're using this as an excuse
because there's a lot of people
that before this whole fat acceptance movement,
if someone said, here's a pill,
it'll make you have slim tomorrow,
they would have taken it in an instant.
But now they've internalized this
and it's become part of their identity
because they're too afraid to put the work in
to do what they actually would want to do.
They're treating the symptom of shame and not the disease
that is the underlying cause.
And I mean, I'm not always saying it's necessarily
always going to be a disease, every type of shame.
Like if you're, I don't know, just an example.
Like if you're like a black kid in like a white school
and like they talk shit on you
because you're black and different,
then like obviously that's not cool.
You got, you know, that's a reason to not, you know,
to fight back and shit.
But like there are real tangible things to, you know,
to get, to be shame for.
I think I should talk for a second.
He's as the token fat character of the PCP.
Indeed.
I would like to explain my reasoning for being fat
on trial here.
By the way, you don't have to defend yourself.
You are anybody else.
You can do whatever you want,
but you know, you can expect blow black.
Blow, blow fat.
Blow black.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, blow fat if you will.
I more or less fall into the category one hippo described
of I, my priorities just do not lie in the,
in the physical world.
I'm about the digital gamer world.
And you may mock me in the physical world,
but in the game world, I reign supreme.
And my favorite is top level.
And you cannot defeat my blade.
He is the platinum trophies reign from the sky.
It's unbelievable.
But seriously, I might like my parties just do not lie
in me living that long or me, you know, being attractive.
And I do realize that I am less attractive
than if I was skinny.
I realize all of these things with, you know,
fat being there because they're just true.
I mean, obviously there's going to be people
who like fat people and they're going to people who like.
To be fair, fat guy is kind of a look.
It's kind of a look that I kind of like.
I kind of like it.
I'm just saying, I'm just telling you
for your information guys, fat girl is not a good look.
It's not a good look.
I'm just giving you the facts people.
Obviously there will be outliers, but that's just, you know.
Of course.
That's just, again, that's the, what's the word?
That's how most of society feels.
And I understand that.
And while I'm not, I wouldn't say I'm ashamed of being fat.
I'm not happy about it
because there's nothing to be happy about.
It's simply me not dedicating like the runescape points.
I've never played runescape.
The runescape points to doing this.
One can recognize faults with themselves
and imperfections and not let it consume them
in terms of like, oh, I'm worthless now.
Like I have this thing that's not ideal.
Like I honestly want to lose weight
and I think about it a lot and it's a little bit embarrassing.
And like I want to lose like 10 pounds
and I'll be happy about it.
Until then I feel embarrassed and ashamed of it.
So, you know, like that's me doing it in my,
I very much practice what I preach here.
That's why I work out every fucking week
so that I can feel better about this.
I have accepted the responsibility
of taking care of this for myself.
It's all about responsibility.
It's about accountability.
I understand that it is my fault and my fault alone
that occasionally I'll be like, oh man, I'm fat.
But that's a fleeting thing.
And that doesn't consume me
because I'm not, that's not where my priorities lie.
And I don't know, part of me feels like
that shouldn't be for you either.
Not like you Nate or that like physicality does not matter
or that being attractive does not matter.
I'm just saying like, like for you fat acceptance people,
you shouldn't let this thing that is your fault
and an ailment of you consume your thoughts.
If you want to be a fat broad,
well then you're just a fat broad.
There's no, there are going to be,
there are going to be men that like you regardless
of how much we do not like it.
There are going to be people that like you.
There will always be a look for everyone
and you're not a worthless person.
I do not think you're a bad person.
But you can't just say that it is good
or it is healthy.
It's, it's just simply a not healthy
and I don't know a good aspect of it.
I think another component of this is that people
have changed this idea of tolerance
to like welcoming things with open arms.
Tolerance is not even praise.
But that's exactly, that's like the whole problem
is that like you can be fat
or you can be whatever sort of like socially
unaccepted thing you want to be,
but don't expect people to like fucking give you praise for it.
Like, you know, people give you shit.
Like that's just part of doing what you're doing.
It's going against the social fabric.
And like tolerance is not, is not being actively trying
to stop you.
That's what tolerance is.
To tolerate something is to say, it's there.
I'm not going to do anything about it.
And that's it.
It's not accepting it with open arms.
So like, don't, I think this whole idea
of like trying to eradicate shame is bullshit
and is never going to work.
And I think it's, yeah, it's ridiculous.
It knows it's never going to work.
It's act, if it, like the, the, the entries it takes
will be extremely destructive.
I mean, I have no doubt that the fat positive moment
has completely destroyed some people.
It has made some people feel vindicated
in their ability to not stop eating.
And it's just made them fucking, I don't know.
I don't know.
I don't know the stats, but you know,
it definitely will not be.
I mean, let's, let's just say there's been a measurable rise
in BBW LVR license plates across the nation.
And that's, that's a tragedy in its own way.
It raises paw.
It, it, incidentally, I guess I can't say
the fat positive moment is all bad
because we do have a BBW LVR.
But I don't remember the thing.
So, so, so, so maybe there's something to it all along.
Okay, that's fair.
Well, I don't know.
It's cool.
Let me, let me tell you about the time
I pooped in my bed.
Okay.
Great.
Well, I took a shit in my bed.
And that's, there's a little more to it.
There's a little more to it.
I just, I got really drunk one night
and I was, I was living with some friends
and I won't, I blacked out and I woke up the next day.
This was adulthood?
Yeah, yeah.
This was, this was, yeah, I was like 23 or 24.
Oh no.
Well, listen, see, I don't understand.
I don't really, I can't really explain it.
I just woke up after having been blackout drunk
and there was just poop on my bed.
And I was like, maybe you're afraid.
I don't want to hear this story.
And I was like, well, why would there,
I mean, my, my, I was, I'm right next to the bathroom.
My room is right next to the bathroom.
Why would I come into my own room and poop on,
like not in my bed, just on my blankets and everything.
So I told everyone, and I convinced myself
that a cat had done it, like a cat had shit on my bed.
But like, I don't know.
I don't know if I really truly believe that.
You know what I mean?
But we all know the forbidden snack
that is just pissing and shitting yourself in bed
so you don't have to get up.
Well, there was no pee.
At least I don't agree.
Unspoken rule of the PCP, that you have to,
that's the hazing ritual.
You have to pee in his bed to get into the PCP.
Oh, come on, no. There was no pee.
There was just some poop.
And I was like, well, it was, it was a cat.
But like, no one believed me.
And I didn't really believe myself,
but I don't really know.
And like, I had to take the blanket out in the backyard
and spray it down with a hose and stuff.
And it was very embarrassing.
You know what that reminds me of?
There's a story our dad has, when our dad was a kid,
he got, he got like hit in the head with like a golf club
and he got really messed up.
So he had to be bedridden for like a long time.
I remember this story and the story is weird
and I don't get it.
It is, okay.
But like one day, just like he's in bed,
you know, he's just laid up
and like his parents are better or whatever.
And like everybody else goes out
and his parents has gotten him a bunch of like weird
tasting chocolates.
So he's, he's just sucking on a chocolate.
You know, I was like a little kid.
He's like seven or something.
They tell him like, don't get out of bed or you'll die.
Yeah, that's right.
Do not get out of bed or you'll die.
And so he, he gets one of these chocolates
from like the bedside table.
He puts it in his mouth and it's just like rank.
It's just like vile.
It's like the most disgusting thing he's ever eaten.
And he just spits it out into his hand.
And like, okay, so he's in this bed, right?
He's got a melting chocolate in his hand.
The sheets are white.
The sheets are pristine white.
And like he's got chocolate all over himself
and the walls are right there.
So he's like, well, okay, here's what's happening.
And so he proceeds to smear the chocolate on the wall,
just in a big brown streak on the wall.
And then, you know, he's just living in fear
of what's to come.
And then like his parents get home, like my grandparents.
And they're just like, you pooped the bed.
What, why would you do that to the wall?
What did the wall do to you?
That was exactly how they said it too.
You pooped the wall.
That's what they said.
Unbelievable, but apparently true.
So there you go.
That sounds awful.
I hate everything that just is transpired.
It's strange, but it's stupid and infuriating story.
I'm so upset that it's gotten this way.
It's good to know that the Bestman family,
or whatever you want to call yourself,
has a lineage of poop stories.
I do not have one.
I have no poop stories.
Yeah, right.
That means it's coming.
That's a pretty stretch goal.
Nate shits himself.
Please.
You're cursed by the family goblin, the shit goblin.
Eventually, he'll shit on your bed.
How fun.
And I have one little embarrassing moment.
We've got all the speeches out, but I think
it's time for just anecdotes at this word.
Yeah.
Well, as a kid, I was just embarrassing as a default.
So I can't think of very many particular moments
that were incredibly embarrassing,
but there was a drama class that I had to go to.
And drama was like, oh, no, not on stage.
I can't do it.
But I didn't say anything.
I was just sort of like put a look at the floor
when they asked me to come up.
And it was generally a voluntary thing.
Like they would do some things in groups, like group in pairs,
and you've got to act out this scene.
You know, like, oh, no.
And I never did anything and ever.
Like I would never, ever do anything.
And they would say, well, OK, you don't have to.
And I would always be in the audience.
And there was this one time where I plucked up the courage.
Like they were cheering because it was kind of a meme
that I would not do drama.
I would never go up on stage and do anything.
And everybody in my class knew.
They knew that I hated drama.
And this one time I stood up when asked.
And they were like, oh, my God.
And it was really like the first baby steps of stuff.
So I wasn't really acting.
I was just on the stage as the other guys did something.
And then I looked at them.
It's basically, if you go to the BronyCon thing, it's that.
I'm just standing there looking at the crowd.
And then I leave.
It sounds hate stages.
You know, that's a good, I'm glad you mentioned that.
I almost forgot about that.
I am a little embarrassed of my performance
at BronyCon 2 for me.
Just going up on that stage and just, you know.
I'm unbelievably embarrassed about my performance there.
Yeah, yeah.
OK, mine was the worst.
I love the bit with the toilet paper, Ben.
It was really inspired.
No, please don't mention that.
I hate myself.
Ben, the toilet paper again, he can't escape at this guy.
Yeah, it's just a poop lord.
Poop story after poop story.
It's poop stories all the way down with me.
This actually brings up an interesting point.
Well, actually, two things.
One, what was the latest time you felt genuinely real 100%
embarrassed?
Because we have small and embarrassing things
that happen to us every day.
But when was the last time you felt like actually,
genuinely, like, oh, god, I really actually fucked up?
And also, second, maybe as I have this,
do you guys have a period of your life that just
was embarrassment central, that you can take apart
starting and ending dates and the reasons you felt like?
You know what I've got?
I went on that golden age.
I have a nega embarrassment a time in my life,
which is very interesting.
Nate, an urban embarrassment, please.
Yes, forgive me.
I think this was in middle school, like first or second,
like fifth or sixth grade or something.
It might have been a little earlier than that.
OK, but anyway, it was just like, I wanted to,
my parents wanted to give me a retainer from the orthodontist.
You know, like a retainer that goes around your head
and fucking fixes your teeth and shit.
And it was a big headpiece.
It was called headgear.
Sorry, headgear is the term I'm trying to find.
I remember.
It was fucking headgear.
And when we went to the orthodontist, like, hey,
you need headgear, I was like, OK.
And they're like, OK, so like, if you wear it at night,
you'll be done in a year.
And I said, what if I wore it all the time?
And they said, well, six months.
But like, are you sure you want to do that?
And I was like, hell yeah, boy.
Strutted out of the office in my heelies.
And so I just wore headgear for like a full six months of school.
And I was never embarrassed about it.
I had like no problems.
I have no negative feelings even associated with it.
It was a really a Chad move, I suppose,
only was completely unnecessary.
And I could have just worn it at night.
Why did I do it?
I don't know.
I just didn't care.
That builds up your reserve so when you became an anime man,
you could buy that vampire 100D hat.
And you don't feel bad about it.
Very true.
That totally is a fucking Chad move.
That's a fucking, that's a make-up move.
That's totally a give-it-it, isn't it?
And like, you know, I'm just going to take responsibility.
I'm just going to fucking do this all in one go.
That was the birth of weird utilitarianism.
Yeah, yeah.
Indeed.
It's true.
It's very true.
Also the first thing I said, what was the last time
you felt like genuinely embarrassed, Nate?
Like recently?
Oh, I would just say that occasionally at work,
at my real job, like discussion comes up of my YouTube stuff.
And just whenever that happens, I feel a little terror inside.
That is the worst.
Wait, why does it come up at work?
OK, there have been times when it has just like,
there's just situations where like I can't quite avoid saying
like what, like I could lie when these questions are asked,
but instead I'm just like, yeah, you know,
I do like some online stuff.
You know, it's just like a, just a little thing I do.
And nobody, nobody there now like knows very much of it.
And nobody pays attention or really cares.
And like I've shared a little more information
with some of the guys who are actually pretty cool at work.
But like, yeah, like one of the guys, this guy Brad
that I work with just said like, hey,
congrats on 60K, dude.
I was like, oh, no.
Yeah, there's just the fact that he could then like tell
like my fucking like real boss about like the things
I'm doing and saying online.
Oh, no.
I like to imagine like whenever there's like a cordially
report or like whatever, your boss interviews someone else
that just like, the boss just like,
so what subscriber account is Nate at now?
You're never gonna believe what video this guy just put out.
No way am I embarrassed of like any of the content.
It's just, what I'm embarrassed of is this crossing
of the world to these people who know nothing
about any of this stuff.
That's it.
If work, Nate, walks through the PCP door,
that will kill PCP Nate.
It's true.
It's like the meeting of the, the George's
or colliding sort of situation going on.
It's exactly what it is.
That reminds me at New Year's this year, like a couple,
a couple of people like had like seen on Facebook
and stuff that like I had a Kickstarter and shit.
Like a couple of people, these aren't people
that I like know very well or friends with.
They're like in my extended circle.
And a couple of them asked me about like the kick starters.
There was this one drunk girl who was like,
oh yeah, I'm really interested.
She had some shit to say.
It didn't matter.
The point is, the point is that it came up
and was being talked about and I was fucking mortified
that like real, these real human people in real life
were like talking, cause I have no idea what to say about it.
It's like, I made this thing and it's on the internet
and you're asking me questions
and I'm like, what am I supposed to say?
I appreciate the interest, but please,
please I have nothing for you.
Yeah, I hear you.
I don't know what you guys' deal is.
That's, that'd be cool.
If I was, if so I was walking down the street
strutting my stuff as I do and some lowly coward asked me
something about, I don't know, fucking the Japanese Juggalo.
Munchy, you're like a Gwynn and Ben is like a furtive pygmy.
So easily forgot, so easily forgot.
He doesn't want to be seen.
I mean, I did appreciate it and I thought it was cool,
but I also felt like very, very embarrassed at the same time.
Remember when we were talking about T-Baptome?
That was always humiliating.
Yeah.
I think it's just you have, when you have an online persona,
you kind of like sit down
and like you have a way of presenting yourself online
that is definitely different from real life.
So when you have to like try and like turn that switch on
when you're not in front of a screen,
you're just like, what the, what, how do I do this?
Yeah.
I'm not used to this.
It's weird though, cause like-
It's not even embarrassment, it's just discomfort
and not being able to under really know
how to present yourself at that point.
I mean, for Ben specifically, you do comics
and that's like more of a real world thing anyways.
So if anything, it would feel less embarrassing than to say,
I have a YouTube channel, I do Pokemon Let's Play.
You can't say, I do, I make comics.
Hey guys, it's me, Ben, I'm a real pokey tuber.
Yeah, he sure is, he sure is.
You might think so, but I feel just as embarrassed.
I feel just as embarrassed talking about the vapors
as I did talking about T-Bab.
It's made me wonder if I was even really bothered
by the whole pony thing in the first place.
Yeah, exactly.
I mean, yeah, I think so.
I'm like, it's embarrassing.
I don't know, man.
It's something about the way,
it's like if they were to go watch a video,
it's like they'd expect me to act like that around them
or they'd be like, why don't you?
I don't know, something weird's going on there
and I can't quite articulate it.
It is weird.
Yeah, I can't quite explain my feelings
on the subject either.
Yeah, yeah.
I just, I don't know, cause like no one feels ashamed.
Like if you were fucking Harvey Oswald
or whoever makes comics nowadays.
Lee Harvey Oswald?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
If you were just someone like that,
then you wouldn't be, like if you were Brian Leo Malley
and someone's like, oh, you draw comics,
you'd be like, yeah, I do.
I actually think I would.
That's a respected job.
I actually think I would be kind of like,
oh yeah, I guess I'm Brian Leo Malley,
but I don't really want to talk about it.
You know, but if you think about what it would mean
to be him, to like have fucking movies
and like book deals and like be, like that's,
you're, you know, I do.
I just think that like if you're really on that level,
like your world has changed
and like it's not like being like a small time YouTuber
or anything, it's like a different, it's like real.
It's like real and then you're like more,
I'd feel more like, like a business executive
like uncle of mine would like be like, oh yes,
you're raking in XYZ and the infrastructure stock.
And that's the opposite of embarrassment.
That's social credit, like social credit at that point.
Right.
Yeah.
I keep imagining Ben as Quentin Tarantino
and people come up to him and say, oh dude,
I love Pulp Fiction.
And he's like, oh yeah, I don't know.
Yeah, I guess, I guess.
Well, that reminds me, Nate, do you remember that one time
that our dad got really like weird about the fact
that we were swearing on T-Bap?
A little bit, yes.
He was like, and this is stuck with me
because I remember I asked him, I was like, dad, okay,
this is gonna sound really fucking pretentious
and like I'm really fucking up my own ass
and think I'm hot shit here.
But I was just trying to make a point.
I was like about art and I was like, dad,
do you think that Quentin Tarantino is embarrassed
by Pulp Fiction because people say fucking it?
Okay.
And I was like, of course,
of course not, right?
Like of course the answer is no.
But dad didn't say no.
He was like, well, I'm sure he's in some cases,
I was like, god damn it.
Well, I get his point.
I just fucking agree with me because I'm right.
He's seeing this like, dad's thinking about this
the same way he thinks about like people who post like,
because this is frame of reference,
like pictures of themselves like swearing
or drunk on Facebook, like, oh, how embarrassing.
Oh, this is gonna stick with you forever,
as opposed to like an actual like comedy video
where it's all like intentional
and presented in this way deliberately.
Yeah.
You know, that's how he's thinking about it.
This is a work of fiction.
This is a work of creative energy.
And it's a work of artifice.
Maybe.
Whatever.
Maybe shame has been corroded for me
because I don't even think of swearing
as like a degrading or like embarrassing thing.
It just helps me communicate.
There is a certain audience.
There's a generational thing.
Like I think millennials and under,
like Gen Xers and millennials
and like it's with every,
it's swearing has just become less and less of a thing.
I don't even think swearing exists anymore
unless you're like over the age of 40.
Modern day swearing is bringing up topics
that are like, oh, God, shut up, like politics.
Like that is swearing now at it.
Yeah, yeah.
Like if you say Donald Trump anywhere,
like, oh, why would you say that?
More like Donald Trump.
Please.
Thank you.
Donald Trump is like,
the butt to ass, you know?
Exactly.
I was gonna say it's the crap to shit
and things of that nature.
Yeah, exactly.
Don't say, you gotta hone that down a bit.
Tune in to the bonus of this month, ladies and gentlemen.
Oh my God.
It's gonna be incredible.
You're gonna want to see that, guys.
You're gonna want to fucking see that shit.
But it's like the same things where the old ladies
will say, oh, what's your language?
I would do that with what's your topic?
I don't want to hear it.
Hey.
Excellent.
I'm just gonna jump in here and say
my most recent embarrassment was yesterday.
Oh, good.
Yeah.
I, for a school project, was going to a school.
Like I wrote up an essay and for some reason at my school,
they give you more points if you like speak your essay.
And so I was going to like,
I was gonna suck up to my teacher real hard
and I was gonna try and like make it seem
like I really actually genuinely cared
about the things I was talking about.
And so I was going to go to like a museum near where I live.
Not like an indoor museum.
I was just going to go near this like historic,
it's kind of hard to accept, like a historical museum
center block called Babbo Park.
If you like Google it, viewers,
and you'll get a better sense.
I was inside of the museum screaming.
But I was going to go there and I was going to like,
like recite my essay just like a way for people
not bothering anyone.
But the mere idea of me pulling out my phone
and like talking while there were people like,
like could like see me like recording something
that other people will see just made me
so fucking upset and scared.
Interesting.
I've tried to do that because like there's people
who like vlog just out on the streets or whatever.
Yeah.
How do they do that?
I have no fucking clue.
That's the scariest thing in the entire fucking world.
I've been, I've tried multiple times
and every time it's like, no, no, no.
Yeah. Is it really embarrassing?
I don't know, man.
I don't know.
I don't remember doing that.
It's cause they're like infringing on their space.
Kind of.
Yeah.
I think that's really where my thing comes from
is just like, I don't feel like I have the right to do this.
Cause I feel like if I was just walking
and someone was like, hey guys, I'm shooting a vlog.
I'd be like, I'm going to shoot you with a gun.
Yeah.
Here's the thing though.
Wait, wait, give was going to say something.
Sure, sure.
Well, I was just going to say that one time
I was walking through a park and doing that.
Like I was vlogging in the park
because I assumed nobody would be there.
But of course there's dog walkers there.
And when, you know, it's a long.
We're like, we call them dog coin miners.
That's what they're up there.
Yeah.
Okay.
Sorry, sorry.
So, and like there's parts where the path is just really long
and they can see you for a long time
and I can see them for a long time.
Oh yeah.
So I'm holding my camera in front of me.
They can see that I have my camera
and then they definitely know that I'm putting the camera down
so that I can walk by them
and I'm just going to bring it back up again.
They know you're embarrassed.
That's the worst part.
Oh no.
Here's the thing.
I talk loud.
Like when I'm with my friends
and I'm walking down the street, I talk loud.
People can definitely hear me
when I'm just having normal conversation.
But I will talk, like I talked really quiet
when I was trying to record this video.
Like I don't think anyone could hear me
or I don't think anyone noticed me.
But like, whereas like normally people will notice me.
So why is it just the camera?
Like the camera itself makes it embarrassing for some reason.
It does.
Because people can see that you're like doing something
and you're like recording something and they're like.
Oh, I don't know.
Oh, I just thought of a life hack about that.
Like if you have like a phone.
If you're filming on a phone
and maybe you should have like a dummy phone
and put the phone up to your ear.
So if people look at you and they glance,
they say, oh, he's talking to someone on the phone.
He's not talking to his phone.
Isn't he trying to film himself though?
Yeah.
You know, you just put sort of like,
like, the pretend that they don't see that on.
You just get a drone.
You have the drone fly like over a hand.
Yeah.
Superb.
That's how you do it, man.
You just have your phone.
You've got that excruciatingly loud like
rrrrrr of the fucking thing in the museum.
It's okay guys, I'm just vlogging.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Please ignore the drone.
That was the cat material.
By the way, Munchy, you mentioned school doing a school project. I've been wondering about
this. You must be a god at your school. You must own that fucking place. Because like,
how could these weak cowards that I went to school with possibly stack up to the intellectual
juggernaut that you are, you know, just in real life. And these are lowly like 16, 17-year-old
freaks.
Honestly, you would, any high school person I've ever met in my life, you would crush
them instantly.
Yeah, what's the deal? What's that like? What's that like?
Well, I actually don't know. I told this before, but I go to-
I dropped out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I went to an, well, I'm going to an online charter school. I've been
in my senior year. So I don't go to a school. But when I did, that was before my, as I
alluded to earlier, the golden age of me being embarrassing.
So as you're saying, are you saying that like, that going to an online charter school
has unlocked your Christ consciousness? Is that, is that where we all drop the ball?
I think literally so.
For Munchy, it's been a huge success. It's allowed you to do all the things I think like
a charter school would like want their kids to be able to do. Like just live your life
and make positive stuff and just do whatever you want.
We missed the boat. If I had gone to a charter school, I could have been a cool dude like
Munchy.
Yeah.
I hear charter school and I think ship chart and I think like sailing around.
It's a nautical school.
Exactly.
He's going to be an admiral when he grows up.
He's sailing across the worldwide world.
He's sailing around the, the surfing around the web.
Hey, when he, when he graduates and he's an admiral, he can come on our ship and come
on the podcast, patreon.com slash the podcast pirate.
The propellant.
Wait, I would like that.
I'm Mr. Regular Old Rear Admiral Wattage.
No, not Wattage. What was his name? What was the tentacle role? What was the tentacle
role?
Uh, colopsic.
Colopsic.
What a god.
Uh, yeah.
Sick reference.
Back when I was in like, like normal school, I was, I was not a god by any means.
I, I, I was, I was disabled kid tier.
Oh no.
That's bad.
That's bad you do.
Yeah. That's, that was, it was real bad.
It was.
Interesting.
I, I, okay, okay. Gay period stuff is too recent for me to talk about and not like genuinely
just like, oh God, like I'm going, I'm going to be real upset genuinely on this podcast.
Muchi, give us one. Give us one, please.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just one.
I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm going to give you, I'm going to give you some.
Okay.
From, from, from my normal, normal school.
Uh, there, I already, I already told you about how I almost like broke some kid's spine.
His fault still. His fault still.
Oh, the hug.
Yeah.
The wheelchair, right?
I was very forgiving hugs.
That was a thing that I did.
Uh, I, I, I don't know why I did this, but, but I was, I, I, I was very flamboyant, some
on purpose, some not.
Everyone thought I was gay.
Not a single person did not think that I was gay.
Excellent.
And, and, and I think like, like, like what, what really like just like, uh, like, I think,
I don't know, uh, uh, in a critical moment in me being perceived as gay was how I was
just walking on, on, on, on the field, mind my own business, not doing anything.
Some like Argentinean exchange student who was like, like four or three and I was like,
I was already like five, like 10, if not higher came up to me.
And she's like, I like, like in a thick bridge, like in a thick Spanish accent was like, I
see, I see you doing the hugs.
You need to stop this homosexuality.
You need to stop perpetrating this fucking propaganda.
You need to stop hugging people.
You're just like, you're just really gay, man.
You're just really, really gay and you need to stop.
Wow.
And I was like, you don't know anything.
You don't know what I'm going through.
You don't understand what it's like.
I just ran away.
He just failed.
To be fair, he probably didn't understand what it was like.
I was in front of him being gay and I didn't even say I wasn't gay.
I was just too gay.
That's true.
Oh.
See, something about that is not even embarrassing.
Yeah.
When you look back on it and you just laugh about it and it's like, I was so silly back
then and he showed that like, you know, you've learned and like, obviously you do it a little
different now.
You probably hug that motherfucker and make him gay too.
That's what I would have done in that situation.
Spread it around.
Indeed.
Yeah.
There's like, there's like, um, there's a certain amount of like, oh, well, I didn't
even know I could do that at the time.
Yeah.
To, you know, to wave away like, like, oh, I was so clumsy.
I was such a stupid bitch.
But like, if you made a mistake like that today, it would be terribly embarrassing.
If somebody, if somebody said, I don't like you and you ran away, like, come on.
Yeah.
Ran away.
Incredible.
Literally.
There's just too many, my memory's too foggy and there's just too many things that I couldn't
really go on it, you know, a whole tirade about my, my, my, my old days in school.
If I, if there's a high demand, I can probably like come up with like a couple stories later
after this podcast, but yeah.
Guys, I think I might need to go soon.
Let's just jump to a couple of questions if you got a minute or two.
Yes.
I'll actually say one more story that will only take a second.
Okay.
But in seventh grade, I forgot the combination to my locker for physical education and I didn't
want to ask the teacher because I didn't want to let him know that I had messed up and forgot
my code.
Right.
So I just stuck my gym code, my gym clothes into my backpack and so it stunk up my fucking
backpack every single day for the rest of the year.
This was on day like three.
Oh no.
So, so for all of seventh grade, I had just kept my gym clothes in my backpack because
I didn't want my teacher to think that I forgot my codes, which I did.
How embarrassing that would have been.
Yeah, yeah, I know exactly.
Indeed.
Okay guys, it's, it's, it's time.
Thank you, Munchie.
Thanks everyone.
Of course.
Thanks for your questions because there's at least one that I need Gibbs answer to.
Okay.
So everyone hashtag SBCP, send them on the Twitter, we take some there and then of course
more likely to get them read is if you go to patreon.com slash the procrastinators, enter
our patron chat discord and that's where we ask for more questions and let me read one
from there right now.
This is my favorite question that the PCB has ever gotten.
I love it intensely.
It is from famous Chai Wenny's singer and it is simply, do you guys munch it?
Or crunch it?
That was the question.
That's the question.
That's the fucking, well, well, definitely crunch it like a fucking sick, sick, crunchy
Dorito when I'm doing strange sports.
I actually crunch it as well.
I crunch it as well.
Yeah, I, I, I crunch it because there's a chocolate bar called a crunchy and I really
like those.
Crunch is good.
Because I like the kinesthetics of chomping into something.
I don't know.
When it's munching, it kind of, that implies that it's not as powerful as a crunch.
You're munching.
It's gamey the same.
You know, it's true.
A munch.
Yeah.
Crunchy.
Munchy is like more powerful, like evil doppelganger.
It's called crunchy.
Yeah.
I, I think in like munchy, munchy is like casual playthrough of, of, of video game and crunch
it.
And crunch it is like speed run, high intensity, you know, high velocity, every Uber hacks,
you know, that sort of style.
Like the other side run no damage.
I think there's a time and a place for both.
You know, first you want to munch something and then you crunch it and there's a harmony
to be found here.
I don't know.
I think munchy should be crunched.
You gotta go crunch or go fuck.
What, what do you, let's, let's enter a wild variable in this one that may change your
perception entirely.
Do you munch it, crunch it or slurp it?
No.
This is like adding the Z axis to the world.
I, I crunch, I, if I could, I would crunch soup.
I don't like liquid.
Do you put oyster crackers in your soup perhaps?
That had some crunch.
I, I, real talk, I do chew, I chew my drinks completely subconsciously.
Like a coke or something?
How would you chew that?
Yeah.
If I just take a drink of soda, I'll just like chew it without even realizing it.
Oh, that's autism.
It's, it's, it's absolutely autism.
Not even, not even.
Fascinating.
Oh, I have one embarrassing story I have to tell.
Just really quick.
Okay.
I got called autistic one time on the internet.
And you ran away.
Yeah.
And I was like, you know what?
That just, that just has to be true.
That just has to be true.
I need to know if that is true.
There's by some random person I got called autistic.
And so I begged my mom to let me take an autism test.
So she took me to a therapist so I could take an autism test to see if I was autistic.
And I took it and I wasn't.
And I was like, this is not true.
This is fake.
I have to be autistic.
I am autistic.
So I, so I was like, I told the therapist like, there must be something wrong here.
I know.
I can feel it.
And she was like, no.
Like you, like you aren't.
And then she was like, well, okay, like, like, are you ready to do therapy now?
Like that, that's what you sign up for.
Like you want to get autism test.
I can help you alleviate whatever pain you have.
And I was like, no, no, I don't care about your services.
I don't care about keeping therapy.
I just want to know if I was autistic or not.
And I still believe that I am.
So goodbye, you're worthless to me.
You didn't give me the validation I needed.
And that sounds like a lot was learned that day.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm going to, I'm going to change things up a little bit.
I'm sorry, editor.
I just want to be able to acquire a little bit of extra work.
I just, this image has to be put on screen.
This is a hashtag askpcp from the Twitter.
And it's simply this.
It's simply this.
Oh God.
What did I paste in the wrong chat?
Whoops.
Sorry.
Hang on.
Shit.
Oh my God.
Right here.
Here.
There.
What is going on here?
Is that Jaden Smith in the middle?
Yeah.
Is that who that is?
Who is that on the right?
No, it's not Jaden Smith.
Is that Ted Cruz on the left?
Oh, by the way, this is from Ask Pro Masticators.
Hey guys, what's going on?
I have no idea who the two right people are.
I've, I've, I've, I've not tall enough to ride.
Wait, no, that's the kid from High School Musical.
That's the black kid.
I'm not tall enough to ride this meme.
Oh.
That's the High School Musical kid, but I don't know who to kid on the right.
Is this implying that DeVoo is so white that he, that he deletes the black musical
meme?
He deletes the black.
He deletes it.
Well, there's a, there's a middle ground.
There's a middle ground, I guess.
Um.
This picture of DeVoo looks like a creepy pasta thumbnail.
It does.
This looks, this looks like, like, like, like a Jeff the Killer episode seven.
Okay.
Well, anyway, uh, that, that's it.
That's it.
Our answer to that is yes.
Good job.
Yeah.
Let, uh, uh, okay.
Here we go.
Once Parr asks, who was your favorite musician when you were 12?
I know that I loved Queen intensely when I was around 12, I think.
That is defined by, by your, your talent show.
Indeed.
I, I'm accurate.
Uh, uh, because I didn't like know any bands except the ones my dad said, I just said I
liked the Beatles the whole time.
Yeah.
Because, you know, those are good.
And I didn't really know how to look at music myself.
They can't even drop the fucking bass.
Ringo doesn't even know that shit.
It took Skrillex to innovate that into the music sphere.
Thank God for that.
That was the beginning of real music.
Dude, can someone please make a dubstep remix of Beatles songs, please?
Like, like, you just like, like, like dubstep remix the entirety of the Beatles discography
for me, please.
I, I need that.
That's your homework for tonight.
Somebody's probably doing that.
Uh, from the patron lounge, vamp the vampire for the draw boys.
What's the best way for a very beginner level artist to develop their school, their, their
schools?
Also, what drawing tablet do you guys recommend?
Here's a fucking bombshell.
I'm going to drop for you.
Uh, the kind of tablet you get does not matter.
It doesn't matter.
Don't.
It totally doesn't.
Yeah.
It doesn't.
Whatever you can afford.
Yeah.
If you want to get some tink shirt, whatever does not matter.
Uh, I will probably use this Wacom tablet to the day I fucking die.
I used a Wacom bamboo for like seven years.
Yeah.
Exactly.
I had an old Wacom bamboo I used from like 2007 to like literally when I started Real
Pixels, that was the one tablet I had.
Sponsored by Wacom.
The PCP.
There you go.
Please.
I will.
I will say if you're using a brand that's not Wacom, you, they tend to have compatibility
issues with open source and free programs.
Yeah.
So if you're using like credit or GIMP or whatever, you probably want to get a Wacom.
They work better with that.
You're going to want to install Gen 2.
Get, get, get, get, get Wacom.
Don't do the other weird shit.
They aren't good.
Unless, unless you're buying them through my Amazon affiliate links and all the alternatives,
please.
In terms of getting better, I just straight up do gesture drawing.
If you want to get better drawing figures, just do like five, then three, then one minute
gesture drawings.
I, I, I will recommend the tried and true classic Andrew Loomis books, fun with a pencil.
Yeah.
And I think the other one's called, I think it's, I think it's just called gesture drawing.
Andrew Loomis is good.
Yeah.
I recommend, I recommend just, just, just, just draw, just draw something and don't
stop until it looks good.
Like just go in there and go nuts with your fucking, with your pencil tool, your pen tool.
And it just, just keep Doug going and control Zing as much as you want until you get, it
would go in with the eraser and just like keep going and don't stop until it feels right.
And don't be afraid to use references.
As someone who doesn't know how to draw.
And I'm definitely 10 times worse at drawing than I would be if I'd use references from
the start.
As someone who doesn't know how to draw at all.
I feel like I gained at least a general understanding by just watching a little bit of, of streams,
specifically Ben streams, the one I've seen.
And at least that, I mean, I don't know, it gives you sort of an idea of something you
could like try.
So, hey man, I know nothing about any of this shit, but that seems like a good place to start.
I should stream more drawing.
I actually might not recommend that.
I mean, that's valid if you want.
But the thing with us is that we are do stylized drawings, which is nice and all.
But please take it from me who finds it very hard to once they've started drawing, go back
and learn anatomy.
Learn anatomy.
Please.
Do that.
God.
Learn anatomy.
Don't do what I did.
Yeah.
Don't like, even if you want to draw cartoons.
Well, the thing, the thing that I confused a lot is that the different, there's a difference
because like my reason and I never learned anatomy as a kid and I still haven't mastered it now,
even though I've tried is that I misunderstood drawing from life as drawing realistically.
And I was not interested in all and drawing photorealistically and sitting there and drawing
like a pencil study for like seven hours.
You can sketch from life and draw like something really loose and not that detailed while looking
at something real that'll help you understand the form better.
Exactly.
There's a huge difference.
So like even when I do, I say do gesture drawing, I don't mean like sit there and spend 12 hours
rendering like hair on the legs.
Yeah.
Just, just like look at it so you can understand how the body works and everything and just
like learn about the line of action.
In the beginning.
That's what I mean.
Learn about the line of action and learn about anatomy and stuff, but don't get bogged down
in it either.
Like learn it and be like, okay, now to put it into practice and then just go draw.
And then after some drawing, you can come back to it and be like, maybe I didn't pick,
maybe I should figure this out better than I did.
Don't get bogged down and study.
Obviously, the best way to draw is to draw.
But I'm just saying as a basic, like Andrew Loomis is fine with the pencil.
That's good because that teaches you the building blocks of how to construct a figure.
But just take it from me.
Learn fundamentals.
They are important.
Even if you want to draw Steven Universe to your bullshit, it helps to have fundamentals
so you can understand 3D space and things such as that.
So please.
Not everyone's been saying who can get a science degree and just be like, I'm just going to
draw now.
And then like a month later, he's a God.
So like most people have to actually try.
Yeah.
Sucks for them, I guess.
If you want to be good at drawing, draw and quarter yourself because it's not worth doing.
It's a waste of fucking time.
It's some bullshit and you should feel bad if that's what you do with your life.
True.
In conclusion, learn fundamentals and learn shit.
Learn shit.
Drawing is shit.
It's all bad.
Get rid of it and it's not good except I really like it.
I like drawing.
It's really fun.
Don't let anyone tell you that it's not fun.
But it is for cowards.
Yeah.
It is the cowards way out.
It's the cowards way out.
Speaking of the cowards way out, we have a wonderful question from Avada Akbar.
It's time to weigh in on this.
The official stance of the PCP.
If you had to choose which one, which would it be?
Israel or Palestine?
All right.
Let's get it.
Who's going to obliterate one and save the other?
I'm going to go with Palestine because they're funny, silly boys over there.
And I enjoy watching them be hilarious.
Which ones are the good ones?
I want to pick the good guys.
Oh no.
Tell me who's the good guys and I'll pick them.
The real heroes are the friends we dated along the way.
The real Palestine was the friends we made along the way.
It just depends.
Do you pick a Wonder Woman or do you pick her opposition?
Good question.
By the way, the objective answer is Israel because it has Jerry Seinfeldt in their military.
Recently, Jerry Seinfeldt.
This is true.
Jerry Seinfeldt went to a military tourism camp to learn how to fight Palestinian terrorists in Israel.
Are you quite kidding me?
Yeah.
He went with his family.
Well, let me just tell you.
We don't even need to choose because Palestine's going to be wiped up a fucking map in like any fucking day now.
With Jerry on the case.
The Pacha is like a bomb going over.
The bomb just goes off.
Oh my God.
It's like they're marching and he's like playing the trumpet and instead of the ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba, it's boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Dude, but like Jerry's going to get to the front lines.
Across the battlefield, leading the Palestinian forces will be George fucking Costanza.
George, what are you doing over there?
Over there. I don't know. I just there was a hot slut. I wanted to fuck Jerry. And now I'm wrapped up with this madness
He outmaneuvers his opponents by using his vast speed as seen in the race
Yeah, exactly
The way he beats the pestilence is again. He gets a head start that no one notices and he gets the absolute quicker
The name one else does yeah
Excellent. Well, that's everybody
Favorite dead. Oh wait, actually, you know what? That's a terrible question
Um, um, I don't know. There's these are all bad
Avada Akbar also asked do you know the way a beam get it get it you know, no
Got a knuckle. Okay, whatever. That's it. No more good questions. I think they're all good. They're I mean bad
Yes, okay, that's it everybody. All right, thank you. They should all feel embarrassed, right? Oh
Correct, correct. Step it up everybody as always. All right, so patron lounge
Thank you for the questions patron.com slash the procrastinators one dollar or more and you can get to the fucking patron lounge and shit
And we hang out with us five dollars or more on the patron and you get our bonus episodes
There are 10. Yeah, there'll be 10 and the next one coming out is gonna be a bombshell
It's gonna it's gonna rock the foundations of this weak
Capitalist economy of which we we we tread upon like grains of sand in the desert
And it's gonna be a nightmare. So yeah, get ready for that shit
To spoil what the topic is let's not yet. Let's do it next time. Okay. Okay. Mm-hmm. It's good. Oh, man
God, we're so excited about it. It's good. Yeah, it's gonna be a fucking heart clincher
Once you read the title you're gonna be like glued to your fucking screen for the rest of the true
We got we got some some birch red bubble stuff click the link down there. It's it's it's cool
It's lit as the kids say that's good
What else we got? Oh the iTunes and the Google Play music store. Tom is so graciously got the PCP
Episodes up there so you can listen to them all there. I think that's everything. I think that's everything
So for now, thanks for listening everybody. We will see you next week with some more dank memes
All right. Good. Bye everybody
Good boy
I am a stupid
Don't want to do