I won't bless that guy. That's son of a bitch.
Hello everyone.
Oh, it's The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Woo!
It's January 4th, 2018.
No it isn't.
Oh yeah, you're right. It's not.
Well anyway, welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I don't know what that was in reference to.
I just thought it was about The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
You should let him know that he made a mistake.
It was in reference to the specific time in the past.
I did a lot of things this week actually. I have a number of things that happened.
Big week.
Big week for me.
Do you want to talk first about Twitter exploding a little bit?
I mean, what do you mean?
Well you know, everybody thought it was going to die when all of the employees were locked out of the building.
Because Elon had fired so many people that it included the guy who was in charge of the doors and the locking security stuff.
Is that what happened?
Yeah, for a brief time, everyone was locked out of the building and then somebody projected some Elon hate onto the side of the building.
And I saw a video of it.
Oh, like video projected?
Yeah.
Oh, that's funny. No, I missed all this.
I'll be honest, like all the Twitter nonsense has just started to blend together and I've just kind of not even been paying attention anymore.
Yeah, I mean, I've been more on Twitter now than ever in part because it's funny.
But now's the time for it, I guess.
I know. Well, it was really fun because like...
Now or never.
All the people I'm following, a lot of them are like, you know, they're doing funny bits, they're making jokes and they're also getting emotional because it's like all their friends were on Twitter and if it actually goes, it would be sad.
And I'm like, oh, shit, you know, it is kind of sad.
I mean, my base isn't on Twitter.
I have like a groove from YouTube, essentially.
Yeah.
So like I have, most of my audience knows me elsewhere anyway.
But it is true that I have made some Twitter friends and I'm like, dang, I'm going to follow them.
Yeah.
But it is sort of like a, people are describing, it's like the end of high school.
Like the night when people were told that things, there was like no engineers working on Twitter and everyone's looked out of the building.
It's like, well, this is probably it.
It wasn't.
But it was very fun.
That's very funny.
I see.
Yeah.
Okay.
I did notice an uptake and people saying like, this is it.
Twitter's really going down.
Yeah.
I hadn't really been paying attention.
And, you know, I guess it's easy to say in hindsight that it wasn't going to be the end.
My expectation is not that Twitter is actually going to like just blink off out of existence.
I know.
Although I guess I can see why you would think so if it's like the doors are locked and the headquarters is closed.
Yeah.
I get that.
That was like, like what?
Huh?
Like how, even then, I didn't think it was going to like immediately blink off because people who knew about technology, they had a few threads and I was reading them.
And they were saying basically that without the engineers that Elon has fired and, you know, all of the people that were good at stuff.
Eventually, if Twitter just continues going, it can work by itself.
But as soon as there's a bug and there's not somebody around to immediately fix it, it'll compound on itself and then the site will become unusable.
Yeah.
And certain vital things will be like your privacy options will be like all fucked up.
There's lots of possible things that could go terribly, terribly wrong and ruin everything.
So it would have been essentially, if any of those things happened, they still could happen because like, I don't know what's going on.
I mean, he's back in the building now.
They've got these, Elon's got his like, the little ragtag group of people who have agreed to work.
His funny little, what do I want to call it, his funny little midlife crisis, you know, LARPing as a little startup company like, oh yeah, we'll just get my little team in here and we'll just problem solve.
We'll just draw stuff on a whiteboard.
Ooh, it'll just like, yeah, just like when we were starting PayPal or whatever, guys.
We were just working out of our garage, just like the good old days, right?
Right, my like 22 year old intern.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir, Mr Musk, sir.
It's kind of sad.
Call me, call me, Elon, call me, Elon.
It's kind of sad that like, obviously a lot of people left because Elon asked them to work harder, longer hours for the same pay.
Right.
Which is what he called going hardcore in order to get the site working.
And most people said fuck that and left and then they got scooped up by other tech companies because they're talented.
But some people like have their visas tied to working for Twitter.
So they can't leave.
Cringe.
So there's just a few like hundred people, maybe a thousand.
And they're just either they like Elon Musk, Lamau, or they just they can't really get a better deal anywhere else at the moment.
I'll be perfectly candid.
I'm not like, I'm not overly precious about like the jobs of people working at Twitter.
Because like, you know, why should they be any more secure?
Why should they read moral outrage over firing people at Twitter as opposed to anyone else?
I'm not like, no, you can't fire people that work at Twitter.
I don't see why you would defend anything Elon is doing in any way though.
Well, no.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm not like that.
What I don't understand, I genuinely, it took me a back and it made me feel like I was going crazy.
When I started seeing the pictures of like Elon Thanos snapping all of the workers at Twitter and they're all the screaming woman from when Trump got elected.
And they're all and I was like, what is it?
What does this mean?
Like is I genuinely was not aware that like is the perception that like everyone that works at Twitter is like an SJW feminist or something?
Like what?
I think I mean, that's definitely that's definitely the angle that like Elon fans.
And Elon himself are sort of sticking with because there's no, there's no, there's no idea where that comes from.
There's no idea where that comes from.
There's no way that Elon Musk made a mistake.
It must be because the Twitter stuff, the workers, there's damn dirty workers.
They're just doing a bad job.
And this is the reason Twitter is dying.
I don't know.
Elon did them a favor by getting rid of them.
Did that stereotype just pop into existence overnight?
Or was it already like a thing that like, oh, I mean, I know.
I know that there's sort of like the, oh, global homo, like every big, every big tech company is like liberal and donates to Democrats and they're all in the pocket of George Soros or whatever.
Is it just that?
I think it must be.
Hmm.
I mean, I don't see that many people doing that.
Doing that is the hardcore Elon sims.
And it's just, it's terrible.
I mean, yeah, that's, that's just when I, when I, when I look at an Elon tweet and I look and you scroll down in the, in the replies, you inevitably see that picture of Elon Thanos snapping away all the SJW feminists.
And it's just, and it just, it, it's not even, it almost doesn't even make me mad because it's just so, it doesn't even like, it doesn't even comment on like a reality that I feel that I exist in or can even like understand.
Um, yeah.
Yeah, it is.
It has been a very, it's been a very odd time.
I'm, I'm, I'm thankful that it's still around.
I feel like what's going to happen.
I would be very sad if Twitter actually died.
Yeah.
Like I would, I would hate it.
Because that really isn't a replacement for it.
I have made a Tumblr, give and take art if you want to check that out.
I posted my Clarissa comics.
I don't know really what I'm going to do with it.
I'm thinking it's just as a backup for my main social media presence because I don't like any of the other options, but that it's not the same as Twitter.
You don't get that, that you can't really do replies to people in the same way.
You can do, you do reblogs.
Reblogs and it's like, I just want to speak.
I don't want, whatever.
I understand.
I've heard a couple times this week I got, I heard the notion being tossed around, and this is not a Twitter replacement, but like people said like Ben, you should make clips of your video.
You should make like highlight clips and put them on TikTok.
Like maybe the funny moments or like funny bits or interesting bits from like the Mega Man lecture, for instance, and just start posting them on TikTok.
And I, honestly, I'm scared to do that because like I'd be starting a fresh account with no followers and like, I'm genuinely horrified of the prospect of doing that.
And then like, it doesn't go anywhere and like I wasted my time.
Like, I can't think of a worse feeling than if that happened.
I feel like, I mean, there's always a site that's like, oh, people are on this site.
You should check it out.
And I'm like, but I don't use it.
Like I'm going to be like weird.
I'm going to be like not the sort of thing that people want to see and it's going to take a while.
And I'm just like, I don't want to involve myself even though it's good for like marketing or whatever.
But marketing sucks.
I know.
Clips of my videos are not the kind of thing that I think of when I see TikTok content, but like I'm sure that like other kinds of TikTok stuff.
I've like, I've never even, I've never used TikTok.
The only time I see TikTok is when a viral TikTok makes its way onto Twitter and I see it there.
Yeah.
So I'm sure there's markets for other different kinds of stuff.
Obviously your Mega Man lecture is about to release today as we're recording.
In about two hours, yeah.
Oh my God.
But I clicked on the premiere thing and it's got that trailer, that snippet of you just listing all of the Mega Man games and there's so many of them and they just fill the screen.
That could make a TikTok.
How is it?
Is it one minute?
Do TikToks have to be under a minute long or three minutes?
Vine had like a really short time.
I don't know what TikTok has.
Yeah.
But yeah, it's probably a short-ish time.
But I've seen kind of long TikToks before.
I think it could easily fit.
You know, it was Doid Gaser of all people.
It was Doid Gaser that DM'd me and suggested clipping stuff for TikTok and I thought maybe.
You know, yesterday I called in to Astereos' show.
He was doing a watch along of Kick Asia, the Channel Awesome movie.
And he told me on Twitter, you should call in and I was like, okay, and I did.
And he also was like, he wanted to start clipping clips of the loudest podcasts and putting them on TikTok.
It's not a Twitter replacement.
And I'm not sure if I'm interested in using TikTok as a consumer.
I gave it a try once.
Yeah.
It's one of those like endless, you just scroll down and if you see something that's slightly interesting for the first few seconds or like half a second or a frame, it's like, oh, I guess I'll watch this.
I don't care.
And you just keep going and going and going.
Yeah, yeah.
It's kind of a brain-empty like noise thing to me.
The YouTube shorts interface is kind of like that, right?
Like he just kind of scroll like one after the other after the other.
Yeah.
And they auto-play.
It's a different vibe.
I'm not really into it, but I could see the appeal of just sort of being like, whatever, just fill my brain with fucking pixels or something.
I just need something.
That's what people say.
That's what people say about TikTok.
It's fucking hypnotizing.
Yeah.
Yeah, I can imagine.
They're getting you with that endless stream of crap.
Yeah.
I mean, hey, that's just content, I guess.
You know, before we move on from the Twitter subject, I just want to ask if you are aware of the chili discourse?
Oh, yeah.
Did we talk about that last time?
Did we mention it?
We did.
It's been going on for such a long time.
I mean, maybe we didn't talk about it, but it's been like more than a week, I'm sure, that that has been like perpetually people freaking out over nothing.
It's ableist to give your neighbors chili.
Maybe we did.
Maybe we did talk about it last week.
I just can't believe it.
It just keeps going.
What is it?
It's unfilomable.
I'm sorry.
Disabled people just have too many rights.
All right.
They've run them.
I'm sorry.
They've run amuck.
We gave them some privileges and they were abusing them.
So we have to, I'm sorry, we have to roll them back.
It's not okay.
They can't keep getting away with it.
It's just so presumptuous on the part of the people that she's making the chili for, that I just don't, like, I guess all of these people who are upset are thinking, God, I hope somebody doesn't knock on my door and say hello to me and give me something.
What if I don't like it?
What if I don't like to talk to people?
It's just sort of like so boring, like so petty, so insignificant.
Don't worry about it.
What if I don't want to have someone knock on my door?
What if I don't want to meet my neighbors?
What if I don't like the chili?
What if the chili has an ingredient that I can't eat?
What it, one of the most fucking buck wild ones I saw was what if they don't have bowls?
Yeah.
What if they don't have, not everyone has bowls.
Not everyone has the spoons to do dishes and have clean bowls to eat your presumptuous white people chili out of.
Cracker.
It's like, I guess, like, if you don't have any bowls, the person making the chili could bring some.
Like, these issues have such simple solutions.
You can eat it with a fucking spoon!
You can eat it with a fucking spoon out of the crock pot.
Out of the pot, yeah.
It's like, they don't think, like, one step ahead of like, oh, the consequence of that, like,
like potential, like, issue is that, oh, sorry, I can't eat, like, meat, or I can't eat this.
But thank you.
And then you close the door.
Like, it's so insignificant of an issue.
Like, it's really funny.
The fact that, like, some people are saying it's like an issue of consent.
Like, she didn't, like, she did not get their consent to give them the chili.
It's like, it's not like, you didn't, like, force this chili, like, through their fucking, you know, doggy door.
You didn't force it on them.
You just throw it at them.
You went to their house and you asked, would you like this?
I made you this chili as a gift.
Would you like it?
They can, they can, that's where the consent comes in.
You fucking psychopaths.
Just, like, getting a little stuff in their mouth.
Oh, but you didn't ask consent to ask my consent.
Oh, you did.
Okay, but you didn't ask consent to ask consent to ask consent.
Yeah.
I sent a little letter to us for consent, but what if they can't read?
Did you ask consent to write the letter?
What if you wrote it on paper?
What if they can't read?
What if they, what if they...
Wasn't on vegan paper?
Yeah, it's like all of these fucking things.
I'm like, I guess people are really bored.
I guess people are just, they really want to get mad at something and they don't have anything.
At the moment, even though there's really so many things to get mad at, I don't get it.
I don't know.
You know, you know, to tie it all back, my hero, George the cat, made a triumphant return.
Again, viciously attacking the disabled community once more as he is want to do.
There was, there was, it's not directly chili related, but it was somewhat, someone was
complaining that like the labor movement is bad because like people at like a Starbucks
strike, people, striking workers weren't wearing masks because so like they're anti, they're
against the disabled.
They want to give me a long COVID or something.
And George, George the cat politely disagreed, thereby setting back disability to say the
rights of disabled people hundreds of thousands of years.
That cat is too powerful.
That cat, I said on Twitter, I said, oh no, he tasted the blood of the disabled once and
now he's addicted.
He can't get enough.
Social anxiety, it's hard to say no to chili and now I have to eat it.
Yeah.
I don't, I don't have, I don't know if I could throw it away.
Then don't have the spoons to refuse the chili.
Oh no, now I have to choose.
Now I've given this this disgusting white person chili and now I have to.
Oh God.
Now I have to, I have to wash a bowl to eat it out of God.
I'm having an episode.
I'm having a fucking anxiety attack.
I'm going down.
It's like, I don't know.
Maybe an anxiety attack would happen.
But like, why is it the chili neighbors like fault for thinking, like not thinking of that
potential eventuality?
Like it's nice to try.
There's so many, so many universes in which nothing bad happens at all.
It's a good thing.
You fuck.
I think you're just racist, Gib.
I think I am.
Racist against the disabled.
Okay.
God damn.
Yeah.
Twitter.
I'll miss Twitter though.
I love Twitter.
It'll never be the same.
I've been doing more, more drunk posting.
It's great.
Oh yeah.
My tweets, they're less funny and they're stupid.
But there's more of them.
There's more of them.
Yes.
Cool.
And also it's just been, I don't know, very, very gender over there right now.
I posted like, you saw the-
On your account, you mean?
On my account.
And also just with people I'm interacting with.
It's just all like this.
It's been very gender.
It's very funny.
I posted the image of me with the goth makeup on and stuff.
And then I posted a picture of me wearing makeup out in the real world for the first time.
I got so many likes.
I feel so real.
I don't got too many likes.
I got more likes than my video announcement.
I didn't appreciate that.
That made me angry.
You should have gone full goth.
I would have made it better.
Yeah.
True.
Well, what's the other one?
What do you say?
I don't know what to do.
Don't care, didn't ask?
I think that's fine.
Yeah.
I've come under-
Too long in Rean.
Or Redman comic?
Can someone give me the TLDR on this Redman comic?
Who is the last panel?
I got to get back to it.
Yeah, with no words.
TLDR.
No.
MMMm.
MMM.
MMMM.
And on the subject of gender?
not really but this is a segue that I'll use. I've made a big change in my life recently.
I have stopped friendship ended with rain sounds for sleeping. No more rain sounds. Rain sounds
are yesterday's news. Rain sounds are like Twitter and now the truth social, the new
platform that everyone's moving to instead is train sounds. Train sounds are the new thing for me.
Oh, so it's like tea rain. I was going to do like a teapane autotune thing but I can't do that with
my voice. Wait, why is that gender? Because you transitioned from one thing to another?
No, the gender part of it is that I had a dream. I was listening to train sounds for sleeping and I
had a dream and I don't remember the dream but I woke up. This was like the day after I had like set
the Mega Man lecture to premiere and so I woke up convinced. I woke up convinced that this had
happened and I was thinking why did I do that? Oh no, why did I do that? That's so like doesn't
make any sense that I did that and what I thought I had done was upload a train like a recording of
train sounds on a Japanese train platform that had included audio of a Japanese non-binary person
getting into a violent argument with a passerby about their pronouns. I was sure that this had
happened. I was sure that this was on my channel and I was like why did I post that like the day
before my Mega Man video? What was I thinking? That doesn't make any sense. That's such a specific
thing. I know and I rolled around in bed I was like oh I should get out of bed and I should
delete that off my channel but no I'm so tired. Was it like you filmed that video and you caught
that and you're just like oh fuck it I'll upload it? Yeah, that's what I thought happened. I wonder
what this means. Why did I record that? Why did I upload it? Why was I in Japan?
Somewhere there's some sort of connection here. Make an answer in Japan. It's just a
wires crossed thing. It's just like I uploaded a video and I'm listening to a video about train
sounds therefore I must have uploaded a video about train sounds and also pronouns.
And I don't know that's it. That's my story. Ben, when are you gonna come out as non-binary?
When are you gonna do it? Everyone's non-binary. That's not true. That's not true.
Oh that's the classic like oh but everybody feels this way. Like literally everybody
every every guy wishes they were a girl obviously we just deal with it stupid.
We're all in the spectrum. We're all in the gender spectrum. Just like we're all in the autistic
spectrum. Yeah literally everyone. So I'm already out as non-binary. We all are one to one degree
or another. I'm just kind of like not very far along on the spectrum. Listen I accept they them
pronouns as does most everyone you know. Is that not enough? Is that not enough? Are you trying to
groom me? I'm being groomed. I'm being groomed. I'm grooming you right now. No you heard it.
You heard it. You heard it here. Oh man speaking of grooming. No but kind of. To make a man
lecture. Well I was gonna say um yeah I was on a stereosis stream the other day and it was pretty
fun. He knew he knew a surprisingly little about channel awesome stuff like he didn't know. I mean
he's a bit older isn't he? He's 40 I think. So he's a few years older than me. But he um he knew
who the nostalgia critic was but like he had no idea who Linkara was or the nostalgia chick or
Lindsay Ellis or Spoonie or any of those people. I mean you kind of I learned through channel awesome
collabs who those people were as well back in the day. So if you weren't like following nostalgia
critic you probably wouldn't have found a lot of those other guys either. Well I never watched those
people but I mean as I explained because he had a couple of people in the call sort of explaining
it to him and I was able to uh I think I was able to discern like what he needed to know in order
to understand like what is the what is going on with this with this collective of people. So I
was able to jump in and explain to him that like okay so the thing about channel awesome is the way
that it was structured was that basically Doug just picked like a bunch of little clones of himself
with various gimmicks to become his weird little like empire. And uh and I and I it was like and
I think I was unusual because I'm like more familiar with a lot of these people from like
after they were involved with the nostalgia critic because I didn't actually watch channel
awesome but I'm familiar with Spoonie and Linkara and then and Lindsay Ellis like by reputation
uh mostly like in like a in like a largely post channel awesome world.
Wait when when did you learn about Linkara? Did you watch Linkara or just hear about like funny
things? I know you know what it was I learned about Linkara through I think it must have been
the something awful forums because people on you know yeah it was it was yes it was because back
in the day I would read something awful and I would read the threads about Chris Chan and I
would read the threads about um Control Alt Delete Tim Buckley you know the webcomic the lost
webcomic yeah yeah um yeah and on the something awful forums I would hear people yeah I would hear
people make fun of Linkara I would hear people say oh he's uh he's a chaser or whatever oh he's a
dweeb uh things like that and uh you know he wears a fedora haha oh he has a funny voice
uh he's he's fat yeah and um that's what I learned about Linkara I think I
probably must have well because you know because he made that webcomic he made that
terrible webcomic called the light bringer yes and so and so yes and I got this and so he got
discussed on like discussions of bad webcomics a lot of the time um other other people I think
I just heard about through like youtuber stuff like other youtubers mentioning spoonie and uh
nostalgia chick and stuff like that um yeah and it was pretty fun the video is probably like still
up if anyone's interested they could probably go still watch that uh on a stereosis channel
be watch along of kagassia and I'm in it for maybe like maybe like a third of it and like
after like an hour or two I don't know what's the time I oh it's I think I think the channel
is is actually called the loudest podcast it's yeah it's the loudest podcast channel on you
know what let me see if I can just find the video uh you know he uh I'd never actually
spoken I was sure that I had talked to him before because I mean I've met sarancha and I've talked
you know who that is right mm-hmm yeah I've met her and I've talked to her but I've never
actually met or talked to his dear I just assumed I had but he told me and I did not realize this
that he he told me he has the cancel ben saint shirt and that he wears it all the time he told me
that's on the stream I couldn't believe it and I asked like wait a minute but did you have the one
I didn't I didn't refer to her by name I did not refer to may by name but I said do you have the
one that my enemy was raffling off or do you did you buy one for me because he wasn't he was not
aware my enemy my I said my enemy because uh you know a person of such little importance a person
of such little uh grace or cunning or courage does not deserve does not deserve to be mentioned by
name but uh uh he he had the shirt I was like wow even I don't have the shirt but he he was not aware
that I had made that shirt in response to may raffling off one so I don't know this is very
it's very strange uh let me see the what does what does the stereos know about your work did he
watch your videos he like your lectures I think that he must well I think sarancia did because
like sarancia was like kind of a chris story in or kind of a chris fan so I think she was probably
familiar with the lecture and she probably showed it to him and so he's probably seen it that because
you know they have like a they have like a side show or like a patron's only show where they do
like chrystery stuff or like sarancia explains chrystery to the stereos I was I was I was supposed
to be on that we talked about it a long time ago pre-covid yeah the plan was that they were going
to do a cross-country tour and they were going to come to Boston we were going to record a live
episode of shit is it called is it just called chrystery I forget the whatever the the their
chris show and I was going to be a guest on that and then COVID happened and then there was no more
and then there was no more travel allowed so so there you go so if there's noises by the way I'm
eating lunch I got a venison stew it's very very nice oh it's really funny oh he titled okay it's
not on his main it's not on the main tab of the youtube channel it's on the live tab and it's
called the nostalgia nerd watch along he like could not remember that the guy's name is the
nostalgic critic he kept calling him the nostalgia nerd um anyway true the link there I found the link
I found the link so that was fun um let's see I have a lit oh well let me see if there's anything
else on my list before I get into that that other thing um oh I played a video game I played a video
game this week wow I think it was actually I think it was like immediately after the last week we
recorded I went and I played this video game just on a complete whim the video game in question is
called clash at demonhead on the on the NES are you familiar I'm familiar with the bands named after
it in the fictional universe of scott pilgrim I didn't actually know it was a game it is it is a game
yeah until what's you do what's you do in the game game it was so it was great it was I loved it
I loved it um the the uh wait a minute I was gonna say I've been watching uh this youtube channel
called hungry gorya which is a I think it's it's one of the legend of zelda bosses is a gorya
the one you have to give the meat to um yeah anyway I don't know zelda oh okay well anyway
hungry gorya does a lot of like retro reviews of mostly like rpgs on sometimes the nests but mostly
like the sega master system for some reason uh and I was just watching her videos and uh one of
them she there was one that was like you know top 10 uh like action rpgs on the nests and one of the
ones that was on there was clash at demonhead and I remembered oh clash at demonhead that's the game
that the band and scott pilgrim is named after and you know I watched the review of it and I was like
this game looks cool this game looks awesome I was like well I'm just gonna play it and I did
and it was awesome it was kind of like it's a bit like zelda 2 you know zelda 2 the one with
like the side scrolling yeah it's a bit like the down sword thing yeah yeah yeah it's kind of like
that only uh the differences are instead of like you know in that game you sort of wander around a
world map and you kind of get into random battles um in clash at demonhead there's a map let me let me
find a picture of the map right uh first of all the game is extremely anime it it feels like it's
based on like a uh who's the mangaka that did like ranma and inuyasha uh I don't know his name
it's a woman oh I don't know her name rumiko it rumiko takahashi it's like uh it it feels exactly
as though it's like based on like a rumiko takahashi manga but it's not it's they just made it a game
that that feels like it's that uh uh anyway so there you gotta rescue you know you gotta save
professor plum who's been kidnapped he made a doomsday bomb and you gotta save him kludo no
from earth uh uh clash demonhead map so you gotta go around you gotta go around this mountain
and post the map of this freaking world map of this mountain and uh you gotta go you gotta go
along these routes and so instead of wandering around around a world map and getting into like
environment battles you start at like the junction of route one and you just choose a route and you
just walk along the path between like you know you walk along route two between like the junction
that goes to up to the the route on between five and eleven and then from there you can take route
eleven to route nine and then after route nine you can choose oh do I go on three or on six or on
twelve or whatever and every time you go along a route there is you know the same little you know
terrain that you gotta go over and there's enemies and you gotta shoot them also you you have a gun
instead of a sword but other than that it's very similar to like side the side scroller uh zelda
two it's a little map yeah and um you go around and sometimes you find an npc who will give you
a hint about where to go okay the thing that sucks the thing that sucks is that in the game the routes
are not well they are numbered but you can't see the numbers on the map you can only see the numbers
of the routes that you're immediately adjacent to so you can see the whole map but you can't see
the numbers so if you want to have an actual I didn't do this I cheated a little bit if you really
were if you were playing the game on the nest back in the day you would have had to take a pencil
and paper and go around the whole world in every map and like label it on like a piece of paper so
you would know so that when fucking michael or whoever tells you you know that you gotta go
and stop the guy on route 33 you would have to refer to your notes and be like wait a minute
where's route 33 oh okay that's route there I gotta go there all right uh I didn't do that
I just cheated and used them out like a fucking pussy um it's interesting you say both route and
route interchangeably oh did I yeah you kept switching
I don't know why I don't know why I do that um it's funny because it's like a route
usually just means to like defeat an enemy and make them run away but a pathway is always a route
and like making pathways is a route and a you know a wireless router
in your home would give you why a wireless route it's a router it's a router
but you but it's it's it's connecting routes it's it's it's one of those words that is just
connecting routes it's connecting routes no I don't know to me to me route and route both
equally mean a way or a path so yeah I guess I just use either way I've never really looked
into the etymology of that why this they sound different I always thought it was just an American
thing but I've heard but now that I've heard you say a route is a route and also a route I'm like
wow what the hell is the rules well a well a route a route like a defeat in battle is r-o-u-t
yeah it's not it's not r-o-u-t-e yeah that's the uh who knows yeah I could wikipedia this I think it's
not well I think it's the same word I mean I think it's just like library versus library
just like people choose to pronounce library well that's that's just like a mispronunciation but you
know what I mean uh like often and often say it's the same word just two different people
choose to say it differently or regional uh I don't know why I say it both ways listen I just
want to I just want to it's going to express how much I just want to clash some demon heads I just
want to express how much I enjoyed clash a demon head there was the one one criticism I will say
of it is that they do have they do repeat terrain like a bunch of different routes have like very
similar shaped paths like they kind of did a little copy pasting which is unfortunate
um there's a shop there's a shop that sells like power-ups and sometimes you need a certain
power-up to like progress like to climb an ice wall or to like super jump over a gap or something like
that it's fun sounds fun sounds like a like a little metroidvania precursor oh yeah yeah yeah a little
yeah I mean it's I mean it's pretty similar I mean it's pretty similar to Zelda 2
except I think it's got a little more character because it's got like it's got very funny anime
cutscenes uh hold on every time you talk to an NPC these dialogue bubbles come up and it's and it
says it's talk time and uh yeah it's talk time and you know you gotta you gotta I mean here it looks
like this oh no it's talking time I don't know it's talking time it's talking time and uh and you
know bang bang has to uh you know confront his enemies or whatever yeah that's that style of the
guy at the top what is that guy what is that thing that's bang police no but like there's a style of
anime like manga I've seen it's old you know I think I know what you mean it's like a big
burly policeman a manga from like the 70s or something yeah no I I know what you're talking
about I know what you're talking about I know him mostly because he's in like all those shonen jump
manga fighting games yes yes yes of course how could how could we forget uh I I don't know what
it's called I know the one I know the one that you're talking about um I yeah yeah I like these
guys Tom Guycott the chief of governors and I'll be waiting for you in my desert fortress on route
33 uh every time there's like there's six well you gotta collect seven medallions but you gotta kill
six bosses and they drop a little they drop a little uh Hebrew a little star of David
little Hebrew one because they're part of the Jewish Illuminati they're all part of like the
bankers uh you know they control in the world governments and all that that's not true that's
not what I didn't mean to say that it just sort of slipped out it just slipped out uh uh Kanye told
me to say it um uh anyway now they got these demon medallions and there's also a demon spoiler there
is a demon do clash I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not gonna say you do clash I'm not gonna say you
don't clash uh suspense you just have to play the game find out for yourself uh took me around took
me around I think it took me around like eight hours like six or eight hours uh maybe maybe maybe
longer than that uh I don't know I guess I guess all I could say is it was just a lot of fun and I
liked the video and I was like hey wow video games can be good I was just impressed that like
this just feels like a really big just feels like just felt like a really big game
for like a freaking nest title you know I mean I guess there were other I mean I guess Metroid
was pretty big the Zeldas were pretty big how how long is a is a route on this um a route
is yeah you've said it already not especially long I mean it's probably like
they they vary but they might be eight or 12 or 60 or screens screens long
okay that's quite sizable and if each one of them is like multiple little screens
some they do they do copy paste some areas and you can tell that like oh this this little like
this little like uh section that I got to jump over is the same shape as this other one just
like with a different like you know a texture pack applied to the landscape or whatever or like this
this arrangement this arrangement of uh of enemies is the same they've just been like reskinned
into like a different like regional enemy type or whatever and that's fine and that's fine you
know they had to do what they had to do back then they had to copy and paste the little stuff to
like make the game to stretch the game out a little bit you know it's forgivable I mean I honestly
don't mind that in lots of games where like you've got the the green goblins in the early stages but
then you get to the harder places and you've got the exact same but they're different they're red
goblins now and they're slightly more powerful it's like oh I'm progressing that's true doesn't
really bother me that much I would I get you know I guess if I have to if I have to criticize a
little more not a lot not a huge amount of enemy variety a lot of the enemies just are like a little
guy that flies around and shoots a little bullet at you some of them like some of them like are
like tall enemies that like run at you but like they all mostly act the same the bosses are very
interesting there's like seven or eight bosses and they're all like completely different and they're
really fun uh so that was great the regular enemies some of them are some of them are pretty cute oh
there's a little red they're a little red man faces ah there's a little picture oh damn do you know
what they're called I don't know what they're called hang on maybe I could find like a list of all the
enemies little red man faces yeah there's this one route early on where there's these little these
little like red man heads uh maybe I could find out that the sprite is resource or something
we got paid for like all the uh clash of demon head playable characters okay
no let's check out clash of demon head oh no there's a sprite sheet for bosses
but not for regular enemies you've got to be joking what about my little guys
there's a little guy uh representation little red little red head man
all right I'm gonna look for it later oh there is a oh yeah one of one of them is one of the
bosses is just undyne it's it's just like an anime like fish fish girl uh gotta play it
I gotta play it now uh she was she was pretty she was pretty cute she was pretty cool I think
she's I think she's the only girl I think only girl boss she's she is literally a girl boss
I didn't realize she was a girl but no she's definitely wearing like
cute boots and like a skirt and also the more I look the more I played it the more I was like
this game kind of looks like Scott Pilgrim like like like tell me that like tell me that like that
tell me that that fish girl wouldn't couldn't have been in Scott Pilgrim uh like as a human being
I don't know I mean whatever I I kind of know what you mean you'd see that it's it's this it's the
sort of the chibi sort of legs yeah big similar sort of like the big big round eyes the stump
the stumpy feet the stumpy leg yeah you know what I mean she's she's got that she's got she's got
the uh the Ramona flowers body type the feet phenotype you know what I'm saying I don't even know
what I'm saying um well shit I guess I don't have that much specific to say because I'm not very
good at talking about video games but what a cool game speaking about not being good at talking about
video games yeah mega man lecture yeah it's finished mega man lecture is finished it is
releasing in an hour and 15 minutes um everybody everybody loves it speaking from the future
speaking from the future of this friday when this episode goes live I can confidently say that
everybody loved it it was a huge smash hit million views in a second oh my god so proud
channel's back channel's back baby um you could even say the channel is awesome yeah
um I'm just thinking you know I've said it before if it does well I have what I what I have done
what I have done what I have accomplished with this lecture is that I have unshackled myself
I've unshackled myself from the chains of radcon right I'm no longer before I was like I'll
make lectures at radcons and that was the plan I gotta be dependent on victor to film me or
whatever give me a freaking lav mic man no hate no hate but goddamn the audio quality in those
old lectures is ass it's truly ass I cannot I cannot believe going back to them that how
shitty they sound all of them I can't remember all of them well I don't know all of them like
the lav mics okay most of the time I don't know I mean I was lav mic'd in the sonichu 101 lecture
and in the um the um uh what do you call it uh the kokoro wish lecture I mean it's audible
it's not like a it's not like an unlistenable disaster but like it's not good it's not good
I mean compared to the new one where I used I used a real mic the difference is night and day
as far as I'm concerned um but anyway I I feel like I might want to do a lecture
but not because I want to tell people about something I just want to stand with a microphone
in my hand like a like a singing microphone and do like a stand-up routine but I'm talking about
stuff in front of what in front of what what what if I did a lecture but instead of like talking
about something I was just telling jokes just standing in front of a wall telling
like what would you call that what would you call that I'd be standing up probably hmm yeah I don't
know uh uh but but I was just saying what I've done is that you know I've I've I've invested in
all the equipment that I need and I've done a proof of concept to prove like I don't need to do I
don't need rad con I don't need there to be this big stupid thing nothing again you know and I say
stupid lovingly um I don't need to have this big like uh production underpinning
making a video I guess I can just make one if I want to um and I probably will so that's so that's
fun um best hope hope everyone pledges to my Patreon and gets me to a hundred patrons and you
can choose my next lecture I think I don't know I'm I might I might tip I might change my mind
at the moment at the moment I'm kind of thinking that maybe like a a a pcp history or like or the
downfall of digi bro or like or or the bro or a new the new brony lecture might be might be the one
that I want to do next hmm uh uh pot I don't know I don't think there's like really that big a market
for it no that'd be like a very indulgent that that'll be like an in-joke kind of heavy one
with the audience yeah maybe I shouldn't do that right away maybe I should do something
that could be a patron exclusive little secret lecture well the well the patreon
thing is like people get to vote on one so like honestly I'm not sure if if that were up for a
vote if that would win because that's like you know that's niche um wait wait I had I had a
couple of like possibilities written out on the list uh let me let me read off my list of like
lecture ideas uh what do they have here oh some of these are terrible
uh some of these are really shit but I'll but I'll read them anyway um
one idea was like the history of Oolulilia eh
uh one idea okay this one is fucking this one is stupid um df and stricks
uh I'm sure you don't know who that I do I remember is the pro Jared and what's her face
Holly's dnd characters yes my idea was what if I explained the fictional like in campaign history
of pro Jared and ha and ha that was topical at the time pro Jared and Holly were like a big
thing I feel like if I release that now like nobody would give a shit
uh so I feel like that was there was a time there was a time limit on that one and in his past
um uh hit the history of nuzlocs was was one that's it's just about the comic wouldn't it be
the nuzzle leaf well it would start well it would start there but you know then maybe I mean I
would have to do some research but like I would track like okay well like how did they grow in
popularity from there like did was there like a youtuber that picked up the idea and like who
was the first person to make like videos about them you know um stuff like that um Andrew Dobson
was one you know who that is um oh I think maybe see like a comic guy that's cringe a little bit
yeah he's the guy that draws himself as like the blue teddy bear yeah I vaguely remember
hearing you talk about that guy I figure what he did he's pretty he's done I can't remember he's
done a lot he's done a lot of things but he's very he's pretty funny um oh then my next one was
mega man so you know cross cross that one off the list um strip search now there's one that I don't
know if it really needs a lecture I don't know if there's really enough to talk about I've talked
about strip search here you know you know I know no I don't okay I'm you don't know you do uh
people they strip you and they search you know oh no it was the um it was the the reality it was
the penny arcade reality show oh I've never been on penny arcade so I'm not aware have I not have
I not told you about strip search because that was like a formative that was like a formative
experience for me yeah that was like one of the things that made me want to like become an artist
was like oh my god I wait maybe you have shocking but yeah maybe you have I just forget what is
cool is it like an art people in a house together yes yes it was like a it was like a big brother
for comic artists living in a house and it was like it was managed like complete shit like the
penny arcade guys had no fucking clue what they were doing it's it's really funny because that
it was very it was very wholesome because the uh uh mike and uh oh god wait what's the other one
mike and not jay gays you know it's Gabe and taiko mike and jerry mike and jerry mike and jerry
have no fucking clue what they're doing they envisioned they envisioned the contest as like a
cutthroat like make these people kill each other sort of like thing uh and they have like challenges
and get voted out yes well they didn't vote each other out they had they had they had to beat
each other in challenges to eliminate one another and um it's really funny because in the in the
house all the artists are like they're all like we're all in this together you know like we're
not they don't they don't make enemies they're all very supportive one another they're all like
whoever wins no hard feelings like you know i'm just glad to have met all of you like they're just
they're just like really happy to be there and they're all so sad when anyone has to leave
and mike and jerry it's really funny because like it they only appear in the elimination
challenges they're mostly off screen except for there's and when there's an elimination
challenge like the two artists will come in and they're both just kind of like looking at each
other like huh i guess i guess we gotta do this like i'm really sorry about that and mike and
like jerry wears this like ridiculous like gold chain like he's trying to look like some sort of
like gangster like uh like i don't know like like a pimp or something he's just like oh i'm gonna
pit these guys to get each other and make them kill each other uh but like by the end it's all
like the the pretense is completely gone every time anyone there's elimination everyone's like
why do we do this why did we structure this so we have to eliminate someone uh i just want i just
want to hang out with all my friend my new friends guys and um and in hindsight i actually hate it
because it turned into this horrible like nepotism club where like everyone who's everyone who stuck
around in the contest for long enough eventually just got like a cushy job like working at at
penny arcade uh didn't matter didn't really matter if you won didn't matter if you if you lost the
winners and losers all more or less came out of it with the same advantages katie rice katie rice
ended up winning and katie rice is fascinating because she was one of the people not the principal
one but one of the the ones who like me toed uh john crick for lucy the the renon stimpy guy um
that's a total total coincidence but she ended up winning but then her winning webcomic idea
ended up i think it was ultimately less successful than the second place winner abby howards
webcomic uh the last halloween which she finished and then she kick started for like
$50,000 or something and then she went on to become like a children's like nature book illustrator
person and then i met her at mice the year before covid and then uh um uh there's there's more i
keep going uh amy clearly this is a lot for for a lecture in this because i have no idea about any
of this you know what that's funny i said there's not yeah honestly i could probably i mean it wouldn't
be that long of a lecture yeah in eight hours you know what i changed my mind honestly the strip
search diaspora the like where are they now sort of um oh yeah that could be good it's because it's
yeah like like half of them half of them just kind of disappeared and were never heard from again
and the other half basically got got cushy jobs like in the penny arcade like nepotism empire
and i hate them even the ones that i like i hate that's not true katie rife sort of didn't do that
the winner was supposed to get a wet they could make their own webcomic and it would be hosted on
penny arcade that was the ultimate prize and she got that and it was like a disaster for her because
honestly there was kind of an embarrassing sort of thing where her webcomic i forget what it was
called but the premise of it was about kids that were like abandoned by their parents forever at
a summer camp and so that's the premise and then there was this cartoon on like cartoon network
or nicolodian or something that was about kids being stuck at a summer camp and katie had the
sort of meltdown where she like thought they had stolen her idea is that craig of the creek or something
i don't think it was no i don't think it was that it was a lesser known cartoon that i don't really
hear anyone talk about anymore but the point is she had this meltdown and basically said that
she'd been plagiarized and like it's really not that similar and it's really not that novel to like
the idea of being stuck at a summer camp it's really not that unique um so that was a little
embarrassing anyway okay the strip search diaspora you know what i might move that one up the list
because that one's kind of interesting uh the next one the next one was like digi which would be like
that would that would probably it would be about like the rise and fall of digi bro and also the pcp
and like the and brony's brony stuff i don't know there's a lot that could go into that one
i think i think i think i think like i think of like the digi bro diaspora could be one that
like people would i would probably call i would probably call it the downfall of digi bro is
probably what i would title that one as a as an seo measure personally i just wouldn't want to
touch all of that but i mean i don't i'll do anything i'll do anything um that that's that's
maybe and then i had one occur oh kirby lore kirby lore is is good but also there are already
videos about kirby lore and also i don't know i kind of think that like the kirby lore is a little
bit like i you know people love the kirby lore because it's like oh a cute little pink puffball
oh but he he actually fights all these cosmic horrors it's like oh you wouldn't think so
but like there's not that really that much continuity like yeah like marx is in a lot
of different games and yeah you know pop star like there is continuity but it's also kind of
just like every game there's like a new crop of like weird fucking cosmic horrors that like
yeah i you know there's that i doesn't that i like be like do you mean the one in the cloud
cracko no there's like a like a zero like a i think it's oh the dark dark matter or dark
matter zero or uh there's some sort of big eye that's like very important i think i think you're
talking about i think you're talking about wait wait the white one with the wings yeah oh yeah
yeah i know the one from i've seen like an image that yeah there's an image i've seen that like
has all of the kirby villains and characters and their links to like who's a clone of who's related
to who from space like how is metonite related to kirby and all that sort of stuff
where does kobe come from what are the kirbies you know what that one probably could be election
i i that one's kind of been talked about a lot i don't know if maybe i would be kind of just
trotting on on like well trodden ground with that idea maybe um i mean i haven't seen another
like big kirby video but i'm sure they exist well i've seen um oh fuck was it uh was it woolly
that did those ones where he sort of like narrates the kirby lore i don't know uh there's um
um uh oh here it is here it is uh no it's not woolly no it is woolly yeah woolly versus he
did us like a little series where he does it he does a very sort of a dramatic he says sort of
like a dramatic reading of like a script explaining like you know the sort of cosmic uh kirby lore
prepared to hi um yeah i mean that's not that's not a lecture though okay okay so that's an idea
and the most recent idea i had was an infinite jest like explain the plot of infinite jest
which is something that you should cosplay as vincent for that one
um and that one's just uh i mean
you could you i mean you could already look up a summary of infinite jest on the internet
if you wanted to someone somewhere might appreciate a video explaining it i mean it does have
a fairly a fairly complicated plot so i mean yeah it could be it is something that one could
simplify a bit and explain in a in lecture format so i mean that's just an idea i don't know commenters
if you if you like any of these ideas or you know let me know in the comments you think any of them
are particularly appealing uh i'm i'm curious because i mean i i don't know i could do any of these
uh yeah those are just some anyway those are just some ideas for lectures that i could do
now that like i can just make them on my own uh now that i know how to do that
and i and i if i did one i would i would hire an editor at least for part of the editing like
for the rough cut just like cut out all the silences cut it down to like yeah cut out all
like the unusable footage i would hire an editor for that part that would save me like a week
um and probably none of these would be eight hours long so it would not take me like three
months to get it done well now how how long from the video being finished to it being uploaded did
it take for re-renders and and uploading and stuff you mean like from after i finished editing yeah
after you finished editing the first time how long did it take for you finally to get the final render
uploaded oh man let me look at my my file history uh for a second uh let's see where did where did
i save that oh it was okay
oh god no that can't be true
what is it like oh no no no no it's not that bad it's not that bad okay okay okay uh all right it
looked from my file history it looks like the video was filmed uh it was filmed at the end of
september and then the rough cut where honestly this maybe should not have taken quite as long
the rough cut where i just cut out all the unusable footage was done by september 20th
and that really take me almost three weeks i must i mean i was busy i was busy moving and stuff
um yeah so that was done by september 20th and then i cleaned it up did it take me a
month to clean up the Jesus fucking christ looks like the cleaner cut was done by october 16th
and then the final cut that i considered like basically done no this was not done on the 10th
i must have like i'm some of these must be like saved later i don't know i think um
um i think the fine i think the final cut was basically done like around the end of october
i was like okay this is complete but then i did make a couple corrections because there was like
there were some mistakes in the render that i had to go back in correct and then i ended up
adding a little bit of extra stuff to like bring it over eight hours so yeah around the end of
october so about almost almost three weeks because it's the 20th today yeah fuck
fuck eight hours is too long eight i mean it just for rendering just just a just a render
now my computer if my computer were better it would probably go faster
rendering the eight hour video in 1440p resolution which is what i filmed it in
takes about like five or six days just just to render it uploading it only takes about like
10 hours and then okay okay this is weird i uploaded the video and it took it spent a whole week
processing like you know you upload a video and then it says like okay it's got a process
in standard definition and then it has to process in high definition and then once it's done then
you can watch it in high resolution right yes right uh it spent an entire week processing in
high definition and i thought it was just stuck and then finished and then i was like oh cool and
i watched the video and it would not actually play in high definition like it said it was done but it
didn't play it and i was like what the fuck so i had to upload it again and i and i just uploaded
like i just uploaded the same final cut like several times it was like maybe if i just upload
three different ones maybe one of them will work and i was right the the second the second one out of
three it finished its standard definition render and then it started high definition rendering
and it finished high definition rendering within like a day or two and then i played it and yet
it played in 1440p as it should and that's the one that is going live in 54 minutes from now
the other ones just didn't do that the other ones just rendered the process for a week and then
when they were done the high res video wasn't there and you couldn't watch it and i don't know why
hmm i it's not it's not on my end i didn't do anything different with any of those videos just
some of them succeeded and some of them failed just like sperm it's just like when you nut into a
vagina you know some of the sperm they're gonna make it and it's just random chance it's just
random chance which one fertilizes the zygote you know and that's me that's me just coming onto
youtube just coming and coming into youtube until i fertilize one precious upload seed zygote
do you think your the sperm that made you was a standard definition or high definition
it was it was it was four by three uh 240p uploaded in like 2006 uh looks like shit
and it's one of those legacy baby no i would you know i would the one i would have liked
to record in 4k uh i recorded in the highest resolution that my camera would do which was
1440p or as colloquially known as 2k uh my camera could not do 4k i would have recorded it in 4k
if i can why 2k you ask why 2k because 4k was crossing the road that that that that that um
um yeah yeah um what was what was i talking about oh yeah so took took took took yeah took several
weeks even after finishing the video to actually get it rendered and uploaded because because it's
just fucking big files are just uh it's just a hassle they're just a hassle to deal with
hmm well what if what yeah what if it goes live and then i'm like oh no it won't it's still not
it's not playing in iris oh no the hd no the 1440p
yeah i wonder i guess it's up to the user to click on the little thing if it's not or automatically
hd sometimes it's happened to me where like a video starts playing in for it for no reason
where it could easily play 720 60 fps well um i mean my youtube generally defaults to auto which
is then like it plays the highest resolution that it can play without buffering yeah so yeah because
my connection is spotty sometimes it defaults to a lower resolution but sometimes usually plays in
the highest resolution or it usually plays in 1080 if if possible sometimes it just doesn't update
though even if it's on auto and my connection's good so i have to manually yeah i mean i mean i'll
be honest like i'm sure that like most people to most viewers it does not matter that much
whether the video is in 360p most people are not actually going to be watching the video no and that's
and that's okay just for my own peace of mind like i would like it so that if you if you do decide to
look at the video you'll see an image that is at least crisp enough that you can make out like what
is on the the little pictures on the board behind me you know i still want it to be crunchy well i
hope you enjoy it over the next six weeks because it's a long video six week oh yeah um i hope it
does well i hope it does i hope it does well the last thing uh that i had on my list of things that
i wanted to talk about uh is one piece i caught up on one oh you did that's that's right um did you
read i think didn't a new chapter come out like just yesterday don't they come out on like sunday
oh did they did one i didn't read one yesterday now i'm behind you i think you are i think i might be
yeah it was 60 or 67 went out one we're definitely on this yeah the one uh spoiler for one piece
everyone leave everyone run away um we should have a jingle no no we we should have a we should
have a eliezer eliezer create a one create a one piece jingle yes create content create
content for it
thanks eliezer uh i i'm two chapters behind actually um no cringe sorry i just don't keep
up with it every week i just be like oh one piece yes and i go and read whatever there is um it's
usually only one or two chapters um but we can talk about wano in its entirety because that's over
now yeah i guess wano's over how did you like that you know i was ready for it to be over by the end
yeah also um maybe i was like stupid i kind of like missed the part where kaito died
or lost i kind of like felt like i wasn't paying attention and i sort of like missed it
and then i didn't go back and like wait when when when did he win when did luffy win exactly uh
oh well i'm sure it happened at some point well never mind well big mom got smashed really far
into the ground and then like yeah too later luffy had his big like i don't exactly remember
it was like his whole body went giant because he's got joyboy uh pizzazz right now he's poppy
he's popping his his whole body his whole body went giant yeah for a bit i forget exactly am i stupid
i don't remember him maybe you skipped a whole chapter maybe i did oh my god you missed the
chapter where kaito was defeated i remember him and i remember kaito and mom being like smashed
into the ground right like they both got ended up like being like tunneled underground
basically right they got hit real hard and they went way down yes so yeah okay i mean i i understand
that so like we didn't we didn't see the body so they're definitely not dead right like that's the
takeaway i yeah i mean i i would i would assume so just because okay big mom has such a connection
to elbaf which is an island that they have been hinting at for so long i feel like that she's
gonna come back for that that's not to jump ahead not to get ahead of myself but like that's the
the thing that i'm the most hype for about uh egghead now is like fucking they're talking
about elba we the the giants we the giants took the books from from uh no you're spoiling your
spoiling yeah that's that's really that's uh not in no it's not i i've said i have two chapters
behind i'm i'm just reading that was too much that was not too i'm so i'm sorry that was a spoiler
but i thought that was more than two chapters ago no no i mean maybe he's talking about it in
this one i'm scrolling through i want to read it properly but yeah they're talking about i mean
it's just it's just it's just a passing mention but uh yeah i mean he mentions the uh he mentions
the giants of elbaf are connected and i'm like oh man fuck yeah i love the giants of elbaf
the giants of elbaf there's so many things usopp and all of his like um his friendships with the
two pirate captains giants that really long ago dory dory and groggy right that's dory and groggy
and then groggy and then the other ones that and he's lobby oi mo and kashi who are also
are out there somewhere they probably would meet them and then there's the the guy who's
like a half giant who's like part of the straw hat grand fleet he might show up so many big people
oh i don't want to now i don't want to there's another detail that got dropped that like shocked
and horrified me but i don't want to say it because it might spoil you well here let's
pause the episode so i can read it real quick okay i'm gonna read i mean okay yeah sure
are you just gonna catch up right now yeah i'm catch up right right now okay i'll do a live
reading i guess live live reading live 20 minutes of silence yeah it's the joke i don't read aloud
epic epic remember when i did a video of that i did a let's read and i just started opening a book
and the the whole video is me looking at oh turning the pages i do yeah i do remember that i do
remember that i don't remember what the book was it's just some like old fashioned like book with
leather bound something or other some sort of well must not have been a very good book if you
don't even remember the title it was it's just old and it was on the shelf and i like old books but
they're not very good often you're right old bad old bad new good oh yeah oh yeah why read a book
play fortnite tick tock is what we have tick tock for we don't need books during the void
century those once a highly advanced civilization the history of the dead certain kingdom oh my god
i love certain kingdoms holy shit okay yeah this this is the chat okay this is the chapter that i'm
like look i was already liking egghead like i like the future being i like the future yeah
technology i like the outfits you seem to get their new outfits right yeah they're all cool
i like the cool future outfits i think it rules yes but then this chapter i'm like oh my god
the lore this is going to be my there's more all right so the history history about a battle
between a certain kingdom and 20 kingdoms the winners were the 20 kingdoms they founded the
world government the world knows today to make sure that nobody carries that kingdom's ideology
the arrays is existence from history probably i'm guessing with the sky like like i'm i'm i don't
know what it is but you know the thing that im did to like sabo you know that the the king of the
world or whatever imsama the king oh wait the guy on the throne the guy on the throne the guy that
nobody knows exists except for uh the top government officials and shanks i guess maybe he doesn't
but i know who you're talking about i i mean i remember that you only see him very briefly
just his eye right um i don't know sabo saw him but like um oh i think we i think you see him again
but like uh sabo like obviously escaped marishwa with too much info and im ordered like destruction
of whatever island he was on they found him and then that island was completely obliterated i don't
know if sabo's dead he's probably not dead okay yes yes that's like a power that has and then i
really loved in that chapter where they had like the the you know the lower people in the
organization of the marines or headquarters or stuff they're like um they've been told to not
pay attention to anything that's happening radio silence please you're being ordered to
not pay attention to what is happening right now um go away and then they blew up the island
yes okay okay okay so i'm like ah cool so that's probably what was done to this kingdom
and the kingdom was uh i don't know socialist or something
what they were doing they were doing communism they were doing communism and it's like let's blow
them up all right they're not they're not buying our exports are you still are you still are you
still reading yeah yeah i'm reading the rest understood understood if ohara was erased because
of this theory that means the government had acknowledged that this theory is the truth
why is vagabond talking to these pirates about this that's the thing i'm not sure about yet
yeah that's a reasonable question and i'm similar to you too even if i work with the
government if i talk about it i'll be obliterated how do you know about that kingdom every book
that ohara had had gathered around the world had been destroyed the will of ohara still lives
oh pog pog pog no this this is this is hype this is hype that day the world was in an uproar
scholar island ohara that was famous worldwide for its knowledge got destroyed in one light with a
lone girl as its survivor the world government labeled them as this evil scholar group they
were plotting to take over the world about months later after that incident i went to ohara which
had become a burning field i met with an old acquaintance what he's survived the scholar leader
professor clover professor clover is alive or was alive oh i know okay okay oh no he didn't
he didn't see he met them he said he was an old acquaintance i understand he knew clover
i've known him as an adventurer that gathered every book around the world he'd been
captured in prison 10 times by the navy uh clover backstory i love this clover backstory
holy shit dude ohara is so cool
number one archaeologist in the world he gathered every scholar in one place so they
could easily get blown up fool foolish yes genius
they even burned the tree of knowledge what is that what is this like fuzzy like club-shaped person
don't worry about it what's this like it's like the the the the looney tunes like big red fluffy guy
no you're thinking too hard like big bird i no no you're thinking too hard about it okay
okay now god he's he's this is a real expository chapter and i went into the lake in the central
area i found a lot of books drowning in there seeing that their island was on fire because the
bus to call the scholars were trying to stop it they died protecting the remaining fortunes for
the future the coolest soldier saw it but didn't realize its value it was a great victory for ohara
then i saw it my tears wouldn't stop flowing oh it's robin's mom no
what's robin's mom's name um nico something nico uh sparrow i don't remember nico belle
yeah i just it was a nice name i forgot it um protect the books bring it out of the library i
remember that robin history is an asset for humanity live go do it and then saul is there
he is a giant oh my god elbeth oh my god robin's crying now elbeth oh my god so i better call him
you know you better buster call so wait wait wait wait wait has anyone made that joke before i feel
like i i feel like i've just discovered i feel like i've just hit upon something really important
buster call so it's perfect holy shit okay okay all right all right oh this is great
hard to try to expose that kingdom just as you predicted then it really was the truth do you
know what happened to the books in the lake that time i wanted to bring them to punk hazard but my
plea to the higher ups fell on deaf ears actually that day i encountered those guys oh my god who
were these guys 22 years ago oh my god who were these guys one slouch off the bus to call incident
it's the giants yoish pull it up why are the giants here wait a minute oh it's this
fucking head is it this fucking head that was his head all right he's very big brain that's
that's very literal okay now giants collecting the books from the from the lake
and oh it's a double page we'll zoom in
been a while vega punk i can recognize you by looking at that stand out hair of yours
why are you here oh it's dragon your head became larger than before huh yeah i was at the library
wait did he say that no he doesn't say that but that's what i was working out of the library
just working out of the library so dragon was also clueless acquaintance
they came from elba they knew the value of those books this is dragon talking their captain is a
strange guy with bandages covering his body he said i won't let the assets that ohara left
become a race from history you guys from the world government don't didn't realize its value
so i'm glad they didn't destroy it
wait i'm not a world government ah fuck you i'm tired of hearing it you even became the
government's lap dog idiot even though we the the liberation has invited you has invited you and
you rejected it don't be ridiculous even with my wisdom and technology what can your poor army make
he's he's a real science boy he's getting all that the going where the money is
look how smart he is look how smart he is i mean i yeah is this really the reveal of vikapunk
he's got a huge tongue this right like right by his balls and it's just out his balls i mean i
guess i guess that's true why is this tongue out i just realized that it's just talking right there
i think he is based on that famous picture of einstein sticking his tongue oh my god i think
that's the idea oh this is so funny um world government is a massive organization especially
the navy lots of people can understand me i will make an army that can fight it oh this is this is
before the revolutionary army i think so because dragon didn't have his tattoos and stuff and it's
also before luffy is born because robin's older than him yeah that's true
i will change the world vega punk i won't let clover's death and the will of o hargo and vane
that year dragon along with emperor of emporio evankov and bartholomew kuma established a revolutionary
army what can what can three weirdos do i mean three weirdos that's us minus one ben
yeah hey yeah and look what we've done we are pretty much like a revolutionary army yeah
luffy's father's very passionate they went to elbaf there's oh they're all they're all
parking at all this info yeah as was i i'm i'm right there with them
the books of ohara didn't fall into the government's hands because i was very interested in them i
secretly went to elbaf they let me read all of the documents in other words oh the guy in bandages
is sol because he's because he was burned horribly it'll frozen yeah i forget yes yeah
in other words i read all about ohara and secrets of the world it's all inside my head
for progressing my research right sol isn't hiding no one will disclose his whereabouts
oh robin's so happy dude sol dude are you sol's are you joking like are you kidding me sol is
alive what the fuck what the fuck i forget what happened um i know that he was out kiji al kiji
frozen frozen yeah he died he we thought he died smiling right like the d because everyone says you
know like the thing about having the d is that everyone with the d in their name dies smiling
and sol was frozen with the smile he was laughing she she she she but he's alive do you know what
why they they say they smile die smiling because they have the d i'm gonna post in chat
right this is why you're gonna post is because they got this colon d it's colon capital d that's
why they always die smiling because of that yeah i feel like that's canon oda would probably agree
i no odin's odas japanese he doesn't know what the letter d looks like
that he writes it he knows the letter no he doesn't the wanted poster was in drawing english
letters he writes it in he writes it in hiragana and then the translators translate the d i'll
translate your d i i i promise you won't you fucking wouldn't dare so robin's crying sol
is alive sol is okay is in hiding okay sol's alive okay what the fuck second of all the giants of
elba saved the books of ohara okay sure fine all right yeah let's just throw that out i wonder why
sol was near ohara in the first place maybe it wasn't an accident that he appeared there
well like you think he's from elba f and like it's near elba i mean like him going like knowing
about the the importance of ohara and and being there well didn't he get sent there by the marines
yeah so i guess i thought he just went because it was like official business is like and like the
government like had their eye on ohara i forget exactly but i think he's sort of crashed well
something with and he landed on the beach and he was like oh what's going on and then nika robin was
there and he's like oh i gotta build a ship to get out of here like and and robin would hang out with
him that would be their thing but uh who knows who knows what his true intentions were i'm just
if he was like secretly a part of a pirate crew or like a giant sailing crew the new and cared
about the these books maybe he got tipped off that they were the the marines were about to
invade and he went over there to to facilitate i mean i think that's i think that's definitely
some what was happening because like you know he was he was like right uh that was he he wasn't
gonna let uh yeah i mean he saved robin from i mean i guess he might have just been doing it
because he didn't want robin to die but i also thought like he probably also was like no i can't
let the will of ohara die either yeah alkiji probably definitely as well because i know alkiji
could have killed robin yeah alkiji could have killed him so alkiji definitely was like well
i'll just okay so alkiji froze him this this and then like got him um somebody got him just like
when he got luffy that all you need is a really hot shower yeah right you know what you know what
it makes sense you know what knowing what we know about okiji it actually makes perfect at least
don't let ohara's battle go in vain i'm an ally for every scholar ah my shoes are moving by my
oh shit so what are they doing so fucking cool i still can't release you follow me oh it was
that they got the magnet boots they got the magnet boots from wretched and clank
right and we're in the ancient ruin part with the other guys
oh it's vega punks in there wait which which vega punk uh it's like half coming out of the
the ancient robot is wait please help me damn it it still failed someone please help me while
i was warping the space got distorted it's like huh your dragon sun right i knew you would come
here welcome also bonnie you grew up gramps are you floating wait vega punk i think wait what was
bonnie's relationship it was to kuma right yeah she's kuma's we recently learned she's kuma's daughter
we don't know how old she actually is because she's got the age fruit
oh that's true she could just be preferring this age i mean i mean kuma is middle aged so she's
probably 20 accurate but there's still the potential there's oh there's theories you could say like
what if she's a hundred um i mean kuma's a robot so he could be really old i guess
it could be that old because the pacifistas aren't that old no
he's showing them boot stuff
okay so luffy and dr vega punk who i assume is the real one because of the the flashback we just
had because he looks like him and that's the end of the chapter and then there's another chapter
that i haven't read but i assume there's not like another world destroying a world shattering
revelation in that one right um the most recent ones it's not it's not okay let's keep going let's
go keep on with the give reads one piece on a podcast where you can't see any of the visuals
but it's fine that's fine it's fine it's fine it's fine what happened to your head this is vega
punk's i just could just cut out the dead end really is our what happened to your head wasn't
it larger like a light bulb oh yes his head became large like a light bulb and now it's cut small
and it's got an apple on it like isaac yutin he is you know like as one does you know he cut his head off
just got it uh i i do like that vega punk is the most fucked up character i've seen in a while
he yeah he's really fucked
my body size grew large just like the giants the truth is i am a brainiac man who ate the
nominomi fruit with it i can remember every tiny detail of knowledge the brain is getting bigger
and bigger with the data capacity after all i was born as a genius with unlimited data
branch in my brain it has grown into the world's largest brain and continues to grow
was he he says he was born as a genius with unlimited data capacity so what does he need
the fucking fruit i don't know that's i don't get it i don't get it he actually got a fruit uh it
sounds like he definitely ate the fruit he's definitely saying he ate a fruit that means
that his brain gets bigger and bigger as he learns more stuff i don't understand what
him being born a genius has to do with it maybe he means like born again a genius after he ate the
fruit i mean you know i either way the takeaway is he's a brain brain man who knows everything
yeah or remembers everything you know the more and his brain is giant i i think this is one of
those things his brain is so giant he had to cut it out and put it somewhere for yeah that part
i mean if you're a that that that i can buy as like a devil fruit power being able to absolutely
maybe i don't know honestly cool fruit honestly cool fruit i like it it's one of those things
though like you you hear about these amazing characters and i don't know it's sort of weird
that there's no one that seems to be just exceptional in their field without a fruit
except for like swordsmen like zoro and mehawk that seems to be like one of some of the only
guys about dragon no wait does dragon i think he does i think he has a wind fruit or like a storm
fruit isn't that just speculation it may be speculation actually but i can't remember like
it wasn't it like at loathtown like smoker was gonna yeah like a light lightning struck when
when luffy was about to be executed and it seemed like dragon before that there was like a very strong
implication that smoker could tell dragon was around and then we maybe even see dragon we just
don't know whether dragon is doing the storm okay yeah you know i i mean yeah the one exception
is like gold gold roger which is uh yeah who uh kaito says like you know a strong fruit isn't enough
roger didn't even have a fruit but he conquered the that i'm glad that is but other than him he
seems to be he seems to be the exception though zoro doesn't need a fruit zoro's gonna be the
strongest non-fruit user by the end swords yeah swordsmen well i mean i guess sanji doesn't have
it kind of doesn't really have all all all the straw hat all the straw hats don't have a fruit
except for some of them it's just sort of like frankie doesn't have a fruit but he's also like a
genius uh and stuff he's a robe i mean he's a robot he made himself like he's so smart and good with
engineering and robotics that he was able to do that and and all of vagabonds blueprints allowed him
to make himself more cyborgian with a timeskip and it's like okay frankie's really smart so
vagapunk must be even smarter which is true but it's because partially because he has a fruit
that helps him and sort of makes frankie like more exceptional if he's able to like ever match him
which i guess is a good thing it sounds to me i mean it sounds to me like vagapunk is a genius
anyway but like the nomi nomi just lets him remember everything it gives him gives him like
perfect memory like vagapunk probably would still be some sort of genius yeah i even without the
fruit that's what i'm that's what i think i'm definitely like i know that there's like a sense
that it completely removes uh like a character's like like uh accomplishments if they got a fruit
but it's obvious that you need to work hard as well it doesn't mean you just mean like obviously
luffy has a rubber fruit he wouldn't have got very far if he didn't try hard though
like he's still well he doesn't actually have a rubber fruit oh you know what i mean like uh
yeah yeah sure sure yeah as kaito said a strong fruit is not enough especially since because of
the kata curry fight is like mochi is better than rubber even though it's not rubber now so it's a
little uh it's not that sort of changes retroactively yeah a little yeah a little bit but i did like
that fight at the time showing that like wait a minute if it's not rubber then why could he punch
enol um because it is rubber but it's also something else but it's also freedom yeah freedom is freedom
from freedom from electricity freedom is when you have an elastic band and no matter how you
change it it goes back to how it was freedom is when you don't conduct an electric current
in my opinion so there it's a little bit of a last pull with the whole joyboy thing it's a
little it's a little bit i don't mind it just because visually it means that when luffy's going
at his strongest he's not more serious he's more silly and he goes full poppy like cartoon
tom and jerry sort of fighting which is like the perfect like ultimate form that he could have
yeah yeah i've i've decided i don't really doesn't it doesn't really bother me doesn't really take
that much away from his care i mean he already had like yeah he had kind of a stupid fruit
that he was doing cool stuff with but oh it turns out no he's actually got a really good fruit it's
like yeah whatever yeah oh well yeah uh are you are you done with that sorry no i was just talking
and i was okay over the page so old man you cut your head this is i mean you became an idiot says
luffy yeah that's just what i would assume all true true oh there's a hanger for his brain in
punk records is that how big it is i mean i guess egghead is like i think yeah i think
that's what punk record is is just a giant contains a brain so his brain makes it grow
whenever he learns something you that's fucking vile you know if he lives too long his brain will
take over the entire world it's just gonna it's just gonna keep growing no it's okay i assume it
grows linearly so eventually you know this the well how much knowledge could there be in the
universe is probably big enough to make a mass larger than the earth what i'm saying what i'm
saying is it grows it grows linearly but it you know volume is calculated uh quadratically so
they're like it's not the the the the increase in volume will eventually become you know relatively
insignificant in comparison to the the current the current volume okay sweet so i mean it's fine
so he's he's got the six robot vega punk not surrogates but like versions of himself that
like Naruto style you know what it's you know it's it's great that he made one of them just evil
it's great that he was like let me just find like six versions of myself that like embody my traits
and like definitely got to have one that's evil which one's the evil one like that's really the
girl the girl there's two of them yeah her the pretty one they're both i mean do you mean the one
with the the first the first one they met the first the first one they met is she evil i thought she
was just sort of like like security no it fighting no it listed it i swear it listed like what traits
they embody and like the one that's just daft punk is logic and i forget the other ones but yeah
that one is like evil is sort of trait i'm i'm and it's like good good job thanks for making one
that's evil that feels like it's gotta be a translation thing maybe it could mean something
else i think so i mean i don't know the version that's what my translation said the translation
i'm reading did not translate the little icon so i don't i don't know how to read the i'm not japanese
i'm not smart well let me let me let me look it up on the wiki but anyway um the one thing i wanted
to say is that yeah i was i was so caught off guard by the one girl who eats food for everyone
and takes shits and that's her job that's that's yeah that's good for her good for her i mean yeah
hell yeah but like it's such a it's such a weird like i don't know it feels like fetish stuff it
feels like like a weird sex thing a little bit but it's also like a silly cartoon thing so it's
not and it's probably my brain that's fucked up it's it's it's it feels a little like that because
like she's wearing like a thong and like while she does it and she's a sexy lady yeah and she gets
all big and she gets all small i guess jewelry bunny all already does that so whatever okay i'm
looking at the wiki according to the wiki um okay yeah this is not all right i thought shaka was
logic but this the wiki says that shaka is good shaka is good and lileth is evil edison is thinking
pythagoras is wisdom atlas is violence and york is greed greed so okay so they're an expert in
their certain field the greed field yeah and york york is the one who eats and shits and sleeps
well if it's logic maybe the other one is chaos instead of evil the wiki says wiki says they're
good and evil huh like an expert in being evil or i don't know whatever they just they just embody
the trait of evilness so every person in his in his six person vega punk thing can add their memories
to the punk records if every person has access to my brain it's as if all mankind has acquired my
knowledge also if mankind reciprocally can update the punk records isn't it is possible to create
and see knowledge for far beyond my brain this brain will someday he's talking about and turning
the world into a hive mind everyone would be this they'd know everything hell yeah
so much knowledge it's like cell phones we've all got access to the internet yeah we don't read it
have you read every wikipedia article i'm working on it i'm getting through it i'm getting there
going alphabetically give me give me give me a little give me a little bit
means every researcher in the world can learn from it our chopper likes that learn about medicine
jim jim is like are you gonna police my thoughts are you gonna be the woke police
are you gonna tell me off you're not gonna you're not gonna you're not gonna cancel my hot takes
of you and see into my my my my non politically correct thoughts are you vega punk you fucking
democrat oh he's just like dr fouchy he's gonna cancel me for not wearing a mask
uh so obviously bonnie is pissed because vega punk made her dad into a robot yeah
i really want to know what's going on with that bonnie please think again if you kill him you'll
end up making more enemies than you can imagine just turn off the switch
that beam function is to attract a large number of insects so it's not a
lightsaber oh you fools you got all the hisk to hisk poor bonnie you know there's one thing
that i have enjoyed more and more because this happened more and more is a female one piece
characters getting fucked up because there's a lot of there's a few characters over the
course of the series that have just been like too pretty to be really beaten and more and more often
nami and and sometimes robin they get a little fucked up and bonnie is also getting fucked up
and it's sort of it's it's nice it lets them play on the same comedy playing you heard of here folks
gib is pro violence against women it's true because it's it allows them to be parts of funny
jokes whereas otherwise it would be just the guys being like beaten up see gib this is why
you're one of the good ones and i'll tolerate you um excellent now i hear you though now i hear
you now they should be subject to punishment comedy pretfalls are not just a boys club thing
girls need to girls need to fall and get anvils dropped on them
gaslight gatekeep and uh girl injuries that was terrible i know i know
her reason to kill me makes sense i'm saved because the weapon she picked is a fail product
by the way you guys recently went to warn her right it was a rumor is it true that there's
another dragon besides kaito ah momo yes it's devil fruit i left in punk hazard it seems to
ate it it's a fail product it's an artificial devil fruit that i created it was created with a
large number of research funds over 20 years from kaito's lineage factor but his growth won't be the
same as the original fruit ah that's why he can be turned into a dragon like kaito why was that mean
his growth won't be the same but he can be turned into a dragon but it was a success he spit fire
and he was powerful what's the color it's pink oh it's a great failure oh that's why well
no it turned into a perfect dragon replica of the real the dragon fruit but pink pink garbage
god damn it a genius and a perfectionist i love this guy yeah i'm i'm vibing with egghead arc
yeah that's legend it's the giant robot here the legendary metal giant that attacked marishwa 200
years ago you know i keep getting i keep losing track of like certain amounts of years ago this
happened two years ago was the timeskip 20 years ago was when most of the characters in the straw
hat crew were born uh so many years and years and what are they talking about like and then the void
century is like a certain is it 200 years ago void century is 800 void century is 800 years ago
okay there's so many like numbers of years ago that certain things happened i need a
timeline i need like a map i can look at maybe it's maybe it's just because the ohara like void
century stuff was some of like the most interesting lore to me but i remember that like void century
was 800 years ago so when they say something happened like 800 or 900 years ago i'm like
that's got that's something to do with the void century ah but this machine was probably created
far more than 900 years ago i still don't know creation i heard that there was no damage due
to a lack of energy the researchers the time was surprised with unknown science it has
no one knows where it came from what it was trying to do is the eye and giant is came from space
the world government ordered its complete destruction but because of their curiosity
the researchers didn't do that it exists here because the information of it has been passed down
from generation to generation the government didn't know about its existence
huh oh the researchers just hid it and then all i'd just been passed down
200 years ago that is the exact year when discrimination against fishermen started
what that's what they say there was never any before that yeah even when they're that ugly
i guess give me a break maybe it's uh they discovered them 200 years ago and they thought
oh cool more slaves oh yeah yeah it could be because they'd be like under yeah fishermen
i don't yeah that makes that would actually make sense god there's so many things i'm trying to
read like quickly but i don't want to like miss understand something yeah fair i mean no no rush
i'm i'm taking this time to prepare a tweet about like oh five minutes till the video goes
live oh shit you know i don't i don't actually need to be there for like the whole that's what i
just want to be like there like when it starts yeah yeah uh but i don't have to like pay attention
to the whole thing so wait those the two groups are both looking at this robot frankie and and
robin and sangy and all that they're with number one and they're watching vega punk talk to luffy
in front of the robot we created vega for us like based on everything we learned from it
there are things i can't replicate with my science i can't believe it was a machine
machine soldier made 900 years ago machine that even you can't replicate the problem is power in
the past there was a power that was enough to change the common sense of the world today
it was called coal we used to burn coal we need to go get some coal from the mines
why do we why do we ever stop burning coal anyway yeah i mean yeah sure the the oceans
rose and now we live on like an ocean planet but like it's fine
it's just like wind waker with the industrial revolution it's just like the real world in
like 50 years for now i'm happy luffy and the others are safe but who's that girl
jewelry bunny yeah they should know her can you do something for me can you take me out of egghead
what luffy wants vega punk wants luffy to take him out of egghead
because he's uh wait he does did i miss something yes straw had luffy it is fated that you have come
here can you do something for me can you take me out of egghead i guess because he is world
government aligned he's monitored so he needs somebody to uh kidnap him if he wants to leave
maybe this is cypher paul we wish to harbor here he is cypher paul fucking luchy they're back baby
it's like they never left who kaku we're gonna get more kaku kaku uh i want to rematch i want to
rematch with everyone but all the other guys are gone i like the chapapa guy whatever happened to him
did he's we did is he dead remember chapapa chapapa wait who's that it's the big uh spherical guy
with a zip mouth the big from cp9 and he's lobby uh is he the door door fruit guy no no that's
balloono balloono chap up i can't remember his name but chapapa is the thing he says all the time
oh yeah i i think i remember you think i remember there's someone like that
i got uh information that jewelry bunny is heading to egghead she's an eyesore who repeatedly escaped
but we no longer have any use for her right next time we meet i'll definitely kill her
what used to check before it's the government ship it'd be bad if they knew we harbored pirates
in here also the cp0 and luchy just let them enter rob luchy is an assassin right
oh is that she's like this is the vega punk 2 she's evil so she wishes like
for everyone to be killed so she's like oh happy that an assassin is going to come
and kill all the straw hats oh let him in
wait who's letting them in why what where where am i uh vega punk 2 the hot lady
evil evil evil evil lady i mean she is also hot lily yes she is she is hot she is hot
um said let them enter rob luchy is an assassin she looks really happy about an assassin i think
i think that when you make an avatar of yourself that embodies your evil you should not let it call
you should not listen when it says to let someone in but then the other version number one it says
prepare to intercept and decline their request to the harbor so it's like both of yes and no
in my opinion the good one is probably the one to listen to it's if i had to if i had to pick
yeah i don't know i don't know who who's right you know who's who could say who could say who's
right in this situation oh my god i like that namie i mean this in this translation namie's
like oh no i hate rob luchy isn't he retired uh god not that guy again it's not even like
terrified it's just sort of like fuck not that not him you nearly killed all of us
oh it's it's coming back a kingdom oh they've got kuma they've got kuma and they're trying to like
un roboticize him but he's been he's been like compelled to move because of something kuma no
is it love is it love for his daughter oh is it love for his sexy ass
i mean not wrong i'm not wrong though no you're not i was i was a thinking of it as like
like a beacon like blipped an egghead is like oh you must come back you are programmed to come
back and then maybe that's what you're supposed to think is happening but no it's actually because
he wants to save his sexy ass daughter maybe the insect beacon was actually a dad come home
yes yes and he's like part insect that makes sense that that that let's go with that
you know i kuma still has his like devil fruit power in this form like he's not a pacifista
he's not like a made from the ground up robot he is still him that has been turned mostly cyborg
to the point where he doesn't really have a self but he still has his devil fruit power he can like
use his poor fruit to like blast himself towards egghead couldn't he
can he do that he should be able to do that he can launch other people i don't see why he can
launch himself i feel like that's the the way he appeared on thriller bark when he was introduced
like he's just sort of there suddenly makes because he's able to do that guy can just be
lit just could be anywhere yeah yeah i don't i don't see why not if he can launch anyone anywhere
with his like precision paw paw fruit that's a good ass fruit oh yeah i love that i'm sorry but
that's a good ass fruit it's such an odd like i i'm assuming there's some sort of pun involved
with like a bear paw and like whatever the effect is like pushing people but i i'd like that it's
like it's a it's a shockwave but in the shape of like a paw with the like little beans included
okay and that's the end of the chapter beans little beans well i feel i feel like we've discussed
the chapter pretty thoroughly as you've been yeah going through it with the disc oh no the
discord link is dead discord oh in in my video uh oh yeah this is cool i'm really liking this yeah
this is cool i've i've sort of lost track of what the cover arc is about is caesar clown and judge
me too um he's hooking up with caesar hooking up with um not cp9 um the germans g twins the germa
and and judge or have judge wherever you say it um they're facing off in the top of this
chapter but yeah i gotta i want to go back and reread because i think it's like how they escaped
from big mom using caesar clown's help and because caesar clown and judge are both like
super scientists they're probably going to end up teaming up and now the judge is like aligned
with sanji at least they're not like on bad terms anymore at least not in the same way
they'd probably be like straw hat aligned so caesar is still going to be an ally despite his
best efforts to the contrary which is funny caesar is such a like wannabe the bad guy but
he turns out to be the friend the the unwitting ally of the straw hats every time after he got
punched by luffy love that guy caesar do i like i guess i don't really i don't really have much
of an opinion about caesar he's fine he's kind of funny he's like uh like a buggy light he's like
buggy the clown light um because buggy the the role the buggy filled early on is was filled
by caesar clown in like the poll cake island arc i think it's it's very funny that uh buggy is
offering bounties on marines now yeah i that's interesting the whole thing with like what a
power move yeah i love the whole thing with buggy's um like falling higher and higher up the chain
yeah he's failing upward failing upwards this whole career the whole thing with like
him at like the the war at marin ford and all of the people who believed buggy was the one who
orchestrated the escape from impel down and they love him so he's got all these impel down breakouts
and then a bunch of other people who saw him being so cool at at in marin ford and they just
used that to to like bolster his crew to ridiculous heights and then the shibukai
like position allowed him to be like un like un uh messed with by the marines so he's just sort of
like he's able to grow in size and relevance he's just his face is just appearing in all the
right places just get he's getting that reach he's getting that exposure i hope everyone and
everyone just so everyone just associates his face with like big important deeds that were done
but like he he's totally useless yep i really would like this is something i've always felt for a
crocodile and me hawker just like ah just let him take the blame for whatever yeah he could he
can be the boss like yeah whatever yeah they just like yeah he'd be the fall guy um and so take the
heat but they're with him and see dad if we need to and those two are so strong and they're with
him so he's like he's he's safe even though shibukai is like no longer it's been dissolved so like now
he's a pirate and because of his relation to luffy and shanks i'm i'm definitely expecting
somewhere later when a huge event is happening is the shanks and luffy fighting over the one
piece and blackbeard's there and then buggy's also there and so he's like seen by all who
can see what's happening is like one of the equals in this battle and he's like oh my
fucking god i'm not i shouldn't be here i'm gonna die i'm going to die right now he's he's
he's he's host oh yeah but but he's gonna survive and then people are gonna believe people are gonna
believe that buggy is the king of the pirates i think that's gonna be the end i think everyone
who's there actually knows but then buggy gets to like like a lot of the credit or like or something
really funny like that i really hope that happens that's like the ultimate conclusion to that is
the buggy accidentally becomes the king of the pirates and the hearts and minds of the world
everybody believes buggy did it and luffy doesn't care because he's just totally free he doesn't
he doesn't want the title he just wants the total freedom that's true we can all we can all
unite behind the banner of buggy yes right or left you know whatever whatever your personal
ball we all we all love buggy so we can all come together i so fucking cool
dude i'm loving egghead i'm really liking egghead so far yes it's super super good
bag of punk is awesome going at a pretty fast clip one oh i think just because there was so much
they needed to set up before they could start like collapsing things down into a fight um it just took
such a long time for all these characters to get introduced and the the lore of the one oh people
and it took a long time i did enjoy it but like there's not a much the only thing we know about
vega punk is that he's a scientist and so you can just also do whatever you want
you just have have big revelations immediately and then seeping zero is already here it's great
yeah things are uh things are things are moving pretty fast i mean i guess we're i guess these
has got to establish a lot of stuff before we get into you know whatever whatever conflict ends up
defining uh this current arc so you know we're we're learning a lot i wonder if we're gonna
spend a lot of time elba we're talking about elba and and and ohara yes yes i'm just so glad
we're talking about them again yes i you know i'm trying to think of like what can be done
in this area like they see all this cool stuff i don't feel like because they're not constant like
they're not antagonistic towards the the vega punk people they're just sort of learning stuff
there's like a little library session they're learning some stuff and then cp zero is gonna
be like they're fucking around but i feel like there's too many straw hats for cp zero to really
do a lot of damage to them like this isn't like um a warlord or or or something it's just a small
group of strong guys that they could have fights i feel like this is more gonna turn into like a
we gotta escape and we got vega punk vega punk is gonna tell us to go to elba because we need to
do something we're like oh shit let's go let's go and then they will go i don't know if how long
an egg head's like arc would be because like what are they gonna do here i mean probably fight cipher
pole uh probably fight the vega punk clones or some of them yeah i mean i feel like they've already
done that they did the bit with jimbay clone and they're like wow what the fuck but they're the
the jimbay pacifista is uh hey what's up with oh um is kuma a uh lumarian
bonnie says that like her dad always says that he was part of like a very special race
did you did you catch that i did catch that i don't remember and also when you see when you i think
you see uh one of the i don't sure if it's a kuma pacifist or if it's kuma himself it's impossible
to tell but you could see one of them and he had black wings in in one of these panels in like a
recent chapter i swear to god i'm not making this up huh and also he was black and also jimbay was
black and i don't know are all luminarians black i'm not sure about that um but no i swear there
was a kuma with black wings and bonnie says that kuma is a lumarian let me go back to chapters to see
because i i i remember that this is fucked up fucking lilith says that like if only there
were an eternal flame like an eternal power source they're talking about they need a power
source to power this stuff bonnie says we need more power if only there was such a thing as an
eternal flame my mind immediately goes to the lumarians backfire like that's that's what they're
right that's the setup here right yeah i'm pick i'm picking up detail there's got they're they're
making lumarians they're trying to duplicate the lumarian backflame yeah we learned about that
through king and through kuma's involved somehow through like big mom wants uh one of every race
at her tea party because she's like insane and one of the lumarians is the race she doesn't have
and king and and kydo's crew was a lumarian he's got the wings so we learned about what the lumarians
are so yeah where's where's the kuma you're looking at you're talking about because i saw the g
there was just like one panel in it was maybe a couple chapters ago it was recent but i don't
know if it was like one of these last two chapters but yeah we there was a you know what i mean maybe
i'll i'll try to find it as well uh yeah i think it's maybe four chapters ago because yeah this
is not where bunny says he's my dad uh 10 6 yeah it would have been in
the my my video is live by the way it's going but i'm just i'm just gonna let it go i don't i don't
have to i don't have to be i don't have to be that attentive to it it's gonna be going for a long time
and i'm not that nervous because i have clicked i've watched through it enough times that i'm
pretty confident there are no big fuck ups or uh anything like that so it's all it's okay
um okay i think i see the panel you were talking about i don't think he has black wings he looks
he looks like he has black fire behind him show me show me show me uh it's when after
uh bonnie turned everyone young and jim bae is young here
yeah it would have been around that time because i remember it was not very
far from when we see uh you know pacifista uh jim bae
guess it's the chapter how they turn jim bae black how they turn jim but fishmen are already black
what the fuck um i'm scrolling i'm scrolling oh did you post it yeah put it in yeah
let me see uh he doesn't look he doesn't have black wings but there is no this is not no this
is not the panel i was talking about i think it was there's the one the one panel with with law
as a female because of the funny fucking doc i think it's that i think it's after this or maybe
it's before this no this was not the panel i was it was like a full page panel all right i'm
scrolling through the next chapter it might have even it might have even been before this
because i see okay the next one the next one has jim bae with the wings
i mean pacifista jim bae why does he have the wings because what the fuck is that he's like
lumarian crossbreed or something why they're they're they're i think
my guess is that they're cloning they're like adding lumarian dna to their pacifistas in order to
create like lumarian clones that will they'll use to power stuff right that's what's going on here
yes if there's an eternal flame i can't remember what was said about the lumarians
she mentioned an eternal uh well uh we just fire on their back they have fire on their back
and they can turn it on or off at will and when it's on they're like invincible or when it's off
they're invincible or something like that yeah i think it's it's like it was a defense thing like
he has to turn his flames off to do an attack and that's when zoro realized he could attack him
yeah it's something like that i don't remember exactly how it works
okay i'm looking at i'm looking at chapter 62 1062 it's loading
oh wait yeah did you find it yeah yeah yeah it's the cp zero you knew it what chapter is it 62
it is 62 scroll down a bit i'm scrolling i'm scrolling yes look at that look at that shit
what's going what the heck is this it's gotta be another wait no so in short our assignment is to
return this problem child back to egghead so this is a this is a a problem child meaning that it was
uh it's a failed experiment or like a world government issued it and it didn't work something
went wrong and so they're bringing it back to egghead okay i can't tell i i think i think it's
relevant it looks to me like this kuma is meant to have like dark skin like his skin looks darker
than the shadow of the background possibly i'm i'm taking this i'm taking this to means that all
that's what all the lumarians look like yeah and then but then okay bonnie saying that like her dad
always said he was part of a very special race what the fuck is that yeah the bear guys no wait no
that's just his fruit that's just his fruit it sounded like it sounded like she was talking
that like kuma told her that he's a lumarian but there's no fucking way that that's true
we never saw him with a fire on his back he never had he doesn't have wings he had light
skin which i think is relevant so i mean i don't think so i mean i think if kuma was a lumarian
that's like a very it's a significant like rare thing so he would be like
like if the reason he's like giving himself up to vega punk is like a good bargaining chip
yeah it would be like we're gonna use him to duplicate the duplicate the lumarian dna and
create that fire yeah and it's like uh yeah so like for some reason to protect someone maybe
to to help dragon to help his daughter he did that maybe he just believes in science maybe he just
believes in science that hard so yeah my eternal flame is he does have a flame he does you know
in that panel you know he does have a flame behind him in that panel you posted and i don't
know it's hard to say if that means anything or not well that's just jim bae's imagination of
of kuma but it could i know i know but jim bae's heard it could mean that jim bae's heard of a rumor
of of kuma having like black flame around him that's that's really funny what does it says image
it says image in front of the i guess that means it's his mental image is his mental image of kuma
from what i've heard kuma's a real piece of shit your dad sucks the fact that here at this point
in the story in the same like in with two chapters before there's there's this pacifist to kuma with
the wings and there's kuma with depicted with fire behind him but then you know jim bae clone also
has the wings so maybe this is just unrelated could be oh boy we just don't know yeah we just don't
know it would do something to add to like the reason kuma is the one that was turned into a robot
as opposed to anyone else if he's like a special race lumarian boy
like why him well he had special stuff they tore off his wings and they doused his flame
so that's why you didn't see it before wait i gotta i gotta be mean to my chat
wait he was already a robot when we meet him in thriller buck he already had robotic parts
zora couldn't cut him properly
he yeah but he hadn't he was like partially robot but he had not like lost his mind yeah
yeah but he was partially robot that means they could have like surgically removed his wings to
study them that's why he doesn't have wings when we see him like that that could be an explanation
as to why he doesn't have wings when we first meet him or anytime we see him i suppose if he's
already got gone under some like cyborgianness and then they whitewashed him so he doesn't look
as dark yeah yeah they they made him more marketable well they were like okay we gotta we gotta make
this guy but we can't sell we can't sell him in china if he looks like this we gotta why we gotta
make him white do you know about do you know about the showbiz pizza gorilla what no i don't you
know but do you know about showbiz pizza and the yeah the big bear their their drummer was a
gorilla oh no i do i do yeah and when they and when they franchise the showbiz pizza animatronics
to china they made the gorilla white because i don't know they liked the gorillas the gorillas
already they made him an albino they made him an albino gorilla to make him as fucked yeah i think
it i think it was china i think it was china uh there yeah there's like one there's like one
version of that animatronics that that has a white gorilla i think it's in china and they just
they just asked him can you can you make him not black please sad cringe um i don't get it
i don't get what's going on with kuma here but i mean i guess i guess we're gonna find out
you know when i first read the like if only there was an unlimited power source
um we could do some crazy shit i'm like are the ancient weapons like used the the ancient
weapons use the power source or are they do they create the power source maybe whatever destroyed
that island that isn't like the world government has is using a similar thing maybe they've got
the power and they destroyed the country that didn't want to be subjugated about it do you think
so you think the the power that um it was lilet that says like no it was um it was dafpunk
that said there used to be a power or someone said there used to be a power
that we don't have anymore yeah i forget who i forget who said it um do you think like they're
using that the the i mean i mean it seems like an unbelievably strong laser beam from space like
what the hell else i would have thought that like that was something that like pluton could do
yeah um like if if the ancient weapons exist but they're not currently operational yeah like
they're supposedly still buried in old wano right yeah but then this this other thing maybe that's
just one of the ancient weapons that is around and in use there are other there are other ancient
weapons i mean god if like if that's just what other ancient what i mean pluton is supposed
to be the best one so do we know where the others are could that be urinus or something was it um
i forget the names of them well i think okay correct me if i'm wrong but didn't in water seven
frankie wanted the they burned the blueprints to neptune right i thought it was pluton but
maybe it's neptune i thought i think it was a different one i don't know frankie still remembers
that i'm pretty sure he does because that would be an obvious thing still remembers that like he
read it once and then you destroyed it but like he could build it because he he had like a photograph
eyeball he took a picture of it oh well sure why would you oh yeah of course he must remember
wouldn't it be silly if he's like oh yeah i just forgot about that officer i just kind of like
stopped worrying about it just didn't seem that important i i i i needed to clear my hard drive
and accidentally deleted it yeah sorry i need to make space for like the new uh fucking update to
my favorite mmo i'm playing in my head i needed to record a new lecture and you know it's a lot
it's a lot of high-definition footage i needed a new hard drive so whatever it's fine nobody's gonna
use it anyway um now i'm trying to think is there anything else uh wacky going on i need to pee
i'll be back in a sec okay uh i'm back you back uh no i'm not here oh okay
haha trick to i'm indeed here um were we were we talking about uh one piece things what else
has been happening that's crazy uh uh this is the most interesting one piece has been
in a while i think i'm still trying to like do you know at the end of one oh when
the the old shogun shows up he was the tango guy the whole time yeah yeah yeah the grandpa
and he goes downstairs and he shows nika robin and trafalgar lord the um shows him the love of
the road ponyglyph right yeah and then they learned some stuff and they got that's the third one and
they need one more i think why no do they do they actually show the ponyglyph or do you just say it's
down here and i don't know if i show it in the sunken world because i know they said that jack
was used to swim down and and see it or get it something i i feel like something in my i think
i remember seeing like they don't really draw attention to it but i think while robin is
talking to that old tango man tango man just like in mega man eight uh i think they talk about i
think you can see like a ponyglyph etchings in like the background so i think they do find i don't
know if it's the road ponyglyph uh but um they i think i think they got the etchings i don't
know if we i don't know if we actually saw the the the cube yeah i remember i feel like that
should have been a big deal because like wano is the place where the ponyglyphs would come from
and the guy who knows the most about it oh that's right oh wait that's right they came from wano i
forgot maybe that's why there there was etching in the background because like the yeah that's the
language they used or i forgot is it that like only wano had like the knowledge of like steel
craft to like make was it all ponyglyphs or was it just the road ponyglyphs it was all of them
they all came from wano yeah because they're all like invincible right they're all like you
can't they can't break like this the special metal metallurgy or whatever yeah they really
called it forgot about that because they make swords they fold swords they can fold cubes
natural i mean i mean in one piece sword metal is like the most powerful substance known to man so
yeah it's it's the same as like when the plane crashes and they find the black box and they're
like well why don't they just make the plane out of what the black box is made out of it's like
oh a sword can cut through an entire mountain well why don't we just make the most important
artifacts in the world out of the same metal that we made the swords out of well they did
that was the genius of wano amazing they thought oh no you thought of everything uh
uh oh man um yeah i feel like um freaking my my understanding of of a lot of one pieces like
bigger like things like the rocks pirates i'm not entirely sure what the hell that is like building
to um well the rock pirates was the crew that was like it was the crew the big mom and kaito and
and what's his face like that that that that guy there was a guy that garp and roger or white
beard were fighting i don't know i i need to reread and get like reacquainted with all of these
things because or maybe just look at the wiki because well they were like read one piece and
there's so many fucking like plot threads going on rocks was like to keep track he was like a big
captain like before roger right or like before white beard
yes yeah and i think he might have been enemies with roger and or white beard
it's unclear i feel like they definitely fought in like a specific island and it's very like
secretive what happened there we don't really know
and then they left and then roger eventually became the king of the pirates and the other
guys the rox pirates disbanded and white beard and kaito and big mom they all went their separate
ways i think white bro was also on that crew white beard yeah yeah yeah white beard was
yes yes a bunch of him a bunch of important people used to be on the the rocks pirates crew
and garb knows what happened because he was there he was like the hero from that battle
that's how he got his fame or something i'm typing sorry it's okay
okay okay i'm i'm i'm back um yeah i guess that's in a week we've said about one piece
so you know i guess there's a lot to say because i just caught up and and then also there was a
huge lore dump just this week last week though i will you know i'm gonna keep i'm gonna keep reading
i'll stay caught up we can uh nice we could we could talk about the next chapter on the next
episode of the plural christened his podcast we will we'll make a little section out of
ellias are sorry for so much dead air that's gonna need some chopping up chop chop chop get to it
next next time i will have read it before we record yeah i checked just last night and i was
like oh shit a new a new chapter like literally just dropped like the night before well okay what
uh what else is on the agenda well that was the last thing on my list of topics let me see where
did i what did i put that that stupid list um yeah one piece clash of demon head train
sounds chili and kagassia was my list so that's everything i am it's a i guess it's sort of a
silly thing to say what's up but um i i've not been very productive recently but it's been for a good
reason it's because i am too happy all the time i've had i think i have opposite depression
i think i have when depression you mean mania is mania the word you're looking for
it's like uh when you get depression you're like oh i can't do anything uh and everything is so
difficult and i have that but it's not because i feel sad it's because i'm too distracted with
how happy i am i'm smiling all the time and i'm enjoying things and i'm like oh shit i should
have worked today but i was i was too happy damn hate hate that hate that hate that when that
happens that's my week i've i've been doing a little bit of things here in there i suppose
there are i suppose there are worse problems to have yeah so you know i'm all right i'm vibing
vibing vibing okay i i do want to get uh chapter four of chelsea gunsmoke done before didn't you
did you say on like twitter that you were going to be posting it you're going to post the new
chapter pretty soon right um yeah relatively soon i haven't started like inking uh and stuff but i
have all of the the blocking for the you know next 20 pages could turn into a chapter think of
like a logical point to end it and then be like okay i'll draw these and i'll draw them i'll release
them shouldn't take too long uh that's that's my main goal for the moment it's a good goal
it's a good goal i've been i also want to to look into anison for printing i know i think i want
to print on demand yeah i feel like um yeah i mean a kickstarter is a whole big like i'm adding a
whole lot of like bureaucracy and and management and organizing to myself which is it is that's
i'm like it definitely if i can get good enough quality on print on demand i'll i'll do it thrams
them you know what you know what it's totally valid i get it that the is a pretty reasonable
yeah uh it's um it's gonna be online anyway so it's just if people want a physical copy
yeah yeah because i mean i mean then it's just kind of like you just kind of you know you set up
you set up the file and you and just let just let amazon handle because then they handle the printing
they handle the delivery and the shipping and all that don't have to worry about it and i just get
i just get currency you can get on your fucking kindle probably probably yeah no i'm pretty i'm
pretty sure you can it's just you need the right kind of kindle that has a screen you can't get
just the one of those kindles that are like low battery usage the only show text
you need to be like a an ipad with a kindle app or something
yeah interesting you know i never even thought of like putting any of my stuff on like amazon
books or whatever but yeah i guess yeah i guess then it's available people can buy it
downloaded digitally and like yeah sure it is up on your website but like i could see someone
wanting to you know pay like a couple bucks just to get a file to read on there you know
their reader that makes i could do like a fucking audiobook where i read all of the characters
all of the dialogue and then this panel she has a gun up and she shoots and goes
then the next panel guy gets shot in the head oh blood everywhere
and he says ouch that'll be the audiobook
and that's the audiobook the audiobook version yes yes uh i think that's a great idea that's
that's like a whole new medium this genre bending describing a comic uh
yeah and then in dishpanel and then in dishpanel she and this panel is very small and and it is
sort of showing that this character is insignificant compared to this big panel it's this bigger
character and then wait and then this next panel yes she's grabbing the gun and i kind of fucked
up drawing the hand the hand is kind of fucked up but like it's it still looks good it still looks
good okay next panel it's still good it's still good it's still good don't worry about it but
you have to mention it you have to mention it but for the for the blind you know
mm-hmm they should be able to enjoy claire's a gun smoke just as much as me close closed
captioning i think i just i think it's strange i don't really get the logic of like you know how
you can add like closed captioning to like twitter image posts closed captioning yeah like
or alt alt text like you can post an image on twitter and you there's the little alt button
on the image and you can click it and it brings up like a text description of the image
uh uh yeah what's that for is is the idea that like someone scroll scrolling twitter might use
like text to speech to like have it like read it out so they can hear the description of the image
you know that yeah text to speech would be the way because that's how you would navigate the
internet normally as a blind person i mean i guess i just assumed that like blind people just
like wouldn't use twitter because but maybe they do and they just like use it in like a text to
speech i i feel like you could you could get a lot out of twitter because it's mostly text
and you could just like scroll and it says things maybe they just play when they're on screen just
the text to speech just plays like if you've got if you're scrolling really fast just loads of voices
keeps shouting at you like as you're scrolling you just keep starting the next tweet yeah oh my god
there's got a donation it's got a donation in chat oh my god i forgot that that's an aspect
of premier is that they act like a stream so people can donate you can't donate to a video
unless you have like a channel membership thingy i i checked i checked and my my super chats were
enabled so um i've gotten a cup i've got a couple of donuts so far which is nice that's uh it makes
me happy i'd like to money i'd like to get to money you laugh but it's so true it's i laugh because
it's so true yeah um um right publishing uh quick quickly i'll note that i have been yeah the the
thing that i've been doing to get slime and punishment done is i've been going through
all the tweets i've been going through all the like twitter exchanges that me and chris had at
the time and i'm just kind of i'm just kind of arranging them into a little into a little like
narrative so like sort of interspersed in the like page notes and indexes and footnotes on every page
it notes like when chris said something or this and like my goal with that is to sort of
because some of the pages were sort of responses to things she said so my goal there is like if
you want you can read through that and you can be like oh chris said this or like chris had this
reaction to this page and some of them are funny and some of them are informative and they're like
oh that's why that next page looked like that or whatever uh so just kind of trying to like get all
that before into into a readable into a format that's readable on the page and i guess i better do
that before twitter dies uh because then all that will be lost like tears in the rain and that's no
no yeah yeah i see mary maryweather maryweather showed up for the premiere that's very kind that's
very cool i see sims he's been i should probably go over there i mean yeah sure uh sim i've seen
sims in the chat i've seen oblivion fall in the chat maryweather's in there um who knows you know
anyone anyone could show up
maybe even my hero quintin reviews if only i posted in chat hypocrite pod i'm not gonna
listen to the video while we're we're doing i'm muted you but i'm gonna watch the whole thing from
the beginning you missed and i can you missed my shout out i shouted your website out that was
like at the very beginning thank you you see i'm wearing the pin you see i'm wearing the lord of
ghost pin yes oh no i'm wrong okay someone in chat mentioned that there's a song about not being
able to beat airman and i remembered that that was true and for a second in my fever brain i thought
i think i might have worked for the guy that wrote that song but no i'm wrong that song's japanese
i did work for a guy one time who was the member of a nerd folk band that wrote songs about things
like that but they did not write that song so i was confused uh yeah i'm kind of like oh yeah
i'm kind of blown away just briefly talking about your lecture how fucking huge this whiteboard is
it's the whole yeah it's the whole wall it's the whole wall behind me oh it's a wall okay well it's
it's not a whiteboard it's uh it's a i bought like a a giant roll of paper so i pretty much
just put it on one of those yeah okay so i pretty much just like papered the whole wall behind me
yeah i bought a whiteboard but it like wasn't big enough and i was like a whiteboard that's big
enough for what i want to do would be like 200 bucks so it's by a big role it makes a lot more
sense you know what i actually i have the i have the the roll you know like with all that stuff on it
i i rolled it back up and i saved it i was thought wouldn't it be funny if i like auctioned it on
ebay or something like i had the the man lecture big old yeah yeah like i wonder if anyone would
buy it for a joke or something or buy it for real uh both buy it for real for a joke and to give me
money to give me the money um yeah let's uh let's go to questions yeah let's go to let's go to
voicemails um i gotta say questions oh my god oh wait i'm checking someone in chat just said i'm
watching this video in 360p and i was and i panicked but no i'm checking wait a minute i don't see 1440p
i see 1080p 1080p works and like that's good maybe it's because it's a live premiere maybe that's why
you can't watch it in 14 i swear i did see the 1440 was working before before i set it to premiere
when it was just unlisted so i hope i hope it didn't lose the 1440 because i i worked really hard
took a lot of extra data space to get that extra resolution oh well hope it didn't fuck up um
um yeah uh let's see speakpipe.com slash pcp voicemail okay it looks like the the last one is called
no three two one go i missed a shackle floor heckles did i did i law am i out of any memes
huh as if you were interesting at all
hey am i out of any me oh memes um yes it's like did i miss any memes you missed you missed
yeah you missed uh you missed me completing marron pans i would i would say legendary uh uh
rowdy roughhouse uh getting over it with ben at faughty challenge oh yeah yeah can i
i just i just gotta say i mean i i've never known anyone i've never i don't know anyone
that can do the things that maron does in minecraft as far as i'm concerned maron is like a is like a
minecraft wizard it's really it's really it's remarkable it's remarkable the things that he's
made in that pcb server i've not yet been um a minecraft server with as much love and dedication
poured into all of the buildings and architecture and stuff no i said i sent him a message after
where it's being like sorry it took me like literally a whole year or more to finish that
stuff that you made but like highly highly impressive highly impressive work uh yeah if you
if you didn't catch the stream basically the i'm gonna try to summarize so in the pcb minecraft
server there is a map of new los angeles city which is of course the setting of endless war
it's much of it is empty it's not all full of stuff but what's there there's a lot of stuff in
downtown and in copkill town and in the rowdy roughhouse and in some of the areas in between
and in the rowdy roughhouse there is a quest you can find someone will give you a book
that gives you a list of um marbles that you need to collect and these rowdy marbles
are based on they're based on a um a web comic that a rfck player named forks made a long time
ago for a contest and this comic was about going around the rowdy roughhouse and finding all the
rowdies and you would have to basically best them in challenges to obtain marbles so in the
rowdy roughhouse in the minecraft server you go around and find all these famous rowdies and you
beat them in in pixelmon pokemon battles and if you win or sometimes you have to solve a little
puzzle or something and if you win if you beat the challenge they give you a marble and you have to
collect them all and if you get them all you can go inside the rowdy roughhouse and inside the rowdy
roughhouse you have to do an incredibly difficult platforming challenge a la getting over it with
ben at faughty uh where you have to jump around on all this stuff to climb the tower and then once
you beat that challenge then you find uh the rowdy fucker himself munchy deep in the in the depths
of the roughhouse on top of and this is an incredibly deep cut that i could not believe
give you remember what i'm talking about you pointed out that the arena is based on that
oh yeah comic that drawing that you did in ten paces and draw of the rock concert being held on
the giant amp suspended by chains yes couldn't it's it's amazing it is amazing i when you pointed
out i was like i was like i can't believe it that's literally the deepest cut i've ever seen ever
um yeah just just uh just just fantastic i don't know uh anyway that's what you missed
because you missed the stream but we'll probably do it we'll stream again soon but i mean that
one's up if you want to that one's up in the live tab of this channel if you just want to go
check it out and see me like struggling to not fall off of pipes
i'm hearing something i hear a weird sound i i think it's coming from outside i think
they're just coming from my computer um okay the next one is called well it's a tumblr post
it's a tumblr post carnival phantasm what is this please come to brazil it's a video
okay okay it's it's zero
the entire furry fandom know this isn't happening dr billy says zoom meeting
and it's just zero yelling what am i fighting for
it's a good meme
you know i say this i say this in the lecture everyone makes this is so annoying yeah everyone
makes fun of x4 for having these terrible anime cutscenes with the horrible voice acting and it's
true they do but in my opinion in my opinion oh my god spark man helps with mining at night
in my opinion the the the story the actual story of x4 is actually pretty good it's just really
really badly told by these awful cutscenes and like the awful in-game dialogue like the terrible
localization what they were true what they were going for is pretty cool what they actually did with
it is a disaster pretty fool pretty fool yeah thank you that better than i could um next one is called
so fucked up man featuring inconsistent parentheses three two one go i'm a couple
episodes behind on the podcast watching fucking clown milk and george the cat featuring cheesy
manfredo but the in the title the featuring abbreviation is outside of the parentheses
that includes cheesy manfredo it's just cheesy manfredo alone is parenthesized that's not the
case in the next episode where the feet the ft is inside the parentheses next to never fade oh my god
what the fuck what the fuck is going on i don't i don't know i don't know what i was thinking
i think i think somebody's gonna have to be killed i alias are i i'm gonna i'm gonna pin this on you
because i'm sure this is your fault somehow um what can i say you got me
what can i say you you freak you freaking you freaking got me dude um
um all right uh next one is an imager link
no apple bloom you're not cutie fluid you're just growing up have you been hanging out in
discord's chat room again lol oh no applejack you're you're behind the times applejack don't
you know i'm sorry i'm sorry basic biology basic biology you get you get one cutie mark
and that's it all right i'm sorry that sucks though i think there should be there should be
trans cutie marks you know you gotta deal with it you know suck it up um that has always been
like a thing with the cutie marks like some people it it is just exactly what they want and for other
people it feels like a prescription that and they're not happy with it sucks for some maybe they
would like a cutie mark change maybe they could get surgery maybe they go oh god they're going
to cutie mark hormones no because they tried um well they tried to magically change no uh twilight
tried to magically give them a cutie mark and it faded away i imagined if she tried to like
magically change someone's cutie mark it would just fade back to the sjw libs tried to change the
cutie mark but basic biology just makes it makes it makes it come back makes it come back i can't
believe i can't believe my little pony is right wing uh um we're uh the sorry just the facts don't
care about your feelings uh lol okay next one is an image wait i already posted the img link
next one is called after i saw gibbs goth girl twitter pics parentheses is gib single at call
me talk 3 2 1 go
you gotta listen to the whole thing though what if there's a god
well well i'm flatter thanks thank you thank you um okay cool next one is a ninja link
oh husband you are post too much racial slur and get fired from job now we are
i don't i don't i don't thumbs up i don't i don't this is michelle this is michelle at the top
oh okay okay they're both homeless so nate post too much racial slur and we are homeless and
but he's like yeah he's like hell yeah ask ask for broader shoulders
oh dear
next one is called daniel mullins also made the hex oh um
zero seconds that's gotta be the the pony island guy right and the and the um the inscription
yeah i don't know the hex i think i've made um the logo am i did phil fish work on the hex
i don't know i don't follow him no phil fish worked on a game called hexels
okay i was i was close but i am vaguely familiar with the hex i've seen it i don't really know
what it's deal is 172 people watching my premiere i feel like that's good i feel like that's a good
number um 171 oh it's going down no it was 169 before now oh there it is again nice it's going
down baby uh next one is called did either you use the the painting in inscription
the painting um i guess not i don't know what that is i think there's a painting in the room
right like it's just looks sort of like a thing like a you can't click on it um is there
wait maybe uh i know there's like there's like that that like picture frame that shows like
a a setup of cards every time you die and there's like a different set of cards on the thing i don't
i don't know what that is referring to yes is that like the like you get a special prize if you
managed to make that board or something i did manage to do it once or twice and um what is it
i forget what you get for i did do it
oh whenever you receive a set of cards well you get the four leaf clover oh oh weird okay
i i only did it once yes you unlock the four leaf clover for the first one oh i didn't know
you could do it multiple times the second was the candlestick wait
oh this puzzle gives you your third candlestick oh wow i didn't know that
and squirrels to bees damn holy shit squirrels to bees is good i wonder if if you get squirrels
to bees does your squirrel like totem still work on them though
i guess it depends on in what order all of these things happen well if you well if you
play it and then it gets a squirrel like buff because it's a squirrel then it turns into a
bee afterwards i i think it would mean that like just the deck just has bees in it
which makes me think that like yeah you wouldn't get the squirrel buff if that's how it works i
don't know uh yeah i did i did get the clover i didn't know you could do it i didn't know there
was a point of doing it multiple times uh it's it's a hassle honestly like it's a it's a hassle
just to check it like the annoying part is just remembering to check it every time you start the
game and then you just look at and if it's easy cards like squirrel and kingfisher then you're
just like oh yeah i can do that and if it's hard cards like oh uh frickin longhorn and uh
and a beehive and like fuck that this is not gonna do it um yeah but i did but i did do it one time
next one is ben's weekly reminder play delta room chapter two okay and then oh ben's weekly reminder
not to catch up on one piece but to keep up to date with one piece i am on it friend yes i am on
the case next one is called a little uh a little song for ben three two one go
i'm in south out but i'll never touch me because i have standards that face looks mad
fucked up and those tits flap in the way here needs positive to be rented hi so is this
fat and ugly as her god i know my husband that's why ben's saying it's my only love well actually
give us better but i'm happy because she didn't post it's like she promised it's all stew and my
little comments when i'm done with ben's this ass will never be home again
i understood some of that i understood bits of it i think that's like an like an ai voice of
somebody singing definitely um i would have posted tits if because like there are other people who
were doing that and i was like uh i could do that oh because i might be at because twitter was dying
it will be dead but like i didn't think it was actually gonna die so i was a little scared i was
a little a little i mean it yeah i mean it didn't die so i guess uh lol true if it if it is like
guaranteed like countdown this is it then i'll do it but it probably wouldn't happen that's your
promise if it's guaranteed countdown shutting down yeah if it's like oh we're turn off the servers
everybody well okay unless they lie and then i'll be a look at what if elon musk is listening right
now and he and he's gonna he needs gonna lie to make that happen dang personally screw with you
he just wants to see my tits
maybe i don't i don't he could he would do who knows what he would he's what he's capable of
um next one is called not much yeah next one is called what happened three two one go
okay now i'm sure some of my voicemails were deleted censored i don't know what happened
but i had recommended blasphemous the game and a ring of pain even though uh inscription is just
the same but better it's not blasphemous is like a uh a metroidvania i think right that's the one
with the guy in like the big metal cone hat uh i don't know i think i've seen a cone hat
somewhere it's like a pixel it's like a pixel uh side scrolling castlevania and there's like a it's
like a sort of like a spanish like uh uh inquisition sort of aesthetic to it's like a guy on like a
torture helmet it's like a big metal cone i think oh wait i think i've seen a bit of that
and then what was the other one he said uh blasphemous and ring of pain i've never heard
of ring of pain yeah we've if you did send the thing we didn't see it because we we look at everything
gib i know that you know what i'm talking about did you you played a game called data scape didn't
you yes i did i did i said a guy a guy on twitter sent me uh a code for it they said they made the
game they wanted me to try it so i did and uh it was a little confusing um i was very bad at it but
i tried it it was it was like a hacking game where you go around a little well 3d realm and then you
go to little nodes and you hack the nodes yeah like typing in in a little console uh i really cool i
i saw that you yeah i saw that you had played it on my steam on my steam page it said that you had
so i yeah i assumed you got the same message that i did it was yeah i gave treat data scape a try
and it was i thought this i thought it was i thought visually it was very strong i liked
how it looked a lot the puzzle hacking did you unlock any like new commands i didn't get that far
into it i was gonna go back to it i just just said like i'll play this for like 10 minutes i played
it for maybe like 45 minutes or half an hour or something and i i hacked a couple of the uh the
blocks or the ice blocks and i got into a couple of little programs and it seemed like each time
you do that you get a little bit of like story progression you unlock a little piece of like
uh i think there's like a you have to unlock like all of a poem and i think that's part of the story
and yeah i got one that unlocked a new like uh command and i and i assumed that like the
way you unlock more and more advanced puzzles is you unlock more and more useful commands for
making your hacking stronger which was yeah i think what what i did was i did the tutorial
and then i couldn't complete it because it was a little hard to like type quickly enough um but
then i finally did the tutorial and then i was in the main game and then i walked over to this like
record player because that was was like odd i went into the record player and then it was just a
big 3d model of like a like a vinyl record player wait that was in the demo right
was it the demo or i just i remember the record the record player was the same
was also the first one that i hacked but i went over there and there was a tutorial there was a
tutorial yeah this was not in the tutorials like beyond this is in the main game or whatever it was
yeah but like i went in there and i just flew around in this like 3d zone like this void this
black void with a record player and like a bright light and i didn't know what i was supposed to
do yeah and then i didn't know how to get out and so eventually i turned the game off because i
was stuck in there yeah yeah it was a little bit unclear i i got i got in there i heard some like
narration uh i think i think eventually after the narration stopped i was like what do i do what
do i do and yeah i think you have to hit like the backspace key somewhere it tells you that the
backspace key brings you out of a program that could that could have been that could have been clearer
or i think i think when when like there's nothing left in the program i really think the game should
just deposit you out of the program or or indicate that it's time to leave um but i did i did that
with a couple of different programs and usually they each have like a little they each have a
little sort of like uh like digital like art piece of them kind of like a little 3d one of
them had a bunch of like neon eyes and like you had to walk towards the eyes and one of them had
like a big glowing thing inside of like a cage and there were some other ones uh one of them had
some text that you had to read and unlock a piece of a poem and you save the poem uh i i quit because
there was one i was trying to hack a block and i kept hearing like voice lines and the voice
lines were saying like get out of there you're under attack or something like oh they're they're
getting us like you got to do something and i was like what are you what are you talking about
and like i stopped hacking and i looked around and like nothing was going on and i was like
i don't know what this is telling me to do so i kept hacking and i kept hearing these lines saying
like you're under attack and i was like okay and then i just i just lost they were like oh they
got us and i was like i lost the game i was like well i don't know how i lost but i guess i i guess
i did uh so it was a little this bad conveyance this bad conveyance i don't know i wasn't quite
sure what was what was happening uh but there was some there was some neat stuff in it though uh i i
do like the the concept of of hacking by physically like like typing out your command in a little
command box rather than clicking around i mean i know you can click around but like the fact that
it's like an odd control scheme it was it was a really weird control scheme to get to grips with
there were like the you and o and j and l to like turn yourself 45 turn your camera yeah i think
the game would have benefited from a more traditional uh was the mouse look uh kind of setup or or
even just was the an arrow key yeah i did like i kind of liked it though i kind of liked it was
weird i i i was i i mean i i was intrigued enough that i gave it uh i put a little bit of time into
it and i unlocked i unlocked i was starting to think that the puzzles were a little bit
dumb but then i unlocked a new command i was like oh i get it i get there's like there's a
progression here you unlock new commands and it makes more and more difficult because i found one
ice block that was like you know how um you know you you put the the little pointy things on the
outside and then the one on the inside sort of like goes around to them and cancels them
well i found well i found one that had like 20 arrows on the inside so like when you used um like
a scatter or um the one that puts all the different arrows on the swarm swarm when i use swarm like
tons of arrows on the inside appear and cancel them all right away and i was like what the
fuck am i supposed to do about that you know and obviously the answer is well you know some some
commands that i can find later will probably make that manageable uh so i thought that was interesting
anyway yeah just a pcp fan sent us a pcp fan sent us their game that they put on steam and it was
called data scape and it was kind of neat and i would recommend anyone check it out check that
i'll put a link i'll put a link i'll put a link in the description
to data scape on steam it's cool it's cool um
i'm doing a shit i'm looking at my chat i'm looking at my chat and they seem befuddled
oh no did i say something stupid oh my god no please no no please no don't let me humiliate
myself on the internet oh no people are saying huh wait why no it's fine i think i'm talking about
like the database stuff and how it's like it like retroactively changes the canon that's true
i stand i stand by that okay anyway i'll stop paying attention to that next one is called fun gba
facts three two one go fun fact about gba hardware is that it actually does not have its own dedicated
sound chip that's why gba music and sounds just sound kind of bad a lot of time because it just
doesn't have the hardware to make good sound uh one famous example is castlevania harmony
dissonance the soundtrack sounds like shit but that's because uh so much of the hardware was
done to just process the graphics that they literally ran out of processing space to
make any music and they're like oh shit well what the fuck do we do here oh wait the Game Boy Advance
is also a Game Boy emulator so we'll just use the built-in Game Boy sound chip to make music
and that's kind of their work around for how they got harmony dissonance to work
and i think that's just really fucking cool that's funny that's pretty cool that's interesting they're
using a previous console's audio for a gba game that's that's interesting and it kind of explains
yeah you know it's too it's too bad because like so much of the lasting appeal of mega man has come
from its iconic soundtrack yeah and like yeah the zero games just uh i mean not gonna say it
doesn't have any great tracks but i don't know if it has anything as memorable as like wily castle
from mega man 2 or or anything like that well but what are you gonna do um next one is called
the secret to success from phantom horn at sex dot you will 3 2 1 go ben i'm uh the video is probably
gonna be out by now and i will have watched a bunch of it's premiering right now the lecture
but just wanted to say the reason your son at your video just keeps getting more and more
more views as opposed to everything else you've done is because of the thumbnail it's because
you're vaping in it vape more vape into your thumbnails that's gonna make it work it's you
holding up your finger being like hold on hold on the pipe the pipe i had the pipe back that's
what made the video that's what it was you know that's that's as good that's as good a theory as
as any that i've heard so i mean yeah it is a pretty good pose with the pipe it is a good pose
like oh you know let me tell you all about christian that is pretty good yeah i definitely
was a mistake to quit vaping definitely need to pick that back up again