Hello everyone, and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast with me, your host, while the best
guy ever is away on a tiny island off the coast of Hawaii having a hand-to-hand battle
with a bread garlic house, just like the end of Metal Gear Solid 5.
These people like who's having a hand-to-hand hand job if you ask me.
Yeah, yeah.
As in a handshake, they're shaking each other's hands with their penises instead of their hands.
Okay, but let's talk about that. Who do you think, whose grip do you think is gonna come out on top in that...
Hey everybody, reporting in from the island of Jamaica, where I am originally from. It's me.
I fucked this up.
Is this the African Undertaler? Has he returned?
Bread, have you joined the podcast at last? Bread, did our plan to depose Nate and put you at the top of the poll?
No?
The plan was a failure. I'm Nate. I consumed Brad. I'm twice as strong as I've ever been.
I plan for this contingency as well. It's fine. Let's just continue.
I've absorbed his incredible professionalism, as you can see, to still be here despite being on vacation while so many of our number are unbelievably lazy embarrassments of human beings.
Total ghosts. Just no sense of common decency or decorum. I would say.
They've gone ghost and they're not coming back and that's just how I like it.
Yeah, it's sad.
Forgive the echo. Forgive the lower mic quality. I'm using a lowly moids, blue yeti, round ass microphone.
Instead of my pristine recording environment.
What is it?
It's... well, it is probably...
I got my snowball ice, which I think is just a snowball but white, so pretty good.
I don't know. Blue microphones. Wait, snowball ice. Oh, it is a snowball ice.
You got a snowball ice too, my dude?
That's what it says on it, yeah. This is Michelle's. She asked to use my microphone years ago and I just beat the shit out of her for daring to use my property.
I beat the shit out of Econ and stole this one from him, so birds of a feather.
He's not using it to make any videos or anything.
We each had to kick an Asian's ass to get our snowball ice. Birds of a feather.
Oh, it feels good.
So how's your guys week been? How are you feeling? How's it going for you?
Well, I like Gib and now an Islander permanently and it feels good.
Gib, do you identify with being an Islander like Sora from Kingdom Hearts because you live on a big Island? Or is it too big?
I can't believe they took Sora, a native Islander, a member of the native Islander population and whitewashed him when they cast Haley Joel Osment in Kingdom Hearts.
I mean, if I travel more around Britland, maybe, I usually just go from here to London and then to other cities depending on if I need to be there, but usually I don't go to the seaside.
Like the old days when mother and father, they get us all in the car and drive down to the beach and it would be the beach and then we'd look at it and it's okay.
You know, I wonder, this island is obviously, I mean, I'm on Oahu, that's like the main populated island in the Hawaiian Islands where Honolulu is and stuff.
And they talk about how people can get like a little stir crazy after a while living here and like it is pretty small.
Like you can easily drive around the whole thing in a couple hours, but if I were to think, I'm just, I'm kind of inserting my normal day-to-day life in Cincinnati on top of this place.
I like travel maybe like two miles, maybe three, like in a day.
I think you'd probably not make much difference in terms of my daily life living on like a little island versus anywhere else.
Just because, I don't know, like everything I do is on a computer.
The most thing I do drive is like to take Michelle to work and I don't know, go to the store, which is across state lines, I guess.
Although, I guess that across, like, because I live in the Ohio River and stuff.
You cross state lines to take Michelle to work.
Do you just happen to live really close to the border?
Yeah, Cincinnati is right on the Kentucky border.
It's like the Ohio River is right there and across that is Kentucky.
So I go do my shopping at like the nice store in Kentucky in like Newport, Kentucky or something.
Didn't know that.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, Southwest Ohio.
Do you, is there a situation where like, okay, all the fucking sovereign stator anarcho-capitalist libertarians live in New Hampshire because they have like low taxes
and like people will like, people here like cross the border to New Hampshire to buy like cigarettes and booze and stuff.
To buy their beautiful flavored vapes bags of paradise over there.
It's true, true.
Hey, did you get your flavored vapes yet?
I did, it just arrived like two days ago.
Thank God.
Thank you.
But anyway, I was wondering if there's like a similar situation with like Cincinnati, Kentucky.
So we better, we better cross the border to get like, I don't know, illegal fireworks or whatever because they're legal over there, but not over here.
Ohio is like very, I guess the word is liberal.
Like they, there are very open laws and like gun open carry stuff is all good to go in Ohio.
Although, I don't know, me and Michelle were like going to do some gun shooting just for fun the other day.
So we went to a gun store.
This is a couple months ago, I guess, but like we, we didn't follow up.
We're going to do it one of these days.
But like they said, they actually are like getting a little restrictive.
So like I did, based on what like the guy selling stuff was saying there, it like does seem like things are a little bit more constrictive.
So like absolutely people like in Cincinnati, it's like, you know, a 10 minute drive and you're in a different state.
And I'm probably, I mean, I'm just judging based on stereotypes and nothing else.
I assume Kentucky is like more liberal than, than other states.
Because Ohio's like it's where Ohio is technically in the Eastern standard time block.
And it's like the most Western state that's still Eastern standard time.
So when I moved like what felt like across into fucking eternity from my parents, like in Massachusetts and stuff, I'm still in the same time zone.
But the whole culture is like pervaded with like Southern influence and stuff.
So I don't know.
Yeah, Kentucky and all that.
There is a culture shock just like from like a short drive across the border.
Like suddenly you're hearing a lot more accents.
You know, you hear a lot of accents in Ohio already.
But of course, it's the reality that I live on the internet and rarely interact with other human beings in real life.
So, you know, Michelle probably sees way more than that doing the real world.
And I was going to say that like the thing about here, like, so Michelle's dad was in the military.
So he has all these awesome military benefits.
And like the place we live now like used to be a military combat, whatever, it's public now.
But like the point is that like we live like right across from the ocean.
And like Diamond Head is this giant mountain that's the edge of a crater.
It's like a famous Hawaiian landmark on Oahu.
You can see that from...
Hang on, I'm going to stand up.
I'm going to stand up and pull the curtain.
And I can see Diamond Head out the window.
Hey, no attention to these...
Did you go mind those fucking things?
Yeah.
It's right that end like the beach is there and like this morning for example.
Little Diamond Helmahamon.
I tweeted about it. I called it Diamond Back like an idiot and looked like a fucking fool to everyone.
That's pretty rough.
That's incorrect.
I went down to the beach this morning as I've done many times.
As the sun was rising from like six to seven and I just did yoga on the beach for a while.
And it was, that's still going on.
Yep.
And it was a great time.
That's so nice for you.
It was really nice for me to do that.
That's so fantastic.
So cool. So unlistening.
I know I said this before, but like I tried men's yoga.
It's too hard. It's too shitty.
You got to do the girl version.
It literally makes me want to kill myself.
You do the girl version because it's easier.
Girl yoga is a thousand times better.
Let's follow these fucking red pill.
Men's rights activists.
That's the one thing that I really think we should adhere very closely to gender stereotypes on.
And I don't really support what you're doing.
Which brand of yoga you ascribe to?
No. You want the gay, non-mistage stuff.
I don't think that, frankly Nate, I don't think that decision is valid of you.
That's fair.
That's well.
Try again.
Every time, I will, Ben.
I go to the gym and I lift weights there and I come home and I do my pussy yoga shit.
Because I'm there for flexibility, right?
I'm there for getting the knots out.
So that's what I'm doing.
I go to the gym, I lift weights, I go home, I put it down.
I stole it.
Yeah, I carry them home.
It's a cyclical operation.
I don't know.
Just this general beach activities and stuff.
I've been working, been a little concerned about these.
I've been sending emails once in a while about all the channels being stolen.
I have given up hope. We're doomed.
I'm convinced we're fucked, yes.
Really?
After 16 or 17 days now.
There was another guy.
I mean, Mars Reviews who also had his channel taken and they just fucking deleted his whole channel.
I'm convinced that that's gonna happen to us.
Okay, that could happen.
But even if it gets deleted, it can come back.
YouTube has the authority to restore all deleted videos.
And even I think set back the clock if they get fucked with to some previous state.
So I've got some hope.
And there's people out there who have...
Panda Popolin?
Panda Popolin, I think, in the Discord.
Panda Popolin, I think that's him, has downloaded every video on every channel.
Which is probably, I mean, I don't have every canton video, did you?
To edit all those, I don't have every PCP video.
Me and Tfap.
I did and then Tfap told me he also did have every Tbap video downloaded.
There's probably a couple hidden ones that I got that he probably wasn't able to.
But the Tbap channel is back.
I really don't want to have to make a new channel and lose all the comments and lose all the views and lose all that history.
But I mean, yes, we can re-upload those and probably others, so...
Well, you know, you could go to the videos as they appear still
and copy-paste the comments into a document just so that you have them.
Well, yeah, but nobody would see that.
I don't really know for myself that much.
No, but if there's a comment from, I don't know, 2014 me
and it's like, oh, that's what I said back then.
That's how I talked.
That would be a sort of thing.
You just want to be able to read it again.
That's so fucking hard.
You could then...
It's a lot of work.
I mean, if you really care about keeping the history, that's one of the ways to do it.
I suppose that's true.
It's slightly unrelated, but one of the things that's been happening on BestieBoy
is that for whatever reason, the hackers have just decided,
maybe just to get more views, to get more ad revenue on the channel or whatever,
I don't know, whatever it is,
they've been publishing my unlisted BGE monthly cast on...
Fair enough, I guess, just to get as many views as possible.
Love that, love that.
The worst thing about that is people thinking that you have it back and they don't get it.
Oh, yeah.
They just sort of like, oh, it's all fine now.
I take a little bit of comfort in that my...
Oh, I've got another ominous thing to say on that front,
but I don't know exactly which channel these are.
I was going to say that the newest BGE monthly cast is on one of the other little zero sub channels
I had just for whatever test upload purposes or whatever.
So that exists on there, if you're a patron or whatever, you can find it through the Patreon.
But like, I'll say this, you know I've been working on some projects for a thousand years?
There are videos that are pieces of unfinished projects on all number of channels
that I'll just, like the real terror for me, the real fear of God,
is in those unfinished projects getting published and people seeing what I've been up to in the unfinished state.
So like the Ghost in the Shell scene where you are running naked through the streets,
like that scene that you already filmed.
Exactly.
That I was planning, when I released it, I was also planning to kill myself in real life
and that was going to be like a really cool synchronicity thing.
But I'll have to do it after it comes out and that'll be a real bummer for me.
You know?
That sucks.
That's fucked up.
That video where I planned the release, the gender reveal of my son,
Oh shit, I just spoiled it, goddammit.
Well, you know, all stuff like that.
And the current video I'm editing, you know, that was like, it's like mostly done
and I had it like large, I'm pretty sure I put these on other channels,
but they might be on there.
And oh my god, if they publish those, I will just be devastated
and I just hope that they don't.
Well.
I don't know.
They might, based on this, they might.
Just delete them, guys.
Brad, dude, listening, please delete those videos.
Please.
Just leave them alone.
Brad, listen, you're a reasonable man.
We can negotiate this.
The good news is many of those are copyright claimed.
Like a lot of the reason to upload was to test copyright claim stuff
and like everything there generally gets claimed.
So hopefully they'll be like, well, there's nothing in here anyway.
I went to the Twitter.
I was on the Procrastinators Twitter at TPCrastinators
and I clicked the channel link and it was like this channel does not exist
and I was like, oh my god, it's happening, but no, it's just because they changed the channel name.
Thanks guys.
Oh, I have one other, this is a big piece of news, everybody.
I'm in a liberal hellscape out here.
It's a true nightmare because in this God for Steak and State of Hawaii,
where, you know, up is down and left is right, gay is straight, etc.
It is the rainbow state after all.
Like straws.
Straws are like illegal or at least like heavily taxed or something.
Do you have to pay for ones?
They sell the paper ones, they've got all kinds of stuff.
That's so gross.
Okay, but there's one, I mean, this is kind of a silver lining I suppose.
We went this morning and we had French toast and Bloody Marys for breakfast
at a local eatery, which was wonderful.
But as straws in the Bloody Marys, I'll upload a picture of this,
they have a very long cylindrical piece of like rigatoni pasta or something like that.
You know what?
That makes sense to me.
I think that sounds okay.
For a Bloody Mary, for a Bloody Mary.
It's a little starchy.
It's a tomato drink and you're drinking it through a piece of pasta?
Yeah, I totally get it.
It's not bad.
Here, I just posted in the gross disgusting audio links.
Look at that, look at that.
It's a beautiful drink obviously.
A piece of pasta.
It's a ragatoni.
It looks nice.
Is that cucumber or lime or what is that?
These are actually pickles.
Oh, okay, okay, pickles.
Gotcha.
It looks pretty good.
Once you go right, you'll feel all right.
And these lefty cucks.
Yeah, that's a great segue into what I wanted to talk about.
But I might go on for a while.
I might have to rant and rave for a while.
Speaking of lefty cucks, you guys have been following the primaries this week.
You guys have been following the IoCoxys.
It's pretty good.
It's pretty cool.
Like Twitter knowledge, Twitter level knowledge of that.
What is it?
Please explain.
Okay.
Let me try and back up and be as succinct as possible and trying to explain what's going
on with the United States presidential elections this cycle.
Okay, so do you guys know what the IoCoxys are?
To choose the representative for the party.
But the thing is, it is not a primary vote.
It is a caucus.
And what that means is people have to gather up in a fucking gyms across the state and
literally...
And lift weights to decide who the president is.
No, they have to move around into groups and gather into crowds to vote for their guy.
Okay, before the primary, before the caucus, there was a...
Wait, vote as in they cuss a vote or people count the crowds?
They basically count the crowds.
But then if someone doesn't hit 15% of the crowd, they're deemed unviable and they say,
okay, this candidate's out.
You guys can realign yourselves if you want to.
And those people can go either way.
A lot of people in the Yang crowd were disappointed that Yang was not viable and they went over
to...
A lot of them went over to Sanders.
Surprisingly, a lot of Biden crowds were not viable and those people probably went and
shot themselves or whatever.
Yeah, probably.
Okay, that's not even...
It's really complicated.
There's these two alignments.
You move around in physical crowds.
They count the heads.
They total them up.
There's some arcane mathematics to determine something called SDEs, which are state delegate
somethings.
And then those state delegates go from each precinct to...
They each go to some fucking shadowy core place.
And those SDEs all convene and cast the vote that's been decided for them.
And that determines how many delegates each candidate gets, right?
So it's like...
You think the fucking primary...
You think that the electoral college is fucked up and too complicated.
The caucus system is way worse, right?
It's so bizarre.
I'm wondering if the caucus...
Still don't get it.
How does the app tie in if they're caucusing in person?
The app.
Okay.
So this caucus happens.
They do their fucking shit.
They record the results.
The DNC, the people running it, they're given this app to report the results to the DNC.
And the app fails.
The app just completely fails.
Last time, it took them like two hours to have like most of the votes tallied.
This time, it took them three fucking days.
It worked on Excel spreadsheet.
Yeah, a fucking pencil could have done it.
So, all right.
So there's this huge...
Now, I'm sitting there.
It's caucus night.
I'm watching the results roll in.
I'm sitting there for hours and hours just waiting for it to roll in.
And I see...
Here's my...
I see like...
Oh, a couple...
If there's like 1% reporting in and it's like...
Oh, it looks like Sanders in the lead.
Buttigieg is second.
Wow.
Didn't expect Buttigieg to be second.
He was kind of trailing.
And then Moore comes in.
It's like 1.8% results in.
And it's like, oh, Buttigieg is in the lead.
Like what?
That's kind of weird.
But it's like, okay, this is 1%.
This is not representative.
And then like Buttigieg comes out ahead, but then like we're less than 2%.
And like they tally up again and Sanders takes the lead again.
And I'm like, okay.
And then the results go dark, right?
Like everything just disappears after Sanders comes back ahead.
And so like days later, they start reporting again.
And I'm watching the fucking...
I'm watching the official tally on the New York Times website.
And again, it's like...
They're like 62%, 71%, like 80%.
And again, like Buttigieg in the lead and like Sanders behind,
but like every time they report more results,
it's like creeping closer and closer.
They get to like 99% or they get to like the last like 3%.
Right?
It's like 97.
And it's like, oh, Buttigieg like a whole like 1% ahead, right?
A pretty narrow, it's like 1% ahead.
Then they report like one more percent and it closes entirely.
Sanders 0.1% behind.
Like so closely tied that it doesn't even matter,
but they only reported just enough to not put Sanders in the lead.
And then the fucking DNC chair, Tom Perez,
he's like, you know what, actually fuck this.
We're recanvassing the whole state.
Like right at that very moment.
In the places where, by the way,
the places where delegates were like largely unreported
were like Sanders heavy districts like Des Moines.
So wait, wait, wait, one more thing, one more thing.
And then like just yesterday, like the DNC puts out a notice
that's like, okay, yeah, we're recanvassing the state.
We're like recounting, but we're not going to change the results.
Like whatever the wrong results are we got,
we're just going to go with it.
We're going to recount to see what we did wrong,
but we're not going to fix the results.
I said to honor the integrity of the election.
How is there integrity if you mess the entire thing up?
That just makes sense.
There's like graph, I got a graph here.
Someone in my, on Twitter, someone posted this fucking image
showing how like, okay, because like independent sources
totaled up like how many errors there are in the caucus
and like which candidates they favor.
So I just, I just, yeah.
Oh boy.
Guess what this, guess what the takeaway here is.
Wait.
I bet our boy, the mayor is going to be looking real.
So look at the errors.
Once to the right are detrimental.
Once to the left are positive.
So overwhelmingly the errors in the calculations
disadvantage Bernie and advantaged Buttigieg.
Ben, it's a statistical fluke.
I know, I know.
I better take my fucking tinfoil hat off, right?
I'm just being one of a conspiratorial Bernie bro.
This is a fucking Jeffrey Epstein level.
Like obviously, like I already know, I've heard that like Pete
is like somewhat involved with the app that was made.
Pete is CIA.
And yes, and that's not even the half of it because the app
that failed that allowed for so much gross incompetence
and obviously corruption to take place.
Pete Buttigieg funded it.
The app is called Shadow Incorporated,
or the company is called Shadow Incorporated.
The CEO is a Buttigieg guy.
Her husband is like literally works for Pete.
So this is cool.
Okay.
And you know what?
That's fine.
One rigged primary.
Whatever.
It's no big deal.
But the real fucking tragedy here is that they did it.
They released the data in such a way.
Like they timed everything perfectly so that like
they never have to say Sanders is in the lead.
CNN can fucking spin it to say,
oh Buttigieg maintains narrow lead going into the New Hampshire primaries.
So like they announce a bit of Sanders
and then immediately Pete is, you know,
more data to show that Pete's in the lead.
So there's no like new cycle where Sanders could be at the time.
Yes.
With 0% data reported,
Pete goes on Twitter and says,
thank you everyone for this victory in Iowa.
Declare's victory without any fucking data.
You know, I listened to some of those things.
I thought that because like everybody went on to like announce victory.
Bernie did it later.
Bernie did it later after the votes were tapped.
Bernie declared victory because he did,
he did win the popular vote by 6,000 votes.
Right.
And they have like an equal,
they have an equal amount of delegates, I think.
And if they don't, like it's,
it's like because of 0.1%.
It's like totally stupid.
I mean, whatever.
If you're Bernie at this point.
What the fuck?
Okay.
So this all happens.
Bernie gets rat fucked by the DNC.
Pete is CIA.
Pete, Wall Street Pete is a fucking cheat.
That's what's going on.
And you know what?
It's looking like it worked.
It's looking like controlling the narrative like this has worked
and Pete is surging in New Hampshire now
where Sanders was the favorite to win.
So, yeah, really.
Wow.
He can't be Bernie in New Hampshire.
Okay.
I don't know.
Polls conflict.
Polls have been showing conflicting things.
Like at worst,
polls have shown that Pete is like close to Sanders.
Some still show Sanders with a substantial lead.
Apparently this morning,
Pete had like the biggest turnout for his like rally
because they're all doing rallies today.
Supposedly, according to social media.
What the fuck?
Pete got the biggest turnout.
Okay.
So this has got me,
this has been like the worst week of my entire life.
This is a fucking nightmare, right?
I don't like Pete.
Pete's bad.
And I was mad about it.
And I was thinking like, man, this is shaking.
I was all for vote blue no matter who.
Like I love Bernie,
but I was still going to swallow my pride
and vote Hillary or whatever.
And then this happens and I'm like,
they're just cheating.
Like they're just cheating.
And I'm really mad.
They literally cheated provably last time.
For sure.
Yeah.
And once it's the first fucking,
not even a primary, a caucus,
and like we're already fucking cheating.
It's obvious,
but like,
but fucking moms at home don't,
don't follow Twitter.
They're not looking up graphs like this, right?
They're just like CNN says,
Oh yeah, wow,
Pete narrowly beat Bernie and they,
and they slurped their fucking wine on their couch
as their husband fucking fucks the secretary.
And they're, and they're just like, yeah, he's,
Oh, what a nice young gay man.
You know, like, like,
Oh yeah.
He looks like a politician.
Doesn't he?
Yes.
So, so I was worried about that.
But like then this morning,
or then yesterday,
I get fucking scared, right?
I get fucking scared.
I didn't even know this about Pete.
Apparently Pete wants mandatory military service
for every kid in America.
Like in the Boy Scouts?
No, like you serve in the military for a year
when you graduate high school.
Like Israel or something.
It's just like, yes, like Israel.
Okay.
Yes.
So, um, yeah.
I don't like that.
It's like we,
it's like we,
we want to establish an expectation for mandatory service.
Um, the, I didn't,
I didn't know this.
I see this and I'm like, oh my God.
Maybe you know community service,
you know, you'd pick up some trash in the weekend,
a little.
No.
Even that, I obviously.
Military means military.
I mean,
it's,
it could just be an office job,
but it's still like in the realm of things you wouldn't want.
I certainly agree.
Like mandatory anything.
Yeah.
Let me, I mean, let me find the,
let me try and find the graphic.
Sure, sure.
Here it is.
Pete's vision.
Let's, let's, let's read about.
I can't wait to see our future president's vision personally.
I'm looking forward to it.
Oh boy.
Um, hold on.
Sorry, I gotta, uh, I don't mean read,
read this and judge for yourself.
I guess.
Oh, our, our,
this is from his website.
It looks like.
Yep.
Our intention is for this proposal to create a pathway towards
a universal national expectation of service
for all four million high school graduates every year,
such that the first question asked out of every college
freshman or new hire is where did you serve a new generation
of American youth bound by mutual service and sacrifice,
aware of the common values that bind all Americans,
uh, influenced by the experience of da, da, da, da, da.
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Yeah.
Uh, hmm.
Okay.
And, and this is apparently from a.
Apparently you have to sign up for his email list to even get to
this part of his website.
Let's see.
So.
Okay.
So this, so this is where we're at people.
This is where we're at.
We've got this fucking rat, this little fucking rat fucker,
uh, surging in the polls because the media,
I guess.
Because he did his way.
So much.
Yeah.
Um, and because.
We need Bloomberg to save us honestly.
Bloomberg, come in here.
Just, you know, get Pete out of here.
Let's go.
I mean, it's, it's exactly the same sort of stuff that happened
in the, in the fucking Jeremy Corbyn.
Yeah.
The most recent election.
Really?
Yeah.
Where he lost a lot because everyone like piled on as soon as
the election had started.
It was all about shitting on Jeremy Corbyn as much as in as hard as possible
constantly and not shitting on the opposition quite as much.
And you know, the media does what the media does.
They get, they do what they're told by whoever's got the power.
And it's like, I mean Jeremy Corbyn, like arguably wouldn't have been that great
a leader, but it, the demonstrably like, you know, he was demonized beyond what he
was actually like.
They called him like anti-Semitic and stuff, right?
Yeah.
It's, it's like, it's all about when the election happens, it's all about lying
as hard as you can, as loudly as you can for just long enough for people who don't
actually pay attention that much to get some sort of idea in their heads.
And then when they go to the polls, you, you win, you know.
Hell yeah.
That's just, that's how it is.
If it wasn't for the graph that you posted, Ben, I mean, okay, this is all still
in theory, explainable simply by incompetence.
Nate, sure.
It's possible.
Look at that, look at the fucking, look at them.
I mean, the difference.
I mean, you're, you're not wrong.
You're not the, the.
In theory.
Yeah, Nate.
In theory, fucking, uh, remember when like Dr. Manhattan is like holding up the ring
and he's like, I've yearning to see a quantum event wherein like a molecule spontaneously
turns into gold.
In theory, that's explainable by a random chance.
I guess you're right.
Okay.
Real quick.
At the bottom, I see this negative two on the left to the three on the bottom.
What, what are those numbers indicate?
I see SD.
That is, that is S.
Okay.
You got your, you got your people show up to vote.
Right.
With their, where they stand, like which group they stand in.
And then they get, they realign into like a new, like grouping for where they're going
to vote.
Um, those numbers are tallied and through some sort of mathematics that I don't know what
it is.
Oh.
A number is calc, the SDEs are calculated.
Okay.
And that is basically how many like state internal delegate, the SDEs.
I don't know what SDU stands for, but it's like the state internal delegates that are
going to like get basically how many points from that precinct they win based on the vote.
And then those points gets, get like all added together from all precincts.
And then those point totals are again used in some weird math that I don't understand
to determine how many final, like actual state delegates go to the primary vote.
Understand?
Okay.
I think so.
I thought at the bottom that would have been like.
SDE is like an intermediary calculation between actual vote and like, and like delegates
assigned.
When I, when I looked at the bottom, I saw numbers.
So like the larger, um, areas in a state or whatever to account for like the differences
in size or like the ruralness.
Yeah.
Like, like how, like, like the Des Moines precincts got like way more SDEs because they're
like much more heavily populated.
Sure.
So as you, so as you can see, because of this, and the race was incredible, remember there
was like a 0.1% difference.
Uh, Buttigieg.
So, so he basically should have won.
I mean, if there wasn't massive incompetence, clearly.
This is the takeaway.
Buttigieg gained more than two, like two and change whole SDEs and Bernie lost almost three.
I have one other question about this.
I don't know if this is true or not.
I heard that Buttigieg had basically gone all in on Iowa.
So it was expected that he would perform well even though nationally he's doing that well
because he's specifically focused in Iowa with the hope of like getting some snowball effect.
I guess it worked.
He, I mean, by any metric he did outperform.
Like he was not like the polls I was seeing had him getting like 15%.
It was like the polls I was seeing were like Warren and Biden, sorry, Sanders and Biden
tied for front and then like Warren and Pete like pretty like trailing pretty far behind
in third place.
Uh, I don't think anyone expected because he did even, even with a knot, if you, if you,
if we fixed all these errors, he's definitely like in a strong second place, which is really bad
and upsetting on it.
Like even that alone would be cause for alarm.
Um, no, the fact that they cheated to put him over the edge and be able to say, oh, Pete
won Iowa.
Uh, that's, that's a problem.
Anyway, I'm seeing that headline.
I'm, yeah, I'm seeing, that's, that's all they want.
That's all they want.
And then I'm seeing, I'm seeing them trending on Twitter.
I'm seeing this like, oh, wow.
Okay.
People this morning are saying huge crowd for Pete at his rally this morning.
However, at the like, they had an event last night where like all the candidates came out
on stage and talked and while Pete was out, the crowd started chanting wall street, Pete,
wall street, Pete, wall street, Pete, um, which is great and all.
Um, oh, and then, uh, Trump, uh, Trump didn't get impeached.
Oh, well, no, who could have seen, who could have seen that coming?
Did you see, uh, Nancy Pelosi ripping up the speech?
Tear up the paper.
Yeah.
I don't know.
People are mad.
Who cares?
Whatever.
She's mad.
Oh, who's, it's fine.
Well, okay.
I'll give my, uh, uh, people be, uh, fucking people on Twitter.
Oh, who's that one, that one fucking pundit is like, that is like, it was like, this is,
this is the most, this is the most disgraceful event that's ever been seen in Congress.
And it's like somewhat, then someone replied like some, like some senator or congressman
like literally like physically beat the shit out of another one.
I heard about that.
For like saying slavery was bad.
There was like emotional abolish slavery and a man, he got tamed nearly to death by his
fellow senators on the floor of the Senate like 150 years ago or something.
But this, this, this is just beyond the fuck.
Okay.
Uh, Trump, Trumpites and conservatives are such fucking coward snowflakes that they cry
and whine about tearing up some paper.
But also fuck Nancy Pelosi.
She, this is like bullshit performative politics and means nothing.
Oh yeah.
Sleigh queen.
Sleigh.
Yeah, it's, yeah.
I saw, I saw, I saw Sean tweet, Sean tweeted like Nancy Pelosi will vote for Trump's third
term, but everyone will applaud because she'll give him the finger while she like Ollie's
out on a skateboard or something.
Well, I was like, yeah, that's about right.
I mean, on the whole subject of this whole thing, I mean, obviously the line from Trump
and his allies is going to be like, I mean, what's the real embarrassment here?
Like tearing up or what's the real disgrace?
You know, uh, fucking like impeaching the presidents over, you know, things that arguably
they think didn't, at the very least they knew nothing would come of it.
They got Mitt Romney's vote, bro.
We did it.
We got bipartisanship.
Yeah, but they were, they were never going to, they were never going to, man, it's, it's
fucking wild how it's just like Democrats.
It, it, except for like Mitt Rom, except for Mitt Romney, who went pro impeach and Tulsi
Gabbard, who just, who should have voted impeach, but for some reason declined to.
Um, they, it was completely partisan.
Like every Democrat voted impeach, every Republican voted not in both fucking houses.
It's fucking wild.
Yeah.
So yeah, it was, it was obviously never going to work and it was a waste of time and it's
just emboldened Trump's support and they go, ha, ha, ha, four more years.
Ha, ha, he can, he's so fucking powerful.
Oh, fucking suck my dick, Daddy Trump.
It's mostly just sad that, I don't know, things are in that way, but whatever.
I haven't said that a million times.
I guess we'll get over it eventually.
I don't know.
Um, well, it's a nightmare.
Um, what else are they going to say?
Oh yeah.
How do you think this bodes for the Democrats election coming up, Ben?
What do you think?
It's real.
It's real bad.
Um, I mean, even if we got, even if Pete were the nominee, uh, he wouldn't win.
Sanders is the only one who might win.
And even him, like, even him, I'm not like, I'm not like a hundred percent sure.
If it came down to Sanders v.
Trump, it might be a coin toss.
Um, oh God.
Anyway, I'm in physical pain.
I'm literally in physical pain, like every day, um, because I'm so fucking worried about,
about it.
I'm like following it constantly.
I can't sleep.
I can't eat, uh, my back hurts.
Um.
When's New Hampshire?
That's the next one, right?
New Hampshire.
When's that?
Well, listener, by the time you hear this, it will have already happened because it's on
Tuesday and, um, there will probably be a whole new cycle of rat fuckery and, uh, cowardice,
uh, from the DNC.
And, uh, uh, these fucking drooling MAGA fucks will, uh, be, will just, will clap their hands
like seals and bleed, and, uh, it'll be fucking amazing.
Speaking of seals, uh, monk seals are extremely protected, they're an endangered species in
Hawaii.
I just got a sick pick with one on the beach this morning.
Wow, man.
You gotta check this out, man.
You gotta see this.
That's so great for you.
It's really good.
I'm so, I'm so glad for your seal picture.
Oh, there was also a dog wearing goggles?
What?
No.
Wow.
Yeah, dude.
Cool.
I'm gonna turn him into the ocean.
You know, we thought we might be going skydiving or something sick like that.
Turns out, we asked the guy, or Michelle did.
He's just, uh, uh, German Shepherds, which he was, uh, are sensitive to UV light.
So he just wears these cool goggles, uh, like a Digimon main character, uh, to protect
his eyes from UV light.
You don't even get very close to him.
Look at that fucking love.
See that sign?
See that sign right there?
You are not allowed to, by state law, get any closer to those fucking seals, uh, than
you are there.
I'm like, that's not gonna work.
Well, really, you're not allowed to touch him.
You're not allowed to touch him.
But these, okay, I'm gonna call them these island autists, get so up in their fucking
shit about, don't touch the turtles.
Don't touch the seals.
Uh, I'm not gonna touch it.
I'm just gonna pet it.
I'm just gonna give him a little pet, and he's gonna love it.
It's gonna be sick.
He's gonna thank me.
Um, so don't, don't freak out.
But, uh, yeah, he's snoozing.
We went to, uh, this little island out, uh, Chinaman's Hat.
Uh, yep, it's called Chinaman's Hat, is the name of this little island.
That's, that's that, like, black thing sticking out there?
Uh, no, no, no.
This is, uh, it's on the north, this is facing the south side.
It's on the north side of the island, I think.
Uh, we, we got kayaks yesterday.
We paddled out, and when we got out to that island, first of all, we nearly died on the
way back because the winds picked up to an insane degree, and, uh, let me, it was one,
one of our group fell over in their kayaks and were being pushed towards the rocks, and
like, one of our, like, the guides had to jump out of his canoe, swim over and save them
like dying, and he came back with, like, a huge fucking bloody mass on his leg because
he took the hit to, like, save him from the rocks.
It was fucked up.
Um, but it was also awesome, uh, and I loved it, and it was totally cool.
But on the beach, on Chinaman's Hat, there was just a big old seal just hanging out on
there, and I got way closer.
I was probably, like, I don't know, maybe 10 feet away, but you're not allowed to touch
him.
Everyone gets way in your case about it, but, uh, he was cool.
He was cool.
Natives do, or tourists do?
Well, I mean natives, which I understand.
It's, uh, they're, they're very into, uh, conserve, uh, what are the conservationism?
Fucking idiots trying to conserve their precious wildlife.
It is embarrassing, Frank.
Get over it.
There's chickens that wander around everywhere here, and I think they're also protected.
Although I know they're delicious.
So, uh, it's my time.
I'm not protected forever.
Um, oh, one, one last thing.
I wake up today.
I wake up to say, and I see hashtag AntifaTerrorist trending on Twitter because, uh, I guess
the KKK are having a rally in Portland or something, and, uh, and, yeah, and Antifa's
there, and, uh, fucking, and of course, fucking Andy Ngo.
Andy fucking Ngo is there to post some, like, yeah, to post some, like, some, like, totally
ambiguous footage that he claims is like, oh, Antifa pushes a woman in front of a car,
and, like, it doesn't even really look like it, but, like, he says it, so I guess it's
better.
Guys, forget Antifa.
We gotta talk about the real scourge.
I saw a video this morning of furries bashing, I believe it was a Chrysler vehicle, apropos
of nothing as far as I can tell.
Not, not Chrysler.
Not Chrysler.
Not one of our good American companies.
I heard something, like, animal.
Are they, are they American?
I don't know.
I think they are.
They were just chanting, like, something about, like, animal testing.
I don't know.
Just Chrysler, do animal testing?
I'm unaware, but they're the real scourge.
I mean, they were just in full fursuit, two guys bashing a car.
Did they have, like, like, claw, like, weapons in their paws?
No, they were just holding a baseball bat in their, in their disgustingly human-like hands,
which was a problem, though.
Oh, not human hands.
No, no commitment.
You gotta at least, like, you know, gaffer tape the bat to the paws as we get around.
Hold it in your mouth and swing it, like, like Sora in the Lion King order.
Like Zorlo.
Oh, speaking of Sora, I'm definitely going to do a picture where I pose, like, like,
Sora from Kingdom Hearts 2, the title screen.
We're standing in the water with a popsicle in his mouth.
Look for that on my Instagram soon, instagram.com, slash bestestguyever.
I'm thinking about, I want to commit to this.
I want to mod a copy of Kingdom Hearts 2.
I plan an emulator where I use whatever image I produce in this way as the title screen.
Oh, I love Kingdom Hearts.
Wait.
Oh, it's good.
I don't understand the plan.
Here, I'll show you.
To take a picture, doing the pose, and then put that in the game.
So when he plays the game, he sees himself and he says, oh.
I'll go, ooh, it's me.
And then I can distribute this as, like, you know, the good version of Kingdom Hearts 2.
You know, the vastly improved.
I'll be an elite modder, just like Econ.
It'll be great.
I bet I could make that happen.
I don't know stuff.
You know, speaking back on, like, the whole lefty stuff.
I have been.
Antifa's the good guys, people.
Antifa is the good guys.
Figure it out.
Yes.
I mean, I have been watching a lot of specific bread tube, a philosophy tube, and contrapoints.
I've just been, like, playing Dark Souls and then having that on in the background and
learning all about these things, such as, I forget all of them.
But Antifa was one of the things that they talked about.
They talked about how Antifa, I mean.
Was it a contrapoints video?
Yeah.
It was a philosophy tube.
Okay.
But like the, you know.
Let's talk about it.
Please, let's talk about it.
I mean, I've watched so many of these videos that they sort of bled together and I can't,
like, pull specific lines out.
But, you know, I get the gist.
I understand that it's the false equivalency that is the problem.
It is the false equivalency that is the problem.
It's true.
There's, you know, there's a lot more nuance and interesting thoughts in the videos.
It's fucking ghouls on Twitter.
It's fucking Andy Ngo types who just make money.
God, the video of someone quote pushing, he says, Antifa pushes a woman in front of a
car, right?
In the video, it's not clear who pushes her.
And there is a car on the road, but it's like pretty far down the road and it's not even
moving that fast.
And like the woman seems annoyed to have been pushed, but not like afraid for her life at
all.
So, but whatever.
The comments are just like hundreds and thousands of people being like attempted murder.
Where are the police?
Why doesn't the mayor crack down on these terrorists?
Like, if I were there, if I were there, I would have shot them.
Hashtag concealed carry.
It's just so weird because like there was this bit where he was saying like they use
the fact that Antifa wears masks for very clearly useful reasons so that they don't get
attacked themselves later.
By people like Andy Goh, Andy Goh who will fucking dox them.
And it's like it's not necessarily an indication of violence.
You want to protest something and you don't want to get backlash for it and it's not illegal
to wear a mask.
But he was making the comparison that like riot police wear masks and they wear black
and it's like the things people are talking about Antifa for being like terrorists, bullies,
horrible people, the police as well.
Which, you know, I think we can all agree that they're kind of a lot worse in every way.
Dude, ACAB.
The Munchy, so I'm on Munchy's Audible subscription and he has got, he got me to read.
We talked about this book Debt.
Debt the first 5,000 years.
He told me to listen to it.
I did.
We both think it's fucking great.
And I have talked about, I think I've mentioned before that I've been meaning to read this
book called Bullshit Jobs, which is about how like in America a lot of the jobs that exist
are basically just like fake and made up and unnecessary and do not exist to like serve
any material purpose.
They are just like a product of like corporate bureaucracy.
And then, and Munchy's like, hey, I got another book by the Debt guy and it's about like
apparently this Debt guy, he was like one of like the organizers for the like Occupy Wall Street
movement and it's like about that whole, the whole experience of like what the Occupy Wall
Street movement was about.
It's called, oh fuck, that one's called Democracy Something?
It's called Democracy.
I forget the full title.
It doesn't matter.
But it turns out this guy, David Graber?
Joshua, I think it's David Graber.
The guy who wrote Debt is the guy who wrote Bullshit Jobs, which I have not read yet,
but it's on the list.
It's next to my list.
I'm going to listen to it.
And he also is the guy who did this.
He was this like front runner in the Occupy Wall Street movement and he's my new hero.
Like what a fucking, what a fucking Chad.
He's fucking, he's doing it, man.
He's doing it.
Oh boy.
I just want to quickly say, I didn't mean like, that like all police are worse in every way.
That was just like, it's the hypocrisy that the people who are complaining about Antifa
don't complain about the police for doing the same things to people that they don't like,
like minorities.
It's pretty appalling.
People calling for like Antifa to be labeled like a terrorist organization and stuff.
They're so fucking scared.
They're so, these conservative types, these gun wielding maniacs are so fucking scared
of these like, of these like, oh, these thugs, oh, these, they're like, they're like demonstrably
so much less violent.
They have like right wing extremism kills like hundreds of people a year and Tifa's
never killed anyone.
They just, they basically just throw milkshakes and like squirts silly string of people,
which is kind of like sad, but it's true.
Like that's what they do.
Maybe a window gets broken once in a while.
And there was that one guy with the bike lock.
Okay.
Everyone's like, oh, that one guy with the bike lock.
That was bad.
Right.
Nobody likes that guy.
Everybody fucking hates that guy.
The thing that really strikes me about like a philosophy tube and contra points, aside
from like their, their reasonableness in tackling these issues and not, you know, they appear
on the outside to be like, oh, outlandish lefty stupid idiots.
But like the things they say are like, oh, you know, they win people over clearly because
I used, I didn't used to be a right wing guy.
Like I had been conditioned by seeing that side of YouTube more and not seeing the left
side of YouTube that the types of people that are stupid look and sound like, you know,
left people.
If you can ever see or hear a lefty idea sort of thinker, then you should immediately think,
oh, what an idiot.
What a, what a social justice warrior.
But going into the videos, they're so well produced that they draw you in and then you
listen to them and the things they say are just, oh yeah, like I get it now.
I understand that I was, I was not really thinking about anything before.
I was just making judgments on people.
There was like the anti-feminist crowd or like the crowd that was like there to like
criticize like crazy feminists on YouTube for a while.
They were kind of like overlapped with like the atheist YouTubers, right?
Or like the rational skeptic types.
And like back in the day, that was one thing, but like a lot of them, not all of them, but
a lot of them like went on to like do this weird morph into these like conservative reactionary
like, like, like people that have these like, it's because like shoe, you know, shoe on head.
I know of her.
I never really watched her videos.
She's like, she's the girlfriend of like armored skeptic who was also one of these like rational dudes.
I always thought his icon, like his avatar uses really goofy.
It's very, very stupid.
Very stupid.
But like, I like, like she was one of these like, oh, look how dumb these feminists are.
But like, I don't know.
I guess I think lately she's been like, she's been kind of like, oh, you know, I kind of, I kind of think maybe I went a little,
maybe I went a little too hard in that direction before.
Like now she's like a big Bernie, a Bernie supporter and stuff.
She's like, I don't know.
I think she's fine.
I think she made mistakes, but she's fine now.
I don't think she's really changed much of her political opinions, but she just does like Bernie and that.
Yeah.
Which by the way, I would use as a moment to show that perhaps some of these people with
opinions, you know, more on that side are more reasonable than you might think.
They are.
It's really just the fact that back in the old days when the internet was new and we were
going through YouTube, just random people and their thoughts, it was novel and you would find somebody saying something crazy
and then you would, you know, find it in market.
And if it was really stupid, you would, you know, it sort of became profitable to do that and that became a whole
sect of YouTube is to, to find people and it just so happened to be like feminists were saying things that could be easily
taken out of context or not.
You know, they still, there are people who say stupid things who are feminists.
And so that sort of became that whole big thing.
And now it's, you know, similar stuff on the left, but it's through, through like progression through like YouTube and culture and,
you know, popular culture of internet stuff.
We've sort of, a lot of people, I think have realized that it's, you know, it's easy to point and laugh at a certain group,
but not nobody is like, what's the word, free from criticism, like every group has problems.
And so to, to really get, you know, really smart about things and be an intelligent man with max manner, like max intelligence,
you need to realize that people you might have enjoyed were, you know, have perhaps like incorrect or problematic or
mis, I hate words, this is why I don't speak so much.
In a society where everyone, this is increasingly how we are, where we're all damned for our, you know, everyone makes mistakes.
And if the damnation threshold is getting lower and lower and easier and easier to cross, literally everyone will be,
I mean, you can find and mock, choose a person, pick a random person on the planet, I guarantee you.
Like, you can cancel them online.
I have no doubt.
Yeah, this is, this is the sort of thing.
Like, I kind of cringe at the same people who like call John Tron a white nationalist racist who is completely evil,
because they don't know everything.
They're overstating the case.
They're playing into a thing.
John Tron obviously is not like, you know, well, not obviously,
but like the things he said in that thing, that livestream, were stupid and wrong.
And he apologized for that.
And he probably was just sort of misled by being, you know, he hadn't found the left side of YouTube
and realized that there was a different way to think about all this stuff.
I mean, I think it's because he's a gamer and he probably just hung out in fucking gamer spaces.
And like, gamer spaces.
I mean, this was like a, I was going to say, like, I can understand, I can, it's not hard for me to understand
why, like, back in the day, people really loved, like, people really loved to, like, tear into, like, crazy feminists
and things like that.
And like, I get it, right?
But then, but then that, that turned into Gamergate.
And Gamergate was bad.
And now we're living in a post-Gamergate world and it's not funny anymore.
Now it's got, like, now it's serious.
And some, some people, you know, some people leaned into that and some people, like, like, chew on head.
We're like, hold on, this has gone a little too far.
I didn't mean for it to go where it went.
I have a universal problem with all of it.
You know what YouTubers are like?
YouTubers are like, you know, there's, there's a giant seaport town.
It's like a ship manufacturing plant, which is obviously highly productive and people work there.
Like, YouTubers are like the, they're like the surface population of, like, divers who, like, wrecks happen
and, like, other people have made cool stuff.
Sure, divers do cool stuff. They go down and they find treasures, but they're not, like, the main industry.
They're surviving off of, like, plumbing the depths for what other people have done.
And a lot of the times that can be valuable.
You can find some really important stuff down there.
But it is a surface industry that exists on the back of, of lots of other stuff.
And, and to that end, I think there's lots of incentives, especially in this.
YouTube is stomach acid, as Davoo once said.
Oh yeah.
Is that, is that what you're getting at?
Yeah, but I was gonna say that, like, the, the, the issue I have that sort of relates to that is that, like,
those divers, to stick with that metaphor, they have such an incentive to, like, play up their discoveries
and to make everything seem like such a big deal.
And more to the point, like, when it comes to actual discussion of whatever topics going on,
there's such an incentive to escalate and flatten ideologies on any side, such that
just take your extreme right-wing stuff.
You got full-blown Nazis, I don't know, like white supremacists, then, I don't know,
you're getting into maybe like, like the, even this, I mean, you could argue how strong these are,
but like the Proud Boys, then maybe like Second Amendment strong guys or whatever,
then like General Conservatives, and then, I don't know, you're getting more to the middle of people.
Like, you, you could choose, and I, to me it seems like this happens a lot,
and on the other side as well, calling them commies or whatever.
Like, you could pick a guy on the early end of those rungs and just flatten him up to Nazi,
because that's like all the way.
And to me personally, on any side, when I see people call Bernie Akami, it frustrates me as well.
I hate, all that is, is a loss of signal and a loss of information,
and this is why I so famously said, back in the day on the PCP, I hate the spoken word.
It is so easy. I just wish we could have direct data transfer between brains so that you can't do that sort of stuff.
Like that fucking magic thing in Digi's light novel.
Did he, does he have that? I haven't, I haven't checked it out yet.
Did you listen to that? It's the chapter two, is like he explains.
Oh, you mean of Road to Radcon?
No, of course you should check out Road to Radcon chapter two, but...
I have, I have not checked out any of his new light novels.
Kusomega, Kusomega, that one.
Kusomega, yeah. His, there's this, I mean, it's very clear, like, ah, this is the perfect thing.
I would love to have this, says the autistic person who can't, like, socially relate to anyone.
It's the magical ability to project thoughts into the minds of people without any sort of speech,
and you can perfectly, like, the more powerful you are in that magic, magical ability,
the more succinctly and perfectly you can relay that information.
And there's like a few paragraphs in a chapter where, like, this is explore and it's like,
people are having thoughts and they're all, like, getting things done super efficiently
because nobody has to actually talk to each other.
That's good, that's good.
It's great.
There is a, there is a really interesting video by Innuendo Studios about, um, oh fuck, what was that game?
The Beginner's, you guys know the game The Beginner's Guide?
Yes, yes.
I do not.
The Beginner's Guide is made by the guy who made, ah, the, the, ah, what's the one, Stanley Parable.
The guy who made Stanley Parable, which was a huge hit, came back and he made this game called The Beginner's Guide,
which is, the, the Beginner's Guide pretends to be a, oh god, um, okay, the conceit of The Beginner's Guide
is that what you are actually playing is a series of unreleased, like, unfinished games by an unknown developer called Kota.
And this guy who knows Kota, who, no, um, oh fuck, I forgot he's, Davey, Davey Redan, is the, is the guy who made Stanley Parable
and supposedly in the game, the real life Davey Redan is walking you through these unfinished games
and explaining to you, like, what he thinks they mean.
And it's just like him, like, being like, yeah, let's delve into the mind of, of this guy, of this, this, this unknown, like, creative genius
that I, that I know called Kota.
But it, like, it's, it's actually, like, not that, it's like a fictional story.
Right, right.
Um, but, um, but yeah, anyway, it's really, it's, it's, but anyway, there's a really good video by Inuena Studios about it
in which he talks about, like, how, in explaining what he thinks the game is about, he, like, goes back and explains, like,
the theory of, like, language and authorship, and he talks about how, like, when someone, like, someone, like, speaks,
when someone, like, describes, they describe something, they translate, like, information in their head into, like, a shared language
and then you take those pieces of language and decode it.
But, like, the thing, the thing that you, the image that you put together in your head is assembled from, like, your experiences with those words.
Right, right.
And it's going to be different from the other person's experiences with those words.
And so on and so forth.
And it's a great video.
You know what, I just heard the other day, I just, I was watching a, a Razor Fist was playing through, um, Bioshock 1.
And obviously he's a big right-wing guy, but he was like, he's like, you know, I think one of the problems with a lot of people is that
when Ayn Rand was writing, or English was her second language, and when she used the word selfish, like, for example,
that didn't quite convey the meaning that she meant to the, to the English audience.
I don't know, I never, I never really thought, I thought she was trying to take back the word when I read Atlas Shrug and stuff back in the day,
but, uh, yeah, I mean, it's the same sort of thing.
It has a very negative connotation in the West and probably due to our Christian roots and whatnot.
Atlas Fugged.
Oh, he has his heavy balls.
He, he bears atop his shoulders that he must relieve himself of, but he just can't.
I was afraid, I was afraid I was going to spend the entire episode raving about the fucking Iowa caucuses, but don't worry.
Next episode, I'll be back to talk about New Hampshire.
New Hampshire, man.
Since it will have already happened, let me just, let me just preemptively say, fuck the DNC, Bernie got rat-fucked in Iowa and New Hampshire.
It's time, it's time to fucking, it's time to riot.
Yeah?
Do you recommend, uh,
It seems like time to riot.
I guess vote bridging would be bad prescription.
I mean, that too.
Let me, you know what, I'll just, I've been conflicted, right?
I've been conflicted about something.
I guess I might as well talk about it here, unless you think it's boring.
Probably, but whatever.
Probably almost definitely.
I was, I was very much like, you know, I should, even though I hate Hillary, I should have voted Hillary in 16.
And then like,
That's a tough one.
That's what I've said.
And like, this, because like voting third party didn't accomplish anything.
The DNC didn't care.
And like the turnout for the third party was not anywhere close to what it needed to be to make a meaningful difference.
And so this time I was like, you know what?
Okay, I want Bernie, but like this time I'm vote Blue no matter who.
But then, but then they start cheating.
And then I read this shit about like mandatory military service.
And suddenly I'm not so sure if, if I'm, if I'm gonna, if I'm gonna do it.
Like that, that policy alone, you know, I think that's one of those things that you just put in there to like,
Okay, the cheating, the cheating made me like, I don't want to vote for them.
But I think I was coming down like, no, okay, you know what, even if they cheat, even, even if pizza rat, like.
If it's gonna, if it's pizza rat, that could be his mascot, the pizza.
For harm reduction purposes, it's probably better to vote Blue no matter who.
And also like being, being Bernie, like, okay, the argument for Bernie or bust is that like, okay, you should be Bernie or bust
because people will see that people are Bernie or bust.
And it's like, okay, if we don't nominate Bernie, we're going to lose all this support.
And like that's going to cost us the nomination.
The counter argument is, okay, but if you are Bernie or bust, you're alienating like the vote Blue no matter who people.
And cause those people already see us, see the, the Bernie bros is like, oh, they're bullies online.
They were rude to me online.
So no healthcare for pores.
Like that's the attitude and I hate them.
They put on their fur suits and they broke my Chrysler.
That was fucked up, guys.
But, but I think I was coming down on the side of like, okay, even though I understand that argument,
I think that probably in terms of what's going to have the best like material consequences,
probably vote Blue no matter who is better.
But then I read this fucking mandatory military service and I'm like, I don't know.
Now I don't know anymore.
Now Pete might be, Pete might be worse than Trump guys.
We might have found a guy who's worse.
I'm scared.
Trump, he ain't going to do that.
He ain't going to do that.
He's not going to do that.
He might fucking, he might fucking, fucking destroy relations with Iran and get us into World War three.
But he's not going to do mandatory military service.
I don't know.
And look, what do we care about more?
If America's economy tanks over 20 years or I personally go to war and meet,
I can tell you what I care more about.
Leave me alone.
Hashtag, leave me alone.
And then, and then of course there's all these quotes from Pete where he says he wants to put an end to endless war.
He keeps saying it over and over again.
So like, hashtag never Pete.
That's right.
It would be verboten.
I mean, I just, Pete really stand a chance.
Elizabeth, it sounds like she's tanked.
There's no way.
No, I mean, even if Pete wins the nomination, there's no way.
Oh, you mean against Trump?
Okay, yeah.
Against, no, against Trump I don't believe for a second.
The DNC can't rig the entire election.
They can rig their own party stuff.
That's true.
Yeah.
But like, nobody actually cares about him.
You guys know that, like, rats, we're rats.
We're the rats.
I don't know that one.
We fuck at night.
We sneak at night.
We're the rats.
We fuck at night.
We come at night.
I mean, if you fuck at night, you come during the day.
I just wanted to make the joke that Pete wants to be the giant rat that makes all of the
rules, and we can't, we can't, we can't let him do it.
I'm the giant rat that makes all of the rules.
What is this?
This is a risky question.
Now let's try and what kind of trouble we can get ourselves into.
I don't know where it's from.
It's just like a video.
It's from, it's from German 985's rat movie video.
You guys, you guys know rat boy genius?
Yeah, of course.
Yeah.
The other joke that's been going around is rat boy POTUS.
This is where I make potato kineshes.
Yeah.
My favorite.
My roommates are big into rat boy genius.
He's got an extended body of work.
I myself have not seen the entire, the entire uvra.
That's too bad.
Rat boy should pull a gorillas and, you know, be a political party that is a fake person.
Rat boy.
That's a great idea.
Oh, Pete should or rat boy genius should.
Rat boy genius should as like, like the creator of rat boy will put rat boy genius as the
nominee.
Rat boy genius runs as a virtual candidate.
They make a music video slash political speech of him and like green screen him into like
public events.
We've got, we've got vermin supreme too.
You guys know him?
I've heard of him.
There's so many rats.
Another, another rat.
Vermin supreme is like a, is like a fake candidate who like runs in a light.
He's like this bearded fucking crazy man who wears a boot on his head.
Oh yeah.
Right.
Okay.
I actually saw him like in real life at the, at the, at the fucking the straight, the straight
pride parade, like how he was there.
Just, just taking selfies with people.
There are these candidates out there.
Like I know there's some who just like are, they're like, Hey guys, if you vote for me,
I'm just nobody.
I will just do, we'll have like public votes for every issue and I will simply do like
whatever it is that like the, the democratic, you know, populace wishes me to do.
I don't know.
I thought those were kind of cool.
That's, that's an idea.
Wait.
What do you, what do you mean?
Who are you talking about?
I can't think of any names specifically, but I have heard of candidates in the past who
think that like the presidency is bullshit anyway.
And what they want to do is like, okay, if you vote for me, here is my platform.
I will decide nothing.
I will simply like put out votes to the public on any given issue that comes across my desk
and I will just do what the people.
That seems like it would be really difficult.
Like since that's not how our like government infrastructure is built.
Absolutely not.
I mean, you know,
To get people to vote on all of the things.
Yeah.
Look how fast China whipped together a bunch of hospitals for the coronavirus or whatever.
I mean, that seemed pretty good.
There's one big hospital.
There is one.
Okay.
But there are advantage as singular, at least advantage to having like an executive who
can do thing singular.
Sure.
But so yeah, I don't know if I necessarily would go for that.
Pretty good.
Pretty good government.
Yeah.
All right.
Let's do stuff.
You know, it's easy.
The one.
Yeah.
Go on.
I was going to say the one thing.
Another thing that makes me really mad is like, oh, Bernie's a socialist.
Bernie's, I saw a great tweet that was like, I already knew this, but I was, I was reminded
in a tweet that like, oh yeah.
They said the same, they said the same thing about social security.
They said this, like, how was the other thing?
They said like anything that any public good, they call it socialism.
God, and it's really makes me mad that Bernie, like Bernie calls himself a democratic socialist.
And I'm in his, in his heart, I'm sure he is.
But like the policies that he's pushing for, they are not socialist policies.
They are just, he is, he is basically just an FDR or Truman style Democrat who wants
to do something, who wants to create like social programs basically on the level of
like social security.
Maybe Bernie's problem is that level.
Maybe he shares my weakness.
And the fact that, and the fact that that's seen as like a radical leftist position now
is just really sad.
I guess.
Super fucking sad, dude.
That's how I feel about it.
But what, what makes you glad though?
What makes you glad in these last few, yeah, since last week.
What makes me glad?
That's a great question.
Well, I've started work, I've started work, great question.
I've started working on slime and punishment again.
I am.
Fantastic.
I'm finishing up the last few, okay, because there's going to be like a bunch of panels
followed by the video.
And I'm working on getting those like pre-finale panels done.
And I'm not going to really, I'm not going to release them until they are, until the finale is ready.
Okay.
But I am putting them up on Patreon for the, like for my,
the ten, the ten dollar people, like people pledging at the level of like getting a cameo in the, in the thing.
Like, yeah, I'm putting them up on Patreon early for those people.
And some of them, you know, I don't know.
I think, I think maybe there's, it's going in some unexpected directions.
I certainly look forward to it.
Should be, shouldn't be, shouldn't be too, too long.
I don't know how long the video is going to take.
I'm going to try and get it.
I'm going to try and keep it as simple as I can.
That's wise. That's wise.
Yes.
You know, speaking of that, I, I haven't finished it as of recording.
But I hope to finish chapter three of Lord of Ghosts by the time this, this PCP comes out and is uploaded to Davoo's second channel or whatever.
Yeah, whatever this is.
Oh, I never, fuck, I never tweeted about Lord of Ghosts chapter two.
I meant, I meant to do that.
I think I retweeted it.
Shameful.
Yeah, that's embarrassing.
You're really churning through these chapters pretty fast, which is great.
That is what I want.
Well, he had them sketched, but still, still that's pretty fast.
I mean, I feel like I've been slowing down a little too much.
I wanted to get them out like every two weeks.
Yeah.
I've just, I've been getting like a combination of like, I go down to work and I fall asleep like actually, like why am I doing that?
And my wrists are starting to like actually hurt.
Oh yeah.
And I don't know, I don't know what to do to like speed up the recovery.
I don't want to not do anything because I need my hands to play video games as well.
And use the mouse and keyboard.
Jick off.
These are important.
All important actions.
I mean, I'm envious.
I mean, I'm here, you know, relaxing stuff, but really I fucking hate it because I can't be working on my current projects.
I can't be playing video games.
That, that too.
What you gotta do.
That too.
I can't be voting in the primary.
Guys, if my, if my phone, oh, one more thing.
Yeah.
Fuck what makes me glad.
What makes me mad is I still don't have a phone.
Didn't you already something with the folks?
Yes.
They had, mom and dad had an extra phone.
Yeah.
They sent it to me.
I took it to the sprint store yesterday.
They were like, nah, it's not a sprint phone.
It's not eligible.
Can't do it.
Oh, what?
But we were all on sprint.
That doesn't make sense.
Maybe I'm wrong.
I don't know.
I don't know where they got this phone from, this extra phone, but it's like, nah, it's the wrong type.
Can't, can't do it.
So I'm still out of phone.
Well, I genuinely, genuinely, if I had a phone, this pisses me off more than anything.
If I had a phone, I would literally be fucking phone calling, phone banking and making calls for Bernie.
I absolutely would be fucking doing that, but I can't.
So instead, I'm just fucking, I'm just selling Yang shirts and donating the proceeds.
Fair enough.
I mean, hey, maybe.
I've made like, I've made like the Yang shirts have raised like 115 bucks or something.
That's good.
And it's all, and it's all gone.
It's all gone to the campaign.
It's all gone to act blue campaign donations.
I mean, with a generous cut for time and energy, you know, I mean, 50, 20, 80%.
No, no, all the profit goes, no, I don't, no, I don't make anything from these Yang shirts.
You're speaking of making things for doing stuff.
How about that Radcon 4 Kickstarter that's rolling right along?
The Radcon 4 Kickstarter is doing pretty good.
By the time this comes out, how many days will be left?
Oh, we'll have like a handful, like three or four days.
Oh God.
Yeah.
This, this will be the last one.
This will be the last PCP before the Kickstarter ends.
Yep.
So we better.
Um, it makes me really mad.
Yeah.
Okay.
I mean, the Kickstarter has, you know, it did really well immediately.
And then it has kind of maintained like a pretty steady growth the whole time.
It makes me so mad that we don't have our channel.
We do not have the fucking PCP channel where we can be posting updates and, and, and like
advertising more.
That's like the place we want to advertise it, but fucking Brad Garlinghouse or Ripple
or whatever owns it and we can't use it.
And like, I know the, I know the Kickstarter is doing good.
Like it outperformed expectations, but like, I'm sure it could be doing better if we had
our fucking platform.
I have no doubt.
Holy fuck.
I have no doubt that that's true.
Um, well, hey, for the record, it sucks.
We're at.
So much.
It does.
I mean, I don't, I mean, I, I mean, at this point, I'm starting to think like, I hope
we get it by Radcon by the time Radcon starts, right?
I mean, surely we've got.
No, no.
We're fucked.
Nate, Nate.
I swear to God we're fucked.
They're never going to do it.
They're never giving us our channel back.
They don't care.
I mean, okay.
Well, just to be callous for a moment, what about my channel?
That 100,000 subs.
I mean, do I,
Your stand's a better chance.
Yeah.
But like that Mars reviews guy had a hundred K two and his channel is just gone.
Well, okay.
Yeah.
Did the people who stole it, they probably deleted it, right?
They did that.
And now he's maybe working with Google to hopefully recover it.
Yes.
He said he's contacted YouTube and he's hoping to recover it.
Okay.
I mean, you know, maybe it might come back.
It might reappear.
I can't, I can't guarantee that it won't.
Nate, I'm sorry.
I hate to say it.
It's my fault.
I really hate to say it.
But no, no, that's not what I'm, no, I don't look, I'm not mad.
Nobody makes mistakes, but I'm saying, I don't like saying it.
I'm afraid that the channels are just gone.
Yours included.
Hey, baby.
And we should probably start, I don't know, just be just preparing for that.
The reason I haven't done anything yet.
Okay.
One is because it's been a little over two weeks.
I know you've been, I know you've been in contact with YouTube.
Yes.
But like the main thing and okay, there will be a time where this will no longer be an
acceptable, you know, course to continue taking.
But right now they just say the same thing every time.
And I do seem to get a human response when I mail them.
That's like, yeah, it's a little bit different every time.
It doesn't seem like it's a bot.
And they're just like, our internal team is working on it.
Okay.
I get nothing along the lines of sorry, like we tried, it can't be done.
I've received nothing and I know that it's in their interest to keep me like pacified
while they, you know, are figuring this stuff out.
But I just feel like there is hope still.
I retain hope for, for these things.
Uh, sure.
Yeah.
I mean, I guess that's it.
I guess that's it.
Yeah.
I mean, if it's not there by the end of February, I have a strong feeling is not, we're not
going to have it back for like months and months.
There should be a cutoff point where like if we are at a certain point, we need to decide
to just make a new look.
If we get our channels back.
Okay, great.
We can migrate.
Do you know if we do that?
If we start re-uploading videos, we're going to get fucking like content matched with our
own channel that someone else stole.
Uh, that's definitely possible.
I guess we could just fight them.
Uh, what we could do.
No.
What we could, what we should do.
Yeah.
Right.
Under the assumption that eventually it may take a really long time, but eventually
the channels will be returned.
I think we should make for specifically for Radcon 4, like a channel to do live streams
and stuff.
We could do that.
Just so that it's there.
That's, yeah.
It's something for sure.
PCP2 or, you know.
This is my first week of my entire life.
I can't fucking deal with it.
I'm my back hurts now.
It's hurting.
Oh, I'm in pain.
Ben, you got to wake up and do some yoga, brother.
You got to stretch it out.
You got to do some of this gay, girly yoga I've been doing.
Do some girl yoga.
Yeah, maybe.
It's great.
It opens the chakras.
Uh, like my, you know, remember when, when, uh, Guy was acknowledged as the number one
Taijutsu user by Madhura Uchiha at the end of Naruto Shippuden?
Literally me every morning.
Of course.
It's great.
It's wonderful.
I have hope.
Oh, and you know, the other thing is I really don't like want to make a big deal of like,
like, I feel like some people have felt like, I haven't seen this a lot, but like, I can't
help that since we have a Kickstarter going right now, and we're like, Oh God, please
help that some people would think to like, I know what to do.
I'll like.
We're literally a Kickstarter.
But wait, what?
Wait, what?
I was just thinking that like, I don't want people to think that like we're just asking
for like money because that won't help the problem like at all.
What I'd love them to do, I don't know, is put some sort of weird arbitrary ghost of
like pressure on YouTube that will somehow manifest in them getting our channels back
faster, which I am dubious at most will even do anything.
We're literally the victims of a crime, Nate.
Absolutely true.
100% true.
This is real crime.
This is real crime has been perpetrated against us and we have been robbed.
Yep.
But where are the cyber police?
Where are they?
It's my question.
We need them.
I don't know.
They just, they only stay, oh, well, they only, the police, all cops are bad.
They only serve the interests of the capitalist class.
So obviously they're on fucking Brad's side because he's, he's paying them.
He's paying them under the table in fucking Ripple.
He could.
I mean, these guys, man, they, they don't need our channels.
It's nothing.
They're not getting any profit.
No, of course they don't.
So little returns.
It'll give a shit.
Yeah.
It's just whoever it is, just like some scammer out there was just like, yeah, fuck it.
I'll just, I mean, these people obviously send this out.
There's like, I don't know, dozens or maybe hundreds of channels they scammed.
Overall, sure.
They can make a few thousand dollars probably just by doing whatever.
Did you see, did you see that screenshot?
Like someone posted on Twitter and Tom retweeted it about like how like a shad, not Shadbase,
that one, that other YouTuber called Shad, like, and in his comments like, oh, so-and-so
got his channel hacked and stolen a couple hours later, he's like, oh, I'm so relieved.
Got it back that day.
Yeah.
I definitely, it's like a China point system only, probably based on like number of subs
like activity on the channel.
I mean, I definitely think that's what's happening.
No doubt, no doubt in my mind.
Here's what I think.
I think that we fucked up and mismanaged the situation by not going fucking ballistic
about it immediately.
And because it's a fucking nightmare and I am fucking in panic mode, it is ruining my
life.
Me, me, me, me, it's all about me, but it is a fucking disaster and like a worst case
scenario type situation.
It is fucking Armageddon and I think that we should have, I think that we should have
just assumed the worst case scenario from the very outset and I don't think, I think
people are not worried about it because we are acting like we're not worried about it.
Let me tell the audience right now, I'm fucking worried about it.
It's really bad.
What should we do?
It's really fucking bad, everybody.
Do we act team YouTube?
Is that the grand play we have?
I mean, yes.
I don't know.
What's your fucking grand plan?
I have no plan.
I have no solution.
I guess act team.
Yeah, I mean Nate, I assume you've been retweeting all of the tweets from the PCP Twitter and
stuff on your own Twitter.
Most of them, yeah.
Like I feel, because one of them did get a response from YouTube because we act team
YouTube.
That's true.
I responded to songs, the PCB accounts.
So like any little amount, I mean, we don't know how it works, but like, the way I was
dealing with it at first, because Ben was like freaking out a little bit and I was trying
to calm him down because I just wanted him to be okay.
Yeah.
Well, I'm not.
And now it's gotten worse and it's like, ah, shit.
I fucked up by trying to like react with reason because it's YouTube.
YouTube is not a good company.
They suck.
I should have realized that it would suck, no matter what happens.
You know, personally with me, I think one of my issues, maybe Ben's totally right and
that is the correct response.
I have, like, this isn't like a monkey narrative where like YouTube betrayed us.
I personally fucked up.
We fucking are the victims of a crime.
We're the victims of a fucking, no, you didn't screw up.
We are a criminal fucking stole our shit.
Okay.
I mean, you're right.
You're absolutely right.
Quit fucking, quit victim blaming.
You fuck.
Oh, but I just have to say.
Your self-finding.
You're self-finding.
I know empathy for women who are victimized and I just have to apply the same, yeah,
I don't know.
I, yeah, I just, I feel, I guess, shame and it makes me not want to tell it.
It's not that I don't want to tell anyone.
I don't care.
I don't care about your feefies, Nate.
You're the fucking, you're the fucking victim and we're gonna, we're gonna fucking cry about
it.
Okay.
Well, it's just, okay.
We're gonna cry no matter how good you feel.
The moment I felt hope was lost, I would feel 100% valid to like one, I would make a new
channel instantly for like all these channels and two, I would be, I would probably make
a video or two about, I don't know, whatever.
I'll probably still do that no matter what happens.
But then I would definitely proceed to, I don't, you know what, honestly, look, look
into my, I don't think I would even make a big deal of, I just feel like, yeah, hey,
here's my new channel, guys.
I hope you'll get one of my videos.
No, you should, you have to.
All right.
Here's the thing.
I think it's easy to use comedy to deal with things that are like, you know, bad things
like this.
Like it's, you know, Brad Garlinghouse, that's funny, you know, that would be, that's like
something we can look back on and laugh.
But you don't want to think about how bad things are right now.
So let's laugh right now.
And because we're joking about it and being jovial in things, people, I don't think got
the sense that we thought it was a big deal when it started out because we were joking
about it.
And it's, it's kind of, I mean, I don't know what any, like our audience could have done
differently other than to do more retweets and stuff.
Because that's the only avenue we really have.
We don't have the channels.
I mean, if we, I mean, you've got the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the,
the link to the person and that's a, a three now.
If, if, if we just step back for a moment, like, let's just say in fantasy land, let's
say hashtag, save the PCP did, which you should retweet, I suppose, based on all these things
and tweet that out, say blah, blah, blah, retweeting everyone who tweets, yes.
Hashtag, save the PCP, if theoretically that hashtag, let's just say mad, became number
one on Twitter, hashtag panic mode, fair enough.
If that became the number one Twitter and like people around were starting to talk
about it, then like, I bet YouTube would, in fact, they'd turn their attention and
they'd sort this out in the, you know, half an hour to an hour it would take to give
us back our stuff and do all those things.
But you know what, you know, I had one other thought on this whole subject.
Okay.
So for us, here, you feel free to go ahead.
Well, it's really just like I am, I was operating was operating under the same sort
of thought, like, there's no reason to scream and cry immediately.
But, you know, because like the likelihood that screaming and crying on our scale for
the PCP channel or whatever, like your scale, maybe it would have worked.
Maybe a hundred, hundred K, but like the idea that, oh, it's probably, they're probably
not going to do anything if I make a big fuss about it.
So I'm not going to make a big fuss is sort of like it only inconveniences you for
no reason.
You know, I just disposition wise, I'm definitely opposed to like being, I don't
know, having people having sympathy for me.
Maybe it's a personal issue I need to work with.
I don't know.
But I certainly don't want to be in that position if I can help it, which, which I
was going to say that like, there's another thing that people have said.
So there's this guy at the quartering who makes YouTube videos about like news updates.
And it happens that he happens to be on this issue recently, it seems.
And I think like I checked in his Twitter, his pinned tweet is like, you know, these
channels have been hacked or excuse me, something like that.
And like, you know, he seems to be trying to do something to get it dealt with.
Okay.
The only thing about that is, this is another complicated thing.
I don't dislike the man personally.
He seems fine.
I do, I do.
Okay, fine, fine.
I don't dislike him as a man.
He's, he's whatever.
He's a, he's a fucking gamer.
He definitely is a gamer.
There's no doubt about that.
So whatever you feel about that, fair enough, make that literally just makes him bad.
But whatever.
Okay, okay.
Well, on the subject of this, see, here's the thing.
I'm sure that in his heart, he feels that like doing this can help.
And maybe he can spread the word.
We were talking about a campaign.
Sure.
Okay.
But I've watched this man quite a bit over the years.
I've seen his content.
I know what he does.
Guys like him, and even to an extent like Tim Poole, or I mean, Sargon has been doing it a little
bit more lately with his like, new stuff.
What a great, what a great cast of characters.
A wonderful cast.
Yeah.
And I don't know, take your pick, any person, any persuasion of any news side,
any political thing, whatever, it doesn't matter.
Like, I really can't help but feel like these people, it does nothing to help anyone.
And it's really like, okay, the thing about the quartering that makes him unique is that
unlike other people, he will go in and he will say, guys, listen, these channels got hacked.
There's only one thing you can do.
You got to share this video.
You got to retweet.
You got to share it around.
Cause this is the only, and I'm like, okay, look, I really don't think that we'll do anything
to help anyone except you and your business personally.
So I, I mean, maybe if you say just hashtag, save the PCP or save the channels or whatever
it is, okay, sure.
And I don't think it's out of malice, but I can't avoid thinking that like, and if you're
listening to this quartering one day, I doubt you are, but like, it's not, I don't dislike
you, but this is just so not helpful.
Like, I already don't think any of this tweeting at team YouTube does anything because let's
say our channel gets restored tomorrow.
That's almost guaranteed because I put in those YouTube tickets at the very beginning
two weeks ago.
Well, explain to me how that guy that like shadowverse, okay, the guy who got hacked was
Todd of Todd's workshop.
I like, how did that guy get his channel back in like a matter of hours?
Let me see how popular he is.
Todd of Todd's workshop.
Let me see here.
Okay.
This man is, is he a million sub kind of guy?
Todd's workshop.
Here we go.
I'm seeing 182,000 subscribers.
Okay.
So, I mean, it's not massive or anything.
That's, I mean, it's big enough.
It's bigger than, bigger than you, but not like by like a huge amount.
He's like one, he's like 180% of assuming this is the right one.
Yeah.
No, one hour ago, he made a video saying we're back on his channel.
They're all putting the show notes.
So what, how was, you know, I'm going to watch this video, see exactly because I
haven't watched this yet, obviously.
If he's like a, he's like a blacksmith channel, I guess I'm, I'm honestly
surprised they haven't fixed your channel.
Nate, seeing as you are a hundred K boy, I'm a little surprised as well.
I don't know why it is.
Okay.
Look, I heard two weeks, maybe they look at watch time or something.
We're still in the, I mean, yeah, that's definitely pop.
My channel isn't like the most active or successful hundred K one or anything.
I like, if we're in the orbit still of two weeks, which we are still now, that's
fine.
These things can take longer.
I know of one guy with a smaller channel who took eight weeks to get
restored, but it did eventually happen.
So like, you know, the two week thing was just something I had heard.
I don't know what it means.
Some people are going to fix that.
All right.
I, I, I know, I know that you're, you know, it's sort of like, you don't want to
look bad.
You don't want to look like a guy who's begging for anything.
Cause it's just, it's not your aesthetic.
But like, I feel, I feel like if there's any chance that it can make the, the
thing happen quicker, then it's nothing to be ashamed of, to try if, if you
actually really like, I mean, you're right.
You're definitely right.
Like people aren't going to be like, Oh my God, is that the guy who got sad when
his channel got taken down?
Like that's not going to be a big deal in the future.
I have wondered if I'm emotionally dead inside.
Cause like I, I wonder a little bit why I'm not sadder and you're all about those
facts and you got to, you got to let your feelings kind of feel in my heart.
Like, yeah, I mean, I fucked up.
Like, I, yeah, I deserve it.
Cause you know, it's, I, I'm the one who did the mistake.
That's fucking stupid.
I know it's, I know, I know it's stupid.
It's just a victim of a fucking crime.
We all are actually.
Yep.
So like, I mean, no offense, but like take your fucking dumb ass.
Like, Oh, what was me?
This is all, I deserve this attitude and like fuck right off with it.
Cause like it's, it's a fact.
Like, like we're all fucking dealing with it.
I, I care.
You guys are all dealing with life.
That's, yeah, it's fair.
It's fair.
Okay.
Well, we're on the same page.
We're going to look literally the only lever of power we have is just to get people
to tweet about it.
I mean, I don't know.
What if we got a protest in front of TYN?
So let's fucking get it fucking going before I cry.
Here's a thought.
What of a public gathering in front of YouTube headquarters, a peaceful
demonstration with signs that just say hashtag, save the PCP, where we just
attempt to get them to a human being with authority to pay attention to the
fact that this is happening.
I mean, is that a, is that a thing we can do?
It's not illegal, right?
I mean, I'm not going to do that because I don't know how to get, I mean,
the cost of money to go to California and stuff, but maybe other people would do it.
Maybe you alone heroes, I don't know.
That's hashtag PCP or I cry.
I cry spelled I C R I great.
Fantastic.
Yeah, that's me.
That's what I'm feeling right now.
Okay.
That speaks to my truth.
Well, let's turn this sadness into righteous anger and get people all we can do at
Team YouTube, just keep, I'll just tell people the news.
I don't know if I've even told you guys this yet.
Team YouTube did message me on best guy ever.
Excuse me.
I DM them all the information about every channel that was stolen in like a big
spreadsheet, love putting it together.
It was wonderful.
Uh, so I've got, I can send that out to anybody who wants information on what's
going on and, and then Team YouTube responded to us at TP.
Crasinators and like their update was just like, we'll let you know, like what we
find.
So like right now everything is, they seem aware, just nothing has changed.
Nothing has been done as far as we can.
Maybe they're researching it right now and it's taking them a while.
I don't know.
It would take them no time.
If that's the case, they should, like I emailed them on the BGE email, I think,
and just like, look, I am losing my livelihood here.
Like just tell me what's being done.
If you're, if it's in the queue, tell me it's in the queue.
If someone's looking at it, if you need any information, I'm in the videos.
You will see, I can prove that it's mine, blah, blah, blah, et cetera, et cetera.
We just need a fucking human who can, who can help on these things.
So it sounds like attention's the game.
You forced our hand, YouTube.
What else can we do at this point, but make your life mildly unpleasant with a
large number of, what else can we do?
But like occasionally remind you of our existence with notifications on Twitter.
What a nightmare.
All right.
Hashtag, save the PCP.
That's it.
Tweet that, make a Twitter if you don't have one.
Fucking get engaged.
This is social media era, you idiot.
Get on Twitter.
That's what I'm talking about.
Ruin your life by engaging in hostile political discourse.
24 seven, tweeting about this.
And then, and then, and then make calls for Bernie, please.
And be very hot.
Be a hostile Bernie, bro.
Just like, call up fucking pizza porters and be like, you fucking neoliberal
coward, don't fucking, don't fucking come to the polls.
I'll fucking end you, bro.
That reminds me.
Are you saying, are you saying you call like pizza places to say that?
No, Pete.
Yeah, pizza.
Yeah, pizza porters, pizza porters.
Pizza porters.
They carry around the porters is what I tried to say.
Pizza, pizza, the, pizza, the port.
And you go to the, you go off your boat, you get a pizza.
By the way, this is very important.
And you get attacked by Bernie supporters.
I had an important note.
I meant to read the beginning and it was just in Hawaii, taken it sleazy.
But really, that was the Democratic National Convention all along that I was describing.
They're taking it so sleazy right now.
And I'm jealous.
Tune in to my Twitter on Friday to see how angry I am about how they
rat fucked my boy Bernie again.
I, I, he's got it.
I mean, he's got to take that one.
He's got to take that one.
We'll see.
I don't, I mean, polls conflict and like, you know, like who fucking knows?
Cause the polls didn't, didn't, didn't anticipate Buttigieg doing as well in, in, in Iowa.
Correct me if I'm wrong, but I heard that the, I think the third one, which they expected
Biden to win was I think South Carolina, like they expect like a black vote to be him.
I think the third one's Nevada and then South Carolina, I might have them back.
But like, yeah, um, uh, non-white people don't like Pete Buttigieg.
Yeah.
Uh, they, Buttigieg has like zero black support.
And like he's like only white people will vote for him.
So like New Hampshire and Iowa.
Yeah, maybe, but like Nevada, no, South Carolina, definitely.
It's Nevada, I don't know the demographics of Nevada, but I think, I mean, I think there's
a lot of Hispanic people, but like I've, I've looked at the polls and like Sanders is still
number one in Nevada by a pretty wide margin.
He got, I mean, Buttigieg's got a little boost across the board, but like he didn't
like soar in Nevada.
Do we really want, South Carolina is still like locked in for Biden of all people.
And Biden is like dying.
I mean, Obama's VP, I guess that, you know, goes the distance.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, Biden has a lot of black support for some reason.
And he's the favorite to win among people who are just like, why can't we go back to
the Obama years?
Why not?
I ask legalized crime.
So like, honestly, honestly, the one shred of hope and also, uh, for some reason,
Klobuchar, I guess Klobuchar performed, oh, I watched the debate at the ABC debate.
I'm sorry to bring it back at the very end.
Um, she had a really, she had a pretty strong performance at the debate.
The ABC debate was like pretty good.
Like as these debates go, oh my God, I want to talk about fucking Tom Steyer, who I
don't know who that is.
I have no idea.
I'm okay.
So, so Klobuchar did well at the debate and she's getting a little surged too.
And I'm, I'm happy that Biden's still in it.
I'm happy that Klobuchar is in it because they're splitting the moderate vote away
from Pete.
And like, thank God, thank God for Joe.
At this point, I'm like, I cannot wait, I cannot wait for Biden to fucking sweep
North Carolina just to make Pete look like a fucking idiot, just, just to humiliate
him.
Um, but anyway, so at the debate, the, the, the CNN is terrible.
The last debate I watched with CNN, it was a fucking nightmare.
This one was ABC and it was like way, I mean,
it was a little annoying, but it was like way less annoying.
Um, Sanders did good.
Klobuchar did surprisingly good.
Biden looked like he was about to have a aneurysm.
Um, Warren was not where she needed to be.
They hammered Pete on being, uh, on having like, they hammered Pete on a bunch of like
shitty stuff, shitty reasons why he's like kind of racist and like how he like ran,
how he, the thing that he, basically the South Bend became like way worse for
black people when he was, um, when he was mayor of it.
And there was other things too, but like that's, that's the long and short of it.
Um, so they, they hammered Pete on that and like, okay, cool.
But like this guy and Yang was there.
Yang was there being like, uh, automation, uh, hey, $1,000 an hour.
Everyone's like, yeah, yeah, that's cool.
But then this guy, Steyer, Steyer is so fucking weird.
He was kind of the like runaway hit of the, of the night.
Like he, he won the meme vote, um, on, on whatever it's S-T-E-Y-E-R.
He is a, he is a, like an oil billionaire, right?
But he, he like, he's like an oil billionaire, like fossil fuels billionaire
who like at some point in his life, he just like decided like fuck this.
Like, and it's almost, it seems like it's like a vanity project.
Just decided, I'm just going to be a liberal Democrat and run for president.
And like he's up, he's up in like, I guess he's, he's, he's the climate change guy.
Even though he's an oil guy, he, he has pledged like the one thing that I'm
running on is like climate change.
I'm going to be the guy who's like, that's his like, that's his, his whole issue.
As far as like running for presidency.
Is he still an oil guy now?
That seems, uh, is, is he like, did he give up his interest or something?
I don't think he is like actively running like oil, like fracking companies now or
anything, uh, as far as I know, honestly, I haven't looked that much into it.
I've looked a little bit into him, but not that much.
Um, but he's, he's like, okay.
And remember that thing about how Warren, like, how like Warren wouldn't
shake Bernie's hand the last time you hear about that?
Okay.
Well, like, well, like they're having their argument.
And she's like, I think you called me a liar on national television.
He's like, okay, you want to have that discussion later.
Okay.
Yeah.
Good.
Um, and then, but like, while that's happening, Tom Steyer is like behind Bernie,
just kind of like waiting to get a word in edgewise.
Like, Oh, was he the guy who just wanted to say hi to Bernie?
Yes, that guy, he was, he was like, hi Bernie.
I just wanted to say hi and he's like, yeah, okay.
And then, and then in this debate, Steyer's up there, like, I mean, he's
a monster to be like, so you have to subscribe to my private Snapchat.
That's only for $20 or not.
He can't, he can't because Steyer's, Steyer's a billionaire and he won't let,
he won't let donors, he won't let billionaires donate to him.
So I can't, you can't do it.
Sorry, Steyer, you're out of the fucking club.
That's too bad.
Um, but I mean, the whole debate, Steyer's mostly just up there, like,
like standing Bernie, just like agreeing with everything Bernie says.
BP, maybe he's going for BP.
I don't know.
I maybe, I mean, I just think he really likes Bernie.
I like clearly seems to like Steyer was so funny the whole time because my,
my sense watching was that he was just like really excited to be there.
Like he's just like, man, I fuck, I can't believe I'm up on stage with,
with Bernie Sanders and like the former vice president, like, damn, look at me now,
dad, like, I can't believe he's the guy who said, I just wanted to say hi to Bernie.
I heard that.
I was wondering who that was.
It's like, it's got to be like one of the reporters or something, right?
That's, that's Tom, that's Tom Steyer and Tom Steyer is, I mean, there are no good
billionaires, but Tom Steyer is trying really hard to be like less bad than
like his ilk, even if it's just for like his own like weird vanity, like, fine.
Okay.
I'll, I'll take it.
Honestly, honestly, Steyer solidarity comrade.
What is it?
We had a bunch of memes.
We all, we all watched it in my friend's room and we had a bunch of memes where
people call like his supporters the Steyer buyers, but then we're like, oh yeah,
I'm a, I'm a pig Steyer.
I'm in the pig Steyer.
Yeah.
I'm rolling in it.
That's good shit.
We watched them while the, for the first half of the bates, I was in my fucking
discord, just like, we were all just like live, like reacting in my discord server
to two things, just being like, oh my God, can you fuck?
Oh my God, these guys are, they're fucking hammering Pete.
Like fuck.
Yeah, it was pretty good.
It was pretty.
I guess cause like whoever's the, what is it?
They say the, the tall nail gets the hammer or whatever, the squeaky wheel gets
the grease.
Yeah, yeah, because like Pete, Pete was like the one who everyone was surprised
by how well he did in Iowa.
So they're like, fuck that guy.
He's kind of the one that everyone was going after him on stage and like, I mean,
thank God, we, yeah, but he's, he has to be, he has to be, he has to be fucked.
Honestly, honestly, but he does suck things.
I mean, he is gay, but gross.
No, thanks.
I know.
Yeah.
But, um, someone like, I like, I said on Twitter, like, please don't make, like,
I want to vote for Lunamatter, but please don't make me vote for Biden.
Like, honestly, I would, if Biden got the nom, I would like grit my teeth and like,
it's like, damn it, but I would go and I would vote for Biden.
Honestly, with, I don't, I don't know if I could do, I don't know if I could do it.
I don't know if I could vote for Pete anymore.
He's that, but I don't know his policy at all.
I definitely don't want that mandatory fucking service.
Shit.
That's, it's the, okay, the mandatory military service thing is fucking scary.
And then his, his Medicare bill is like, it pretends to be good.
He has this like, the lion's like, oh, no, no, no, no, not Medicare for all.
Medicare for all who want it.
And what that basically means is like, he will do.
Okay.
The problem, it sounds good, right?
It's like, oh, give people a choice.
But like the problem with that is that if you do Medicare for all who want it means
you don't have to, like Medicare doesn't work if like everybody is not paying
into it, like social security.
Like we have progressive tax brackets, like rich people need to be like
paying in like a proportionally higher share, because that's how like we
fucking have, that's how fucking social benefits are done in a civilized society.
Yeah.
And if you give Medicare for all who want it, you have to opt in.
The only people who will do that are poor people.
Rich people will just continue to use their private health insurance because
they want to be able to like buy priority over poor people in getting healthcare.
And then it won't be fun.
It will, and it just won't work and it will collapse.
And then it will be even worse because Republicans, the, aha, you see, we
tried a public option and it failed.
But guess we better, guess we better privatize even more.
That's, that's how they do it.
Uh, yeah.
You, you, you propose it.
You propose a shitty half measure that's designed to fail.
It fails.
And then they say, aha, public options just don't work.
Socialists blown out.
Yeah.
I mean, when you, when you try to, back in my day, we, we put, picked ourselves
up by our white skin and we just worked hard for our milk or milk health.
I was out there.
I worked hard.
I, you know, it was backbreaking work, whipping slaves in the cotton fields and
they're trying to just, but, but, but now here I am a self-made man made it all
on my own.
And, you know, we have to institute, I mean, you know, as you describe,
communism requires everyone to be fully on board or else the slave subjects will
escape to those lovely states nearby.
We can't have that.
We need everybody to be on board.
So, uh, that's what happened.
Yeah.
Uh, like Bernie needs three more houses and we've all got to pitch in to make
that a reality.
Like if, like, like it takes it, not, not me, us, like all of us,
us, my houses.
Thanks Bernie.
Appreciate that.
Yeah.
Only I'm not allowed.
Not, not, not me.
U.S.
Oh, us, not me.
That's good.
Not, not me as in the state of Maine, us, as in the United States.
Perfect.
Maine gets, Maine is excised from the union.
All right.
Voice mails.
What do you say?
We got, we got a bunch of voice mails.
Let's do voice mails.
Holy shit.
Okay.
Uh, let me see.
First now, I think these are gonna, oh wait, no, we had, we, we, we had an issue.
Should I try to play it?
You think I should give it a shot?
What?
From the, uh, the rhythm bot here, or should I just say fuck it?
And we'll all, uh, try, try rhythm just one more time.
Okay, we'll just give it a shot.
All right.
Uh, let me go over here.
So as you always know, people go to the speak pipe link down below in the
description and leave us your lovely voice mails.
Uh, and do, if you have a more complicated one, as long as it's good,
don't waste your time if it's bullshit.
But if you have a longer one, you can always leave a link like in the title as
some people do to like a longer one, but I'm telling you right now, if it's not
good instantly, I will skip it.
Uh, all right.
Anyway, let's try this and see if it works.
Uh, first one, if it works, this is from, Oh, right.
This is just set in the tone for today.
It's a Brad D M garling house.
Uh, who, who could that be?
I wonder go play that.
No, no, no, no, no.
All right.
This can happen.
Okay.
That's all right.
We'll just play them ourselves.
Okay.
Let's play it.
That's fine.
Brad D M garling house.
Here we go.
Count three, one, two, three, go.
You see?
I've come to add the voicemails.
Thanks, Brad.
God, great.
Wait, he just, he just, the beginning of the voicemails.
Oh, shit.
He just takes and takes.
He will, he'll have no satisfaction.
Uh, no.
Okay, give.
That's why we played it first to prove him wrong.
You'll never get us down, Brad D.
I don't care how many M's.
Why did he put the M in here?
What's the D M about?
There's probably like some other thing.
Like obviously it's a one piece.
And that was a one piece sounds, which is good.
But I don't, you don't get the M.
I think we should exclude, I think we should exclusively
refer to bread garlic house in emoji form because I, I was
tweeting, I was tweeting and there's a bread and a garlic
and a house.
That sounds good.
So like we, we should just speak in code.
Like we should never actually type out his name because
like, like Voldemort, he knows whenever his name is mentioned.
You're right.
We need to speak in code with a bread garlic house emoji.
Fantastic.
I love it.
Uh, let's do this.
This is, this is, this is how we're, this is how we're going
to build the resistance.
One loaf at a time.
Uh, all right, let's, let's go to the next one.
I don't know why that, that really got me over.
All right.
Next one.
Okay.
This is good.
This is let's shit on Digi with a moral, a moral is a useful
word that Digi doesn't use.
Right.
All right.
Here we go.
One, two, three, go.
Digi, you don't use the word a moral correctly.
Use it to mean morally bad instead of morally good, but that is
what immoral means.
A moral means that it's not on the moral spectrum, which I think
is a useful term to have.
You could say like sexuality is a moral.
It isn't good or bad.
It just is not even to do with the moral spectrum.
Uh, so yeah.
Start using it right because it's cool.
Take your pick, which side of the fence I fall on.
This guy is technically right.
I don't know whether you would describe sexuality as a, well, it's
like, I don't know.
It's such a, it's like fire, right?
Like fire.
Yeah.
There you go.
That, that would be an, okay.
Burns as bad.
Oh, but what if it's heating my house sexuality?
Sexuality is like a morally good or bad depending on the society
in which you live, but fire is fire.
Yeah.
It just burns.
Uh, there you go.
I don't know.
I, this guy's technically correct, but like, he knows what he means.
So we feel like it's a little bit pedantic to be like, eh, like, I don't
know, did you use all kinds of words wrong?
He definitely does.
Uh, I feel like, but do people actually use the word a moral to
mean like negative?
I mean, I, I always know what he means when he says it in the context
that he says it.
I like this guy's definition.
He's right.
This is a useful word.
And I wish it was used correctly all the time.
I think I like it.
I feel like when someone, you know, honestly, I'm kind of curious.
Um, a moral definition.
I mean, let's look it up.
Okay.
A moral means lacking a moral sense, unconcerned with the rightness
or wrongness of something.
I feel like it's not, I feel like it's not wrong to, okay.
If you, if you say like, oh, uh, like a murder is a moral, I, I, that
would bother me because it's like, okay, when you're saying it has no
morality, but like, I think what you're trying to say is that it is morally
bad, but if you say a person is a moral and it's like, they don't care
what, whether something is right or wrong, like they're a sociopath or
something, probably it would make sense to infer from like, Oh, okay.
So they do things that are morally wrong because they're a moral and they
don't care.
I feel like there's an argument to be made here that using a moral in
that case is not always bad.
Uh, yeah, I guess you're right.
I guess you're right.
Again, this guy is technically correct.
Now for, for the true definition, I went over to urbandictionary.com and the
first two are boring, yawn, don't care.
But the third one, uh, definition of a moral is simply legalized narcotics.
That's the definition of a moral.
Um, fair enough.
All right.
Moving on.
Let's go to our next narcotics legalized.
Narcotics is their third definition.
That's super good.
That's so good for you.
I'm very helped.
All right.
Let's go to the next one.
Uh, adulting question mark.
Uh, all right, let's play this one, two, three, go.
So Nate's definition of adulthood is providing 100% for yourself, paying your
own rent, not living with anyone else, being entirely on your own.
So by that definition is Ben St.
An adult, I mean, on the podcast, at least we've only ever heard tales of him
living with 15 other men in his own squalor, paying as little as possible for
rent and surviving on less than $1,000 a month in a city like fucking Boston,
which how do you even do that, dude?
I'm genuinely curious.
I need these money saving hacks that you're using to survive in that shit
whole city.
Please share.
I am genuinely curious.
And if you have ever provided 100% for yourself, Ben, please share
your experiences.
I'd love to know.
I love Nate's little heartbreak stories and I can relate to it as I've lived
on my own since August 2018 and I love it.
It's the best thing that ever happened to me.
Anyway, thanks for listening, guys.
Hey buddy, come and fight me in real life, huh?
Huh?
What are you, not so, not so tough now.
You're real tough through the computer screen, huh?
We got so, not so tough when you're facing down the barrel of my fist, fucker.
Everybody comes, everybody who comes to my house.
Says, wow, Ben, I expected you to live in like a complete shit hole, but
actually this place is pretty nice.
Like it's pretty, it's, it's true.
It's pretty decent.
Um, uh, well, okay.
He's, he's, he's, I'm so fucking blustered.
I'm so fucking mad.
I don't understand.
I do.
Is this guy being genuine?
I mean, okay.
Is there something wrong with having roommates?
Okay.
Is this such a problem in 2020 in this economy?
The fact that he correlates being an adult with not having roommates.
I mean, Elaine Bennes, the most adult person I've ever known had roommates in
Seinfeld.
Yeah.
I think the thing that he's, I think he's trying to be like, ha ha, jokey jokey.
Let's make fun of Ben because of the fact that he brought up Nate's definition of
being an adult.
Which isn't even my definite, I mean, you know, yeah.
I mean, Ben is an adult because Ben runs his own shit.
That's, that's what being an adult is, you know, yeah, you know.
Thank you.
Like, I don't know.
If you, if you live in a duplex and like, and like you're, you, you live on one side
and another family lives on another.
Are you not, are you not self-sufficient because another family is paying for the
other half of the house?
Um, whatever.
Okay.
No, my shit's, my shit's covered.
My shit's fine.
Okay, but that's the definition.
I am definitely, no, I fucking, I pay for all my own shit.
He does.
So far as I know.
I, yeah, I feel like this guy was trying to make a joke, but I'm like genuinely
offended.
Yeah, I don't, I don't blame you.
But I mean, the, the second half of that, I mean, he said he likes living alone.
It's the best thing that ever happened to him.
Okay, cool.
Great.
I very much agree.
I hate going back to my parents for long periods of time for like one day it can be
fine.
Uh, but, but he wants, he's looking for tips about how to live that.
Uh, what, what's the word?
Alternative lifestyle.
Wait, was he asking me for advice?
There was a part in there.
Yeah, yeah.
Where he wanted to minimize costs and whatnot.
I mean, it's like straight up just like having a bunch of roommates is how I do.
It's like my, I guess that's number one, that's the number one thing.
Surprise, surprise.
You already knew the secret.
Yeah, either, either you live as a child or you die.
That's, that's your two options.
Being, what's more adult than being deceased, you know, like you had your life as a child.
Now it's over.
And, you know, time to, time to move along.
All right, enough of that one.
Oh, and, oh, and never, never eat out, never, never eat pussy, never eat pussy.
It's simp behavior.
It's simpy.
No, never, never eat out, never eat out, cook all, cook all your own food.
That's it, those, those two things.
Buy a giant bag of rice, get a bunch of rice, a bunch of beans and just eat that forever.
Honestly, yeah, it's great.
I mean, yeah, you'll be fine.
You'll be fine.
When I went on, you know, I just ate tons of rice and I was like, this is delicious.
I could eat this every day.
And for a while, I did.
I love rice so much.
It's so delicious.
Oh, wait, no, best money saving tip.
I love Japan, period.
I love curry, I love it.
Okay, the one exception to the never eat out rule.
I'm doing this right now.
Go to five guys, buy some shit.
And then while you wait for your order, just shovel free peanuts into the fucking bag.
Yes.
Right.
I left the way.
I left with the entire cover costs, almost the entire fucking like paper bag
that my order came in, filled with peanuts.
I'm still eating them.
I'm eating them right now.
Fantastic.
It's so good.
Oh, man.
Speaking, I was going to say on rice and all these things.
So that's, that's my secret.
Actually, that's been the main secret.
Yeah.
Five guys change the game.
How do I, Ben, Ben, I love, I love your content.
How do you live such a carefree lifestyle?
My secret free peanuts at five guys.
It's all about those free five guys peanuts.
It's the, it's the basis on which I've built my entire empire.
It makes sense.
I know I've said this a probably a long time ago, but it might as well say it again.
A little known fact, did you guys know that Hawaii is basically Japan too?
That pretty much just is a fact.
You have said that.
Oh, by the way, it's great.
It's where all the Japanese tourists go, right?
Absolutely true.
Actually, you know, Michelle, while we were here, watched the K-On! movie.
It's because Ohio sounds like this is like, ah, it's the Hello Island.
That's, that's Japan three, Ohio.
But wherever I go becomes Japan three, frankly.
Oh, wait, no, Ohio is not Hawaii.
They sound so similar.
It's like Hawaii.
Actually, there is an island called, but it's spelled like weird, you know,
Islander, like K-A-U-A-I or whatever, Hawaii or something like that.
Still epic, but Michelle was here and she watched the K-On! movie.
And she was telling me that like, oh, actually, like all the class,
because like, depending on the class you're in or the, sorry, the club,
because they're in the Light Music Club in K-On!
I'm like, all the, all the Japanese, you know, because of Japanese and K-On!
They all went to Hawaii, which was considered the like, safe vacation place to go
at like, as a graduation thing or whatever.
But like, as a crazy, kooky, spooky one, the Light Music Club girls went to London instead,
where it's not as many Asians.
Yeah, yeah.
Going to Hawaii in Japan.
It's like a four hour flight, by the way, from Japan to Hawaii.
It's like right there.
It's as close as California.
So, yeah, four or five hours, whatever.
As, wait, as close to Japan as California?
Well, Hawaii's in between California and Japan, like right,
right, equidistance or so, yeah.
Hawaii is, oh, oh, yeah, it's an island, Ben.
It's an island.
OK, OK.
It's an ocean.
It's an ocean, Ben.
DeWave, man, DeWave.
And I was going to say that I desperately want to go get both curry and,
oh, I already had a ramen with a little Naruto in it.
It was fucking sick, dude.
Oh, what does Naruto taste like?
They're a little, well, frankly, you always get them in ramen,
so they taste like ramen broth.
It's the fish-paste little cake thing with the spiral on it, yeah?
That's right, but they absorb the flavor, so it is made of fish,
but it just tastes like, you know, the miso soup or whatever you got in there.
But I cannot, I'm going to go get curry, and it's going to be great,
and I can't wait.
If I can divert for a second.
I'm done, I'm done, yeah.
When we were talking about HIPAA, when you brought it up,
when you brought it up that you were watching Bread Tube,
I wanted to say that I was sick and tired and I couldn't,
I wasn't going to take it anymore,
so I've decided to start subtly radicalizing the killers.
So I went to Copkill Town, and I created a separate,
I created a separate channel in Copkill Town
that anyone there can see.
It's called the Radicalization Station, and all it is,
it's just every video that Thought Slime makes.
Because I thought that was pretty on-brand.
So the Radicalization Station is just where you go to watch Thought Slime
and discover that all cops are bad and that we should dissolve the state.
And that's it.
Man, I can't tell you about a time where things didn't improve
when my video games went political.
I can't think of any examples.
It's pure straight up, man.
Unfortunately, it's true.
Endless War has gone political, and it's not fun anymore.
All right.
Oh, I learned one other fun fact that people may be amused by,
which is, you know those famous Hawaiian shirts, Ben,
that you and I wore from Billabong with the flans and all those?
I had so many and so many colors.
They were wonderful. They were wonderful.
Well, so like traditional Hawaiian shirts out here,
they're like, they're like officials will wear them.
They're like actual like uniforms for things,
or they're like considered dressing up or whatever.
Are they the same pattern?
It's hot.
No, all different patterns.
So it's very colorful and all different stuff.
But like I learned the origin of them at some, I don't know,
we were somewhere or something, and there was a sign or whatever
that just said, like, did you know?
I think around a museum or like Pearl Harbor or something
that originally the famous Hawaiian shirts were so the Japanese
like immigrants or whatever came from Japan to Hawaii to look for work.
They work in the fields and stuff.
And their kimonos, which are all different patterns and colors,
they would cut and taper down and pin in place
so that they could work on the plantations.
And it's those like morphed Japanese kimonos
like in this Hawaiian style that became the Hawaiian shirts we know today.
So it's actually a Japanese thing originally.
Fucking weeaboos.
Isn't I know they can't escape them.
Every culture is a whole island of weeaboos.
Just just just just pickable culture is their number one export.
All right, let's do next one.
The truth. You ready for the truth?
No, probably not.
I'm ready. All right.
Here we go. One, two, three, go.
I've done it.
I figured out the big secret of the whole world.
Everything is going to come apart after this.
OK, at least sex isn't real.
I've made twenty five laps around the sun.
I have seen no physical evidence of sex at all.
Babies, the stork.
Yeah, is the actual way babies come from.
Is they're pulling the ball over your eyes when they say it wasn't.
Sex isn't real.
Porn is a whole sci-op by the government.
Yeah.
There's no other way to explain it.
How could I, after twenty five years, not have had sex?
It was the only way. It's got to be fake.
Yeah, I guess.
Holy shit.
Good logic.
I mean, I mean, even if sex was real,
I don't know why we have to bring babies in because I've seen correlation
between like people having sex and babies, but like I haven't seen a causal link.
It's not there. It's not there.
Yeah, yeah, it's, you know, you do you sleep you sleep in the same bed
with a woman and then an angel comes and, you know,
they talk to the woman about something and you something happens.
Tell you what, the truth.
Why don't you bring me your girlfriend or your mother
and we will try to figure out this causal link.
Just the two of us will see what happens.
Oh, won't that be?
Oh, you cut out.
Did you say your girlfriend or and or mother?
I did. I did.
These are the two options on the table.
That's how you do it.
No age is too ageing.
All right. Next, we got four, Nick, eight.
OK, all right. Here we go.
One, two, three, go.
A, B, C, B, A.
So the dating sim is being released this week.
Oh, my God, that's right.
I'm an undecided dator from Nevada.
I still don't know if I should date Tom or Digi or Brad
or maybe I'm just better off being a meek towel.
Why should I date you specifically?
What's your position on gay marriage?
Personally, I don't want to date
candidate that supports it.
It goes against my founding principles,
right, liberty, having a small government and sucking a dick.
When you over PCP, Pete, 20, make my heart flutter,
make my mind explode and make my soul yours.
Right. Now, this guy's got a winning attitude.
I'm happy to pursue his vote.
Yeah, like, um, Valentine's Day is the what, the 14th?
The 14th, five days away from a recording.
So that'll be out.
No, that is coming out the day.
The day, when you hear this, it will be out.
Holy Christ.
It will have, I mean, unless something fucks,
unless they fuck it, unless it's shadow incorporated,
like causes like deliberate app failure.
Yeah, part of Valentine's Day and Valentine's Day gets canceled.
Valentine's Day will get replaced with Valentine's Day.
And it's going to be a nightmare for this guy, if no one else.
So yeah, it should be out
right now, as you hear my voice.
Yeah, how exciting?
You should, you should not.
Lincoln the doobly-do.
You should not go for me.
No, I don't want anyone to fuck me.
Reverse psychology, right?
I also don't want, I honestly, I don't want anyone to fuck me.
Please don't.
Okay, I don't know this for sure.
I don't consent.
Hey, hey, viewers, I'm saying right now that I do not consent.
Oh, Lord.
Hey, do you guys know?
I wonder what he means by that.
Dating sims come in all stripes and all sizes and shapes.
Is there sex in this?
Like, are there sex scenes?
Because that's a pretty clean divide between dating scenes.
I have not heard of any actual, like even implied sex scenes.
But yeah, I mean, there could be.
But I have no actual evidence.
I don't know who would have drawn them.
I mean, I'm very curious.
The absence of evidence of sex is not evidence of the absence of sex.
Very, very true.
It is evidence of abstinence.
Well, I mean, maybe there is sex, but it's behind.
You have to, like, hack into the mainframe and, like,
and, like, re-remove some, like, some, like, code or something.
Yeah, a.k.a. open the folder of all the images in the look.
Or maybe you have to, you know, pledge to the silver or gold tiers
on their, you know, PCP dating sim Patreon in order to get the exclusive.
I've seen some shit like that.
Oh, it makes me mad.
Oh, I don't like it.
Oh, I'm filled with fury.
But hopefully not.
Maybe they maybe they did, like, funny censor bars that don't.
There is nothing under this.
I mean, there's plenty of room.
I don't know.
There's plenty of room for comedic sex scenes that aren't, like,
you know, actually porn.
I don't care either way.
I will experience whatever happens.
They make you laugh, but they're still fucking hot, though.
Hell, yeah, that's that's the idea.
It'll be all in text, like, and then the sex happens.
Ooh, unga, bunga.
By my cat's rays.
And they got, like, like the version of the avatar with the glasses,
like, slightly tilted, like, and the hair ruffled.
That sounds great.
I hope that happens.
I guess we'll see.
All right, anyway, go check it out.
I believe it's at PCP dating.
I think it's at, I think it's at PSB Day.
We'll put a link down below.
Let me make absolutely sure.
Okay, okay, yes, please.
Take a pause.
Yeah, because there was another one.
The joke one.
Yeah, it is, yeah, PCP dating.
At PSB dating on Twitter.
You can definitely get it there on the day.
So be prepared.
We will, all right.
Do they have any updates?
I haven't checked.
Do you see anything there?
I assume you're looking at that.
On Jan, a week ago, they tweeted, hold on to your butts.
PCP dating sims script.
Okay.
They released the script.
There's a picture of the script.
Oh, the giant text dump.
Like, that's gotta be like 200 pages, 100, 200 something.
Yeah, that's a lot of tech.
Why would you print that out?
They've been a little quiet.
Their last tweet was on January 30th.
Well, can-
Maybe it was already nearly done.
They got nothing to say.
Maybe, maybe.
Maybe they're just, maybe they're just cranking.
I mean, it's gonna be too late when we hear this.
But certainly on the day you hear this, everybody,
I'm sure they'll listen to this episode.
It looks as though that hopes so.
One of them, likely too.
Let us know at TP Crasnairs, at least once.
We'll make sure we get the word out, if we forget,
because it's on Friday, so it might be.
It's gonna be Aloha Friday.
So that's gonna be a day to take it sleazy
like the Democratic Party.
All right, next one.
Let's listen to Brad is a god.
Let's say that name.
All right, here we go.
Brad is a god.
One, two, three, go.
I quickly wanna thank Brad Garlinghouse,
my lord and savior, Brad, for allowing me
and my poor, poor fellows to listen to the BGE Montel cast.
Oh, god.
It was really nice of him.
He's really turning the channel around.
It's giving it a new life.
Thank you, Brad, and fuck you, Nate.
This guy sounds like a guy in his turn.
Brad Garlinghouse is for the people.
He is one of the good billionaires.
He is redistributing the wealth he has taken.
Did you know that 1% of the best guy ever listeners
have access to 99% of the content of the Patreon exclusive?
Not anymore, baby.
They power to the people.
Brad is a fucking hardcore right-wing populace.
Everyone will listen to these podcasts,
and then we will get the Jews somewhere.
Not saying they're there.
Don't worry about it.
Well, what was I gonna say?
Remember that website we discovered?
Maybe I shouldn't talk about it, but who gives a fuck?
There was a website that their purpose and being
was to make all paywall-blocked content,
like non-paywall-blocked,
and they had uploaded every PCP bonus episode and stuff.
Yes, yes.
I don't remember what it was called,
but I know that there are things like that.
Yeah, me neither, me neither.
Look, that's fine.
I mean, whatever.
Hope people support if they like the show and all that,
but I wonder if that's been done.
We all have basically, all of us,
have our pay-off-treatment-only podcast
that we're doing now.
Actually, it's funny because I'm not gonna say anything,
but the Slime and Punishment finale images
that I've been uploading,
I think Christine would have an opinion about them,
and part of me wonders if some troll,
if some Pee Wee Farm's troll or other
isn't gonna like pledge 10 bucks, get them,
and then like post them early,
be like, Christine, look at this.
Honestly, I don't know if, I mean it would be interesting.
I sure hope you don't pledge the money.
I sure hope somebody doesn't give me $10
to get access to this exclusive juicy content
that would surely cause an incredible stir.
And that's just me.
I hear you lifelong to Christine Weston Chandler, no doubt.
Making her subject to any and all trolls
that may be a concoct of nature.
I sure hope there's no one around
looking to stir the pot a little bit.
You might not have some extra change lying around.
God, that sounds fantastic.
All right, moving on, let's go to Red Orange's
big boy, AKA Long JJ or Jelly Bean.
That's good.
Those are all his names, I guess.
All right, let's hear it.
One, two, three, go.
Nate, I've heard that you like grapefruits.
Yeah, true.
There's this new thing called Red Oranges.
Yeah.
They're oranges and grapefruits combined.
They're so fucking good.
Don't show this on the podcast.
I just wanted you to know.
Too late, fuck you, dude.
I'm playing on the podcast.
Okay, this guy's a fucking moron, okay?
Let me tell you all about it.
Fuck this guy.
Fuck you and your grapefruits.
Okay, first of all, Red Oranges,
no, they're called Blood Oranges,
and they're not across between...
There's a different thing.
Maybe this is a new thing.
I don't know.
There's no, I just googled it.
There's no such thing as a...
A red orange.
Wait, okay, a blood orange, it's a natural, okay.
It's a natural mutation of an orange,
which is itself a hybrid,
probably between the pomelo and the tangerine.
Okay, so, yeah, blood orange is not half grapefruit.
You fucking idiot.
He didn't say blood oranges were,
he's talking about red.
He said red, but there's no such thing.
There's no such thing as a red orange.
Okay, fair enough.
He seemed to be implying that they're new,
so maybe they're local or some, I don't know.
Maybe it was at his local farmer's market,
and some guy there.
If he's talking about blood oranges,
we've known about them for years.
Dexter ate one every fucking episode.
Is that true?
Yeah, yeah, the opening sequence to Dexter ate a blood orange.
I was thinking of Dexter's laboratory.
It was supposed to be evocative, you understand,
because he's a blood orange.
We'll see, I was thinking Dexter's laboratory,
so that was the...
Oh, no, it was the computer.
And that's wrong.
He ate those because of his ginger hair.
Makes him really smart, yeah.
Makes sense.
That apparently is a cross between a grapefruit and an orange.
It's called an orangello.
Okay, I think I've heard of that.
I've heard of that.
This guy had an alternate name that was jellybean
and an orange-yellow-y-bean?
Orange-yellow is a hybrid citrus fruit,
believed to have originated in Puerto Rico,
the fruit across between a grapefruit and an orange.
Okay.
That's funny, because an orange is a cross
between a pomelo and a tangerine.
Well, all right, look, all this is grape gnaw.
So then you take a pomelo and a tangerine cross,
that was a grapefruit, and then you get an orange-ello.
Well, actually, no, I think a grapefruit
is also a pomelo hybrid.
Blood orange, zero.
So I guess, yeah, you are doubling up on the pomelo.
Okay, listen, none of this matters,
because his main point here.
You get a strawberry and a carrot,
and you get something that you don't want.
You get rhubarb.
Yeah, you probably do.
Listen, this guy's like, oh, I've solved it.
I combined the orange with the grapefruit.
What?
No, I love this shit.
Yeah, a grapefruit is a cross,
an accidental cross between a sweet orange and a pomelo.
So an orange is a tangerine pomelo.
A grapefruit is an orange pomelo,
so it's a tangerine pomelo-pomelo.
Wait, what the hell's a pomelo?
So it's just two parts pomelo, one part tangerine,
and that's a grapefruit.
And then so you cross them.
With an orange.
I've never heard it as pomelo before.
You just get like five sixths of pomelo,
one part tangerine, and you call that an orange-ello.
Wow, I guess it makes sense, kind of.
Okay, I had never heard of a pomelo until right now.
I have had a pomelo, they are not good.
No.
Okay, okay.
But, I think a pomelo is, imagine a grapefruit,
but like, it's like huge, it's like massive,
like football size, but you open it up,
and like most of it is just rind.
Like most of it is just like white fluffy rind
that you throw away.
Yeah, I've seen that.
And then there's about a regular amount of grapefruit,
of like grapefruit-ish flesh in the middle,
and you eat it, and it just doesn't taste like anything.
It's like grapefruit, but like bigger,
with less edible part, and tastes worse.
Here's a cross-section, yeah, look at all that.
That's a waste, that's too much fluff.
I mean, I kind of love it, aesthetically, but.
I have heard that, like, I've heard, I don't know,
there's, I guess people use it in like vodka or something,
like it has its uses, but like,
I don't think many people eat it,
cause like it doesn't taste that great to just eat.
Okay, so it was a tangerine cross with a pomelo
that made oranges or something?
Apparently an orange is a tan, no, the orange,
this one says the orange is a hybrid
between a pomelo and mandarin.
Okay, AKA a mandarin orange.
I'm getting conflicted reports here.
Okay, you know what?
I'm going to spit all these fucking fruits.
I am way into all this.
This is fascinating.
But the point I was gonna make here.
I love this shit, I love this shit.
Listen, his original point was like,
Nate, you know, you love grape, I do love grapefruits.
It's true, I'm a huge fan of grapefruit.
It's better than oranges, fuck oranges.
Me too, I was the original, I liked it first.
I mean, I'm sure that's true, I'm sure that's true.
I'm out here, Ben likes it first cause he's oldest.
I'm out here standing for my man, the grapefruit.
Shout outs to grapefruit, by the way.
Shout outs to grapefruit, dude.
Every fucking time.
Why is it called grapefruit?
It's so big compared to a grapefruit.
I'm speed running, like Bikini Bottom.
I'm fucking no clipping through the floor
to get to a grapefruit.
Bikini Bottom, I say, shout outs to grapefruit
for powering this one.
Bro, you know, anyone remember that kid
who no clipped through the floor
to get to the snack drawer faster
to get his precious grapefruits,
like coming home from elementary school every day?
That was me, I admit it, it was me.
I was speed running in a big way.
Look.
God, I remember no clipping at school.
Because I was clipping through the bathroom stall
when someone else was inside.
And rolling out of class.
The blood orange page says that the orange
is a hybrid between pomelo and tangerine.
But the orange page says that the orange
is a cross between pomelo and mandarin,
which I guess is called mandarin orange,
but it is not the same as a sweet orange,
which is what we call an orange here.
It's all fucked up.
I guess their factions are at war
about the true history, I don't know.
My friend, my roommate has a tree.
Oh, the sad story of the calamundan tree,
which he called a scarlet lime.
But calamund, he called it scarlet limes,
but I think it's actually more commonly called
the Philippine lime.
I think a scarlet lime is actually something different,
but it is these, they're like limes,
but I guess they turn orange,
but they're still very tart when they,
but he's got this potted tree.
And it, one year, last year in like the spring,
it flowered and it smelled so good.
It was like such a sweet smelling,
like nice smelling flowering tree.
It was like really great.
But then, I guess it got put in the wrong place,
like the weather turned bad at the wrong time or something,
and it lost all of its, it died.
But not entirely though.
So now, so he had to cut basically the entire tree down,
and it just sprouted like one little leaf
from the side of the little foot-long stick
sticking out of the dirt pot.
But now it has kind of grown like a little bit more.
It's like, it's not quite a bush,
but it's sort of like a little bunch of leaves
just kind of coming out the bottom of this one like stick.
And like, boy, I'm rooting for it.
I really hope it flowers again.
Were they green or were they orange?
Okay, because it was not, yeah.
Well, if it's like fully mature, they look like that.
It only sprouted like one lime,
and it did not fully mature.
So it never turned orange.
It had like one actual like fruit on it,
and it was green because it did not like fully mature.
Sure, sure.
Well, listen, this guy's point was that I got a genius idea.
He got to smell him.
At some point in your life,
he got to smell the flowers of a calamandan.
To respond? Or a calamansi, I guess it's also called.
Who the fuck was it?
Red oranges who didn't want me to play this voicemail,
but I did it anyway.
He's like, I'll defuse a grapefruit in an orange.
It'll be like a grapefruit, but the size of an orange.
Why the fuck would I want a grapefruit
the size of an orange when I could just take
a normal big grapefruit, which is just more fruit?
Why would anyone want that?
Would you have a grapefruit as bigger?
Retarded, I like that they're bigger.
It's so much better that they're bigger.
I hate how small oranges are.
The main reason I don't eat oranges
is because it's so much work for less fruit
than a grapefruit.
It makes me mad.
I wonder if an orange yellow is good.
I'm sure it's acceptable.
I don't know, maybe not.
I'll give it a shot.
Okay, give it a shot.
What about a lemon?
Get the fuck out of here with that.
All right, let's go to our next one.
All right, these are peas in a pot.
I mean, apparently an orange yellow
is just like sweeter than a grapefruit,
so I guess it's just like right in between, I guess.
I prefer grapefruit to orange,
so I would probably just rather go
for a fucking grapefruit.
Yeah, obviously we're not these cowards.
We're talking about who put sugar on the grapefruit.
Like idiots, it doesn't need it.
Oh my God, oh well.
They should kill themselves, it's retarded.
They're so good.
What is wrong with these people?
Who fuck with a delicious grapefruit like that?
All right.
Waste of a good fruit.
It's like turning it into a fucking pie.
Like, okay, I guess that's fine, but whatever.
All right.
Waste of a good fruit, I tell you what.
It is.
Man, I got at the local farmer's market,
I got some, or one of my friends got some
grapefruit marmalade.
Okay, sounds good.
It's really good.
It was really good.
I gotta tell you.
I'm glad to hear it.
All right, let's go to the next one.
That's all I had to say about that.
Next, voicemail.
All right, here we go.
This is the Lost Tape Archive,
Lost Tapes Archive Interlude.
This was sent special.
This is one of these long ass messages
that was sent with the link.
So, let's, well this one isn't a lot,
but all right, let's play it.
Here we go.
One, two, three, go.
Previously on Lost Tapes Archives.
There it is.
Lost Tape Archive, DeVoo?
Question mark?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Jesus.
Horrific.
I think that was a war crime.
For this crime, he's putting straight into voice jail.
Can he exist in a superposition of jail and?
The voice Azkaban.
Voice Limbo.
Yeah, I think he exists in both simultaneously.
Torn between two worlds.
Continue in part two.
Wow.
What did he even, I do not remember what he did
to get into.
That was just a recap.
That's right.
No, what he did was he did the Lost Tapes
and it was all about DeVoo's fetishes.
Oh, was it?
Extreme and it was like, ooh, ooh.
Okay, thank God.
I had also forgotten.
So I'm glad he reminded me.
Me too.
Me too, one of these rare reviews I'm happy to see.
I needed to be caught up on the lore, yeah.
All right, well, let's jump into it.
Them's tapes, number two.
Let's do it.
One, two, three, go.
I am Trent in a void.
There is no life, no food,
and no tapes.
That's no good.
If I could make the PCP laugh,
they might set me free,
but without any tapes,
how can be?
Can I be in his voicemail?
Yeah.
Them snakes.
What?
I was once a snake dealer,
but I can be your tape dealer too.
How are you here?
There's no ground to slither on.
The method is irrelevant.
I have a tape and I am here.
If only we had a cassette player to play it with.
Do not worry, my slippery, snakey fuck.
I have a cassette player built into my fucking face.
Put it in, big boy.
Greetings.
My name is Ben's Taint.
I am a big smelly Taint
in the shape of a human.
Shut up.
A true walking keto crotch.
I draw pictures.
I spew poo.
BRB, I use blue.
No, turn it off.
Listen, buddy, I don't think this is gonna cut it.
We already did Ben's Taint.
Besides, I can tell it's you.
It's not my fault that all them snakes and personators
sound the same.
You'll need to awaken your a Kundalini
if you wish to find the funny fucking tapes.
I can provide them if I can find them.
To please the PCP, to be set free.
The only payment is entertainment.
Ooh, ooh, it's cool.
So, PCP, do you agree?
I agree.
The only payment is entertainment.
Yes.
I mean, it's yes, true.
That's good.
That's good stuff.
That's good stuff in there.
I hope you don't expect to be let out
of superposition voice jail.
I mean, he himself acknowledged that tape
was some bullshit.
We need, we gotta step it up.
Yeah, I can't remember the tape.
I don't think he's done me yet.
I don't think so.
And now he's done Ben twice.
No, no, he did you, he did everybody, didn't he?
I don't think he did everybody.
I can't remember.
He was in the process of doing everybody.
Someone let us know.
I know he did, Digi and Jesse and you and Ben.
Yeah, right, right.
I don't know if he did Munchy or not.
I think Tom, yeah, I don't think he did Munchy.
Okay, well, we shall see.
I do not remember.
But I know one thing.
Please, please in the comments, point to the time codes
of the episodes and we'll have a look.
Make a YouTube collaboration.
Highlight video, yeah, of all of them's tapes.
Just do that for me please, that would be great.
Yeah, or at least tell us who.
Put it in the comments, say who's been done.
I would love to be reminded.
I am excited for more of them's tapes to come.
Please, God, bring them to me, deliver them.
And save this voicemail from Brad Garlinghouse's
devious attempts to ruin all voicemails
by sending in pure shit voicemails
as I'm sure he's responsible for all the bad ones.
If we just taint the PCP brand enough,
you'll have to relinquish the channel.
It'll become a liability.
It'll be such a liability, yeah.
Now that's a plan that can't fail.
Well, I guess that's it.
Hey, hey, you wanna leave voicemails?
That was epic, that was great.
Them snakes, yes, star, them's tapes, good job.
Hey, leave your epic voicemail
at the Speak Pipe link down in the description.
Do it up, we're waiting for them.
What else is going on?
We got Patreon people, patreon.com slash the procrastinators.
Support this show for a couple of dollar
reduced on there per episode.
$5 and you get the bonus episodes.
The new one is already out.
Talk about comics and whatnot, good time.
And there's like 34, 35, something like that.
What a deal, incredible, you're welcome.
Updates for all things that are happening on Twitter
at TPCrastinators on Twitter.
I would again, highly recommend you follow that
because when we make a new channel
or get our channel back,
that's gonna be the place to keep our SP out.
That's where we'll announce whatever it is.
I mean, you can follow me at Best Discover.
I'm also discussing these things, Ben at BenSaint
or he's at also ugly.
Follow me on Twitter at patreon.com slash BenSaint.
Any of us, we're letting people know as fast as we can.
And of course, the RadCon Kickstarter
is going on right now.
And when you hear this, you'll have just a couple more days.
It's like, wait, wait, hold on.
Five days from now.
If the day that it ends will be like one, two, three,
four, five, it'll be the Tuesday
or it'll like the Monday or like Monday or Tuesday.
Yeah.
Yeah, after, so like this weekend is it.
That's right, this weekend.
That's it.
The 18th, I mean like the 17th, the 18th.
I think it's gonna end like the morning of the 18th
because it like went live on like the morning of the 18th,
like 31 days before or whatever, so.
Well, so really the 17th is the last full day.
I think Monday night.
Yeah, pretty much.
Whatever, the point this weekend is it.
That's your last fucking chance.
Yep, so hey, we got tons of good stuff on there.
And now that all our fucking tiers have been fulfilled
except for Digi's, Light Novel's still going for those.
We are close to the Brad lecture.
And then after that, we've got the Digi's.
The higher chapters are still waiting.
Yeah, of Road to RadCon 4.
That's the one.
Should we make a new one like an intermediary
like for like 75?
I see no reason why not.
Fuck it, let's do it.
Maybe we should think about that.
Yeah, let's think about it.
Okay, well, let's think about it.
We might even add more stretch goals, don't know.
Check it out.
But right now, we've got 224 backers,
eighties to go, 176% funded, 14,659.
That's like, I think it's like $100 from when we started.
So we're just like 300 and change away
from the Brad Garlinghouse lecture,
but there's more stuff beyond it.
So check back when you see this.
There may be updates added to it.
So how exciting for all of us.
RadCon's coming up no matter what.
None's gonna stop RadCon, baby.
So hey, if you wanna donate, you got, let's see.
T-shirts, pins, you got the calendar.
If you pledge $100, you'll be in the fucking PTA,
making decisions, participating in live streams,
part of the Discord, et cetera.
If you go to that $200 tier, oh my God,
you get the fucking to be part of the art,
part of the cast members of the RadCon art.
On the posters, that will be sent out to everybody.
You'll be immortalized for all time.
If you wanna be a mad lad, you can be in the Royal Rumble.
Like two people already have been.
So hey, consider it.
I should say, there's the dark,
have we talked about the dark champion?
How like the $200 patrons,
they will collectively build a Royal Rumble.
That's right.
Attendee, do we have, I don't know.
There's like a whole bunch of like weird shit in the reward.
Yeah, read through, read through.
It's good stuff, it's good stuff.
That's a good one, yeah, we didn't talk about it.
But like the $1,000 guys,
they get their own individual champion.
But at the end.
Yeah, that represents them all collectively.
They're attempt to subvert the caucus with Shadow Inc.
Shadow the Hedgehog Inc.
My favorite guy.
All right, well, that's it for the episode everybody.
We'll be back again next week.
I will be back from vacation
and we'll do this whole nightmare all over again.
See you there everybody.
Bye.
Later.
Save the PCP, hashtag.
Save the PCP, tweet him up.
Hashtag it.