Man, fuck school. Fuck school. I don't even know what these guys fucking said about fucking
school, but... Man, my fucking experience with school sucked ass. School's the reason
I wasn't able to be on this fucking podcast. That's why I'm doing this stupid, faggy record
by myself down in the fucking basement like a piece of shit thing. So this isn't even
gonna fucking... I'm not even able to know what the fuck anyone was saying. I'm recording
this fucking like a week after everybody else fucking did it. And it's all school's
fault. All right, so fucking... I mean, I'm not even like too pissed off about it anymore.
If this was like three or four years ago, I'd still be salty as fuck, but now I'm just
kind of like fucking disappointed. School just seems like such a waste of time, a waste
of effort, and most importantly, a waste of fucking money. And there was so little preparation,
so little understanding of what college in particular... I'm assuming we're talking about
school, we're talking about college, we're talking about high school as well. I think
high school's a necessary evil, but it's desperately in need of some sort of reform. Remember to
be a little bit more effective. I think education as a whole, like, even needs to decide we're
gonna go for like the fucking like, you know, classic Greek Academy style of school where
you're actually trying to elevate people to be the most intelligent they can be, or we're
going to say, fuck it, school isn't for intel intelligence, it's for preparing people for
the workforce, in which case we need to understand that school needs to be more specialized because
people's careers are specialized and we're wasting so much time doing all this fucking
bullshit, like, 80% of it we're never gonna use in our vocations. So we need to decide
just in general what we need to do with school, but that's neither here nor there. I'm gonna
rant about how much I fucking hate school. I don't know, I just, I guess maybe that does
kind of lead into my experience with school is that so much of my time spent in college
was doing classes that I had no interest in, and have zero application in my life today.
And the same thing can be said with high school. I think, you know, elementary school, middle
school, and even to an extent high school, a lot of the subjects that you do in school
are very much necessary, you know, to create just sort of the basic core education of a
human being. But I think a lot of the stuff, I should probably turn the second sound off.
Wow, my phone and my fucking, all of you shut up, all of you fucking shut up. I'm trying
to be intelligent and you're ruining it. God, turn off none. No, no, don't bother me.
What was I even saying? There's so much of school that is done almost like for the sake
of dick wagging than like actual application, you know, like I, I went to school for graphic
design. I guess I'm an artist by trade quote unquote, in terms of what my education should
be and we can get into that later. But I had to take like all this math shit that I'm never
used, you know, even like high school math, like nobody ever fucking uses it. It's really
interesting because I took you take all these math classes. And then I have the interesting
perspective of like reflecting on that. Because I have a younger sister who's you know, I'm
27. She is 14 right now. So there's 10 years sort of difference. You know, I can kind of
see her going through all this shit in high school that I did. And then my dad and like
me having to help her with math homework and all this shit, and just like asking about
all this math things that none of us use, nobody uses any of this shit. And that kind
of goes back to where I'm saying about specialization, like if you're going to go into math, like
if you want to be a mathematician, and like who really fucking knows what they want to
do in high school, right? But but let's say, let's say for shit and giggles, you did, you
know, that would be important. But there's there's practical math that were never taught
in school. And this is why I think like the whole kind of like romantic, you know, Greek
Aristotelian Academy kind of school is just not even true anymore. Because if you wanted
to really empower people, if school was really a way to educate you, and make you a well
rounded person, why don't we have more practical skills? Like why don't we learn how to balance
a checkbook? Why don't we learn about, you know, taxation and tax laws and how we can
you want to take math, like let's let's learn how to balance your budget. Like that's
something that everybody in the fucking world needs to do is like, understand, let's have
classes on how debt works, how fucking, you know, applications of interest work, how bank
works, how you taking a loan and things like that, like practical math, if I need to sit
there and learn math, I want to learn math that I'm going to use in my life. And school
doesn't do that. You know, we have like this we've romanticized the STEM fields, but at
the same time, such a small percentage of the world actually uses STEM field knowledge
long term, but we hammer away that and make it so much more important, you know, and at
the same time, we kind of poo poo on the arts and stuff. And like that's always the first
thing to get budget cuts. But I think a lot more people, you know, or maybe not a lot
more, but just as many people would go into the arts, they wouldn't do STEM fields, but
the STEM field is so much more fucking grandiose, and it's sort of like position. But from a
culture perspective, we don't really we ignore STEM fields, and we, you know, fucking rock
stars and movie stars and shit. So the arts is respected culturally, but not intellectually.
And that's kind of weird. I would say it's definitely harder to be a scientist or a
mathematician or a physicist than it is to fucking play music or anything. But there
are two different kind of applications, and they take two different kind of mindsets.
I'm fucking going all over the place. But school fucked me over. Because I think there's
a lot of pressure, at least there wasn't my house to go to school, to continue my education,
even when I wasn't sure if I even wanted to do that. I knew when I was a little kid that
I wanted to do storytelling in some fashion. And I always fancied myself an artist, even
though I wasn't really good. And that's kind of the weird thing is that nobody in my house
would just even to this day, no one has the fucking balls to say, Look, Tom, you're not
that fucking good. And so I know I'm not that good. But no one else will allow me to function
under that kind of mentality of that I'm not good. So I was forced in my house to pursue
art as a career, because that was something I'm interested in, even though I wasn't sure
at the time, it was something I wanted to do. I knew I liked it. I knew I enjoyed drawing.
But I knew I wasn't good at it. But I wasn't good at anything else either. Like I was good
at playing Devil May Cry and drawing shitty comics. And that was it. So I really don't
have anything in terms of like applicable life skills. So I guess to some terrified
parents looking at their 18 year old son, who did nothing but play PlayStation and draw
terribly like the no eSports weren't a thing. So they couldn't funnel me into that nowhere
they probably want to. So I was the only thing they had to do. So I started applying to a
bunch of colleges for art and they all rejected me because I wasn't fucking good. And I knew
I wasn't fucking good. And so what I wanted to do is I wanted to take a year off of school
and just like work on my portfolio. Like if this is what I'm going to do, you know, I
guess I should work on my portfolio and maybe like figure out if this is even what I want
to do with my life because I don't fucking know like I'm a retarded kid. I all I did
to play PlayStation for like seven years straight. Like I don't fucking know what I want to do
with my future. But you know, the parents wouldn't let me do that. You know, they threatened
to like, you know, kick me out if I didn't go to school because they knew they're like
we're all fucking study show that if you don't go to school right at high school, you never
go. It's like, Well, maybe because those people realize it's not for them. But I never got
the chance to do that. So I ended up going to a really shitty school just because I kept
getting rejected from all these schools I was actually interested in. But the one school
I was really wanted to go to was the Center for Cartoon Studies in Vermont, which is a
two year program for learning how to do comics, which is like the thing I was really interested
in. And it was right in Vermont, there's only like a couple of states over. So it wouldn't
be that far away from here. And like, I was like really gung ho about that. That was like
the one time during my senior year of high school that I was really interested in like
college was like, I will continue my education. This sounds cool. Like this sounds like
something I would be interested in. But the one time I showed interest, the parents had no
interest because they were just like, this is comics, you're never going to get a job with
this is stupid, we're not going to cosine loans on this. So don't bother applying. And I guess
loans lead you to the fucking money aspect of it. I'm $40,000 in debt. I got a terrible
education because I went to a shitty school that I didn't want to go to. And I went to
school for graphic design in 2007, which was probably the worst year to go into that fucking
field because in 2007, the iPhone launched and the iPhone changed the entire design landscape
because it went from shifted from print and web being two separate things to like everything
being web based everything being app based and because everything became app based and
the web exploded in terms of complexity, designers also have to be programmers now. If you want
to get a design job, you have to do all of the graphic stuff, all the layout stuff, but you
also have to be able to code websites and code and WordPress. And you had to do both
disciplines, but I was running on 2007 level education and curriculum. So by the time I
graduated, I could do print stuff, no problem. But like 2011, the iPhone four s was coming
out. The smartphone craze was in full swing and the industry was completely different. I was
completely unprepared for it. And to top that off, I was supposed to I did some internships
at my dad's place, he worked at Hanscom Air Force Base, and I was supposed to start doing
design work there. But two weeks before I graduated, they cut the program. And so I had no
job. So I wasn't looking for a job. So school just kind of fucked me over. So now I'm 40k
in debt. And all I can do is make YouTube videos that I don't even like doing, because
that's all I can do to make money. And I didn't get a good education because I couldn't get
into a good school because I wasn't good at the thing I was actually passionate about. I was
not allowed the time to get good at it, to get into a good school. And I probably wouldn't
even have gone to school anyways, because I've always wanted to be kind of an internet
entrepreneur, because that's the thing I kind of grew up doing was watching YouTube playing
video games, and drawing shitty little comics. So I just got kind of forced on the stupid
fucking path that I didn't want to do. And I've just kind of come to resent school as
a result. It just it fucking sucks. It sucked for me, you know, I just feel like I think
too many people go to school because you're supposed to, when so many people probably
don't. And I think even now with the fucking economy, the way it is, doesn't even matter
anymore. Does it's like school worth it? I think if you're going into a STEM field, school
is definitely worth it because the returns there are still big. You know, especially
if you're a woman trying to get into a STEM field, you got a fucking golden ticket right
there, you know, that feed that field starving for women, you're going to get into school,
no problem, you get, you know, bonuses and like fucking scholarships and whatever to
get into school. And like, it's going to more than pay off because those fields are hugely
fucking, you know, the salaries for those are massive. But like, if you're an artist,
if you're a creative, like, do you really need to go to school now? I think even now,
like you look on shit like LinkedIn and you look at like artist profiles, like people
judge you by your portfolio more than anything else. If you can fucking sit, stay, stay at
home or stay, you know, just go live on your own, work a shitty job and just grind out
a fucking beast portfolio, you can probably land a job somewhere at a smaller design firm
or a smaller company doing graphics work, or doing websites or whatever. And your experience
will build your portfolio and your resume at that point, and you never need to fucking
go into debt in the first place. This industry is evolving at such a fast pace, especially
now that it just seems ridiculous to go into that much debt for a field that like is mostly
freelance now, so you're never really going to get benefits. And even if you do that,
it doesn't pay that much shit doesn't really pay that high. So I don't know, man, like
I just feel like everything I did in relation to school is a mistake from just like not
paying attention in high school and not learning that shit to going into fucking college, even
though I knew I really didn't want to and I wasn't ready going into a field that I knew
I wasn't good enough for but everyone else wouldn't let me believe that for the sake
of my views, even though I was the only one being realistic. So and then I just feel like
school in general is caught in this weird middle ground of like wanting to be kind of
this Aristotelian greatness sort of thing, but also understanding that it's really just
designed to fucking have people like make good grades, fucking good do good on SAT scores,
so schools can get fucking more funding, and just prepare them for a fucking menial job
that 90% of their graduates are going to eventually fall into just because that's the way the
world works. So I don't know if this fucking fits with the podcast at all. Maybe it was
kind of depressing, but that's my thoughts on school. Nate, have fun figuring out where
this is supposed to fucking go. Hello and welcome to this week's episode of the pro
crest and natives podcast here. Once again is me and all my buddies. I'm the best guy
ever bestie boy.
We got the 21st century digital boy Digi bro over here. We got patron. Oh, he's still
going. Patreon.com slash Ben St. Patreon.com slash Ben St. That's that that meme ain't
going anywhere. And we have the Davoo collective. What's up, buddy? Every nuclear bomb has a
silver lining depending on the inflation rates. Yeah, Hiroshima has some really great
earthworms now. All right, so thanks for joining us again. Once again, folks, and we're here
to talk about a topic that, oh man, the passions are running so high in here. Some of us have
a healthy relationship with this. Most of us do not. I know, and it is. No, go on, go
on. Okay, I'm just going to say it is, in fact, a schooling with a particular emphasis,
I think on higher education, but we'll touch on the whole system. Let me let me just let
me just say, sure. We know a lot of our viewers are younger. We have some we have, you know,
some high school age viewers, I think, and to all those ones who might be wondering about
their future and wondering what direction in life they should take. Let me just say,
don't listen to your parents. Don't listen to your guidance, counselors and religious
authorities. Listen to this now. Yeah, this is the real deal. We've had real life experience.
All those religious authorities in your life, they all come from a previous generation before
this system got to be unbelieved. That is very true. We are all from your guys' generation.
We know what's up. I mean, I'm not me personally, but these guys do. I was being partially satirical.
Well, you can take it at your own risk. We are not professionals. You follow our advice
at your own risk, but here's my general advice, guys. I do not think that it is super beneficial
to go for a general education sort of thing. I would highly recommend you have a specific
plan in place with, like, action points there so you can guide yourself to what you're going
to do and go to, like, a community college. And hopefully by the time, you know, you guys
are rolling into a school, maybe a fucking... I don't recommend any of that. I don't recommend
any of that. I don't recommend you don't fucking go to school. Don't do it.
That's the best plan. That's the best plan. There is no chaos. Just don't go to fucking
school. All right. Well, it depends what you want to do. If you want to be a fucking, you
know, nurse or whatever, you got to go to school, but whatever. Like, okay, let's get
into our anecdotal stories here. Who wants to go first? Ben, let's hear about your relationship
with schooling. Well, fuck, it's complicated. I'll try to condense it as much as I can.
So I'm, I did the pretty normal thing, you know, graduated high school, immediately went
to college, was, you know, for four years, got my degree in four years, graduated, went
on to, you know, quote unquote, join the workforce, sort of, not really. And, and, uh, all right.
So like what I do now is obviously not the, like I majored in physics and philosophy and
what I do now is obviously not the that, you know, do art and whatever. So basically it
had, it had no benefit whatsoever. Well, I mean, I did, I did, I did work in physics
jobs, like jobs that I needed a degree for a while, like for several years after school.
So it's not like I got nothing out of it. And I mean, more, more, more of the, here's
the thing, I can't, I can't extract who I am and what I do right now from my own personal
history, which includes having gone to college. So to me, like that decision was like an essential
part in becoming who I am. So I can't say no, it didn't work out. It kind of did because
I'm pretty happy with where I'm at right now. Yeah, but that you could say that for every
bad thing that happens to you. Yeah, I mean, that's true. How much do you have a lot of
debt or a medium amount of debt? Yeah, I do. I have like a like 10,000 or $20,000. See
that immediately. That's easy. That's, that's poultry. No, fuck that. Having any debt is
fucking disgusting. Having any debt is imperatively speaking here. Having any debt is disgusting.
I have like, I make so little money that I managed to get some of it. My payments like
deferred. So I lately, I haven't had to like pay that much back. I mean, I'm going to eventually
like, I mean, it's still accruing a little bit of interest. Like a couple, it accrued
like, yeah. So, so like it's still a problem, but it's not, I mean, I can safely ignore it
for right now. I don't know. I'm going to start paying it back as soon as I have a little
bit of extra money. Let's just, okay, yeah, that's cool. But let's hear DeVu's side of
it. His education experience, because this is a totally different story. Yeah. So my
dad was a dude who got several degrees and then realized he thought that school was giant
and giant gay. What kind of degree? Just had a curiosity. Like, okay. So like when he was
like 20 or so, he became a Christian and got into like Bible studies stuff, which were
like church leadership stuff that like, you know, is not necessarily as advanced as physics,
but stuff that does require legitimate education. Like he knows the Bible extremely well. He's
a big Bible otaku and he knows how to like do church leadership and stuff, even though
he's a Bible analyst on YouTube. Yeah, he actually wants to be. Dude, have me on his
co-host. I want to be in that. Well, yeah. Well, what he told me is that, hey, DeVu,
if you make videos, if you edit my Bible analysis videos, you won't have to pay rent
or pay less rent. Oh my God. That's the arrangement. Thankfully though, he hasn't, he hasn't actually
put me up to that yet. He's still working on it, you know. Interesting. Because he's
got a job, right? Can't get any internet work done when you have a job. Oh, let me tell
you what, that's like people. Okay, but go on. Yeah, we'll make that a whole separate
podcast. Yeah, having a job, the biggest problem in the universe for sure. Yeah, pretty much.
All right, go on, dude. How about you schoolin' now? So after all those degrees, I guess
he just, I don't know, I think my dad is just opposed to human institutions in general.
He started his own business. He just doesn't, so he did, he homeschooled all of his children,
including me, since I'm one of his children. Does that mean that your mom taught you and
stuff? Yeah, kinda. It's really weird like that, you know, because obviously part of
it was like religious motivation too. Yeah, yeah. That was a bit of it. But there's plenty
of Christian schools, like my own sister. Me and Ben went to church when we were younger,
with some homeschooled folks, and I never quite understood what was going on with that. Yeah,
hey, I didn't have a choice. I had to fucking go where my parents would literally murder
me, so, you know. Yeah, they would've fucking, they would've fucking Abraham and Isaac'd
their ass. They would've sent us to the hell that we so longed for by choosing not to go
to church, but, alright, go on, dude. Yeah, so, like, it was just, in general, my dad
just doesn't like the idea of school as an institution. He thinks it's kind of a waste,
right? Okay, hey, I wonder where you get that idea. My younger sister, who's 12 right now,
is so much like, she needs a social environment in order to learn. She just needs a school
system in order to even, like, be productive. So after like a year of, like, my dad just
trying to keep her out of this one Christian school, she's just like, she wasn't getting
anything done. She could not focus, so he finally brought her back. And my sister hates
all of her classmates. Whenever I talk to her, she goes on and on about how everyone at
her school is idiots, but she needs that environment in order to function. Interesting, okay. So
those are the kind of people for whom school is required, and I guess those are the kind
of people who invented school as a thing, right? Yeah, you know, there's different strokes
for different folks. It's the Aristotle model, you know. You all get together and you fuck
each other and you occasionally learn something cool. Right. That's what school is like. That's
what college is like. That's it. So I think that the two different like versions of homeschooling
that people are able to visualize is either no one ever gets anything done because it's
impossible to motivate yourself at home. Yeah. Or everything is extremely strict. I don't
know anyone who is like either of those extremes, because I know a bunch of homeschooled kids
because that's the environment my family brought me up around. You've got a little brother
though too, right? Yeah, my brother was also homeschooled as well. Yeah, okay. I think
we definitely leaned more on the never getting anything done side because me and my brother
are both, I mean, my brother particularly, I think actually has dyslexia. He can't read
super fast, even though he's very smart. And even though obviously I'm a genius of all
times, I can't, I can't focus. I can't learn anything in like a coherent way. And it's
written in a Thomas Sowell audiobook. Yeah, right. You know, stuff like I just, you know,
even that if you wanted to like do a test on me to like remember specific names, there's
no reliability with my ability to remember specific names is not intelligence. It's
dumb bullshit. They make you do it. Right. But now here's what I want to get into, right?
Because like, because as I've been getting into YouTube and really, really admiring the
like vast knowledge of people like James Rolfe or even movie Bob, but like particularly
Jesse and Digi over here, Jesse who has an unbelievably broad knowledge of things and
Digi who has a unbelievably deep knowledge of things. And I, you know, I came to realize
that neither of them learned those things in any sort of way that they'd be able to
take a test on. Like imagine if they wanted to do an anime like school, it'd be like,
all right guys, today we're going to study Nietzsche Joe. You need to all memorize the
names of the staff members who worked on Nietzsche Joe and remember the air dates, the
air dates of each episode. And so you'd spend all week just learning a couple of random
facts about this one show. And you know, and like, whereas like all these anime analysis
people on YouTube who have all this knowledge, they just got it from like going on Mal or
anime news network and this just looking at random shit for like an hour every night.
It's amazing what the human mind can do when it has passion for its subject.
I look back on like how I like history. I think history is fascinating. I just hate
learning history the way school wants me to do it. Right. So like, because like the way
the idea is the right way to learn history.
Yeah. Um, like, okay, because like, so my mom basically just gave me pre-packaged curriculum.
Like she didn't do a whole, like, you know, she was fairly hands on, but it wasn't like
she was composing curriculum herself. So she just like gave like here, here's a CD that
teaches the sixth grade, put it in.
I'd like a hands on education from your mom.
So I basically, I basically got a standard curriculum in a way, right? So I know exactly
how all that goes and I know how tedious it is because it's like, I'll, I'll get a history
textbook and I just have to remember all these arbitrary names of things. And it's like,
you know, in the same amount of, think, think about this, think about it this way in the
same amount of time it would take to have a teacher explain to you what you're going
to learn and then go home and then read the chapter over and over again to make sure you
remember it and then do the homework and then like go do the tests and then like pace around
hoping you got the test right and then looking at the test in that all that time, you could
just read half the entire textbook.
You know, you can just get so much more done. Like if you are the kind of person who just
can just read stuff and like remember like 30% of it, that's a totally valuable piece
of knowledge. And like if I were to go back to myself as a kid, myself as a kid who always
wanted to be able to read, I mean, I'm a good reader. I always liked reading. I just always
was bored by all the books I had at my disposal. I just didn't find any books I liked. And
I was always like upset about it. If I could have talked to myself, I would have told myself,
just read the first chapter of every book in the universe, just read the first chapter
and stop as soon as you get bored because you could be like the knowledge guy and get
other people to read the books for you. Yeah, I mean, I like reading. I just think that
books are boring. And by the way, I attribute that to God. God denied me good books because
all good books have like spells or magic or violence in them. I wasn't allowed to read
Harry Potter.
Oh, yeah, that's true.
Well, yeah, but it's just one book. You get tired of it eventually. I told my parents
that last week. No, I'm not doing another Bible study. I've studied the Bible enough.
I'm done with it. Oh,
dude, nice.
I mean, yeah, it's true. Like it's just like how the heck are they still not bored of that
one book? But like Harry Potter, right? There were stories in the news about kids being able
to finally get into reading because of that book. And I heard those stories on the news.
My parents were there. They knew that me and my younger brother were both not really able
to get into books, but that 0.0000003 percent chance that reading them would get us into
witchcraft was just not worth taking the risk. Let us be stupid instead.
Listen, listen, dear viewers, messed up, but hey, that is just that is just the first
example of how school is fucked up our lives irrevocably or irrevocably. And there's
that. I figured it out.
My biggest concern with this podcast is that we are going to make ourselves look like fucking
idiots somehow and convince everyone to go to school.
Like if anyone is like actually smart, someone who could actually like take tests well and
then is able to like really get a hold of their life and get a good paying job and just
like work at it like crazy until they pay off all their debt, you know, clearly the higher
education system will probably work out all right.
The higher education system does work out well for some people. There's no my good buddy,
Michelle. My good buddy, Michelle is now she's like 25 like me. She's married. She has been
a nurse like since she was 21 or whatever like after she graduated and she's just been
on the ground. Her student loans paid. She now owns a house with her husband. She's married.
She's I'm sure she's working on having kids like she's got herself a good situation going.
It's like the thing you gotta learn is that you gotta learn hard. You gotta know when
to give up. Like that's another thing I would have told myself as a teenager is hey, by the
time I was like by the time I was in eighth grade, math was just beyond me. I could not
follow it anymore. I would stare at a problem for an hour and a half and not be able to
do any of it. I would just not be able to figure out at all. It was, I just couldn't do it and
you know, I have, I programmed, I made an RPG like all by myself. It's buggy, but it works
most of the time. I made an RPG because I can do some basic
allergy when I what multimedia fusion, a program where you do need to do the programming
yourself. So, but like, yeah, like I can do math. It's just that the way that math is
taught is terrible. And Maddox was talking about this. And I think in one of the, one
of his bonus episodes of his podcast with Dick rest in peace, biggest problem about
how that math is taught terribly because all they do is teach the formulas. It's like if
you taught history by just telling you like the formulas of how history.
Look, I got better stuff to say. Let's, let's take a little break from Davoo.
I'm going to segue this back into other stuff about homeschooling, right? Cause like Maddox
would also talk about how like he, he brought in homeschooling as a problem one time.
They made a bunch of really good points, like how the parents will now monopolize the way
that that kid is raised. You don't get to have a diversified portfolio of authority
figures as you think that is indeed true. And he talked about how, cause like I think
people are concerned about the homeschooling thing cause a lot of it is for religious reasons
and a lot of times I was like, Oh, well, are they going to like deny evolution and stuff?
Like, are you not going to learn about that? Well, in the case of, um, cause I think this
is worth talking about on this podcast, right? In the case of my family, what they did was
they had this DVD that explains why evolution is not real, right?
But like, right, right? It was like this, this movie is like this documentary cause it talks
about the flagella motor, which was this, this one device in a cell that's like, when
you look at it, it's like so fucking complicated. There's no way it could just be put together
randomly. And then of course later on, I look on a YouTube video of some lecture of this
guy being like, Hey, you know that flagella motor that people make a big deal about? Here's
this other motor that's exactly the same minus two parts.
Yeah. So it evolved into it.
But the thing is, the thing is though, through that documentary, I learned everything about
what evolution was. And then it was just later I had to learn the reputation to it. And then
I was completely on page with everyone else.
So then it's like, there's a thing called critical thinking that can help.
Right. Critical thinking. The biggest solution in the universe, no joke. So in general, my
stance on school is that it should just be whatever the heck you want it to be. And that,
you know, like homeschooling might be the best way. But like, you can, you can get plenty
of social interaction with homeschooling because like you have all this time on your hands.
If other kids are not always in school, there's plenty of kids to hang out with. It's not
really. So are you in favor of homeschooling?
I got 100% of my social interaction from school. I honestly can't imagine like a life without
having gone to school. It just seems totally alien to me.
Right. Well, here's what that's like. It's sort of like couples who get married early
into their adulthood. And then some of their friends don't get married. And they're like,
how could you not be married? Because my whole life is based around my family now. It's like
with school. It's like, because you have to spend all your time there, of course, most
of your life happens there when you don't have to be there.
There are young ladies at that school I went to, numbs and dog, numbs and dog.
Yes, you have made yourself perfectly clear, best guy ever.
Yeah. I had plenty of social interaction. I just, I'm just awkward because of awkward.
You know what they say about high school girls? I keep getting older and they stay the same.
Let me break into this topic and say that on the, like education in general, right? I
think, I mean, yes, some people can succeed. And like you said before, some people need
that like social school environment to learn. I know that in discussion of like, like a
lot of people ask me if I went to art school. The answer is no, by the way. And on the subject
of art school, he went to fart school. This comes up a lot. People want to know, like,
is art school worth it? And the answer is like, you don't need to go to art school to
learn art. You can learn art on your own, but you have to be self motivated to do it.
You have to. And like the other benefits of art school that you can't get on your own
are like social networking and like meeting people and other artists in the field and
also that like structured environment that will like, here's where I'm going to break
it. That's a good point. Give me the in here. Okay, but I have to continue that point in
a minute, but go ahead. Well, okay, you just continue yours because I'm going to fucking
tell you. Well, that bit about being self motivated is really important. I mean, I think it applies
to all schools, right? And like all education. Yeah, we can get self motivation working.
The rest of this will work. Like, okay, in our society, a degree is important, but a
degree is kind of arbitrary. And without the degree, all a college is is just like, they
give you books and they bring you into a group setting and someone talks to you and tells
you stuff, right? And like anything you can learn in the classroom, you can learn on the
internet or by yourself or somehow you just have to be self motivated, right? You can
Google it. Like, if you like, if you really want something like Digi, you've talked about
this with like making videos, right? Like, no, you didn't go to school to learn how to
make a video. You just looked at other videos, figured it out. And because you wanted it,
you made it happen. You like, by whatever means necessary. And like with learning, it's
the same if you want to learn something, you're going to make it happen. You got to be, you
got to be passionate. Like, that's the thing, Ben, I think that the problem here is that
the same self motivation that would drive you to learn this shit on your own is the exact
same one you need to even be successful at school. So in the end, if you're so self motivated
that you could actually do well in college, you can just teach yourself shit. Like, okay,
my good friend, my good friend, Don, son, who I bring up all the time in some of my podcasts,
because he's a super fucking intelligent guy. This is a dude who had to he actually had
to drop out of high school because the fact that he had cluster headaches, which is a condition
where every morning he's so dumb, he dropped out of high school law every morning, he would
wake up and have like a size migraine that made it so he just couldn't do anything for
like hours on end, right? Yeah, yeah, made him a Hickey Comery. He stayed in his room
throughout the last two years of high school. I met him just because he happened to come
to school like two times. And one of those times he had a lucky star book. And I started
talking to him. Okay, so he's the guy. Now I'm connecting the name with the story. Okay.
So Don son, when I met him, he was in my Japanese class. He already knew how to read and speak
Japanese because he looked it up online. And he taught partly is because he'd seen every
anime ever. So he had some good roots in there. But like immersion learning or whatever. Yeah.
He learned, you know, just by just by looking at shit, he would read Japanese, like he learned
the basic symbols, then would read manga to pick up on some of the kanji. Like, you know,
a lot of manga has furry Ghana, where it tells you what each kanji means above the kanji,
if it's like a shonen manga and stuff. So he learned through that. The dude knows how
to do anything involving like building computers. He's like a super he knows a lot of computer
hardware stuff. And he knows everything about like networking, like he specializes in networking,
like computer networking is in connecting to the internet and shit like that. Right, right. And
he's super passionate about that stuff. And so ever since I've known him, he's been my tech guy. I
refer to him as my tech guy, because I don't know any of that shit. And I'm not at all motivated
to learn it. So anytime I have a technology problem, I come to him, you know, he's helped me
build computers. He's helped me figure out all kinds of new layouts for, you know, making our
house capable of having internet because it's too fucking big. This dude knew everything, right.
Then he got his cluster headaches got cured not too long after he was like 18 or 19 through magic
mushrooms, incidentally. Really awesome. It was an experimental medication. Did you know that if
you lock arms around a retarded girl and scream nightmare, nightmare, nightmare, nightmare,
it'll it'll cure her retardation. Yeah, that's on that's on record. Oh my God.
That's like why the only one laughing at that. I don't I don't know what what.
All right. Anyways, never mind. This dude, he got his cluster headaches cured. So he went to
college to community college, right? Because right, right. He he actually like, because he got his
GED, right after dropping out of a high school, he had never like he didn't study any of this shit.
He just like walked out, took the tests and got like perfect scores on all of them because he
knows everything. He's just a fucking genius, right? So he perfect scores all his GEDs. He goes
to college. He takes two years in like, you know, networking and computer fucking learning shit.
He gets his associates. He already knew all the stuff like he literally went to school as a
formality because he needed the degree in order to be hired. But he already knew all the things
he was learning. He already he got like a million qualifications, like took all these, you know,
tests for qualifications and stuff. He just knew all this stuff. And yet he still can't get a job
because nowhere in the field of fucking computer technology will they hire you unless you have
five years of experience. How do you get those five years of experience? Nobody fucking knows.
You could do an unpaid internship. Oh, great. For five years. Unpaid internships are such a
crime. They are the biggest meme that needs to die. They're destroying America as far as I'm
concerned. But you know, I got a buddy get away with that. I've got a friend, Rich, who went to
school out west in Seattle at like a heart. This place called DigiPen, which is like a hardcore
gaming school that like if you work there, you will get a job at Nintendo or like or one of these
gaming schools or gaming companies or whatever. And it's just he went to school with this guy,
Quest. That's his actual name, just pretty dope. And I know, right. And like Quest went there with
him. Quest was an awesome programmer went there for two years. It's a four year degree just dropped
out immediately got hired and has been doing that ever since he's been living the good life.
It's his last name, apostrophe revenge, probably probably.
So my what I was getting to there is if you're the kind of person if you already have like if
you're if you're graduating high school with a 3.5 grade point average or higher or even a 3.0 or
higher, like you have the mindset that you could succeed in college. But if you applied that
mindset to something you want to learn, then you will probably learn that thing. I think the
people who need to go to college, there's two types. One is if you have if you're trying to get
into a field where you can't do it by yourself, like my brother Victor, he's trying to become a
filmmaker. And I mean, it's possible to learn how to make films on your own. And there are some
directors who have done it. But like just even being able to handle the kind of equipment you
need to make real movies, which all of the equipment is at minimum $40,000 a piece. Yeah,
collected all on your own unless you're fucking rich. So in order to even have exposure to the
tools, and because you need a crew to be able to make a film, it's almost impossible to learn
that specific skill set without going to college, which is why for someone like Victor, it's good.
And then I think the other people who need to go to college are the ones who all they have is
study skills. Like if you graduate high school, and your skills are that you know how to study,
then you can go to college. And it won't matter what curriculum you take, because you'll probably
succeed at it. And I think that most people who become doctors and stuff, those are the kind of
people they are. They're people. Yeah, you know, my dad and my mom both didn't know what they wanted
to do specifically when they went into school and figured it out. And I've had great careers. I
mean, I had no idea what I wanted to do when I went into into college. Like I got there. And at
some point, I kind of decided that physics and philosophy were the mostly physics. Basically,
I just I chose that while I was there. And then I just kind of went with it for the foreseeable
future. And I mean, a lot of people, I mean, did you say that like, if you didn't go if you're
good enough for college, you could apply that knowledge to something you want to do. But what
if you don't know what you want to do? Or you want people who don't know what they want to do,
and or people who aren't that self motivated, you know, it's like, okay, people say, well, at
very least, school is a great way to get you to be motivated, right? Well, getting a job, even a
dumb job would probably do that just as well. If not better, I don't think it's good to be, I don't
think it's a good thing. And then guess what, here's the job. Oh, I fail. I don't care. You know,
right, because there's a thing though, right, a job, let's say, let's just say all things are
equal, that it gives you the same amount of inspiration or the same amount of like, allowing
you to eat up time while you decide what to do with your life. You'll walk away from a job with
positive money instead of negative money. That's the most important thing. That's like such a huge
difference. If college were free, I would say, yeah, if you graduate high school and don't know
what to do, and aren't that self motivated, go to college, but like Bernie 2016. Yeah, like it cost
so much money. So like, I don't, I mean, I feel like my college take my takeaways from college
were overall pretty positive. And yet, can I really justify all that in light of the like $20,000
I have yet to pay back? That's the question. I don't know. I really don't know. Because like my dad,
like right when he started a business, like 10 years ago, he started making me come to work
every once in a while, like once a month or so, like, Hey, David, or Davoo, which everyone I don't
know if I'm going to be like Maddox, where all my family members call me by my username.
Did they do that to his family members call Maddox now?
Well, like when he talks about his family members, they call him in his imaginary imagination. But
anyway, he started the window cleaning business. So I started like learning how to clean windows
by the time I was 13. And I was able to do it pretty well by the time I was 15. And then when I was
like 17 and a half, he made me start doing it full time. And it took me like, you know, three and a
half years or four years to finally make enough money on YouTube to break out of that. But the
point is, like if for whatever reason, like the internet just died, like like the internet just
all fried, there was no way to make any money off of it anymore. I would be able to like even
to and then let's say my dad's business just went under because no one wants to work for it, even
though he does a great job. I would be able to get a job doing like any sort of blue collar
thing, or that involves like getting on ladders or cleaning windows or like doing gardening. I
would know how to do that. Even though I would hate my life and want to die every second of my
life, I would be able to do it and like do it in a way that would like be friendly and like I'm
able to work really well when I'm at work because I have that experience. And meanwhile, like even
though I hate cleaning windows so much, and it's the most unsatisfying thing in the universe, it
is 1000 times more unsatisfying than 1000 times more less unsatisfying than figuring out when two
trains that don't exist will cross one another with cargo at 3pm.
I think the biggest problem here, I think the reason that college is so over glamorized in our
society is that everyone thinks that you need college to get a good job, to get a high paying
job. That's the meme. The imagination of it is that you get this high paying job. But the fact
is that blue collar jobs don't pay badly necessarily and there's a lot of jobs you can get with no
college education that you can make a lot of money doing and also an electrician or a plumber
people. Yeah, you'll be great. You'll be in great shape. Yeah, and it's also fun and cool to do
those jobs. You're building fucking houses. You have a life skill that will always be useful for
the rest of fucking time. But like, you know, like, I think, okay, here's here's my perspective on
all this because I want to I've been like a dragon in the waiting for like this whole time. Like
the same way I just want to just bite the head off of this whole entire school meme. There's a
meme that needs to die. Yeah. Like, in my experience, all of my friends went to college and
none of them have done shit with it. All of them are working normal ass jobs. I have a couple of
friends who just graduated who have like ideas of what they want to do with their degree. But like
overall, Victor is the closest anyone is to doing anything with it. He graduated and he's doing
film work, but he can can barely get paid. He can barely find work can barely get paid doing that
work. The only way he will have like an easier end would be if he went all the way out to LA
where everyone's trying to be a filmmaker. So good luck, you know, fucking tiny fish in an
enormous pond. But it's like impossible for any of these people to get work. And yet, my dad, who
he went to, he dropped out of high school. The second he turned 18, he got his GED, and he joined
them the Navy. He was in the Navy for six years. He got I think like two years of college
education in the Navy. I don't know what he studied like he didn't I don't think he majored
anything. I don't even know if he graduated or got marine biology, but he was in the Navy for all
this time. And then, you know, him and my mom were just working kind of like odd like my mom and dad
have always just been managers at like wherever they work, because they're both extremely hard
working and goal oriented people who love to be on top. Like my mom loves to be in control. Your
mom loves to be on top. Too easy. Too easy. She, you know, they both were always managers in like
in managerial positions. And then my dad started working for a car dealership, which anyone can
do. Like as long as you have the personality for it, it's really just a matter of being able to sell
shit to people. He became a car salesman, which is an impressive skill, by the way. It's a good
thing to have. Right. And he he had no idea how to do that. Like my dad, this is how, because most of
the salespeople are like very money motivated, like go getter type people who are very like sly and
shyster type people who built America. So they're exactly like me is what you're saying. Only better
in every way, Ben. Right. Only they can actually do their job. My dad's a super honest guy. He's like
the opposite problem right there. But here's the way that that one of his friends who he met in the
car business, who both of them went on to become general managers, he's he described my dad's
technique as talking at people until they're so confused that they just buy the damn car. Oh, yeah.
He's like me where he'll just keep rambling on and on about it. And then eventually, oh my god,
you're talking about fine. K on his deep Jesus. Imagine as a salesman, Jesus Christ, I would do
anything to shut you the fuck up. I was almost gonna. I almost took that job. My dad almost got
me a job as a salesman. But imagine you looking like you do now. Yeah, no way. But yeah, like he
he's just a guy who just like wanted to work very badly, applied himself to this job with all he
had. He was employee of the month every fucking month forever, and then rose up the ranks and
became a general manager. And he makes a stupid amount of money. He makes way more money than
anybody else I know, or have ever known or likely will ever know unless I start rich people, you
know, like,
well, we we can't all be managers, though. Right. But the thing is, I'm saying that like, it's
possible to to never go to college. And yet, I mean, he, yeah, it's possible. But is it the likely
outcome for most people? Well, you know, what also isn't the likely outcome for most people doing
anything with your college education, right? Now, here's no one does anything with it. There's
like a lucky few who accomplish anything. That's a bit of an exaggeration. That's not an
exaggeration. Almost everyone drops out. You don't go into a field directly related to your major. I
mean, I think most people who get degrees still end up in, you know, maybe not necessarily better,
but in some thing that needed a degree to get into. Well, then it's kind of worse. Let me cut in
for a second. I mean, the what I do for like my tutoring job, I needed a degree to do it, technically
right. All the jobs I had before were things that I only got because I had a degree, like having
a degree. I mean, it's I don't disagree with any of the stuff you're saying to disparage it. But it's
true that having not having a degree disqualifies you from a lot of potential things. But also
disqualifies you is just not having knowledge. Like it like with the electrician job, like you
would be amazed how much that doesn't matter if you have the degree. My current job is a perfect
example of that. I just when it comes to getting jobs, it's all about credentials and knowledge is
not a credential. You know how to program. Do you even know what is a program? I do know what is a
program. But the idea was that you come on. That's the amazing thing that I learned, like with some
of these jobs, once you join like a like a real job in a company that like will give you benefits,
all that stuff, they will train you to do the job. So what's even the fucking point of the
education? Well, here's the thing. There's a big there's a big fallacy about in our society that we
had about college degrees that formed over the course of 120 years, right? Now, this is a bit,
this is going to be pretty conjecture, but I'm pretty sure of it. Anyone feel free to correct
me. But okay, back in the day, the 1800s and the early 1900s, having a degree meant that you were
either really privileged or a genius and or an incredibly hard worker, right? And then you were
an exceptional individual, right? Yeah, this is what we now this led to what we call the fallacy
of composition, which is what's true of one person is true of the whole. For example, if you
were in a stadium and you stand up, you can see better. But if everyone stands up, none of nobody
can see better. If everyone runs out of a burning building, they all get stuck. But if one person
runs out, they'll do great. So back in the day, a few people got college degrees. It meant they were
better than everyone else. So you were more hireable. But when everyone has a college degree, it no
longer means you're exceptional. It means you're hopefully competent. So now all it's done is it's
created this artificial need to have a degree just to prove that you're even like capable of doing
anything. So now it's like we've basically we've duped our society has duped ourselves into you
have dozens of thousands of dollars in debt to be proven as competence. And that's a pretty messed
up. Alright, alright, alright, let me tell you my story now. Alright, my story is the most. It's the
worst thing about my life, my relationship with my with my higher education. So I to went to high
school, same school as Ben was two years younger than him. And then I went to college with the dream
of becoming a doctor. So I went to school in New Jersey, with a aiming for a biology degree or
something, then to go to medical school later. So two years into that, I decided I don't want to do
that anymore. I want to be a computer science major, which was fine. Now, the biggest problem
along this whole thing was that I met with my advisor, like every year to make sure I was taking
the right classes. Nobody along that way ever informed me that no matter what I did, I would not
be taking enough classes to graduate on time. So when I hit that four year mark, you know, I was
aware I'd have to do more. But I didn't think it would be much. I thought it'd be like a year. And
now I'm sitting here. Well, okay, I'm doing okay now. But basically, after after everybody, all my
buddies graduated, I then spent I went back to Massachusetts, spent, what is it now, three years,
spent three years taking like a course or two a semester, working at these shitty jobs, paying
student loans at this point, I've got I've got like $20,000 of debt or something, haven't made a
fucking debt in the thing, been taking these disgusting, horrific jobs. The only thing that made
my life bearable was when I discovered YouTube and started doing tbap and stuff. Those were the
only things in life that gave me joy. My I lived with my parents, I got zero to almost no
puss during that time. After college, my my my hunger had awoken. It was a nightmare. And
have just been treading water ever since until miraculously, and this is what really
infuriates me. The only way I got out of this was just that my dad has had a has a good family
friend who just who just basically made a decree, give this kid a job at your company in Ohio. So
here I am, here I am with the job because it was handed to me. It's not like I earned the privilege
alert privilege alert. I was but that's the thing. I obviously I was I was super privileged,
but that should not be how it is. No one should this whole I mean, that's how it is with me too. I
have super privilege alert like I could just I could just move away for like five years and come
back and immediately start I know I don't want an unfair advantage. I don't want that for anyone. I
got like, like, it is kind of fucked up that like after going through all of that and that's the
thing. That's the thing. You get a degree that supposedly gets you a job. You just like, you
know, because we have this family friend. Yeah, just get you just get one. Like, and I'm just
juxtaposing my life. Yeah. And I'm juxtaposing my life for those three years with no more credentials
than I have now. Just suddenly someone just like gave me an opportunity. And now I'm doing just
fine. Now my life is like pretty decent, I guess. But like, there's no difference between those two
states of being other than someone decided to hand me shit. Like, do you understand how
frustrating that is? It's a nightmare. And my fuck like I've had all these problems. I've had all
these fucking problems like getting credits to count with like the school. And like I took a
class. It wasn't actually approved. That's thousands of dollars down the drain. Every time that
happens. I hate school so much no one should ever go if you're going to go people for the love of
God. Have a plan. Don't go because you think you want to figure out who you are. You're going to
waste tens of thousands of dollars. Just go get a job and figure out who you are. Figure out that
you want to do YouTube. Figure out that uploading videos makes you happier than anything else you've
done. Find a group of people who respect you and that you love and who are your best friends.
Don't go to school. Don't do it to yourself. So hang yourself for the rest of your life.
Ben, I believe you asked me earlier, like, are you in favor of homeschooling? I'm just in favor
of total, like, libertarian school choice. Just like, like the parents have to evaluate the kid
and decide what they think would be best. Like, okay, here's a world that I want, right? Well,
maybe doing math and they're not doing good at it. And then they try again, and they still suck at
it. And they try again, they still suck at it. Get out of math and take the kid exactly. Exactly.
They go, All right. Hey, guess what? You get to give up now. I would love nothing better than to
give up because like the thing is my parents ultimately weren't that good at homeschooling
because they didn't know how to do it. They were both raised. Yeah, they were newcomers too. They
didn't know how to do it, right? You know, especially back in the 90s, it was, I think, you
know, so it was a more new thing than it is now, obviously. How I want to do with with my kids at
least, at least at the beginning, when they're like little, is just sit them down and talk with
them for hours. Because I remember sometimes like talking with my dad about like, history stuff,
and then we like go on Wikipedia and we, I don't know, Wikipedia at the time, but we'd go on the
internet, look something up. That would be a perfectly fine way to like, teach your kids stuff.
It's just like, hang out with them for hours a day or, you know, however much time you have, and
just talk to them and read books and Wikipedia articles. Well, obviously, the thing about that is
the reason most people, the biggest reason we have public schools is because most people can't
raise their own kids. Yeah, yeah. Well, we got, we're trying to compartmentalize the time that
parents, you know, so they can grind out the corporate machine and, you know, make America
more money and stuff. Right. Which is the biggest fallacy in it.
Cat begged to get into my room. I got up. I took my headphones off, let her in, and she
immediately wants to go back out. You know, I like to think you're referring to like a woman
from the 1950s. Yo, this cat wanted into my room and now she won't even put out. What's up with
this garbage? Man, I'm still just sitting here just quivering with sorrow and anger from your
story, Nate. I'm glad. Good. Yeah. It's terrifying. Good. Don't do it, people. Learn from my
mistakes. Let's look at it this way. It's like you decide to drop out of math. Just drop out of
all the degrees. Let's say like, well, I like, well, hold on. Like I like history or I like
science. You can do a little bit of that stuff. But you know what I really want to do as a seven
year old? A song and dance man? I really love the piano. I want to play piano. All right. You can
just drop. I mean, not me. I'm just saying like some other kid. This is like a figure of
speech. I don't play the, I don't do music. This is just an anecdote, a false anecdote that
doesn't exist. Okay. It could be, right? This kid wants to play piano. It's like, okay, well,
let's say if you drop out of school entirely and don't do any work other than like a little bit
that you want, you could do five hours of piano a day. And that's six days a week. And
actually it would be seven if we killed God and you could go do it on Sunday. But let's just
say that we don't kill God. Yeah. Let's say there's a couple of weeks you'll take off. So
that's 50 weeks a year. And then what if that was the plan of a JRPG, a bunch of Japanese
friends get together and use the power of friendship to kill God so that they can work on
Sunday.
And then they celebrate by going to Chick-fil-A on Sunday. Yeah. By the time that kid is 17
around the same age, he'd be graduating high school. He'd have 15,000 hours of playing
piano. That's genius.
Ben, before you say that, just let me say that that is what my life is currently. I have to go to
work. Well, I see you and Digi every day working on making better and better videos and doing so
well. Not only am I not like working at the same rate, like not only am I not currently as
successful as you, you guys are like accelerating faster than me while I have to go grind away my
life at this job that I hate because I can't leave because I can't make enough money. We'll make
this a separate podcast. I'm so envious of you. We will do a podcast about this whole topic.
Nate, how... It's a trap. You see, my job is a trap. It was all a nightmare. I'm living in a nightmare.
If you subtract your debt from all the money you have, what are you left with?
Well, that's kind of a personal question, dude.
Well, I... No, I don't mind. I might, like with all the money, which includes stuff I have to spend
to live, like maybe it would have equaled out by now.
No, I mean, I mean, like right now currently... Oh, right.
I mean, I'm doing all right. I'm doing okay.
Does you having debt mean that you ultimately have negative money? Do you have an amount of debt that would
equal negative money? Yes, yes, I do. That is correct.
And Ben, I assume the same is true for you. It is true for me.
I have $9,000 sitting in my bank and no debt and perfect credit.
I'm coming for you, Digi.
Yeah, one of these days. All right, Ben, you were saying something.
Oh, fuck. Shit. What was I talking about when I was going to break in there?
I don't know, but I could... You better hurry, because I'm going to go on my ranch.
Well, move on, because I forget what I was going to say.
All right, all right. Forgive me.
Yeah, man, I'm like... I think we need to restructure all this shit. I think that...
I agree, man.
Because here's the thing. I think that for the vast majority of people, what school is, is daycare, right?
Yeah, yes, totally.
And your parents don't have the skill set to raise you or, I mean, to teach you things.
They're fucking parents. They probably didn't even finish school themselves, right?
I mean, like, what are you learning in, like, elementary school?
Like, when you're there and you're all sitting at desks and there's 30 of you and the teacher is talking to you for...
Like, do you really think you're there, like, learning every day?
Well, you know, guys, the one upside of this whole thing is that with, you know, automation, AI stuff and all, like, individual computing,
school is probably going to have a revolution in the next few years that makes it way more...
Whoa, that's a whole other mess. I'm going to get into later.
We should bring that back.
Let me tell you my story before everybody interrupts this with the fucking AI stuff.
What were you saying? What did I say?
I said that's way optimistic to think that there's actually going to be that...
There should be that revolution, but I really doubt it.
So anyway, school is daycare, right?
And you send your kids off there, they learn...
It's a way for them to not be around your house in danger all day and also they happen to probably be learning something
and maybe making friends and learning how to socialize.
Pretty good system, right?
Here's the thing.
At some point, you...
Like, when you're growing up, especially when you...
Pretty much when you reach puberty, when you're getting into high school.
Like, personally, I think that the existence of elementary and middle school is pretty justified.
Yeah, I agree.
Kids need to learn some basic shit.
Kids are worthless trash and they need to be held in line.
I do think that we're probably...
We could better optimize what we're teaching kids.
I honestly think...
I don't get why...
Like, okay, in fucking high school is the first time you can even have any classes that are just life skill classes
and they're always electives.
Like, home ec.
Like, why is home ec not like a mandatory middle school class?
They never learned anything useful in home ec.
Yeah, but that might just be because...
I just meant that...
Okay, I wasn't actually talking about...
I didn't mean literal home ec.
I just meant, like, that's the kind of subject.
Learn to cook is a good skill, though.
Everyone's gotta eat skill.
I think everyone needs to learn how to cook.
Everyone needs to learn how to fucking build shit and build a car.
We brought this up in me and Ben's podcast that I was saying that we could just make a whole class
around learning how to fix machines.
Learn computers, make a class about building computers in middle school.
Mandatory.
Everyone needs to know this now.
And most important of all, most important of all, there's sex education.
Why isn't there dating education class?
Why isn't there dating education?
I mean, once you go on three dates, you have sex, but how do you get those first three dates?
You gotta find out.
We need to teach a school.
How do you ask a girl out?
They were up to me.
This is a Chris Chanism, by the way.
I would say that the elementary school, we teach them all the basic shit they need to know.
Middle school, we continue to teach basic shit, and then we throw in a heaping helping of life skills,
which I mean, there's some in there.
That's when you start getting sex education and stuff like that.
But it needs to be a lot more.
We just stop beating around the bush with the sex shit and just teach kids straight up what the fuck it is.
I've got friends who get taught what's up, and they're much more well-adjusted.
We need sex in the culture and whatever.
Kids, we're going to stop beating around the bush.
We're going to beat directly on the bus.
Oh, god damn!
And we need some education on how to get a job and maintain the job and how to just be a working person.
I don't think you can teach that.
That might be true.
That's a complicated and diverse skill set.
One of my offline friends was really screwed over for a year because of that lack of being taught how to get a job.
When you're a kid, you see people working behind the counter at McDonald's, right?
And you know you aren't supposed to walk behind that counter, right?
That's not where you belong.
Some kids have a hard time even ordering at McDonald's because it feels like some social thing they're not supposed to do yet until they're older, right?
It's this boundary that you're not allowed to cross.
When you're a kid, you think of anyone who has any sort of job as someone who probably has some sort of amazing skill.
How do they know what all the burgers cost?
Oh my gosh, right?
Yeah.
So you have that mentality.
And when you're like 20 and your parents are telling you you have to get a job, which was the case for one of my friends,
I feel like a part of her problem was just general anxiety.
But I think a lot of it was how do you go up and say you have a job?
How does this work?
How?
Wow!
Okay.
I kind of know what you're talking about.
Here's the thing.
And we kind of did a little bit of this in elementary school,
but it would be even better if we just had a school trip where we all went to McDonald's or to a bunch of restaurants,
and we all just sat in the kitchen for a while and just watched what people do.
Oh, I see.
Just learn the basic shit of what's going on.
If you were coming here, this could be you one day, kids.
It would be the worst day ever for everyone who works at the McDonald's,
but it would help sprout better careers in the future.
In the Boy Scouts, we did that at a Dunkin' Donuts.
Oh, that's cool.
Good idea.
And I also was in the Boy Scouts.
Oh, yeah, I was a Boy Scout by the way.
Eagle Scout over here, Eagle Scout.
That's me.
Yeah, I never made it to Eagle Scout.
By the way, this is a big millennial thing.
I'm an Eagle Scout because my dad basically forced me to do it,
so I take almost no credit for it.
Anyways, I think we need success skills, general life skills.
And computer programming.
I can't even fucking fathom that at no point in all of schooling,
at any point, I went to fucking 12 years of regular school,
two years of college, and at no point did someone teach me
what taxes are and how to do them.
Oh, my God.
How the fuck is that?
How the fuck?
The education system is a little bit too wedded
to the Aristotelian model of learning general knowledge.
People, we need to know how to do our taxes.
How the fuck?
Every single person in America has to do it.
It's a government mandated thing, like you can go to jail
for not doing it.
Not really, most people who are employees, the taxes get done for them.
That is not true.
I'm an employee at a company and you've got to file your fucking taxes every time.
Okay, maybe that's not the case anymore,
but I know it's the case for a lot of people.
No, everyone has to file taxes.
Everyone has to follow.
Literally everyone.
Yeah.
Okay, well I don't know what the heck I've heard then.
I know I've always had to file them.
The thing is to do, everyone has to file them.
It's if you have a normal job,
which I realize you've never had like a really normal job.
If you have a normal job, then your company takes out a certain amount of your paycheck every time.
And they give it to the government.
And then at the end of the year, you file a tax form that tells you how much they took out,
and then they give most of it back.
However, if you're a fucking freelancer like me,
you have to figure out, all on your own,
the fact that you have to pay like a third of what you made last year to the government,
because no one took it out for you.
So you have to figure out how to give them the money.
And they don't tell you.
I mean, they invariate terms.
Nobody tells you.
Yeah, no one's like, hey buddy, just so you know,
tax season coming up, here's what you have to do.
Dude, I'm just...
No, they don't tell you.
I just knew because I knew what taxes were through television.
I guess it's the thing your parents tell you.
I mean, that's how I learned because my parents taught me shit.
My parents are like...
Your parents aren't like sole proprietors of their own business.
They work at places, so it's a different system.
And they also...
My parents are like...
They have a difficulty...
They've always had this.
A difficulty of realizing what stuff they know that is not obvious.
You know what I mean?
Sure, okay.
They, for whatever reason, assume that me, Victor, and Shade
would learn certain things that we don't know anything about.
You know, I kind of feel that as I'm getting older
and people are more retarded, as I see younger people,
it's hard to know.
It's really...
I have some sympathy for that
because I don't know that these fucking kids don't know what like,
I don't know, a VHS tape is.
Right.
Some shit like that.
You know, whatever.
Yeah, it's like you take certain things for granted
because you know how to do them
because you've been doing them forever.
But like, I have no idea how my parents learned how to do taxes
but it wasn't until like, I had to pay taxes
and I came to my parents like,
what the fuck do I do?
There's some things that were like expected to absorb
through like the osmosis of life.
I mean, I always assumed that the fact that I didn't absorb those things
like how to do taxes, like how to hold it regularly,
I always just assumed that I was just a little autistic
and that I was just this wrong.
No, no one learns this stuff.
No one teaches you it.
I mean, control the spectrum.
I just figured I was a little more on the spectrum
and everyone else figured it out.
I know exactly what you mean, Ben.
And I think everyone assumes that they are the idiot.
Like, I must be the idiot.
I kind of remember the figures around my dick quote.
Well, I must be the idiot here
because I had it in my head
that the tunnel between demon world and human world
had been sealed.
No.
I think everyone just assumes that there's certain shit
because I've had that experience plenty of times
where I'll have a friend who I might say something like,
oh, this is how much is minimum wage or something
because I have no idea.
Or I'll ask somebody like, hey, what's a huge question I had all my life
and I only learned it in the last couple of years
is what is a normal amount of money to make?
I have no idea.
Well, there's no real answer to that question.
When you fill out those surveys,
because I used to buy a lot of DVDs
and they would come with these little surveys
that you're supposed to mail in.
And I never would mail them.
I would just fill them out because I'm a fucking weirdo.
So I filled out all these surveys
and they would always have a question that's like,
what is your house's annual income?
And I had no idea
because I don't know what my fucking parents make.
I don't even know that shit.
Yeah, and so I would just stare at it
and I'd be like, well, what's normal?
Because it has this enormous gradient
from like $12,000 at the bottom to $250,000 at the top.
And I had no concept of how much money is $12,000
versus how much money is $250,000.
Oh, well, you're a kid, sure.
I really didn't grasp it until I had money.
And it was really the moment when I started,
like once I got up to like minimum wage,
like through Target and then through YouTube,
like then I would look at,
like I found out how much my dad makes
and like did the comparison that it was like 30 times
what I was making and I was like, oh,
so he does make a lot of money.
Oh, so this is like, this is what entry level is.
This is what most people are making, like this amount,
this is minimum wage, this is the common amount.
Like, oh my God, now I understand what money is,
you know, but it took so long and like so many years
of not getting it and like my entire appreciation
of what my parents were doing all this time
would have been totally different.
If I had any understanding of money,
it would have totally changed my perspective on things.
I guess I thought that those things
and understanding all that normal stuff
just comes as a part of like following the,
like the quote unquote natural, quote unquote normal,
like life progression as I saw it.
I thought that if I just like followed the standard model,
you know, high school, four years of college,
you know, get a job or go into graduate school
because I intended to go to graduate school
and get my PhD when I was in college.
That's what I wanted to do.
But yeah, no, they don't really tell you that stuff.
Let me tell you a little bit about my like,
my emotional relationship with education.
Like when I started college
and through most of my college life,
I honestly saw the institution of education and learning
with an almost like religious reverence.
Interesting.
I thought that it was like,
that like a college was a place where people go to learn
and learning was like sacred.
Like I was into it.
I was like, this is a beautiful magical thing.
And then like I graduated college
and I got a job, you know,
my first real job was working as a teacher at Astro Camp
and it was like just a bunch of fucking kids
walking around asking me dumb questions
and I had a little lesson thing I had to go through
and like, oh, here I'll show you this dumb demonstration
where I fill up a balloon with hydrogen
and blow it up in a big old fireball.
Here we go.
Yeah, whatever, it was bullshit.
And then I went and I fucking,
now I'm a physics tutor and I went
and I was taught in Poland for a while,
taught college level physics classes
and it was like the same thing.
It was the same as teaching kids this dumb crap.
I was just some idiot up at the board.
I had a lesson, I would go through it.
Like kids would sometimes pause the lesson
and ask me a question and I'd be,
you know, sometimes I could answer the question
but I like, I can't stop the lesson
just because one kid doesn't understand.
So I could just, I could try to explain a little bit,
but mostly I just like what you said before,
did you like just talking at someone
until they're so confused that they buy the car anyway?
I would just have to kind of think of some like
quick way to respond to the question
that was truthful and honest,
but like just get them to like think that they understood
in the hopes that I could then continue the lesson
and they would hopefully go and look at it
on their notes later.
Education just is way too generalized.
The thing is, I honestly felt like,
I felt weirdly embarrassed
about teaching this class because I knew,
like this was all stuff I learned in college
and it was in the textbook.
I was always thinking to myself,
why are these kids even showing up to my classes
and being taught in a classroom setting by me?
Why don't they just go home and read the textbook?
It's all in the textbook.
I do not have any special knowledge
that I'm sharing with them.
I don't even know why I'm here
and yet I was just expected to.
You say all the right things, Ben.
So now I've been totally,
I've been very much disillusioned with the idea
of that like college,
like classroom setting learning,
like now I kind of don't even understand it anymore
after having done it.
After having been on the other side of the equation.
That part where you said
like you can't pause the whole lesson
and understand like that brings us to the whole subject
of tests and stuff like, okay,
let's just deconstruct the whole education system.
Let's say it doesn't exist. Let's say it's 2,000 years ago
we need to invent school and like,
let's just imagine we're in the board of directors
where they invent school and they're like,
but wait a second, what if kids are just sitting
in the class and never paying attention?
How can we determine that they're paying attention?
Well, we'll have these pieces of paper
where they have to write out their correct answers
and then however many they get right becomes a percentage
and then we evaluate them based on the percentage
like, okay, that's obviously how that got invented.
But think about just how inefficient that is
because all you have to,
all you can worry about at school
is how can I
know just the right amount
of information in just the right ways
to get that percentage.
And that's like the number one thing everyone is worried about
at all times and it's the most inefficient way
to learn things and let me just say this,
this is for me the number one thing to say.
If the internet existed
on the day they came together
to invent school,
they wouldn't have invented school.
If the internet existed, there would have been no point.
School was invented back when most people
couldn't even write books.
It's an antiquated system.
Back when these books were almost impossible to come by.
You don't need it now.
It's based on a totally antiquated mindset
from a time before, yeah, you're right.
Oh, this gets to the number one.
Okay, this is the other thing I've got to talk about.
Nolan Bushnell, creator of Atari, father of video games.
In an interview one time
he was talking about his history with Atari
and the things that he accomplished
and the things he was disappointed about.
And he said the number one thing
that he was disappointed about
that didn't come together the way that he wanted to.
This is a guy who failed a lot.
This is a guy who fell from glory in the 80s.
But the number one thing that didn't go the way
he wanted to was educational games.
There's educational games,
but they're all boring, most of them,
except Oregon Trail and a couple other classics.
Using gaming
and computer programs as a form of education
never took off in the way that he wanted to.
Obviously, you know, video games
took off like wildfire.
Well, I don't know about that. I played Oregon Trail.
I think educational games are as good
as they need to be.
Well, the fact that they didn't just overwhelm
the way that we do education is a pretty big failure.
I think he was probably hoping the world would be transformed
into smart people or something by video games.
Here's the thing. I'm about to get very libertarian here.
He said that the reason why it wasn't allowed
to happen was because
of teachers' unions who don't want to be replaced
by computers.
And the way in teaching is so...
Oh, fuck.
That is making me write the fuck off.
Did I mention that B having been
a teacher gave me a lot less respect
for teachers?
I know it's an unpopular opinion.
You're supposed to pedestalize teachers and say that,
oh, they have the most important job.
I mean, there are some good teachers
who are really passionate and go above and beyond,
but I think in general I do not consider
teaching to be a noble profession
in and of itself.
So here's the thing. Education is such an institutionalized
thing, at least in America.
It's one of those...
I think now that all the other unions are going
by the wayside, the teachers' union is one of the strongest.
You can't get anything done.
They're so set in their ways
and so many of them are so old with these
30-year pensions.
Innovation is ridiculously hard.
And Nolan Bushnell was saying
first-hand that...
Dude, we're going to get an iPad in every class.
Every desk.
It's happening, but the fact that we didn't get an iPad
in every class, like one month after
the iPad came out, means that
there's this one very
creepy libertarian podcast called
Freakonomics that I listened to a couple episodes of
and they made a great point, which was
if you were to travel from the year 1890 to today,
almost everything would be different.
Everything works differently, but
except schools. They still basically look
the same way they did 130 years ago.
Hey, you know they got the same fucking buildings
a lot of the time.
A lot of them were the same people still teaching.
Yeah.
Dude, I got a...
Here's an anecdote. From the 70s, they built schools
without windows, because apparently that would allow you
to focus better. But then I guess a couple of
children just got a little bit crazy
from that and they stopped that whole trend.
Someone in Japan built a window
on the side of a classroom and some anime character
sat next to it and everything
was different from then on.
That's right. Alright. Well, I want to get into
since Ben went into his
emotional relationship with schooling, I have to
do mine too. Because I want to paint
this picture of why I feel so
negatively about the school system.
Because I think
I have uniquely been
failed and am surrounded by people
who have been failed by
school.
Oh man, yeah.
Starting with myself. See,
my mom raised me to
be extremely
grade oriented.
She was very
disappointed if I made a C
and she would reward me highly if I made
A's and B's.
I had this mindset of anything below a C
is a titanic failure.
We kind of did too.
When I was in 8th grade, I think
I got my first D
or F on one report card.
Didn't even fail the class, but I
carried it like a
fucking noose around my neck that I had
gotten at that grade.
The same thing happened to me in 5th grade.
I got like a 50 on a test for some
reason and I was distraught. I banged
my head on the blackboard in class
and like just, yeah.
I was fucked up.
I had this experience where when I was in elementary
school, for the first few years
everyone, like my mom
and my dad and my teachers were all convinced I
was a genius.
If only they could have known
how wrong they were.
I would do really well in every subject.
I was really great at schooling.
In the 2nd grade, they put me in
a gifted program they had at the school
where it's just like they did a little
extra mile stuff.
Then they had a whole gifted school
like the advanced learning school and they
were like, alright, when I went into 3rd grade
they put me there.
What very quickly became apparent
was I was not good enough for the school
because the school is for people who are
I think honestly I could
partially maybe blame my mom
for just not understanding the way
that studying works because she would
just tell me to sit at the table and not
stop working until I was
done and I would never do it.
I would just sit there and stare at my work
and like not, you know.
Same. I was a big procrastinator.
Even back then I was a procrastinator.
Me too. I was all about putting off my work.
I never wanted to get my homework done.
I would just wait and wait and say fuck.
I was in 3rd and 4th grade at this gifted
school. I was not doing as well
and particularly in 4th grade and my teacher
was a huge bitch, right?
Here's the thing. I ended up
halfway through 4th grade I dropped back
down to regular school and at this point
I had been
bullied a lot as well
at both that school and when I went back
to the normal one. They'd push you down
and say, enemies of Japanese colloquialism.
No.
They'd take my glasses
for, you know, just fuck with me
and just call me a girl because I look like a girl.
But they, you know,
I dropped out of that
advanced school and apparently
I found out later that that teacher
something like
6 kids dropped from her
class and they fired her.
Because they realized that she was so
because she was fucking terrible. All she would do
like if someone, I remember
several times because there was a kid who dropped
out of the class before me because
every time he didn't do it, like he would come in
with no homework or something, the teacher would
like berate him for 10 minutes
and he'd be like crying and shit.
That's a good use of class time.
Yeah, just like berating this kid and she would give us
these like assignments that were like
these insane logic puzzles
that involved researching shit on the internet
that we hadn't even learned how to do
that, you know, and like.
Dude, quick insertion story
like so she eventually got fired.
That is so wonderful to hear because
my mom tells me these horror stories
about this woman she works with who's like a teacher
she's like my mom's the head of the class
this is like a second level lady but
this woman is a horrible teacher
and no one wants to work with her
but instead of fucking firing her
they just transfer her from classroom
to classroom because no one wants to deal with her
oh is that how we want to handle things
we've got people that are so bad we just keep moving
them around instead of just getting rid of them
I don't understand how people can be bad at their
jobs and not be fired
it's like a thing that happens
it's a union thing or something I guess
I don't know
well one of it is you don't know
well hold on I have some experience with
hiring people because I see my dad doing it
a lot of it is you don't know if you're going to
be able to replace them with someone who isn't worse
that's I think the number one reason why bad people don't use their jobs
this woman it would be better to have no one
than to have this particular person
well I don't know like you have to fill the
you have to get the kids sitting down for
a correct amount of time
further distribute like the time of each
individual teacher if one person goes
they'll find some anyway go on
so anyways to continue my story
after that experience I kind of became
disillusioned with the idea that I was
good at school
I come up with this idea that I was this genius
and then I had to drop out of the
fancy school
and I just wasn't I never did as
well as I did when I was a little kid
man that didn't happen to me until college but I wish
it happened a lot sooner
well and my parents I just felt like I was a genius
and then I spent like the rest of
like regular schooling not believing that
and I had to get on to YouTube to
reaffirm my assumptions about myself
I kind of had a similar thing like I
you know was in gifted classes and stuff
and like I really I really saw myself as a smart
kid and it was a strong
part of my self image that I was an intelligent
person and along with and that gave me
this this like this like religious
all over learning and institutionalized learning
and that self image of being a smart
person I think was a huge factor
in me being motivated enough to
do my classwork and like actually yeah
that's where we're getting those two things fed
into each other because we got to get to this
because this is how it all goes down this is where
the big event happens right so like I
sort of disillusioned with the idea that
I'm super smart but I always wanted to
recapture it you know so like
in ninth and tenth grade I didn't
do all that well I was kind of going
downhill a little bit but I was going into
eleventh grade and I was like you know what
I'm gonna pick up like I'm you know college
is gonna come pretty soon and
at this point I've been like horribly depressed
like because my whole teen years were
spent like depressed as shit and so I was
just like really desperate for a way to like pick
myself up and get get into
the action right so yeah good
so I was like I wanted
to there's my school
had this program where
basically the community colleges near
here called TCC they have a certain
building called the ATC building
where they teach like
college courses to high school kids
essentially so right you know if you're
one of those smarter fast-track kids and
you want to learn like special skills
usually involving computers and like
you know any kind of computer
related shit they would bust all
these kids out to this other school
across town and
then bust them back at the end of the day
they would go there like every other day
so I wanted to do ATC
so I could learn like some
I think it was just programming or something
like wanted to be a video game guy or something
like that I just wanted to learn some computer skills
yeah so I signed up for
ATC and then I also signed up for
an advanced English class because
I was particularly good at writing
I always have been so I
wanted to you know take an advanced
course in it so
I settled like that's the those are
what that's the thing I applied for
like I set everything in motion here's the
thing no one
at any point contacted me
to tell me that
I couldn't do this
schedule because
the amount of classes
basically there was like a contradiction in the classes
I was taking where I had
like I would have had an overlap or something
like I had too many like I had
one class and
to take
the ATC thing
and so I approached
like I know here's what it was
it was that when I had first signed up
for all those classes my I told this to
my guidance counselor before
like the 10th grade
had ended and she had said well
if you take this course load then you'll have to take
algebra 2 over the summer
as a summer school class
and I said okay that sounds great right
uh-huh
summer rolls by
you know and she meant like the next summer
I would take it as a class I go to school on the
first day and no one's contacted me
at all about how to go to ATC
I don't know what bus I'm taking
I don't know where it is
because I didn't know much about it I'd never done it before
so no one's told me like how to get there
so I go to the guidance
office because I'm just like fucking lost and confused
and I go to her and I'm like so
am I doing this ATC thing like am I
going there and she was like well
you can't do
all these classes because they
there's like a whole and I said well I thought
you said I could do algebra 2 over the summer and she was like
uhhhh
no that kind of thing
so basically on the first
day of school she asks me
like you know on the spot
like you have to either
drop out of ATC or drop out of
advanced English and I was just like
well I guess I'm not doing ATC
so I didn't do it so
that was just stricken from my thing right
so at this point like I'm majorly
deflated because I have this
go get her attitude towards 11th grade
and already half of what I wanted
to do was gone
so I start taking the advanced English class
and at this point I get extremely depressed
and I hated this class my teacher
was like really trying to push
this like feminist agenda and stuff
and was super into like
she was like one of those super
um like reading
all this meaning into the text
but then you had to like
like she would teach you that like oh
you can learn you had to read the same meaning
exactly like that is by far
the most pissed off I've ever
been at any curriculum I've ever taken
like what is this character feeling
as she gets out of the car and sneezes on the inside
of her breast pocket depression
disdain disorder
distrust I uh
why do I know what you're gonna interpret it as
who want this
why is that a thing in school
that makes no sense
why is that a thing you can get graded on
that's a good question
you just wanted to scream
I think so too
I couldn't believe the world
when I heard that
like why can we ever
critique Soviet Russia
or the Nazis or the ancient
Incans or anyone else
with their terrible practices
and their terrible ideologies
when our society
can't look down on them when we have
stuff like that that you're supposed to go over
but at least we didn't burn all the Jews
you know we've got that going on
to finish this story
but the Nazis had a very
relativistic view of how the Jews
were feeling
someone came to my house and said
go to his gas
you either have to go to this gas chamber
or
answer all these bull crap questions
about this book
it would be a hard decision
so anyways
I had this advanced English class
I hated it it was way too much work
like ten times more than all the other
classes combined basically
just shit tons of work
and the teacher was a bitch
and I hated her and so
she would assign us like these
writing assignments based on whatever books we were reading
and we were like chomping through books in this class
like every other class would get assigned
like one book a year this was like
reading all the time writing all these essays
like all this really deep
high-minded stuff and this is the kind of shit
there was a lot of kids in this class because we only had
like one advanced placement English class
but like most of them weren't going to make it
it was like you had to be like a straight
A student to be a part of the advanced placement classes
at this school
so
at this point I've become extremely depressed
I don't care about anything
I'm bombing this class pretty hard
and I start writing the most like
fucked up essays possible
right so at one point the teacher
asks us to like
take five quotes and like
write an analysis of them
so I choose
and I don't know
oh it's much better than that
one of my five
was the speech that Martin Luther King
gives in the boondocks
where he gives the whole
all I see is fucking niggas
would you ignorant niggas
please shut the hell up
shut the hell up
I wrote out the whole speech
in my essay with all the niggas
intact
I hope you just said
an asterisk
every single one
the whole essay is just asterisk
it wasn't very long
we only had to write one page of analysis of each quote
but I did that quote
which the teacher
not only gave me
a shit grade for that
but also wrote into the notes like
Martin Luther King never said this
which is you bitch
because I said in the essay
that it was a quote from a show
so she didn't even read
your fucking essay
the epitome of fucking commenting
before reading the entire video
she was the first
she was the first shitty commenter
you ever had
imagine in the board of directors
when they're inventing education and someone says
you have to have a test with grades
someone would have been like wait hold on
all the essays that they have to write
that's subjective how can you grade that
just get out
we just gotta get this system over with
we gotta get back to not dying
I had it in my head because like one of the books we read
early into this class
had the word cunt
and the word fuck in it
so I kinda got it in my head like okay
we're reading stuff with swears in it
I can write those into my essays
it's advanced
we're all mature adults here
I wrote some swearing
I got into a lot of trouble
the word niggas
is like water and the school system
is like the wicked witch of the west
when you put one on the other
the whole thing just collapses
here's how I almost got expelled from school
so I wrote an essay
oh by the way your story is very American
history X
so this essay
that I wrote was
our teacher assigned us that we had to take
one
author
who we had read in class
and apply their style to a story
about a time when we had failed
and so I chose George Orwell
and to apply it
to me failing
to do my English homework
and I wrote this five page essay
that was like this
unbelievably depressing manifesto
about how much I
hated doing schoolwork
it's like bouncing between
it was
I assume it was pretty good
at this point I had gotten a handle
on writing in this Gonzo style
that I kind of do now
so it read kind of like an S4 Diary video
but it was bouncing between dialogue
between me and Donsan
and storytelling or narrating
and so there's one part where I'm talking about
how I'm
holding a gun to my head
and convincing myself not to pull the trigger
to the deck down
there's one part where I'm in the text
because I was texting Donsan in part of the story
and he says something like don't flip out
and stab your teacher or something like that
oh boy here we go
just like how when you did those update videos
with you with a gun they took that seriously
and thought you were trying to kill yourself
so your teachers really were shooting commentary
is that the one where you shoot yourself in the head like eight times
and it doesn't do anything
that's the sort of online announcement
so I wrote this essay
I turned it in and like
like she was like always
grading this stuff like a month after we turned it in
like she was it was like a really long cycle
so it was a long time before I heard back about this
but I happened to be like
out of the house
and I come walking home and my parents are like
furious and terrified and like yelling at me
like what the fuck did you do what did you write
and I'm like confused as fuck because it's been a while
since I wrote this thing so I'd forgotten about it
and what the funny thing is
like the motivation for writing it was
I wanted to get out of this English class
like it was a cry for help
it was a cry for please get me out of here
so I get into all this trouble
and my dad's particularly freaking out
because this is like maybe
two months after the Virginia Tech Massacre
so like
the idea that they called my parents
and are like your son wrote this essay
where he mentioned stabbing teachers and shooting people
and they're like that's how it was
put to my parents
because what had happened was
this essay and she got scared
and she came to my guidance counselor
who as we've already established is an
idiot and a bitch
and she read the essay and she interpreted it
way more dramatically
and she thought it was like this
you know this terrifying
manifesto kind of thing
so she's the one who called my parents and was like
your son's writing about shooting teachers and stuff
so I have to go in
the next day to a meeting
where it's like my assistant
was like a disciple for my grade
and the school psychologist did not know
that was a thing
but apparently there's a school psychologist
who they bring in for moments like this
and we sit in a meeting with them and my parents
luckily they were both
way more they were both cool
they were understanding
the psychologist liked the essay
he was like you know I think
he read it and he said I think you're gonna be a great writer someday
so they
they liked it and they were like alright
take the rest of the day off and come in tomorrow
and we'll discuss this right
so the next day at the very end of the day
like the bells ringing for everyone
to go home and they like take me into this
side meeting room that I didn't even know about
and there's like all these teachers
in there like the English teacher
the assistant principal, the school psychologist
and then like a bunch of people I don't even know
are all like having a round table with me right
and
I didn't quite like understand what was
happening at the time because I was a really shy
offspoken kid and I didn't handle
quick decision making well at all
right? If you do, if you do at that age
we're all on the spectrum
what I eventually figured out was they were
basically trying to get me
to say I don't want to take this class anymore
because
why did they just fucking say that?
they were saying like hey
are you sure you want to take this class
are you sure you don't want to stop because it seems like
from this essay you don't want to take this class
and I kind of got the sense that maybe the teacher
is just afraid to have me in that class anymore
yeah that's totally possible
so moral of the story
is eventually they talked me into dropping the class
she's a feminist and she fears the
of the manpower and dude it was so epic
when this happened because I come walking out of this
boardroom and like they had told my
bus to just like wait for me
so like I come out like
all the other buses have left and I come
walking out of the building and my bus is waiting
there like by itself with all the kids on it
and I just get out and I'm like
I got everything I wanted
like I became convinced I was God
after this because
I had finished to miss a day of
school and stay home
I got out of the English class I didn't want to be a part of
no repercussions, no punishments
we're looking at a
light yagami level intellect over here
it's fucking amazing what this guy can do
like you can find on my anime
blog where I wrote like a post that's like
to the effect of I'm a fucking God
I can't believe how great I am
God of the new world did you bro
um so I
it's a death note reference people
I got a shitty essay story
it's gonna be quicker than yours
I'll just wrap up my disillusion
because like after that
I ended up in a normal English class
which I literally passed while sleeping
through every class like it was on the level
of idiocy that I could do
I could not fail it like I couldn't
possibly fail the class
but from that point forward
like this is what school is
to me it's guidance counselors failing
you and getting getting your fucking
shit messed up it's teachers
who are fucking don't understand
you and don't have like I mean how could she possibly
have just like figured out
my problems when she had like four there were
literally 40 kids in this class like per class
and she was you know grading essays
a month after they were written how the
fuck is she supposed to deal with my hang ups
you know like she can
which is why they had to have school psychologists
do it so like in my
like I just became so
like in the mindset of like wow
school means nothing and like the 12th
grade at my school they were so
desperate to graduate kids that
12th grade was just a skate
like they would get like none of the classes would give
homework everyone was trying to like
baby the students
that's pretty common my English teacher
like he was supposed to assign
like 1984 as the
reading for that thing and he literally
didn't give us a book because he was like you guys aren't
going to read it and I don't want to fail all of you
so he didn't give us the book
so it was just such a walk in the park and I've
had like you know just to summarize
really quick like one of my friends Mike
he this dude
couldn't this dude had like
29 credits
but there was one class that he hadn't
passed and he was like
18 and you know full
fully graduated
except that he couldn't take this one class
and they wouldn't let him take it because he couldn't
take one class like they
you can't just come back to school and take one
class in high school why the fuck
not I don't know but he had already
done all the other classes
he had 29 credits the maximum you need
to graduate is 24
he had 29 and he couldn't graduate
they wouldn't let him go take the other class
I'm so far over
my graduation requirements for school in terms
of numbers it's just the fucking specific
piece of shit
in my senior year
of high school in English class
by the way English was my best subject in high
school definitely
so and I was in
like advanced English
and we had like a big
literary essay for the last
semester of fucking 12th grade or whatever
and or 11th it doesn't matter
and we had to
like we knew about it the entire semester it counted
for like a third of our grade it was big
and
you know it was very strict about like
notation like you have to
you have to make a bibliography
and notate it in the APA format
I remember doing that yep
you have to be very strict about that
anyway the day finally
comes when it's due I've been writing it for like weeks
and I've got
and I bring it to class and I realize
like I look at my bibliography and I see
you're supposed to have the
titles underlined and the other things
in quotations whatever anyway one of my things is not
underlined properly it's
underlined I tried
I drew in an underline but it looked bad because
I drew it on the pen and I was like shit
this doesn't look quite right
so I went to my friend
who was in who had like a computer lab
class and I was like hey
would you mind doing me a favor
could you just like reprint
this one little page
with the underline
in place yeah like print this
with an underline just so it's it's right
when you're in the fucking computer lab and she was like
share Ben I'll do this
for you so later
so later that day she hands me the
retight version it's in a totally different font
this time oh god
whatever at least at least it's complete
I hand it in I get
the essay back like a week later with a big
fucking zero on it
because I had because
because it was because she had forgotten
one of my sources
and because it was missing a source
they gave me a zero for plagiarism
of course
oh my god
I lost like an entire letter and my
parents were furious they went to school
and were like this is totally unfair
this is a stupid that you would give a
zero for this like typo
is basically what it is but they were so
fucking set on like they had
like oh no we laid out the rules really
clearly like we're really set on sticking
to these fucking guidelines we've laid out
so yeah I got a big zero
like the biggest essay of the entire
schooling
every time I hear something like that I just want to
go burn down a school
yeah absolutely
here's a different kind of story on that
by the way I've only got 14 minutes left
of disk space let's wrap this shit up
listen to this I don't know why
because I'm an idiot
but listen to this
my buddy John in college
was taking astronomy
yes astronomy
one of the assignments they had to do
he just did not give a fuck
he had calculated that like it's such an easy class
that like he had already gotten an A
no matter what he did at this point
the worst he could get was a B
no matter if he got a zero for everything else
so what he did for the final assignment
was just like this big like summary of like
it was kind of like just your thoughts and opinions
on like what astronomy
is about like what it's meant to you and stuff
so what he did instead of actually writing
this essay properly
he wrote it a stream of consciousness
like about his current feelings
about astronomy
while just like thinking about the night sky
and so it's just this whole big thing
is that what it was supposed to be about
no well I mean not really
it was supposed to have like sources
and like we learned this this and this and like
but he just interpreted it
something like your what you've learned
in the class but it's supposed to be like a fairly big
like five page paper about you know
substantive stuff
but he just talked about like Mars
Mars is red red makes me feel
angry I look up at the sky and I see Mars
I get I get so angry
but then I look at Venus and I see Venus
and I'm filled with hope and I'm filled with lust
for a woman's body you know like
this is what he wrote in the paper and like
so he gets it back like a month later
after he turns it in it just says
on the paper F
terrible and that's it
and that's it
that's kind of when to go John
all of my essays in high school were always
like stream of conscious meditatives
like they all were terrible
just the one word
and did he just did he just shrug and go like
yeah yes so
yeah that's exactly how he implied it
to me
another thing that happened like when I was
in 12th grade we had
like a government class I think it was
and like
these
we had this new teacher who like
she had just come from like another school and she
transferred in and like
half the time in class
she would just like not be able to
explain the subject matter to the students
in a way that they could understand
because she was like super by the book
but she always seemed like really nervous and stuff
like and so I would often
like there was one time she was trying to explain
affirmative action and
oh boy oh boy here comes the white
trying to do this like yeah she
wouldn't like use like
words white or black and stuff
really trying to like tiptoe
around the issue
she was white I assume she was
was white okay about half the class
was black so yeah
like I could tell
everyone in the class seemed interested
and like they wanted to understand
but she just could not explain it because she
was walking so hard on eggshells
and finally I did this
like a lot of times during this class
I would just say yo niggas let me tell you
I literally said to the teacher
can I explain this
and she was like did you stood up with his arms
crossed with his backwards hat and his big
and his big and his big flavorflave
chain and said yo let me break it down
for you I would say can I explain this
and she'd say yes and I was just like
if you have
10 white guys and 5 black guys
in the community that's how many you have to hire
you're like it's that simple
you know and everyone got it
you know and but it's just
that like she was so by the
book about everything and it's funny too because
I didn't do well in this class because I would goof
off the whole time like me and that kid
Mike I mentioned sat next to each other
and we were just fucking talk and pass
notes and be assholes and so like
even though I knew the subject
well enough that I was
teaching parts of the class better
than the teacher could I nonetheless
because she was very
strictly by the book and I was completely
not following the book
didn't do well in this class but I just
to me all of this just says like all I see
is a joke when I look at the school system
all I see is all these cracks
like people fall through the cracks and there's cracks
everywhere it's all cracks
it's just a joke
you say it's a joke I say it's a big
old fucking circus that's how I feel about it
like when I'm
tutoring someone I'm just like
this is a joke like you don't need me
you don't need me to tell you this stuff
you could look it up on your own but you just don't
for some thank you because I'm being paid for
this I appreciate it but why
why are you going on and on and on and on
about all these problems what are some solutions
everyone here's my
here's my solution
we will start
the TPC institution it'll be the easiest
school ever right you go
you go to your decent human behavior
class and it's just Jesse being
don't stop being a fucking faggot
you go to your economics class
you go to your economics class and it's just
all standing there in a circle going get money
get money
get money get money
and you're in a school in like 45 minutes
and you've learned everything you need to know
that's the best fucking thing I've ever heard to do
other than that my solution would be
I think
I think we take elementary
and middle school maybe add one more year
under middle school and
turn it into teaching
way more life skills way less bullshit
I can't tell you how many times
I relearned US history throughout school
I don't care none of it mattered
like I learned the same
10 names about American history
in every single year of education
cut that shit out learn it once
and then it's over because if I ever need the knowledge
I'll look it up on the fucking computer
so cut out
majority of history can be cut out
and you don't even learn the good stuff for example
there was a civil war general named Hooker
where that name came from because he had all these women in his tent
never learned that in school
so yeah cut out most of the history shit
if you have a kid
who's not doing good
at math and you really try
but it seems like he's not making it
put him in something else
take him out and by the way also in the civil war
general Burnside had the largest
sideburns of all time and that's where the term sideburns come from
so you see the civil war has a huge
wealth of knowledge
with all of the money
that we've saved by cutting
three entire years off of the education system
and
and just burning down lots of schools
because
like
now that we've saved all this money
let's put it into
making way more trade
schools and way more schools where
after the
ninth grade, ninth grade is the last grade we have
in my new school system
you have nine grades, they're way more specialized
we put in
there's lots of different types of courses
it seems like he doesn't know anything about math
put him in an arts course
if he doesn't know anything about arts
put him in a math course, find somewhere
have different course loads for different people
way more so than we currently have
get rid of the fucking common core
nobody needs history this fucking badly
put him in something else
cut a bunch of bullshit out, restructure it
then after ninth grade
have three years of trade school
they can pick whichever one they want to go to
because even if they don't get a job in that field
it doesn't matter because just like college
you'll pick up a bunch of life skills
if you learn how to
become, let's say
a computer programmer those skills
will help you forever in
everything and my advice
to our audience
don't go to college, go on google
type in the phrase what is code
and read the bloomberg article
that's 34,000 words long
it teaches you everything in a very
pleasant format that's easy
to understand and learn
what code is and then learn how to code
and code everything forever because
you are an inexhaustible resource
that everyone needs in the world
and there you have it
those are our solutions
that's uh, you know
just go do it folks and hey if you want to tell stories about
your nightmare college shit just leave in the comments
I'd love to read them, I'm interested
I want to hear about everyone's gotten fucked over
listen to Kanye West
let's have a toast for the douchebag
not that one
no, that's about me
alright, well alright thanks for watching folks
we'll see you in the next one
bye
what the hell is wrong with me
funny I'm
supposed to be creating
funny
think that the people
gladly
will pay for
artistic genius
that's what they came for
instead
I'm tweeting
hashtag repeating
that's why there's no
weed and holes in
the ceiling
yeah
it's quite the burden
it's a hard knock life
being
a genius