Hello everyone and welcome back to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm
BG and we got BS over there. The shitter himself. We got TO. What's up, T?
Yo. Yeah, his catchphrase. Yo, we got GT.
Lord of Ghost Chapter 5 will be out by the time you're listening to this. Always
pushing that L, O, G, and D.B. Yo, I'm sorry I've not been on the show for a long
time. I was spent a long six weeks trying to figure out exactly how gay I
actually am. Results? Any closer? Very gay, it turns out. Extremely excessively
gayer than I ever thought possible, so now I have to live that life for the rest
of my life. I want to say, first thing, today, when this is coming out, this
will be the last day that the Rowdy Frickers Cop Killers Pin Kickstarter is on and
we will be streaming the end of the Kickstarter on twitch.tv slash Rowdy
Frickers Cop Killers tonight. This is the big finale. We've achieved, we've
outdone all of our expectations, as always. That's great, that's great. You
guys, you do that and here's some incentive. I forgot to do it until now.
I'm gonna do it today, the day this is recorded, but you should go do it. Yep, I
know, I know. I'm gonna make a note to myself. Go get those. I want those. It's
very sloppy, it's very sloppy. Was there any updates on the pixel V-non pixel
red man face? The pixelated version overwhelmingly won, like almost two to
one. But was there any issues with the guys? Can they do that kind of? I
suspect they can do it. I suspect it is doable. Well, cool, cool. But we'll see.
Well, there you go, folks. Hey, other news in the, in the news, it's May, which means
some people are doing me a math of a type things. Not me, though. No, sir. It's May,
so there's new butterflies on Yakitori Island. Oh, thank goodness. There's the
big one. Is that true? There's a scorpion. I got stung by a scorpion the other day.
Oh, goodness. Does that have the same effect as a tarantula? It is the same,
it's just you pass out and die. Epic.
Good, good. Glad to hear. Wait a minute, wait a minute. You already did the thing.
I'm sorry. But pause, everybody pause for one second and listen to this right now.
I couldn't. Okay, was that an animal crossing? Rose thing? It was. I couldn't hear the words.
It was. That's the same guy. Is that the same? That's Eleazar. That's our editor Eleazar.
Wait, that's Eleazar? Yeah, that's him. Okay, then was Eleazar the one who did the,
it's time to shit on the pizza party podcast song? It, I think it may have been. Yeah,
it must be because it was, that's the clearly the same guy. I didn't even realize that was Eleazar.
Also, wait, there's another one. There's another one. Let's listen to this.
Ben Saints Animal Crossing Time To Talk About All The Times Has Had Breeding Flowers
In Your Dazed Tool of Poses To Ben Saints Animal Crossing Life
There Is Full Of All The Black and Purple Flower
Ben Saints Animal Crossing Time
Yeah, well guys, my Rose Garden has expanded. It's covering like almost a third of the
freaking island at this point. It's real good. I got a lot of blacks. Purples are getting up there.
I got a lot of pinks by accident. I'll just probably throw them in the garbage or something.
Yeah, fuck those. Yeah, you know, I'm going for pinks actually. I'm trying to. Well, hey,
you know, I think today I'm going to fucking do the thing. I'm going to do the fucking thing
where I spend the money to get online. So if you want to come visit my island and you want to,
you want to dig up some pinks, that's fine. Or I can just bring them to your island. I don't know
whatever. I want pink windflowers specifically. I don't have any windflowers. Well, fuck that.
What are they? Wildflowers? All I've got is roses. Oh, I'll take roses. Roses are good too.
Okay, yeah, yeah. Sure, sure, sure. Sick, sick. Well, there it is, everybody.
We've got a jingles. Did I already mention that I was on the bonus episode that I talked about
winning the stock market? Yes. Yeah, I think that was, yeah. Well, I'll briefly mention then I made
a shit ton of money on the turnip speculation and now I have a mansion of a fully upgraded house.
Looks great. But there's this village Fauna, the deer. She lives on my freaking peninsula
and she's cramping my style. It's my peninsula. She wasn't doing anything with it. I know she was
here first, but I moved here now and I've got big ambitions for it. So she's got to go,
she's got to go to the animal ghetto where she belongs, down in like Kramn of the bottom left
with Curlose and Gala. It's time for a new trail of tears. Yeah. She's got to, she'll be,
she'll be happier there among her own kind, I think. And she's standing in the way of progress.
There could be none of that on Yakutori Island.
Future, Utopia. Utopian is real in Ben St.'s world. We have to, you know,
where her house is standing would make a really nice parking lot. Oh, you know, that's true.
Hey, we got a voicemail that I did not play, which was someone said they had a genius idea
of how to make so much money. And this was their genius idea. You go to your store, I think, where
you can buy the fruit that they sell on your island. This is what he said, for 400 bells,
then you, I assume you fill your inventory and then you go to another player's island
and you sell your fruit on theirs for each fruit making a 100 berry or belly, berry,
whatever it is, profit. That seems like a very low profit each time you're going to be doing that.
Well, you would make a hundred, you would make a thousand bells per stack.
Would times 40, I guess, which is 40,000? So you would make 40,000 bells, yeah.
Okay, that's not bad. That's not too bad. Now you could definitely do that.
If you went to someone else's island where your fruit was for into them.
I'm glad we crunched the numbers. I was wondering about that.
Oh, anyway, hey, I just want to say, since it's May, I made the definitive version
of the Miyamafufa jingle, Miyamafufa 2 theme, that is. I am very proud of it. Lots of memes in
there. If you watch my streams, I'm sure you'll appreciate it very much. So go check that out.
But beyond that, congratulations. And I'm excited to see what the other people who are doing Miyamafufa
is doing, of which I know too, that is Nexus and May, aka Pantsu Party. So good work on those.
I bet there's more people too. And corrupting your kids, because it's across both channels
that she's doing. Right, right. What is she doing every day? Making videos. May, May, May is what it is.
A video every day, is that it? Yeah, video or live stream. Okay. What's Nexus doing?
He's drawing a picture. Yeah, he's drawing a day, I think. Good. As you should. Jade Moro.
I think Nexus is in particular, it's like some weird experiment where he has like a character
and you have to fill her room with stuff, like people have to comment stuff that he will draw
around her or something like that. What's the girl? It's like generic girl. It's filler girl.
He used her for like Inktober once. Yeah, that's right. You always got funny ideas.
Well, I hope it doesn't take too much time away from Nexus finishing the vaporette.
Jade Moro says she's almost done with hers and I haven't heard from Kazi and Munchie in a while,
so I can only assume they've been working hard on theirs. I've heard tales of Kazi
doing some work on it by her own admissions. She says I'm working on it, so I think she may be
working on it. I also heard tales, but Jade said like yesterday, she said hers was like basically
done, which I... That's good. That reminds me of something else I wanted to bring up regarding
that, because last year when I was doing me a MAFA, I had the film festival, the film contest or
whatever, and a bunch of really talented people entered and some not talented people don't get
me wrong. But some of the impressive guys, I've been keeping tabs on a little bit,
see what they're doing. Most notable was the winner, Fune Bure, who is an insanely talented guy,
and there was another guy, 404Tales, and I just happened the other day to stumble across a video,
like buy that guy 404Tales. That was like, oh, it was like the greatest cringe of all,
horny on main, something like that. And I thought to myself, absolutely not. Oh yeah,
of course did you would say that. It occurred to me that this seems like the kind of name
a video would have that gets really, really popular. And I'm like, oh, that must be why it's
recommended to me. But I click on it, it's got a couple hundred views or something. It'll be in
the show notes, I'm sure. And I watch it, and I had some thoughts about that and Fune Bure too,
because both these guys are insanely talented and put ridiculous amounts of effort
into their videos. And they're both in like this weird, I don't know, that starting enigma place
of like starting your YouTube channel, or it just like you've been doing it for a while,
but it hasn't really grown yet and hasn't caught on. And I was trying to think of why that is,
considering how much production value there is in this. And I think I had, yeah, go for it.
Because this is something I've been thinking about lately as per my whole fucking neuro typing
chart thing, which has helped me to understand my own content in a way, because I've always
insisted that I'm somebody who's like doing non-objective, opinionated, like it's just me,
it's Gonzo, and anybody who follows everything I do would obviously know that. But there's always
been this weird disconnect where people watching just my anime videos expect me to be like a critic.
They're like, oh, you missed this detail, you got something wrong. How could you criticize a show
if you're not going to be exacting about it? And it's like, well, that was never my point.
That's why I'm a Gonzo journalist. But I realized that the problem is I had not figured out how to
translate the script in a way that focuses on the emotions instead of the logic. If the point is
not to be perfectly logistical, but to tap into an emotion, then it's like anything you put into
the video that doesn't contribute to the emotion is essentially pointless. That is exactly kind
of what I was thinking. But yeah, go on. You can add all these things because you think people want
a video to be flashy. They want it to look clean. They want it to look good. No, they want to connect
with the video emotionally. They literally just are there to feel something. They're there to take
the ride that you're providing for them. And you've just hit them with facts. How is that ride so
great? That's kind of what I was thinking about. And I think that clean presentation can work for
if you're a channel like Polymatter where it's like literally facts being dumped into your head.
And it's like just very clean animations and information and all of it contributes to the
point. And that's important too. If you're trying to make a point with your video, all the images
should help make the point. It shouldn't just be that it looks nice. It's that it looks nice and
it's helping to make the point. If you just have like a bunch of pointless animations,
then it's just like, why are you spending all this time keyframing something that nobody cares
about? Like, just to make your video have the impression of being fancy, who cares? That's
pretentious. That is the definition of what is pretentious. I suppose so. But I mean, for both
of these guys, yeah, I mean, when I was kind of reviewing this and I didn't watch all of it all
the way through whatever. I'm not speaking about these guys in particular, by the way. I've never
seen anything like this. Right, of course, of course. These are just the ones I haven't
ever seen enough. And I thought that with both of these guys, who obviously I respect a lot,
and I think they're great at what they do. But it's a key issue of there's a missing narrative
throughline through some of these. Like, they're just describing thing. And I get some people can
succeed with that. But when I watch these, I get to the end, I'm like, I've gone on a ride,
but where did I get at the end of it? What have I achieved?
Would you say it's like akin to an editor putting like random images that match the words
phonetically, but not, you know, they don't serve the point? Right. In a sense, yes. But
there's even a bigger problem, because I really don't feel like I've like, again, not I like
both these guys, but I'm just trying to be constructive. My criticism here, it's that like,
I don't feel like there was a real point. I feel like that like in the writing stage,
they put down some thoughts on a thing that just kind of go, I don't know, not particularly,
and you know, there's no, you could see you could express the exact same feelings. But I feel like
a well written script would leave you with like a punch. It's like, ah, like a like an aha moment
at the end. It's fun to feel that. There's lots of people who make content like that. They just
like, you know, cringe, horny, or main, like, they just look at a bunch of things that are cringy,
and they as a YouTube personality reacting a funny way to it. And then them reacting in the funny
way is the point. So like, are they not doing that? Are they like just displaying it?
I think the key issue here is that may be true, but so far it is working for these guys.
I mean, I would say that I had a conversation of like this earlier that was about like,
just explaining that I think a lot of people, they don't really understand how to put the
thing into words, and but they still are trying to make an analysis video. And it's like,
if you don't understand how to put it into words, put it into something else, put it into,
you know, put it into the editing, the music, the sound, like whatever, but convey the idea.
Like, don't just like, give me fancy editing and you telling me how you can't figure out,
like how to explain this thing, like, or explaining it in a roundabout way, you know,
where I don't really feel like I get the point, like, make the point however you can,
but there needs to be a point, you need to understand the point. And if you can't put
the point into words, put it into something else, you know? Yeah, yeah, I basically agree.
I don't know. I like these, both these videos, just an example to be mildly critical, contained a
lot of some thoughts swirling around the issue of like, horny on main and like, simping in that,
like, Budokan show that obviously I had strong feelings about. But, but I don't know, something
was missing. And I'm trying to help these guys and anybody who finds himself in a similar position,
because I upon watching both, I'm like, I enjoyed this ride for the surface value, but like,
it doesn't give me a connection or like, I want to hear what this guy has to say about
next thing and a reason to come back. I don't know. I'm listening. Oh, I'm not listening,
but I'm watching muted the four or four tails video. And he's got like the four or four logo,
like DVD, like, jumping in the back, but he cuts, he cuts and it doesn't, he doesn't let it go all
the way. He doesn't stay there. He cuts and it changes around. That's the worst thing about this
guy. This guy sucks. That was a little unsatisfying. It's true. I wish he had moved his avatar, but
left that thing bouncing around. And you know what, just because I watched this one, watching this
video, I thought that like, what this video would contain, and I was disappointed when it didn't,
was lots of examples of people being horny on main that he would present in an amusing way,
but it's mostly just his thoughts about it. And that was somewhat unsatisfying, considering
that it was just his avatar moving around as he continues to describe various thoughts about it.
Again, not bad, not bad, but there's way too high effort to have like 299 views.
I know, I know. And it makes me feel for the guy, which is why I want to want to help because I
respect both these guys greatly. I don't know. I don't know. So hopefully this has been some sort
of useful critique. As I'm working on my remake thoughts and stuff, I've just been reassessing
like everything. I'm kind of getting back to like what I originally did on YouTube now with this
kind of shit. And it's like, I'm trying to think like, what was the point of all this? What am I
trying to achieve? What makes a video good? Why bother criticizing a video when quality literally
doesn't matter, and it only exposure matters? Well, the question is, is it that these guys are
not getting the views because they're not connecting with the audience? Or is it because
they're not, you know, they're just not getting seen? You know, like I do think that, you know,
it's not quality doesn't matter, but connecting does. Like it's just that a lot of videos connect
incidentally or through almost no fault or consideration of the actual, you know, creator
of the video. But, you know, as long as there's something people want to see, that's why they
come to it. And like, just looking at the simp moho video, like the thumbnail and title are
terrible. Like they don't convey anything to me at all. It just says simp moho. I don't know what
that means. The thumbnail says simp and then there's like, I don't understand what most of the
thumbnail is. There's like vaguely an anime somewhere deep buried in this thumbnail. But
like, what the hell is all this black shit around it? What is this whole silhouette thing?
That's his style. That's why would I click on that? It literally does not tell me anything. It
just says simp and then it's confusing. Okay. Okay. First of all, everyone knows what a simp is.
And when you see this ominous shit and a little bit of anime thing, I think this is a more provocative
title than I know means click on this video. It's sort of in the right direction. But like,
yeah, it looks, it could be any name of the show. I mean, what is this video supposed to be about?
Just simp in general? Like, is there a question that it seeks to answer? It should be okay. I
watch like 30 seconds of it. And I guess it's him talking about simping. It should be called like,
it should be called something that is like, let's know that it's going to be a guy talking about
video should just be called simping the anime and then have a big picture of the main girl,
like doing a simping move and just that is the thumbnail. It should be a picture that indicates
simping, you know, like, this is just a picture of the show. It does not show simping in the thumbnail.
Like there are the show definitely has many, many, many, many powerful visuals to convey
simping as a concept. What show are you talking about? The show that he's talking about in the
video. Which is definitely about simping. It's a show about simping. That's why me and Nate covered it
in extensive depth earlier. I know it's a little cringe, but I don't think it would be a bad idea
to have like, he's got a very expressive, like, and stylish avatar. He should feature his fucking
avatar, like, you know, making the DreamWorks face and like crossing his arms or something, you know.
That does work on YouTube.
I mean, why have an avatar like that? Like, it's a nice avatar. I like it. It looks good. I think
if I saw it in the thumbnail, I would be drawn to maybe click on it. I think me and Fune and probably
404Tales as well. We have this thing where like, he clearly, he clearly, if you just watch the video
and look at the thumbnail, he has a vision for like the style of what he wants to create. But this
is YouTube. Our vision is worthless. It matters not at all. What matters is getting people to
click on the video and keep them coming back. I mean, I just don't think this is a good title
or thumbnail period. Like, it conveys nothing emotionally. Like, a title and thumbnail only,
I mean, aside from on YouTube, the meta is that it has to be an ad for your video. But aside from
being an ad, if you're treating it like a title or like a, then it needs to be an artistic encapsulation
of the point of the thing. Like a title of a book, like to kill a mockingbird, you know, like,
that is a fucking title. You want your title to sound like that, you know? So that's why I said,
like, simping the anime and then like a picture of simping, you know, and then I get it immediately,
I would definitely click on. Maybe put your avatar cringing. I don't know, something. Yeah.
All right. All right. That's my advice. Well, I hope that's been constructive feedback, Fune,
out of love for you and your craft and you 404Tales. That was what it was intended to be.
It pisses me off when people put so much effort in, but they're not rewarded fairly.
I mean, life isn't fair, right? It's all about putting your effort in the right place. You have
to work smarter than hard. Working hard won't get you nearly as far as working smart will.
The 404Tales one is better. At least there's like, it tells me a little more about what's gonna...
The title is good. I like the title. I actually like the thumbnail of that one. I mean, it's
evocative. I would say this one's fine. I'm surprised it doesn't have a shit ton of views.
Like you said, it seems like... It seems like a video that would get lots of views, but I mean,
it happens to be a small guy who I had heard of, so got recommended to me, but it did get
recommended to me. That's a sign of success. That's good news. He's got an interesting avatar.
I like this idea. This is very... It reminds me of like Kimono Friends,
like the studio that does that, like their style.
Oh yeah, yeah. That's cool.
Well, okay, there you go. Hopefully that's been useful. Ladies and gentlemen,
please continue. Good luck, everyone, on your quest to succeed and not die.
I really like titles that are excessively informational. I mean, that Final Fantasy video,
like Final Fantasy 7 remake came out and I have thoughts pertaining to it. That's the entire
title. It's a really stupid, bad title, but I really like it. I would click on things that
are like that because it's unusual and also it tells me what it is. It's like all those memes
where it's like Shrek, but every time Shrek appears, the movie doubles in speed or whatever.
Like the title is the entire meme, but then you click on it and it's actually true and that's the
joke. Even though it would be my inclination, some guys like Matthew Matosis get away with it
because they're over the hill of this sort of thing, although they probably could do better,
but I have to resist the urge to, when I put out my video calling it, Final Fantasy 7 remake
review. That's the worst possible title. Matthew Matosis titles, he's successful despite those.
I don't see why that's a bad title. I think the only thing that would be better is if you also
gave it like another, like a secondary title that is like your particular brand of like,
these are my, this is my review series. Sure. Like if it was Final Fantasy 7 review.
Like as much as I dislike, I hate everything's content. It is a very good gimmick to say I hate
this. It's a good gimmick. It's a strong word, gets people interested. No doubt. Even though
sometimes I think he hates those things a little bit less than the title might imply. Oh my god.
That fry. No. Impossible.
Well, that's all I had to say about that. I did go mushroom hunting yesterday, which was kind of fun.
Yeah. Please play Cowboy Bebop mushroom hunting in your mind as you listen to this, ladies and
gentlemen. Why did you go mushroom hunting? The conga drum. Sicily, Tijuana, India, Osaka,
Indonesia. But why did you go mushroom hunting, Nate? I want to know. Well, Michelle has been
enraptured by mushrooming culture. Yeah. Yeah. This is the thing. Who are a notably secretive?
I like a good mushroom from time to time. Yeah. Of course. Of course. Very secretive,
like cult of protecting their secrets. Because, okay, there's a mushroom called
a Morrell. Here, I'll get you the image. There's a, what's that fucking show on YouTube?
Best of the worst. Yeah. There's a, there's a Best of the worst where one of the videos they watch
is, it's like a guy. Morrell madness. Morrell madness. Just a guy just gushing about Morrell
mushrooms and how to hunt them. I've got to check that out. Well, we went, we've gone out twice now,
hunting Morrell's, which are supposed to grow in Ohio, in southern Ohio, which is where I live.
Badass. I know. They are, they trigger that, trypophobia. You know what I'm talking about?
They look like sponges. It's the holes. They, they, they frighten me. Okay, but they're supposed
to be delicious. And they, they supposed to grow, Michelle just goes down these rabbit holes sometimes
and we, she's just gotten into mushrooming and Morrell's are like a prized find in this area.
And she's been watching, she's been getting very depressed, watching people who are finding
like hundreds of Morrell's. We've been out twice, has not found any, and it's making her very sad.
Well, you must not be looking in the right spots. There must be somewhere else. Yeah,
this is what I'm saying. Like southern Ohio, which is where we are in forests. And you know,
we've been looking around a little bit. So we were just out there. Sit down and wait for them
to grow. What would you do with a Morrell if you found one? You, we cook them. You cook them is
what you do with them. They're supposed to be delicious. Slice them up and fry them or?
You know, I asked the same question. She said, you know, fricassem in, in butter,
make a little cream sauce served on a. So yeah, slice them up and fry them. Slice them up.
Yeah, yeah, whatever. You just, just fucking bite them out of the ground and eat them.
And put them on a, what are they called? Like a, like a toasted slice of bread or
something and you eat it with like a sauce on it or something. It's supposed to be delicious.
I can't stop staring at them and mushroom hunting is overpowering all of my thoughts now.
That baseline is rumbling through my body. It's on my mind every moment we're out there.
I would eat that. I would eat one of those. They terrify me, but she ordered some from Amazon
anyway, just to try them while we continue the hunt. I have gotten my fucking oligo saccharides,
my friggin tapioca soluble fiber. I have been like blending the shit together to try and make
a gummy. I finally got a gummy consistency that was hard enough, but it was not sticky enough.
It like fell apart a little too hard too easily with the teeth. When you bit into it,
I think there was too much coconut oil. So back to the drawing board. But yesterday,
I, I got my fruit flavors. I got peach mango, pear, you know, the works. It's going to be great.
But I don't, but the thing that I'm waiting for the most is my citric acid, the thing that will
make them like really tart and sour and you roll them in like a sour, like a sour gummy.
Oh my God. I feel like I'm making progress. I'm making progress on the candy front. It's very
exciting. I'm looking forward to it. I want to try some. I can't wait to get molds. When I have
the gummy, the worm molds, that's when it's going to really be real. Yeah. I'll send you some extract
of morel when we find some. Yes. I'll make some morel gummies. It sounds good. And by the way,
last thing on the subject is just that I mean, one of the reasons it's been challenging is because
the morel community specifically is extremely protective of the locations of these morels.
We, the first time we went out, we, we were just out there, there were a bunch of people and one
of these guys just like, Hey, how's it going? Like, oh, you know, doing a little mushroom hunting.
They're like morels and we're like, you know it dog, you know it. And they said, we have scoured
this forest. You met other mushroom hunters. We met specifically morel hunters and get this,
not only that, they had a bucket of some substance and we were like, Hey, what are you guys up to?
They're like, so there's no morels in this forest in Cincinnati. We have a bucket here of spores.
We are planting around this forest to grow specifically morels for next year's season.
Yeah. This is the degree to which morels are beloved in these areas.
How did you meet other mushroom hunters? We were simply in the woods walking around and it
happened to come up in conversation. And did you pick where these woods like specifically
recommended as a mushroom hunting location? I think, yeah. I mean,
otherwise it just seems like an incredible coincidence. Maybe it's like a thing like
with quarantine, the only people like daring enough to go outside is the mushroom hunters
because they love them so much. And by the way, all the only people you could find.
I can't help but think of, remember Elizabeth, that real thick mushroom from Dark Souls one DLC
You keep Myra in her curves. Yes. All these images flood to mind. Also, the bad ass mushrooms
from Dark Souls one, you just beat your ass and they're like the strongest enemies in the game.
All good stuff. All good stuff. Anyway, so mushrooms. I wish you'd been doing that. Me and
Michelle have been out there. That's the reason for the name.
Indeed, on Twitter. I always wondered why she was called that. It didn't make any sense before.
Michelle Tobin. It's very unfortunate. Well, that's it. Been hunting mushrooms,
so that's what's going on in my life. Mushroom hunting. It's a great time. It's a great time.
What's going on with you guys? Shit, other than animal crossing and mixing gelatin into
goop. That's all I got. Oh, you know, okay, here I'll just get my other thing out of the way and
everyone else can say their piece. The other thing I'm doing is watching the tutors,
which is a showtime historical show about Henry VIII and all his wives. And it's pretty based.
It's pretty excellent. And the main thing it's doing is making me think that history is in fact
awesome, even though there's some inaccuracies on the show, which is fine. But I want to call
out Munchy. I wasn't sold until I heard inaccuracies and now I'm down. Now, yeah, it sounded boring
until you said that they were inaccurate. No, it's the story of Henry VIII is like,
truth is stranger than fiction. Shit. It's awesome. I love political machinations,
though I didn't even know what the Holy Roman Empire was until I watched the show.
When's Munchy's freaking lecture coming out? That's what I'm here to roast him about. Where the
fuck is the French Revolution lecture? I want to hang it with my nibba, the Marquis de Lafayette,
our guy. He's the coolest guy. And I miss him every day. Fuck you, Munchy. Harass that man.
The spirit science lecture was extensively edited and came out months later, so I wouldn't be
surprised. This doesn't even need any editing. He put visuals. We don't need to see what the
fucking Marquis looks like. I mean, I won't go into spoilers right now. That's not the kind
of editing the spirit science lecture had. It didn't show anything from the spirit science.
It was just madness. It was just crazy, delirious, fucking aesthetic editing.
Sure. Well, I would argue this doesn't need any of that, and I just want it out.
This is good, though. Munchy, don't work on the lecture. Make the vaporette. Thank you. And good
night. Do both, please. I mean, it was like my favorite lecture, and I want to watch it again,
so I'm missing it. All right, there you go. He's been canceled until that comes out.
Apparently, I guess I'm off scot-free until Munchy's comes out then. Is that the way this works?
Oh, yeah, I forgot about yours, too. Wait, didn't you say yours was going to be done soon?
You were working on it, too, but it stopped. You said it was almost ready.
Look, things changed. I never said it was almost ready. I never said anything like that. I just
said I was working on it. Okay, okay. You were working on it. I mean, initially, my plan was to
not edit it at all and to just have both cameras in full streams the whole time,
but then I found a way to edit it that made it much more entertaining,
and so I just wanted to spend the time to make it good, but then I have a lot of things I have to
work on. I'm just too much on my plate, dude. It's fucking a lot. I didn't edit my first lecture
at all, which was fine, but then I saw Nate's the intro, the one-piece lecture. I was like,
you know, I like that. Maybe I would like to put something like that on the Sonichu one.
I mean, I really like. There's definitely something to be said for just starting the lecture when
the people start out. Yeah, but you're a little like just like five-second like musical intro. It
just makes it feel like more substantial, and I don't think it takes anything away, so I like
that. I want to do something like that. It's cool. It's cool. Just a little something-something.
I have a question for the first May-May-May video. Why are you the tripod? Is that your
idea? Do you want to be the tripod the whole time? No, it was really distracting. It was simply a
matter of the fact that we thought, oh, we could do it in front of this Henrietta Wallscroll that
we have, but directly in front of that is the couch, so I am on the couch holding the camera
to film. But the thing is that from the description I was given of the video, I thought it was going
to be like eight minutes long. Like, so I didn't realize I was going to be like holding it for
45 minutes, so, you know, I had to kind of get comfortable. It was one of the things you start
filming, and then you realize, oh, I have to hold this camera in place. Like, oh, right, that's hard.
I don't have any physical strength to do that with, so. Same. Yeah. Well, the good news about
these things is that, like, I don't know, like, when I started MiaMath of a one, for example,
I, like, had not figured out my style, but, like, by the end of that, when I was done with that,
I was like, oh, like, I've made, like, 30 videos. I, like, this kind of placement for the camera.
I'm just going to do this, and then all of Viagua's for, like, two years happened, and I was reasonably
happy with it. So you figure out a lot of shit real quick about, like, how you want to make your
videos and what you're into. So you burn through that stuff all quickly, so I don't know. You
realize you need a tripod after one episode. That's probably the best thing about doing a video
every day. I mean, like, when I did it in August, back in 2018, it was very much, like, every video
was completely different style, just because it was, like, the question was always, what can be
done within this time of day? Like, all right, I've got an idea for a video, like, what edit,
like, what level of editing can I do on this concept in the fucking five hours, you know,
and you get really inventive. And then you go, actually, that was fine. Like, that little 30
minutes of editing I did there. That video was entertaining, and I had no problems with it.
So let's do all of them that way forever now, you know. Yep. That's the goal. Goals.
It's a very educational experience. You should try it if you're thinking about it.
Well, so I've been just working on books. I've been writing novels. I've been making songs.
I've been fucking having, smoking more weed than anybody's ever smoked since Snoop Dogg.
And so cool. No, it's not, it's not cool. It's not cool at all.
But, you know, but it helps. So, so I've just been sitting around thinking about shit and making
stuff, and it's been sick. I have nothing to talk about. I thought I did at some point.
Tom, Tom, please.
Tom, save us. Tom, Tom, you're, you're a crazy, you're a wacky guy. Tell us some shenanigans.
The only shenanigans that have been happening to me the last couple of days is that I've been
hit with some sort of technology curse and everything has been destroyed. So I'm recording
right now with my old microphone because my audio interface is just not, well, it works.
But the problem is that for like a long time when I got my old computer, it would constantly like
crash and was saying like, Oh, one of the things connected to it is crashing a computer. I'm like,
well, that's dumb. So I finally built my new computer. I was excited to never have that problem
again, but it's still happening. So I guess my audio interface is just broken. And then my friend
let me borrow one of his computers yesterday because he's like, I got a new one. I don't need
this anymore. And I was going to use it as a render slave. And I touched it and it died. I don't
know what happened. I like would I just cleaned it out because it was covered in fucking dust.
I've been sitting in a closet forever. And so I was like, Oh, I'm going to clean it. I'm going to
make it look good. I'm going to like be a good responsible person and make this computer not
choke on itself. And I turned it on and there was no video. And I was like, okay, that's dumb.
Then it just didn't turn on at all. So I guess all the components died and I thought the power
supply died. So I guess I got to buy a new power supply for him because I broke it. But then I
figured it wasn't the power supply. It was the motherboard and the graphics card that both died
at the same time. And I was like, well, that's stupid. Then the graphics card just started
working again for no apparent reason. So I don't know, I'm in a cursed zone right now. And
that's all bad. It's all gay. I don't like it. I have like my old mic taped onto a
arm so it can still be not crappy. It's all it's all dumb. It's all bad.
Well, shit, man. Where's the happy ending to this? I don't know to be concluded so much for my happy
ending. Digi, what I want, I was wondering, because a couple of days ago you tweeted out about
artists and their inspirations, I guess, and saying, oh, this art reminds me of that.
And then I responded to that tweet saying, this is the problem whenever someone comments,
like, oh, your art reminds me of whatever. And they get pissed off. That shit drives me crazy.
It's so dumb. It drives you crazy that you think that? No, it drives me crazy that people,
when someone, when some normie comes into your art's mentions, like, oh, this looks great.
It reminds me of some popular thing. And they get offended. Yeah, it's just like, that's not meant
as a derogatory statement, 99% of the time. But like, artists get on their fucking high
horse and are just like, oh, it's don't, this is the wrong thing to say. You know, they have their
dumb little like graphics as they can draw on shit. They're like, don't say this, say this. And
it's just like, shut up. You're not a boss of people. I think the problem with the culture
around artists is that with it being such a like, you know, art kind of is an inherently like emotional
thing to do, you know, and these people, they want to feel like, you know,
protected in their ability to express these things that they have these intense emotional
attachments to. So it's like anything you say, it's like, you know, oh, you're going to say
something negative about my baby, you know, but it's like, you really need to be understanding
about the intentions of the people talking to you. Like it's, it's one thing to be like, oh,
this is an insult like inherently, it's like, well, it's not, it's not inherently an insult to
compare your art to somebody else. It's usually complimentary. Like if that is upsetting to you,
you can tell the person, but like, you know, it should be under, you should be understanding of
the fact that that person would not assume that you were going to have a problem with that. Like,
why would they think that was an insult? You know, like when I tell Ben anything, I'm excited.
Champion is like Naruto, but gay, you know, hopefully he takes that in the positive way.
Sure, sure. It's just funny that you tweeted that because I'd like, I had for a completely
different purpose, I was like, made this meme for my friend, because we were talking about this very
topic and I didn't post it because I assumed to art Twitter would get mad at me. But that's,
that's my thoughts on the matter. Lincoln, I agree. I think the reason I was able to
make the tweet funny was that I made it like sympathetic to both parties, you know, the
fuck is the limb in the foreground? That's what I was wondering. It's a very ominous limb. It's
very scary, right? But that's like the image macro for the meme. Yeah, what the fuck? It just looks
like part of the furniture. It does. I think it's, is it an arm or a leg? I want you to imagine
that it's leading up against that desk, like that it is that size. Oh, it's that big.
That it was leaning on the desk. We just, we just don't know. That's fucked up.
We just don't see a giant gross head. Sick. I think it's a guy in the foreground who's doing
like a weird, weird arm angle thing with a bent elbow. Like his head would be right off. We're
going to have to track down the guy sitting there and get an explanation, but all right,
what was going on in the frame over there at this exact moment? But I don't know. I mean,
obviously when somebody looks at your art and is like, and like doesn't engage with it the way you
want them to and is like, Oh, I have a more popular thing in my brain that this reminds me of,
which is like distracting me from just appreciating this the way you would ideally want me to. Of
course, that doesn't feel like ideally good, but you know, you got to, you got to control how you
react to these things to a degree, I suppose. Speaking of that then, Lord of Ghost chapter four
was, I think, not quite out by the, maybe it was out last time, PCP, but now it's definitely out.
Yeah, you guys have seen it. What is my comic? What is my art reminder of? Because nobody's
actually made comparisons. Lord of Ghost comic is fucking cool. I was going to say,
homestuck a little bit, but not really. I mean, hmm. I like reading it because it's cool.
Thank you. I can't think of anything offhand. You're welcome. Oh, there's a comic I really
like called Stone Toss that there's a lot of overlap here between the themes. Yeah. Yeah.
Really gets my my noodle going.
What of the 13%? Hmm. Yes, I must consider this.
Hmm. That 2% though. I don't know. I think there was, I don't know, like some of the
thing was maybe it's a reference like riddle me this. Oh no. Okay. I'm sorry. It was a racial
slur. Something me this Batman. What is 13, but also 51 or something very, very based.
I can, I can fill in the list. Indeed. Indeed. Disavow. And thusly be amused. Indeed. Indeed.
I love all of God's creatures. Anyway, this guy needs to work on his posture is the main
thing I'm seeing going on in this picture. Both him and our man kind of shrink that down,
not enjoying this. What if he just has a big arm? What are you talking about? Oh,
it must be the legendary Coomer. This is this gigantic arm from all that cooming he's been
doing. There he is. His bones also. His arm did not get any bulkier just longer. Just longer and
wider. Yeah. Proportionally larger. Yeah. Great. Great. As is Dick also grew proportionally,
which happens when you coom excessively, as I understand it.
Did you have an actual answer for that? What my art style reminds you of? Or at least the Lord of
Ghosts. Oh, your art style? Yeah. I mean, yours is very distinct. Like, your art only reminds
me of your own art, for the most part. Like, there's obvious elements of homestuck, especially in
like, Baaljape and the stuff that's, you know, done in that style. But, uh, like when I think of
Lord of Ghosts, um, yeah, and it's just like very Hippocrates style, you know. Not much just comes
to mind. I mean, okay, honestly, a little bit of like the rounded characters like in stone toss,
like there's a little bit of an overlap in just like the, I don't know, character. I just sort of
see it a lot. I would assume that like where your illustrating influences come from are probably
things I am less familiar with, as they are probably more like British. I would assume, but.
Well, no, I mean, I'm mostly going off of like Scott Pilgrim and One Piece. Okay. I can definitely
see Scott Pilgrim. Specifically the hands and capes and stuff, the boots. I'm thinking like One Piece
sort of stuff. Your style is just so abstract, you know. Like you tend to, I imagine everything
with you has like a wobbliness, like a bloobliness, you know, that like makes it very distinct. Like
that's what I tend to focus on is that the wobbliness of the aesthetic. When I think of the
Lord of Ghosts comic, like the image that comes to mind is like my favorite or most iconic panel is
the one of like, I think it's from chapter one where the Lord of Ghosts is like screaming with
both his mouths and his eyes are like bulging out of his face a little bit, and he's like
reacting to whatever it was. And I'm trying to think of something that looks like that, but
I just keep it back. Like when I try to like imagine the Lord of Ghosts comic in my head,
I just keep picturing all the like epic sewer shots of just like the gigantic backgrounds in
the sewers. That shit was ill. Control alt delete seems like a major inspiration for the art style.
Yeah, honestly, I'm like, I'm looking through it right now. And, you know, the closest thing that
it reminds me of, I guess, is like some of the like, not not all of them, but some of those like
mid 2000s, like new grounds, flash animations, just because for those projects, they had to use
like really simplistic form just because that was kind of like what flashers about and they were
animating it. I feel like you're really capturing that kind of like simplistic
form where like it's very much everything's defined by its silhouette more than anything else.
And like it doesn't have too much detail, but enough to to separate everything from each other
and give everything a distinct look. Like I could easily see this animating in that shaky kind of
old school flash kind of style. Like like there's a fish in my door.
You can see like hippo inviting a vizek or something maybe. It's like my favorite
new grounds. It's like my favorite new grounds anime series, CCC city, the greatest work of art
ever committed to the internet. This looks epic. Have I gushed about CCC city?
No, I don't. I see a guy with dark circles on his eyes, so I'm sold.
This it's it's it's only like like a dozen flash animations by this guy called Vinny.
And I guess there was a webcomic, but I never read it. It's just like this like it's that like
yeah early new grounds kind of like crappy anime like style like pseudo anime American
take on it, but like they're actually great and they're really good and they're really cool.
And I want them to be real life. Maybe we'll get the Netflix live action adaptation one of these
days. There's one one of these is like the whole video is like slow motion in reverse of like a
guy falling out of like an airplane and it's just you watch him like rise up from the ground and
like shit like this battle is going on around him, but you see the whole thing in slow motion
reverse and it's sick. What do you call it? The not the cinematography the fucking directing
I can tell is really good. Like they're blocking things out and they've got like depth of field
transitions, which is really difficult to do in flash. That big idea I can immediately see they
have a lot of like ideas. It's a lot of solid they do. This whole the whole thing it's like I
guess CCC city is just this big like giant like fucking it's like it's like the city in um in um
what's that game space port janitor yeah yeah it's like space port janitor but like it's huge
and it covers like a whole planet and it's like all everyone is like a weird anime character with
like all this weird like bullshit like armor on their fucking sticking out of their heads and stuff
and it's what a fucking treat. Is that one spanish? My favorite fucking thing in the world.
Well it's watch these flash videos. Flash was cool. I'm watching it right now and then you'll
understand me better. The drawing's not super complicated but yeah the composition the shot
composition and stuff the way he's like framing all the the cuts is really good.
I'm watching the start of gravataxis right now. Remember Rebecca the stamper that's still the
greatest video ever made on Newgrounds. Short and sweet baby that's all you need. Wait what? Which one?
Rebecca where uh oh god what are the names Jerry and Rebecca and the uh the kid I don't
fucking remember their names but it's legendary. Oh yeah Jerry, Rebecca and the kid. Wait you're
thinking of Hot Diggity Demon. He did Jerry. That's not true. Yeah it is. Yeah Jerry the and
like he's a depressed guy and he has a terrible life. Oh Jerry right right well fuck that I'm
talking about Rebecca the legendary animation by stamper whatever it'll be in the description
people will know what it is everyone everyone loves it especially me. Yes correct correct.
Well boys I feel we're out of steam here and we do have a bunch of voicemails if you want.
I forgot to say about the Kickstarter the rfck kicks it ends at 9
p.m. that's when we'll be 9 p.m. EST so we'll be streaming for like a bunch of hours maybe four
hours or six hours before that that's when that's when the ball fucking drops at ratty
twitch.tv slash rattyfriker's cop killers. I got news I got my trump bucks today. Okay that's nice.
I got my $1,200 for being a good American. I have not yet. Thank you Donald. Did you
get it in the mail like a physical letter or something? Huh what did you get it in the mail
as a physical thing or was it a transfer? They are supposed to direct deposit it if they have
your information. I don't know why they didn't do that but yeah I went to the IRS site and I
they asked for my information and they were like okay we're gonna mail you a letter and they did.
Okay you know yesterday I was getting my tire I had a flat tire so I called triple A to help
me out with it and the guy said that he was gonna give me like the guy would happen to be
changing what we were talking about whatever and he was like uh yeah hey have you gotten your thing
yet? I was like nope not yet. He's like yeah there's a website that my mom found that you can go to
that they will tell you like if you're ready or like if you're eligible. Yeah it's just the IRS
website. Just the okay I gotta fucking do that. Just be like the IRS homepage there's a button on it
that's like get my payment and they will ask you. Okay I'm gonna do that then. Yep I got my payment
yesterday as well so we probably got them around the same time. All right not bad thank you Drumpf
you're back at it again. All right well if there's nothing else to say I want to shout out Vic and Hope
so they're doing like real serious stuff I've been watching the videos they've been putting on the
channel and you know they've launched a patreon. Victor is trying to do like real youtube show
stuff and he's just put out a they just put out a podcast let's play where they're talking about
um you know well Victor's been talking about like gaming the system and doing all this SEO
shit and his approach to youtube is very like tactical I think that's really cool and I hope he
succeeds. Yeah he's had for a while now he's been the guy that we've thought about like uh uh like oh
you know like canton was partially inspired by like Victor saying like guys I watch these other
youtubers I don't even like because they do the thing about the shows I want to hear about please
do that so it sounds like he's doing it now which is good that's what I've been telling him to do
for fucking seven years god damn it like he's just literally doing what I was like badgering him all
the time like hey Vic it's really fun to listen to you just describe shows you should do it as a
youtube video series like there's actually a video uh on the Modal Soul production channel
it's probably unlisted right now because the audio is like almost it's so quiet you can't hear it
but it's Victor in a wig in that that girl wig that he wears some of the time of just describing
the the first episode of Aquarian Evolve for like 10 minutes and it's just like because he used to do
this like he used to just watch movies and then just describe them to me in the funniest way and I
would be like you have to do this is this is like a gift you need to do this all the time you need
to do this on the internet and then there was a double shot the drinky pony where he did it with
my little pony episodes but he did like two I think he did one that actually got posted and
then I don't even know if he finished the second one I don't remember if it ever came out I think
it did but uh yeah that never happened and he just kept being like uh he was just so down on youtube
it's like a thing as a career as uh it's gay I don't want to be some youtuber it's like he's
right the second he found himself on lockdown and was like oh this is actually the most reliable
career right now all of a sudden bam youtube time you know what he's right it was probably for the
best to not do it to develop other useful skills let me sure solve everything and tell tell him how
to do it and now he can just come in and fucking sweep the sweep the sweet rewards the sweet nectar
of my knowledge and uh that I brought to the world so make sense make sense sick I mean victors victors
camera alone makes him uh epic and good and very very nice well I mean if it does become a full-time
youtuber then like we we got him you know I mean that's got him he's in our clutch I mean his
because the schedule is so flexible it's it's like like gig-based or whatever I'm sure he can
do camera work and then also be a youtuber when he's not doing that probably seems like a pretty
decent business model especially because they both kind of lend each other I don't know about
I don't know about like like to be a really successful youtuber you need to be putting out
content forever until you're dead constantly I'm thinking of it more of as like a hobby that
happens to make money but I see your point I see your point yeah you can I guess you can be like
pretty big as long as the videos you make are like really substantial like if you're making
impressions on current shows it obviously needs to be very soon after the show is aired
that you make that video that's true and also it's not like high um no it's not high art it's
not the greatest stuff like people aren't going to wait months for like a you know a first impression
sort of thing right right they'll wait months for a genre an episode for some reason well that's
that's led by the comedy and it'll be about things that aren't timely so you can get that pretty
much anytime I feel if you're like one of those legacy youtubers the rules don't necessarily apply
to you as much you know that's true your name precedes you it's well you know what I think it's
the comfort of just seeing a familiar face like I think I think in a lot of people's minds like
if you never had a moment of disillusionment with John Tron then your impression is just like oh
John Tron he's a funny guy ergo it's funny to see John Tron saying things I mean what's a game
lizard brain it's so powerful oh you know here's a good example if Matthew Matosis released
just like his bloodborne review I would be on that shit I don't care how outdated it is or
how many lore videos I want to know what Matthew Matosis thinks about bloodborne yeah but that's
because Matthew Matosis has never let us down you know like yeah that's true it's like I've
really been enjoying his smaller videos he's been making oh yeah you know I caught up on like
all his videos except for a couple of the Zachtronics that those are the ones I'm watching now
and I'm just like ah yes I've forgotten I don't know like I got a little bit out of it when he
was doing all the Zachtronic but now I'm like caught up on almost everything I'm like mwah
this is the good shit I love these little videos I just want to hear him talk about a game that
Kiro Blaster video I was like yes I love this I want to hear more things like this I'm still
got to watch that beautiful Joe one because that is not interesting to me I am bored by that video
yeah but everything else that Victor I like and hope I don't even know why are you telling me that
you have to have played the game that he's talking about to he did listen to the video no no not at
all uh beautiful Joe beautiful Joe then I don't know something about it was just playing yourself
I don't know maybe it's weird like I loved his commentary on Devil May maybe it really is that
I haven't played it and just am not interested in that particular game because I loved his ones
about I mean the the Dark Souls ones I loved his deep dive into those I do think your impression
would be very different if you had played it simply because yeah the gameplay that he shows in the
videos is the highest conceivable level gameplay of that game yeah and that game is almost impossible
like it is that is one of the hardest video games I ever played when I was a kid like even just getting
through the first couple screens was hard like understanding the controls like I think you
would you would not have trouble with it obviously as you know what I think that's exactly it but I
think I need to play it in order to appreciate that video it's definitely worth playing it's fun
yeah okay it's it's his literal favorite game except for Wonderful 101 right is that
do I have this correct it's his absolute favorite but yeah yeah I love all them camea games that
game I did play so I enjoyed his shilling of the remake or the Kickstarter for the remake or whatever
if you play Devil May Cry there's a couple DMC references in Beautiful Jet I clapped I clapped
when he did the the reference it's my favorite as a kid and I still clap today because I don't care
I wear my fanboyism on my sleeve unabashedly unashamedly well you know what I it's different as
opposed to like making a sequel to something you know this is funny it's like with Final Fantasies
every game was distinct and not a sequel and so when you got like to the next like for example
in Final Fantasy 7 the fact that Holy and Meteor are like giant plot devices which just like were
black and white major spells like up to that point and actually Meteor was kind of a big plot
point in Final Fantasy 4 it's like oh what a cool way to like capitalize on this meme in a way that
like in no way like messes with like continuity or anything because it's its own it's its own story
but like wow so cool that they would do that and and same with like the Clover Studio stuff
whatever the old Capcom going into Platinum and stuff again that's really cool to see those kind
of references done in that way but with like a sequel I don't know something about that has far
less soul back to the the the soul discussion or whatever it's uh it's more I don't like Final
Fantasy 10 like of course it references the shit out of Final Fantasy or 10102 I meant to say like
that inherently is more boring and I would be way less interested in any of these like connecting
threads than in like I don't know like Final Fantasy 11 or whatever. Some sequels are good obviously.
Of course of course I don't know just just a fun thing I like. Well I mean you expect a sequel to
reference the thing it's a sequel of. Yeah yeah so I guess it just feels more like. Or be weird if it
didn't. I guess it becomes like an obligation as opposed to like a fun bonus in in that sense so
I don't know. Anyway we weren't talking about that we were talking about. Yeah yeah that'll
that is all to say that like Matematosis can get away with making a video whenever he wants
because his opinion his take on video games is so powerful for lack of a better term because I
don't know terms. Yeah so powerful that people will wait for that and I don't know yet whether Vic
and Hope can make videos like that. Victor is definitely incredibly entertaining to watch
and listen to. Like I would I just love seeing him but he would probably need to like make videos
all the time in order to actually gain traction. Yeah of course. I mean I just hope I like you
know his his main sort of series is that like just describe the plot of or anime done quick
that's what he's calling it even though it took a really long time to describe the plot of Fate
Zero or Fate Stay Night Rather. But like you know. As quick as can be done. I've always enjoyed
watching him do that and like for me it's legitimately made Fate watchable like I would
not watch Unlimited Blade Works. It is fucking boring. Listening to Victor describe the plot
was a thousand times better than trying to sit through the fucking show so. I enjoyed the visual
novel. I don't need the anime. It's just that was enough. You're not a visual novel guy though so.
Well particularly I just think that the visual novel is written like shit. I actually have a
video. I wouldn't say it's good. I was inspired to buy Victor's recap to write a video about Fate
that I might do soon. That is just about like how I think it's basically just emotionally retarded
like like it's a story that's like just obsessed with having like as much shit in it as possible
but like the story is garbage. Like it stuff just happens. Like have I mentioned it's just
character standing around and talking and then showing up in scenes and fighting. Yeah I mean
that's true. I know I've probably said this before but like have I mentioned like how unique an
experience reading the visual novel of Fate was and I did like every route. I didn't get every
ending but you know there's a lot of like little ones whatever and like the very particular experience
I've never had before in a story. There was a little bit of an Harry Potter I guess but it's like
the vast amount of detail describing the unique specific agonies of a character engaged in battle
like oh and then I felt my left tibia break and ooh that made me have to stagger forward. Like in
an anime you won't get any of that. You're going to see like him take you know 50 hit points of
damage basically and then get up with a little blood and keep going. That was a very uncomfortable
reading experience but it was unique and I always I always remembered that uh uh after finishing it.
I don't know like even just the way that like I don't know it's actually kind of fun to think about
when if you're if you're in a battle like in a war and you've got like you know a 50 pound sword
and like a 20 pound shield or whatever maybe maybe less than that whatever and you are continually
swinging at your opponents you don't see this in video games you don't see this in a lot of
anime or whatever like you will get tired and your bones will start to hurt after your I don't know
fifth swing I've practiced like kendo a little bit you just do like a hundred swings and you get
fucking tired with like a bamboo sword uh so like when you're doing it one hand I don't know
fucking battlefield or whatever you get fucking exhausted and shit and the novel goes into detail
on like how fucking tired shiro is at any given moment and I kind of love it I kind of love that
it goes into that stuff even though it feels very strange like for an anime uh very very unexpected
it just seems like a lot of like what is what is good about fate is the details and so the visual
novel is the best way to experience that because it's just uncompressed detail like it's it's just
nothing but rambling about fucking information for 90 fucking hours you know and like if you
remove a bunch of that then all you're left with is the story and like that's what you get with the
anime it's like the story sucks who cares about the story you know they still think it's good
for some reason they still think it's good because the animation is cool and flashy you know it's like
all that anybody cares about is that all this dialogue and all this boring shit they just see
it as all of that is the justification for why I get to watch this fight scene you know like and and
not have to uh not have to think that the show is stupid you know let's say oh it's a turn your
brain off shelly no it's a think you show you have to pay attention to follow the plot the plot
stupid don't think about it here's a hot take I heard uh this will be my one comment about the
remake it was that uh in the original ff7 you would like grind a little bit through battles
to get to the story uh which was enjoyable it was the best part kind of in the new remake you
grind through the awful agonizing cutscenes uh to get to the fun gameplay sometimes and uh yep
hits the mark for me here you go this is my angry rant oh you know what's funny I watched
what were they thinking what were they thinking it was very i watched angry joe's review of it a
little bit angry joe loves the remake but he never played the original these perspectives are very
interesting god what i'm not surprised i'm not surprised how do you got it look yeah he can like
the original i guess or he can like the remake okay but how do you how do you be a professional
video game guy and you've never played f***ing final fantasy seven yeah he's just a different kind
of gamer i don't know he started off as a college differently abled he is differently abled yeah
were you saying something didgy uh no should we get our voice mails now uh we can certainly
that's literally like a film reviewer who's never seen like citizen kane it's like i mean
what you don't have to be a good reviewer of movies i don't know but you don't have to
see every classic but you should at least understand it's it's it's not that i don't think he can
it's not that i think you would need to to have a an informed opinion and be a decent critic i just
if you're gonna be that why would you not play like the most f***ing influential games of all f***ing
time i mean why would you do it that'd be good because you get into it too is to be this way
you see a fan of jr pitchers no not really no well then there you go he's the first person
shooter stupid guy i suck stupid ass dumbass angry ass okay uh enraged uh uh what's the spanish name
pablo uh but what begins with ease would be rhyme though say enraged pablo is good it's my it's my
new uh gaming youtube channel i'm starting right now ranting raul ranting raul that's a good one um
uh furious screaming simon now screaming simon whatever we solved it already we got it all right
all right anyway uh these are all good i'm gonna make my channel today uh i anger no that's he
already angry joe we got it perfect not to be confused uh anger man furious jesus uh sure
oh god um i have been listening to music as i work uh i have that that twi uh the tweet
that i pinned where i asked people to send me bands to listen to the entirety oh yeah the
entire discography of i've been going through those recently uh i uh listened to king gives it
an elizabeth wizard oh hell yeah which i've heard of but i've never really listened to pretty good
i recently i've recently finished murder of the universe which is like cool which is like war of
the worlds but you know like cool i love the universe is it the narrative the fucking that
there's a narrative definitely there's like narration that goes throughout uh part three has
this cyborg like synthesized i am a cyborg yeah and all he wants to do is to vomit and like the
vomit and die is he cannot vomit or die and so he wants to do those things to be human the last
song really stuck with me because it was like one of my big i don't know what to call it like fears
but like cool fears that i enjoy having um where it's like the like uh exponential growth of he
vomits so much that his like head explodes and then it is like his entire body is filled with
vomit and then just it grows and grows and takes over the entire universe and kills everything with
vomit it was disgusting it's like four minutes of this guy describing the the the exponential growth
of the vomit as it fills the universe for four minutes on end as the music gets just like rises
and keeps getting more epic in the background it's awesome have you i mean this reminds me very
much of that comic maybe i can find it i google it don't see it immediately where a guy's like puking
it's all stick figures and then someone starts pissing and then shitting and then every person
on the planet catches this thing where they are vomiting green pissing yellow and shitting brown
and like and it's a virus that captures the entire planet and it zooms out and you see there's just
massive spirals everywhere of like a three-point spiral of yellow brown and green as every person
on the planet sounds pretty similar to what they're actually doing it more that's it that's the
comic it just ends with that maybe i'll see if i can find it oh i found it i found it uh hang on
i got it right here it's got parts it's got parts like vomit coffin filthy breeze rotting skull vomit
bomb it's good shit man uh that that album also has the 30 minute song about altered beast
about becoming the altered beast whoa oh sick this comic is fucking awesome yeah it's great it is great
he's like spiraling upward as a project that would force him up stronger and stronger like boil down
to one image this is good thank you for chan for making this i appreciate that this is basically
homestuck this is basically what happens when you get the coronavirus sicko thing i'm staying
indoors like here's splatters of bodily fluids on the window i can't stop this is a this is a work
you're right i do need to give a succinct piece of apocalyptic fiction i've ever seen
like yeah well well well this is basically no man this is what how impact is lost at all
every panel uh has purpose and meaning every image is so dense there's so much going on every
panel they're pointing with their mouths open what do they expect to happen they get hit with piss
and then vomit and then shit and then every man woman and child i know i know this is just funny
but like the line of action on these are really good it's really shows the comedy
there's real talent here i mean i don't know small one my favorite thing in the third panel is okay
and the shitting intensely this is it isn't there's just a tiny little piece yeah the tiny
history of this starts but then it too swirls into infinite power look at the way this expression
changes across the first three panels as well he realizes what's happening just like uh to like
oh it's like oh no like by the fourth one he's moving so fast that you can't even make him out
he's just a complete blur i i legitimately love the effect of like the spiral that starts so
type of then widens out and then widens to the big like beautiful like end of evan gellion
yeah like why did he start spinning because each stream is so strong it's it's just forcing him to
spin i guess we need to track this artist down and interview him get to the bottom of all
like the sixth panel the p-stream has become as big it's like giants oh my god the panel where
all the people are pointing up at the sky did you notice that there's a u turn sign that just says
no you every panel's so dense it's a rich tapestry right here what what caused this i why did this
happen to this man i don't know what began this cascaded ronavirus
once i made a thing i can't remember one guy i made a comic that really had to be
i mean this is like this is a classic i made a comic somewhere this is making me hungry
i need some chocolate this is like some fucking uh bloodborne shit i think this is what's
gonna happen at the end of bloodborne when the the celestials touchdown the elder gods have their
way with us uh what is the um what is the long blue line in the it's a river the panel right
oh that's just a river as we zoom out for larger and larger that's a that's a river yeah yeah we're
just getting the largest scope of the world i think oh that's we're looking from above down at the
ground yeah yeah oh it's cloud spiraling round i see yeah that makes sense what was like i made a
comic i linked it on the pcp like a years ago somebody in the comics linked it i'm sure somebody
knows where it is it was like the sun has sunglasses and like isn't impressed by your
problems at the end of it or something i don't know that was like the theme i had somebody
linked that i don't know wait you made that yeah i made it i made it like i wasn't inspired by this
specifically but like i just wanted to make like a shit posty like apocalypse style comic kind of
like this uh so sometimes you just hit with the spark i guess and then you make it real fast
well on that note uh speaking of the apocalypse this is just a random story i'll never get tired
this is absolutely wonderful how do we even get here i forget i don't know or care this comic
this is yeah you don't watch devil man uh don't watch end of evan gellion you just need this this
really gets to the core of the matter and it's great and it's great all right let's let's do our
voicemails we've got voicemails let's do it if you have a lot i just want to get it done there's like
seven or so i think oh this one is very appropriate for what we've just seen this is called uh good
pcp content uh of which i think we've just delivered all right well uh let's hear it up
take it away go i just want to say this is one of my favorite arcs of the pcp in a long time
because every week ben will talk about animal crossing and i'm like playing that game and every
week nate talks about final fantasy seven remake and i'm like playing that game as well i feel in
the loop of everything like back in like november when every week you guys were just talking about
pokemon it was it sucked because i play short and shield and it sucks and it was it was just every
week it's like oh man right pokemon sucks they could all have the pokemon which scissors um but
now it's like you know you love final fantasy seven but also you hate it and like the remake and
you know it's cool conversation and animal crossing is just a giant pure force of good um
yeah that's correct there you go all right oh that's it i mean sure uh the our instructions
i know yeah instructions are do thing that guy knows and it will be good content uh agreed
understood messed received all right next one is uh rad content rollout okay here's an informational
request uh take it away yo lads uh i just wanted to ask you guys uh what are the holdups for
further rad content coming out at the moment uh nate kind of hinted at this at stream uh all
my stream but it wasn't very clear uh he said he couldn't release the rad lecture because he was
waiting on the diss track but my question is like is that what's holding up everything else
like is everything else being worked on because like it's just a little confusing like you guys
pumped out those you did really good you pumped out those lectures super fast you know but then
now we've been like stalling sitting on like these other two what is what is it two or three for
like a month how long is this going um i mean i just want to know what's up with that here and
like if the distract okay is what's holding everything back all right we get recorded yeah i get
he says stalling but it's like they're bigger projects they take long yeah i have okay well i'm
not i don't want to release the sonichu lecture until i finish the slime and punishment finale
which i have been stalling on and just putting off doing to do for other stuff uh so that's the
holdup on that uh lol this is the story of my fucking life i mean i've got so many projects
i want to do but i've got a first project i got to get done first but yeah let's just do it idiot
i'm just very curious about like which content exactly he
is waiting on because of the fact that like well yeah that's what you said is it there's the lectures
there's the brad carling house um yeah our distract distract and then there's the well there's the
distract in the lecture which are tied together the ova is obviously going to take some time and
the animation is a part of the ova uh the dojin admittedly i don't know if we've even started
like workshop i mean we're we're kind of not worried about that right now because we've got
lots of other stuff hold off on the dojin until the um the ova gets a little bit more yeah for
a lot further along i mean we need the character designs to do the dojin exactly which we're
working on which we're working on so we're making progress yeah the progress has been made on the
animated op for that so um be excited i guess indeed i guess good and then i mean i mean some of the
lectures you know whatever bed and munchie they got there we already talked about we already talked
about what's going on with digi's lecture and munchie's lecture yeah right right uh yeah we do
gotta make some progress on the distract uh we're being a little behind the curve on that one we
could uh we could move that one for itself what about what about all of the can tent that you filmed
well you know we did digi and i did make one can tent that uh is in production and i it will be
released but it's not quite ready and i'm just wait i mean i've just got other oh at least one
waiting till nate is done working on what he's working on before we relaunch canton yeah and
then we'll get back to it like yeah the the fact of the matter is canton got taken down and so it
was like okay well we're not going to worry about this channel until it's back and then by the time
it was back we had radcon four and then also having to pick up our own careers after radcon four
while doing radcon four editing which is generally what radcon does that's why we wanted all that
extra money to cushion us for the fact that you know yep it puts us in that position the good news
though i mean i'm very excited because can tent finally got to a point where like it's monetized
and we're getting like enough viewership now we will actually be making probably some profit
when we get back to making those videos so i can't fucking wait we had we had gotten monetization
we're already the videos were very profitable like the second they started making money because the
cpm is really good but it was just like we made like there was like one or two months and then
the thing got stolen we only had like a small window yeah but once we're back there i'm excited
or something like that but yeah yeah it's gonna be good it's gonna be good ton of potential and of
course if uh if nate is still moving on down to virginia beach then canton can be i mean like
basically for me it's hard to like the idea of the show is that it's going to be a show we do in
person so it's like yeah of course it's like almost to to do like a relaunch without it being like
okay we're relaunching so that we can get to the point where you're moving down then it's like
doing it before that point is kind of pointless like the show is not supposed to be a podcast
recorded online it's supposed to be recorded in person so like you know once we are ready to make
those kind of decisions that'll probably be when cancent is like fully ready to come back
which should be before too long yeah basically i've just been busy and me and digi need to
work out some details and we will do that we're both extreme both because we both bite off more
than we could chew and have too many different projects at the same time and uh and no matter
what you drop somebody will be pissed off so you can't just be like oh i'm just gonna not do this one
thing i said i do to do this other thing i said i do um that's true everybody wants you to do all
the things you said you were gonna do so yeah never promise anything never promise it's the only
safe way so wait so how how close are you digi to getting all those rants done you're still behind
the last time a lot left yeah i mean there's there's a lot of there's a lot of rants i have to do
where i already consumed the thing i have to rant i just didn't record the rant because i wanted to
do them all at once um sure there's plenty of them that i have i still have to like most of my
stuff i have to read which is a pain in the ass because it's a lot easier to just watch stuff
because i could just get high and watch it and not have to fucking read um sure thankfully i'm
changing the way all this works after i'm done with it but uh yeah there's a lot of catching up
to do good but it's it's like well okay there's all the projects i have on my plate are all big
they're all equally huge projects and like it's the same position i found myself in once before
and in order to to make it so that i don't disappear for two months to go do those big projects
i'm trying to figure out like what can i release that can come out that's not that hard to do
that will be satisfying so that's what the otaku ganzo journal is about i already wrote eight of
those so that's just fucking smooth sailing um while i go work on this other shit but yeah i'm
working on a lot of fucking big projects so it's going to be as usual with me all of them will
complete at the same time and so it'll go from like six months of people saying digi bro's not
doing anything he slowed down to all of a sudden wow digi bro put out six books and fucking 20 movies
and you know he's active again and it's like no i just finished everything i've been working on
you know oh and you know what i don't know i this seems like an interesting thing to mention just
while we're on the subject like the other day you made a tweet that was it was it was a joke but it
was something in the spirit of like um what like people are complaining about that i'm not classic
digi something along those lines um no it was that people have been saying that i've been losing my
mind for the last three years there's particularly this was addressed about my my uh not discord my
reddit because when i created the digi bro patreon discord all of my patrons went to the discord
and abandoned the reddit so the reddit is only occupied by people who are watching my videos
but are not patrons and most of them have a have a problem with me but it's weird because
they've been in there for years saying the same stuff like these are people who have been hanging
out in my subreddit and they're the only people there like it's just a bunch of people who are
like really sour and bitter about like the changes i've made to my content but like when
they talk about it the way that they perceive the content is is really fascinating you know
and and it just goes to show that they in their mind it's like i've changed because of the fact
that i'm doing these things before or doing these things now that they didn't know i was doing before
you know it's like this is the stuff that i used to post on moda soul productions or used to post
on after dark or used to post wherever but now it's on the main channel and like i think for those
people or even you know really i should say it started from when i started posting stuff on after
dark that wouldn't have been there before because even that was a more manicured channel up until
2017 when i decided to start putting stuff that would have been on personal channels there so
like from these people's perspective it's like oh digi rose losing his mind his content keeps
getting weirder it keeps getting his view counts are dropping and it's like well if you look at
2015 where i only put out four videos a month and one of them got a hundred thousand views and the
other three all got less than 10 000 and you compare that to now where i put out 30 videos in a month
and one of them gets a hundred thousand views and the rest have less than 10 000 which one do you
think benefits me more and makes me more buddy it's the second one you know like putting out more
content has only benefited me it's just that it it changes the way that it looks it changes it from
looking like oh this is a guy who bats a hundred every video he puts out to like this is a guy who
puts out whatever he wants and when he feels like he needs to you know make some money he goes and
makes some content that he thinks he's gonna make some money you know um but like that's a decision
that i make and like you can turn that valve on and off because i don't i don't always i'm not
always in a position where i need to be busting my ass and growing in order to survive you know
like i can take my time and think about what i want to do and do something that's emotionally
satisfying uh because i have that that extra leverage of you know of of my career but like
it's it's been a very difficult balancing act and the whole time it's been dysfunctional like it's
never been perfect i say a difficult balancing act because i've never been balanced you know i've
been imbalanced if you couldn't tell this whole time so you know still trying to find that balance
but finding that requires going through the process of exploring everything that you think
might lead you to get closer to there you know and i do that in a public way because i have to put
out content all the time like a lot of this content might be stuff that you know if i didn't have to
put out a video all the time i would only release a video once a month when it was a fully considered
well thought out idea you know but like um and there are some people who succeed with stuff
like that so it's not that i couldn't do that it's not my style you know it's just like it's
just funny to me that from my perspective it's like i haven't changed what i'm doing i've just
made it more clear what i was trying to do you know the whole time it's like my intentions have
become clearer and therefore people who thought that they could relate to me because they thought
i was somebody else are now upset because i'm not like them you know i'm not or i'm not who they
wanted me to be you know it's like to some degree i think i understand the the counter position uh
and and i can articulate so when when you put out the tweet i responded to you uh privately
in a way that i thought would represent what i thought at the time you didn't really you weren't
seeing the other side of the argument and we had i don't know we had like a little bit of a long
back and forth um where i i tried to present it where i said that like basically yeah the way
that you've articulated here is pretty accurate it's that like your main channel has not had a lot
of like the kind of classic digi content which which specifically i would think is is basically like
scripted content and actually the video you put out two days ago the fear of continuing a show
that right there that hit that like ah this is the kind of classic digi flavor well and that's
that's what i've been looking for but so to put it like in in terms of like my chart again like to
because this is how i it's easier for me to understand it it's like uh it was very difficult
for me to create a style that represents what i am trying to do with my videos in a way where the
audience will feel the same way about it that i want them to you know it's like so so long so
many of my videos the problems people have with them are lexical problems it's like you you said
something wrong you had wrong information or you came at like you didn't watch the whole show this
or that and it's like how do i make these people understand that i'm not trying to be a critic
like how do i make them understand that this channel is not being about fair and balance it's
not being about it's not about being objective because i don't believe in that and it's like
i think the problem is that in my mind because of the fact that i don't believe in objectivity
to me it's just obvious that like whatever data i'm presenting is not hard data because in my
mind there basically is no hard data people don't think that way though and so if you present your
video in a way where it feels like it's data driven it feels like it's meant to be informative
people are going to look at it as attempting to be an informative video and i did not know
how to make that feeling go away while still writing the same way i do which is to use lots of
information to make an emotional point basically and so that's what the otogonzo tapes is about
it's like this is the the each of these videos is using stuff i know about anime but the point it's
making is an emotional point it's not this show is good this show is bad i think i understand you
know i understand your point there but i think that my analysis of the situation is much simpler
which is that you're a guy i like listening to and i have for many years and and i find your
takes interesting frankly speaking just the fact that this was a scripted video that inherently
gives that kind of cadence that alone yeah i understand why that matters for you you're
you're completely spot on of what what my intention was here because the the idea of
otogonzo tapes is for quadrant appeal i'm going through the same thing right now as well so i
certainly i think i have some insight the the idea of it is just simply like i looked at it and i
said what is like how do you appeal to everybody on my on my neuro typing chart right like if you
want to people just because somebody is a more lexical thinker doesn't mean they want lexical
content they want if if the content presents itself that way they want it to be perfectly
accurate if it doesn't present themselves yeah itself that way they don't care so like how do
i make the video appeal to those people because my audience comes to me because of the fact that i
i do have information i do have insight but like yeah what i use that insight for is not to make
objective statements is to help you deal with emotions like my channel is mostly emotionally
driven it's mostly about like trying to understand what emotions a show is trying to fill you with
or like what message it's trying to send you know so like by focusing on that and presenting it as
like okay if this video is really like rough and rugged if it looks like it was filmed in a bedroom
on a vhs tape like it looks like a home video and it doesn't start off like it like the tone of it
just feels so raw and personal and emotional in spite of the fact that i'm mostly talking about
data you know but the data is there to make the point so it's like it appeals to people on both
ends of the spectrum both emotional and logical and it doesn't have nobody has to get hung up on
anything nobody has to be like oh i don't get where he's going with this or like you know nobody's
gonna miss the point because the point is so blindingly obvious in every aspect of the creation
you know and so like that's what i've been looking for is how do i make a video that's easy to make
and also true to myself and also not confusing you know and i don't think it's a confusing video
i hope i i thought found it pretty narratively coherent yeah but if i i mean in general i mean
i think we're on the same point here if i could if i could make one recommendation for your channel
i i your desire to i think there is a certain logic in the way things were split up before
where your your more polished work would go on the main channel because i don't think there's
anything wrong with in theory someone having a specific channel with a specific purpose
to attract a specific kind of audience i don't find that inauthentic i think that's a totally
legitimate way and then you have another channel where the stuff that's fine it's taking the approach
of just putting everything on one channel also makes sense however that just makes people sometimes
feel that they're missing some elements because it can get over flooded it's harder description would
be more scripted content because i just there's a thirst for that i think just more not all not
even most but more would be satisfying for the audience i think i mean ideally for me all of
my content would be scripted like the reason that this i guess the reason i'm positing this is like
such a breakthrough is that you notice that was a scripted video with no editing it was just
one take it was one shot one camera take it took no time to create because it relied on the idea
basically like when i i think nate you probably are somebody who when you write a script you already
have in mind everything that is going to visually or audially appear like in relationship that is
how i kind of create them yeah i am not like that i write the script and i have like maybe five
images in my head of like scenes from the show or the thing i'm talking about that are like
like where there's a sentence that i wrote this sentence because i had this scene in mind but
there's literally like five of them so for me everything in between those images is just filler
like most of my videos comprise of just lazy filler where i just cut you know 10 second clips
together out of the first episode of a show to fill as much time as possible it is not exciting to
watch you know but it fills time and it serves attention well enough for you to finish the
video but it's not memorable those videos are hard to rewatch or sit through again i want my
videos to be something that in spite of the fact that it only took me 30 minutes to make it was
memorable it made the point all the visuals contributed to both the emotions and the logic
of the video you know that's the ideal so sure and like you know once i had this it was just it
was kind of funny that you you sent me those messages and i i agree with your sentiment but
i was already like ahead i was already in that mindset like i already wrote eight of these videos
you know like i'm already ready to bring scripted content back it's just like a question of how can
i write a script and not have to spend 10 hours editing the fucking video you know for a perfectly
understandable yeah and still be exciting so that's what i might well i mean just some thoughts from
an observer and a fan and a friend um and that's true the same thing with like fune boray and uh
and 404 tales i just uh hope to be useful and i would happily welcome any any pointers about me
as i as i try to i know this all makes me think though there's all these things that other people
think about their content that i i feel like i am just blind to because of my particular perspective
and i want to avoid that i feel like there's very obvious things like i don't know ghost the shell
like big and a fucking best anime ever stuff just didn't come out for years that strikes me as just
a blind spot things i should have been doing all along and then i just let details get in the way
of why why that has happened well it's just missing the forest for the trees which is very easy to do
if you're a detail-oriented thinker you know very true very true okay well that all said hopefully
people enjoyed uh hearing some of those thoughts we do have more voicemails such as oh my god i'm
excited for this one okay this one is called uh is e pal simp okay listen listen to this lads
i found this strange website called e pal dot gg and uh it's like you buy like a session with
someone to play video games with you and uh it's mostly girls but there are dudes and like is that
simping is it because it's like it's one person and uh you're not paying for like uh explicit
like content like you know pornography or something it's just you're playing a video game with them
it's got they got like you know like overwatch you know there's people and they're like and
they even got like little voice clips to preview them but you're like hey indeed i'm absolutely
simping 100 percent simping let's uh okay we get the idea disconnect now okay is it is it simping
i mean sort of is it because it's sad you should just have friends that you can hopefully do this
with play a game with you for like a dollar that's right that's right okay but but i found a true
hero i don't know if you guys have gone to the website is it asian andy asian 25 bucks asian andy
25 dollars per game he has a platinum in league of legends was by the way there's some diamond and
challenger people that's not even that impressive they have tags like sweet voice silly friendly
no flame or toxicity easy to get along with i think i just figured out nice with a little spice
i think i just figured out how to define a simp you know what a simp is a simp is somebody who
who willingly puts himself in a relationship in which they have they do not have any control
or could not make any of it wait a minute wait a minute i'm thinking now is this about maybe this
isn't necessarily about being a simp maybe it's about like raising your like win ratio because
you play with someone who's really good i mean i think that might be part of that actually that
actually is not a bad idea i mean if you're playing with a guy who's challenger you're gonna
do better if you're playing with someone who's platinum or diamond like your team's more likely
to win i still think the optics are just terrible that you had to go to this website true but i could
understand but if that's not simping though dude they call roblox mobile if that oh fuck yeah
dude you could play roblox with asian andy in the gang if that's your motivation like i would argue
that isn't simming is all about what's going on in your mind you know that's really what it's about
so would that be something no if you're doing it to have any contact with a girl because i because
i think that a key part of simping is that like if you could get around it you wouldn't do this
you're doing it because it's like your last option it's your only way to and no one no one should
operate their life and they're doing like the last case scenario if it can be avoided but by the way
listen i i did a little digging i did a little preparing here because i want you guys to hear
all right i prepared the voice clip of the legendary asian andy i want you all at home
to hear the the dulcet tones of this man this is how he sells you 25 dollars per game with platinum
asian andy in league of legends here we go this is his pitch go yo what up um i'm just gonna try
my hardest i don't know cool that's it that's all he says oh that is he was at the top he was at
his number two best seller he's number two on the charts people okay this is really funny do you
i love it i love him is it only like one time payments or can you subscribe to somebody you
know i'm not sure how the business model works i really think that and this is why i'm trying to
like find a way to kind of escape from patreon to a degree not that i want to shut down my patreon
but i want to make it for specifically the otaganzo tapes as a show instead of being okay sure and
because i see a huge problem in selling yourself as a product because you by the way did you i
totally agree with you can we just observe this uh this rainbow dash next to asian andy in this in
this main uh just absolutely beautiful absolutely wonderful okay he's he's a king it's like when
you make a transaction with somebody right like each of you has to like make the decision to make
this transaction about this thing like you understand what the product is to whatever
degree you've you know interrogated about it and they want your money you make the trade
it's done you know if there's hard feelings afterwards take it to fucking court you should
have done your research right but like right on patreon it's like you pay me every month to do i
don't know like stuff it's very vague and like different people will be disappointed by different
things and i'm kind of swayed by their influence they're kind of swayed by you know and it just
it's such a weird relationship and it's exactly what we all feared patreon would be like when we
got on it in the first place i think sure sure uh which is why like i think you're still per video
aren't you or did you ever go monthly um oh sorry that cut off could you say that are you still per
video or are you monthly no i switched to monthly a while back okay because like per video we were
all doing that because we were afraid of this exact thing of like i want people to understand
what the product is you know and it's hard to do that with patreon and i think that's what i think
that simping in general tends to be the result of subscription of like committing to a relationship
with somebody who you do not have a relationship with you know right like oh i'm going to pay you
ten dollars every month because you're hot and i'm gonna watch your streams but like you don't
really know what you're getting you're not there's no real product it's just like i mean there might
be a guarantee of a certain number of streams or a certain number of photos you'll be provided with
but like will they all be of equal quality will you get the same emotional reaction there's so
much up in the air and it comes down to just this very strange relationship where like these people's
feelings get really tied up in it you know and like simping is extremely emotionally damaging
it just not a good thing uh so you know stopped i totally sympathize with your point how does
it make so much money twenty five dollars a game i think he's 301 people not bad i think it's because
he's uh like a uh a known stream that's what i'm wondering like this guy must be known outside
the side right he's gotta be i would think i think it says on his thing it was bio like streamer or
something okay it's the only way it makes sense makes sense so like he that they go to him because
he'll help them win the game he's charging more than these other guys though i mean jesus he's the
most expensive he must have a kind of love his pitch i'm looking at these other pages and um notable
but league of legends probably this is like sprung around league of legends and this is why that is
the top billing yeah that's why asian andy's up there's like like it's playing with good players
is important yeah um all of these other ones the best seller category is entirely women of course
of course we can play animal crossing it just shows you what's really going on you know they have
animal crossing there animal crossing great yeah there it is there it is hey but by the way though
to digi's point you know uh my uh about the patreon thing my look my ideal patron is like a i don't
know maybe he's like a a 25 year old man maybe i don't know 26 27 with a job and like likes my content
but spends very little time worried about it and then is just happy when a video comes out
but is not spending tons of time like concerned or like thinking about and his investment is low
you just want to imagine everyone who watches you is like the coolest person they could buy my
ideal really what i'm trying to describe what i'm trying to describe is someone who's not overly
my ideal patron is you to sublimate listener yeah you're it yes you you can do it uh yeah i mean
my ideal patron just somebody who's card clears at the end of the month
that's just a warm body yeah that's fair i'll take cold buddies i don't give a
shit i don't know that almost sounds a little bit like i'm trying to wiggle out of responsibility
but my my favorite patrons are always the ones that give me like 20 dollars and then their rant
request is like i don't know i just give you money so do rant about whatever you want sick sure
dude sure that's good that's truly king or even the ones who just don't request anything and just
they're like i don't even care i don't want any of this extra shit i could barely watch your content
there is no favorites in my patreon my i love you all equally you're so special to me i love you
so much i love you i love you proportionals of the amount of money that you have given me that
as well this is not a i can't even promise that yeah yeah yeah you well moving on if you're a dick
about it you can be a dick about it yeah yeah there is such a thing as an annoying patron that uh
that uh i don't think i have any we get i don't think i have any of those at the moment it's pretty
sweet i don't have any either all right well anyway we'll rush to clarify patreon yeah not you
no no you're fine no not you not you of course if you're thinking i hope he's not talking about me
it's not you it's you if you're having that thought it's definitely you oh shit he's definitely talking
about me i don't know 100 there was nobody i was talking about so it could possibly be you
why would you have that thought if it weren't you it's you right i do this thing a lot where
i speak in hypotheticals and it digs me into holes because i just sound like i'm you know saying
horrible things but uh legitimately uh no no i mean there are people who hang around my community
and aren't patrons and are annoying those people definitely exist but as far as i know no patrons
are annoying you know you can make it so only people with roles can see your discord so therefore
oh i mean that's true i don't even necessarily mean in discord like on streams or i don't know
comments i mean those people exist obviously but you know and if you're thinking that's you it's you
all right anyway let's go to our next voicemail okay we got patreon.com slash give and take give
and take dot side for a non-judgmental patron experience uh you will get the things that i
promise in the patreon fair fair all right here we go uh soundcloud uh what i'm saying
fucking the next next voicemail oh by the way speak pipe link leave his voicemails description
there you go this is a buster one nandesca let's find out go
matao pcp it is i eroge samura today i want to teach you the english word buster
please
you know that is a good uh just dose of reality because we kind of were just speculating what
does buster mean it like it has a definition it kind of works you got a gun buster it's got a gun
it busts the aliens well wait he just said he just said yeah it doesn't you don't bust the guns
and you do bust the crime so like what's going on it's not the same god the the words can be is
there outwardly two words like with the exact same spelling meaning the exact same thing but
they're two distinct words impossible i'm thinking maybe criminal okay well beyond that we have a
follow-up sort of this is a little voicemail called fuck die buster old good new bag okay take it away
go die buster is a shit show and you're all wrong it could have been a great original show but instead
they decided to make a shitty sequel the key to the striking plot and themes and gun busters
space and time and how these properties affect the characters and their relationships keeps
building upon this theme until the end of the show when noriko and kawasaki are are sure that
they're going to have been forgotten 12 000 years later in the future and at least that amazing fucking
ending that nothing could top uh all this shit not in die buster i have no idea where the characters
are what they were doing and why they were doing it warp technology was somehow banned i think in the
show uh but the characters can still be wherever they want to be it makes a bullshit science fiction
terms where everything in gun buster which was sick as shit also die buster had more budget but
somehow looked worse than gun buster last episode of gun buster wasn't finished or in color and was
still more visually compelling than anything die buster had to offer okay it was fun hold on okay
we got this guy i hate this guy we have to address this thing i get i get that i get i'm sorry i'm
sorry it didn't have the time dilation thing i'm i get it it's really cool i know you really like
but it doesn't make it a bad show because it doesn't have the fucking time dilation shit we have
to address this fucking thing that comes up where people try to like talk about the last episode
being in black and white and that this was somehow a cost cutting measure which is the opposite of
true that's not true it in fact i think costed more money because they had to like shoot in a
different way than i looked into this yeah you're right and yeah i mean like well just even think
about it they had to paint all the fucking grays it's not like they just yep like why would color
be more expensive than gray i don't understand i thought it might have been it's all paint it all
cost the fucking same it's at least the same possibly more uh yeah it was a stylistic choice on
purpose so that that that's out the window uh well i mean this guy i don't know it was this
point that like he does like that about the original about gun buster gun buster was not even finished
and it still looked better than die buster which is oh well it actually was and he was
trying to say that die buster had like a way higher budget it probably had a higher budget
but i'm sure it had a higher budget completely different in in my opinion die buster looks better
i mean die buster was like i agree most cutting edge looking show of its time like it was like one
of the first yeah like digital anime that looked amazing like it looks so good to this i get okay
you know i get a maybe you don't like the cg on the robots and i'll give you it looks a little
awkward sometimes but i don't i don't care i sense that this man just loves the like the
theming and the styling of the original which is more grounded in reality uh like okay i totally
respect that you would prefer this the narrative of the original and stuff but he's just making
shit up like how the characters just move around too fast as ben said remember how noriko's like
giant arc on what's that episode five where she unlocks her fucking power to get that to teleport
she's she's gone for a while because she has to go to the edge of the solar system to get that
you know to supposedly get that uh buster machine which is okay and whatever man you like a style
more that's fine as fucking dumb you know the fuck you like it's like a shitty sequel because it
doesn't stick to the theme get the hell out of here it is a unique story it's got different like
you get like one more voice jail voice jail voice jail voice yeah this man's going to voice jail
yeah it's just for a stupid ass take you know talk shit about die buster around here
his name is was fuck die buster he's going straight to jail there you go no i don't think so
fuck die buster obliterate it fuck you i won't fucking have any of his and it's just the only
other thing is just it's just that like yes it doesn't touch the themes but like the ending
like honors the themes of the original and in no way does it like fuck with the original in any
way it just adds good stuff i guess i guess he thinks opinion okay i mean like this the sci-fi
stuff is like messy maybe you think that like oh like all the science in in die buster is like
it's all like weird like fantasy science oh yeah like gun busters fucking uh like the actions this
robot does in space would like what is that thing where it electrifies with those weird
things on either side like the sci-fi of what gun buster did specifically was real to begin with
i mean it's obviously not stupid gun buster is cleared more harder it's harder sci-fi it's more
it's more grounded for sure i don't know it seems to me like that's the point like it's the far
future and like the technology has advanced all these crazy ways but also they've locked off all
these technologies in some ways the world of gun buster is more advanced because they use warp
technology i don't think they um that's true yeah did they um like i don't think they ever do like
light speed travel in die buster although i don't think they do they must because like i mean well
no no does but no no figures how long did it yeah yeah but like before that how long did it take
her to get to pluto it was like an episode where she was like shipped off or something she was it
was like a couple weeks i think right you know what because that would tell us if it was faster
than light if we knew how well the distance to pluto in light years is um well it's three point
well it's three billion miles okay three billion miles in light years is oh yeah okay it's point
zero zero zero five okay that's not light speed and she's not going light speed to get there so
i mean she's going really fucking fast but like a fraction of light speed like a small
for maybe like a tenth of it or something there might have been a little bit of dilation
um yeah okay all right how much is that is that one gunlation is that one two thousandth
of a no wait if it could be a person i guess it would be that's like that's like one two
thousandth of a of a light year okay so there's nothing where do the uh nothing okay question
where are the guys going in gun buster when they travel and experience dilation like in the episode
like three they go to like the center of the galaxy in that's really far away that's in gun buster
in gun buster they travel like all throughout the galaxy in die buster they only go inside the solar
system yeah because the um the red the like drones like are like they won't they're protecting the
solar they won't let them leave the solar system and warp technology has been locked away well there
you go we have just confirmed basically that die buster does not fuck with the sci-fi in those
important ways sorry sorry you wanted more time dilation i get it but i get it but it's just go
to jail it did everything it could do with time dilation in gun buster it pushed it to the limit
which is why it's good you wouldn't even want to show to try to do more time dilation stuff it did
the best job ever so let's do some imagine if if gurren legan two came out and they just said uh
we're going to be the size of two universes this time yeah i'd kill myself i would end it right
then and there uh yes yes so there you go oh but we found like a new energy source that is even worse
for the spiral nemesis that's the fly roll the by roll yeah with a big b emoji at the front the
viral energy oh i hate that double um all right anyway now that he's in jail and we'll never
hear from fuck die buster again we can move along with our lives the menace has been stopped
huh oh here we go okay this is um how many more we got two more only two more and it is
art so fuck so's wuxo duck so uh has something to say let's uh let's give him a chance go
i recently picked up drawing with the mindset to improve after several years of casually doodling
i've made progress since starting and i recently changed my head shape to be more stylistic and
i quite like drawing that way the issue is that i can only draw half decent body when it's done
realistically which completely clashes with the style i'm aiming for any advice on how to
overcome this dilemma would be appreciated i don't understand he can only draw body he can only draw
bodies realistically but i think he's gonna get a problem with realistic no he can only draw the
body realistically but the head that he has developed is more like stylized and so he's trying
to figure out how to reconcile these two things i mean you gotta just keep you're just gonna have
to practice realistically yeah it's just practice you're just gonna have to experiment with uh body
shapes that you are good at drawing the reason you can only draw bodies realistically is because
you don't fully understand anatomy yet once you understand anatomy yeah changes to it maybe if
there is anybody whose art style is like similar to what you have done with the face see what they've
done for bodies and see if there's like a an answer you know that's been been arrived at so far
oh but then they're gonna say you remind me of Naruto with your body shape and just wear it
probably be like yeah this guy was like yeah i'm developing my style it's like this there's seven
billion fucking people out there most of us are fairly similar in most ways why would you even
think you were gonna make something unique enough to be noteworthy to like like i mean it's so
frustrating to me because like the the artists who are like oh don't compare me to other artists
it's like bitch have you like spent any time looking at art like there is no art i wouldn't
compare to another piece of art there is no fucking such thing as one i'm not going to do that too
it's a pretty immature like mindset to be like i i don't want to be compared to anyone else like
like that's an insult if if you want art tutorials and you're just starting out and
you like people who are cool this guy is very very cool which like five seconds of this video
and you'll understand that he's the only smart you art tutorial person in the world it's a very nice
spider-man it's a good peter parker oh i've seen this guy once or twice the only two mistakes you're
making what's well there's a gunbuster game for ps2 the way he delivers the information is like the
least boring and therefore the coolest and the best way to do art i don't like his go actually
listening i'll have to check it out that's i don't i will not watch this man because he has a goatee
but he has a butcher's knife he he puts he puts his microphone on a knife and he speaks into it
that's true you're not wrong about that it's pretty killer it's america i i just clicked
on youtube and i was watching american flag aviators you know this guy is with me on team joe
dude fucking oh yeah no doubt i'm watching this fucking ps2 get the point yeah go on go on yeah
say that yeah the point is that he's like a professional artist and his advice is really
good and he's also a really good youtuber and i like him sick so he's got two microphones one
clipped to a butcher's knife and then one that's just a microphone i i've seen this guy around but
yeah he does a lot of experimental stuff i don't know why i'm so mad at him click play on this
ps2 gun buster game gameplay to watch intense noriko sweeping action as she pushes a broom
around the fucking sports field i assume this is the end we see coach appearing on the top left
presumably to give her anime hype speeches as she does this this looks epic and i love it uh this
is made for the ps2 we gotta play this so this is made like decades after the original uh fascinating
this is delightful i kind of want to explore this uh okay but anyway i wonder if we've got one more
voice for the game or the capture card that is just like the frame rate is dog shit yeah i'm gonna
guess it's like emulating it i think so probably capture yeah okay one last voicemail and this one
is from uh oh it's simply called azumi is based you know uh tom mo i just wanted to say that
azumi is very based i absolutely love azumi uh it just looks so cool i don't know if it's a girl
or a dude but like i wish i could play the game but my computer doesn't have internet right now so
i can't really how did you say this um maybe a mobile port would be cool but that would probably
take a lot of work so uh what the fuck i don't know man this is pretty cool it's based
voice jail voice jail voice no i don't know i appreciate it what's wrong with that he got his
point across just fine i am but isn't it just a suggestion for the the man who wants to play on
mobile yeah just bluetooth game pad the demo has game pad support if you can hook up a game pad bluetooth
to your phone you can play it on your phone oh hey what the fuck do you know cool wait does
actually run on your phone then wait the game is on web app it's a web app right the game's on
new grounds right yeah it's on new grounds oh yeah it's on game jolt yeah right okay any of those
any of those there you go boom i was thinking like wait was there another release that i didn't play
yet i mean i updated it a couple like before ride con on new grounds yeah with like some
combos and better hits done can you continually update your like that link on new grounds with the
oh cool cool okay i was wondering is it me or were all these voicemails from the same guy some i
think i think this one and the good pcp content were from the same guy i think all the others were
from different people soundly like paradox now i don't like maybe it was no that's not paradox
what if you put one voicemail from a person in voice jail and the other one from the same guy in
voice grail does he get split is he like the emperor from final fantasy two who is his good
aspects are put into heaven and his bad ones went to hell and took over yes uh yes okay good
settle that all right voicemails leave more for us at the speak pipe link down below they
tell us it's full but they just keep adding more get fuck speak pipe i don't respect you because
you have no boundaries um that's it we've got patreon.com slash the procrastinators there's a
new bonus episode out there's 37 of them goodness gracious koof cast is out join us as we don't
listen to the fucking koof casts oh don't don't do it to yourself it's painful in more ways than
was it just koofing nonstop or what i wish
we've uh but there's 36 other voices well bonus episodes that is like a big political argument
for two hours yes we do have intense arguments about things and it was a rough time but we got
through it and we remained best friends so i feel i feel grateful for that you can experience that
in real time great won't that be fun um or you could sit right now go on right now if you
listen to this when it dropped right now probably we are getting either doing or be getting close to
the the Kickstarter ending stream ends 9 p.m today this friday right now right fucking now will we
make a million fucking dollars how many fucking pins will we make we already made so many can we
make even more i think it's possible for running prickers cop tours twitch.tv get some exciting
get some go do it lads uh uh follow us for updates and what not uh more release and stuff on twitter
at tpcrastinators that's the hub of information blah blah blah you'll see everything there uh
more kickstarter stuff will be coming in time we're working on it so give us some time we'll
keep rolling out if you've heard your updates here today and uh and that's it and more voice
smells the peak pipe blah blah blah yeah all right that's it everybody yeah you guys never
think about how you're just a brain jellyfish in like a bone mech with like meat armor yeah
yeah sometimes yeah sometimes yeah i like it but it's like a ava mech where you're like linked
and you can feel all the pain that it feels yeah that's true that's true yeah i like that i like
thinking of being a mech skill i want to upgrade my neck to like actual like i i turn i turn my neck
and like uh dude the the spine is so fucking complex dude what was that uh what's the philosopher
that's about like the homunculus that lives within like the brain and that's like just what people
used to think oh really yeah well then what gave that guy his ability to think uh another
homunculus inside his brain and on and on it goes yeah he's just jellyfish piloting jellyfish
piloting jellyfish all the way down i love it we have a word for that Nate it's called the ghost
in the shell uh i mean that's true okay but but what gives the ghost its consciousness is my
question the ghost and the ghost the shell oh the ghost we're all just meat we're all gonna die
we're all gonna be in the grave soon guys but life can still be coming it's coming to find our own
meaning things will be so much easier dude you can't make yeah you make your own meaning and then
it doesn't oh you're dead well it doesn't matter that's great that's coming oh i mean if we made a
meat we may as well barbecue if we're made a meat you might as well have a barbecue now that's
an sentiment i can get behind that sucks that absolutely base have you guys seen oh was that
one video i think we talked about it where a guy climbs onto a bargain but he asked his friend
to drill yeah that's what i that's what it was by the minute the hour the uh that's the one i forgot
the name we will link that the minute hour barbecue i'm gonna make sure that one's linked
all right uh that's it for this week everybody enjoy that have a good day
and we will see you next week with another pcb episode see you then bye