I'm going to bless that guy. That son of a bi-
That son of a-
That son of a bi-
I gotta say, my new microphone does make me feel a little bit cool.
It wasn't really even that expensive.
Should have upgraded a long time ago.
But better late than never.
Microboy.
That's what my sexual partners call me.
Anyway, welcome to the Procrastinator's podcast.
That's as good a place to start as any LA's are keep it all in.
Welcome to the Procrastinator's podcast.
The program podcast.
It's Ben St. who's giving to you.
Hey, here's my bit for the day.
Okay, ready?
Yeah.
Are you ready for my bit?
Row, row, row v-way, gently down the drain.
Merrily, merrily, merrily, merrily.
Life is pain.
Okay, yeah.
Pretty good.
That's pretty good.
I think I've improved the mood.
I did it.
I...
Damn it.
I had forgotten about...
I had woken up this morning and I hadn't thought about that.
Yeah.
And I had forgotten about it until you just reminded me.
It is one of those things where it's like everyone was so upset, understandably,
and there was the only thing I could see on Twitter.
I was everybody talking about it.
I think everybody wanted to not have that be the timeline anymore,
so they decided, okay, I'm just going to talk about other things now
and then Twitter is completely different the day after.
And I was like, wait, I don't want to forget about this.
I would like to not worry about it,
but I don't want this to fall into the background.
It did not fall into the background for me at all.
You know, I had a realization about who I follow on Twitter.
I'm pretty sure that like a lot of the people that I follow
are people who have podcasts that I don't listen to,
but they were like friends with the chapeau guys.
I feel like a large percentage of people that I follow
are people who are on Twitter who have podcasts,
like who were on chapeau, who are friends with chapeau,
and that's how I know them, even though I don't listen to their podcasts.
Because I don't know where a lot of these people come from.
I just like their takes.
So anyway, all that is to say,
no, I never stopped seeing it on Twitter.
In fact, you know what I did?
I did something unprecedented yesterday.
I downloaded an app and I blocked Twitter for myself.
Oh, good.
Yeah.
That is a good thing to do.
Not specifically because of Roe v. Wade, although that doesn't help.
I just don't think I use it in a healthy way.
I don't use it in a productive way.
Even though I feel like I see other people use it the way that I use it
and nothing bad happens to them.
Well, I mean, you don't know that.
I guess I don't know that.
I guess that's true.
I was looking into the Supreme Court
and I didn't learn too much.
I didn't do a big research.
I see all these pictures of guillotines
and I'm like, cool, nice.
We're all on the same page that this isn't good.
Change the Supreme Court would be the thing.
And I'm like, okay, well, how would we do that?
And they are on there for life, apparently.
They retire, but there's no thing to force them to retire.
They can retire, yeah.
So they would have to decide to do it and...
Well, the other thing would be to pack the court,
which is to expand the court and make new positions
and then appoint new people.
Right, I heard about that.
Joe Biden didn't even give a shit to try that.
He was just sitting there.
I don't know what he does.
No, they don't want to rock the boat.
Well, we don't want to upset the fascist.
We don't want to upset anyone.
So it's like, I don't know.
Why don't we just lock them in a hole in the ground?
Called a grave.
Maybe you've heard...
I don't remember who I saw say this,
but this is a sentiment I've seen expressed by a lot of people,
but the most succinct way, the most punchiest way I've seen it,
was people hear that the Supreme Court Justice appointment is for life,
and most people hear that and think that it's a long appointment,
but I hear that and I think, hmm, but it could be a short appointment.
I thought that's pretty good.
Yeah.
What was the old lady who died recently?
Ruth Bader Ginsburg.
Yeah, how old was she?
I remember hearing things like she was like...
I don't remember exactly...
Almost 90, I think.
And she had cancer.
People were saying she was so old she had to retire,
but she stayed on for some reason or another.
Yeah, she had cancer a few times.
She was very old and she had a history of cancer.
I don't know exactly what killed her, but...
Was it COVID?
Because I know she went and she was at that wedding.
One of the last things she ever did was she officiated some people's wedding,
and then she died.
Just like Andrew Hussie.
Did that happen?
He died?
No, not that part.
Yeah, he didn't attend a wedding, but he did die.
I need to know more about the Supreme Court.
I haven't really wanted to...
The vague things I've seen are like,
wow, this sucks.
Either you stack the court in order to make it more...
so that you can push your agenda, whoever's in power.
And it's like, well, surely that means the other side could do it again,
which is obviously what Trump was able to do by stacking the court.
That's not what he did.
Like, primarily Republican Christian idiot people.
He didn't expand the court.
No.
It simply worked out that he had to make three appointments.
Well, okay, there's actually a little more to it,
because it's not like Trump had to make those appointments fairly,
because Obama had appointments that he could have made,
and the Republicans in the Senate,
they didn't refuse his picks.
They simply refused to convene to decide whether to appoint his appointments.
See, like, this is stupid.
So it's not like it was fair, yeah.
Obama should have made one of those appointments.
From the ground up, the idea that this, hypothetically,
the Supreme Court is a bunch of people who are very, very smart,
and they make the unbiased opinions when partisan people in the Congress
make a bad idea, and the Supreme Court, who are so above all that,
who are not partisan at all, will sort it out and make it good.
But they don't, because they're humans, and that's a stupid idea,
and I don't know why the system even exists to this day.
It seems very archaic, and obviously will be a real problem for democracy forever.
It's some sort of fantasy to believe that these people,
oh, they will simply look to constitutional precedent.
They'll simply look at the Constitution itself,
and in interpreting what one document or precedent document has said before,
they will thereby arrive at the most, I don't know, the most constitutional thing to be done.
The Constitution...
It's stupid, it's outdated, it's just paper making new country.
Sure, but even if we accepted that the Constitution is good,
it's not like there's any objective truth to be arrived at about what it meant.
Maybe sometimes there is, but it's not like you can actually go
and just read into it exactly what was meant in every situation,
and dig all you need are the seven of the most unbiased people in the world,
and you will get the most constitutional government.
It doesn't make any sense.
It's vague, and it doesn't know the future, so certain future things have to be interpreted
based on text from the past, so it's impossible to know the rules going forward for everything,
and it's just a bad idea, which is why it's still there,
because it can be easily manipulated to do whatever you want,
and that's great, they love that.
Fuck in, did you read Clarence Thomas saying,
yeah, well, we got this, we got rid of abortion.
We should literally look at interracial marriage,
we should look at interracial marriage next, and gay marriage, and contraception.
We should reconsider whether those should be protected.
There's no secret about it, they're just saying,
alright, so civil rights, we never liked those,
and now that it's been proven that we can just get rid of them,
we should think about getting rid of all of them,
and there's nothing that anybody can do about it except, I don't know, nothing.
There was that one senator saying, we should look at Brown v. Board of Education,
we should consider segregating our schools again.
They're just doing it, man, they're just going for it.
And the Democrats are all saying, vote, vote, on what, how?
What are we supposed to vote for? You're already the president.
They said this was on the ballot, and then, well, we elected Joe Biden,
and I think we expanded, I think we expanded, we got more seats in,
we got more seats in Congress, Democrats got more seats in Congress,
and they didn't, you know, they did not codify Roe,
so, well, you didn't do it, and now they got rid of it.
So how is it on the ballot? How is this on the ballot anymore?
Yeah, I don't even know, like, from their perspective,
like, all I can assume is that they like abortion being gone,
some of them, maybe Joe, I know Joe has been like anti-abortion in the past,
but like, you know, like, what do they feel like a game plan is going forward with this knowledge?
Like, all I see is them saying, remember to vote for us because we wouldn't do that,
even though you let it happen, and you're not doing anything against it,
so it's almost like, I don't know, there's an evil villain,
and there's like, I'm evil, I'm doing evil things, and then a little, like, frog is there,
and he's saying, I'll stop him, but it's a frog, and the evil villain has like giant boots and a gun,
and like, he can squash the frog, and the frog's not going to do anything anyway,
he's going to rib it in the pond, and that's it.
Like, why would I vote for this? Why would I give money to this?
You're not going to do anything.
It's true, it is true, so that, I don't know, vanilla opinions on Twitter said,
and they're right, like, on the one hand, it is true that like, had a, what was it,
like, if we had more Democrats in Congress, or if Bernie Sanders had won the nomination in 2016,
or if Hillary Clinton had beaten Trump in the general election, then it's true
that Roe v. Wade would still be on the books.
Like, any of those things would have done it.
Sure.
So, it's not like voting doesn't do anything, but on the other hand,
What is voting going to do right now?
I think more than anything, like, very, very, like, notable protests are the bare minimum,
because if people in power, if the Supreme Court don't feel like this decision has impacted
America in a negative way, or at least their own, like, situation in a negative way,
if they don't feel scared about it, nothing will go right.
They need to know, somebody needs to know, somebody needs to know that this is not good,
and the American people don't like it.
Yeah.
So, protest is like the bare minimum.
Well, I'm sure they do know that.
I'm sure they do, but like, you know, you can't rely on the morals of the people in power,
but you can rely on their fear of, like, people running into their house
and burning it down and killing them.
Yeah.
That doesn't seem to be happening, though.
No.
That's what I've been waiting for, is knowledge and stuff like that coming on the news.
Hasn't happened.
Sad.
Yeah.
Well, what are you going to do about it?
I don't know.
I'm just going to...
These extreme...
I've seen some people calling it, like, backwards, like, oh, these justices are so backwards,
like, oh, this is such a backwards decision.
It's not...
I don't agree with that description.
It's extremist is what it is.
Yeah.
So, these extremist judges are just going to keep...
You know, they've got a 6-3 majority, so they're going to do more stuff just like this.
And then they're going to...
And then Congress is going to vote to give them more police protection,
as they continue to take rights away,
and then people are angry and they want to do something about it in Minecraft.
And then Congress is going to give them more protection to prevent that,
and the cycle will just continue.
And I don't know what's there to be done about it.
Yeah.
Our lawyers have said we cannot continue the podcasts from this point.
We must move topic.
Yeah, that's right.
It's true.
There's nothing else to it that you can infer the rest.
Moving on.
God, it's so fucked.
It's really fucked.
It's hard to even talk about.
I'm glad I'm over here that he's in there.
Yeah.
Over here in the UK where...
Everything's good.
Everything's good and there's no, like, idiot in charge.
I mean, the only thing I'm hearing about Boris Johnson lately is that
he had that party during COVID that has been, like, the monster beach.
He had a party during lockdown.
Like a Super Spreader event?
Like, no, no.
It was like during COVID lockdown, like you said, everyone stay inside.
Oh, like a big masked ball inside of a castle while the commoners were outside?
Yeah, essentially.
He had, like, a party with alcohol and no masks and no vaccine didn't exist at the time.
And he was just like, haha, people have to do what I say, but I don't.
I don't have to follow the rules.
And he was like, that has come to light and it's, like, been proven.
And it's like, aha, we got you.
That's all.
Is that what they were doing?
The vote of no confidence in Boris over?
I thought it was a big, like, referendum on Boris.
There's been a vote of, I don't know if there's a vote of no confidence specifically,
but like a bunch of people in the conservative party have left in embarrassment
or to save their own careers to not be associated with Boris.
Boris is just sitting there and saying, I'm not going to apologize.
I'm just going to stay here.
And that's that.
Cool.
And there's been by-elections in the areas where members of parliament have left.
The conservatives have left being in charge.
And so there was a little election and there was a Labour win and a Lib Dem win.
And so there are less conservative MPs than there were before.
And Boris is just sitting there saying, I don't, I'm not going to change.
I'm just, this is how I am and I'm going to the future.
Ukraine, we've got to give money to Ukraine.
Good for him sticking to his guns.
Yeah, I mean, you know, I love him.
You know what?
I'll kiss him on the mouth, but I hate him.
When the woke mob comes to cancel you for no reason like that,
you just got to stand your ground.
Don't apologize to these people because it's never enough.
So that's never, never, never enough.
That's all I'm hearing about at the moment with regards to the leading of the UK.
It's just, if Spar is going to resign, no, Bob, but, but, but please resign.
No, I won't.
Come on.
No, be reasonable, please.
It's just, it's just so like whatever.
Nobody, he doesn't care.
And he doesn't need to leave.
You could do so much better.
So he's not going to.
I think we should get together now.
And that's what everyone's talking about.
Yeah.
Hey, hey, you, you, I don't like the prime minister.
Okay.
Sorry.
No more.
Yeah.
So like Boris is like shit and he's Trump adjacent and he's a, he's a money grubbing,
power hungry idiot who doesn't know anything.
Huh?
Is this his second term?
He, we don't have terms in the same way.
Right.
So they're not like, it's not a set amount of years.
But I guess, yeah, it's his first like being in office.
I think he did.
There was a, some sort of a referendum at some point.
And he got more members of parliament, like conservative, one more.
Cause Theresa May was embarrassing.
But because of the, this, the, the smear campaign against Jeremy Corbyn,
Boris Johnson gained more power.
And it was dreadful.
It was awful.
So like the UK sucks politically, but at least, at least we're not getting rid of.
At least abortion is legal there, right?
Yeah.
We're not getting rid of like.
That's dire.
It's so fucking dire.
Civil liberties have been enshrined and like everyone in, in most of the world agrees
are a good thing unless they're like a fundamentalist, extremist, religious, zealot idiot.
Yeah.
Well.
What did, what did, um, I just keep, I just keep thinking about Contra points tweet about
that, that woman that screamed when, when Trump got elected.
She was right.
She was exactly right.
She was 100% right.
And we all look stupid for making fun of her.
She had a completely proportionate reaction to what would, to what would come of that.
She knew much better than we did.
It's incredible.
Yeah.
Um, anyway.
Well, I'm going to go move to Saudi Arabia.
See, uh, they got better, they got a better healthcare over there.
A civilized country.
I just have to pretend I'm not trans.
Uh, Saudi Arabia.
I'll be safe.
Wait, that's the really bad one, right?
That's the extremely bad one.
Yes.
That's the really, that's the one that Trump's like friends with.
It's weird.
This is going to sound stupid.
It's, it's weird to me that Trump seems like he's like, like he's like taking credit for
this win.
And I remember, you know, he, like during the campaign drill, he was saying like, uh,
will, will, he said he would do exactly this.
I'll put judges, conservative judges on the bench and they'll rescind Roe v. Wade.
And that's what he did.
And it's kind of weird to me that like he cares about that because he doesn't seem, he's
not a religious guy.
He doesn't seem like a guy who would really give it.
I don't know.
Just like that's what his base wants.
So that's what he's going to promise.
I would imagine it's what his base wants.
Yeah.
More so than like, cause he's a power.
Cause he's a pro vaccine.
He's like, like he's like in favor of the vaccines.
And he's like, he views the vaccines as like being like a big thing that he got done under
his presidency and he's proud of it.
And like a lot of his base really, that makes them really mad.
Yeah.
Trump is not extreme enough for them.
As it turns out.
He's the QAnon king.
Yeah.
He's more of a human being than they want.
And they are looking for more like free.
What's the, what's her face?
Marjorie Taylor Greene.
Yeah.
Like she, she's the, the sort of person QAnon and, and that type of, of, of conservative
once in a Republican once in a, in the old power.
Yeah.
Well.
Uh, that's, yeah.
He, he's got, yeah.
Trump has his, has his regrettable human foibles, like, uh, thinking vaccines work and so forth.
Uh, you know, forgive, forgivable eccentricities.
I mean, he did deny them for a time.
Cause, you know.
Well, yeah.
And then, and then I don't know when, I do remember he said, but you really should get
the vaccines and then his whole crowd booed him.
Well, he didn't, he didn't say, he didn't say like vaccines bad.
He bunk, he did bungle the COVID response, but he didn't say like,
I can't remember exactly what he did.
Don't get back.
I'm sure it was a Trumpism.
I'm sure it was really stupid.
He just, he basically just said like, uh, you know what, don't worry about the virus.
Uh, we're going to try to like, we're just going to ignore it and hopefully, and not
let it hurt the economy.
And, uh, and that's, and that's our strategy.
Yeah, that's probably it.
Get back to work.
I'm going to wear masks.
He, they, they, they, they like didn't do anything about it.
Like when, when it was becoming clear that it was going to be like a serious deal, he
like really downplayed it and was like, we're going to, uh, what do they call it?
There was this particular, was it like the no fear strategy or like the no panic strategy
or something like that, which is basically just pretend it's not a problem, uh, for
as long as possible.
And it was great.
You know, uh, she, man, she, it's, it's pretty, it's, I don't know.
It's all, it's all pretty disheartening this week.
Yeah.
It was a rough week.
It's, it's been a rough week.
And it was, for me, I was dealing with a bit of depression.
Oh, you too.
Before the news.
Me too.
Great.
It's not just me.
All right.
Cool.
No.
Yeah.
I, I got a therapist or like a, on better help.
I don't know if that's good.
I was just sort of like, I don't fucking give a shit to like research anything.
I'm just going to type in a therapist on Google and get something because I just, I just
need something.
Um, and I got this lady and I'm talking to her a few sessions now and I was talking
about her, I was talking about being depressed and she said to fight depression.
I don't know how smart this is or not.
Uh, but to fight depression, you need to get out of your own head.
Sitting there stewing in your own brain is the worst thing you can do.
It can lead to suicide.
When you're depressed, you need to distract yourself.
You need to get into someone else's head.
So like talk to someone.
Failing that, uh, distracting yourself with video games and TV is, is adequate.
And I'm like, Oh, well, you know, when I'm depressed, I feel more depressed and guilty
when I go binge like a show or just play a games over and over again and feel like,
Oh God, this sucks.
But I do realize that in the moment when I'm watching something really good, like, uh,
I've been rewatching Breaking Bad.
Yeah.
I do not feel depressed during those times.
And so if that's, that's, if that's adequate to like distract myself, I've always felt
like distracting yourself from your problems is a negative thing and you shouldn't do that.
Damn.
If that's adequate, then call me the king of adequacy.
Yeah.
Cause it's just, I don't know.
You get these, these impressions of how you're supposed to do things based on life
experience.
And then a therapist tells you, no, it's okay if you want to binge watch stuff.
Yeah.
Just try not to like focus on your negative thoughts because you're going to go in a
spiral.
And I do.
So, uh, everybody distract yourself.
Uh, do, do anything.
Do anything but think about the current state of the world.
Yeah.
Uh, I've been, um, I've been playing, I've been playing Mega Man.
Sometimes I do it on stream.
I've been, I've streamed again on my Twitch for like the first time in forever.
Uh, yeah, which is kind of neat.
Uh, feels, feels, makes me feel a little bit bad because well, yeah, distract, you know,
playing video games doesn't accomplish anything and it makes me feel a little bit bad.
I feel a little guilty that I'm like, what am I, what am I accomplishing here?
Um, I feel when I, when I stream on Twitch, it's like, it's good, but also I feel bad
because I let, I let that language for two years.
I've been in the stream for two years and I feel like I lost all the momentum that I
had with streaming that I once had.
And that really bums me out.
Um, I mean, I guess that's, that's it.
The, the, the guilt of, of things, I mean, I, this is not something the therapist told
me, but it's like, um, something I picked up is like, uh, when you're worried about
doing a lot of work, being productive and then you're depressed and you don't feel
like you can do the work.
Um, and you say, or you're told you need a break, you need to give yourself a break.
And then during that break, quote unquote, you keep thinking about how all the time
that you could be spending doing the work, uh, you're physically not working, but you
are not on a break while you're thinking about it.
You're still mentally taxing yourself with the, the, the stuff that you should be doing.
An actual break is like to not think about it, to, to completely indulge in anything
else, to get your mind off it for real and not for a little bit, you know, for an actual
break length, which is why I've noticed when I, when I take a break, um, in a stupid way
and I'm like playing a game or doing a thing and I'm like, okay, this is just one day of
this.
And then I can back, back to work, back to work as fast as soon as possible because,
oh shit, all this time, uh, I hope, I sure hope this break doesn't take too long.
Like that sort of, that sort of mindset is like stressing yourself out and you haven't
actually started the break.
Your break time is zero.
And then you get back to work and it's like, oh, what the fuck?
I thought I had a break.
Why am I breaking, what am I breaking down immediately again?
It's just, it's all so fucking difficult.
You just got to actually fuck off.
Uh, I, on the, on the upside, on the upside, I am, um, I am nearly done with those fucking
book footnotes that I've been kind of working on here and there and like putting off and
putting, I've been putting them off a lot.
I don't know why I've been putting them off so much.
I should have gotten them done a long time ago.
I was like halfway done with them like three weeks ago.
And now I'm, I might, I'm genuinely, genuinely going to try and finish them like today after
this podcast because it's, I only have a little bit more to go.
They're like 20, it's like 21 pages.
It'll probably be like 22 by the time it's done, which is, I mean, that's kind of a
lot, but it's not that much.
The average is out to, I wrote like less than a page a day, which is not.
No, there you are doing like the spectacular.
You're thinking about all the productivity stuff.
Yeah.
It makes it harder to like get back into the swing of things if you're always like
shitting on yourself of things that have already happened.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah, I guess so.
It just feels like, it just feels like I haven't learned anything.
It feels like I should be, it feels like I should have figured out how to, how to get
my shit taken care of sooner than this.
I mean, when you're depressed, it's just not easy to do anything.
Yeah.
It's not like you can logic your way out of depression because it's not a logical state
of mind.
Like the, it's like a, what is the worst thing that I could possibly be thinking about myself
right now?
Oh, that, please think that over and over again.
It's not, it's not logical.
It's silly.
It's chemical imbalance.
It's dumb.
Maya.
Are you dumb then, Saint?
You know, that's a great, that's a great, let's explore that question for a while.
I think, I don't know, I've been, I feel like I'm pretty stupid lately.
Yeah.
I feel pretty, pretty dumb.
I think I have, you know, that secret project.
I think I've definitely fallen into a spiral of like infinitely preparing for it.
Like, like I was, I was ready to do it a couple of weeks ago and then it got delayed and I'm
like, okay, well this means that I can be even more prepared for it.
This means that I, and I think I have, I think I have fallen into a cycle of, you know.
A cycle of playing Mega Man and not even doing that.
Yeah.
A little bit partially, yeah.
I, you know, this is, this is not really related to that exactly.
I mean, that's, that's just, that's one thing that I'm like, I should, I should have done
that by now.
There's many things that I feel like I should have just done some things.
Why didn't I just do them?
I feel.
Because you weren't, you weren't mentally all there.
What's the term that isn't rude?
You weren't mentally like, I don't know, geared up to do that work, which is why you didn't
do it.
I guess so.
I mean, that's just, that's just how depression be.
I don't, I don't know.
I just, I think.
Like hypothetically, if, if, if we didn't have these, these problems, obviously we'd do more
work, because we wouldn't, we wouldn't be stopping to second guess every decision we make all
the time.
But that's not like, that's not reality.
Sometimes it is just, it's a blockage.
I think, I don't know.
I think I don't know enough to like give advice on that.
But I feel like, like the mindset of, oh, I should have done and why haven't I done is
like, it's, it's doesn't like, it doesn't like constructively get you closer to being able
to do what you think you can, or have done in the past.
Like, like I drew, what, like the whole of Lord of ghosts and almost the whole act one,
two Lord of ghosts and Clarissa in one year, within like a, in a few months stretch each.
I'm like, surely if I can do it that quickly, I should have finished all of those two years
later and have like a whole other thing going.
But I'm still like not doing that.
I'm still like fucking around.
But if I think about that too much, it just becomes more difficult to actually get back
to that level of, of productivity that I was.
So it's not helpful, I guess, to think that way.
I feel, I feel like, I don't know.
It's not, what worries me is like, it's not just that I'm not productive.
Like I've gone through like productive and unproductive spells and like, you know, whatever.
The fact that I didn't get the footnotes written until now and it's like too long,
like that's not great, but, but whatever.
It's gonna, it's gonna get done.
It bugs me out that like, I feel like I don't know, I feel like I don't have like anything to,
I feel like I don't like want anything.
Like I don't feel a strong drive to like, oh, when that's done, like I can't, I can finally get,
get to work on, on something else.
I don't know, I don't know, I don't even know like what I want to do after that's done anymore.
I had other things that I, that I wanted to work on.
And now I'm, I'm just like, I don't know.
I was gonna get back to like old projects, but like none of them ever took off and are they even worth doing anymore?
And if not them, then like, what else even is there to do?
I don't know, I'm kind of feeling like I've wasted my life lately.
Kind of, kind of feel like maybe I should have done something else.
I mean, what do you want to do?
I don't know, nothing, nothing, no, I can't.
I don't know, I don't know, I hate everything.
I hate everything.
I have no, I have no passion for anything.
I hate, I hate drawing.
I hate art.
I hate, I hate the, I kind of feel like I wish that I like had like written more.
Like maybe I like actually like wrote stuff like wrote essays.
I feel like maybe I used to be kind of okay at that, but I haven't done it in so long.
And like, I feel like I kind of deliberately avoided doing that.
Like I deliberately avoided like doing any sort of activity that would like carefully structure my thoughts on things.
And now I have like, and now my mind is completely disordered.
And like, all I have are like vague feelings, like things that make me angry.
But no like clear thoughts about anything.
And no desires or passions.
Do you feel compelled to like finish projects for no other reason than just a vague compulsion?
Because you do that and that's what people expect of you?
Sort of a little bit.
I mean, I feel like all the things that I started in the past,
I mean, there were reasons I wanted to finish them.
It's not like it's completely irrational.
But I mean, I do feel like I want to do that.
I do feel a sense of obligation to go back and finish old things.
A lot of them have built up and some of them I probably might never get to.
But some of them I feel like if I were more effective, I would finish them.
Some things I don't know even what I would do.
I feel like I don't even know what the champion would be if I went back to it and started working on it again.
I don't know what I would do with it anymore.
You have obligation based on past precedent, but you don't have motivation to do any of it.
Something like that.
You feel like if you were a better worker, if you were someone else, then it would be good that they get done.
Yeah.
Hypothetical question.
You're a Benz saint and you don't do any of those things.
How do you feel?
You decide not to do them ever and that actually is the case.
You don't ever go back to any of these things and you just live your life and that's the end.
How do you feel about that?
Like I decide, okay, I'll never do any more of the champion.
I'll never finish Biscopades.
I'll never finish my Winnie the Pooh retrospective.
I'll never make another Nuzlocke and I never kickstart the Slime and Punishment book.
All that.
All things you don't have motivation to do, which is everything.
Well, I guess I would feel like I wasted years and years of my life.
Well, would it be wasted if you didn't finish them?
What about the things you did do?
Yeah, sure.
Well, I guess I would just feel like there was lost potential there.
I think that I had started things and not finished them when they would be better if they had been completed
or seen through to a more logical conclusion.
Would you feel good if they were better?
Like if they were done?
Yeah.
Yeah, if that list of things that I just rattled off, if it was shorter, yeah, I think I would feel better.
Because if maybe there were just one or two things on the list, I would feel like, oh, I can just get to that.
I can just do it.
So if all of those things either abandoned or finished, what would Ben Saint be doing?
Oh, that's a great question.
I don't know.
I feel like, well, I guess I could maybe start a new comic project, but I don't know what it would be.
I have no ideas.
I could maybe start, I could try doing more writing essays, but I don't know what I would write them about.
I don't care enough about anything to write about it or think about anything.
So you're thinking of stuff you've already done doing more of that?
I could just quit doing the internet stuff and go get a job, but I don't know what I would want to do.
I've thought about that and even that.
I'm like, yeah, but what would be the point?
What about that would even give me joy?
What would you do with money?
I don't know.
I don't know what I would do with money.
I already can afford to live and what else do I need?
I don't know.
That's it.
Yeah.
I'm just struggling.
I don't know.
Well, surely there's things you do like, like the gummy creation that you seem passionate about.
I like that, but I feel bad.
It makes me feel bad that it's not more of a fruitful endeavor.
I don't really get anything out of it.
I guess I wasn't happy to.
You mean like money?
Yeah.
It's not like accomplishing anything.
It's just like a thing that I sort of do as a hobby.
I guess it's my hobby, you could say, but like, you know, I figured out a recipe that I'm happy with.
I made some gifts out of it, gave them to some people.
That was good.
That was gratifying, but like, well, I did it.
I feel like I would be more satisfied with that if I had an idea like, oh, okay.
Well, I finished the recipe now to the next step of my plan, but there isn't one.
Do you feel like there's no point doing anything if you don't have a larger plan to work towards?
Yeah.
Have you ever heard of Jesus twice?
No.
Maybe you could tell me about it.
I don't follow his plan.
Have you ever heard of this guy QAnon?
No.
He's posting again.
Oh, I love posting.
You had me at posting.
So, yeah, I just feel very unmotivated and very adrift and I don't know what I even want to do with my life anymore.
I have thought about this a lot, this sort of thing.
A friend of mine talked to me about how I'm beating myself up over things like, what's the point if I can't make it a career?
Or if I can't increase in skill enough to do well for it to be worthwhile for me or other people.
It's usually a down to money.
It's also down to satisfying myself.
And they were like, do you accept yourself existing?
Aside from accomplishments, past and present, future, do you accept that you are allowed to exist?
And I realized, talking about it, I feel like I don't.
I don't think of myself as worthy unless I have accomplishments under my belt or that I can work towards getting money, notoriety, skill, self-satisfaction, fame through art that I make.
I don't feel like I could live with myself if I didn't do any of those things.
And they said that was an unhealthy mindset that you should be able to hypothetically accept yourself and that's it.
There's no prerequisite.
There's no bar you need to reach.
You don't need to do anything and you should be able to be okay with that.
And that's tough.
I still don't know really how to do that, but it's helped to think about it a couple times where it's like, if I stopped doing everything that I'm doing, would I be okay with it?
How do I accept who I am?
Because when there's no motivation to do anything, there's no reason to do it.
You feel like there's like, what's the point of everything you could possibly do?
Everything left is like nothing and then are you okay with that? Are you okay with nothing?
Yeah, not really, no.
I feel like I could be doing something that means something or matters or contributes to the world in some way and I don't feel like I'm doing enough.
And I feel like it's a waste.
Like I said, I feel like I've wasted my life.
If you know what I mean.
Yeah.
I think it's something to mull over at least.
Oh, I will.
Don't worry.
Because being, I don't know, like requiring yourself to reach certain standards of worthiness for you to feel okay causes you to never do anything because you're so upset with yourself.
And it's not so much that you should accept yourself as a hypothetical do nothing person for the purposes of being productive later.
But that does tend to happen when somebody is like, it's like the whole like, oh, nothing matters.
But they got sunglasses on.
They're like, yeah, nothing matters.
When you reach that point.
It's like a funny thing looking at it but to actually reach that point you need to genuinely like feel like if nothing happens and you don't you don't do anything then that's cool too.
And then it's easier to just do something for no reason.
I think the past couple years, you know, I think a lot of what gave me, you know, what gave me a sense of motivation to do anything was like, I don't know, a couple of my videos or whatever got pretty popular people knew me, people like knew about that stuff.
And I had like some recognition for those things and people wanted to talk to me about those things.
And like, it's not that I was like super, it's not that I was like super invested in the things that like, I don't know, Chris Chan or a unicorn jelly or whatever or tails gets trolled.
It's not that I like love those things passionately and want to talk about them but just like the fact that people knew me for something and wanted to talk to me about something.
I was passionate about that.
That gave me motivation.
And in the absence of that, like the things themselves don't mean anything.
And I guess I could try to like do that again.
Think of something random that is not actually important, but like try and do something with it that gets people to be like, oh, hey, Ben, you did that thing about the thing I like.
Well, let's, I have an opinion about that.
Let's have a dialogue and I'll be like, okay.
You get a little envelope.
I like dialogues.
You open it up saying, hey, Ben Saint, I saw your video.
Now you can live.
Now you feel like you're worth something.
Sure.
Yeah.
That's like my hog, my version of the Hogwarts letter.
Only it's better because it's not from JK.
Yeah.
So it's, it's, yeah, I felt like that as well.
But it does lead to, to feeling that if it's unlikely that people will care to not do anything, which I guess is a lot of what you're feeling with like, oh, I haven't streamed in a while and my momentum is down.
So there's going to be less people who are going to be affected by my streaming if I continue, if I started up again.
It's like, well, if people aren't going to say Ben Saint, I love your streams, what's the point of starting it up again?
I've lost everything.
Exactly.
You're exactly, that's a great point you just made.
I couldn't agree more with it.
Well said.
No.
It's a bad thing to think that.
Well, I mean, bad and good is whatever.
I just think it might be.
There's actually no difference between good and bad things.
You idiot.
Yeah.
I just, I felt like it's, it's been something I have to try and get away from hoping like to get validation from exclusively outside is, it sucks when it doesn't work, when you're not getting constant love and attention.
And as soon as you're left on your own and your momentum is gone, you feel like there's no reason for anything because you don't know how to like feel accepting of yourself as a person who isn't making big fat stacks and loads of views and clicks.
As Zero would say, what is it?
What is the line?
Zero subs.
Oh, no, it's like, uh, well, it's like this, this can't be happening.
There's no reason to go on.
What am I fighting for?
Yeah, you know, what are you fighting for zero Ben?
And nothing, nothing, just, just to live and feel cool about myself.
That's the only two things I want.
You just want to stay alive and I want to feel like I'm cool.
And I'm only managing the first one.
It's not enough.
You got to feel cool by being alive.
You got to, you got to find the, the, the self acceptance.
Ben Saint, the zero subscriber boy.
What do you think?
Oh, pathetic, pathetic.
No.
He's valid.
What's even, what's the point?
What's the point?
Yeah, sure.
He's alive.
But what's, what has he, what has he ever contributed?
What has he ever done for anyone?
He doesn't need to.
Does he not?
No.
I don't, I don't care about anyone I've never heard of.
So if no one's ever heard of me, then nobody cares.
And what's the point?
Well, that's the whole thing.
If you're living in a vacuum and you don't care about you, there's no one else to do it.
You just got to do it.
You got to love yourself, Ben.
You dumb motherfucker.
Um, yeah, I mean, I guess you're right.
Yeah, but yeah.
It's difficult to do it, but like knowing that that's something to work on is important.
I, I just, um, I guess, I guess I just, you know what, I guess I just wish.
I think even if, you know, it's not, it's not so much a clout thing.
It's not like, oh, I don't have enough clout.
It's not even that.
I wish that I had something, I wish I knew what I felt passionate about.
Something that I like, I wake up, something that makes me wake up and I'm like, I can't
wait to do that thing that I do today.
Like I got something I'm working on and I'm like, I gotta get back to it.
I, I haven't felt that way about anything in a while.
And when you have something like that, it doesn't matter if you're, if you're fucking,
if your video got a lot of views or whatever.
It's just, it's just like, it's, there's a reason to go on.
What am I fighting for?
I don't know if this is like a common thought.
Probably is, but I feel like a way to do that, a way to find purpose in something is to think
selflessly about someone else to like, I don't know, to help someone else with their problem
and forget about your own for a bit.
And it's, it's easier to like find passion to get that done than it is to, to love yourself.
And it's sort of, I don't know, it helps kickstart things.
If it, you know, if it's difficult to like create a gratitude from nothing, if you're
just sitting there doing nothing and I'm like, well, I'm not making anyone's life better.
And I don't like myself just sitting here.
So it's, what am I supposed to do?
You can just like, service someone else, be, be there for someone else.
Oh, okay.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, you could suck a dick or two.
I mean, I don't care.
Sure.
You do, you do what you like.
If that's what gets you out of bed in the morning.
Yeah.
Like, I mean, did T-Bab, you, I mean, T-Bab was like a joint venture.
And so you had the, the, the sense of doing it because you were doing it, but also Nate
was doing it.
And so you were helping Nate and he was helping you to make the show.
That's so it was, it was easier to stay motivated and get motivated because you were, you were
helping someone while you were doing it.
That's true.
That is true.
I mean, even for the PCP, like it's easier to come on the show when there's someone else
to talk to you because I'm not just doing a podcast for myself.
I'm, I'm there to be part of the show.
Man, I don't know what I would do if like it was just me.
I don't know if I would have the fortitude to carry on with it.
Yeah.
Sorry, I wasn't there last time.
No, it's okay.
It was a Father's Day thing, but I also sort of forgot.
It's understood.
I mean, yeah, it's fine.
I'm not, I'm not saying like, am I saying every Ben cast is a, is a, is a tragedy that
like devastates my self-esteem.
Well, I'm not going to say it out loud, but no, I don't care.
No, it's fine.
But my point was just like, you know, I mean, I don't know.
I don't know if, if I could be like, well, I'm the only, I'm the only procrastinator
left that I'm just going to keep showing up every week and rambling into a microphone.
I don't know if I, if I could do that.
Yeah.
But like you said, like you said with TBAP, it was like, it wasn't just to get the project
done.
It was we are, we both are working on this thing and I must do it not just for myself,
but for my, my partner as well in this, in this business venture.
And that was helpful.
It was.
And, you know, okay, what you're saying about like, think about how you can help someone
else.
Like I, I agree.
I feel like I don't know what value I have to offer someone because all I can do, this
is why I say, this is why I feel like I've wasted my life because what, because what
can I do?
I can, I can draw kind of.
And that's it.
I used to be, I used to be good.
I don't think I am funny.
I don't feel like I'm funny.
I feel like sometimes I'm funny by accident, but I'm not, I would not, I'm not like a comedian.
I'm not like a, I don't like make jokes.
Well, I don't mean like it.
I mean, like just talking to someone.
Like it's, you're fun to talk to.
I do, I do feel, well, I don't know.
Sometimes, sometimes I feel like I'm pretty good at talking to people and like I can be,
and like I can be, I don't know, charming.
I'm sorry.
I don't mean to tube my own horn.
I feel like I can be, I don't feel like it's a, it's a huge boast to say.
I feel like I can be charming and that's fine.
That's, that's good.
I guess that's, that's a quality.
I don't know what to do with that.
I don't feel like that's value that I could give somebody.
A value would be if I could, if I could, like if, I don't know, if I could write something
that was really like insightful and people could get something out of it and be like,
ah, this, Ben has had an idea here that has taught me something or clarified my own thinking.
Or I mean, it doesn't have to be writing.
If I could do that through art somehow, I guess that would be fine too.
I don't know how to do that.
That's why I say I have no ideas because I don't know what would be like a valuable activity
I could be participating in that other people would get something out of.
I guess the most straightforward thing to do would be if I like got a job
and then I would be giving value to my employer in the form of wage labor in exchange for, for a wage.
But I don't want to do that because I hate capitalism.
And I would see that as an evil.
I would, I would, unless there were some side benefit to it, unless I were achieving some other thing,
by that I would see that as like a net evil that I was inflicting on the world
by moving capital into the hands of a, of a bourgeois fucker.
You know what I mean?
I do know what you mean.
I've seen these videos on YouTube of like people powerwashing random people's driveways for free
and then making videos about it and getting paid via the videos.
So they have their powerwashing equipment and they go by, they drive by,
they see somebody's like got a really dark and dirty like overgrown sort of driveway front porch area
and they just go knock on the door and say, hey, I'll do this for free and they do it for free.
And then they leave and it's, it's, it's a nice feeling thing.
It's also very satisfying just ASMR just powerwashing something, seeing everything become cleaner.
And so it's like, it's revenue for them so they can exist in capitalism,
but they're not like taking anything from anybody in the community.
It's, it's, it's nice.
I always thought like that would be a nice job, kind of.
I don't have anything like that.
I gotta say, that sounds completely ridiculous.
I don't think that sounds stupid.
I'm not suggesting you get a powerwashing equipment.
I'm being perfectly honest.
No, it's great.
Look how clean that, that concrete is.
Okay.
It's not, people aren't going to slip on it anymore.
That's true, I guess.
It's not just dirty.
It's like overgrown with like, like, like a, like a walkways like covered with years of mud falling onto it.
And when they clear it, it's just better for people to walk on.
I don't know.
All right.
Okay.
So it's a civic, this is like basically like a civic sort of volunteer.
Yeah, it's volunteer work.
But via YouTube, they can, they can fund it.
Yeah.
It's just sort of a nice thing about YouTube, I guess.
Who would watch that?
Me and thousands of millions of people, honestly.
Commentary, is someone like commentating the cleanup job that they did?
I think it's just sort of an inherently satisfying thing, watching something be cleaned.
Is it like a time lapse?
Like you watch, like you watch the area become cleaner?
Yeah.
Like they set up the camera and they do it in first speed and they just sort of spread,
splash all the water and they get all the grain gone.
And sometimes they commentate over bits, but most of the videos I've seen people just like
watching it slowly be cleared.
It's like, ah, yeah.
Cleanliness.
Oh, I'm parking.
I mean, I can understand the appeal of watching something, watching a transition from disorder
to order.
That's an inherently satisfying thing to witness.
But like, I don't know, I was, in terms of like, oh shit, what was I talking about?
I think I was saying something about like jobs.
I don't know.
Yeah, you don't want to be a capitalism wage slave.
I don't.
That's the first thing you can think of to help.
That's the most straightforward way of like, oh, Ben, how could you feel like you were actually
accomplishing something?
How could you feel like you weren't wasting your life?
It's like, well, if I, if I just got a job, then I would be doing something.
But also, I don't, I think, I don't think like a lot, you know, a lot of people say like,
oh, just get a job.
And like, then you'll be contributing something.
And I don't agree with that because most jobs, well, a lot of jobs are worthless.
A lot of jobs exist like solely to just like solve a problem that like the company that is hiring you created for themselves.
Right.
Sure.
Bullshit jobs as the late Graeber wrote.
But I mean, that's why I mentioned the thing because it's like these, it's not just power washing.
It's like there's this guy who clearly very autistic, but loves clearing drains that have flooded and they've got like Schmaltz started like blocking the drain.
And he's just going around the side of the road, usually in the rain.
And he's got like his like scraping tool.
And he's like, oh, we got to go to clear this drain here.
And then you watch his like a whirlpool form and the water goes down and he just does that in the local community.
And the people around like know him and he makes his videos and people just love seeing like the it's it's selfless.
It's like it's hard labor, but it's serving the local community.
And it's just sort of, you know, it's it's making places safer.
It's solving problems where bureaucracy might get in the way and like a guy would never come around to fix these things.
If he didn't.
Yeah.
And it's just sort of like that's the sort of work that is gratifying is is helping people locally in ways that like capital bureaucracy doesn't help.
Just like, I don't know, like clearing somebody's driveway of snow, if they are too old to do it themselves like some some small thing like that makes you feel good.
If it's not like commercially viable.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know if that's sounds that appealing.
Look, I'm gonna.
Well, yeah, I mean, I'm not saying you should do any of these things, but like, right, sure.
Jobs aren't all bullshit.
There are there are things you can find.
I'm sure it's just volunteer work that you do like part time, you know.
Yeah, I just if I feel like if I had something, if I feel like if I knew what I wanted to be doing and I were doing it or I were doing anything that I felt strongly about, then what would naturally I feel like what would naturally
happen then is that I would feel is that I would have things happen.
Things would happen in my life that I would have feelings about and that I could talk about and that I could, I don't know.
And maybe and maybe then I would feel strongly enough about something to like write an essay about it and make a video about it or something like that.
So, or or.
Yeah.
But in but instead I'm like, well, I don't I'm not doing much.
I'm kind of just wrapping up old stuff that I did before.
I'm not doing anything new and I'm not like engaged in any like exciting new projects or I'm not working towards anything really at the moment and and therefore I have nothing to say.
And it's like, and it is a self reinforcing problem and then the fact that I have nothing to say about anything.
It's like, well, I won't.
I'll just, I guess I'll just won't say anything and then there's no.
I don't know.
There's no push and pull of forces that would compel me to act in any particular way and I'm just like, well, I guess I just going to just going to keep existing then.
You're an art.
Yeah, which is like, I guess I should be.
I guess I should be happy to theoretically accept the existence of a Ben that doesn't do anything, but I'm not.
But I feel like maybe I'm talking in circles now.
I understand, like the whole like, I don't get how I could accept myself if I don't do anything.
I think part of the thought process you're supposed to go down is like realizing that doing nothing is bad.
And so you want to be doing something that's productive or good for who and that's why it's like help someone.
And even if it's like you don't use your skills in the most efficient way, something as simple as just being there for somebody that you know, or like talking with someone.
Small things that are like selfless and just provide whatever you got to someone else will like kickstart a feeling of, I don't know, feeling like you can, you can help you can do things.
And it's sort of ideally spirals into feeling better about yourself in general because you can you have value to other people.
And it's like, I don't I'm not like explaining it the best.
I mean, it's not like you can just like get it like figure it out after one conversation on a podcast, but it's a it's better than being sad all the time.
Okay, I don't know.
I don't know what I don't know what it is that I want to hear.
No, neither do I.
Yeah, like I don't know what I want to hear either.
I feel like maybe I'm helping.
This is a therapy session.
I'm the therapist now.
I have been the therapist.
I am.
I know that they say that like, I guess they say that like, when you have a problem sometimes it's best to like, how would if someone else came to you and told you that they have the exact problem that you have.
Like what would you tell them?
Like what what would your advice to someone else in the exact same position as you're in be.
And I guess I guess what I would tell myself is like, oh God, I don't I have to I'd have to get I don't know, man.
I have to give myself some platitudes like, well, you just got to find you just got to find what what you're passionate about.
You just got to find something that excites you.
Oh, you just got to like, yeah.
What else?
What else could I say?
I know.
But like, um, that's that's the sort of thing that's not what you want to hear from someone else.
No, no, no.
So how what would you say to yourself the thing you want to hear?
What I what I'd like, what I'd like to hear is like, what I'd like to hear is like, hey, hey, Ben, you know what, I've looked over your resume.
I've looked over your skill set.
I've looked over everything you've you've done in your life.
And I've just and I have I have a I have the perfect job for you that is going to that is going that is perfectly suits all of your skills, all of your abilities, and also includes a kick my microphone and also because full dental insurance.
You start on Monday.
Ben, that's a capitalist job.
I'm a how can you live with it?
I would I it's like I said, I would I would a job would be fine.
It's not that I think jobs are bad.
It's just that I think bad jobs are bad.
I would like a job that was good and that had me doing work that I cared about.
So what's your skill set?
I don't know.
I mean drawing.
I feel like I can I feel like I'm okay at like I feel like I'm like drawing and writing dialogue.
I feel like I'm pretty decent at naturalistic dialogue.
I feel like I could like storyboard for a show or something.
I feel like I could do something like that or it could be like a presenter.
I don't know.
I feel like I'm pretty good at just talking off the cuff.
I could present.
I could I could lecture.
I feel like I could give like lectures in like a classroom maybe.
I hate although I mean I when I was it when I worked as a teacher before like I didn't I didn't like it.
I like talking.
I didn't like like lesson plans.
I didn't like answering questions.
I didn't like explaining things.
I didn't actually like the teaching part of it.
I found it really frustrating.
I mean it seems like like video essayist as like maybe like the YouTube cringe as it is seems like you would enjoy doing.
Yeah.
I wish I could do it.
But like I would like I can't you.
Oh well I would have to write something and I don't know.
I don't care about anything.
I feel like I would have to care about something in order to have something to say about it.
And then I could write it and then I could make a video about it.
And that's what I'm that's what I'm missing.
Well.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
No I mean it's not like I expected us to figure that out.
Like.
Yeah.
I feel like with me my problems late my problems all boiled down to just like a lack of motivation to do anything.
If I could if only I could solve that if only that one that one Lego brick could snap into place.
The everything else could become could be erected around it if you know what I'm saying.
Well I mean I think we're going in circles now we are going in circles.
The motivation if you have nothing if you have nothing you care about then caring about someone else's problem and trying to help them.
Right.
Sure.
It's like it's a way to start.
Yeah.
If you don't know what you're doing someone else is doing something.
Well that's great.
I don't know.
I don't even I don't even know what that would look like.
I mean when I think about like.
It could be as simple as just.
I really.
You know asking people how they're doing.
Yeah.
Sure.
I mean whatever.
That's not something to do with your life.
It can become I think I think the motivation like passion for things usually comes from experiences that you have.
Not thoughts that you come up with like in a vacuum just like no no love for anything sitting in a blank room and then suddenly you decide to care about something that like like it's doesn't work like that.
Out in the real world things happen and eventually you like have strong opinions.
Yeah.
Like OK I've got to do this and then suddenly you're motivated to do one thing.
Yeah I know I agree.
Well I agree but I don't know what else to say about it.
Yeah.
Do you want to hear about my fucking house hunting that I've been.
Oh yeah.
Tell me.
Yeah I've been I've been shooting off emails to people on Craigslist and it's been going OK.
I've seen I've seen two houses so far and they're one of them was one of them seemed like it was about as shit as my current place so I wasn't that excited about it.
One of them seemed better but a little bit more expensive and a little bit less a little bit less convenient like location wise but not that much less convenient and like maybe OK I don't know.
Part of me wants to just like jump on that and just be like I don't even want to look at any more places like second places saw like and it's adequate like I'll take it.
I got it.
How does it compare to the things you've seen to your current situation.
Well it's better than my better than my current situation.
I would say.
I got it actually.
So I think some guy has been impersonating the landlord from that place.
Here's here's a weird thing that happened.
So I went to see that place.
A guy who lived there showed me around.
He was like OK.
You should OK if you if you're interested in the place contact contact Ross Ross is the name of like not not the owner but the property manager like the guy that manages for the owner.
I'm like OK.
So and then I get another email or maybe it was a text message.
I don't even remember from someone being like hey my email is like Ross something at something.
You know message me back and I assumed it was the same Ross.
So I message him back.
He's like he's like send it to me on my send me an email at my personal email this other email.
I'm like OK so I contact him and he's like and he starts asking me like Ben sign up for this website like sign up for this website like pay a subscription fee.
Like sign up for this website and get like and show me a screenshot of like the information it gives you and that's what you got to do to sign up for the property and I ask him like are like are you.
And he's he asked me if I want to see that I'm like I already I already saw the property like what are you talking about are you.
I think he was a scammer or something and I and I and I told him like I think you're a scammer and he said like and he the way that I know that he's a scammer is that when I told him.
You're a scammer.
He continued to ask me like OK but if you want the property like you got to you got to sign up for this website like you got to you got to send me that.
And I like that's not something that like a real a real person would would take would be called a scammer and be like well I guess our business is concluded then.
You're like a mouse sniffing a mousetrap.
You say this is a mousetrap.
And it's like yeah OK but if you want the cheese you really have no no I'm not.
Yes yes yes.
I don't know why this guy wants me to does this guy work on commission to get people to sign up for this fucking website.
It's I don't know very very sus but I asked the guy that showed me the place and I asked him like I asked him is this the guy.
And he said he said yeah it should be him but then he gave me his phone number so I texted the guy's phone number and I don't think it's him like I really hope it's not him.
That would be really creepy.
The guy the guy seems the place seemed fine I would I don't know.
There's no way that like a legit landlord would ask you like hey go sign up for a paid subscription website that will tell you like if you're a good renter and then send me a screenshot of your home page.
It's insane.
There's no way there's no way that's a real thing I refuse to believe it.
Legit landlord I don't know if those exist.
Right right well sorry.
Anyway there was another place I was.
They wanted me to come see it this morning but I told them like I can't do it on Sunday mornings and so they said like okay well I'll contact you and tell you another time you can come see it if it's still available and like fine.
So I don't know.
Might just jump on that might just jump on that that's second place.
Because whatever.
Well I hope the move is.
My bullshit free.
My current landlord will certainly give me some bullshit there is certainly going to be some nonsense where.
She wants me she wants me to give her more money than than I actually need she's going to want me she's going to want me to pay the last month's rent even though I already paid the last month's rent when I moved in.
She's going to expect that she should be able to keep my security deposit on top of you know the 12 months rent that I should rightfully pay even though I didn't do anything fucked up to the to the room or whatever.
There's going to be some bullshit.
But I'll just fucking have to deal with it.
Came home from a thing the other day and the landlady and her husband who I had never seen before were in my kitchen.
They were they had gone into my room.
They had opened my door and looked in my room which upset me a lot and I complained to them I was like you can't do this like you like you need to give me notice I didn't get any notice.
And the guy was like oh sorry sorry.
And I was mad and they knew I was mad but they didn't know what to say.
And then the guy came back and he knocked on my door and he showed me an email and he had he had in fact sent like a group email to everyone that lives in my house.
So there had been an email notification I just hadn't seen it because it was like one day before.
And I just like shit.
This doesn't make me happy.
This like this doesn't make me feel better.
I guess it means you're technically right.
But I still don't like it.
So I don't know they're going to they're going to there's they're going to try and get away with everything get away with.
And that's just I've accepted that.
I ended up I ended up regretting not just picking a place that I found like right away not just jumping on be like I'll take it it's good enough I'll take it.
I'm debating what I don't know like is this is the place I found already is it good enough that I need to do that.
I'll I'll be honest.
I don't know.
I last last year when I was looking for places I thought like I don't know I kind of thought like it would matter.
I kind of thought it would matter like if my place was nice or anything.
I don't know.
I don't know if I even care if my place is nice.
What's the point.
What's the point of a nice place.
You know if my come you live there and if it sucks then you hate it.
I don't know.
I feel like I feel like even if it's even if it sucks or it's nice or whatever I'm still going to do the same shit.
I was just going to do the same shit.
It's just going to sit around and accomplish nothing either way.
That's how that's how I'm thinking.
That's how my thinking is right now.
And it's probably not.
But yeah but hypothetically suddenly Ben St.
You got like motivation back.
All right.
But you're in an ugly place that sucks.
It's harder to do stuff.
I guess that's true.
I may as well be nicer.
I would be setting myself up for success.
Yeah.
To have a slightly nicer.
Rent for the life you want.
That's true.
Maybe.
I guess I'll send off maybe a few more.
If I send off a few more emails go check out a few more places and maybe then if none of them measure up to this place then I'll jump in it.
But that's what I said last time.
And all it took was a few days before the place was not available anymore.
And it's like I want to wait and see.
I want to wait and see.
But I can't.
Place could be gone already.
I just don't know.
Yeah.
Things are.
From what I've heard.
From you and like from other people.
Renting.
Is.
It's it's almost like.
Built to force you to make snap judgments and buy the place because.
It moves so quickly.
Yeah.
I mean.
Landlords just they just want to get the room filled.
They're just like.
We just want to make absolutely sure there's no like downtime where nobody is.
Is renting it so.
Yeah.
That means that like as a renter you're like well.
You better be you better be the first acceptable.
Person to ask to rent the place because they'll give it they'll.
They want you.
Yeah.
The like.
It's so quick.
If they're like oh there's a land mine in the bathroom but you didn't have a chance to see that.
When you looked around the house the first time.
And then you're like sure it's fine you get it.
And then go into the bathroom explode and die and the whole building crumbles.
The guy showing me around the house told me we went to the basement.
And he told me like.
He told me like yeah you know years and years ago.
There used to be like there used to be like house shows down here in the basement like they used to do you know like bands.
Like they used to have parties with like hundreds of people down here.
I can't imagine how it was wasn't that big a basement I can't imagine how hundreds of people fit but I could.
I you know I'm sure you could fit a lot of people if you really wanted to.
So we said that.
And I was like okay it sounds pretty cool.
And he was like yeah you know things are things are quieted down a lot you know since the pandemic and all.
And I was like that's that's great.
And it just and it just made me feel like I'm living in the post apocalypse.
And what reason is there to go on what am I fighting for.
That's the title of the episode.
Yeah I think what are we fighting for.
I don't know what I'm saying.
Did I say what that's a reference to do you know did I explain that.
You said is Mega Man zero something something in Mega Man X five in zeros campaign.
There's a part where zero has to fight his girlfriend I guess and she dies and he holds her body up and he yells this can't be happening.
There's no reason to go on.
What am I fighting for.
Amazing dub on that game the best.
Oh like voice acted.
Yeah they they it's if you ever see clips from X five in particular they really what console is on that's on PlayStation.
They it was yeah it was in the era where like they had just the PlayStation was new.
They were like wow we can actually fit some like video on like these discs.
So they made some like anime cut scenes for the game that look pretty good.
And the Japanese voice acting is all right but the English the English dub is like remarkable remarkably like awkward.
Frickin I can't I can't do it just just look it up I guess just look up clips if you want to see some some good but that one of zero yelling while he's holding Iris is the.
It's basically the I should have been the one to fill your dark soul with light.
You know that one.
Oh yeah.
It's basically that it's just as good.
I'm watching a clip.
Is he going to say it.
You watch zero.
Can we play the clip.
Eleazar play the clip.
No this isn't happening.
There's no reason for me to go on.
What am I fighting for.
The second way is the way he kind of gets like all nasally at the end of his yell.
Yeah.
That's great.
There's a there's a there's two characters Iris and the Colonel they both have like I think they have New Zealand accents for some reason which like that's fine on its own but like the way that they talk like they sound so like calm.
I don't know.
There's a part where like the general is giving a big speech to all the troops and fricking Colonel comes up but he's like yes.
I concur.
I concur with the general sentiments.
We are the we will create an independent nation for all reploids.
We are the greatest military in the world.
We are the repliforce and everyone goes.
Yeah.
It's pretty it's pretty good.
It's pretty good.
All those people don't know what they're fighting for.
Man to be to be a to be a to be a member of a insurrectionist robot army trying to create a robot ethno state in space you know at least at least I would have at least I'd be passionate about something.
Anyway what was I was I talking about how do I get on the subject.
Zero zero yell.
I don't know whatever.
What are you fighting for nothing.
Nothing.
I'm fighting for.
Big old tits that's what I'm fighting for.
That's my that's the thing I like that's just that's just crass.
That's just despicable.
I'd rather be crass than grass.
What are you dead.
Oh yeah.
When we die our bodies become the grass and the antelope eat the grass.
Yeah.
Hey you know someone you remember how the stream didn't work.
Yes.
Well I got a Wi-Fi extender.
I haven't set it up yet.
I don't know if it will improve things for like you know the like remaining like month or two that I'm here.
But it might so I'm going to set that up and see if that improves my my connection situation.
In the discord F Fka Ren suggested something called a power line adapter that I've never heard of before do you know what that is.
Parallel I don't know the things like what they're for for making Wi-Fi stronger but I think the one I have is like you plug a thing into you plug the the router into this thing and that plugs into the power of the house and then you
you plug you you plug a receiver into another wall thing and that is like it takes the signal from the thing from the power from the power outlet somehow.
That sounds that sounds insane.
It's that yeah I don't really know how it works it's different from a Wi-Fi extender I believe.
Yeah.
But it I plug I plug my my like LAN cable into that like power outlet thingy and I get really good internet.
Oh you have one.
Yeah.
Huh.
Because because my my room is far from the the router I can't get a good signal through the wall.
Well I don't I don't know if that would work because I don't know if that would work for me because yeah my router is up on the second floor in a guy's room.
And my like power is on a different switch like I I might have mentioned that I lost power like three times last month.
Oh shit I didn't know it was more than once.
Oh yeah it happened it happened two more times after that like I guess it's been like two weeks now but it happened like once a week for a while there.
Yeah I lost it multiple times it was really annoying.
But it hasn't happened in a little while so the problem might be fixed.
But anyway when I lost power I would only lose power in my room and in the adjacent room the kitchen didn't lose power and the upstairs didn't lose power.
So we're on different circuits so I feel like it would not work to plug the yeah probably yeah maybe maybe in the next house I could do that something like that.
Yeah I would look into it more that it's really confusing that there are different multiple different ways to extend a Wi-Fi signal that are very similarly named.
Yeah well this Wi-Fi this Wi-Fi adapter might do something I was only like 25 bucks so I was like I'll try it I'll see if I'll see if it has any positive impact.
Like I said I used to have a Wi-Fi adapter down here but the guy left and he took it and it hasn't been haven't had a problem without it but maybe the fact that it is missing now has been negatively affecting things and we'll see if I can fix them.
Damn I went to a birthday party yesterday.
Oh you know what I kind of want I wanted to mention I don't know we were saying things that I'm good at and I said I can sometimes be charming.
Well I didn't I didn't feel charming at this birthday party yesterday because I didn't know anybody.
I was there I have a friend he invited me to his thing I had met him and I'd met his wife before and I didn't know anyone else.
And I I don't know I didn't feel good I didn't feel good about it.
I some of the time I just kind of stood around I did talk to people here and there and mostly I just was I don't know it was mostly just neutral.
There's a lot of neutral shooting the shit feeling like feeling like why am I even why am I even bothering.
Why am I why am I talking.
I don't like I do these people even want to talk to me they don't know me.
Should I just shut up.
Was it like that image of the soy jacket the party and he's like they don't even know that I'm Ben Singh.
No God no I you know I really tried.
I actually really tried not to bring up like Internet stuff or or like it did it did end up coming up once or twice and I tried not to dwell on it.
But I did at one or two points explain a little bit talk a little bit about like doing a podcast or whatever and I felt terrible I felt shame.
I like tried to move past the subject as fast as I could.
Is it like what do you do sort of conversation.
Some someone was talking about I forget how someone was talking about a podcast that they listened to and they talked about like drama that had involved in it and like how it like the members had broken up or something.
And I and I and I felt like I could not not mention that like oh something kind of like that happened to me a little bit.
I sort of had a similar thing.
I wouldn't you would not.
I don't think I would know.
No.
I feel like the I because people know what drama is you could just talk about drama.
I wouldn't I wouldn't want to say oh yeah I had a bit of that I had a podcast and by the way I'm on the Internet and you can find me here.
I didn't do that.
I didn't I didn't do that.
There was that and there was another someone someone else was talking about something they had posted that had gone somewhat viral and someone else mentioned that I like do comics or something and this person asked me like oh where can I follow you what's your what's your.
I was like yeah this is my Twitter like yeah.
And then the and then they actually that person specifically asked me.
That person specifically asked me like can you tell me more about like.
You know your like your podcast or whatever about that thing you were saying about like how like you people you split up with the other like whatever they asked about it and I had to be like I'd rather actually not get into the details about it.
Like I kind of don't want to talk about it in its length here and now.
And so I didn't.
And I when I wish I wished I had not mentioned anything about it.
That sucks.
Yeah.
I mean at the end of the day this was not this was not like this was just one thing that got mentioned among many many things we mostly talked about birds.
And that was fine.
I don't know I just felt like.
Oh here I am out in the real world among real people.
Yeah I am a sap.
Yeah I have frittered away in my life on worthless worthless things.
But that's okay.
You know what.
Well it is.
Yeah.
Like like all right.
I don't I don't know if it is.
Well I mean I don't know if I think it's actually okay.
But like what would a non-wasted life look like.
I don't know something that something that left me in a position now where I feel like this is what I can contribute to the world.
This is this is how I can give value to other people and do something that matters and so that people appreciate.
I don't know what that would be just something instead.
Oh maybe I could maybe I oh if something is bad if there's a problem.
Oh well maybe I could podcast about it.
Maybe that would maybe that would help.
Oh maybe I could maybe I could draw a comic about it.
Well no because like I don't know what I would actually say with with with drawings about anything because I can't I can't think anymore.
But almost that's all that's almost a skill.
I think it's like if you if you didn't have a clear idea it's sort of unhelpful to just say I've wasted my life.
If you didn't like because like I don't know how's that going to help right now.
Well you know they say the first step of getting better is to admit you have a problem and continue admitting it over and over again.
Sure.
Well I mean it's easy to admit you have a like you're unhappy.
Right.
But I don't think wondering about like if only some nondescript thing had happened in my life I wouldn't be right here.
That would be great.
Like you get a time machine is like OK Ben you can solve your problems what are you going to do.
I don't know.
I'm going to go back to that time I missed the sports ball and I'm going to I'm going to I don't know coach my young self to do it right and then I'm going to become a sports guy.
I don't know if I if I if I'd stayed in if I'd stayed in school gotten my masters become a scientist or whatever I probably would be feeling like damn I work in a lab.
I work for some fucking stupid military contractor or something.
I do I do I make I make some some garbage for industrial equipment.
I've wasted my life.
This is all meaningless.
I wish I wish I'd done something.
I wish I'd done something creative.
I wish I'd been an indie comics artist instead.
Now that would be now that would be the life.
Yeah.
And then I could express myself or whatever is grim grim.
I don't know what else to say.
You can't keep being grim.
Can't keep getting away with it.
You can't keep shitting where you think because then you have a poofy brain.
I you're not wrong.
I'm out of topics.
I'm out of topics that I put on my stupid list of things I wanted to talk about today.
Yeah.
I didn't really have any topics aside from just mentioning Roe v. Wade.
Oh yeah.
We already talked about it.
Who cares about that when I feel bad?
What about I feel bad?
I guess I'll say here the the commissions that I was doing.
I'm going to close those.
Yeah.
So they're already closed by the time you're listening to this.
Just because I've had trouble getting the rest of them finished.
And that sort of it's always with this with commissions where I'm like, oh shit, they've paid money.
Now I've got to deliver.
And I deliver it like pretty good.
Honestly, like some pretty good art.
And then I got stuck on one of them and the the the the the slowing momentum caused all the problems in the world to happen.
And so I made me depressed.
And so I'm trying to work on feeling better.
Yeah.
So I've got to do those.
And I don't know what I'm going to do after that.
But I'm singularly focused on just trying to actually feel better first.
So I've been watching Breaking Bad.
And I'm like, ah, remember when he said we got to cook?
I like that.
I like the characters.
I like the writing.
Good show.
Oh, good show, everybody.
Clap clap.
Yeah.
And then I've been fucking playing oblivion and slashing people with a sword and playing Team Fortress 2 and being like, what if what if I was in the past and this I was playing sniper and I shot him.
That would be good.
That's what I've really been occupying myself with is just trying not to be depressed, trying to do things that make me happier.
And then we're doing a podcast now.
I don't know what I'm going to do afterwards.
Oh, wait, wait.
I'm going to finish my footnotes for Slime and Punishment because they really are like very close.
They really are really close to being done.
And that is a bright spot in my dark life.
I do have a topic or a thing that I've been doing that's new.
When I got back from the whole being in America thing.
This whole America business, yep.
I got a calorie counting app and I'm like, okay, I'm actually going to do that for once because the last time I got a calorie counting app, it was for Americans and they had like American products in it and I'm like, I don't know what I'm looking at.
So I found a UK based one which had things I recognized and I'm like, okay, I can actually use this.
So I've been tracking my calories and it's been very helpful.
And I've always been very thin.
So I've actually been trying to gain a bit of weight.
And I've been being like, wow, I have a normal day where I eat what I expect is fine.
And I'm like, oh, you need to eat 700 calories at 11 p.m.
You're saying that you underate?
I underate.
If I left my own devices, I just normally don't eat enough for the goal weight that I want to achieve.
I'm like, shit, gotta binge right at the end.
That's always really weird.
I can't even believe this is a real problem that some people have.
Well, I get it.
Shut up.
In theory, I guess.
It's not a difficult problem.
I'm not trying to tell you that it's not a real thing.
But also, it's so bizarre to me.
It's not anorexia.
It's not a serious issue.
Some people are just, I don't know, peckish.
Peckish?
I feel hungry.
I'm not used to going out of my way to get something when I'm hungry.
And so I will be like, oh, it's only one hour till dinner.
And I forgot to have lunch, so I'll just have dinner instead.
And that's like, oh, I have a calorie deficit.
I have a fat deficit.
This is not good.
That's something that has helped me not overeat is just not having things that I can snack on.
Because if I can snack on stuff, then I will just continuously snack on stuff.
And I'll eat an infinite amount.
So now I don't have that.
The only option I have to eat is that I have to actually make something,
even if it's something simple like a wrap or a sandwich or something.
And just that little energy barrier that I have to cross to eat,
it keeps me on track.
But yeah, aside from a couple nights where I'm like, shit,
I got to chug some milk or something to get that fat content up,
which has been amusing.
Are you going to go mad?
I've looked at, somebody said that, and I'm like,
Do you know what that is?
A gallon of milk a day.
Not a gallon.
Not any closer gallon.
I used to do that.
A gallon of milk is like an unbelievable amount of excess for me.
It's not a small amount.
If you're a bodybuilder and you're doing like strenuous exercise,
there's people who say it's like decent enough
because it's very easy to ingest a version of the amount of nutrients you need.
It is a good way to gain weight.
Yeah.
But I mean, a glass of milk a day.
I'm doing go mad.
It's different.
Like a little lowercase g.
Yeah.
Go mad.
Glass of milk a day.
Cute.
So that's sort of working.
And yeah, that's something in my life now where I'm eating something
and being like, okay, what was that made of?
That's one of these, one of those.
Okay.
That and I just, I'm logging it.
I'm logging my weight.
And now I just got to do exercises as well because I did one day of exercise.
And I was like, okay, that's, I did, I did it.
Now I just got to keep consistent with it.
And I didn't do it the second time and I forgot every time after that
because it was like, ah, but I fucked it up.
Ah, whatever.
I have, I have also, I have not been lifting the last couple of weeks.
Maybe two, maybe two, two or two and a half weeks, two or three weeks.
It's been, I was into it for a while and then I fell off and I should start again.
Do you mind, I mean, do you want to share your like fitness goals?
I'd be curious.
Like, do you have a goal weight in mind or like, is there some form of exercise
you'd like to like be able to do or something like that?
The goal weight is at the moment.
I just pulled a number.
I didn't really think too much, but I was at like 64.7 kilograms.
Oh God.
Oh, right.
Kilograms.
No.
Yeah.
Okay.
No, I was 62.7 kilograms.
I wanted to get to 65 because that's more healthy for my height.
So I've been doing that exercise wise.
Mostly I've been looking into like butt shaping ones because that's that's epic squats
and leg lifts and lunges and things like that.
I guess I could do push-ups as well.
I don't really know.
I'm kind of an idiot and researching these things.
I look at all the numbers and the words and the journals and the articles and I get
overwhelmed and then I just ask people, what do you do?
And then they say, well, it will depend on what you want.
And I'm like, I don't know what I want.
So I'm just sort of guessing mostly.
I'm like, oh, what's a rep?
What's a set?
How many of them do you do and why do you do them?
Well, here's the thing.
I follow a very orthodox philosophy.
I believe that everybody should do a basic strength building routine.
Squat deadlifts, bench press, overhead press, rows.
And I think anyone that says no, no, no, that's two.
I think that's like the baseline.
I feel like that's the baseline that everybody should be working off of.
You do that and then when you can't improve that anymore, you branch off into some other things.
And some people try to say, oh, no, I have some fancy alternative.
But no, you can't beat the basic.
That's just the most basic.
I'm doing star jumps exclusively.
Works all the muscle groups.
So that's my if not to work all the muscle groups.
You just tense all your muscles at once.
You just sit there.
Your whole body.
All intention.
Well, one way, first you contract every muscle in your body as hard as you can.
And then you extend every muscle in your body as hard.
That's our early joint.
Implode, explode.
That's the system I'm going for.
Yeah.
But anyway, I'm not qualified to give any advice because I haven't lifted in a few weeks and I'm a hypocrite.
So, you know, disqualified.
But if I were qualified to give advice, I would say to do starting strength, Mark Ripto.
Ripto, like from Spyro?
That's the guy's name.
Yeah, Mark Ripto.
R-I-P-P-T-O-E?
He wrote the book.
He wrote the starting strength book.
Maybe we'll look into that, but I probably will forget.
I think a basic strength building routine with the basic movements, squat, deadlift, bench, et cetera, et cetera.
That's how you get all the muscles in your body.
That's how you get them strong in the least work.
That's the most efficient way to just get all your muscles strong.
And then from that, you might branch off and do, okay, well, in addition to that, I also want to increase hypertrophy in certain parts of my body.
And then you might add onto that baseline.
Okay, and then I'll also do, I don't know, three sets of 12 bicep curls, three sets of 12 triceps extension to get big arms or whatever.
Yeah.
That's the slash fit way.
I don't really have the space to do a big bar deadlift.
But I do have smaller weights of some of them are quite big.
Does it work doing bench press but with two hand weights?
It's not the same, but it probably could work similarly.
I mean, yeah, you can do a dumbbell press.
You can do dumbbell press, dumbbell squats, dumbbell press.
I guess you could do a dumbbell deadlift.
I've never heard of anyone doing that, but you could do something similar.
They would have to be pretty hefty.
I guess you could just get a stick and glue them together.
The important thing is that it's some free weights, that you're doing it with free weights and that you're using your body's natural leverage.
I couldn't advise you how to do those ones because I'm sure the form would be completely different if you were holding.
I've never done it like that.
Honestly, the last time I moved, finding a place with a basement was a big priority because I wanted to set up my weight rack.
And now Anna is putting it in Munchie's house in his basement.
Fortunately, he had a basement with room for it.
When I was over there, I tried it.
Yeah, you mentioned.
I don't know whether I mentioned on the podcast, but I tried to do a curl with the weights.
Just the bar itself was like 45 pounds.
I couldn't even do one curl.
Yeah, I mean, that's a pretty big.
That bar is pretty big.
Yeah, that's my case.
It's not made for curling.
I could do a few, I think.
There's a specific bar called a curl bar that has a bend in it that gives you a more comfortable grip than the flat straight bar.
Yeah, it's been a couple weeks.
I'm sure I've lost some of my gains.
It hasn't been like months.
Like the last time I stopped lifting, I didn't lift for months after I got COVID.
I should get back over there.
I should get back into it.
I just have been telling myself, oh God, it's proving everything you said right.
I've been telling myself, I should be working.
I should be finishing something.
So no time to do something that might make me happier, like working out or whatever.
No time to think about that.
Your mind's locked in.
It's not relaxed.
It's not relaxing on thinking about anything else.
And now it's been long enough that I'm thinking like, oh, well, I can't tell Munchie that I want to work out again.
It's been long enough that if he wanted to do that, he would have asked me already.
So he must not want me to.
He must just want me to leave alone.
No, no way.
Yeah, there's no way.
Nobody wants to hear from me.
Just message an idiot.
No, no, no.
He would have talked to me if he still liked me.
Everyone hates me.
Everyone's secretly plotting behind my back.
I mean, that is true.
I know.
I was trying to assassinate you.
That's why I came over, but I couldn't find the right moment.
No, no.
You were going to do it.
I wanted to be the PCP's only host, only person.
You wanted to be the procrastinator.
I did.
There could be only one.
I got to get Nate.
I got to get Nate to finish.
I transferred over most of the account.
The last thing that needs to be transferred
to me is the AdSense account.
It needs to be switched
from his Google
to my Google.
I don't exactly know how to do that,
but apparently there is a way to do it.
That's the last thing
that needs to be moved.
Everything else, the Patreon
has been switched so that it pays out to me now
and everything like that.
I'm mostly set up to be
handling payments going forward.
I think Nate owes us
several months.
When was the last time we got paid?
It's been a while, honestly.
It has been a while, yeah.
We missed the money from April.
Lamal.
Other than that.
I'm not even stressed about it.
This is what I mean when it's like,
I don't
I don't need money.
I do need money,
but I'm also at a
position where I don't feel
pressured to earn money
in a way that's like, oh, I gotta find a job
that makes more money. It's like, no,
I don't really need to do that.
So I can think about
hmm, well, if I had
you know,
this is gonna sound like such a
I hate this phrase,
but such a first-world problem.
That's like,
they ask like, if you had all the money
in the world, you know, what would you do?
If you didn't need to make money, what would you do?
I kind of feel, even though I don't
I don't make that much, but I make
enough to live on and now I'm like, well,
it kind of feels like I do have all the money in the world.
I feel like I have everything I ever need
and now, like,
and now what?
I've reached the top of the mountain.
I say this as someone who like
barely exceeds like
the poverty line
and yet, and yet what more?
What more is there?
I mean, I guess I could like buy a house or something,
but that feels like so far away
that it doesn't even feel like it's worth
thinking about.
You know?
That's like a whole other level
that I'm like,
why even bother?
My
anyway.
Anyway, that's so
darn.
If only
wish I was poor. I wish I was poorer
so that I have more problems so that I'd feel more
motivated to like do something about it.
I wish, Dan, that would really compel me to get
on the hustle and grind set, you know?
And then I'd be making moves.
Until you started to have any
success at all and then you would stop.
That's right.
But I'd be so relieved to be like,
now I can have an existential
crisis again.
I've been waiting for this.
Ugh.
See, the transition from feeling
motivated into feeling depressed is
that's the goldmine there.
I love that moment in my life.
Every time it happens, it's just so great.
You know how there are people
I think there are some people
who are like
they're addicted to like
the start
of a relationship.
Like they really like to like get into
relationships because it's like
exciting and it feels good.
But like they're not
but they just do it for the
initial rush.
Yeah, there is an initial rush, like
chemically in the brain.
The whole like love
honeymoon phase, whatever.
Right. Well, for me
for me it's
that feeling of
ugh.
There's nothing left
to work for.
I've peaked. It's all over.
It's all downhill for me.
I love to hit that peak
and get that rush of it's all downhill.
I'm addicted to it.
I would say
message Munchie
and say, want to work out
or I want to work out, please let me work out.
Yeah.
And do some of that exercise.
That's clearly something you like doing
and it makes you feel good.
It does make me feel
a lot better.
When I'm lifting, I feel better about myself
regardless of my other
circumstances.
But do I deserve to feel better about myself?
Maybe I should
deliberately withhold that
to punish myself.
And maybe that'll really get me back
on track. The feeling of
like, oh, well, I'm not allowed to feel good
until I accomplish something
that fixes all my problems.
Think about it.
I know that your therapist says something different
but have you considered that I might know better?
That I might have a better idea?
No, I've never thought of that.
Because it's so stupid.
Why do we have to listen to the expert?
America is sick and tired of experts.
We're tired of scientists.
Let's talk to a scientist.
Y'all motherfuckers lying and getting me pissed.
All right?
Aren't you a scientist, Ben?
No!
I should have been.
I should have been miserable as a scientist.
I should have been the kind of guy I would listen to.
Instead of miserable as an artist.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I guess if I'd become
like a
material scientist or like
some kind of researcher.
Maybe I'd have a specialization.
Maybe I'd have a specialty. Maybe I'd have some expertise.
I saw someone
on Twitter
say like,
I don't know.
They were just talking about like
a big platform or whatever.
Cloud is not important.
It's better to have expertise.
Better to be an expert in something
so that you have a stable income
and then you can just shitpost
online.
And like,
I get that.
And it's not so much that like, oh my god.
They're right. I want to shitpost.
They just made me reflect on, oh my god.
I have no expertise.
I,
what am I, what's the point?
What can I, what do I have?
I guess I just
wish, I just want to
feel like what do I have that I can
what can I do?
What can I do
for other people? Right?
Cause that's, that's what's important.
You're right. It is, it is like doing something
for other people is like a good way
to feel
passionate about it.
And you know, when I think about
people that I really admire,
like I really admire,
I really admire Dan Olson
like the, the NFT video.
It's not just that it was a good video.
It's, that's not what makes it good.
It's that it like,
it gave people something.
It gave people the tools to understand
something that they didn't understand
before. It, he gave
something to people with that video.
It's like, I want to give something
to people
so that they'll like me.
What if you give them
the knowledge that
Ben St. is ripped?
Maybe, maybe that's
the thing to strive for.
I can't guess there are worse things.
Man, oh man.
I mean, I don't feel like
expertise is something I have.
I, I like pick up
bits here and there and I'm like,
yeah, but I'm not a master of my craft.
Any of, any of the crafts I know
of, I don't really like
excel at them.
That sometimes annoys me
that I, I, I, I don't
have a personality that is
better at focusing on
a single thing and going
just for that. Every time I
see something cool, I'm like, oh, I want to do
that. And then I
stop whatever I'm doing and try
to learn a new skill and then get distracted
again. I just have all these
like half skills
and it's a
yeah.
It's, it's a little, a little
upsetting, but I don't.
I feel like I'm a dabbler. I've dabbled
in many things.
I'm not, I'm not really a master
of anything. I guess I'm
I guess I'm okay at drawing.
I guess, I guess
if I had to pick one skill that I'm the
best at, it might be drawing,
but like I don't feel like I'm,
I don't, I wouldn't call myself
a great artist or anything.
I wouldn't call myself an expert draftsman.
Yeah.
But I think that what I've
tried, struggled with
and tried to get better at is just accepting
that I don't need to be
like the master of
anything. I can just be
a dabbler
and that's fine.
It's, it's fine.
It's
there's always a preferable thing
that you could be. It's, it's fine.
You don't need to beat yourself up
about not being that like
hypothetical perfect person.
It's fine to dabble. I just
wish that there was some, I wish, wish
that I could find some
thing that would
be a task
that would like
require like a good assortment
of the, you know, I've
heard people say the
skill stack, right? Like your, like your skill
stack.
As in like the things
that you can do are
is your skill stack. Your Pokemon types.
The stamp damage.
And it's like, and it's like, I don't know,
like it would be really great to
find something to apply myself to
that combined,
you know, the things that I have dabbled
in
in some, in some meaning that
combines them meaningfully.
And
I don't know.
Drawing.
Presenting.
Programming.
Yeah.
Yeah, somewhat.
You have a voice?
I, I guess.
Did I, you know,
You have more voice than me for sure.
I did do that voice acting audition.
I'd like to, I'd like
the voice act. That would be fun.
I don't know, I don't know what
the name for this is.
Is there a name for
the thing of like
stuff, stuff like
getting the road to Radcon book,
The Pleeve and the Weave Blu-ray, stuff like,
or getting my, or getting my Kickstarter books
like made and shipped, like
fulfillment?
Is that a skill?
That's, it's management, it's organization,
it's a
I feel like I've done that sort of thing
enough. Like, like, get a thing,
get a thing made and ship it to people.
Yeah.
I feel like that's a skill that I have.
Because I've done it many times now.
Yeah. I mean, that is overwhelming
for some people, like me.
I get, I get a little fucked up
looking at, like,
I mean, I, don't, don't,
don't get me wrong. I also,
it fucked me up a little bit too.
But I've, but I've pushed,
I've pushed through it a few times now.
Yeah.
It's although, organization and,
and managing
multiple different things, managing
people.
It's all, it's all,
it's hard to say what the skill is,
but yeah.
Yeah. Those are important things. I don't know
what the name for it would be.
I guess,
I guess I could just say,
I don't know, I'm thinking about, like, if I put it
on a resume, I guess I could just say, like,
yeah, I've, I've
delivered on,
like, four different kickstarters
or something. I've done, like,
I, yeah, I don't know.
I got here.
So I don't, but anyway, I don't know what,
what a, what a,
what it looks like to take something
like that and turn that
into a, here's what I'm going to do with
my life.
You know?
It feels like an ancillary skill,
like, that's not something to do, that's
just something you can do in the course
of doing something
else. That's a skill that might help you
accomplish something else.
I feel like it's
far more likely you would
come across situations that
would require, like, two
combined skills, rather
than everything you know.
Yeah. Like two skills
are needed for this, three
skills are needed for that project.
Yeah. I don't know
if you'd find something that, like,
validates everything you've
dabbled in.
No. Maybe during
parts of the process that, like,
I don't know, you're
doing something
that isn't explicitly about
programming, but having programming knowledge
helps you think about something in some
way that, you know,
hard to get into specifics when you're just talking
hypothetical, but, like,
everything you do
has some minor
impact, I would think.
Yeah. I agree.
Nothing is, like, nothing
is wasted. Nothing's completely wasted,
like, oh, you'll never use that
in any capacity ever again.
So, like, I feel like I'm not
equipped to
make
Berserk 2
with the level of art and
writing ability that I have, but...
And don't you just feel terrible
about that.
Yeah. But, like, I
have
different skills
and they combine in different ways
and I can make Bell Jeep too.
I can do different
things. I don't know.
I know what it feels like
to see the best thing in the world
see one piece and think, well,
if I can't make a manga as good
and as long and as successful as one piece
then why am I doing any drawing?
It's easy to say that,
but, like,
don't worry about it.
Right. You don't need to.
But I like that, though.
You can't make one piece, but you can make
Bell Jeep. You can make.
And you're the only one that could do that.
Yeah.
That's what I told myself.
That's what I told myself about slime and punishment.
I said I have to do it.
Because nobody's...
This is not quite like anything
anyone has ever done and nobody
else could make exactly this.
This could never happen again.
It has to be me.
So I have to do it.
Uh...
And I guess it's true.
I guess it's true.
But also, who cares?
And what's the point?
No!
You'll get it.
I think you'll get it at some point.
You'll feel better about, like, motivating things.
Perhaps.
I think I will feel...
I will be glad.
I will be glad when the notes are done
and when I can finally be like,
okay, put the book together.
It's printing.
Set up the Kickstarter.
Just get it done.
I hope...
I hope that when it all is said and done,
I will feel good about
the whole slime and punishment project.
Uh...
And everything.
It's too early for me to
say, like,
well, Ben, you just wasted two years of your life.
And this is all you have to show for it.
Um...
As long as the Kickstarter is
even somewhat successful,
I'll be like, well, you know...
Well, you know...
At any point, I could go and say,
oh, there was a time in my life
where I wasn't drawing comics
and I could have been drawing it
from a much earlier age and I would be better at it.
So, you know, you should feel bad all the time, Gib.
You should feel really bad about that fact.
Yeah.
Like, I just don't... It doesn't matter.
Yeah, you're right.
It's...
Hey, you're right. Hey, it doesn't matter.
Hey, nothing matters.
Yeah.
Ah...
Ugh.
All right.
I don't know. Do you want to...
What about voicemails?
Yeah, let's voice.
Okay, then let's voice.
Let me pull it up here.
Oh, I'm seeing a lot of
stupid-looking voicemails.
I'm seeing a lot of skips.
I'm seeing a lot of skips on this...
Yeah, where did we start?
Oh, wait.
I didn't see the ones from last time.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's on the second page.
I think the first one
this week is called
Question.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
Did you guys watch
Monkey's Sex Take when it came out?
No.
I didn't watch it, no.
Although I did see some screenshots.
I think...
I didn't go to look for it,
but I did see in Discord
either a gif of like five...
Not five seconds, like one second
of something, and I'm like, oh, god.
And then a screenshot of his face.
I'm like, oh, why is this happening?
Oh, god.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Good times.
No, I didn't watch it.
I...
Why would I want to do that?
Um...
Okay, next one is...
Next one is where is Tom,
but not where, like,
location. Where is in, like,
a werewolf?
Yeah, okay, three, two, one, go.
Okay, there's no audio.
I feel like... Didn't we explain this already?
Didn't I already say...
Tom said he doesn't want to...
be around for the show, because...
He's busy with other things,
so he's not going to be around.
That's it?
I'm making a...
I'm making a hand gesture.
I'm making a... Oh, I can see it.
I'm making a repetitive hand gesture,
which is nature I won't specify,
but I'll let you...
I'll let you all...
He's blown kisses.
I won't say one way or the other.
Next one is called
My Secret Message Part 1.
Three, two, one, go.
He's breathing into it.
Breathing softly into the microphone.
There's no message.
I can't tell if maybe
he is just breathing
and there is no message.
He is saying something, but it's just not...
It's really quiet and not picking up
and it's completely unintelligible.
It's unintelligible if there is anything there.
Alright, next...
Don't do that.
Next one is Part 2.
Three, two, one, go.
God! Alright.
Thanks for the message.
Thanks for the message, buddy.
Good try.
Next one is called
Punished Air
Sensored Mad
Three, two, one, go.
Did I mention
that I legitimately
saw YouTube
delete
a comment from
the PCP account
on a PCP video?
Huh?
Like we've commented?
Yeah, like I replied
to a comment
on a PCP video
and I was like,
what?
I replied to a comment
on this account
and YouTube like deleted it
or like hit it.
What was the... Do you remember what you said?
Yeah.
I think I like called someone an idiot or something.
Like, it was
something like that.
Hang on, I'm going to
comments
to see like
held for review.
There's no comment from air
that's held for review.
So...
They disappeared it.
I'm looking...
YouTube be disappearing comments
that say idiot and fuck.
Ahhhh!
No, we've got to do, we've got to bring back
the YouTube replies.
Remember those?
Video responses, but like
baked into the system.
I never really
engaged with them or even really like
back when they were a thing.
But I hear people talk about them
being gone now
and how it made a difference.
I think the reason they left is because
girls with big boobies
would have their boobies in a thumbnail
or even not people.
They would just reply girls
and reply bait to get views
easily and it's like
if you could put boobs into a comment
you would get more likes
I guess is the parallel.
If only...
Yeah, I don't...
It's not in our mentions, I can't
approve it so like it's out of our hands
like it seems like YouTube is just
decides sometimes that a comment will simply be
gone into the ether and even
we don't have any ability to restore it
and I don't know
what the fuck is wrong with them.
Well at least
you can always send a voicemail
with your sentiments.
They can't censor you as far as I know
on Speakpipe.
The next one is
Happy Birthday Ben You Asshole
3, 2, 1, go.
I think that's a kiss
is that like a kiss sound?
Yeah, I guess so.
It's like a smooch
based?
Based? Happy Birthday?
So
next one is
YouTube links and I just, I'm not gonna
I'm not gonna engage with this
and then Happy Birthday
There's four Happy Birthdays in a row.
Happy Birthday Ben
and then there is another
YouTube link which I will not
which I will not be
not be
engaging with
in any way, shape, or form.
Thank you very much. Then there's simply
a link to youtube.com
and then there's just the word
please.
No.
No. You say please
I say no.
The next one is Happy Father's Day
Ben
Thanks
and then there's one from
MillerPrince930 and this one seems
to be real.
So three, two, one, go.
Please
please say that something
is
something or someone is a popcorn nihilist
is probably my favorite
meme.
Favorite Olden
semi-current meme.
I remember the popcorn nihilist but I can't
remember what it was about.
Did Munchy make that
up or did he get it from somewhere?
I mean, I don't know.
I feel like it's simple
enough to come up with. Somebody
who's a nihilist and they get the popcorn
and they watch things happen.
Yeah, I feel
like I get it and yet
ah, man
maybe I don't
remember if it came from somewhere. I feel like
if you google it
there is a, I found a
like on Urban Dictionary there's a quote
that's like Charlie Brown as a popcorn nihilist.
Is that from a PCP bonus episode
though?
I feel like that might have come
from us. Maybe.
That's funny. It's not
like a popular phrase. And then, I don't know
this guy probably remembers, but you remember
that I called, I called
Mr. Medicare a popcorn nihilist
and he
didn't understand the expression
and he thought it was funny so he put it in his
twitter bio for a bit there.
But he called it like
he didn't understand
that I was calling him a popcorn nihilist
he just thought I was calling him like
popcorn, like an adjective
so he said, he put something
in his bio that was like the popcorn party
pavilion
and like I get, he didn't
he sort of misunderstood the intent
but
for a while my insult
was in Medicare's twitter bio and then I think
he deleted all his accounts and I think he's
like dying of cancer or something
rip
next
do you have anything else to say about that?
No, I was just thinking about
sewer priest and if that was
an original, like a munchy original
wait
munchy original?
I thought that was a Jesse thing
I thought it was like a thing that munchy
said that Jesse really liked
maybe Jesse came up with sewer priest
I guess it would fit
with like the
the
sewage video
Man Sheld Marsh
Well now I don't know
I feel like
there were a lot of time
I remember sewer priest and like Christ Consciousness
like
Christ Consciousness is a munchy isn't
but he got it from
that video
but like I feel like sewer priest
would not have come from there
No, I mean
it just seems like a funny thing
to be
I know there were a lot of times
that like Jesse said something
that I thought was really funny
and then only like a long time
later would I discover that like he was quoting
something that I had not realized he was quoting
at the time
so I don't know
I don't remember
munchy ever saying it but maybe he did
I am more associate
that phrase with Jesse but I could be
misremembering
Okay, next one is called
Le Peeps Units Will Never Be
Defeats
3, 2, 1, go
So I was at the protest in Austin
about the Supreme Court stuff
and at some point during that time
we started doing the People United
Will Never Be Defeated chant that Ben
brought up
Why not make it rhyme?
The difference here is that some people
actually did sing divided
and there was like first time
they were kind of confused and then we kind of went back
and forth between which one
was like dominant
which all of us
to say I got to rhyme
I got to sing it in rhymes
when you did it in Ben saint, how does it feel?
They weren't united in what they were saying
When I
heard that chant I think there were some people
around who were saying divided and they
seemed a little confused that the
bulk of the chanting
was defeated
The People United
Will Never Be Confused
But we were though
Oh no, well
we're not united, that's how it works
Next one is Ben's Weekly
Reminder Play Delta Rune Chapter 2
I'm playing Mega Man right now
leave me alone but also
I had a good old
good old go back
and listen to Toby Fox Music
for a few hours the other day
it's like ah you know what
music sure is great
mood improved
It's okay I guess
I want to learn
Rude Buster on the piano, I feel like that
would be a good thing
Which is Rude Buster the
Delta Rune battle theme?
Yeah
It's kind of like
kind of jazzy
That one? Yeah
I think I remember
I mean he makes
a good
He makes a spicy soundtrack
He makes a good chiptune
No one denies
that
But then I was going back to
Undertale and the
I lost music and like
My favorite
It's so good
I might actually replay Undertale soon
I've said that
when the demo came out
when Undertale was only a demo
I loved the Toriel fight
Heartbreak, right? It's called Heartbreak
Yeah
I love Heartbreak so much I listen to it on repeat
for like days
It's great
He's pretty good
at all that shit
that
Next one is called
voicemailers where are you
Yeah where are they
They're right here
We're listening to them
Next one is called
Ben's Weekly Reminder to have a happy
Oh there actually is audio
3, 2, 1, go
Happy birthday
Well thank you
Thank you so much
Next one is called
Le Peeps Our Defeats
Unfortunate Leeds
3, 2, 1, go
You know I didn't pick up on the irony
of the fact that in the last voicemail I left
where I said half the people were saying
will never be defeated and the other half were saying
will never be defeated means then
that the people were literally divided
over what they were singing so never mind
I was just wrong
and bad
Get picked up on it
Stupid
Something in my throat
Gross
Next one is called
Hi Ben, 3, 2, 1, go
Hi Ben
Say
Patreon.com
Wow
Getting started on my arms
Get them on
That's delightful
That's
I can't
I can't improve
on that by commenting on it
So I'll just let it stand
Thank you for that
Oh boy
Adorable
Next one and this is the last one
is called
Redneck Jimmy has a question
Question
3, 2, 1, go
Howdy PCP
This is Redneck Jimmy here
I've been a long time listener of the PCP
and I'm a big fan
but I've always had a question that has somehow
been addressed on the show before
and I think it's a dagum good question too
I can't wait
What is your favorite anime?
Now anime, that is some gay shit
I mean, what is your favorite anime?
That is to say
What's your favorite animated bovine?
Yeehaw
Well
That's all I had to ask
Love you guys
Muah
Make out Redneck Jimmy
Animated bovine
I'm trying to think of if there even is
one
Well there's the DreamWorks
Home on the Range
Cats
Yeah I guess so
So I guess it's them
I can't think of any others
I'm trying to think of like
Oh, is there like a good
animated film about the Minotaur?
Is there a good animated Minotaur?
I can't think of one
There must be
Wait a bovine
What is that not a
Well it is a cow but I think
giraffes are bovines too
Kaku then
Yeah, I think it might
have to be Kaku
From one piece
I mean he ate the Ushi Ushi
He ate the cow cow fruit model giraffe
Oh yeah
And he's a square giraffe
It's the funniest giraffe
ever put to animation
I would have to say
I would have to think that's probably true
Okay let me see here
There's the guy from
the giraffe from Madagascar
and then there's Kaku who would win
You know it's anyone's game
Okay the four horned antelope
The nil guy
Water buffalo
Anoas
Tamaras
Gars, Yaks
Coopries
Domestic cattle
Sayola
I don't even know what some of these are
These are all
That thing doesn't, the Sayola doesn't even look like a
What the fuck
Hang on, look at this
Look at this creature
Are deer's bovine
That has the markings
on that and the shadows make it look
low poly somehow
Like it's neck
It's like a vertex
or a lion, whatever you call it
You know
I'm not seeing giraffe on here
So maybe it's not
a bovine, but I kind of want to
call it one anyway
Let me see the loot
To find out
what the classification of a giraffe
is
It's a hoofed mammal
It's a pecorra
Pecorra giraffeaday
Okay no, it is not a bovine
A bovine is a pecorra
And then under pecorra there's
Servaday and then whatever's
not a servaday is either a bovine
or a muscaday
I think that's like a deer
Okay, so bovines are like yaks
Yaks, antelopes, buffalo
Yeah, okay, things I normally
associate with
I guess there's the
yaks from My Little Pony
There's the buffalo from My Little Pony
Oh wait a minute
There's the cows from My Little Pony
Okay, I don't know any others
I'm going to say the answer is
unicorns and my justification
for that
is that in the Bible
in the Bible
the King James version
God
Flem
The King James version of the Bible
includes mention of unicorns
in the original
Hebrew
the word is reem
and reem
is probably not meant to
refer to a unicorn as we
perceive it
it was probably meant to
refer to
something else like an oryx
or a wild ox or a bull
or a buffalo or a rhinoceros perhaps
so
I'm going to go
with the biblical unicorn on the assumption
that it is either an ox
or a buffalo or an antelope
if it's a rhinoceros then that doesn't count
so the reem, thank you
good question
yes
and here, check this out
check this out, it was animated
because they made a fucking
tile mosaic about it
in ancient times
that's not an animation
you just have to run past it really fast
and then it moves
that's how they watched movies back then
do you think
did they ever do
a cave painting
or a hallway mural
where it's a sequence of events
and the goal is
you're supposed to run down the hallway
and it may be blinking
really fast and it makes you think
it's one image after another
I feel like that's something someone
would have tried
maybe would have tried
I feel like if you're in a cave
with
a fire in your hand
you'd probably slip and hit yourself
no, it probably wouldn't have been
run into a wall
I'm thinking it would have been not in like a cave
like caveman, I'm thinking it would have been
in maybe like a palace
of some
some king or something
like the kings or the emperors
like running around like I love this
I love this one
I don't know maybe
running around in a circle watching it
sort of a diversion or an amusement
there's some built some hallway of
hey if you run down this hallway
and you blink really fast and you look at the wall
you can see, I don't know
fucking Amaterasu
descending from the heavens or whatever
I feel like something like that would be
something kids do
more readily than adults
which is why tapestries and stuff
they show the sequence of events
but like
snapshots rather than
actual animation
right, like the goal is not
to like, I'm just thinking like
cause someone had to think
you know that like wheel
you look in one side of the wheel and you spin it
and you look at the other side and you can see
the horse running
yeah
like that
like that's animation
and like flip books have been a thing
for a long time, flip books are a kind of animation
but like before that
I don't know, maybe
did they try other stuff that like just didn't work
very well
the reason I brought up cave paintings
I think my hallway idea would probably work
I feel like someone somewhere
probably tried it, cause what else are you gonna do
when it's ancient times and there's no
TV
the reason I brought up
like cave paintings and stuff though is
there was a discovery
that a cave painting that looked
like they had drawn
the same thing
like over layered
and they couldn't make sense of like why it looked like that
but then under like
firelight
if you move the fire from around the wall
the shadows cast on the
like the indents that they made
like carvings into the wall would change
what you could see
and what you couldn't so they would have
like a very primitive like literally very primitive
like flip book
like left to right up down
changing the scene
in real time as you move
the fire around
that's like that they realized that's how
they viewed these things
instead of with a direct source of light
like a flashlight
and they got a sense of like
ah this is a
a little old caveman movie
theater
wow
I've never heard of that
what was it do you remember like what it was a scene of
I think it was like an elephant
a mammoth hunt or something
some sort of hunting thing where they would have
the if you look at the image
fully lit
it doesn't really make sense
what you're looking at
but if you have like
the candle
or like a flame
the flickering
creates like an illusion
of movement and it's pretty cool
and it makes sense because they
would not have been able to see
inside the cave without fire
because they didn't have any other alternatives
would it have given sort of the same effect
that like
in a cartoon like
you have it's like
the character is standing still but you sort of draw
you animate them with two
frames so like you flicker back and forth
between the two frames and it's sort of
looks like at least three but yeah
well yeah the wobbly lion stuff
yeah
I don't know because I haven't seen video of it
but I did read about it
they invented wobbly lion
pseudo animation
I guess
they got like Ed Ed and Eddie in the cave
yes they invented Ed Ed and Eddie
it's a timeless
transcends era
uh
yeah well that's the last
voicemail unless someone sent in a last
minute one
nope
we're done baby
well
this was a fucking
vent cast if ever there was one
yeah
mmmm
sorry I hope
you feel more motivated soon Ben
and I hope
that you the listener
give us money on Patreon
Patreon.com
now that would make me feel a little better
I know I just said all that stuff
about how like I don't need money
but I was lying I was just I was just lying
that was you fell for it
I was just lying to seem like more
uh
good and natured I actually
am a money
enjoyer
it's sad it's sad but true
I saw tweet
that was like
like me like me online
like uh like
uh capitalism bad
I hate I hate
money is fake money is made up the economy
is fake me in real life
oh my god I love $20
something
oh my god I love specifically
$20 and I do I do
love $20 I mean
it's it's hard to deny
I mean think about think about
what that could mean is the the
potential of $20
you could get a meal
that's you could you could buy a video
game as as Michael
of Reps2Gog
would have once said
uh that's that's like
that's 40 sheets hot dogs
so
that that'll keep you in hot dogs for
days
hot dog heaven
you'll be in hot dog heaven yeah
uh
shout you know Reps2Gog
I actually I actually
watched I actually binged Reps2Gog
uh this week uh what does it
stand for it is we we review
every
PlayStation 2 game yeah yeah
yeah it's a tectonic improv
and uh and Michael yeah
formerly null toxicity
uh yeah I just watched
uh
thanks for thanks for wasting my time
with that I mean
giving me content that I
enjoyed uh
shout outs
anyway yeah the sheets hot dog
comparison is uh evergreen
what was I talking about
$20
$20 on the Procrastinators
podcast patreon.com
I love to I love when you pledge $20
to patreon.com slash the
procrastinators for instance
you get the bonus episodes
and you get the minecraft
uh server
which we will be streaming on hopefully
with a better internet
yes I will uh
maybe today
I think today I will try
and set up the
wi-fi extender and see if that
fixes the uh the connection issue that
was preventing me from
playing on the minecraft server
and then I'm gonna go
and do my I'm gonna go finish my
fucking uh
assignment punishment notes because I'm almost there
this might this has
been a long time coming but it's
ugh it's gonna it's gonna feel
good to have that done so that's nice
uh
I am going to
gonna play oblivion
some more
okay
I have like how many
how many things like five
the uh commissions
left to do I was only really stuck
on one you know when you get like yeah
but when you get stuck on yeah I know
exactly when you lose your momentum
when you lose your momentum and go to the next one it's like
ah but that's still in my head that
I should be doing that one but I think I've got
it I think I've I have like
what it takes to finish that one and then
at least that's
done
yeah don't know when I'll do it
I'll try maybe tonight to do a little bit
so I'll open up the the the program that's
the bare minimum I think it's the hardest
part is starting but if the the goal
of starting is to open the program
you end up starting easier I think
opening up the program really
is
I do when it's like
when I just do that I already it's already
like okay I did I did the first
step I did I've already
made some progress yeah
it seems silly but it really is
like it feels when you're thinking of I've
got to finish that you don't want to
open the program but if your goal is I
got to open the program tonight
and then you do it it's like well
maybe we'll draw some lines
yeah
yeah it's sad but true
exactly we're talking about
ah
um
alright I think we're I think we're ready to
wrap up yep
alright well
there's a game for listening already
we've plugged everything so
thanks for listening
see you next week
bye everybody
what am I fighting for