Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemails for the Minecraft stream. I really want to have Redcon funded by you. We can be Pro Crastinators.
I guess this is the start of the podcast. Hello. I think it's another one of these. It's another drum roll please.
Solo Bencast. Welcome everyone to the Pro Crastinators Podcast. No guests this week. I didn't set anything up. Gibb was gonna show up, I think, but she has, I guess, internet outages.
Her internet provider is just black out right now or something. Tom is unavailable, both scheduling-wise, but mostly emotionally.
It's just me, I guess. I'm the only one that showed up again, so we got another one of these. And this time it's not even funny. It's not even noteworthy.
Bencast 2. They did this gimmick already. What a fucking joke. So, for your benefit and mine, I will do you the mercy of just getting this dang thing over with.
I'm just ripping the Band-Aid off, so we can all just get on with our day. We can get in, get out, say we did it, fulfill our mutual contractual obligations, and be on our way.
Anything else to ham and haw about before I get down to business? Do I even have any business? No. I didn't do much this week. I have been continuing to work on The Lord of Ghosts' comic.
Well, some. I was. It was derailed. It was derailed a bit. I think last week- I feel like I always say this, but I hope I'm not repeating myself because one week just blends right into the other. Time is just a flat circle.
I think last week I said I was worried about my kidney. I was worried about back pain. So, I think it was this week, so I think this week I went to the doctor. I scheduled a doctor's appointment.
Right? That was this week. That didn't happen last week, right? I wasn't telling the oblivion fall that, oh, the time I went to the doctor, right?
No. No. Surely. Surely not. Wait a second. I can find out.
No, I did. No, I fucking did. It was October 1st. It was October 1st that I went and got the urine test. Time is a flat circle. Okay, I already talked about it. Good thing I checked. Sorry.
Next item on the agenda. There is none. I hung out with Kauff from RFCK, came to visit and hang out at the Munchie Kazi house. That was pretty fun. It was very hung over.
Oh, and that actually leads me to another item. This was separate. This was way more hung over than I was from Kazi's birthday, which was what I was complaining about last week.
It was so hung over after one particular day of that, that the next day I found I was too sick to work. I couldn't focus on drawing Lord of Ghosts, which led me to lose my momentum and spend the next two or three days just being like, eh, I don't want to do it.
And I kind of just didn't do anything. And that was kind of my week. Not entirely, but somewhat. So, you know, big shit head energy on me this week. A lot of poo. No, egg on my face. Shit head. Egg on your face. Not shit on my face, but also that.
Lord of Ghosts is about half done. I think it was probably almost the same as last week. I probably only spent like two days, one and change days working on it this week. I think I can get it done this week, and that'll be pretty cool.
If you want to know more about the stuff I've been doing, if you want to hear me ramble about the shit that I do, that I have been up to, you can always go to patreon.com.
I've been saying where I just released a catch up episode of the bent of the, I guess I call it the Q&A, the Q&A slash update podcast, I guess is what I call it, in which I accept questions, which I answered, but I also give a general update about just what's going on in my life.
And I had not done that for a while. I had let several months go by. Usually I keep that to about 45 minutes under an hour, so this time I did a big catch up one where I talked about moving and I talked about, I don't even remember.
I had a whole list of things that I had to go over my calendar. I had to go through emails and stuff and been like, what was I talking, what was I doing, what was I even doing like three months ago?
I was like, oh, some of it was different, some of it was just frustratingly the same.
The only other thing I can think of that is of note at all that I did this week is that Kazzy got a, what do you call it, got their submission, except for like, okay, I don't know if many cities do this, but probably some do, but in Boston there are these electrical boxes that stick out of the sidewalk,
and a lot of them have like paintings on it, like from local artists. Well, Kazzy got a design accepted to be on one of those, and they have started the process of drawing it on, so I went with them one day.
They had a whole multi-day project, but I went with them yesterday and we hung out and it was already primed. They had to prime it with primer, and then the paint is going on after that.
But before the final paint layer goes on, we had to lay, we had to pencil line lay in like a grid on it, so Kazzy could, you know, accurately transfer the design onto the thing.
So we spent like the afternoon like drawing the pencil lines in and like measuring very carefully and like getting it all perfect and then they went and did a pencil sketch over it and then that was pretty fun.
So that should be funny, that should be funny and cool.
I would love to keep rambling, I would love to keep rambling, but I have less than usual to say about my week this week.
I have been very, I just kind of bled into the last week and I've been very, very, I've been alternatingly sick or depressed or lazy for much of it, so, you know, they can't all be winners, they can't all be winners, but that's life.
And so, oh, if you don't like it, what are you, anti-life? What do you hate life?
I can say that about literally anything, literally anything that anyone ever criticizes you for. Here's the hot tip, here's the hot tip.
Anytime anyone criticizes you for anything, you just go, well, that's life, man. What do you hate life? Easy.
It's the new, it's the new I'm just being cool. I did it. Iconic.
God, what am I, like five minutes in? Yeah, like seven minutes into this thing and it's already time to go to voicemails, baby.
You should have, life should have come at me faster this week, I'm sorry.
Life should have given me more, more shit to talk about on the podcast, but it didn't. You just got to deal with that.
Let me get, let me get, let me get my folder. Here we go.
It starts with number three, seven, four. It's annoying because, yeah, they have the, I save them in order, but sometimes the download times are different.
So the times that my computer organizes them into are sometimes different by time downloaded, as opposed to in, they're not quite in numerical order.
And sometimes they get, sometimes they get, sometimes they get a little mixed up, sometimes they get just a little bit mixed up with that.
So anyway, this first one is called three, seven, four, six.
Ah, found it. It is called Master Time Thief Speculative.
I don't know what that means, but here we go. Three, two, one, go.
What if we could be sneaky time criminals, right? What if we went into the future, which is right now?
And we saw something, a media that we liked, maybe a video or a song or a whole video game.
And we just took it back into the past and we just pretended like we made it. We made it our own.
And whoa, what would you take? What would you do? You sneaky time criminals? What would you make money off of it?
Or would you be famous for your effort and your hard work and your vision that wasn't really yours? Oh, what would you do?
Well, I guess, yeah, I wouldn't care about being famous for like, oh, he wrote like a classical masterpiece or something, or he made a great work of art.
I wouldn't care about that if like, I didn't really make it because like, okay, I'm famous for something that I didn't actually do.
So like, what do I feel good about that? Not really.
So I guess, I guess what I would do is I would try to find the boring answer.
I think I would just try to probably bring back like scientific advancements and just things that like would generally be like good for humanity.
I think I would just bring them back and then, you know, I go into the future and I bring back, you know, I mean, bring back the cure for AIDS or whatever.
I bring back the cure for homosexuality, aka Chris Chan's blood from the future, right?
I bring that back and, you know, I can't feel like, oh yeah, I invented the cure for AIDS or whatever.
But I can be like, well, I did a genuine good to humanity by bringing it back and giving it to people and giving access to it before they would have otherwise had it.
And then I could, and then I could feel genuinely like I did something worth, worth, uh, uh, adulating.
So yeah, sorry if it's a boring answer.
Boring answer is I would do good for my fellow man.
Sorry, it sucks.
I wouldn't care about bringing back like artistic masterpieces.
Who fucking cares?
They'll be appreciated in their own time.
So I don't feel like, I don't think the world would be any better if I went and, like, the next, the next, a blockbuster movie that comes out, you know, 15 years from now.
And I bring it back so everyone now can appreciate it.
I don't think that, I don't think the world is any better for that.
Um, uh, if anything, they got to enjoy, maybe they got to enjoy it earlier, but like, you know, they would have just enjoyed it later.
Like, it's a net, net neutral.
Um, next one is master, no, that's not it.
Uh, next one is a heartfelt plea.
Let me find it here.
Yes, three, seven, four, seven, a heartfelt plea.
Three, two, one, go.
Remember guys, when the podcast is angry Jesse, man?
Angry yellow? It ain't yellow, he said.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
After those days.
Fucking, fucking Jesse.
Uh, I, I just, uh, you know, not, not to be too, not to be, not to be too, not to speak ill of the dead or anything, but one thing that always really bugged me was how, yeah, he would,
there's, there's basically no denying, but yeah, he would definitely put on this exaggerated ang, angry character.
He would put on this, this ranting, raving, shouting persona.
Haha, funny man, funny angry man.
And then in the same, in the same breath, be like, oh, everyone, everyone talks about me like I'm angry or something.
And nobody knows, nobody knows, nobody really understands me.
I'm not, I'm not really like that.
And like, it's like, yeah, obviously you're not, but also like that many times that is the character you project and like, what, what do you think is going to happen?
What do you, what do you think they're going to know you as if that's the fucking character you project?
Uh, a little, he's a little bit like, I don't know.
Uh, funny shit.
Uh, next one is, oh my God, it's a fucking Imgir post.
God help us. Here we go.
Dude, if you like, okay, it's cheesy, it's, I guess this is cheesy Manfredo, not depicted in his classical, his classical style.
Uh, dude, if you like his classical clown, Sona, if you like Marvel and Star Wars, you'll love Villainverse.
The, why is it 799.95, the price is a metaphor for capitalism.
Sometimes a metaphor is just distinct indistinguishable from the real thing.
And then me over there in the background selling, is this supposed to be me at mice selling my copies of the Vapors books with Endless War in the background?
I mean, it's pretty much exactly how it was only it was outdoors.
So, I mean, I don't know, good drawing, I mean, I guess it's just true.
I guess this drawing is just true, and I can only appreciate, I can only appreciate the great truth of our world that it expresses.
Uh, very nice.
Next one is called Ben Saint is cooler than Radcon.
Three, three, seven, four, nine.
Uh, here we go.
Ben Saint is cooler than Radcon.
Well, we'll just see about that, won't we?
Three, two, one, go.
Ben Gibb, Tom Commwin.
Ben Gibb, Tom Commwin?
Ben.
Gives.
Tom.
Communism.
Will.
Win.
Oh, I see.
You're saying that I need to distribute my wealth to Tom in order to create a classless moneyless society in which the dictatorship of the proletariat dismantles the bourgeoisie.
the bourgeoisie. Well, well, isn't that so easy for you to say? Why don't you give all
your money away, Mr. Communist man? Capitalism? Socialism is with no house. Well, well, you
Rube, I have, I have, I know how to handle these objections, and I can, by simply ignoring
them. Not today, Satan. Next one is called, oh dear, next one is called Lollicon Enjoyer.
Okay. Three, two, one, go.
Kids are automatically more interesting than anyone your own age.
No. What do you mean by that?
Wait, who is that saying, what do you mean by that? Who said, what do you mean by that?
Um, kids, kids are automatically more interesting than anyone your own age.
I mean, that's, I mean, it's a truly bizarre thing to say.
It's truly bizarre thing to say, but I'm sure if challenged on it, she would just say,
I was kidding, or it was satire, or some stupid shit. So like, why, why even think about it for
even a second? Why even, why even think about what she means when like, the answer is nothing.
The answer is always nothing. Next, next one is called, it's Janess. Okay. I gotta find three,
seven, five, one. Here we go. Three, two, one, go.
Isn't it great how all the radcon forwards are nearly out? This gives me so much hope for
radcon five, at least late 2022. Speaking of which, I mean, I have a couple of stretch goal
ideas for the eventual kickstarter. I'll tell you how to stream for those who likes Ben St.
Cineboy. Also, those who pay a certain amount gets to vote on a poll for which games the PCP
will stream at radcon five. These were the ideas I thought of so far. Is that anything else you
would suggest? Post these down in the comments, and I'll click a like on them.
Yeah, right. I've said this before, a hypothetical radcon five, which would
definitely, which would certainly look a lot different than previous radcons, obviously.
No plans at the moment for one, but you never know. The last,
oh, I guess I should mention, I might as well mention one last time that the road to radcon
books, I think orders have pretty much stopped trickling in. I think I'm ready to be like,
okay, done. That's all I'm gonna get, and I'm gonna send it off to Prince. So probably this
week, maybe like this weekend as this comes out. So like, if you're hearing this, it's not
quite too late, but it's all, it's gonna be too late, like tomorrow.
Some fucking construction work's going on. Oh, yeah, I guess that's, yeah, there's been this,
all this week, there's been a backhoe fucking like digging up the parking lot behind my house,
my fucking rat infest, rat and raccoon infested parking lot.
It's, you know, it's been a bit annoying, it's been a bit annoying, but I haven't been spending
that much time in the house, or as much as usual, so it hasn't been a big deal. Not that it would
be a big deal anyway, it's just a little, it's just a little noise, whatever. Anyway, road to
radcon, I'm making the order, I'm calling it. So if you want that, it's really now or never,
and then I will, I will be, I will maybe be making the final print probably like
tomorrow after you hear this, so. But yes, it's good that that's done. I've said this before,
the last thing to do is the dogen, which is Being Drawn by Edward D. Al at Wolfheart on Twitter.
And it is in the process of being drawn, I think it should be done this month.
I mean, some, I don't even, might even not even be that far away. I haven't, I haven't talked to him
in a little bit about it. I, I hope he's been working diligently. And the last thing is the OVA,
which I believe Nate will be editing. I hope, I hope Nate will get around to editing shortly
after that. And I think that's it. Oh, in the music video, the Brad going, there was a Brad
going has music video to go with the, the song. And I think that's it. I might be forgetting
something. I don't think I am. Anyway, I don't know. Yes. At a hypothetical ride con three.
Yeah, we would probably do many of the same things before where, you know, you, if you're,
if you're, if you pledge, you got to pick the game we stream, you know, that's, that's just a
pretty classic, pretty classic stream move. I hope you can hear the voices of these people,
these fucking, these, these darn, these, these working blue collar workers out my fucking window.
But they're, but they're South Boston accents. God help us all.
I mean, yeah, I don't have any, I don't really have any specific ideas.
Uh, they would probably be everything we did at previous ones. We would try to do all the
same things that we could with, you know, whoever ended up going being there. And maybe we would
think of some more that would go with any theme we thought of, but I don't know what the theme would
be. So I'm sorry, I don't, I don't really have any ideas, but we would think we would think of
something. LeMau. Next voicemail is called the Ballad of Ben St and Trixie. Where, where was I?
It's, it's, it's three, seven, five, two, found it. Okay.
Ballad of Ben St and Trixie. Well, let's hear it. Three, two, one, go.
Ben St.
I really think that she and I could be friends, but by the way, I think you're attracted.
Yes. Ben losing me now. Here's his room. We're going to be doing some thing, things together,
you know what I'm saying? You are a freaking freak and a moron, a low IQ subhuman troglodyte.
I hate you.
I mean, what can I say, but the funny, funny, funny shit.
I'll briefly mention a funny, funny dumb shit that Trixie did this week. Number one,
making that tweet about, because Chappelle made that comedy special where he says he's on Team
Turf, a fucking Trixie making the, the genius tweet of like, I haven't seen it, but Netflix
better keep it up because it would be censorship if like the most famous comedian in the fucking
world didn't get his Netflix special. I haven't seen it, but I have free speech and you gotta
keep it up, even if it hates me, even if it's hate speech against me. That's just how bad I
want people to fucking like me and think that I'm not one of those bad trans. I mean, that's how
much I believe in free speech. Solidarity. Next, wait, and the other one was getting engaged
to Bird, lol. I saw they had their fucking like trashy got proposed at a concert with like a
ring pop ring. Very funny, very cute. I think I remember the last time, remember the last time
she got engaged? Lamal. Here we go again. I feel like the comedy is, is clear and I don't have to
explain any further. Next one is called, oh god, we're on a, we're on a kick, I guess. It's called
A Message From Riley. Here we go. Three, two, one, go.
Man, that fucking shit with the hanging chads sucks. That shit with the fucking man.
I, I know it's maybe a little, you know, it's a bit maybe, sorry if this is a, if this is a democrat
thing to say, but we probably would be in a much, much better position as a society if, if fucking,
if they had just done the recounts as they should have done and just, you know,
George and, and Al Gore had been the duly elected president as he legitimately should have been,
but republicans stole it because they just have no honor or fair play or they will, they will just
cheat to get whatever they want and like half the time it works. Next voicemail is called and then
the, and then the, and then 9-11 happened and then like the whole, like we probably, we maybe just
wouldn't even have had the Afghan, I mean maybe we would have, wouldn't have been the same. It wouldn't
have gone down like it did genuinely. Also, also climate's really bad right now and Gore was big
on climate. So like, you know, I'm pretty, pretty undeniable, pretty undeniable failure there on
the part of American quote unquote democracy. Anyway, next voicemail is called, well it's also
called Riley, so let's, let's just get into that, shall we? There it is. Three, two, one, go.
What's up, fuckers? It's me, Riley. I love you. And now that the dust has settled, I think we can
all agree that trial of the golden niche is the greatest mixtape of all time. It's me, Riley.
Thank you. Have I ever, have I mentioned before that Riley you sound so much like,
you sound so much like, uh, like, uh, like, uh, Colt Corona. You sound who's Colt, Colt Corona,
who's fate, by the way, you will learn in the pages of Road to Radcon available,
still available for a very limited time from me. You gotta send me Ben St. Money and then
you get the book. You gotta fucking message me on Discord or Twitter DMs or whatever. It's the only
way. It's the only way. Um, next voicemail is called, um, only new PCP is able to do this.
I'm gonna upload it here. One, one weird trick discovered by the PCP. Podcasters hate them.
Okay. Only new PCP is able to do this. Three, two, one, go.
PCP Wandering Sun. There's a manga for it and there's a complete anime for it. This is capable
of the future. Make the doubters in shambles, in shambles. PCP Wandering Suncast. Wandering Sun
Oh, I'm, I've heard of this. Is it, is it a trans thing? Is it about, like, is it about, like, a
gender exploration? Uh, what's the, what's the word I'm looking for? Character study? Uh, maybe, uh,
Bill Dung's Roman, perhaps? Uh, yeah, looking, looking briefly at the Wikipedia page. Yes,
it is what I'm thinking of. Um, I guess, I guess I could read it. I probably won't.
But anything's possible. Uh, next voicemail is called, why would I read manga? Why would I read
manga when I can, when I could be churning credit cards? Give me a fucking break. Um,
uh, sorry, shit, shit, shit, fuck, shit, fuck, I lost my place. Uh, next one is called,
oh, it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a fast upload.
Oh, here it is. It's called What Happened to the PCP Wiki, and I feel like I know what it's gonna
say, but let's listen to it anyway. Three, two, one, go. My guess is that the guy managing it
looked at all the pages and went, oh no, it will take weeks of work to retcon all the pronouns
and dead names. And I am a fat American who sits on his couch and smokes weed all day. I can't be
doing work. So he private it and made it a secret club for his discord friends. The same thing will
happen to the PCP episodes after Twitter pressure's been enough. Save them onto your hard drive if
you value them. Um, I don't know if that is specifically the reason. I mean, I, I know you,
it's possible. It's, it's possible that there was some, okay, I say, I say this, I say this as a
specific insult to the kind of person who is so brain dead that like they still like or respect
Trixie in any way at all. Like people like that are like, oh, you can't say Digi. That's a dead name.
You can't, you can't say Digi. Digi is a dead name. Uh, no, first of all, no, it's a screen name.
Second of all, shut the hell up. Shut the fuck up. Uh, uh, uh, I, while, while in a, while in a
perfect world, while in a perfect world, I feel like, yeah, sure, you go through the whole PCP
wiki, you change all the pronouns and you update it. But like if the PCP is not wiki, wiki was not
updating anymore. Okay, that's in, in, it may, it may have been a pronoun thing, but it may not
have been. And I don't know if it was, I still don't agree with it because I either way, whether
that was the thing or not, if it's not updating anymore, this is, this is, this is so stupid.
The idea that like, wait a minute, the thing, the thing changed. The thing is not how it was then.
So my record of how it was then must be destroyed because it is too, because it no longer reflect,
reflects present day truth. Like, what do you think a fucking record is, dude? What, what,
what do you do any, what do you write anything for? What do you, what do you record anything for?
If like, the moment, the moment that the circumstances change, you're like, I must destroy
the record of how it was. The record must be expunged. Like, deranged, deranged. Oh, geez.
Hello. Oh, wait, I gotta, I gotta filter your voice through my, through my headsets.
Um, well, geez, I'm like, I'm like halfway through voicemails, dude.
Oh, uh, well, okay, I guess I'll go then.
I mean, you, yeah, I guess you, I mean, you don't have to. No, you know what's
day, I mean, you're here. Um, uh, here we go, changing to speaker output, yeah.
Uh, how many more do I, do I even have? Um, I have,
I have like, I have like, I have like 10 left. So, well, all right, pause, pause on the voicemails,
pause on the voicemails. Gib, what's up?
Uh, well, I don't know. Uh, the fucking, all right, the reason I'm an hour late,
55 minutes late is because the internet was fucked and that's, it made me mad,
but it's just sort of working now for no reason. I didn't do anything.
So that's nice. Uh, well, uh, the, the procrastinators podcast, patreon.com
slash the procrastinators. Uh, we have a bonus episode. Oh, I've set, uh, I'm stupid. I said the
bonus episode was going to be out by the time the last one came out and then I didn't, I forgot to,
but I forgot to post it. Uh, but I will post it. I will post it like two day. I will post it two
day. So it should be fine. It should be fine. Don't be mad at me. Nobody get mad.
Uh, people have been sending me messages being like, Ben, please put the, the audio on,
on Spotify and like, I don't know what to tell those people because I don't do that.
I don't, I don't know how Spotify works or, or like Apple podcasts or whatever.
I don't do anything except, I don't even usually upload it to YouTube myself. Occasionally I do,
but yeah, I don't, I don't even know how to use those other ones. Uh, but like, I think we're
missing, I think we're missing a few on like Spotify. Uh, but I don't, I don't have, I don't
know what to do about that. Anyway. Okay. So internet, internet problems.
Yeah. Internet problems. I mean, it's just, who cares to talk about that? It's just one of those
things that sucks for everyone all the time. Um, but what I wanted to talk about was my
Clarissa Gunsmoke comic is out. I think I talked about it being out, uh, but before it was out,
but now it is. And now the next chapter will probably be out by the time you're listening
to this as well. Give and take dot site. Wait, pinned tweet. How many chapters did you make for
the original run, the original, uh, uh, Tezuka challenge? For the, for the Tezuka challenge,
uh, because it was a hashtag Tezuka challenge on YouTube. Um, fucking 50 pages was the maximum.
And so I sketched out the story that I had written for it and it came out to be more than 50
pages. So I was like, okay, I'll cut it off at this point here, send that in. I drew all 50 pages
and I'm currently shading and like neatening and tidying them up to release. Uh, in terms of like
how many chapters that is, I guess it varies because I wasn't thinking of them as in terms of
chapters. I was thinking of it in terms of a one shot submission. So I don't really know. The
chapters will be at different lengths. This new one is like 13 pages, but the one after is 17 pages.
13? Just sort of, sort of choosing the points. How long was the first one? 20. Okay, okay, okay, I got it.
And then, and then on the, uh, the Photoshop file with all the sketches on it, there are still
yet as of un-drawn 32 or 36 new pages that I could do, which I didn't submit to the Tezuka
thing. So nobody has seen those except unless you watched the live streams where it happened live.
But yeah, that's like, that's like another three chapters or another two chapters or something.
Oh my, so some of this, some of it is new. It has not been shown before.
Yes, if you had gone to the Art Street website where I had submitted the original Japanese
version, uh, that's 50 pages. If you paid the 700, 420 yen and there's the 50, but then there's
beyond that 36 other pages, and that's not, it's still not done after that. I would still
need to sketch the rest of the story. So there's plenty. There's plenty of Clarissa.
Yes, I, I have not yet, I have not yet gone and peeped it, but I will.
You fucker.
Yeah, yeah, I am. I'm a big fucker. I am a big fuck.
Um, yeah, I think I should really, I think I mentioned this before. I will, I will probably be,
I should get around to posting those, those vaporettes from Vapors 2 on my Patreon. Maybe
I'll do that today as well. I have a, I have a bunch of like housekeeping things to do and
yeah, posting the bonus episode is one. Yeah, I was thinking about this yesterday, posting the
vapors, the vaporettes on Patreon is another one. I realized that my taxes are due. I forgot
that I extended my tax deadline to October 15th and now, now I have to like scramble to do my
taxes really quick and I think it will all have been for naught because I will probably just be like,
well, I don't have anything to change. I'll just click done and be like, well, why didn't I just do it?
Why didn't I just do it before? But oh, but oh well.
That's the, that's the choice I made. But I gotta fucking, I gotta fucking go over all my finances
one more time and, and, and do all the numbers and be like, that's a business expense. That's a
business expense. New bedsheets, that's a business expense. That's a paddling. That's a paddling.
Uh, I gotta do that this week.
Speaking of finances, I am, I was like, I was, oh, the Lord of Ghost plushes.
They said they're ready to ship. Please give us the money.
Give. That's what I did.
Give. Okay. I just remembered.
Mm hmm.
Sorry. Sorry if I interrupted, but I just remembered.
Someone, I think it was, I think it was Steve that proposed this to me the other day and it's
actually sounded like it might be a great idea. And it was that like, okay, you said that like,
your, you said that your shipping cost, your shipping costs to America are like insane.
So what if, what if you sent, what if you sent, had some of the original like, like product
just sent directly to me and like, I would handle, I, and like, I would do, and like, I could do
like postage to America, to American backers. I would want, I would want like some nominal fee,
like for, for like to send them out, but like, it might, if it, if it might save like $5 a package
on postage, maybe you could pay me like, like $2 or $3 for one that I send. And then it would
save, it would save money overall. That might work aside for, except for the fact that like,
everyone who's getting a plush is also getting the comics and some other stuff.
Yeah. So I would need to get the comics all sent to me.
And would you need to do that?
Well, I guess I, I, I had it all like planned out my head, like I, for the plush ones, I could get
this particular size box and that would be enough for everything. It's also a little late because
they're already on their way. I see, I see. Well, okay, think about it. If, if I do, if by doing
something like that, we could save some money. If we could save some money, that would be nice.
I'm trying to think of how it would work because like, I'll have all of the things.
Yeah. And the, if I send them direct, like to send them to you would be to send them to
America anyway. So like, would I really even save anything?
Yeah, I guess that's true. I mean, it might, it might cost cheaper to send them all in bulk
to me in one bulk thing, like possibly, I guess I was thinking that like,
like when you, when like the plushes were, were shipped, you could just maybe tell them like,
yeah, just send like, you know, 25% of them to you in the UK. And then the other, like,
however many to meet, just like tell the distributor, like don't send them direct to me,
send like split, split the order between two destiny. And yeah, it probably would cost more
to ship them to me, but probably less overall. I don't know, maybe.
I would have to ask them, I guess. I don't really, I feel like they've got them all in
like a box and they're just sending the box. Think about, think about if any, any money
could be saved this way. And if it could, I'm more than happy to help with it.
It would definitely be good if we had planned it beforehand.
To have like, like a UK and a US base for these things. That would be epic, actually.
I mean, it kind of sounds like, it kind of sounds like maybe we still could,
like if they haven't, if they haven't shipped them yet.
I will ask them, I will email and say, have you shipped them? Because I feel like,
because I sent the second half of the invoice already.
Okay. Okay. So then they, I don't have like a tracking number though, so maybe they haven't.
It's possible. Just, just, I don't know, think about it. So think about it.
Steve just like mentioned that to me the other day and I was like, wait a minute.
It just, it's just crazy enough to work, perhaps. Okay. Well, now I've, now I've,
I've almost forgot about that, but yeah, I'm glad I related to you.
Uh, what were you saying?
Yeah. Yeah. The, so I was thinking, because you've been talking about like credit,
crunchery. Yeah, churning, churning.
Can I get a card? Can I do that? And I'm like, I don't really know how to do it. It's confusing.
Building credit history.
I saw that I could pay them through PayPal and there was like PayPal credit and I'm like,
does that, is that good? Because like building credit,
surely you can transfer credit from a thing to something else. Surely that's just a number,
right? I, I don't, I don't know if, if PayPal credit works the exact same way.
It might not. I was assuming it would probably be a little different.
But I was thinking, I have the money to like pay it back immediately. So what's the harm?
So I got PayPal credit purchased through and that's like a couple hundred, six hundred
pounds. I, I am not, I am not sure, I am not sure if PayPal credit builds it like a, like a credit
score history. Yeah, I don't know. I'm not sure. It's certainly something. So what's, what's,
what's the benefit? What's the benefit of PayPal credit? I don't know. I just,
see the word credit. They see the word credit and they say, you need that if you want to buy a house.
I'm like, dang, that's a, that's a house I could buy in the future. Credit, huh?
PayPal's not a credit card company. I don't know. They are a company though. They are a,
they are a company. They don't have card involved, but they don't have card involved. Gee whiz.
They sure move money around. I don't know. You know what? I have no idea. I have no idea.
I'll, I'll keep you posted on the, what the fuck the point of it is. Keep me posted. Yeah, okay, cool.
Whether I made like a completely, like no, no losses, but no point either. Sort of
Purchase. Keep me updated on if your credit score skyrockets. Uh, sure, sure, sure. I have been,
I have been, I have been cash, I have been cashing in my, my benefits. I just cashed in,
I just cashed in my, my Citibank 200 reward. I cashed in my, my say, my Capital One 200 reward.
I cashed in my, my other Citibank, no, no. One of my Citibanks I still have to cash in,
but I think I've cashed in like 300. Like, no, I've cashed in three of my four $200 rewards.
Uh, I've got like most of a fourth, and now I'm like,
I earned this. I, I were, I, I built this. I built this castle, this sand castle for myself.
You did all of that extra, like, extraneous bullshit with bank stuff.
I've been talking about this for months. I've technically labored over that extra money.
I sure did. Probably, probably more than I would have had to labor to make like $800
in like, you know, how much was that? How many, okay, $15 an hour, $800 is
53 hours. I'm going to say, I'm going to say, yeah, I probably put in more, more work,
more time than that, just on like, well, well, I don't know, because it was spread over such a
long time. I don't know if it would add up to be more than 50 hours or maybe, but I don't care.
It's about the satisfaction of a job well done. Do the, do you get credit for the, the churning,
or is that just money you're getting? Like, like the bonuses? The bonuses are just, are just money.
The bonuses are just money. I don't, I don't really care about getting credit. Like, I don't,
I don't really care that I like, about like, how much like my credit limit is. Like, I've not,
I don't, I don't use my credit limit. It's just about, it's just about, it's just about the bonuses
for me. It's just about the bonuses and about, and about maintaining my, my, my credit history,
my credit score. That's, that's the, that's, that's what it's all about.
What was, what was I, what was I talking about? I have no idea. Well, oh,
I joined so late. Oh, yeah. Doing voicemails, I guess. Do you want to listen to a voicemail?
Uh, well, how long does the PCP, we go in like an hour?
About 45 minutes. Wow. Yeah, we might have an under two hour episode this week. Oh my god.
If you, if you can believe it. Uh, well, let's see if there's any, is there any padding in my head
I can use? There were, there were no, there were no voicemails yet that like, specifically requested
your, you respond to them or anything. So I don't feel the need to be like, oh, let's go back over
this one with you or anything. Yeah, I don't know. Mostly I've been like, working hard,
doing the Clarissa thing, getting distractions out of my brain with cold turkey, and it's all been
going all very nice. And the weekend is like, you know, designated don't work time. So like,
based, I've been drawing a whatever tober, which is a drawing of Rui. I've been drawing.
I'm a drew, I'm drawing, I'm drawing. I'm drawing. Yes, whatever tober, whatever tober.
Whatever tober has been fun. It's just like, it's like a feeling of accomplishment, even though
there is no actual accomplishment. I'm just making an image and posting it.
You set yourself a completely arbitrary and like, what's the word? The word is
not negligible, and it's like a trivially easy set of requirements to meet,
and then you meet them and you're like, yeah. Yeah, I'm so fucking whatever.
Nice. It's like, while all the people are out there challenging themselves and
testing their limits and learning by doing all of their art techniques, I'm out here making
content on Twitter. And I'm outperforming them every time.
These suckers, these suckers. Yeah. You know what they say, quality is the enemy of
content. Quantant. Quantant, yes. Crack into another seltzer. Another seltzer over here.
Yeah, I don't know. I don't do... I haven't done... I don't do anything. I have never done...
I don't think I've ever stuck to a tober challenge or any challenge ever, in fact.
I get annoyed by them. Part of the whatever tober is that I haven't completed any of those
challenges, those specific challenges. I guess I did the Igmovoa tour did years ago,
making a fucking hypocrite video every day. Yeah. That was cool. But a drawing,
Inktober, never bothered with it. I always get bored. I always feel like my...
It feels bad to do a drawing that is not quite as good as the drawing from Friday,
two days ago. Oh, you know what? I'm getting bad. I should give up. But if the point is to be whatever,
then it's easier. I just wanted to see if I could actually get to the end.
That's my challenge. Could I stick with such a pointless thing?
Time will tell. Well, damn, I can't...
Shit. I can't believe it's... I can't believe we're 10 days into October already. Fuck. I think I
started... I think I started working on The Lord of Ghosts. I switched gears to working on The Lord
of Ghosts at the end of... I think maybe on the September 23rd or 24th. It's been almost...
It's been over two weeks. I've only got five pages done.
I mean, they're good-looking pages from what I've seen.
I'm pretty proud of them, especially that last one. That last one took me... I mean, honestly,
it's not even worth... It's not even a brag to say that that last page took me a long time,
took me several days of working on it. That just means that I planned it out poorly,
and I just didn't... That's a failure of planning on my part. It's not that it's such a masterpiece.
I spent days laboring. I mean, I did, but not because it's a masterpiece. Working hard, not smart.
I was working... Yes. Yes. It was working hard, not smart.
I can't imagine working on an image or even a comic page for more than a day. I guess that shows
my patience level, why my comics look the way they do.
I do have... I think patience is something that I do have. If I were a Naruto,
every Naruto has their own little thing. Neji Naruto has that he can see weird shit,
and Sakura Naruto has that she's super strong, and Sasuke Naruto has that he's good at everything.
Naruto Naruto is that he's got really high chakra limit, and all his abilities are things
that you just need a shit ton of raw chakra to do that nobody else can do.
I think patience is one of the things. I have just a shit ton of patience,
and not much else, but I can do things that other people can't do because I'm
just willing to throw any amount of time at doing it, and not care.
Incredible.
Yeah, and on the one hand, that's how I got Vapor's One done. That's how I'm getting
Phantom's Revenge done, so that's all good. But then on the other hand, on the other hand,
you also spend 750 hours playing Noida by the same token, so it's truly a blessing and a curse.
What were you going to say?
I was just wondering if you know how long the Vapor's One took you to draw from beginning
to finished published product.
Yeah, I think I spent like six months working on it, which is not very good. It's not a very good
rate. I mean, it's only like 40 pages, so I wasn't working like eight hours a day,
five days a week on it or anything. But it took me, I think, around six months.
Generally, my page draw time tends to hover around. Sometimes a page will be really fast,
and I'll be really lucky and easy, but most of the time, drawing a comic page tends to take me
around six to ten hours of actual sitting down and drawing time. Sometimes a page will be very
complicated or I'll get stuck on something, and it'll take me much longer, but six to ten
hours is pretty average. I'll average it around and say eight. But eight hours, which is not good.
That's not a good rate to be making commercial comics work, if I'm being honest.
But if it was like eight hours times, I think it's more than 40, but I'll just call it 4045.
Okay, that's 360 hours. So if I was working a nine to five job, 40 hours a week would be nine
weeks. So that's about nine weeks worth of dedicated nose to the grindstone work.
So that's about three, that would be three, no, two and a half months, two months in change.
But it took me six months to do it, but I wasn't working on it every day,
nine to five or anything. So I guess that's not a complete disaster.
I just, I wish I had some of that, that patience, because like,
in times when I have forced myself to go over a drawing when I like, I could put it out now.
I was like, no, I should go over it again. I should maybe do another layer, better line art or
something. When I do spend the time, the drawings are so much better. This is, which is why I know
like my skill level is higher than it actually appears to people.
It's, yeah, I mean, I mean, it takes time to make something look just the way you wanted to.
Yeah, I mean, I think that's why like my pages take so long. It's because I'm like,
you know, I'm like, I'm like, I'm redrawing and redrawing and redrawing like a pose until it looks
right or like a hand until it looks like a hand should look or whatever.
Yeah, it just sort of demoralizes me a little bit when it's like, oh, I drew this,
I did the line art. I'm like, this just doesn't look good. I need to delete it. Oh my God,
all that progress, all that time gone, the grade ever closer.
Yeah, I think I've gotten, I've gotten more, I've gotten more efficient though, to the point that
like if I, you know, if I spent like maybe 10 minutes sketching a hand and then I think it
looks wrong, I don't really care that much about, well, I lost the 10 minutes. Eh, well, I lose,
I lose, I lost more than that, you know, already this morning, because I like, you know,
accidentally put on a YouTube video and like zoned out for an hour watching a blind Castlevania
Symphony of the Night speedrun or whatever. So, so what's another 10 minutes? Ah, fuck it,
you know. Yeah, true, true.
You know, I've already, you know, I've already lost 10 minutes. Oh, I lost an hour because
that panel came out like shit, eh, whatever. I've already lost, you know, 33 years of my life,
just totally into the void, nothing to show for it. Eh, what's another hour? You know what I'm saying?
Ain't that the truth? It is, it is, it is the truth. You can't escape it.
All I wish, all I wish is that my comics will exist, so that before I turn to dust and bones,
hopefully it'll happen. Well, well, it's, it's possible. It's, it's not impossible.
It's just not gonna look like Berserk, it's just gonna look like what I draw, but that's okay.
Yeah, but I mean, not, not, most, most things can't look like Berserk.
And that's, and that's, and that's okay. I don't even, I don't even care. I don't even want my
shit to look like Berserk. I would, I would rather, I prefer, I prefer the look of like Scott
Pilgrim to the look of Berserk if I'm being, if I'm being honest. Yeah, I mean, it's, it's a taste
thing. I just feel like there's a certain sort of feeling reading a Berserk, like double page,
beautifully rendered, or whatever you would call it, draw an image of like 200 horsemen.
And it's like, oh, it's real, they're real, they're really there. And they're charging into battle.
That's true. So good. That's true. But like, if I were to do the same thing,
I would draw two horses at the front and then a bunch of squiggles to imply horses. And it would
be cool, but you wouldn't really feel it quite as much. I mean, Miura, you know, you say that,
but like Miura is doing the same thing. Like every manga guy is like, you know, is fudging it a
little bit and taking, taking as many shortcuts as they know how to take. Yeah, I mean, Miura didn't
take that many. I'm sure, I'm sure, I'm sure if you I'm sure if you zoomed in real close on the
on like the background horsemen, you'd be like, oh, this guy kind of he's sort of even barely,
like barely has a face or whatever, you know, I think it's it's well, obviously there's some,
but like it's like, if you use a sliding scale of like how much of the horses in this panel are
fudged, it would be a lot less than your average person. Most people wouldn't even draw that many
horses. I mean, show the camera like, we don't need to show that many of them that close.
It's too much. Well, Miura was too many lines. Miura was, you know, obviously a very, a very
detail oriented artist, kind of his thing, I guess. And that's, and that's fine. And that's fine,
if that's what you're into. If you're, if you're that sick, if I could, if I could make Berserk,
but it's actually one piece, but it's actually Homestuck, but it's actually Scott Pilgrim,
then I will have made my comic. Anything less, I disavow. Anything less than I would say,
ah, it sucks, and I would burn it alive. That's not my real, that's not my vision.
Spit on it. Spit on it. But aside, that aside, I am very happy with Clarissa so far. It's,
it's looking pretty good for what I was, for what, for what, for how quickly I drew it at the time.
I'm not really going over it too much and like redoing bits. There's a few bits where it's like,
this looks so bad and it wouldn't take much time to redraw. So I'm like redrawing a face here and
there or an arm. But mostly it's how it was. There are some, there are some panels in,
there are a few panels in my old comics that like kind of look bad. And like maybe, I think,
sometimes I think like maybe if I ever continue them, would I go back and redraw them? And I,
I want to say probably, I want to say probably no. Like the purist in me wants to say no,
that's how it was. It should never be changed. But I'm specifically thinking of a couple of
panels in The Champion of Damien where like his, his eyes, I drew his eye like really huge and it
looks a little bizarre in one or two places. And looking back, I'm like, that's bizarre. And maybe
it should be changed if I ever return to this story. But I don't know. A lot of people thought,
a lot of people thought, I tried to give Agatha kind of like a frilly, like a frilly like, like
poofy, like poofy shoulder sort of, not like a princess dress, but you know, kind of like a
fancy-ish dress. And a lot of people, a lot of people read what I tried to draw as like frills,
as like lacy frills. A lot of people read them as like, ragged tatters and thought she was wearing
like a potato sack, which is a little embarrassing. That's kind of a fuck up on my part. But what can
you do? You know, it's just part of the charm. Let's just let's just call it part of the charm,
I guess. Lemau. Wait, wait, wait. I read a really interesting thing about minting the coin. It was
like a, it's like an American government like politics. There's some weird fucking stupid thing
happening with like Congress. And it may come to pass that Biden has to just be like,
okay, well, we're just going to mint a platinum coin and declare it worth a billion dollars and
pay our own debt to ourselves with it. And that's the debt solution. And it's really funny. It's
really funny. How in the fuck does that solve any problem though? Okay, the way that it works.
Congress approves a budget. And then the president, the executive branch, borrows the money
to pay for the budget that Congress approved. That's how it works in most countries. But in
America, there's another step where, okay, then the president has to request that Congress approves
a budget. The president requests to borrow the money. And then Congress then has to approve,
yes, you can borrow that money to pay the budget that we approved. So basically what's going on is
Congress approved a budget and Biden is trying to, Biden needs to borrow the money to pay,
to spend that on the budget. But there's a thing called the debt ceiling where like there's some,
there's some clause, there's some provision where like federal debt cannot exceed a certain amount
or a certain, you know, proportion of something, right? And like we're at that limit. And the
thing about it is that that sounds really bad. Like you think that debt is bad, but it's actually
not. It's actually like fine and normal and it is not causing any problems. Other countries have
like a way higher debt to GDP ratio than America has and they're not having any problems. It doesn't
cause any problems. So America is not in any kind of debt crisis. We've technically hit what we have
defined as our debt ceiling. So Biden is sort of not allowed to borrow the money that he was told to
borrow to, you know, execute on the budget. So basically the idea is like, well, this is an
intractable situation that Congress has put me in. Congress basically needs to vote to raise the
debt ceiling in order for me to do what they told me to do. And the thing about the debt,
like because naively, the debt ceiling sounds like a bad, like if you're hitting the debt ceiling,
you think that's bad because debt is bad, right? Well, not really. But it sounds bad. And so all
politicians use it as like a gotcha. Like if they, if they'll point it that whoever is they're running
against and they'll be like, that guy voted to raise the debt ceiling, that guy voted to increase
the national debt. And like, yes, they did. Because of course they did. Everybody does.
Everybody knows that you have to continually increase the debt ceiling. It's ever everybody
point everybody points at everyone else and says, you did it, you raised the debt, you raised the
debt. And then the time comes where it's like, well, we got to raise the debt, should we raise the
debt and everyone goes, yeah, I guess we should raise the debt, I guess we got to raise the debt,
right? Everyone knows this. But Republicans, Republicans are like, well, Republicans will
actually like, they will actually vote not to raise the debt, they will use it as leverage
to be like, if you don't, if you don't accept our agenda, we will as a bloc vote not to increase
the debt ceiling, it will destroy the economy, it will destabilize the United States dollar,
it will be a complete global catastrophe, but we'll just fucking do it, because we don't give a
fuck. They'll fucking do it. So, and like, that's what they're doing, they're basically saying,
we'll, we will Biden, no, fuck you, we're going to vote to destabilize the entire economy
and destabilize the dollar, the dollar itself, the fucking bedrock of like, everything.
We're going to, we're going to fuck it just because we don't like you and we don't want to do your
budget. Well, what they want, what they want is for, they know that the debt ceiling has to rise,
but they don't want to do it. They want Democrats to do it all by themselves so they can point at
them and go, the Democrats just keep raising the debt, the Democrats raise that even more,
they're spend, they're spendocrats, they're, they're, they're, where is it coming from,
how are we going to pay for it? How are we going to pay for it? Oh, they're borrowing against your
future or whatever. That's what they want. And so, so basically the answer is, if Biden just
mints this coin, because he has the power to just, there's a clause that's like, the executive branch
can, from time to time, just mint platinum bullion worth whatever they say they're worth,
and it's, and it's, and they just can't, so what he can do is he can just make a platinum coin and
say, this is worth a trillion dollars, and I'm giving it to myself to pay the debt. And then
there's a trillion dollars less debt. And the thing is, it doesn't even, it doesn't actually
do anything. It doesn't, like it's not money in circulation. It doesn't contribute to inflation.
It doesn't actually have any negative. What it, what it is, is like a stupid and arbitrary solution
to an equally stupid and arbitrary problem. And I genuinely hope that he mints the fucking coin,
because it's really funny. And the whole thing is bullshit anyway. So like, whatever.
That's pretty wacky. Yeah. Yeah. There are, there are maybe other ways that he could argue his way
around it and that he wouldn't have to do the silly, funny. Yeah, mint, mint the fucking
trillion dollar coin. Literally, literally the plot of a Simpsons episode is when they made the
trillion dollar bill. But he's just gonna fucking do it. I hope he fucking does it.
The question I guess I would have is why does the debt not be a bad thing? Why is it always
normal to raise it and it doesn't change anything and it's just normal? It's because that's a more
complicated question, I guess. Yeah, it is. It's complicated. I can't give you like a full rundown.
But like, basically the debt that we owe is not like a, it's, it's, it's in, it's in the form of
like, it's mostly in the form of like bonds to United States citizens that are like payable
at regular intervals. Like, it's not like we're not like, we're not even close to defaulting
on New Orleans. Like, we have the spending capacity, we have the GDP to meet all of our
debt obligations, you know, at the contractually appointed times, right? Like, you know, people
buy bonds where it's like, okay, they'll, they'll basically, they loan the government some money.
They're essentially, they're essentially buying American debt and then, you know, they will in,
in, you know, five years or whatever, they will give the debt back and for owning the debt, you
know, they will get some amount of interest on their investment. And like, we don't have it,
it would, it would be a huge problem. Okay. And the thing is, it would be a massive problem
if America, if suddenly we couldn't, you know, make good on our bonds, if like America, American
debt is basically like the most secure asset in the world. It is, it is basically a zero risk
investment to buy like an American bond, a debt bond. And to, so, but, and we're, and we're not
in any, in any risk of failing to, to fulfill those. If, however, if we don't raise the debt ceiling
and we don't approve the budget, then suddenly we might not be able to fulfill those, those bonds.
And then it suddenly, the most stable investment in the world, the most stable asset in the world
would suddenly become destabilized and like, and, and, and, you know, all of a sudden because,
because there was suddenly like a greater element of risk involved, you know, suddenly the interest
rates on, the interest rates on, on American bonds would, would have to skyrocket to accommodate,
to accommodate that increased risk. And, and suddenly America would just have way less money
available from borrowing because it would just be way more expensive for them to borrow because
they're, because their debt would be a higher risk asset. So it's, it's actually way more dangerous
to not increase the debt is like the long and short in the, in this case. Apparently this almost
happened like with Obama, like they base, there was kind of the same situation and Obama was
considering minting the coin, but he didn't, he didn't end up having to do it. But maybe this time.
It's, it's, it's basically just, it's, it's literally just him give, basically like, give it,
writing himself a little permission slip to do the thing that he, that he was already was told to do.
The other possibility that like he might have to resort to is like if there might have to be
like a, like a legal or like constitutional argument that like the constitution both demands that I,
you know, the, the, the constitution both demands that I fulfill the congressional budget and also
that I not, that I, you know, not exceed the debt limit. But, you know, these are two mutually
exclusive things that are both, you know, congressionally and constitutionally demanded of me.
Therefore, it's sort of an open legal question over like, which would be the less constitutional
thing to do. So you could make the argument that like, well, I nevertheless have to exceed the
debt limit because you told me to, right? Yeah, I really, I really fucking thought this was like
interesting. And I made me laugh. And I was like, just fucking do it. Just fucking do it. It literally
wouldn't do anything. Yeah. Yeah. The coin is funny. I, it's hard for me to wrap my head around the
other things. Just like the slime corp coin. Yes. We should add the, the, the, the trillion, the
trillion dollar slime coin. It's, it's, it's worth a trillion PC pennies.
We, you know, we have the, we have the executive authority to just, you know, to mint a bullion
of any kind we like and, you know, declare its value in PC pennies to be whatever we want from
time to time. This, this bottle cap, this bottle cap here, this is actually worth a, this is actually
worth a quintillion PC pennies. Man, what a shit currency PC pennies must be. I'm going to throw it
against the mic. There, you just heard, you just heard it hit the microphone. That was a trillion
PC pennies down the fucking drain. Okay. That's, that's my, that's my spiel about the, about minting
the coin. Hey, Gib. Oh, she left. She left the call. I feel like I can safely assume
that this is a, that this is an internet blackout thing. Gib, you back?
I'm back. I'm using my hotspot now. I fucking, I don't know how much tater I have, but uh,
it should be fine. We're not going to go four hours from here.
I was just about to play the next voicemail.
Okay. Well, have you posted it? No, I just posted it right now. I'm posting it right now. It is
called, it's in, it's in general, like it's called funny bug story. Three, two, one, go.
When I was training at my job, I had two layers of shirts, one that had my uniform and a white
undershirt. I decided to go on a break since I had the time and I took off my shirt, was wearing
the white undershirt and I felt a weird little like scratching or like poke inside my shirt.
So I take it out and I'm like, huh, you know, maybe a rock up in there. So I take out the rock
and the rock just gets up and flies away. And then I realized that rock was actually a bee
and my shoulder started hurting. No, saddened. You got stung. How do you get stung and not notice
it until later? Wouldn't it hurt when you got stung? I think if you feel like a pitching
thing, but you're not really imagining there being bugs near you, you just sort of assume
your clothes are catching on you somehow. Yeah, yeah, that sounds reasonable.
That's the worst realization where you're like, it's sort of like a weird thing.
Then giant spider drops to the ground is like, oh no, he was laying eggs in my brain.
Oh yeah, many such cases. Yeah, I mean, I hate, I really hate, I sure do hate finding bugs on
myself and I definitely hate when I get stung by bees. I think I've ever been stung by a bee.
I definitely got stung when I was a kid. I got a bee sting as a kid, I think. It's been a while.
I should try it again sometime. It was pretty sick. The next one is called actual drawcast idea
voicemail characters. There's no content to that. It's zero, okay.
To drawing the voicemail characters? That's, I mean, we didn't, no, we didn't do that.
We never did that. For a PCP voice, for a PCP drawcast, that is actually a pretty solid idea.
Maybe. I can't really think of what they look like. What does a nightfucker look like?
What does, I know what the pig looks like. Well, that's the challenge. Well, that's the challenge.
We did get fan art in one, somebody sent, I'm sorry, was it never paint? I think never paint
drew a bunch of the nightfucker, the league of nightfuckers. That was the first time I had seen
them rendered and they were really fucking weird looking and shit. It's weird. There's so many
different nightfuckers that I completely have forgotten all of them. They're all just oblivion
fall, like putting words together and being like, I'm this thing. I'm has a nose for a penis,
man. Oh, I tried to fuck, but the nose between my legs won't go into pussy. Now how could I
fuck, Nate? And that's the character. That was a great impression. I thought they were in
the room with me. They are. Turn around. And also, they don't have a penis, they just have a nose,
so they can't do anything. They can sniff. They can sniff. True. Gross. Man, if you had a nose
between your legs, all you'd be smelling was like your thigh sweat all the time. Yeah, you'd be
smelling your taint, your anus. Yeah. Would piss come out your nose? Trills. I'm going to say,
yeah, we're also going to come out. Oh, god. So you'd be smelling urine the entire time
unless you cleaned it out all the time. Yes. Man, this guy sucks. Man, this guy sucks. Hey,
fuck you nose for a penis, man. Try harder next time. All right, next voicemail is called,
I should have uploaded this one, is called sober pride worldwide. Here it goes. Okay,
three, two, one, go. There's so many drunk people in the voicemails and on the podcast lately.
What? It's pathetic, really. Dab, dab, dab. You're sober pride. It's nice to get drunk every so often.
I was not drunk on the podcast. I was hungover. This is a high school baby child who doesn't
understand. I was hungover on the podcast. Have a little schnapps. Why don't you? I was not drunk.
Have a little schnapps, underage child, school child. Yeah, why do you think you're such a big
man? Why don't you try? Why don't you try drinking some milk on the rocks? Yeah, yeah, and then come
back to me when you're fucking stupid and wasted and you can't even fucking stand up straight and
you're puking everywhere. Then we'll see who's cooler. You don't really want to be sober in a
world like this where things is fucked up. I know, right? I have to drink all this big bottle of wine
because I have to review land before time 18 and it's going to take so much alcohol to get
through the process of reviewing this movie. But I have to do it for some reason.
Is that a, did Jenny Nicholson do that? I don't know if she did it. I mean, a lot of
YouTubers do the thing where like, oh, I don't want to, I don't want to review this movie,
so I got to do it. Oh, no, I mean like the land before time, the dinosaurs or something.
Oh, well, she did do a land before time retrospective video. But yeah, that is a funny thing like,
oh, I don't want to review this, but I'm going to review this. I'm going to review it. Don't review
it. It's so bad. I'm going to review it though. I have to do it. We all understand the social
contract here. I make videos, you watch my videos, you want me to do it. I remember it so you don't
have to. And I don't have to do it, but I got to pretend that I have to do it. And I'm going to make
a big bit out of it because I got to make this video longer. So let me just take my little
prop wine bottle and then go glug glug glug and then I go, and then I go, oh no. This game sucks,
except it's actually fine, but I hate making a video about it. Anyway, anyway, pledge to my
Patreon to support me making more videos like this. I hate you and goodbye. Basically, I mean,
that's basically, that's capitalism, I guess. It's really like a metaphor for capitalism.
And by a metaphor, I mean, it is literally just the thing. Next voicemail. You're like,
we're getting down there. Next voicemail. You look at, instead of like the classic like,
oh, what are you doing in my review? You look into the mirror. What am I doing in my review?
What am I doing in my review? You have like, you have like, you have like face blindness or
something and you look in the mirror and you don't recognize yourself and you go, what are you do?
Who are you? Why are you in my review? Wait, whose review is mine?
Who am I and what, who am I and what am I doing in someone's review?
The repeat that I just watched. That's an indie RPG in the making.
Oh, what? The protagonist, and that's an indie RPG in the making of somebody trying to figure out
why they're in someone else's review. Oh, no, I was just eating, I was just eating at my favorite
local cafe and I fell through a rift and now I keep showing up in all these YouTube videos
and there's all these ponies everywhere. There's a dark, there's gotta be some kind of dark,
some dark intelligence is behind all this. I can't believe I got isekite into a review.
And now I gotta review it. Oh my god, wait, it's like you assemble your party and your party is
you have a knockoff nostalgia critic, you meet a knockoff nostalgia critic because you're in
his review and then you meet a barely animated MLP Pony Maker model and that's your next party
member. Who else would join you on your quest? The more I'm thinking about this, the more this
is actually a good idea. It is kind of a funny idea for what am I doing? You could literally
give it like a light novel title that's like what am I doing in this YouTuber's
video review or whatever. Honestly, I think it's a workable idea, it's a saleable idea
that I would buy. Nobody steal it, I'm gonna make that. No one steal it, no one steal it.
Um, next, oh I already uploaded the next one, it is called Ben Saint question mark, 3, 2, 1, go.
Ben, did you listen to the Anamorphine Time episode with the voicemails with Mr. Chris
crying yet? Because I have proved how much harder I could shitpost. Um, shit. Well, I'm glad you
took them up on the offer to leave a voicemail. No, I have not, I have, I am behind on my Anamorphine
Time. I think I'm, I'm gonna tell you exactly how many episodes I am behind. I'm like, I think I'm
maybe like four episodes behind, one, two. Yes, I am exactly four episodes behind on my
Anamorphine, wait a minute. Oh no, it's six episodes now, two more have come out since then.
Oops. Gotta get on that content, gotta consume. They gotta, I need them, I need them to stop,
I need them to start wasting more content so that I stop falling so far behind. I would
really appreciate it if they could be less efficient about with their content creation process.
Uh, thanks. Next voicemail is called 61, it is called More Like Ben Taint. Three, two, one, go.
Leave Nate and Tyler alone, they're good boys, they're good boys.
Uh, next, next one is called, next one is called I Am Serious. Okay, three, two, one, go.
How do y'all deal with the existential dread of dying alone because nobody likes you?
I don't care if nobody likes me, I just don't want to die.
That's not entirely true. Obviously I want people to like me, but dying, period, dying in any way,
is almost equally terrifying to dying alone. It's like the difference is marginal.
I think that they're more upset that they're gonna be living alone.
Yeah, I agree. Because death will just happen.
Yeah, dying alone, you just either way, you're dead. Yeah, say what you mean.
It's living alone that is the, that is the annoying part. You know, if you like,
if you like camaraderie and all that shit.
You just gotta be epic.
Easy peasy.
Have you tried being epic voicemailer? No, didn't think so. Didn't think so. You gotta be,
you gotta be disrupting, right? You gotta be making moves. You gotta be disrupting,
like Elon Musk. Wait a minute, wait a minute, I have, I have, I have terrible news. Oh God.
Elon Musk is joining the PCP.
Oh God, don't, I'm sad to report, I'm sad to report that Bitcoin has made a significant,
a significant rebound and has gone up back up to 55. I am so sad. Let me just vent.
I was watching it. I was watching it plummet. I was watching it fall. It had fallen down from
over 50 and it was basically hovering around like 40, 42. And I was like, ha ha, fuck Bitcoin.
Fuck the blockchain. And then, and then I briefly entertained the like,
maybe I should buy the dip. I was like, maybe I should buy the dip right now.
Then I was like, no, I think it's gonna keep going down. No, I'm not gonna buy the dip. Well,
if I had bought the dip when I was thinking of buying the dip, I would have made like 35%
back. I would have made 35% in like a week. It would have been huge. But I didn't. So,
you know, what I'm saying is that lesson learned and you should always go all in on any stupid
investment idea that crossed your head. Anytime you think, anytime you're wondering, should I buy
this? You already know the answer. The answer is always yes. And you should buy double of it of
whatever you're considering about. Because then you'll get that's the only way. It's the only way.
It's the only way. Ben, you said that every single time when you bought, and it didn't work out
afterwards. It didn't work. It mean it, it, it wasn't a disaster. It didn't, it didn't,
okay, but it, but if I had done it this time, but if I had, but if I had done it this time,
it would have been amazing. Think about it, right? Would have been great. Yeah, life is a bunch of
wood of shit. Well, I mean, so I guess we, so, so, so we agree. So we agree. I should, I should
have bought Bitcoin. So we agree. I should have bought the dip. I was going to buy in if it went
like crashing down to nothing. But it wouldn't do that. So I'm just sort of like not interested.
I knew I could at any moment like, Oh, well, it's down now. It could go back up. It could go back
down. I feel I wanted to go really far down. I wanted to crash and go into the negative actually.
I thought it was, I thought it was going to go, I thought it was going to dip much further than it,
then it ended up dipping. I mean, it could still, it could still dip again. I don't know. I,
I'm feeling, I'm feeling a little bit of that pain of like maybe in like 2010, you were thinking
like, maybe I should buy this Bitcoin thing I've been hearing about. I'm feeling a little bit of
that pain looking at this because I, I looked at it. I looked at it when it was 42 and I was like,
maybe I should buy the dip. Nah, fuck it. And now we're looking at it's 55. Like, oh, God.
I mean, the dips, the dips are only ever going to, it seems like the dips are just going to keep
getting higher. Like the dips aren't dipping hard enough. That's why I'm just like, I can't really
feel what you are describing is, but you're describing a bullish attitude. You're, you're
bullish on Bitcoin. Me? So you should buy, you should, so you should buy. No, right now.
Well, you just said, you said that you said the dips keep getting higher. You said the
dips keep dipping less. Which is why, which is why it's like, doesn't mean you think it's going up.
Well, yeah, over a long period of time, like at the beginning of the year,
it had a bit of a, well, if you think it's going up, you should buy, you should buy it.
Yeah, but then I, if I feel like I should buy it, I shouldn't have sold it ever.
I mean, and I feel like, you know what? I fucked around too many times and made too many mistakes.
I don't care anymore. I'm leaving the money on the table. I'm doing it. Not, not, not buying in
can be a mistake as well. This was my logic last time. Like if it goes to the moon, it will have
been a mistake not to have bought in. I don't know. I mean, I hate to even consider it because
at the end of the day, it is all, it is all a scam. It is all a scam and a, any pyramid scheme.
That's true. But never, never, I can't help but wonder, yeah, but what if I could, what if I could
sneakily be one of the, one of the few that does end up making some money? What if I could kind of
sneak some, some sneaky profit out of it? Like, like, like, like a few people get to do. What if I
could be one of them? What if I could be at the top of the pyramid? What if, what if I could
position myself atop the hierarchy and oppress those below me instead of the other way around?
You have to admit, he's got a point. He's got a point. And the point is the, the point of like a knife
and he's going to stab us. Maybe. He's going to stab us all down on below him. Maybe, maybe, maybe
there isn't, maybe it actually, I don't want to flatten all hierarchies. Maybe I want to,
maybe I actually want the hierarchies to be even more pronounced as long as I'm on top of them.
Maybe that's even better for me. Wow. So smart. Wow. I didn't even think of that before.
Before I was just doing it for no reason.
Next, next voicemail. This is a, is this the last voicemail? It's almost the last voicemail.
Um, next one is called Tom clickbait. Three, two, one, go.
The PCP of the week I came along and I see the thumbnails of back pain and I think to myself,
yes, a Tom episode. Ben, you can't take Tom's brand like that. If, if Tom had been there,
I feel certain that my piddly little back concern would have been scoffed at, laughed out of the
room for the, for the, for the, for the trifling nonsense that it is. That's why you, you had
people sent around to Tom's to break his back even more so that he couldn't be on, be on the episode.
Because I don't want him stealing my thunder on this one. I got a, I got a minor health complaint
to make a whole fucking PCP episode about God damn it. And we can't have no, we can have no
disruptions to the status quo. Anyway, yes, sorry, sorry, sorry to clickbait you like that.
The, oh wait, there's, there's one more. Okay. The next voicemail is, it's a, it's a go, it's a
go fund me link. And I know what, I know what go fund me it is, but I will play the voicemail.
There's the, there's the audio. Okay. Three, two, one, go.
I guess probably already did this, but just in case you didn't, just a friendly reminder,
please shout out that go fund me that Ethan made for Acro to help her move out of her shitty home.
Yes. True. True. This is a, I'll post the link right here. I'll put, we'll put the link
in the description. This is, this is a, this is a friend, friend of a friend of the show.
Acro is, is a trans girl who has had to, had to vacate her, her house on, on short notice
and is scrambling to like figure out like how to like move across the country and such.
And it's a, we have a fundraiser going, it's gone pretty well and it's, it's, it's, it's gotten
made pretty big progress towards their, their goal in like the last couple of days. So
check, check it out if you want to help out with that. She is friends with, with Munchie and,
and Kazzie and those, and those people and they are, they're looking at, they, oh really? And
they're, they're well looking out for it. Which is nice. They're like arm retrieval alumni. Yeah.
Oh, that's true. That's true. They were on arm retrieval. Wait, they were on arm retrieval?
They weren't on arm retrieval, but they did fan out for it. And I talked to them a lot.
And I guess she did, you know, we're like tight and all that. So this is, this is a,
this is a sad situation. It's an abusive household basically. And they're a little too young to
like just move out. So they're, they're struggling. Many such cases. Sad, sad stuff. Yes. Uh, I,
there, I, I, I, I, I donated a little bit. Um, a little bit of my, a little bit of my pocket
change. Uh, give it a look. Give it a look. Uh, um, link in the description. Um, okay, that's it.
That was the last voicemail. And it's been, what, we're like an hour? We're not even,
we're not even an hour and a half. This is what, what is this? What is this? 2017?
Dan, was there ever a PCP that short when there was like six people?
Yeah. They, they used to, they used to be that short, like a lot of the time, even when we had more people.
Unbelievable. I think that I actually don't believe it. I can't believe that such a large
amount of people talking so much, so loudly could not reach two hours plus.
I, I, let's, let's, let's, let's investigate this. Let's, let's look at the, the oldest episodes
and see, um, let's work by oldest.
Yeah. Episode two, hour 16, episode three, less than an hour. Uh, episode nine, hour eight minutes.
Episode 12, 43 minutes.
What the fuck? Yeah, they were, they were, they were like, they were semi-regularly under an hour.
Man. It's mind-blowing. It's mind-boggling.
Episode, episode 26, internet upbringing. We were, we did two and a half hours. We must have been like,
really earning our keep today. Damn. What a death. That was rough. Man, I'm, I'm pooped.
Over two hours. This is, they'll, nobody's going to listen to this. Uh, and nobody did. Oh wait, no.
Uh, 20, 21, 21,000 people did. So it was okay.
Anyway. Yeah. I don't know. Any, any last, any last words before it's fucking coitans? It's coitans for you?
Uh, well yes. Go check out the Clarissa Gunsmoke comic on Gibbentake.site.
Link in description. Uh, also please check out that GoFundMe. Give a little, give a little money
to, to Acro. Uh, you know, a small amount doesn't matter. Homelessness, homelessness is bad.
It sure is. It's bad. Especially when you had no, uh, way to avoid it happening to you suddenly. Uh, it's very,
it's fucked right now. It's not good. It's not good. Uh, true.
Um, I'm, anything else? I guess we're, I guess we're, I'm fucking done. I'm fucking done. Uh,
okay. We'll start. No, no, you know what? I'm going to reframe. You're, you're welcome for the short
episode. You're welcome for the short episode, viewers. I don't, you know, I don't want to,
I don't want to waste your time. I don't want to bullshit you. We just get in, get out.
No, this is, this is a tactic. Wham, bam, wham, bam. Thank you, ma'am. Get your daily dose. It's a tactic to,
to make them yearning for more, wanting more, to, to be pining. They're, they're so used to, to these
like huge episodes. They need to, they need to remember what it used to be like without the
PCP. They, without hours and hours of entertainment for me. They, they will, they will, they will
finish listening to this, this pitifully short hour and a half long Procrastination podcast
episode and they will say, oh, I need my fix. It wasn't enough. And they will have no choice,
but to go to patreon.com slash the Procrastinators and pledge their $5 to get access to the latest
bonus episode, the fun fact challenge. And finally, finally, they will know
all the things that we know. They will know the funnest facts. They will know the funnest facts
and be able to reference them in the future. They will have the secret knowledge that we possess.
If they have the courage, that is. Okay. I guess that's the end of the fucking show.
Good, goodbye, everyone. And I'll see you next time.
I just copied you. I just, I'm just a fucking copycat. I just hear things that I repeat them.
Take it. Take it. It's yours. Thanks. And I took it from you. You was going towards the audience
and I took it. It's mine. No, it's mine. It's mine. Wait, are we still, are we still,
is this still the episode or do we? Goodbye. Goodbye, later.