Hello. Okay, the show's starting. Yeah, okay. I didn't say the show's gonna start. The show's
starting. This is the beginning of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. We got me. Ben Saint. We got Gibbontake.
Hey. We got Tom Oliver. You all know. Back in the saddle. Okay, our guest this week. I'm stoked
to have her on. Mallory Malapert. Is that your real name? Is that your Twitter name?
No, that's just a Twitter name. Malapert is, my name is, my last name is Udicious. No one knows
how to. Udicious? Mallory Udicious. Malapert is just a Twitter name. Malapert means someone who's
saucy that likes to talk shit to, you know, people that are, you know, above them.
Yeah. News, news to me. Okay. Okay, so I will, I will try and introduce you. And if I, you disagree
with anything, you can, you can correct me. You might know her as the, the artist on Twitter who
made two, two particular pieces that were, that were controversially received by the broader
community. The first one was the new guy comic, right? Show that on, Eleazar, put it on screen,
show the new guy comic on screen, pause the video, read it, and think about it and consider,
consider, form your own opinion. Second one was, I don't know what to call it, the shoplifting one?
Well, you know, I should probably say like, you know, I do a webcomic called sweet beans.
People call me sweet beans. That's not my, but I call myself. I was calling you sweet beans until
like a week ago. Yeah. That's just the name of the webcomic. Okay. Now, now we've, we've cleared
that up. Right. Right. So the comic, your, your comic in general is called sweet beans, but that was,
was that like an episode of sweet beans? Would you call it? Yeah, you know, I don't know. It's
like sweet beans. We'll first off, you know, like I, yeah, I'm sorry, you might have to edit out
all my mumbling, but you know, it's just like a webcomic about like these, you know, characters
and, you know, they, they have feelings and I don't know. It's just like, yeah, I don't, I always
wanted to make a comic about characters and they bump up against each other and I wanted to develop
these characters. You know, I grew up watching the Simpsons and stuff like that. And, you know,
before sweet beans, I was doing like, you know, comics are, you know, like, the transphobia is
bad, you know, like that I started like in 2000. And I know, hey, you know, and like, hey, whoa,
self deprecating kind of stuff. And, you know, and, you know, I gotta just got sick of that. And,
you know, I just always wanted to make a comic with, you know, just a bunch of fun characters
with different personalities than, you know, struggling within securities and,
you know, just silly jokes and, and depressing stuff, you know, just like whatever comes to
my mind, you know, and have these characters. How long? I was going to ask how long sweet beans
has been going for? I started it like in 2019, like at the beginning. So it's not very old,
actually. You know, I feel like it's still new. I'm still figuring out all the characters. And
that like this past week, like one of the new comics was about characters, like I have that
have only been in the background so far, you know, so I feel like it's still new. I'm still
like figuring it all out. The one about the one about the two are like all hugging and stuff.
And the other two are like, yeah, yeah, yeah, you know, like the Oh, thank you. Yeah. I literally
gave it a like on Twitter. That was how strongly I felt about it. Yeah. Okay. Anything else? Anything
else I forgot to mention? I mean, I was curious if we're just going to continue the conversation.
I was curious, like the name sweet beans, because like multiple times in the comics that I've been
reading, the characters say sweet beans as a reaction to certain things. Is there like,
is there a connection to real life? Like, is that something you just say all the time and you
decided to integrate that into the comic? Or is this something kind of came naturally? Like,
was it like a did the name come first? And that's just something you say? It was just kind of like
a coincidence? Because I wasn't sure if that was like a through line, because your your comic has
multiple characters. There's there's not like a central protagonist. There's like a couple,
there's characters that reoccur. But it's not always the same like continuous story. There's
like a little, it seems like from what I was reading, it's like slices of different characters
lives. But like multiple characters say sweet beans. And I was wondering if that was
relevant more than just like a phrase. And I'm just kind of connecting dots that aren't actually
there or if there's any story behind. Yeah, sweet beans is it came from, you know, like back in the
day, I just, you know, I've worked at slew of retail jobs. And, you know, like this, I worked at
Starbucks. And it was just like this, this phrase that, you know, like, all the co workers came
up with, you know, like, because we had this customer that came in all the time. And he'd be
like, Hey, guys, cool beans. And I'm like, cool beans, this is the stupid stop saying cool beans.
And then, you know, and then we decided sweet beans sounded cooler. And so like, basically,
anytime anyone's instead of saying cool, or yes, or any, it's like, we replaced it all with sweet
beans, sweet beans. And it just stuck around. And like, so like, you know, I don't know, for like
15 years, I've been trying to get people to say sweet beans. And then like one day, you know,
one day, I'm like, Oh, maybe I could just call the my my comic sweet things. How you do it.
Comic that, you know, sneak it in. And, you know, because I feel like it has like kind of like a
peanuts vibe, you know, like, oh, peanuts, those are cute little peanuts in there. And it's like,
it says sweet sweet. I assumed, I assumed that it referred to like pause like toe beans.
You know, you know what I'm saying? Little cats have little beans on there on their little
That's what I thought it meant. I don't know. That's cute. I like that. That's that's yeah,
that's what it's from now. Okay. We've successfully rewritten history.
Awesome. So, so yeah, I became I became aware of you. It was I remember it like it was only
yesterday, even though it feels like a lifetime ago, it was at the beginning of this year.
There was a kerfuffle the kerfuffle about the new guy comic didn't didn't
It was I remember it wasn't it. Okay, I might be misremembering, but I'm pretty sure that like
Oni plays like retweeted it and said that like this is like the first meme of the new year
or something like that. Fuck that guy. Yeah, well, because if the shit started on January 1st,
I woke up to it. Yeah. And that's how I knew 2020 was going to be a bad year. It's like I'm like,
no shit. And like it has been, you know, awful for me ever since like besides like, aside from
like the pandemic stuff and everything else that is like anxiety, like on a personal level, like,
it has been shit. And but yeah, like it's it's that comic is so stupid. I like I drew it
like in a couple hours, I just like wanted to test out these brushes I had. And like my friends and
I were like, you know, we're kind of complaining about like, how like, you know, it's just so much
bad stuff is going on in the world that people don't have empathy for, right? You know, and like
everyone's like, you know, I just see on the internet, like all these people like pouring it out
like love for this like millionaire douchebag gamer guy, you know, it was because PewDiePie had
gotten robbed, right? That's that's what it was about. Yeah, in reference to like, yeah, I was never
a hundred percent sure. Okay, I thought so. Yeah. So, you know, and like, I was just like, oh, whatever,
you know, I'm just gonna like I drew, you know, I was in a good mood and I drew this like stupid
comic out, you know, and like, you know, and it's it's funny to like, you know, at the time I
belonged to this, like, you know, the, you know, chat group full of cartoonists and they're all like,
yeah, this is great. This is hilarious, you know, and, you know, and so like, you know, and same
thing with, you know, comic artists are well, you know, the same thing with the the the shoplifting
comic like got approval from like all of my friends, you know, this is great. Sure. You know,
and then like, you know, never trust your friends. Right. The public has a totally different
reaction. It's it's always like a blind side because you think like, you know, when you're
making something, you always kind of want to run a pie people just make sure like there's not like
spelling errors or it doesn't look like crap or whatever. And you get the okay from your friend
group and then you go out into the wider world and it's a totally different reaction like I tried.
I tried to avoid this. I did my best. I ab tested it and it didn't work. The the the meat. So,
so the meme was right this this the like oh first first meme of the new year whatever new decade
whatever was that like the the new guy, the guy who the guy who was like offended on behalf of
PewDiePie is the the night sky he's he's right basically was the joke and like people were like
people were like drawing like redoing it with like like, you know, making him look good and him
you know showing like oh what a sweet guy like oh he's so sweet he's so kind. I
and I was like puzzled because I saw all these redraws and like aren't about that guy before I
found what it was from and I was like who is this person like what is this even in reference to
and then I found it and I read it and I was like what is this about and I was like oh okay PewDiePie
got raw and I was like no no fuck it fuck PewDiePie who gives a shit if some gamer bro gets robbed
like why am I supposed to feel bad why should I feel bad for anything that happens to fucking a
multi-billionaire fucking Felix fucking like a you know douchebag idiot youtuber guy kind of
a little bit of a Nazi sometimes man like no thanks so I was like when when I had finally puzzled
out what was really going on with the whole like the whole meme or joke or or whatever I was like
indignant I was like no fuck this I hate this I hate that this has been the reaction to to
something that is so like yeah and I'm still and I'm still mad about it to this day when I think
about it um you know like honestly like the new guy thing it didn't bother me I I thought it was
funny like all the jokes that people were making some of them were funny yeah you know like you
know and you know and it's like so funny these days like everyone that has a hard time with me
like you know this is just like how it is on twitter it's like they want to they twist you
into this like thing that they want to see you as you know like you know and like it was just a
stupid comic that I didn't even care about I was just like you know I was just testing out brushes
I wasn't even thinking you know there's like this one asshole cartoonist I was like breaking down
how I like messed up the design because like you know this was a good guy you know and I was just
like oh I saw that yeah oh my god yeah I was I wasn't thinking any of that stuff out because I
literally like it was like you know and not like my sweet beans comics were like I give a shit about
it I it was literally like a doodle comic you know what I mean right yeah it's like that sort of
stuff pisses me off so much like the the the like nobody in their right mind would get so bent out
of shape out of like the design of this little slice of like like comedy comic webcomic that
they saw on the internet unless they had some other thing that they were trying to say although
there's some other problem that they had they had secretly that they didn't want to talk about they
said I'll just I'll talk about the art style instead and in order to bash from this person there's
all different ways people do this yeah you know it's it's such a huge problem on the end and like
it sucks how like everyone has just accepted it you know and like it's it's ridiculous and
these like social media platforms they just completely encourage all this behavior you
know it's like yeah I mean because I remember when I first read the comic my my initial reaction
like is like in the middle of the drama is like I can't understand where people are coming from I
guess I guess you'd like you know if you're if you're someone who's overly empathetic not even
overly but like you're an empathetic person you probably like you know anybody has something
bad for them you kind of feel bad for it sure like I could understand the perspective of the
comic too of just being like this guy has so much shit we don't need to like go to bat for him you
know and and when I when I saw the comic I was like okay and then I kind of like moved on and then
when like a week later people were still talking about it yeah why why is this such a big why why
is it such a big deal I wonder why I think it's just like it's because it's because Oni retweeted it
right because like you you get someone who has like a big profile to make a statement and then
their audience kind of piles on to it I you know what I I would like I would grant Oni that probably
I don't think he meant for it to happen either you think you know like because like it's so easy
for any of us to just make a comment yeah and just think nothing of it and then your audience takes
it and runs with it yeah you know yeah I mean I like Oni I think he's a funny guy but Twitter
makes you the worst version of yourself only Oni seems like kind of a douchebag honestly
that's my impression yeah like uh he like the week before he was messing with me he was messing
with this like other uh transgender cartoonist you know it's uh um it's it's a weird you know it's
like you know it's funny how people have a you know I feel like we're just like easy to pick on
you know what I mean yeah did so so so Oni was giving you shit before New Guy there's a there's
a history here then because I didn't know that oh well he wasn't giving me shit specifically
there was this other transgender um cartoonist I think what it is it's it's like it's um it's
the the boogeyman that is social justice and and everything that is you know under that umbrella
or perceived to be under that umbrella is all in in circles where people don't like
think of the nuance of these topics they just hit you know they watch a video about a person
dunking on a stupid comic or you know the the worst possible interpretation of of something
that's a little bit strange to them and then they just ascribe that thing to you know way too much
stuff so if anything is in any way social just to see or tumblery or trans or you know of that
nature they'll just think of it as a bad thing before even looking at it no absolutely and
then like these like they all think I'm like this like vokes gold you know like super tender queer
you know and that's like that's not not what I am at all you know like I'm very rough around the
edges I I'm trailer trash I you know like I you know like I try to be kind and respectful
to everyone you know and do this you know the nice social justice thing but like you know like
I mean like I yeah I'm definitely not like you know one of these people on Twitter that are like
you know constantly like screaming about you know that you're not you know you're not a school
yeah you're not a cop you know I I'm I'm you know I'm you know I'm something of an SJW
cut myself but also but also I also am not a cop that's the line with like when you're when you're
telling people when you're telling people what they should and shouldn't be doing that's that's
cop behavior and I don't think that's the line that's usually the stuff that people like the like
anti anti SJW youtubers bash on on the people who are saying this is you know like policing
language and and things like oh my free speech is being violated and then they just take that
animosity and they just put it on everything that even slightly resembles you know social
justice in any way or or even things that aren't related but they just think of it like that because
like I saw a lot of the new guy stuff you know you see comments underneath these things about like
you know this is what's wrong with America these this generation is fucked up and you know what
they're talking about and it's like yeah nothing to do with any of that it's it's the intellectual
shorthand of taking what you like the smallest possible context of somebody and applying all
the baggage of what you perceive their positions to be you know it's a you're literally straw
manning people you know they look at like that comic and they're like you must be this type of person
and so all the faults of that collective is ascribed to you personally and you're held to account
for it all which is ridiculous no I think I think you fucked up and I think you brought it all on
yourself because you gave yourself a little angry eyebrows and it made you unsympathetic and that's
why that's right that's right new guy was a round soft character that made him seem empathetic
and and the pointy glasses too many points the points implied negative connotations
he looked like heavy weapons guy from TF2 my favorite video game
you know it's it's it's funny so like a year and a half before so maybe two years I got
quote canceled again you know the the you know or base this is like the first time like yeah I got you
know uh fucked up you know I saw like people arguing on Twitter about like uh you know what
labels that LGBT people can and can't use and I just like came out like dude shut the fuck up who
cares what other you know yeah and then like people twisted that into like oh uh you know
you hate lesbians and bisexuals and I'm like oh my god you know but but the thing is it's like
these they ran with it you know like the the uh you know SGW or whatever you know you know
section of Twitter you know like the you know they ran with it and like you know there's like
people to this day I get like messages from that like oh you know you hate lesbians and I'm like oh
my gosh I've been married to lesbian for 10 fucking years what the fuck are you talking about it's
really it's really easy I don't know it's really easy to find something to like I don't know pretend
you have a problem with someone about if you uh if you I don't know if you if you've got some if
you I mean why would they do it in the first place I don't know the whole you know the whole like
I mean the whole micro label like um or whatever discussion is very fraught emotionally uh it's
it's it's it's people get people get really uh yeah hung up about it this is the thing that's the
problem right now I feel like it's like people are getting so passionate and like passionately
angry about these issues that deserve tons of nuance you know like you know it's a shoplifting
comic for instance you know it's like like there's obviously different sides to this
you know and uh you know and it's like why not like we can't why can't we have a discussion you know
it's it you know it's like this weird black and white thinking that uh that happens I don't know
if it's social media I don't know if it's just like human nature or what there's a lot to dissect
about the about the response to the shoplifting comic which I didn't mention but that was the
second like big time that I saw your stuff getting circulated around and was like oh it's
is that same is that same person oh what's going on now that's and again I saw I saw the reactions
to it and I saw edits of it and I had to like sort of work backwards and like what is this
referring to where did this come from and then again I found it and I was like no fuck that
fuck these people fuck uh a stealing is good actually but that's not even what I know that's
no I know that's not necessarily what you're saying in the comic it's just what I personally
think is that stealing is good that's that's all that's me though my views do not reflect those of
anyone else I associate with I'm gonna steal your computer next time oh why don't I doesn't
Bernie distribute all 90% of his taxes or whatever yeah okay sorry anyway what were you talking about
oh I guess uh never onto the shoplifting comic right that uh yeah so like
you know like I was I just wanted to like you know this is like something that I did in my youth
a lot right I shoplifted for you know because I grew up in poverty like I said I was trailer trash
you know like I just like for me and my friends like shoplifting snickers bars and stuff was
just normal you know because we didn't have money at all you know and like it you know and we lived
in trash and so uh you know and and this is another of my friends were like yeah this comic is great
you know I just it was to show this character you know I just like wanted to show this character
like doing this thing and then like later on in the series like slowly show like who this person is
you know and this is like just part of who this character is the comic presents the action like
pretty neutrally it doesn't even really comment or like it's just the thing that she does it yeah
like that's the thing they wanted to turn it into this discourse you know when like the actual text
of the comic was like you know and I could I guess I could you know like it's like I said I'm
I'm not like a professional like you know like like I didn't get to go to school or anything you
know this is just something I love doing you know like you know I didn't go to school to learn how
to like what how I should develop characters and story arts and stuff like that I'm just trying
to have fun and do my thing sure it's it's it's really strange because like that was one of the
things I was wondering when I read that shoplifting comic because I read it and it didn't come off
as that like much of an issue to me again it was one of the things that kind of shrug my shoulders
I'm like why are people getting so bent out of shape because like I guess the the question
that I was wondering and since reading more of your stuff it's been answered was like is this
like an autobiocomic trying to be prescriptive or is this just a character living their life
and doing things because if it's if it's the latter like there's no problem clearly it's not
it's not the latter like the comic makes no commentary about like yes you viewer should
go and steal I me I've been saying I'm saying that but the comic isn't
uh and and even even if the comic was saying that like who cares like you you can choose to
be like I don't agree with this and just sure move on even even if you thought even if you thought
that's what it was about for whatever reason it's just so strange how people like get so preachy
it's so preachy I guess it's all I don't even think it is I don't think it's cloud chasing like
like dog I don't know see responses to it like on twitter it's like it's like you know
posts or twitter accounts with like five followers are there just be okay I want to I want to unpack
it a little bit like the thing that people seem you know people say like oh those employees
they're gonna lose their jobs now they're gonna they're they're gonna they're gonna they're it's
gonna get taken out of their paycheck but first of all no it's not how jobs work second of all no
you don't nobody gets fired over this shit it's it's simply doesn't happen you're simply being
you're just it's it's so scoldy it's so fucking scoldy and it's such cop behavior why is everybody
so fucking hungry to act like a fucking cop on the internet it's because it's because they're so
fucking scared of of the video games being taken away by the scary women yeah I agree like and we'll
wait a second this is the part where I disagree right because like you know the chuds the right
wingers yeah you know like they're gonna do that thing you know that's a she violated the non-aggression
principle ah my my uh the no no no and and cap joke whatever I think I go on sorry you know
like you know no it is completely fine you know um like the you know the part that hurt me right
was like literally my own community right okay it's like group of lgbt cartoonists and allies
right yeah like a couple really popular respected folks in the community were like this is irresponsible
you know blah blah blah and that's that's that's when fucking shit hit the fan for me that sucks
so bad I don't care I don't care about right when you're you know like they could hate me all they
want like the whatever the chuckles never gonna please them laughs yeah you know I don't I really
don't care you know what like broke my heart was like how like it caught fire within my own community
and like basically I got canceled you know canceled uh that thing that doesn't exist you know um in uh
like you know and like you know all of a sudden all these people who I thought were like honestly
like friends who I talked to on the regular or at least acquaintances and well-wishers
are all of a sudden talking crap about me like you know just like unfollowing me blocking me
soft blocking me you know and uh you know like almost no like almost no one came out to defend me
it was so heartbreaking was it you know was it because there were I had a different yeah I
I was just gonna say I I only saw the chud stuff I didn't really see much of of of like I don't know
uh be heading like like like from it within like why like I don't understand because like
because now there's like oh I don't know like people are people are mad about this and I like
they just want to be like oh no no I don't endorse this no no no don't be mad at me too right that's
part of it too you know um I think uh you know uh there's like a lot of you know the stuff is
complicated I guess you know because there's like so many you know people doing different things you
know but I think you know basically uh a couple cool respected people in my community were like
fuck Mallory and like tons of people just like follow it along you know do you want to name do
you want to name names I am definitely not going to name names I'm not gonna bring myself down to
their level you know like you know I'm I'm just sort of curious like why would that even happen
like what what is so offensive to well I well okay so I've been trying to process this for months
you know because like I said like like you know I don't know if any of you have ever been part of
community and then getting exiled from it and then having like you know like people who I like
talk to on the radio just Tom was uh Tom here was uh lambasted by the Brony community once upon a
time that's true yeah quite a quite a few guys Brony's huh I when I was we were talking on Twitter I
told Mallory a little bit about our Brony history and uh you know I wouldn't say I wouldn't say we
were ever like ostracized though we pretty much left of our own accord except maybe Tom I mean on
that level the the the Brony stuff was mostly just shitty commenters who were mad that the baby
wasn't getting their bottle anymore and we weren't going to talk about pony videos uh pony episodes
anymore they were just like yeah you know I want you to do that forever I don't think any like friends
that we had made yeah I mean the thing that happened to me was I was just getting a lot of
shit from people for not being uh positive enough I was just like my whole my I was being paid
the pony show and that's evil that's something that discord would do I was is criticize the
ponies I was being paid $1,500 a month on patreon to talk about this show and so I talked about
this show and they were like you're not sucking it's dick enough and I was like all right well then
maybe I'm just shouldn't be doing this anymore and you guys are kind of dumb and then I lost
90 percent of my income in like one week yeah at the height dude 1500 a month completely insane
I'm drinking I'm drinking a I'm drinking a those are the good days so I mean like that's like
that is like the constant you know people like losing their income because like you know like
you have like a opinion about a cartoon show Jesus Christ yeah you know like it's it's it's
it's ridiculous you know well I'll defend the bronies I'll defend the bronies on that one I mean
they signed up to hear you gush about their favorite show to hear you you spread love and
positivity you know much much in the way that pinky pie would uh and then and then you didn't
deliver on your implied promise and so you you failed them I would say yeah I mean that's fair
but I mean like I mean I don't know it's like you like the pony show like why not like
take in other points of view that like might be critical like I it's it's it's ridiculous that's
you know like I I I love it when people tear apart the stuff I love it's funny like but
uh it's it's funny to think it's a funny question uh it's you know the the brony uh the brony
criticism the brony analysis youtube scene had a very particular uh culture surrounding it
and uh you know they were really in the market for a particular particular kind of analysis
I think I think the way I had always interpreted it uh just from the very beginning is that I
think so many people were into like the stuff that we were doing talking about the show in a
positive way is because they were looking for affirmations a bunch of dudes who felt who felt
like oh god I like this girly thing this feels so weird and then here's these people saying
that it actually has like legit merit so now I feel justified in my deviance and then anytime
you you said something that wasn't super positive it put their own identity the more the more
question the more people there were and like the more of like a professional veneer that they
could give themselves like say echoing the same like the show is good the show is a masterpiece
the show is important the show is valuable you know it's like it's like yeah reinforcing this
this uh yeah the whole the whole thing which people were really invested in uh you know
so yeah people were tying their identity to consumer products and felt insecure about
themselves and uh curious like consumer product isn't perfect yeah yeah it's kind of weird
it's kind of weird I don't think does perfect even exist um if you ask brownies it's my little
pony oh I wanted to make a joke I want to be like ha ha you've never seen uh have you I don't
have you seen the sonic the hedgehog 2006 oh that was a good joke thank you thank you very
okay I'm sorry um uh but yeah you know so yeah you're we're talking about like basically you
still like you know and like I'm not joking like this this shit affected personal relationships
you know like you know and like by the way folks out there listening don't try to be friends with
people who care way too much about their like social media like persona or like you know reputation
or whatever because they'll just like act like you don't exist anymore you know because like you
know oh no I you know because like associating with this person is iffy now so like like you know
I mean imagine like I don't know nobody nobody got mad nobody gets mad when like uh
ah god I don't know I'm trying to think of like another like comic or something that includes
I don't know a bit of mischief this is just some mischief that a character does and that's
I don't yeah and it's like imagine imagine being like this is irresponsible it's irresponsible to
depict mischief in Paris an upcoming comic is going to have a lot of mischief in it actually like
more more stealing destruction of property round three let's do it based did you see there was a
headline a couple months ago that like some people were had like done a little done some like they'd
like messed up a building or something and they were going to be like they there was a possibility
of them being sentenced to life in prison for mischief yeah it's yeah yeah it was because
this fucking like company that owned the building was like wanted to like make an example of them
or something uh I mean I I hope that it didn't god occur uh but that was property owners am I
property owners can't live with them gotta kill them uh okay uh yes you know but um but yeah you
know like it's like with this whole situation I feel like it's so easy to dunk on the right wingers
the chuds you know it's like sure you you know and that's like I'm just so sick of it you know it's
like you know you turn on the youtube and it's like another video of like some leftist like oh wow
you debunked Jordan Pearson again no shits wow you know like you know it's like it's not 2013
anymore man like things are different now I feel like you know like the left and progress it we need
to look at ourselves and see like our failings and try to do better in the future and like part of
the thing that we're doing is tearing each other apart over the smallest fucking little things I
the the left has a problem with like an endless purity test you know yeah you know there's these
people and they roam twitter and other social media and they're like you know like another
thing that happens to me the thing that happened to me last week right you know like uh someone
trotted out a comic that I did seven years ago to like I was just about to bring that up
so basically okay so it's been six months since the shoplifting comic right and I'm like I have no
regrets about making that comic you know I'm proud of myself you know like Cart making comics is
this thing I always wanted to do and I'm growing and I'm getting better and I'm starting to get good
at it you know and I'm proud of myself and like you know um and you know I'm not gonna be you know
I'm not just gonna carve away and like apologize and do that like fake apology thing that everyone
does you know when like the you know when I'm glad if I if I saw you apologize for it I'd be like
that sucks well yeah it's nothing to apologize for yeah well it's like the thing you know well
it's not apologizing you know it's just like I think to like when I was a kid you know like
you know like my my dad had a bad drug problem my parents are screaming at each other you know
we had no money we were barely making it by you know like I was always out of the you know I had to
get out of the house I was raised by wolves you know and like I was a feral kid and like you know
I'm not going to apologize for you know like in just you know because my audience is like you know
the age is like 15 to 45 is like you know and I just imagined some 15 year old kid that was in
a similar situation to me you know like you know it's like hey it's okay you know like
like you're not a bad person for stealing a Snickers bar or some you know uh some markers
you know and that's like another thing that got me um you know it's like well you know oh you have to
you should only steal things that you need to you know and it's like don't 15 year old poor
kids need you know uh art supplies too you know it's like you know and it just brings out how
much people in like these the so-called leftists or whatever progressives they you know they don't
like it and that's what I was going to get like these uh get to is that like the folks that gave me
a hard time you know it was mostly people from like these uh the queer animation folks right
and all of these people you know they grew up middle-class you know like LGBTQ folks in the
animation industry you know okay and like and and and like a lot of them you know they grew up middle
class upper class they got to go to college you know they you know they're not they've never really
struggled the way that you know I just I just couldn't I just couldn't get into Aladdin because
you know he steals that bread at the beginning and like he doesn't even eat it he gives it he
doesn't even need like it was terrible like like that that fucking that fucking merchant you know
that merchant's probably gonna like go out of business and die uh because of that bread you
know he really should have got his hand chopped off uh I mean he like the guard said like he knows
the penalty for stealing so he should have just accepted it in my humble opinion and that's the
thing too they they twisted it into this like you know I'm anti-worker now you know and it's all
like have you ever you know and it's like funny because like as when I was younger I helped organize
a labor union you know and it's like I you know I'm pretty based actually yeah I I'm carcaring I
ww member you know it's like don't tell me I fucking hate workers you fucking rich piece of
shit yeah damn yeah fuck that fuck yeah I'm so mad the the the you know this is the thing instead
like like you know like and like I said people who I thought were friends this stuff has cut me up at
night you know uh like the mental toll that it's it's taken on me I've lost sleep you know like
you know like some of my closest friends just gone
just because and it's and it's it's because they just didn't want to be associated with like
well you know that's a thing you know like what I don't want to like this I don't want to assign
too much now this to it you know what I mean but like it's it's just like you know like that's seen
in like the sci-fi or horror movie right where like the dystopian thing is happening and like
the person's getting shunned or like taken away and everyone just puts their head down and lets
it happen even though they all know what's wrong you know it's it's it's you know like
you know and you know because like people you know like they're trying to make money too and
they're trying to like you know do their thing you know and oh yeah you know what I mean like so
like even even if they don't think it's fair like I guess they think I think it's like they think
if they defended it they would like be perceived as like they would think it would look bad too
I understand yeah like oh you're now you're supporting this irresponsible mischief you
troublemaker you you you rascal they would say to this hypothetical person
I I get it I guess uh hmm yeah you know it like but you know like it burned you know it
chewed me up on inside and the insides and like I even like at one point like you know during one
of my lowest points you know like a couple of the people you know in the community who like I feel
like did me dirty like I sent some messages to you know and I was like hey what are you treating me
unfairly what happened to me was nuts you know like you know and you know they like just came back
and you're manipulative you're trying to make me feel bad right now and I'm like well you should
feel bad like that shit sucks you know like you know like yeah Jesus Jesus Christ not likes the
comic the and then just like shut there's so much stuff I don't like and I just shut up about it
you know you don't have to say you know you don't have to like you know try to ruin a person
shit you know well uh yeah you know but and and that's and that's the thing you know it's like
we can't have we can't have this conversation at all on the lefty it's like you know because like
you know ass like right wing assholes like are constantly complaining about like cancel culture
right it's like you know it's like these rich you know fucking comedians and stuff they're like oh no
people are being mean to me on the internet and so like and now like you know ours you know the
leftist response is like well that doesn't exist canceling doesn't exist you know okay yeah you
know and it's yeah and like I feel like that's like kind of um the thing that like we need to
start doing you know it's like some of the things that right wingers complain about there's like
nuggets of validity too that we should sure like honestly answer to you know like you know like uh
the virtue of signaling thing you know it's like how like companies you know like like uh
you know companies try to sell stuff to like lgbt people you know by putting a rainbow on it but
they don't give a fuck about us you know like oh yeah i've always hated that the whole you know
look disney and like capitalizing on of people's um acceptance of of these sorts of things they
don't actually care as soon as it stops being profitable they'll stop making it what did right
letter media call it passive progressive which i thought was a good coin of phrase for it you
know it's such a i don't know i don't know if it comes from like genuine ignorance or if it's
like a deliberate bad faith when people say like oh the the left is hypocritical because like
companies sell i don't know people like conflate it like they think that that's what the the left
is like that's what progressivism is is like oh it's just companies selling stuff with rainbows
on them oh it's just hypocritical and like no they're doing that in spite of what's good
you know yeah you know i'm capitalizing on on on on idea that's not that's not the
that's not the thing in itself yeah really you know when we get like overly happy about like
this like corporate intellectual property is like slightly more oh yeah they put the
you know they put the lesbian cop in that in that one in that elf movie or whatever
but even like the stuff that we consume you know like that like a lot of us like you know like
everyone loves shira right you know and everyone's like you know but like
you know like i it's it's uh sorry you know um but then like you know but the people who make
these things they're like they're they're rich and they're like yeah at the end of the day it's all
owned yeah it's it's you know they're making money off of you you know and like and i think
representation is good i want more representation in the media but like it's this like kind of
let's examine maybe you know like maybe just not blindly celebrate stuff and like you know
like hey are you just trying to like get money out of us get brownie points you know because like
there's a lot of you know cynical shit going on and uh it's it's it's uh it's sad i don't like it
representation only only happens in the framework of like when it's when it's uh you
know when it's gonna make money yeah that's what that's what you know people that are so concerned
about like uh you know uh uh i don't know white erasure or something or whatever i don't know they're
like uh they're like they think that like an agenda is being forced here that like oh this is
this is a conspiracy the illuminati or something is like oh they're all putting oh they're all putting
colored people in my in my media and for for various uh i won't speculate on what they think
the goal is there but uh you know it's like it's not true it's never it's never true it literally
is only done to to sell shit yeah it's it's the demographics changed and now they can make money
off of it and and then they know too that like oh we get this like you know like oh we have a
lesbian making this tv show now and so that we'll get you know and that you know it's it's also
girl boss it's fucking bullshit man and don't get me wrong i love that you know lesbians
should make all the tv shows you know what i mean like agreed that's great yeah it's it's like it's
it's a fanciful notion that it could all happen naturally but we know it doesn't and it's annoying
yeah it's capitalism man like that's you know it makes you question everything you know because
when when the motive can be so poisoned you can't really trust anybody at their word that they're
doing this for a legitimately positive reason there's always a financial motivation and it's like
well then what was the point you know and like i'm that's i'm being a little cynical about it too
you know and like that's why i keep stressing i like shira i like all of this stuff too you know
but like i don't know i think it's something about the internet just like creates this like
black and white thinking you're either on this side or that side you know like these like uh you
know there's like these fractions on the left it's split up you know there's like these people who
just like you know they're like fuck identity politics 100 percent and you know and like you
know and then these other you know on the other end that's you know like people getting mad at
like you know my comic for you know supposedly hitting trans men when a trans man actually helped
me write that comic you know and it's you know um yeah i just uh i wish there was more nuance and
people yeah i think but you know most entirely the problem is the platforms that we use to
communicate such as twitter it's mostly twitter i feel like youtube is also a bit bad because
you know comment sections on youtube videos are terrible and nobody ever likes reading them
and video responses are usually lengthy and hard to to watch all of and twitter is like
the opposite problem there's so much like small bite size takes you can't have a big discussion
in a twitter thread without it being very difficult to read it's like yeah it goes wherever
yeah and you know i think it's in a in a forum like discord it's a little better because two
people can have like a lengthy one-on-one and get to the bottom of the disagreement i've seen it happen
i've had a few disagreements and arguments in discord and they've been a lot more fruitful than
ones ever had on twitter another good thing about discord is that it's not as public you know when
you're having an argument on twitter there's a pressure that like you're in public and you need
to fucking slam dunk this thing because everyone's watching when you're in discord you have like the
freedom to make mistakes you know because if you're talking one on one with somebody it's just you
and that other person and if you say something that's wrong no one's going to be there to fucking try
and dunk on you or like analyze your conversation it's just the two of you and that's how conversation
generally has worked for like all of human history and it's only now with social media that we have
you have 250 characters to take down this other person because everyone's watching you.
Arguing on twitter, arguing on twitter really is a farce it really is just uh you know something
you do for the sake of anyone who's watching yeah it's true it's that's all it is and it's because
like you can never you never you never don't feel that like oh this is public like everyone like you
know anyone can see this right it changes everything so i i never think about that stuff you know i
can't help but to be really genuine and like messy well i mean come on you know like i think
maybe it wasn't you that was saying oh i like how messy you are you know and uh maybe uh yeah then
maybe it was someone i don't know someone recently said oh i love like how you know messy you are
you know like i don't like your art or like in your your house no like yeah messy like as in you
know like i'm raw and genuine you know that's so maybe that was not you know i don't think that was
me but but you know what i was trying to get at is that you know you know everyone's so worried
but i i don't know i think it'd be nice if people would just like just you know would be able to
loosen up a little bit and you know and then give space to others to process feeling lost or like
you know it's it's just moved so fast you know it's like you're either right or wrong you know
and good or bad you know and it's it's it's it's garbage it's it's it's not working it's obviously
not working you know there's like nazis on the street now fucking killing people you know i mean
it's because it's like social media is all about it's like the business of attention arbitrage
everybody who's on there who wants to like make something of themselves you have to gain attention
i know it's a nice word right it feels it feels good to say yeah nice um and so like the the things
that sell are the extremes and so it pushes everybody more and more to the extreme because
that's what gets you more attention and then if you're trying to have any nuance you're shot down
as a centrist or just like you know milk toast or your your lack of like hard line stances on
something means you're empowering the other side because everyone else is ingrained in their own
opinions and it's like left no room for nuance and it's left no room for growth you know people
people have just used people have used like people have like uh i think the well is a little poisoned
on nuance because people have like i don't know people will sort of pretend to be trying to have
a nuance take when they're what they're really doing is trying to push an agenda but they're like
they pretend not to be doing that they pretend like oh but you know there's more there's there's
a lot of that is obvious though you know it's like because then you go and see how they're
following it's like Ben Shapiro and stuff you're like okay go go help you know what do you mean
yeah you know like i you know i think like you know when you know it's someone like in your own
community like like you know enter a conversation with them in good faith you know but that that
did not happen whatsoever you know like well i mean like don't get around there's been tons of people
who've been supportive and love me and i just am forever grateful to the folks who stuck around
in the face of you know like being judged you know by hanging out with a priah or whatever
you know but uh ah gosh i i'm sorry i lost my train of thought so that i got i got i was gonna
i was gonna say uh what's uh what's uh i don't know what's everyone up to how's everyone feeling
how's your week how's your week been are we all uh i i i can talk about nothing because i've been
doing nothing i've been playing war the warcraft a lot based and i've been i've been going through
a weird phase where i'm like i'm i'm gaming hardcore or casual or rather you know i'm
gaming hardcore on online on surf in the web um and i'm like usually i would feel terrible and want
to die because i'm supposed to be working i'm supposed to be a hardworking artist making comics
making things supposed to be working right now and uh and usually that would lead to by the way
yes that would that would usually lead to a depression spiral um but it hasn't i'm just
i'm just playing games and i'm really into it and uh that's my week hell yeah it's a it's a really
good happy story but there's not much to say i could talk about the world of warcraft lore but
i don't know if anyone else has played uh that that game i haven't played enough to understand it
unfortunately oh i know i just really like it board rules uh alliance rules i've been yeah oh hell
yeah um but i've been going through like old quests and being like you know things that i
completed for the first time in 2011 i'm rereading the quest text and i'm like damn
i like this this is good that's cool good shit okay nice happy for you you know i'm the same way
uh with uh if i don't do the comics i get super depressed and feel weird yeah it sucks yeah uh
i'm i'm depressed and i feel weird because i'm still not done with uh uh sending with the kick
starter uh uh rewards i did a kick starter last last year and then it took me all that time to
actually get the product ready to ship and now it's taken me like two months to actually get
around to shipping them and uh it should have been done it should be done by now but it's i have like
i have like seven more to do and i'm like uh because i because i have to make drawings in each of
them yeah those drawings you've been doing are looking really good uh you know i don't you know
they've been an opportunity for me to try uh uh making art with uh physical media and i'm it's uh
it's wild it's uh it's uh it's kind of i sometimes i really like how it comes out i've been using um
these copic markers i have a big collection of copics actually that i never use but i've
finally been using them and sometimes i'm like oh my god blending these colors it's like oh it looks
nice oh it looks good it worked it actually by god it actually worked yeah yeah i my mom my mom gets
me like five new copics uh for like every christmas and birthday so i have like i don't know i must have
like almost a hundred here now holy shit yeah i've got a lot that's crazy um yeah um did she steal them
she better i wish that's the only way i would say mom i won't accept it if you pay money for them i
want i only want stolen gifts from now on police um uh yeah i don't know i'm i'm depressed because
i still haven't i'm still under the yoke i'm still under the yoke of of doing a delivery on all this
shit uh and it's kind of my fault i've just kind of been like dragging my ass about it again as i
always do that's i'm supposed to be working right now and uh and then when that's done i am about to
receive i am about to receive in the mail the final shipment of the rewards for the rfck kick
starter so then i will have to do it again and i've been thinking never like god it never ends
but when when that's over then i will be like now what do i do with myself and and and i'm thinking
like okay well i have that one i have that one rfck like uh uh the slime and punishment finale
project that i've been thinking about for like a year now and then i'll finally be able to do that
and then uh i really want oh man i really want to do another nuzlocke lately i've been thinking
more about nuzlocke and i and i started huh that would be fine you should do it i i will i will do
it uh it's just um you know only one my other stuff is like only when i feel like i've satisfied
uh my other shit um i just want to i don't know uh it's just like dive into it i could i could even
see myself just like maybe streaming it just like every day just like wake up and just start streaming
pokemon just do it like every day for like you know a week or a month or however fucking long
it takes uh it would be something to just like lose myself in i don't know something to so i could
be like gib and i could just be hardcore gaming and not even feel bad about it um i would um i would
um oh fuck i was gonna say oh yeah i've been watching i've been watching this youtuber well
i guess he was a twitch streamer who has like recently gained a bit of a following on youtube as
well uh uh uh pokemon challenges who is the best the best nuzlocke or in the world is his uh claim
to fame uh and he does like he just he's on twitch and he just fucking he just nuzlocke's
like even nuzlocke's fan games he just does them over and over and over again uh he you know does
imposes all kinds of like extra extra uh challenges on himself when he does it
and i'm watching his shit and i'm just like yes um oh i love it it's so i don't know something
something about it is very uh it just just makes me want it makes me want it makes me want to do
another one but i can't do it but i can't do it because i'm too anxious about all the things that
i have not done other than yeah yeah the struggle yeah it's it's a it's a pretzel of like um the
anxiety the anxiousness of having all this hanging over your head is more of the obstacle that stops
you from doing it and you you've got to try and somehow untangle that in you know do things in
the right order and it's like i can't figure out how to do this in the right order in order to
untangle it and you just sit there for months right the analysis paralysis of like what do i do
makes you do nothing and then you just feel worse i've just been doing resin printing
i finally got my resin printer all set up and going i posted one on twitter uh that looks so good
it's like so much better than the old prints i was doing and i'm just like oh man like i would
actually be okay like selling this like the other ones like i was sending them to patrons
i have to send a bunch out actually today or tomorrow because it's sunday uh but these ones
like i would actually be able to sell they look professionally done and just like oh my god oh
this is the best thing in the world so i'm just gonna make it army folks try to uh have you tried
Adderall have i tried no oh god no not i've heard that of that being used to be productive i don't
know what it is so exactly i thought it was an alcohol for a while but it sounds like
because it starts with an a and i know of absence as a thing i thought maybe that will help i was
brief i was briefly on i was briefly on some i don't think it was Adderall i was briefly on
some like adhd medication when i was like in high school even though i don't think i have that uh
and it didn't go that well made me very irritable i and i punched a hole in the i kicked a hole in
the wall uh and then my dad was like i'm taking you off that stuff but i'm still gonna but i'm
gonna even though i i i ben's dad uh uh got ben prescribed this stuff because i thought he was uh
he was being a little bitch uh and then and then when ben freaked out and kicked a hole in the wall
i will take him off the stuff but also punish him for it by making him repair the hole i see no
contradiction in this i take no responsibility for anything uh thanks dad given you beast pills
so ben's got daddy issues huh uh uh that's a terrible thing to say about a person
i would never accuse my even my worst enemy i was just trying to be funny well well everyone
else laughed so nah bullseye bullseye you got it yeah yeah okay throwing him under the bus all right
all right moving on moving on uh you guys all okay got we gotta talk about it wait wait wait
we can't move on we have Mallory hasn't said if they're doing anything cool we we all just talked
oh now we just sat there and listened patiently are you making any new cool comics do anything
fucking sick oh i do have something coming up uh uh let's see so i i i have i have been pretty
quiet about this uh so far but uh there's gonna be a plushie of my character ivy available soon
so oh fuck where you get is he getting that made through like a site or something or you're doing
like by hand or how's how's how's that production begin uh yeah so yeah so this is the thing this uh
marketing dude from this toy company called make ship got ahold of me and was like hey we want to
make your character into a doll this is what we do and uh basically it works like Kickstarter
they like i guess they go out and find people who they think could uh sell enough of these i
need to sell 400 for it to work what and uh yeah i think i could do it i don't know maybe
we'll see now that's so cool that they came to you i tried to make um i tried to kick start a
plush of my character once it didn't work but i just went through Kickstarter i was i found this
this this what was it called uh i can't remember i got this thing and i was like
yeah and they do mass produce orders uh i'm so angry about it still
i i put my money down i was there you should you should um i think we maybe talked about this
before but when you do uh the uh you should make you should make it a stretch goal for uh the next
thing that you're going to bell jay book yeah yeah the bell jay book
because i think that's because i think yes yeah because i think the um the issue was like you
know it's kind of an expensive item uh you know kind of a high barrier to entry whereas i think
if the if the book was like you know maybe 20 bucks or something i think there would be a
lot of people who would go for that uh uh and uh you know i think more people would be interested
in making you know you know there's a there's a certain crowd you know people got a budget
for this kind of stuff uh yeah so i don't know piggyback it piggyback it off of another thing
perhaps uh i would like i would like a pump a pump plush uh be pretty pretty pretty epic
haha uh oh yeah oh yeah and you put the you put the you put my pins on it on it's on it or on
on shawl right or no on your brisker yeah my brisker plush that i they got from the same company
yes right it's it's cool anyway the ivy plush how's that how's that going uh i guess well right
now they're just designing it and then i have to approve it and then i guess the camp the pan can't
then the campaign is going to start in the next couple weeks oh shit soon that's so cool have you
seen yeah i hope it works have you seen i've never done do you know what it looks like no i've i've
just seen i've seen the designs for it well how would you feel if i stole one wouldn't that be
ironic hmm oh i know yes it's the that is that it's completely on the same level it's dealing
from a multimillion dollar corporation yeah yeah get owned okay well that's pretty uh yeah i'm pretty
excited about it um right now i have a comic promoting it on my patreon like once it gets closer
to the actual campaign i'll share on the other social medias um based based yeah i hope it works
out because i definitely couldn't handle another public humiliation at this point i think who among
us could uh do you have can you show us well they haven't designed it yet so you don't know
what it looks like yet right yeah but um i don't know if you go to my uh patreon there's a comic about
it uh uh you know there's a public for all god no no okay okay you gotta pay the dollar baby
shut down uh wait what's your what's your patreon uh is it plug sweet things patreon.com slash uh let's
see mpng is my png oh wow oh wow nice nice killing it you're killing it over here uh
see that's because i don't make promises i can't make you know basically my patreon deal is is like
you know people who sign up could see the comics before i put them on social media and that's it
you know and then that's the deal you know that yeah because uh because like i you know i got the
ad hd i got the depression uh you know sometimes i could go a little bit without doing anything and
i don't want to make promises i can't make or can't keep yeah i would be um yeah my my patreon
is also it's like tom does like rewards and stuff and i'm like that sounds hard it's yeah a lot of work
you know and like that's it you know with my comic i'm just like i make all these comics for me
i'm not like i don't think about audience and stuff like that which obviously keeps backfiring on me
you know um sure but i don't care because it's like you know it's like i'm just doing this for me
and i'm just very blessed and lucky that a lot of people enjoy it so you know it's like i pay my rent
doing you know uh anthropomorphic comics you know that's pretty cool that is the dream
have you read tales gets trolled uh no but i i know the drawings okay okay good it's a good
it's a good comic i reckon i recommend it highly um how does that stuff work with all the copyright
stuff you know i just you know like uh one of my favorite artists right now they they do all this
Burton Ernie uh fan art and they're doing a comic of Burton Ernie and they're gay together and stuff
like that like oh i've seen some of those that's really cute yeah isn't that great i love that
i think i think that's probably uh yeah i think if they're like making money through patreon i think
it would probably not be a problem i know that the the the mario that that like mario animator guy
got his patreon shut down by nintendo let's see mario bro depends on on who owns the coffee right
and whether they're willing to go out and you know hunt down people using the the likenesses of
characters just to put like a lot of the time you can just get away i love but mario no no no no
i love nintendo games like they're my favorite but god they're such fucking ass they are yeah yeah
yeah they're very litigious you know it's like they can they they can lose money every single year
for like 300 years and still like be a decent business like what are they doing with this
shit like why what is the point of it you know they're the i think they're the richest company in
japan as of like this year i believe so yeah the switches don't really well they're shareholders to
please some some people with i gotta wear suits are they need money i think and that's why
they say please more money and they nintendo says yes they get it yes so you know what no but but
what the i don't you know see this is the thing we're just like rich people in general i think
in companies and stuff it's they don't want more they specifically want other people to have less
you know like because they have enough all these rich people have enough nintendo has enough
they specifically want you know these people making their fun little games their their tribute games
and you know comics or whatever they want them to have less it's really disgusting i think i
think rich people treat money like normal people treat social media followers it's about it's
just about score it's about keeping score i need a higher score because once you have that much money
it's no longer a resource like your bases are covered you're never going to have to worry about
money and like spending it to acquire things to live so that point you're just keeping score who
could be the richest person i want to be i want to have the most subscribers i want to have the most
money and so it's it's about squeezing as much out of the people so you can be higher on that
like tier list of of rich people it's just like that's why jeff basos has a bajillion dollars
he's just like ego tripping hardcore do you know it's really funny about that too it's like just
like rich people like you know folks with like lots of followers say like want to pretend like that
isn't any kind of currency whatsoever you know like it doesn't exist like uh you know like people
like they like turn their nose up at the term of social capital when like you know the only reason
why my stuff gets seen is because i got 22 000 followers and like you know like a couple's even
more famous people follow me you know that's like it gives you legitimacy and then it just helps you
even further you know uh it's social capital is translated like directly into actual capital
all the time it's like how it works yeah but you know you'd like go into some of these like
progressive or leftist spaces and they'll crucify you for saying that you know is it like i mean do
people i don't know i i think it's if you've got if you've got clout if you've got the followers
it's probably pretty tempting or pretty uh you know to say like to want to pretend that like
that's not a thing if you've got it uh uh but like you know i mean who who among us you know
when you interact when you have like a twitter interaction with like someone with way more
followers than you or something and then suddenly like you're you're flooded with uh you know
with notifications like way more than usual you know like it's obvious it's obvious that
like a phenomenon is occurring here that you have we have we have we have butted up against a
a sort of a power differential here that is causing uh some effects you know it's very it's yeah
and do you know it's funny i think we just got to the crux of a lot of the issues that we've
been talking about today you know it's a bunch of weird power dynamics you know that happen
yeah oh yeah like like uh i don't want to like assume too much but like i i know people would
like just turn on each other when like uh you know their friend is like oh now they're famous now
they go to all this cloud well now i hate them and i want them to die and i want them i want to
cancel them to see how they like having nothing just like me people get really emotional about
things like that oh absolutely they do you know it's like i even even have friends right you know
like uh recently like i'm like hey you know i told one of my you know comic friends and like
i got this plushy thing going on and like the first thing they said was like well why didn't
they come to me for the plushy i'm like what the heck why can't you just be happy for me man
yeah it's i mean i understand the temptation to succumb to the sour grapes it's it's okay to have
sour grapes you just don't lead with it you you say you know sour grapes are a natural phenomenon
but you can't let that you acknowledge your sour grapes you can't lead the the charge with a sour
grape it's a bad look yeah it's not very nice acknowledge them and move past them
um no one likes talking about sour grapes or envy or jealousy it's like this such a taboo
subject that like everyone's like oh no i don't feel those feelings ever you know um and i feel
like uh especially on social media especially with like people who are trying to like do something
and have an audience you know i feel like that stuff is a lot more common than it's it's obvious
the numbers yeah everybody you obviously are there you want the numbers to be higher because
that like makes it more effective at whatever it is you do it yeah like who who does what people
are embarrassed to have emotions people are embarrassed to admit that they get angry at
things and it's it's not good they got it it's all part of humanity and living and being a person
if you if you hide behind like oh oh no no i'm i'm like like a robot that makes me cooler than
you actually it's just it's just lies be true be real it's it's weird you know and and that
that's why i don't trust anyone with like over 50 000 you know followers on twitter it's like
you know it's like wow you're you're pleasing that many people at once you know you're just
good at keeping the mask on right you know like giving everyone what they want yeah i mean as your
audience gets bigger it gets more difficult you know it's more difficult to kind of juggle all those
competing interests from people who follow you and like i on the one hand it's like we'll just be
yourself like resist that temptation but like when your livelihoods tied up in that it becomes a much
more complicated equation yeah it's true it's true you just gotta be i i i try to be very genuine
yeah that's a cool thing i mean as your as you when your audience is big enough when your when
your platform is big enough i assumed i assume there comes a point where it all just becomes
noise and you just like can't listen to any of it and you just kind of probably have to just
just zone it out and like not even worry about like what anyone's like saying uh because if you
list because there'd be so much i don't know imagine you have like a hundred thousand followers
and every time you tweet you get like hundreds of replies i mean you might you might read some
and get like a sort of like feeling about like the general kind of thing people are saying and
like what people think about what you're doing but uh you know you would sort of just that's all you
would could really get is like a feeling like there's too much yeah you you would need too much to
really need managers you would need like um people vetting like reading and being like hey have you
heard that people are saying this like because you personally couldn't keep track of everything you'd
need you would need other people to to sift through it if there was a reason to do so yeah and i think
that's really tough because like from a user perspective like like the reason like people
who aren't creators who don't have a huge audience like social media so much is because it gives you
a communication line to people you care about right like we all have people who are interested
in our work and they can talk to us on a level that normally you wouldn't have access to with like
a celebrity and like traditional uh media um yeah and so there's like that personal feeling
and then once you get big enough that feeling dissolves on your side because it's just there's
just so much you like literally just as a human being can't process all that information but all
those a hundred thousand people still feel like they have a connection with you and it's incredibly
difficult and then it gets back to the thing that you're saying earlier like you know as soon
as something gets popular people look will fuck that stuff exactly it comes cool to hate because
then like there are a bunch of people but hurt that you made it well you know and and that's
completely understandable too you know because like you know it's like i i love comics and
cartoons right and like every single day i just see such incredible work from people that have like
a thousand followers two thousand followers you know it's like what do i do that's so special
you know i got 22 000 people on twitter following me 20 000 people on facebook
you know like i i don't you know like i just feel like there's so many more
cartoonists that are doing you know better work i've seen i've seen really great art from people
with a lot less of a following than me and i'm like huh makes makes you think makes you think
that maybe the meritocracy is a lie it is a complete lie you know it's uh i'm just i'm just
i just can't shut up i'm an attention whore you know i'm just lonely and so i go to twitter because
i'm alone and it's this like false sense of community and i'm like and i just say my random
thoughts and people are like hey yeah that's right you know i hate to admit that i also do that
but it's it's so obvious that's what it's for it is i guess that is what it's for i mean
studies show that uh folks that uh feel more lonely are more likely to post more
on social media so like when you see you know one of your favorite you know someone posting
over and over again you know like yeah give them a comment or even rich i'll be like hey how you
doing today you know um i feel i feel called out i feel seen in a bad way any of folks that
listen to the the guy the musician jeff rosenstock i don't no i don't know anything
about uh he's like this uh you know kind of punky musician he uh he got to start doing like scott music
in the early 2000s and then um uh went solo but uh you know uh he's getting he actually oh he does
all the music for craig of the creek uh yeah yeah he's uh um if you like punky type of music i highly
suggest it um but like basically all of his watches cartoons i do watch cartoons i like them a lot
yeah curtains are fun i love all ages cartoons um but yeah like anyway one of the lyrics that stands
out to me is you know he says rushes to his phone because he doesn't want to feel alone you know um
you know that's like exactly what i do too you know it's like i'm sitting all alone and i'm like oh
maybe twitter i won't feel so lonely you know but i mean it's even you know but that's a lie too
because twitter is bullshit you know yeah it's i've like purposely put my phone away for a while
and i've gone like a couple days without any social media and there is like a kind of zen that returns
that i haven't felt since i was like 12 before phones existed i'm like ah there were times you
could just literally be alone because like it's a totally different feeling having your phone on you
than not because like you feel like especially when you're someone like me who's like a fucking
shut and neat and like all your friends are through online so it feels like everybody is
with you and nobody's with you at the same time all the time so to actually be alone and to cut
that part off and have no computer and no phone around you just like oh i'm like alive again
almost yeah it's like a different way of thinking that was i think it's been months since i've gone
a day without checking twitter um you should do what i do i i have uh app block on my phone and i
have said it that i am allowed to use twitter for 60 seconds every day and then it gets blocked for
the entire day so i always like every time i wake up i'm like 60 yeah i go to twitter i'm like okay
what's on twitter and then oh oh that's right i'm blocking it and then i forget about it and it's
great i get to do that little uh i'm waking up and i need to check twitter like i do every day
but then it immediately goes away it's it's it's actually quite cool that is awesome because i i
struggle with addiction in general you know like i was saying earlier you know the addiction runs in
my family it's you know it was really bad growing up but yeah like uh you know so i read books on
how to deal with addiction and uh one of the things they say is that like you know the difference
between a habit and an addiction is this feeling of um of despair like of hopelessness right and
you know you feel that hopelessness and then you could get control you know by turning to your
addiction you know and you know i couldn't you know i completely feel you know it's like i feel
utterly alone in the universe i'll go on twitter where people are you know and i was like i i you
know i haven't gone a day without twitter and i can't remember the last time you know yeah it's uh
it's ridiculous yeah i mean every time i go on twitter like i kind of i took a break from twitter
i think last month or the month before for a week and then i came back and i've just noticed
almost every time i go on twitter i feel worse than i did before because there's always something
that's on my timeline that like is annoying or insulting or unfortunate or like i'm just i
just find myself doom scrolling because it's 2020 and that's all the timeline is i'm just like
like i need this because this is my primary platform where i interact with like my audience
but at the same time it's a net negative on my mental state always it's like why do i do this
see you know and for me it's like uh it's it's kind of a mix right you know kind of like i like uh
i use the cannabis too right you know and like a little bit of weed right will help me and make
me feel good and like you know just a little bit and then i'll get more productive i'll come up with
ideas and stuff but then like i get sucked in and then i start doing i smoke too much weed well i
don't smoke it i eat it usually but um and then it stops working well for me you know and then
it's just like it doesn't feel good anymore you know i feel like twitter's the same way for me
like a little bit you know like i get that interaction you know i have some funny conversations
i actually connect to people i have kind of the same thing i kind of do the same thing with booze
i'll take if i have like a shot or something or half a shot sometimes it makes me a little more like
a little more willing to like sit down and like you know like draw something whereas like otherwise
i might like overthink it and be like no i don't want to i don't want to do that i don't want to
draw that no i'm i'm nervous it'll be bad or like oh what if i what if i fuck it up and it's a waste
of time uh and then i get drunk and then i just pass out and then i hung over the next day it is
an unfortunate pet and it's a disaster yeah yeah like like was that you who said you were hung over
today yes yeah i feel better now that's good yes thank you
uh where were we what's going on where am i i don't know i'm sorry i brought up addiction
i don't know i brought up addiction oh sure and feeling alone and all this i don't know i
like talking about stuff that's like hard for people to talk about so i make the room silent
a lot of times no it's it's real shit i mean we don't we don't rule talked about it before
yeah we're no we're no strangers to interesting depth conversations like that it's not
doesn't have to be all fluff so i mean i deal with it all the time it's like that depression
and just the feeling of just like inadequacy and like comparing yourself and like it's that's like
really the thing with social media right is it's it's uh social media and patreon have like put a
number to your success in a very clear manner and so it's very easy to compare yourself to others
right like i can look at anybody that i like and you can just break it down to numbers like they are
ex followers better than me they are ex patrons better than me uh you know their ex engagement
better than me and they shove all that in our face too it's like when you write on that's the first
thing you see you know and then people pretend and then people pretend no that stuff doesn't matter
it doesn't just some people i'm sure it doesn't i mean some people if you have like a lot of
shit going on in the real world and you have like a career and blah blah blah i'm sure like
twitter doesn't faze you because like you're busy like going into the office and getting
shit done and being like a real cog in the machine i don't know what that's like i'm sure it's grand
quote unquote but like if you're in it if you're trying to like be successful and you're trying
to be an artist like the way to be an artist or creative person now is to go on social media
and whore yourself out for views and clicks and it's just like that's a metric that's like your
guidepost for how well you're doing and it's like the people say don't compare yourself to others
but i'm always feeling at the same time i don't know how i'm doing the only way to measure if i'm
like doing well and to course correct is to look at that information and compartmentalize it and
like analyze it and try and like course correct when things are bad and things like that and it's
just like it makes something that started out as just pure passion very monotonous and mechanical
and it almost doesn't feel worth it at that point and then you want to reject that and just like
fuck it i'm gonna just do what i want to do but then it's like oh now i have no money and now i'm
dying so it's just like uh gross yikes yikes yikes you gotta give the people what they want and
high doses yeah seriously it's like quality and quantity on point 24 7 every day it's never be
wrong don't you have to be correct yeah constantly if you disappear for a week the algorithm forgets
about you and then you got to start all over again i i like being nobody i like being somebody who's
just sort of like pretty cool like niche like but not even like a large niche just sort of like
like you know one of these days i'll start my career but not yet and i i guess i have i literally
just want a cult following and like a literal cult i just want to have like 10 people who give me
$10,000 that's fine that's fine with that i guess i i guess that i i like some aspects of being
niche but uh mostly i just hate being a small fish in a big pond and i just want to get big and crush
my enemies you mean physically i just want to be more i want to well sure yeah obviously um i just
want to be i just want to like wield power and destroy those who oppose me that's that's just
that's why that's why i get into this whole internet creator game nice good good for you hope
of you you've reached your dreams i just it's you know i feel i don't know man i feel i see
i follow all these people on twitter who like you know i like the stuff they say i like the
stuff they post and i'm like oh these guys are cool i like these guys oh some of them are like
friends with each other they they taught they tweeted each other like oh that's cool that's
funny to see and then i'm like oh i am like nothing to these people i am like an i'm an ant
i'm like a one i'm like a two percent of like their power level on the internet uh and it's it's
something very demoralizing huh what you mean something to me yeah well how many followers
you got um nothing i've i've got good followers they they count you know you know you know when
when i get in that comparing mindset it's very it hurts it makes me feel bad and just makes me want
like i must i must accrue power i must accrue social capital you know well just just compare
yourself to your past self instead of other people think think of t-bap been yeah but my past
self made 90 like 10 times oh no don't think of that t-bap and the fucking base oh yeah that's it
so uh you know i speak comparing myself to i was i was i uh you know for some reason because i
was in a nuzlocking mood yesterday i went and i watched a little bit i watched the finale of uh
nuzlock uh genocide again and i i think i mentioned this on a stream recently but like
i can't believe how how different i sounded my voice is like markedly different in like that
era i'm like bad at like maintaining the breath control i'm like there's parts where i'm like
almost like gasping and like my voice sounds so like it sounds deeper but also like more
it's it's weird it's it's strange to hear like such a clear difference it's only like
i don't know exactly when it stopped but there's like a pre that and a post that that like era
in in like my stuff and i don't know exactly when the transition happened uh it's it's really
working on a podcast you probably end up you know just learning the way that you're supposed to
talk like you know halfway through these podcasts i got super i'm like insecure i'm like oh my god i
sound like an idiot i'm yelling i'm like seeing you know i i come off as trashy probably i don't
know that's like what i was you know thinking halfway through this thing i'm like it probably
do it i i blew it i fucking blew it um did she blow it guys no no did you blow it okay all right
commenters let us know if she blew it you know i got all passionate about like people being mean
to me and i'm like
we have plenty of mean people in the comments uh so you know actually our our commenters well
i mean they're not you know they're not great but they're i think they're okay you know i think
they're maybe a little above yeah they're below par they need to step up their game okay okay commenters
flex how cool you are in the comments you have to flex your brain you have to do more controversial
stuff you have to get controversial guests on and they have to say like extreme things and you
have to have we have to get alex jones sort of get out it goes straight to alex jones the most
extreme possible we could do it are any of you folks are any of you folks old enough to remember
when that guy was just like about aliens and like very mild conspiracies like before he was like
i might be old enough but i used to watch all of his documentaries on youtube and i
thought they were hilarious like the one where he's like i've infiltrated bohemian grove and
like all this crazy shit oh man i was i was into alex jones before he was cool i i love that crap
as a kid you know because i was like man fuck these rich people you know like you know it's like
you know they do weird ceremonies and stuff like they're controlling the world eating babies
demon spawn yeah i never really uh looked at build a bird group and the trilateral commission
are controlling everything i've only ever seen clips of him just problem but that's enough and
he's very funny from what i've seen crazy man he's a treat he's a joy we we should have and then he
turned into like yeah get him on buy my pills oh but then yeah but then he got into the right wing
grift so he know yeah that's where the money is i guess because i know is there any left wing
grifters is that i'm sure there's some bends are left for ingrifter bends uh doing something with
his mic i guess ben's mic is muted so i could say that and i know you wouldn't say anything back
i'm back uh i am a big big time grifter uh i just want and i want to be bigger i just want to be
the biggest grifter i can be um uh you know man there's a are there left wing grifters either
there probably are kind of depends kind of depends on how you define grifter i feel like people throw
that word around a lot i feel like there's some people on who are like formerly in like the
skeptic community who are now left leaning and some people say that's a grift and not like a legitimate
change of opinion yeah i don't know like i don't know if you wanted to do it for money i mean there's
way more money in in the right wing like i mean is maybe not for everyone yeah yeah like um tim
tim pool has become the fucking goblin that he is now because like of info wars money oh as uh as
he's associated with info wars now tim pool not he i was asking i asked someone about this in my
discord and i guess uh uh info wars like funded him to do something i don't know i was asking like
why did he i was asking like was he always like this and i guess the answer is no and there was
like he he did he did some shit for info wars for a while holy shit yeah i didn't i didn't know that
i i don't know much about it even now because i can't give you any details like as in peace
he's so big and he's so bad he's so i think he might be my most hated person in the entire world
i know that probably in the grants i i'm not i'm not joking i know that in the grand scheme of
things there's probably worse people and people who are worse for the world but in terms of just
like how much i viscerally hate them i think he might be it he's he's really he's really
climbing the ranks every single time apparently apparently vosh is going to his studio to debate
in real life and i'm excited it's going to be a fun time did you see that whole the whole thing
about how he kept he kept like he refused to like uh leftist won't debate me and then like all these
people would but he's like no i won't do it on a call i haven't i haven't you only you can only do
content in like three years well people were retweeting it because he kept like saying like
no no debate me no no debate me but he's like he won't do it over he won't do it remotely he you
have to like travel across the country to come and do it in studio and it's like why yeah why would
you do this if you heard about they catch covid and die on the way so we can win by default i don't
know i did hear that vosh was going to do that it's funny she just wanted to make it as unlikely
as possible that a leftist would actually try to debate him and so that he continued to say
that leftists won't debate me all these commies don't have any money that's why they're commies so
they came in afford to come here he's not he's not a smart individual and i don't think he can defend
himself against i mean i i think i used to watch tim pool like back in like 2017 or something and
he was still a pretty small channel and he definitely was not the same kind of duty as now like like
him and sargon have shifted so far right in the last couple years where like they were they were like
misguided but palatable to a degree when you're like a fucking
a centrist right kind of person like i am but like i listen to their content now they're not
even the same person wait oh my god tom you're you're a centrist right person i mean centrist left
my bed that's the that's the opposite yeah yeah i said the wrong thing i'm i'm definitely more
the left guy i'm like a sock kind of dude everyone should everyone should just become
communists malibu is like literally ready to kill me it's like oh we're gonna go to
i was gonna be like oh my gosh i can't believe you know because like i don't i feel like you're
really cool i grew up conservative christian so i guess at one point i was centrist right
i have a friend i have a friend who who calls him he's if you ask him he'll like call himself
kind of like right leaning but like the thing about him is that i don't know i think is that he
he strikes me as like genuinely apolitical and i think what he means when he says that is just
that he's like trad he just you know wants like you know white picket fence wife two and a half
kids and a dog or whatever like whenever like politics comes up he doesn't like he doesn't
say the things that you that i would associate with someone who calls himself that he's like
i don't know he talks about like uh you know how like oh like uh uh uh yeah vietnam had like a really
effective like a public housing uh you know infrastructure or something like i don't he's
interested in that kind of stuff so i don't know it's it's uh i think i don't know or i don't know
who's vietnam he he's an architecture student and he was talking about how like you know like some
some like southeast asian countries like compared in terms of like how they had like you know solved
the housing crisis with like public options and whatever uh i don't know the point is like he i don't
know i think it's interesting but like yeah he he will say that he's right leading but i don't think
i don't even think he is and that's why he's still my friend lemau see this is the thing i i'm beginning
to notice that like people like they love leftist policies like when they're in action you know
but they hate they hate our guts they you know and it's because it's obvious for fucking you
know like the left is just filled with like smug we're better than you assholes you know
and uh you know i think that turns off a lot of people you know like yeah um i mean people people
people think libs people think libs are the left and it's very frustrating it's a very you see all
over the place and again i said this before i'm not sure if they don't understand or if they're
like deliberate if deliberately misrepresentation i think it's definitely a little i would imagine
they don't understand because i didn't understand until a few years ago or maybe maybe even just one
or two years ago language like i didn't understand the left because the only things i had seen
were videos by um people dunking on feminists and i thought yeah this feminism stuff is silly
that it's it's it's worse in in uh countries in the other places in the world not in the western
world and like you know i've just bought into that because i didn't see the alternative side
once i had i was like oh well there's there's there's there's more to it than i thought
we'll see the uh do you see the debate the last debate i have never seen such a thing ever
never will i i i actually i actually did watch this one i thought it would be funny it wasn't
that funny uh but there was the part where it's depressing yeah i kind of like the part where
trump said that the kamala harris was like more he said more liberal than bernie sanders it's like
okay uh he's like uh i mean i get that is that is true technically more yeah you're not the way he
meant it though yeah yeah i know well that's uh sure uh i don't know and uh i wouldn't wouldn't
wouldn't recommend uh it was very um boring but it wasn't that long yeah i was just gonna say you
know um i i find all of the drama in in the left really interesting you know um i like because like
i don't know the people in my circles on social media they hate all of the youtube leftist people
they just despise them all you know you know yeah i get that i don't know i i i think uh i like
them i like you lefty i like bread tube what there i said it you know even though i don't i don't
watch as much so i don't watch as much of it as i as i was for a while because i feel like i've
reached the point where i kind of get it but for a while there i was down the rabbit hole and i was
like yeah this is cool i'm glad people are saying this shit you know i i definitely don't hate any of
them i uh i i uh you know i have their videos on in the background a lot of times when i draw
and stuff like that you know because i mean you know what else am i going to listen to you know
yeah but yeah it's like it's funny how like you know it's like i don't know like every like
there's groups of people who hate fosh and then like you know there's everyone hates
contra points and then everyone you know like god you know are we all we're all riding with
biden right we're all riding with biden hell yeah choo choo choo the biden train is leaving
the station i'm lucky that i don't need to yeah you know i've never voted uh for a democrat for
president in my life it's always been third party yeah well i mean i i've lived in states
i live in i've only lived in blue states like i grew up in chicago and like yeah and 2008 right
i was like a nadir person you know like uh yeah yeah you know someone spit on me once uh in chicago
uh when they saw my nadir pin yeah it was during 2008 when things were you know yeah i got spit on
for wearing a nadir pin it was pretty intense uh i love uh walking around uh in my yang shirt uh my
yang 2020 shirt is going to be a uh a treasured possession of mine uh for the rest of my life
i hope really a yang man oh Jesus no okay for like i had like a two week period where i heard
about yang and thought he was pretty cool and then i was quickly disillusioned and realized he's
kind of just a libertarian tech bro and uh and that his ubi was a little like i kind of like the idea
but like his version of it is like the worst version of it uh so no but kind of but only briefly
no i'm sorry i apologize i apologize for my if anyone sees me wearing my yang shirt i'm sorry
you know it's it's funny how like everyone just argues about like these individuals you're like
oh yang or oh bernie or like how oh the the dnc screwed over bernie i'm like they didn't screw
over bernie bernie's fine they screwed over us that's who they screwed over sure you know
you know like like you know all these politicians they might be different but at the end of the day
they're on the same side you know what i mean like even bernie is like a wealthy dude who benefits
from all this stuff you know and like yeah he's become biden's little bitch and uh you know and
so it like it makes me angry you know and that's the thing i wanted i wanted bernie
you know but like the thing is it's it's it's not bernie it's not him it's us you know that's the
thing it's not you know it's not me us not me us yeah you know and i i really think that
people should take that kind of stuff to heart you know like they didn't you know the bernie
bros are just so they they screwed bernie and poor bernie and then it's like no poor us that dude
has health care you know like and he's never gonna not have health care we're the ones who need
the health care you know i think 150 thousand years old had a heart attack and made it through
so like his health care must be doing great i think that's fair i think that's that's that's
perfectly fair and true yeah keep it keep it in perspective i guess yeah yeah i think i'd probably
fall for that trap sometimes i mean we make it we make it all about the individuals so much you
know like you know we get mad at like one one person for you know their stupid shoplifting
comic you know but not at like you know the system that maybe might have drove this character to
shoplift you know what i mean it's easier to target individuals for our simple monkey brains
to wrap around the concept so reality tv people want to see the different face as the president
yeah the what they're gonna do is like not as easy to most people now edit it in again
oh the burp you guys don't keep burps then uh not anymore as of right now they're no longer
included yeah new policy uh what are we talking about we're talking about president oh we're
biden biden biden
we got we've got our soul the soul of america guys yeah back to brunch everybody let's go back
to brunch yes i saw a left tube bread tube uh person called lonely box uh who who made a video
about racism in the uk and i thought that was a pretty good video never heard of them because there's
not a lot of like talking about yeah he's i think it was quite small uh i will grab the link and put
it but i liked it because it's like you know i'm from the uk and there's not a lot of of like i
guess h bomber guy but he's a bit wacky funny oh i love the h bomber guy he's such a sweetie
he's all right he's nice i it's just his his his brand of comedy is a bit loud i like i like
boring videos i like videos that are like yeah no i know what you mean uh my favorite uh
i've left us youtuber is thoughts lime you guys like i love thoughts lime yes i love
thoughts lime i have he's he's so good he's unpretentious that's the thing that is key i
feel like you know i i hate pretentiousness and he's just like down to earth he likes horror movies
he's and then he's nice on top of it you know he's like wants to be like kind i'm into it
i uh uh so uh i uh made slash run sort of this game this discord game called uh endless war
which is in which in which uh people compete for a slime-based currency uh and uh i like
thoughts lime so much that in my in my in my gang i don't know how to explain it in my gang
headquarters in uh in universe i made a a secret room that is called the uh the radicalization
station which was just it's just all of thoughts limes videos uh and i thought that that was pretty
funny and i wish you would notice me uh and uh and play uh uh play slime games with me
thoughts thought slime put uh my shoplifting comic in one of his videos um actually it was
like just a split second i think i may have seen that a split second and i got so excited it was
this video where he was actually apologizing for another video i guess i didn't get to see the
video he apologized for because he took it down but uh basically this video he i guess it was really
mean spirit or something and so he apologized for it but in the video he's all like everyone's jumping
up this person's ass to apologize for this comic which is ridiculous this comic is awesome
and then you know and then went on to apologize for his thing so it's not even one of his
very good videos it's kind of boring just watching him apologize but you know i was like ah he
noticed me for a second yeah ben have you ever reached out to thought slime that's sick as fuck
huh have you ever reached out to thought slime i sent him i sent him an email or wait um
is thought slime a he or thought slime they i forget they and he okay okay yeah oh it's it's
peter coffin it's peter coffin that's they i forget okay um so thought slime i sent thought
slime an email uh because he asks for you know um rent send me the the the the the the eyeball
zone uh thing yeah left his project the eyeball zone i sent him an email thinking that maybe uh
endless war kind of qualifies uh i don't know it does and i perceived no response so either
he didn't or he picks i mean it's it's not really much of a of an overtly leftist anything it's just
a funny slime game video game yeah i thought he would at least think it was cool i am in his um
or i was in his discord but like i didn't really do much in there i just kind of was in there and
was like okay i'm in uh i'm still in there i don't even remember you try to get peter coffin on here
no okay no no uh no i'm talking about thought slime okay all you mentioned the peter coffin for
a second uh no i just i uh peter i just because both of them i don't know they both kind of look
alike i guess and they both go by they and sometimes i forget which one's which uh but not
usually because they're different lol um okay that's so that's that what what else guys
yeah let's let's let's ride we're riding with biden we're riding with biden here i just want to
i can't stress enough how hard i'm right i think uh i think biden's gonna win i think it's
gonna be oh sure yeah yeah he's gonna that seems that seems to be where the wind is blowing
yeah it's it's good it's good it's gonna be a weird you know and it's it's it's kind of funny
too because it's like he's biden's gonna win based on what he's not going to do
they you know like oh he's not going to you know be as bad you know yeah that's what that's what
they do they're all they're all like i don't know i saw i think i saw shon oh i love shon
by the way if we're talking about lefty lefty tutors yes shon is a shon is sick as fuck um
i can never make it through shon's video is too boring for me oh no there that's that's what i like
that's what i like yeah i love videos that suck that's true i agree um uh i think he oh god what
was i talking about he retweeted something that was like um oh it was like a video of like
they're interviewing they're interviewing some a couple of like black women about how they're like
they're not convinced to vote biden and the the headline is like these women aren't convinced
about biden despite all the things trump has done and it's like well those aren't the same thing uh
you know the the it's like well shouldn't shouldn't biden have to do shouldn't what
biden does enter into it in some way you know what one would think yeah it's like that thing
we're like you know i don't know what's like it's like someone will hear me trashing liberals and
they're like yeah uh you know you're a republican right i'm like god no ew gross yeah you know
yeah it's like i hate liberals with all my heart but uh uh i'm not a conservative at all uh there
yeah well you know that's why we we gotta reach across the aisle we gotta reach across the aisle
and bring the far right over based on our shared hatred of liberals that's the thing we can all
agree on um i don't know i don't know if that's i don't think i don't know if i actually believe
that uh huh i don't think people agree with that at all i don't know i don't know if i actually
even agree with that it's probably not it's probably not actually gonna work that well
i mean i'm sure some of them you know like i don't know i wouldn't be surprised if there's
folks out there that like you know they just see like you know like these liberals on the tv and
radio and they're like shut up college boy you know like what's the alternative you know is oh
conservatives you know like yeah like you know what i mean like i know exactly because you know we
don't have like you know like far right discourse is acceptable in the mainstream media but not far
left you know it's like it goes as far bernie is as far as it goes and i might you know in my eyes
he's kind of like you know a centrist leaning to the left you know it's like not really change much
if you're if you're far far right discourse doesn't threaten capitalism whereas far left stuff does
and every establishment media source is pro capitalism so they're not gonna platform that
shit if you're some moron uh watching you're watching television and you're like uh well no
not you don't even i'm not even to say you have to be a moron but if you're just a person watching
television watching the news and you're like boy liberals sure are smug and hypocritical
and suck you know you rightly come to that conclusion and then you're like yeah and then
you're thinking what's the alternative like the visible alternative you know is conservatism uh uh
who who who you know yeah they don't people don't acknowledge that the left is even real and to
a large extent it's not we don't have an organized left in america uh to the extent that they do in
other countries japan has a communist party i want i want that i want that i think it's easy
like in our bubbles to think that we're a bigger deal than you know we really are you know what i
mean like yeah you know but it's sad it's it's and it's there's not very many of us like you know
it's in the grand scheme of things yeah that's true yeah i think i think destiny was talking
about at one point breaking down like oh yeah like there's a ton of like you know super left
people on twitter but twitter is like one percent of the population and like only like a couple percent
of twitter would be like really far left so like you're talking about a fraction of percent of the
american population actually believes these things so you're but you're so insular on twitter it feels
like there's this big movement you know and it's not really there yeah and like but but and the
mainstream media you know it's like we have no history about like labor it's like this you know
label rights you know people don't even know what mayday is about or you know yeah you know or any
of that kind of stuff and uh yeah you know so you know it's i think it's easy to write off these
right wingers is like you know people call them stupid all the time or they call them all bigots
you know and uh you know i'm and a lot of them are that you know a lot of them are just they they
hate trans people that they're a lot of them are obsessively hate trans people for some reason
it's it's kind of weird isn't it have you noticed that like yes they're always talking about us
it's so yes they're very there's there's a certain yeah there's a segment of the population that's
really fixated it's kind of weird you know and they're like they we shouldn't have rights because
they're barely a fraction of the population i'm like well if we're barely a fraction of the
population then why are you so fucking concerned like you know whether we get like the healthcare
or like you know we use the fucking toilet you know jesus i um you ever you ever venture on the
kiwi farms you're jealous you ever venture on the kiwi farms i have a page there uh you know
just for my own mental health i do not look at it because yeah it's like i mean back in the day
like i used to look at it you know um and it just like always made me feel bad or you know
you know and yeah the level of disc you know i the level of discourse there that i have seen
is very it's very weird the tone that like every thread takes the tone is always very like
the it's it's it's it's always like um i don't know it's it's so scoldy it's so
scoldy and coppish and like like i don't know the conclusion that they always seem to come to
about these people that they you know really hate and really want to like say bad things about just
you know for whatever reason the conclusion that seems like they always come to is like oh
this person should have just like stuck to the straight and narrow this person should have like
you know uh uh you know just like maintained his traditional western values uh or whatever
i don't know there's like a really strong like sort of traditionalist like
enforcement's mentality there that like anything that someone anything bad about someone is because
they deviated from like the the the the norm i don't know that's uh that's something i noticed
going on there and i think it's very weird oh yeah hey by the way like you know during that whole
like harassment thing you know like uh when my own community was turning at me when i needed
the most i was getting doxed they those fuckers doxed me based yeah yeah yeah terrible uh
yeah they're they're weirdos it's it's weird the tone there is very strange uh like uh you know
the one thing the kiwi farm is like they can't they keep comparing me you know i don't know if
they do this anymore because i haven't like looked at that page in a while but they keep
comparing me to this other transgender comic artist named sophie labelle who does this um
sophie labelle yeah she does this comic called assigned mail it's it's like this kind of like
cuddle party like oh i know i know assigned mail i know yeah it's just like it's all like uh transphobia
is bad yay you know that kind of stuff you know which is fine you know like you know sign people
yeah but uh you know for some reason that they always compare me to her for some reason like
you know like uh well it's because they're they're really fixated on on that on that aspect of
people and like that's all reducing people down to a label it's stupid it's pretty it's pretty bad
i don't know you know uh i mean i i was familiar with kiwi farms because uh famously i'm a big uh
i'm a big christorian i'm a i'm a big i'm a big time youtube uh sonichu man
the the thread on chris is like particularly bad like the the the thread on on on christine is like
almost like weird and like they can't type or spell and it's like i don't know what's going on there
it's like they're seething it's like literal children are the only ones like in that discussion
anymore or like people who just like can't fucking use a computer correctly i don't understand i do not
understand uh that um yeah and then everywhere else it's just very like hmm you see this person uh
um this this youtuber uh he has you know uh lost subscribers because they uh they didn't uh i don't
know they didn't uh uh get out of there because they're gay or something they didn't they didn't
i don't know whatever they're degenerates they're yeah that's that that's what i was trying to
say this person is degenerate here's here's why that word that word is so weird it's it's they
constantly use it and and like yeah that's what it means is that you deviated from this like
this normal this like normative idea that they're like kind of obsessed with
and like anyone anyone boring yeah i don't know i feel like do you think like kiwi farms comes
i mean i always associate kiwi farms with like 4chan right like like kind of like a similar
sort of crowd of just like people who kind of like take the piss out of like other people online and
like you know like making fun of like deviance i suppose and it feels like yeah 4chan's very much
like an anonymous sort of thing right and so like being anonymous means like blending in and like not
not sticking out or anything and so if you're like really big into anonymity like you would you would
want to pull back people who stand out from the crowd and i feel like maybe that's kind of part
of what it is is like if you're kind of coming from that background that like anybody who like is
deviant goes against what you kind of have self-identified as i definitely wouldn't say taking
the piss out of like these kiwi farms people just pick on small-time trans artists a lot you know like
you know it or like oh my gosh that antoons guy you know like how they went after that you know
like you know and like i saw i saw this thing like antoons was saying that like like this puppy
chan they have all this power and like dude they have like less than 60 000 followers on twitter
you know like your antoons is like antoons has like a million fucking subscribers on youtube
have you have you seen his youtube channel i only vaguely understood this antoons debacle
but like here like he's making a video about me right now wait really yeah someone leaked stuff
from his discord he is gonna he's making a video either with just me in it or about being or something
like that so um antoons videos are so strange like his biggest videos are like the it's like
deathbed scenes of like popular cartoon characters there's like i think his biggest one is like
homer simpson's deathbed and like friend flinstone is there and it's like it's like everyone's just
crying and like i don't understand it at all it's it's really weird i guess it's i guess it's meant
to be funny like you think so i guess it's common in a meta way i guess 129 million views sonic funeral
yeah that's what that's what he does but that's what he did before he decided to be like a
fucking bigot on twitter professionally lol yeah what is with that like all of you know these like
people have like a decent career all of a sudden like get irked by trans people and then that's
like what they become about you know is like yeah they're fucking pussies they're scared of the big
boogie man who's gonna you know femboy eyes them with the femboy ray and like no i don't want to
do any of that i don't want to oh they're taking over everything oh it's just it's hysteria
yeah they don't know anything about anything and then i assume that antoons i assumed that
antoons was just one of the cadre of people who just wants to be another stone toss and we'll just
like you have a little cottage industry that sprung up about like just get trying to like
make a comic that gets retweeted by stone toss and then and then you know a couple thousand at
least a couple thousand people will be like yeah i'll follow this guy because i like what he's saying
um and uh but no he's he's already huge on youtube and he's still up to this weird shit
he's also like super old he's like my age lamal like 40 uh 30 something oh yeah like like me
like me ancients yeah god it hurts
i was born in the 80s too i get it yeah i'm the youngest one here i win i'm
yeah it's a better time we have to go back it it happens uh to everyone man
no that's the thing well i mean like our culture is so not not this not this one here our culture
is so youth obsessed you know it's like you know like it's like once you had 30 you know you turned
on the tv and stuff you're like oh my gosh like all these tv shows and movies are about people
who are younger than me now you know right yeah you never notice it when you you're growing up
but like every protagonist of most things is like from like 15 to 24 25 most cloud
cloud strife is like 18 no cloud strife is in his 20s that's the the one weird exception
wait really no wait no it's it's um he's okay he's 21 okay well squall is like 18 yeah a lot of
protagonist i mean luffy luffy monkey d luffy only 17 at the start that's just like he and he was
considered old like naruto is like 15 or whatever yeah i think he's 13 in the original or i don't
know he's a young lad uh yeah yeah yeah fuck it yeah well you know it's like fun and like our
color we're just so mean to old people too like all the time like you know it's it's uh old people's
opinions don't matter we shove them into homes we just you know wait for them to die you know
in fairness though boomers are the worst generation uh and deserve it well you know i listen you know
i feel like you know boomers they grew up with a lot of lead they you know i yeah yeah i know
it's the lead to a certain extent they totally is the lead like you know like they have like
no empathy they're they're quick to like be angry at at weird shit for no reason you know i i honestly
feel bad for a lot of these boomers you know they they don't know what's happening and it's not you
know i like yeah i would feel bad for them if they weren't like actively ruining everything for the
rest yeah that's i know i'm just talking about well you know you know moms and stuff like that i'm
not talking about like you know people's power you know i think that's yeah you know like lady on
the street you know that is like you know not the action they're voting it's the lead it's the lead
the lead is voting for us now the lead wants uh you know the lead wants the wall and it will
have it by any means necessary uh made of lead
you know like my mom is just like it's so hard to get things through her skull you know i have to
tell her over and over again and like she it's like it just does not understand it like anything
you know maybe my mom's just an idiot but um yeah and it's like and i'm just like you know
but really i think it's like she ate lead chips as a kid you know what like yeah i'll do it uh what
was that uh it was just like actually like eight lead chips no oh you know like i don't know because
like back in the day you know paint on the walls was made out of lead and it would chip off and
children would eat it you know and like all the gas was leaded you know like when my mom was a baby
you know i think i don't know and see yeah it's not my fault it's not my fault for that i have
those daddy issues you mentioned it's the lead it's the lead that did it you know that's the
lead that made uh my dad get me uh put me on fucking uh uh adhd and i punched the hole in the
wall it was the lead all along you know it's not it's not me anti-lead we were taking an anti-lead
stance on this podcast now we're pro-circumcision and anti-lead um
wait no we were arguing about that before the last time i i think i came off as being a little
i mean i was doing it on purpose i all i all i wanted to say about the circumcision thing was
that i'm open to being convinced that maybe it's good uh uh not not that i not that i actively
think yes it's good we should do it just that i am available to be persuaded by evidence that
suggests that it is you know how dare you it's not it's not it's not my default my default
position is not we should definitely be circumcising always abc always be circumcising and uh and
you know you got you'll need to you'll need to make a compelling argument uh otherwise to change
my mind it's not like you guys you guys had a podcast about circumcising we got we talked about
last it was yeah based on a voicemail i think right at the end of the discussion about it
yeah um speaking of voicemails i mean we've been going we've been going for two and a half hours
now uh i don't know do you guys i'm sorry was i interested enough that i do okay here i well
i almost feel bad saying it because like i feel like we could keep going uh uh and and yet and yet
the podcast must conclude
eventually i mean we've had long episodes before it's fine and you can also like cut out stuff
you know because there is points oh no no no no no no no no no that's good content that's good
content right there that's not we don't we don't pay we don't pay our editor that much i mean go on
this is a shoestring operation hmm you hear that alia czar get fucked
like honestly this is fun i like like i'm just excited that i get to talk with other people
um this quarantine is naming nuts yeah because you know i'm a high-risk person i had a kidney
transplant you know oh shit oh i had so many bad things happen to me in my life it's uh you
know i can probably write a book about that um you know and so yeah it does suck you know but
whatever i'm it's made me home yeah but yeah so i'm on these uh anti-rejection medications
which lowers my immune system so basically if i get covid you know i also like struggle with
hypertension so if i get the covid there's like a 40 chance that i'm toast oh jesus christ okay yikes
yeah so i don't even hard car lockdown yeah i don't even go to the grocery store i have you
know people bring me the groceries yeah and you know it sucks i'm going crazy i hear i think
if it's driving me bonkers like that's why like you know i mean i i was pretty much i was pretty i
was a little bit of a hermit even before lockdown and lockdown has made me think like i need to like
once when when normal comes back i should probably like take better advantage of it
and like actually go out and do more things than i used to even you know because like now now i have
to do it and it's like uh you know maybe this isn't uh maybe this isn't the way to live uh yeah it's
not that great um i i i also love just having this podcast and then the streams we do just
it's just nice to talk to people about stuff every every week i'm a people person i need people
i like going out and doing you know i need my alone time too you know like but i just i like
people a whole heckin lot and um yeah and uh so this has been really difficult for me my partner
on the other hand she's like thriving you know she's like has you know you know she's more of an
introvert um you know but it's like you know i'm all itchy and like bouncing around and you know
and she's just like chill i'm i think i'm pretty good i'm pretty good with isolation but you know
enough enough so i'm probably doing better than a lot of people but i i i'm also i'm also pretty
over it uh yeah you know this covered thing and not a big fan honestly uh i could take it to leave
it i guess i thought hey you know it sucks too it's like you know this might not be the first
this might just be the first of uh a few pandemics that we get in the next two decades
yeah it sucks good to think about i know blows but hopefully hopefully not you know
you know and hopefully this thing mutates and hopefully it mutates and it's not as deadly
or you know the vaccine is good or something right right yeah i i feel like optimistically
by the middle of next year there'd be a vaccine out and we'd finally start actually dealing with it
the um i i don't know between the fastest it's gonna be the fastest time it ever took to create
a new vaccine was four years fastest hey yes i think it was malaria no not really i don't remember
there's a lot of new vaccine technology you know where they like just type shit into a computer
it spits out the vaccine why haven't they done that that's um suspicious
i you know i'm simplifying it because i'm an idiot you know i don't really know how
it's probably much more complicated than that mumps it was mumps was the fastest vaccine ever
developed and it took four years in 1967 well yes a while ago i think i can definitely do it first
to now well i mean who knows right well that i guess i guess we'll find out based on all of the
things i've heard from all of the experts saying they're projected um thoughts um it's it's something
that could happen within one or two years so i'm pretty confident that that will be the timescale
if such a thing happens at all like how do they know maybe they are bullshitting but this is the
novel coronavirus it's a new virus like like i don't know maybe they know something i don't
but like how would you how would you be able to be like oh yeah i think this new disease that has
never been researched before i think the timescale for making a vaccine for that should be about uh
like this how would you begin to answer that i think they definitely know more than you do about it
but no you know i don't think so actually it sounds okay all right point taken point taken
experts are really boring yeah is that hard to talk to because they they study all the time they
don't know how to speak in front of cameras on the news i thought you liked boring videos uh i do
but like it's it's it's hard for people to agree and like like really get into something an expert
says because an expert is an expert at their thing and not at speaking yeah i agree that i see people
on my timeline kind of afraid of the vaccine even though they're not like those anti-vaxxer types
you know like afraid of rushing out the vaccine and i would be nervous i would be nervous to take
a vaccine that's like yeah you know like that was new and that hadn't been like tested that much
they would have to have like loads of volunteers be like okay we have something we can try anyone
want to try it and people will be like oh please me and then yes and then they would try it a bunch
and after a few weeks or months we'd we'd have more of an understanding whether it works or not
i feel like what kamala harris said during the the vice president debate was also not a great
thing either she was saying like oh it comes out during a trump presidency i won't take it it's just
oh my god why would you say things like that yeah that was like what does that have to do with it
because she was saying that like if if dr fouching everybody clears it but if it comes out during
a trump administration and trump's the one pushing it i don't want to take it and it's just like weird
like weird trump doesn't have the authority to like clear a fucking you know like he's not going
to be like i did the trump vaccine and i developed it myself but it's just the trump vaccine you know
uh uh he just he just like puts his like fucking name on regeneron or something and
starts hawking it or whatever but like a legitimate vaccine like it's not trump's not the one doing
it so like putting that in people's minds it definitely makes a part it makes a vaccine a
partisan issue which is like not a good idea yeah i was about to say that stupid culture were
bullshit you know that needs to die it's like the uh like the stimulus package like i don't know
like i guess i guess they think that like getting the stimulus package out now like people would
think trump did it but like does anyone think that there wouldn't be a stimulus package under
like biden like does that does anyone really think that like trump is the one doing that and
that if it wouldn't happen without him you know what i mean it just seems like no it's congress
is doing that am i right yeah i'm right yeah yeah of course you're right you know yeah okay hell yeah
you know it's it's the culture war thing you know it's like yeah you know it's either bad or good
i don't remember kamala saying that that's what seems like a really bizarre statement
i must have missed it i was like what the isn't she like a cop or something too
yeah she's the the the da like the oh god i don't know she was a da somewhere and yeah she uh you
know she did some uh uh she kept some uh some people in jail uh for no reason uh yeah she
prosecuted a bunch of uh you know people probably shouldn't have gone to jail but they did because
the prison industrial complex you know needs more slaves haha yeah fuck yeah uh so yeah she's a little
bit of a cop a little bit of a cop that shit sucks big big cop big time cop no she's awful she's
terrible uh but i mean you know i guess mike pence makes her look good i guess so you know yay yay
biden biden biden biden uh well i know about pence is that he's some kind of like fucking like
idiot like local like news jockey or like like radio host or something and like that was his thing
for a while really that's yeah yeah he was it's funny because like he seems to have like no
personality whatsoever well he just seems like to be in the back yeah behind the scenes doing
whatever he's like the anti-trump you know i can't i can't even picture what his voice sounds like i
don't even know what he sounds like i don't know i don't i don't think i've ever seen him talk i
miss the i miss the kamala debate so i'll maybe i'll maybe i'll go the rest of my life never
knowing what he sounds like that would be nice that'd be pretty good actually oh it's me mike
pence hello this is what i sound like that's it that's what it was uh yeah he ran like a he ran
some kind of radio show for a while i think uh i don't remember i learned i learned this from um
the renegade renegade cut did a video about him oh i love renegade cut that guy that guy's awesome
he's good i have not watched a lot of his recent i went on i went down a renegade cut rabbit hole
for a while and then i i'll do this like i'll watch it all of one guy's thing for a while and
then i'll like be like okay done and then i'll like find something else and then like i will
forget to watch their new stuff uh do that all do this all the time just just hop from channel to
channel binge it all and then i'm like well what next where do i go from here yeah yeah you guys
have any good uh you know youtube things that i should watch
um i've just been uh yeah yeah who do you guys play i've just been watching fucking uh i like
watching really long speed runs of like final fantasy games uh i was watching uh i still haven't
finished actually a final fantasy 10 speed run is eight hours long i think i got about
two hours to go on that one uh who the hell yeah i like uh informational videos i've been
like going through the recommendations and there's v-source there and i've been like yeah
v-source so just watch loads of v-source videos before i go to bed um i still don't understand
the banach tarq ski park paradox but one of these days i'll watch that video and i'll get it
that's that's all i know uh i mean i've been watching pokemon challenges i mentioned him
already but i've been watching his videos lately uh oh my man weird explorer weird explorer is a
is a hidden gem about a guy who uh just wants to try every fruit in the world uh he just eats
weird fruits i see it's really cool i see oh a year ago he uploaded this one oh he's eating the
gack fruit um that's here look you want you want to see what the gack fruit looks like uh look like
the nickelodeon on the inside hopefully there it is oh yeah nice there's my man uh thumbnail
what is that face he's making doesn't look very excited yeah he looked very sad
he he posted a video not too long ago where he he he he wanted to try the cloudberry um but he
didn't just like get one he like went on like a trip to um i scanned an avia and like went like
foraging in the woods to like find one find one like ripe off the the bush or whatever uh it was
great yeah uh and you know what he said it tasted pretty good so that was a good video who am i to
disagree are all of his videos like he just puts in his mouth he says that's pretty good most of his
videos are just him kind of he'll just kind of hold the fruit and like shake it talk about like
where where it comes from talk about like you know how it's generally eaten by whoever eats it or if
it's eaten anywhere yeah and then he'll like yeah he'll just cut into it and eat it and like be like
taste uh bad um taste like a mud uh taste like a shit uh subscribe there is a way to do that but
that's that's the gist i've been watching this guy named brutal moose i think his name is brutal
moose he i am familiar with that name yeah he he uh does the thing called brutal foods and he just
like eats uh tv dinners and talks about how disgusting they are and funny sound effects
amazing i are they that bad i don't know i'm looking at some of these thumbnails and like
that doesn't look hungry man dinner doesn't look too bad you know i mean that's so i think i could
stomach it i guess yeah there's lots of salt in those things you should not eat them yeah
especially if you're especially if you're born in the 80s you know because you're old
it's true no you know i'm really wrong i'm really thinking about like what youtube stuff i get
excited for nowadays and i don't think there's anything left really that's what i'm saying like
i don't have anything every time i used to be so excited for like jon tron for example um or you
know i had a list of like i love these creatives and now i'm just like uh jon tron didn't he do
the right rain grip too didn't he like trans people i think he got led down led down the wrong path
i feel like he said he said some pretty fucked up shit on a stream with destiny and he has never
apologized or taken it back uh so it's a little like he quote unquote he clarified it but like
he didn't understand did not do like anything for me it didn't really like it's clear that he
still hasn't looked into the things that people are calling him out about and you just say guys
i'm not a white nationalist i'm i'm not that's basically what it was that that's pretty much
all he said but he didn't explain like he didn't explain like how he changed his mind or anything
or like how he actually in hindsight i don't agree with the things that i said no it was terrible
it was a terrible apology yeah so like public apologies are always so terrible you know when
people apologize to public it's just so it's cringy every single time i i hate them yeah yeah i mean
it wasn't the like the stereotype that you might imagine of him like being like with the sad piano
music and him like pretending to cry he like walks in from off camera sits down guys it's time to
be past that side yeah you know who'd had a you know who had a good had a good public apology though
who yeah you know i guess uh my man my man my man pro jared pro jared uh had a great public
apology uh and pro jared did nothing wrong and i i stand oh the yeah yeah that was a pretty crazy
video wait what what did everyone hate his guts for oh man i have a hard time okay with all the
internet drama well this was i mean that was a while ago but there was a lot there was um okay well he
got he he got divorced from his wife and at the same time some people accused him of uh of uh
basically pedophilia and uh he and he he he made it you know he basically like disappeared
and like people were really it made me really mad because people like treated these two things
is like the same like people were angry about him and like they would talk about like oh how he was
like his his ex-wife would like say all these terrible things about him and like oh he was
such a bad husband and stuff and they would say that in the same breath as they're like oh yeah and
he was also a child groomer and it's like those are not those are not even comparable um but then
you know he disappeared from the internet for a while and then he came back with with a big video
when he's like with a big receipt he didn't yeah he didn't he didn't talk about um the divorce at all
in that video but he just said like um yeah so like here's why you know here's why these allegations
are false and like he made a pretty good you know a pretty solid case for it and it was like yeah okay
good I just uh I just really hate his ex-wife uh uh so you know I was glad I was glad that
he made a comeback just uh because you know I think it would be funny if she had a bad time
that's what I think amazing cool these these public personalities on the internet and
all the callouts and accusations it's it's so weird like it's uh yeah you know like I have
a hard time wrapping my head around all this you know like I mean this because cloud is currency so
you know you gotta you gotta jockey you gotta try and maneuver you know you gotta like take down
someone so you can get their cloud you know or whatever if you're if you're the guy who like
owned someone hard enough then uh you know like like uh you can oh yeah you can be you can be the guy
who canceled some other some other big dude you know and that's and that's that's cloud in itself
you know I have zero interest in like calling out or trying to cancel like even people who've
wanted me you know like I you know like earlier we're talking about like how people in my own
community treat me like garbage you know like I I forgive them all you know like I you know I
I'm a very forgiving person you know like I get it you know there's been times
where like someone whispered in my ear like hey that person actually really sucks because of reasons
and I'm like yeah yeah they suck you know and uh you know like it makes me wonder like how often
like do people just get totally reamed that like just don't deserve it you know
yeah I think it's it's quite often but it's it's hard to tell and and getting all of the information
necessary to know is sometimes such an ordeal that I don't even want to get into like I'll just
assume everything everything is wrong and nothing is real because I don't want to have to form an
opinion on whether the ex youtuber did or didn't do the things that they said or have been told
they're doing by this other youtuber it's like everyone's stupid I don't want to I don't like it
yeah like recently there is that uh that transgender woman who like I guess she like hooked up a
controller to or like you know a vibrator or something like that right you know and um
um you know she had the the the vibrator you know like well here the story was is that like
you know that she was masturbating with children on uh let's play you know that was like the info
that I got yeah right you know I'm like what the fuck is this and I looked into it and like
apparently she just like she uh hooked up this controller to a vibrator right and then had the
vibrator like laying on her chest and like basically uh I forget which game it was but uh you know
every time she like bumped into a character the vibrator would vibrate on her chest you know
and then like then she realized um like oh this might be weird and then she like disconnected it
right and then it turned into this huge thing where like you know I got people in my DM saying
it's all like you follow her you gotta unfollow her she's masturbating you know on this video
came and I'm like holy shit and you know and like all it took was 30 seconds of research to like
you know realize that what they were saying was yeah yeah blown out of proportion it just
wasn't true you know she wasn't masturbating you know um it's like it's like the thing with with
progerid was like even though the bigger allegations were false there's still a bit of
iffyness with him like having a weird um like alter ego sexy tumblr so it's not completely clean
but at the same time it's not too bad either it's it's just you know I mean it's not yeah it's it's
expanded into it's not what people were saying ever yeah uh and it's very very very very very
frustrating all your folks here seem very like forgetting and open you know like in my like
online circles it's like fuck all of these people 100% you know it's um god no it's exhausting
living like that yeah I mean and honestly is uh you know like I I have a hard time I mean there
are there are people who I think like fuck them forever about uh but you know but but not people
you've heard secondary information about right no right there's people who are like scoring you
in real life and you're just like you know what I'm done dealing with that person but when it's
like secondhand information from someone online who you're never going to have an actual interaction
with it's like why waste all the time and energy like hating on that person you know you could just
kind of like acknowledge it but like okay that happened and just move on it doesn't have to become
this huge fucking ordeal and it just seems like unhealthy to have that kind of standard anyway
because like I don't know eventually like if we keep like making this purity test
more and more stringent eventually you're not going to pass it anymore and then you've
helped create an environment where everyone's going to turn on you and it's just like I'd
rather like let people have room to learn and grow and get better and like make mistakes
yeah you know and it's another thing that you know the recently someone's in my DM saying you
got on follow this artist they they draw you know child porn I'm like holy shit you know I'm like
you know and this that's that's a big deal you know and then I'm like well you know
I asked the person where it's the evidence for this and like the evidence was literally
a drawing of Birdo or Yoshi from Mario but their butthole was showing you know
oh what that's funny you know and that's child porn
okay it was a youthful Yoshi why because like is Yoshi canonically like young or something I don't
know yeah maybe that's what it was but I'm just like you know and like and that's like a big deal
like because she's only 17 according to the according to the guidebook with uh with a super
from a super nintendo this is fucked up you know and like you had Yoshi in the game he's only 10
minutes old yeah yeah oh shit that's true that's true you know baby and it's it's it's like but
this stuff pops up like constantly you know and like it's like it's gotten to the point where it's
just like I don't know what to believe about people anymore you know it's yeah no I when I see um
yeah I don't think much of it when I see like if I hear that like you know someone you know did
something like I really need to see like evidence I need you know if someone is doing something wrong
I'm not it's not enough to just hear it I I have to see it like that's the only that's the only way
I kind of think that's probably how it should be yeah yeah yeah yeah um I mean I think probably
things would be better uh if everybody uh did that I know I don't know you know they on social
media there's like a lot of kids there's like a lot of there's cloud chasers there's like young
kids who are stupid and there's you know yeah that's like another the kids like they're uh they're
super concerned about zoophilia have you noticed that like you see a bunch of teenagers and they're
all super concerned and like is this a problem or like people fucking animals is that a thing
that's a problem right now in our society they've discovered not safe for work are for the first
time and they're shaking they're literally shaking that's all it is is it just that they if they want
is it just that they want to shame furries and like call them like uh you know perverts or whatever
and like is that what's going on there I have no idea but I feel like it's the thing that
that just keeps cropping up because you know young people come onto the internet all the time
and they discover the internet um for the first time and they learn all these things and then
they get mad about certain things and it's just sort of it's a it's a wave it just comes and goes
I don't know I don't I don't pay too much attention to a lot of the outrage because I know a lot of
it is is very young people coming to terms with some strange things about the internet that
aren't really that big of a problem do you guys see that tweet the other day it was like it blew
up it was like uh liking petite women is rooted in pedophilia though that was a great that was a
another great take from the twitter uh take machine yeah um
I saw a lot of really I saw a lot of really funny responses to it I wish I could remember
them off off the top of my head but whatever it was big big shit show that that is disgusting
and bad you know and like but some of these like accusations are huge like big crimes you know like
like pedophilia is disgusting you know like you don't do that to children you know and like to
just like they're throwing it around like it's confetti you know and uh they gotta be the most
outlandish they gotta have the biggest headline to get the most twitter likes in on twitter it's
all about being extreme like we were saying oh yeah I mean it's a it's a serious accusation and it's a
really easy it's just a really easy way I don't know it's a it's really easy way to just like
spread something bad about something if you just want to destroy them that's like the the simplest
way to do it um you know I don't think we got to talk about it but uh you know like um so I
reshared that shoplifting comic right you know and like yeah I guess some people couldn't handle that
I had the confidence to do that and uh you know they dug up that seven-year-old comic of mine
you know and uh and you know now that I think about it I think the only place they could find
that comic is on kiwi farms so I'm pretty sure kiwi farms person what were you saying what was the
old one what was the old the old comic so like this I it was a comic I made you know oh my god so
like it was like back in 2013 I was like super sjw back then you know um you know because like
you know like I because like you know I transitioned in them you know you know started
transitioning the mid-2000s and you know family and friends treated me like shit I got like
super sick of it then I kind of discovered you know the social justice thing and I you know
you know ran with it hard you know and um you know well because it was super empowering to me like
as a you know trans person that like has been sucked over you know uh and so like you know
my old comics were all about that kind of stuff you know like how how shitty transphobia is and
stuff and uh so this comic that you know that I that one of my friends helped me make right
you know because like especially you know because like all the canceling stuff that was a thing back
then too you know I was super paranoid to like talk about anything that wasn't inside my own exact
experience so like I got my you know this person I'm still friends with to this day I actually
did a social distance hangout with yesterday honestly um you know we uh you know just made
this comic about uh trans guys you know struggling with uh you know machismo culture and like the
pressure you know to be like you know super masculine and kind of shitty you know kind of
like you know and like you know as a trans you know femme like I kind of related to that but like
on the opposite end you know like people tell me I have to like wear you know high heels all the
time and put on makeup every day you know it's like you know but I you know um so like I basically
you know me and my friend we made this comic about like just a trans guy struggling with um
you know and like basically the narrative that uh these kids came up with was that like I hate
trans men because I think that like they're oh embracing toxic masculinity you know and uh but
like that's the thing that's such an easy like I don't know it's just like a lazy like you know
like hey if I look at this thing and I don't engage with it and I don't like think about it
I don't know it's just I can spin this they say I can spin this yeah yeah such a lazy spin
but but you know and that's the thing like I you know but but that's the thing it caught fire
and like thousands and thousands of people saw it right and then like the person got pressure to
apologize and one of the people who shared it also you know apologize and like a dozen people
saw the apology but now like you know I'm still getting dm this like from people being like you
hate you know trans men and like you know or like you know like you know like something uh some of
the replies under a comic of mine recently it's like why do you hate trans men you know and it's
and it's like this thing and it takes on a life of its own and like even no matter how ridiculous
it is it's like you know you get stained with that and it sticks it sticks to you it's and it sucks
I I have to wait hold on one second I gotta I gotta end the craig recording and start a new one
let me do that right now it's okay okay we're good we're good okay um
it I mean it reminds me of like the buck angel thing on contra points right and how everyone
said that like oh it's like she is you know has this like this guy on this kind of who said like
transphobic things and then there was the the the the whole um I don't know there's such a fucking
kerfuffle like every time contra points does anything yeah yeah it's it's it's that that thing
of of the popularity getting people more ready and willing to try and take them down
contra points is huge so it's like oh wouldn't it be great if she fell
from such a great height all of my online social circles hate her guts 100% you know I
I can't understand what I mean can I ask why well I mean the narrative is that she is
quote truce gum and she hates non-binary people uh that's what people say yeah okay and um
you know like I'm gonna say I'm like I do not stand contra points I don't I don't like I'm not I'm
I'm not a huge fan I I mean like I I've seen all of her videos you know like what one of them drying
and stuff they just autoplaying stuff like that you know I like a lot of the stuff that she says that
is good like it is just old news to me and then you know I you know for you know and it's like
for me let's um you know I don't hate her guts you know I think like the worst accusations against
her uh like are aren't true like I don't think she hates non-binary people I'm a non-binary person
I I you know I if all there are non-binary people think she sucks like that's their thing and
they're completely you know they could uh I mean I uh I mean I understand how some of the things she's
I understand why she's rubbed people the wrong way but like I mean I I don't know it's a and I've
seen people say oh yeah she hates non-binary she's a true scum I mean she has said in response to that
like no I'm not like that's not what I think and like has explained what she does believe so like if
you claim that you're basically just saying that like she's just lying and like I don't believe
that she's I don't believe that she's like making these videos and just like pretending to believe
things that she doesn't I really don't yeah that's she's just willing to to entertain her own um like
thoughts of because I watched her beauty video not too long ago and she goes into like um you know
asking the question of like why would I go to such lengths to you know get surgery to change the
shape of my skull and all this stuff and it involved like talking points and and discussions like
like a like a genuine introspective discussion about like things that could be labeled as
true scummy thoughts but like it's it's what she does is to like invite the discussion which is
why she's so popular because she through asking these questions and then discussing them openly
has reached so many more people than she would have otherwise so like her personal beliefs
like just because you're you're you're willing to entertain ideas and talk about them in a video
doesn't mean that you necessarily believe them and she's you know she's explained what our actual
beliefs are so it's like they just they just they're just mad you know it's for me it's like
obviously there's things to critique about her you know but you know and but there's this thing
that the part that people ignore right is that I think that trans women especially there's something
about us that people they just we they they you know and this I'm talking about other trans people
you know like they just jump up our asses big time you know and it's like you know like if
it was anyone else saying the same things you know like sure get the criticism that you deserve but
you know like you know but the way like people talk about like these you know not just contrabot
tons of people like it's like all this bad faith that like you know they're like like I remember
when Chelsea Manning right do you remember when Chelsea Manning went to that like alt right ball
or whatever uh you know maybe she like crashed this like party of full of like right wingers right
and like everyone on my feed was like like fuck her and I'm like oh my god you know she's like
she's a fucking hero what are you talking about you know like yeah you know and
it's like it's cop it's cop behavior it's very much like oh you shouldn't you shouldn't do that
you shouldn't say that you shouldn't uh it's very very uh uh uh just very much like please
please follow my script I guess yeah kind of uh but yeah my about behavior I think you know trans
women are getting held much higher standard than everyone else you know yeah yeah I think uh
let's probably agree with that I see I see that kind of you know and like that's you know and like
I wouldn't be surprised if like someone listened to this and then like you know took it out of
context and they're like you know like oh now Mallory's uh you know I see the term contra points
apologist unironically used you know you know and it's yeah it's just like this is just a person
you know like yeah you know and it's like does she deserve to be as popular as she is I don't know
probably not no you know like yeah like yeah you know she's not seeing anything very new
you know um sure you know like I think I think the reason why she got so popular is because like
her videos look cool and they got the cool music and stuff like that you know what I mean
yeah maybe no for sure for sure it definitely had a part to play although at the very beginning I was
turned off by how extremely feminine it was I was like that's silly but I really got into it afterwards
um but you know it's like but then people get obsessed with like you know with like other
people get to be wrong and then they forget about it right you know but when a trans woman is seen
as wrong it's like you know like people obsess and obsess and obsess you know um I like I used to
belong to this like group filled with trans women on facebook right you know and there is this one
person in there who got you know popular and but this person was an asshole right you know they
treated they treated people unfairly they were smug they were exclusionary you know they pissed off
a lot of people in the group right you know kind of like you know contra points you know by saying
like being a jackass like contra points you know contra points is jackass sometimes you know I think
like you know what I mean and uh yeah I think so and you know it's like
you know other people get to be jackasses and like it's kind of forgiven or forgotten about
you know but like you know this this person in this group you know and like this is like not a huge
clout thing you know they don't make videos or anything you know people to this day are still
obsessed with this person being an ass this trans woman being an asshole like people made
separate facebook groups based around talking shit about this trans woman you know who is like
you know and it's like weird like people just get you know and you see it like the kiwi farms
like all the so many people in there are trans women you know that you know get shit on yeah you
know and uh and we do you know it's like not even um you know it's not just the chuds it's our own
community oftentimes other trans women you know and uh it's you know like the world doesn't like us
very much you know and I think in turn you know like it makes us not like ourselves and each other
and it's a big problem you know um damn yeah it's I I haven't felt that quite as much um
I I don't put on a voice but I am trans myself haha um uh I haven't tried I haven't tried changing
my voice to I haven't really tried presenting yet quite new but um oh you're new well congratulations
on all of that and coming out and stuff hey good for you thank you yeah let's yeah yeah no it wasn't
for the applause I know I mean it's not you think oh you want to like give once a middle you know no
when I first transitioned you know this is like you know I started in the mid-late
2000s when I you know and like it was before the the tipping point right and like oh like I remember
the time magazine trans tipping point from 2013 or 14 no so I mean okay well basically uh the time
magazine came out with an article about like you know the trans tipping point about how like
we're like you know we're visible now basically you know we like in popular culture that was
basically the whole thing you know and so like back then I had no idea how just disliked we were
in general you know and there's like tons of reasons why people dislike us you know like
you know name you know there's it's a whole whole thing you know but I was like naive to all that
right you know um I was just super excited that like I'm like oh my god I get to be myself now
you know and like this is a good thing for me personally and like it's making me a better person
you know and so like it kind of came as a shock to me that like you know all of a sudden
you know like I wasn't given the benefit of the doubt that I used to get you know
like in the workplace my work got critiqued you know I I went from employee of the month
to you know like uh getting breathed down my neck all the time that's really nice though yeah you
know and it's like it's it's so subtle it's hard to talk about you know especially in public
because like a lot of this stuff is subtle right you can't like you can't like point to like one
thing and be like that's it yeah you know it's like people get annoyed with us a lot easier
you know that's like part of it it's like you know it's just subtle and like even like you know
someone was you know someone who uh I saw on twitter just like uh like a month ago like someone was
making a joke right about how trans women are annoying you know and like they were trying to
be ironic making fun of how people hate trans women and then like the whole like thread was like
other trans women be like yeah we're fucking annoying I get why people hate us and it's just
like oh my god unfortunate you know and I mean there's a lot of like there's a lot of insecurity
about it and you I don't know and well I'm I think it's so when it comes to you know like
you know like uh people who are in the public sphere you know um I that that is more easily
annoyed thing gets you know amplified a lot you know and you know so when someone like
country points comes around and says some jackass things it like you know people latch onto it and
they don't let go you know and um yeah you know or like you know it's like you know uh
Mallory hates trans men now and they won't let go you know um and it's it's yeah I don't know I
I haven't yeah I was gonna say that I hadn't experienced a lot of that towards me although
I'm thinking about it I have gotten ever so slightly more like shitty twitter replies
um since coming out but mostly positive and it's I guess I'm I'm thankful that I'm such a small
like internet figure that it doesn't affect me quite as much like if I were to get big I could
I could see it like oh being a bad thing absolutely yeah especially you know like you know just the
stuff that we were talking here today you know it's like you gave projair the benefit of doubt or
I forgot who was doing that earlier but like you know just like giving you know these youtubers the
benefit of the doubt is enough to get like your ass reamed on uh you know twitter you know and um
you know and like what you're you know like when I get some in the benefit of the doubt it's it's
not like I'm not trying to put them on a pedestal or anything I'm just like trying to be a good person
you know and like you're trying to be a human being yeah you know it's because like if you think
about all of this all of the the drama and the things at the end of the day it is people
who have opinions about other people and other people getting extremely frustrated about that
it's strange and unnatural social behavior that doesn't happen in real life like you don't
it's impossible to get mad at someone that you don't really know personally
about what they think about someone else except on the internet where it happens all the time
yeah such a strange like it you can easily not do that ever but yeah you don't fall into things
like that and my thing personally is this like I rather give a piece of garbage you know the
benefit of the doubt and another chance and another chance and another chance than like you know
accidentally like condemning and maybe even like you know exiling and just screwing over a person
who has like is a decent person who has you know good in their heart you know it's like
you know because that's what happens you know like you know I lost a community because I made a
character shoplift you know in my comic and now like still so ridiculous it's like and that that's
the tipping point for some people that's enough you know and like and it's made me afraid to
like engage with like other artists you know like uh you know because it's like oh do you think I'm
a piece of shit or not I have no idea you know um and it sucks because I think you're cool well thank
you but uh you know what I mean but like I'm a person with needs and and desires and flaws and
you know and um you know like I need community you know and uh like it's uh you know especially
during quarantine like so much of our social has been uh constrained to the internet you know and
but like the way we treat each other on the internet is fucking awful you know and I don't
think enough people are talking about it and uh you know like you know like I think it's gonna
take a lot of work to stop it you know because uh you know like we have to change the way that we
think about things you know it's a complicated uh puzzle and and and it's also like something that is
it it would require so much mental and physical energy uh that a single person cannot figure it
out on their own they've got their own life to live and so like the way it gets sorted is
it's kind of like even if you think of how to do it how do you make it happen is another thing
you know you need to dedicate your life to it and it's like I don't want to dedicate my life
to cleaning up the internet I didn't break anything I didn't make this mess yeah you know I just exist
yeah exactly you know and I think you know like I think we touched a lot of on a lot of the things
that are causing you know like that cloud stuff you know the numbers are in our face and everyone
wants more numbers you know or you know they're mad that like oh this other person is popular not me
you know or like they're mad that like you know there's this like disagreement and you know like
you know I have no doubt in my mind if certain people listen to this podcast later like we'll
just like want to cut me off because like I'm I gave Natalie the benefit of the doubt you know
even though I said I'm not even like a fan or anything you know but I gave her the benefit
of the doubt so I'm done you know yeah and I mean I can imagine that even if like they they listen to
that the fact that you're on a podcast where we uh like I personally like Natalie and so like
association like oh how could you be in a podcast with give and take who likes Natalie
they'd always find a way to make it the bad thing that you did yeah doesn't matter how
many times you say you know qualified like I'm just saying I'm just saying no they just want to hate
and the thing is and then but then you go and they turn around it's like no this thing that
we're complaining about does not even exist you know like it's it's so fucking bizarre and uh
you know I I uh and so that's why I'm the Joker now I don't care you know I've I've
I've transitioned to the Joker uh my pronouns are now honk and uh and giggles you know that those
are you know like you know it's you know so I see why like people get cynical about this
and then like they turn around and they're like well fuck all y'all you know like um
you know it's uh yeah it it stinks and I and I and I I want I want something to be done about it
you know like because uh you know we're looking down the barrel of a really shitty future and
we need each other you know especially trans people trans people we you know like you know
because like the larger left they're you know like they're sick of us you know um you know
we need each other you know uh and uh like like saying that you know like like this one person
aids bisexual people uh you know and it's you know and that's another thing too you know I have like
all my content creator friends like they all of them unanimously you know like anyone listening
to this like you know everyone is afraid of you know like this thing happening to them also you
know like having their own community come after them and rip them apart and take away you know what
little like you know like uh you know um you know because like people make you know uh you know
some of their income is based on you know the content they create you know and that could go bye
bye like that you know um if you know you say if you say some jackass stuff and the apology
isn't good enough you know yeah I don't know I feel like to to to worry so much about the
possibility of it happening is it's it's almost part of the problem because if if you know like
you're saying like people stopped associating with you now that you're cancelled if they
didn't stop associating with you and if that wasn't a thing then cancel culture wouldn't feel
like it has any weight anyway and then you would still you know people would stand by things rather
than hype like angry hype which is what it feels like yeah you know sort of snowballs out of control
and people don't really they don't really take the time to like think about what it what it all
spawned from they're just like oh I don't want to get hurt I'm just gonna go with whatever everyone
else is saying yeah yeah exactly you know and that's the thing you know like I don't think I'm
entitled to an audience or anything you know I never wanted to be popular I just wanted to be part
of the fucking group you know what I mean and um like uh you know but this like weird demonization
of individuals in our in our groups that that you know barely did anything wrong or was just
being kind of a jackass you know um it's it sucks and I don't like it especially you know
because it keeps happening to me over and over again you know right uh well I mean we live in
hell so you know I you know and part of I invite some of it too because like I said you know I'm
way too genuine and vulnerable on the internet which I probably shouldn't do but I can't help it
because like I you know I had a lot of bad things happen to me in my life and I just you know I'm like
you know I just don't care anymore and I just like I'm sick of like feeling ashamed of like
you know my background and stuff so I have to talk about it yeah but you know probably
pales in comparison to when we all got called ugly on Twitter today uh so
oh ugly did you guys did you guys see the the the tweet that I made or it was a YouTube comment
what on on the on the Jennifer Diane writes lecture someone left a comment that said
nearly everyone in that room is grotesque and not lucky with the opposite sex
yet people take them seriously internet is very strange
wow okay
grotesque all right no I'm none of you are grotesque
and not lucky with the opposite sex so there you go two things you really shouldn't be
if you uh if you know if you can help it I I think okay I'm sorry I don't want to cut off but I do
I think we gotta kind of wrap it up yeah it's been a while because I have to I have to go and
compete in a pokemon tournament oh yeah pokemon pixel moon minecraft in an hour and 40 minutes um
this is so okay this is fun I agree and I'm really glad you came on um yeah and I'm glad you um
you don't hang out with us for a bit I'm sorry I complained a lot I feel like I complained a
lot about internet that's fine that's good that's good it's good good all all good content for the
viewer to listen to exactly yeah um yeah okay uh this has been boy I don't know I don't know what to
say uh I feel like uh I don't know just don't just thank you just thank you go read my comic
yeah give me yes follow me on the social medias look up sweeping comics comics that c o m i x
I think that's how I said sweeping comics it's uh you know it read Mallory's comics and it's about
sad gay suck anthropomorphic characters they're sad they're gay good you know they're they're
struggling with insecurities that might be relatable so maybe possibly uh yeah links down
in the description uh for all Mallory's uh stuff uh all right so I think we're gonna we are gonna
move on to voicemails and try and do them really quick uh and I guess we will see you later yeah
thanks for having me on it was fun and uh yeah you got you folks have a new fan I'm gonna check out
your podcast now so hell yeah thanks so much yeah folks have been very nice and kind and
understanding and caring you know well all the rest it's our pleasure to hear it yeah cool all right
peace yeah you folks have a good day god god bless yeah god god speed god bless
Ellie's alright at this part out oh I'm still in here I'm trying to get out you know actually
keep it in actually we we gotta all right you guys you guys got the you guys got the voicemails up
I'll have to get them there's only was there one two three four five six seven eight nine
ten eleven twelve there's only 13 oh still all right we gotta do like 10 seconds for each one
yeah yeah we're gonna we're gonna rapid fire him god damn that was a long conversation that was so
long I mean it was fine it was good it wasn't it like it wasn't like a grind but I'm just I'm
surprised it went so long I it's kind of unfortunate that it went so that this it went long this week
in particular because now I'm gonna have like no fucking time to sort out my pixel mon team uh
shit uh fuck don't worry about it I'm streaming tonight too so as soon as this is done I gotta
get ready for stream so it's just like god it doesn't end and I gotta record the bonus podcast
you need to do voice on dot com slash polystation two bonus podcast we have 63 of them now can we
can we are we ready for voicemails yeah please god okay okay uh all right first up how it started
versus how it's going three two one go this is how I sounded when I started listening to the
procrastinators podcast this is how I sound is a fully fledged pcp head get it the joke is that
um like that there are um he like um there are lots of unlike trans people who listen to the podcast
okay true okay amazing good good good call thanks uh next up I'm fucking shaking and crying right
now please play minesweeper three two one go okay so I've been playing an assload of minesweeper
recently like you know okay you know the problem with minesweeper how at the very end you end up
like having the the last mine is just like random chance if it's in spot a or spot b and you have no
way to tell and you just have to guess and then you lose and die um and it sucks uh well there's
this website minesweeper dot online that it has regular minesweeper but it also has a no guessing
mode where it guarantees that you can solve it um even if it's really hard and like non-intuitive
there is a way to 100 percent guarantee uh that you like know where the mines are uh and there's
like a ranking where you can like compare your times it like saves you all of your runs all of
your your fastest times it's like a big leaderboard it tracks the three bv which is the minimum number
of clicks required to complete a board and then like your efficiency compared to that there's like
quests with like daily quests and season classes like give you experience and mine coins and gems
and you can like use those to buy coins and gems fucking like equipment that gives you more experience
and gems and arena tickets when you play games and you can go to the arena I don't even know what you
do in the arena I don't know how that works I've never even gotten an arena ticket yet I haven't
leveled up that far this place is insane minesweeper dot online I'm going I'm going right now it's
based yeah that minesweeper dot online that seems like it can take up a lot of my time
it looks like nothing I mean that I mean this is great there's minesweeper oh there I see
there is an arena season rankings oh man okay all right fine cool thanks for thanks for the call
next one up is from uh Janess three two one go hey pcp now that the movement towards socialism
has won in Bolivia we can hopefully get justice for the indigenous protesters who have been massacred
by the fascist regime this is how you win against fascism by uniting the working class
into strangling the economy until they have to give you a free and fair election solidarity
towards all for the next decade uh yeah cool good uh uh those that uh that uh do you see that
do you see that video of the uh uh of the fascist guy crying when he lost the election
no uh it's funny is I don't remember what his name was just some the the other guy they were
really hoping they were really hoping they were gonna keep their keep their fucking that the coup
was gonna take but unfortunately it just wasn't it just wasn't in the cards form so sorry uh next one
random pc prisoner three two one go oh dude to do it's me living my life in the pcp voice show
oh holy shit is that fucking margar oh my god margar is dead on the ground oh my god stay with me
oh fuck no it's sorry it isn't being anymore he's dead oh the samurai killed him oh shit he can't
leave voicemails anymore because the story is over because he died oh man oh this is so bad oh god
golly gee willikers I am so sad at his death oh shit oh why'd he have to go so soon oh damn it
sucks that he can't leave voicemails anymore oh i'm so sad about it oh well he's you know the arc's
over oh but i'm so sad i'm so sad damn destroyed can't believe the margar arc would end on such a
such a dramatic no oh jeez oh oh i'm so sad though uh you know i think we all feel that way
yeah yeah it's so so tragic uh who could have prevented this
okay next up looking like a rat fetus three two one go so i was listening back to old episodes
and some foolish cuck calls in saying he has the world record 100% run of the shower speed run
oh he soaked down everything only took five minutes bro i hate to bake i hate to break it to you
that's not the 100% run 100% run needs to be a full body shave get that smooth ass skin everything
gone like your hair your eyebrows everything not a hair left i believe i am the current world
record holder with a measly 20 minute shower speed run okay well challenges if you're moving
that quickly in the shower with a razor blade this you're gonna die uh so how you know that's the new
challenge how fast can you shave your entire body you start the clock go go go we at the
procrastinators podcast are not liable for any injuries you may sustain attempting a shower speed
run but we are gonna laugh about it oh we'll laugh about it for sure but we're not liable
next voicemail check and mate three two one go
no
how could you kill margar like that
how samurai geto scroll because the samurai not forgive and beno san
red to guard down that hoen hawasaki samurai in my shoulder attack and strike and steal samurai
scroll but oh sadly this cover in a beno san sheet so scroll users mission accomplish
but mission pointers samurai scroll contain birthday cake recipe beno san you run away
from birthday banquet prepare by kawasaki samurai i didn't want to be 30 you break those
right heart you break my heart now samurai commit to zeppuku and no see no anymore
oh come on that's a little bit dramatic sayonara
oh
how to next time i never got to tell him something i don't know i never got to tell him to go fuck
himself yet so many opportunities you just forgot every time he's taken he's taken the one thing for
me i told you i didn't want i told you i didn't want a birthday party he's turning 30 i was like
no it sucks no i don't do it 29 for life baby no this was a while ago but he wouldn't listen
it was samurai tradition he said we're making you the traditional kawasaki clan cake and i said
and i said i got fuck it i'm i'm out and then the rest was history the secret the secret tragic
backstory down everyone is just fucking everyone's dropping dead margaret samurai we need some
beautiful colorful characters who will be next who who will rise to take the throne next next
voicemail cross y'all we're talking about circumcision three two one go okay the definition of mutilation
is cutting off or causing injury to a body part of a person so that the part of the body is
permanently damaged detached or disfigured so circumcision does fit the definition of mutilation
but so does getting your ears pierced also just going to add that considering the extremely negative
connotation that the word mutilate has it probably wouldn't fill you with confidence to hear people
use that word when talking about your genitals it is permanent disfigurement but it doesn't really
have any noteworthy downsides and the few cons that it does have are barely worth mentioning true
foreskin does function as a natural lubricant but it doesn't really make a huge difference and while
lube is a product that you have to pay for it does exist and even if you have foreskin you'd be an
idiot not to use it the foreskin also has a lot of nerve endings which assumedly makes sex more
pleasurable but again it doesn't seem to make a huge difference and we can't ignore the sizable
chunk of biological males who suffer from premature ejaculation which if the whole nerve
ending thing is true circumcision would slightly reduce the effects of also ben talked about
circumcision slightly reducing the rates of stds and it being cleaner overall which is technically
true but the reason that's the case is because if you don't wash an uncut versus a cut penis
the uncut penis will get dirtier just by virtue of having surface area that the shower water
isn't touching a properly washed uncut penis is just as clean as a properly washed cut penis
it's just that some people are retarded and don't wash their dick and the effects of that are more
prevalent in uncircumcised penises conclusion all of the pros and cons of circumcision are negligible
it literally is less impactful on a baby's life than getting their ears pierced if a couple wants
to circumcise their kid that's fine if not that's just as fine it doesn't matter who gives a fuck
um i feel like that's true i feel like that's fair i just i just there's the there's um
like that's all like medical and and like pros and cons like to have or to have not
an uncut or cut penis um but i would still have the extra argument of
fuck you mom and dad you don't get to do anything to me yeah i mean i you know i agree and honestly
like if i had a kid i probably wouldn't circumcise him because like yeah why is it up to me
yeah so true truth true next up we were right three two one go
everyone's gonna acknowledge that we're right in a few years once they bring gilgamesh back to life
and insurrect him as god of the new world order all right uh screencap this post
i don't know what that is in reference to is that is that supposed to be that they
was a reference to gilgamesh in hillary's emails uh quick google uh uh uh so cool so cool alex
jones calling into the show you know gilgamesh uh well like gilgamesh there is nephilim slash
gilgamesh in hillary's emails uh what the fuck um okay there's a link on reddit but like it doesn't
go anywhere incredible okay okay this is this is referencing something that is uh you know
probably true that's that's all we know um next up some fucker voice review three two one go
hey guys it's my fourth waste man and i'm here today to bring you voice with you the segment
where you review my voice so what do you think my voice is able to you or else you confuse you all
of the world this is what this segment is all about what do you think i form what do you think
i like who do you think i'm some fucker on the some fucker on the internet you are co-ed
oh my god uh voice review i think i think uh it was lovely it's it's it's good uh it's just like
you're slurring your words together because you're moving too quick yeah man go to have more clarity
go to take a easy take a sip of that sparkling wine and and speak slow next up is called review
voicemails smiley face three two one go hey there pcb this is my review of the voicemails from the
center perspective it's a cool and vault way to interact with some of my favorite per social
personalities it gets me playing good recording my own voice and editing and audacity which is great
a bad part is i can't fucking read so i need post production and voice meter and audio channels are
a nightmare having voice meter installed made me feel like i might as well send a voicemail every
week because of some cost lse of keeping it installed so i'm sent some really shitty voicemails in
uncreative states of mind it feels great to hear my own voice in the show and to make you guys laugh
and it stings when my emails are so bad they're literally getting skipped through or cut two things
for are for certain it is not a place for meaningful or nuanced discussion because of the one-sided
nature of it two parasocialism is a hell of a drug but it is not a viable replacement for meaningful
social interaction with actual friends or loved ones overall score 709 pretty good
bazinga that sounds about right
okay well i'm glad you like the voicemail section friend uh uh yeah uh yes friend
best friend of us oh you think you think we're not as viable substitute that's where you're wrong
see if you would only go to patreon.com slash uh the procrastinators or whatever the fucker url is
you would find out that that would be a great replacement that one would really do it for you
yeah in fact if you you should go to if you hate your friends and you don't want to have an anymore
go to patreon.com slash the procrastinators yeah and sign up and something friendship under capitalism
like everything else is pay to win so pay us money and win yeah we can we can we can solve your
problem whatever it is we got we got the solution it's behind a paywall um next up honest question
three two one go what do you guys think of amvs i made one in high school it was uh i made a fully
coolly amv how i set it to uh um set modus but modus mouse song float on float on by modus mouse
it was epic i wish i could find it i wish i still had that i made it on on videotape like on actual
like physical tape like on vhs ships yeah yeah because we had that we had a um an av like production
class and like it was like make a video like cut tapes together and we had equipment for that
and so like i made it as a class assignment and uh yeah yeah that's how i did it that's very based
i would like to see i i wish i wish i still had it i wonder if it's in like some attic somewhere
and like a box and like my parents house i don't know i wonder if i ever find it i'll
fucking put i'll fucking tweet it well uh next up some fucker takes issue with ben saying three
three two one go ben are you found because i found someone else so perfectly balanced between
base and cranes every time you do say something base you have to follow up with some dumb shit too
usual times in the last episode but the left half are language swap but you've been saying
say things in the most authority way possible like previously gone biologically six you just
say it doesn't exist you can't say i'll call reframing my idea of biologically six it's no
a six could possibly a more broader spectrum or something but instead you phrase it in the
worst way possible and don't follow up you constantly do this and when i think you finally
get your political shit together you go down a new avatar system dumb shit about the circumcision
god damn it ben you're supposed to be the smart one i i gotta i had a little trouble i have a
hey look i gotta review your voice it's bad i can't fucking follow you uh um well he was just saying
you say something based and then you say you follow with something cringe and how dare you
no if i ever say anything cringe that's i'm being sarcastic that's that's it yeah everything
do you think you agree with i'm serious about and everything you don't i'm not it's really easy
that seems very very simple very simple jay fray uh narrow's eyes image
uh whatever some whatever sometimes i get a little facetious and that's
base sometimes you're stupid no i'm i'm many things but i'm not that i don't worry
somefucker i am the smart one i i promise
all right that's it that's it we made it we made it to the end oh three and a half hours
one of our longest ever i should think uh and i get a i have like so little time to go and get
ready for the fucking uh pokemon tournament on the pcp minecraft server check us for heckles you
will have already seen it or not seen it you can go see it now on the channel see it again see it
again relive the magic did i win did i lose uh you probably know already uh but i don't
uh any last words guys before we kill ourselves i mean i mean patreon.com slash the procrastinators
get the bonus episodes get in the patreon discord which apparently is like a thing i see it i i'm
in there uh but you know um and uh follow us on twitter at tpcrastinators uh and um see us next
week and uh malorie and her things she was a good guest i liked her yeah links in the description
patreon.com slash give and take and that's the end of this fucking podcast
bye bye everybody