Hello everyone and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm back, and the fun is over!
I'm the best guy ever. And also we're joined by Gibbontake. Hippocrit.
Hey guys, belljapes finished and there's a fucking Kickstarter. We're going to talk about that later.
Oh, that's right. Please, please, please.com.
Was that not done when they last spoke, but like it was going to be listenable by them?
Yes.
But now it's out and we've all read it, at least I have. I read the whole thing.
Of course.
Great shit, great shit. Ben Saint is here.
Woo! I fucked up last episode.
Yeah?
Also.
Very embarrassingly, unlike Hippo, who's got his shit together, last episode I said,
guys, when you hear this episode, there will be one of the Vaporettes from the first Vapor's book will be published on the website.
And I just forgot it was Friday and forgot to do it.
But it's there now. And for real this time, when you hear this episode, there actually will be a second one.
So there will be two by the time you listen to this one.
At stcomics.com slash something, hit fucking whatever, go to my Twitter to find the direct link.
Very fantastic.
We got Munchie. Munchie's here.
Nate?
Yeah?
You're going to have to answer some fucking questions.
I'm ready.
Now or later?
Later.
And did you, bro, is here.
Soon, soon, your time will come.
Hey, I'm awake at 1pm on a Sunday.
Imagine that.
What better thing could I possibly be doing?
You know, I've been sleeping a lot lately as a result of massive exhaustion from, you know, me and Mavva2,
which should be done by the time you hear this PCP, everyone.
Yes, it's after the end of May, but you know what, 31 days, whatever.
I'm doing my best.
Those were the questions.
How could this possibly fucking happen?
Okay, you had more time, did you not?
I thought we talked about this on the show that you had more time.
I did have more time, that's correct.
Wait, are we talking about the me and Mavva being late?
Because there happens to be a very prominent X factor in this equation.
There's one major thing that's different between Nate's life two years ago and Nate's life today.
I wonder what could possibly be delaying me and Mavva.
Are you saying that getting a girlfriend ruined best guy F?
I'm just saying that he drives her to and from work.
That is accurate.
Wait a minute, were you single a year ago?
Well, that was two years ago, me and Mavva2.
I actually met Michelle as a direct consequence of me and Mavva1 as it would happen.
That's right, it was two years ago.
You either die a fan or live long enough to see yourself become the girlfriend.
I am fully prepared to engage on this topic because I couldn't agree more.
It's true, so I started at the beginning of this month, so here's the thing.
I'm going to talk about this in the final episode of me and Mavva, but whatever, I don't mind.
I had more time because I hoped to be done with my job and have left it.
But because of the particular situation of my job, I suck my own dick a little bit.
I'm kind of an important member of a particular team, and if I'd gone, they would have been fucked.
So they asked me to stay.
Normally, you give them two weeks, I give them a month.
They asked for three months, basically, is how it worked out.
And I was just like, you know what, these guys did me right.
And frankly, if things don't go so great as a YouTuber, I'm going to come crawling back.
So I'm going to plant some seeds, plant some seeds.
Sure, I get that.
They're paying me for half-time work, and I'm working more like two-thirds work.
It's how it's shaped out.
So yes, I have a couple more hours in the day to do stuff.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, hold on.
Did you say you're working half as much and they're paying you two-thirds as much?
They're paying me half as much.
My pay was slashed by half.
However, the way it's shaken out, I'm actually working more than half.
That's kind of...
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
So they gave you a pay cut because you put in your resignation?
Well, because I'm working supposedly half-time, which is, you know, how it's supposed to work out.
But then you end up working unpaid overtime?
I mean, that's, yes, that is what's happening, yes.
Which is, I mean, I'm not thrilled about it, but the thing was already with my job.
My job already had it.
Fair.
Well, you know what's interesting about my job?
After years of, I don't know, I guess I'd call it high performance and then being happy,
I actually got into a category where I got a monetary bonus per quarter based on an evaluation of my job.
So there was an incentive.
If I did extra work and they were happy with me, I did get paid more.
I mean, it's kind of funny to think, frankly, compared to my YouTube earnings as my side gig,
it was like a drop in the bucket, which is like a second career entirely.
But it was extra money if I did better.
So that was nice.
Okay.
But the point is, yes, I had a few extra hours to work, not a ton, but some.
But that would balance out the Michelle driving.
The relationship factor.
Yeah.
To treat it as coldly, callously, robotically, heartlessly, demonically as possible.
Which you do every day in your life, so it's no way out of character for you.
Correct, correct.
The fact of the matter is a relationship does in fact take time and energy.
And I'd be lying if I didn't kind of wistfully remember the kind of pure robotic autistic dedication
to being able to simply sit down, block out every other need and concern,
and simply generate, you know, video.
And now I have at least one human relationship.
I cannot avoid, you know, investing time into it.
I wish you could see the fucking smile on my face.
I'm so smug about this.
Inarguably, it is a nightmare, Nate.
Indeed.
Well, why did you?
Why are you so smug?
Just because you gave everybody so much shit about having a girlfriend
and that you got one and all the same things happened.
Well, I mean, I just want to say, do you remember the days when, like, Digi would mention Mae
and you would vanguard, you would leave the charge of, like,
listen to this guy on top of bringing up your girlfriend again.
And then he brings up his girlfriend on, like, every PCP episode.
He did, Nate.
You're worse than Digi was about it then.
Hang on.
Are we just ignoring the fact that, like, in this example,
she's being purely brought up in a negative sense
as, like, the detriment that she's causing?
Well, sure.
As long as you're shitting on her, then it's okay.
Well, in this case, I brought her up, so it's different.
But, yeah, there you go.
There you go.
It's just, it's hilarious because I know that it doesn't matter.
Like, there's no way for you to ever have to be...
I know I was accepting the devil's pact here, people,
by getting into a relationship.
I don't think it's typical.
I'm accepting the losses.
Yeah, no, that's what makes it so great, is that...
We're just saying how the ables have turned, how the ables have turned.
You will never feel, um, you will never feel, like, embarrassed
or offended if I point these things out,
because you're just gonna be like, yeah, it's exactly true.
I've become the beast that I was, uh...
Yeah, that's right.
Making fun of all this time.
I'm just a bad man now, you know?
You know, I think the difference about me...
Failed masculinity at its peak.
There are some aspects of life where I think other people reject this,
but I just embrace being a bad person.
For example, pirating video games and movies and software and music.
Other people make arguments for why it's acceptable.
I make no such argument.
I accept the fact that I am a bad person for doing so.
Now, that's it.
Now, on the one hand, I respect that.
Actually, no, on both hands, I respect that.
Be a bad person.
Yeah, that's fair.
I mean, I guess one should aspire to be a good person, so...
I'm completely with you.
I have completely embraced that.
I just, you know, do what I want to do,
and you can make value judgments about it.
I'm not going to, you know?
I'll just be like, uh, bad, good?
What are these words?
I'm just doing me.
It's an interesting, uh...
I don't know, paradox isn't the right word.
When you get a girlfriend, you do have less time for work,
and you spend that time with your girlfriend.
But your time, I don't know...
It's a quality of life investment, right?
It's better.
Like, your life is better, necessarily.
Yes.
Well, that's insane.
I feel like it's almost, I don't know,
it is good to force yourself to experience pleasure,
because if we're up to us, we would just not do it.
At least I would.
There have been multiple times, very recently,
where if it were up to me,
I would have just worked tirelessly
and wanted to kill myself.
So in a way, yes, work was delayed,
and in fact, I was doing things that I could have finished.
I was going to finish it in this work.
And I haven't done it yet, because I was with my girlfriend.
But when I say the time has been misspent,
no, because I had a great time.
I feel like I have improved my life.
This week, I've worked less,
because I've been spending time with my girlfriend,
Monty.
It came me, yeah.
Exactly.
But on this front, though,
I do want to say that obviously,
I make all these, these are not jokes,
these are real consequences of investing in a relationship,
but I do think that it's a net positive,
and I'm happy to be doing it and whatnot.
So, yeah.
I mean, everything that could be said.
Wait, wait, wait.
Flash, flash cut to Michelle,
sitting on a beach somewhere,
whatever she does in her spare time,
with her paper.
With her divorce papers in hand.
And she goes, oh, he thinks I'm a net positive
and starts shredding the papers.
Everyone should think they're a net positive.
No one's perfect.
Everyone has negatives.
That's the highest problem that I can do.
I'm saying she puts her hand over her heart
and says he says I'm a net positive.
Right.
Okay.
Well, good.
Good.
But I did want to say, though.
Well, I just want to say that this doesn't, you know,
exclusively apply to relationships
in the sense of, like, romantically.
I mean, this happens for friends.
I mean, as Ben just said, it happens with me.
I'm over here in Boston,
so we're obviously hanging out more.
So, I mean, I'm sure the productivity
has extremely just dropped off the face of the earth
because I met him for, like, combined,
like, 10 hours total.
Absolutely.
However, I would never claim that you are a net positive,
you know what I'm saying?
Okay, hey.
My final point.
So, I mean, look, I can hide behind the shield
of, like, my job and Michelle, you know,
like, girlfriend time.
And plus, my dog also takes time.
So, that's another factor.
A dog also takes, you know,
you have to walk him and whatever.
But the real thing is...
You have to love him.
I mean, yeah.
The real unadulterated truth
is that I have made many mistakes in this Weagawa,
I mean, in this Miyamafava.
Look like that mistake, for instance.
Yeah, like that one.
I mean, just, it has been more than anything,
just me getting sloppy and getting...
Look, I was on track with Miyamafava
until day, like, 21 or 22.
And it was at that point.
So, the thing that happened was, like...
So, okay, there's two major things that caused me to fuck up.
One was, I accepted the thing that I had never accepted
with Miyamafava 1.
And that was, I accepted being able to go to sleep
before posting a video the next morning.
I said that this is something I'm going to allow myself to do.
That was my first and biggest mistake.
Doing that allowed me to get lazy and sloppy.
I should not have done it.
I should have just chug coffee and got it done
and then slept the one or two hours that were left.
But the other thing beyond that is that I...
I think because of this initial weakness I allowed myself,
this mental weakness that crept into my mind,
I then, when I got, like, a copyright strike
on my Point Break video,
that got me a little bit upset and fucked up.
I was like, no, my perfect, like, plan day-dive-day
isn't going to work.
And then the next day's plan was to release the Miyamafava theme,
which is ready to go.
And the thing is, right now, it's sitting in copyright hell.
It cannot go live on YouTube.
And it's in the, like...
It's in the secondary stage of copyright fight
where, like, I'll get a strike if I lose.
And so, like, the reality of that video just...
I prepared it.
It has a little bit of fancy editing.
It's got the song.
I did a bunch of stuff.
It's ready to go.
And seeing that that video just wasn't able to post,
I was like, okay, well, there goes the video for today.
And then as a result of, like, the next day or two,
I was just kind of fucked up and, like,
I don't know what I'm gonna...
Yes, I'll just...
Yeah.
It was so...
This is all on me.
100%.
I just let things get to me and got off schedule and whatnot.
But it was that initial weakness.
Because what I should have done is...
You should have said, I ain't gonna let it get to me.
I'm still gonna creep.
Yeah.
Down in Pumpkin Hill, I got to find my lost feet.
I know that it's here.
I sense it in my feet.
I think I'm gonna...
Great inworld power allows me to feel.
Yeah.
There's no excuse for me not being, like,
posted a video.
It didn't go up.
Okay, I'll just make another video right now in the next,
like, I don't know, hour or so.
That's what I should have done.
And I didn't do it.
And it's my fault.
So I'm late.
And that sucks.
But I don't know.
I'm also kind of wondering how upset I should be with myself.
But not at all, because nobody gives a shit.
Yeah, nobody gives a shit.
I'm more upset with myself.
When I did the August video series, like,
my takeaway was that I was mad at myself for taking it so seriously.
That, like...
Really?
Because I tried to get...
I got every single video out before midnight.
And there was no point at which I had said I was gonna do that,
or when that was, like, in the promise.
The promise was only really to my patrons.
Nobody was even...
Nobody had really made bets on it.
Like, there wasn't really much at stake.
If I had made them late, or if I had, you know,
taken more time for myself.
It was just like...
I just imposed it on myself because I felt like I had to do something really crazy
because I really needed money.
And it did make me some money, but like, I didn't...
I don't know, you know, if money was the goal,
it needed to be pitched better, it needed to be more planned out.
And I came up with the idea for a very last minute.
Like, literally, like, 8 o'clock PM on July 31st.
I did tons of planning, but I fumbled the execution opposite of you.
Well, if I am allowed to pull a Nate in hell,
ringing that bell, best guy ever, real quick,
and play devil's advocate,
I just want to say, isn't the whole point of BMFA to be like,
guys, or this one specifically, like, guys, it's really happening.
I'm going to be a professional YouTuber.
You can expect this level of dedication to me,
and I will deliver videos on time,
and you know, this is big glory, like, hyping up me as an AirNet creator,
and that you failed to deliver that.
Would that not mean that it's like, oh, well,
he couldn't even do this, like, initial, like, high promotional thing?
Would that not be a failure there?
Well, you know what...
Now, okay, I mean, I would understand people making that criticism.
I would argue that this Miimath of a...
I mean, if you watch the original pitch video,
the thing is, I should have done this and mostly intended to do it,
but I leaned a lot less on the idea of, like, getting one video out per day.
Now, I mean, maybe that's a cop-out.
Everyone fucking knows what it means.
It's supposed to be one video per day.
But, I mean, I don't know.
I don't think it's gonna matter.
A long-term, no. No one's gonna care.
But a lot of people are already comparing it to Miimath of a one.
I have reached a point in my career where I literally don't have any fucking idea,
like, what's going through the heads of anyone who watches me anymore.
Like, I don't really understand the mentality of people consuming my content
because, like, there's the people who talk to you,
and that makes up such a small percentage.
Like, even in my patron discord, like, I have a thousand patrons.
There's maybe 30, 40 people who talk in the discord.
So, like, I can talk to them and kind of act like, oh, this is...
I have a sense of what my fans care about, but not really.
It's just those people who hang out in the discord.
And there's all these other patrons who I don't know what the hell they want or care about.
I don't know how many of them are watching each different type of video.
You know, I try to make multiple channels, multiple styles,
and, like, a lot of my videos aren't even getting pushed to my audience
or nobody's clicking on them.
You know, I've got way more subs than the amount of views I get on average.
And I just keep asking.
Like, I've gotten to a point where I just pull my readers or listeners and stuff or whatever,
and I just say, like, why didn't you watch this video?
Like, I did that.
I put out this hour-long Utana video,
and I did it because that was, like, the most requested show I had gotten.
Anytime I ask, like, hey, what anime would you like to see me cover the most?
The one I get the most is Utana.
So I put, like, I made a video.
It's got less than 20,000 views after a couple of days.
Damn.
Oh, God.
And, like, that's not too surprising because it's an hour-long.
It's about an old show that not that many people have seen.
I just thought that because the show has been more hyped over the years,
more people, you know, people specifically wanted me to talk about it.
Maybe I see it on Twitter.
Maybe I see references to it on Twitter.
His mid-sentence.
Ben, no, kill yourself.
Yeah, no.
No, well, Ben's right.
It is on Twitter.
That's what I thought, too.
And, again, like, it gets requested a lot, but I put out this video.
It doesn't get that many views.
So I put out a Twitter poll and I said, hey, have you watched my new Utana video yet?
If not, why?
And the options were I haven't seen Utana.
I don't care about Utana.
It's too damn long or I haven't gotten to it yet.
And the majority was I haven't seen Utana or don't care about it.
Like, 60% was I haven't seen the show.
So I'm like, OK, that's not necessarily surprising to me because I know that not that many people
have watched it.
It's just so weird that that is the overwhelming majority of what I get if I ask people what
I should cover.
But it just means most of my audience isn't answering.
You know, Digi, you're so right.
This phenomenon of the vocal minority is so prevalent in, like, the YouTube comments
sections and the kind of feedback we get when, I mean, I don't know, I don't know if it's
cynical or anything.
But the things to listen to really are the total viewership numbers you get, the like-like-to-dislike
ratio, and of course, like, the amount of Patreon support one gets.
The thing about that is, yeah, and it gets weird, though, when the Patreons make stuff
in it because sometimes you might make something that gets a shitload of views, but your patrons
don't really care about it or vice versa.
Right.
You know, I make tons of stuff that gets no views, but it's the patron's favorite.
So like, for me, ultimately, it just comes down to don't fucking listen to anybody.
Like, just do whatever I want and market it in a way that makes sense to me.
There's a gut instinct.
It's the only thing that's ever worked, and I know the data better than anybody else does,
because every time I open my mouth about anything, I get a thousand people telling me their idea
of what I can do to fix it, and always it's missing something.
It's always like, yeah, like, that would be a good idea if not for this other element to
it, and like, you guys don't know all the data that I have, so like, there's no victory
here.
I've just got to do my own thing and try to figure it out, you know?
Yeah, it's-
There's no victory here.
I feel quite anxious sometimes, like, whether or not to post my Patreon on certain things
that I do, because the Patreon, I mean, it's changed, like, hands in a sense.
Like, it used to be for pony compilations or analysis or whatever.
Now it's- then it was for hypocrite videos, but now I don't really shill it on things
like my Red Man comics, or like, my, uh, Bale J, or whatever, uh, because it feels like
I should make a separate Patreon for those things, because I know that if I post certain
things on the Patreon, I mean, it's a monthly thing.
I just need to, like, advertise it more.
But, like, it's kind of weird.
It's kind of hard to, like, market yourself as, yes, this is me, and this is- I do lots
of different things, and if you like any one of them, uh, pledge.
It sounds like how I heard the Osterios Patreon described of it just support this
internet man doing internet things.
I mean, that's kind of- I don't know whether that's, like, it's- I don't know whether
for me, specifically, that's, like, quite, uh, you know, a good, uh, idea.
Well, not a good idea, but, like, uh, it's a hard sell, because the things I've done
are not similar, like, comics and YouTube reviews are a little different.
Yeah, I mean, it depends on whether the audience is there for a specific piece of content
or for the creator, and that's- that's another place where it hook- like, it confuses me
because I always follow creators.
Like, I per- just if- if somebody makes something good, I follow that person because I expect
them to be able to make other things that are good.
It doesn't seem like most people really think that way, and I guess that's obvious,
because, like, most people don't base what they watch on, like, knowing directors or
knowing, you know, staff members, but, like, that's entirely how I consume media.
So, like, to me, if I were to make, like, a separate channel that's about some other
subject, like, if any of you made a separate channel, I'm going to follow all of them,
obviously, and it's not just because you're my friends, it's because I expect anything
you make to be good, so, like, it's a given.
Yeah, I'm going to follow that other channel.
Most people don't think that way.
Subscribe to the news update for piece of shit tabloid news by a deceptive evil man,
Johnny News.
And, like, I've come to realize the only way you can get people to care about your
other thing is you just have to, like, fucking shill it constantly.
Like, I think YMS is the only person I've ever seen who, like, launched a secondary
channel and built it up from nothing over, like, the period of, like, a year and a half
with this gaming channel, because he advertised it at the end of every single video
until it had steam.
And, like, when IAMgames launched, I had advertised it as, like, I had put it at the
end of a couple videos, I had put it at the very beginning of one called What is Deep,
which is a video I wrote just so I could put an IAMgames promo in it.
I did a video announcing, like, my Tales of video on the main channel.
And, like, at that point, I was like, okay, surely I've done enough.
Like, I've mentioned it a bunch of times, I started getting comments of people telling
me to shut up about it, so I'm like, okay, this must be good enough.
It never, it didn't amount to that many subscribers.
Like, it didn't push people to the channel.
The videos still aren't getting a lot, and so the question becomes, like, okay, well,
is it that people aren't interested in the content, or is it that I haven't promoted
it enough?
So, my latest video, I just did one on Metroid Prime.
I posted it to IAMgames 13 hours ago, and on there it has 1.8 thousand views.
I posted it to my main channel, opening with an advert for IAMgames three hours ago,
and it has 5.3 thousand views.
So, clearly-
Makes sense.
Yeah, I mean, it makes sense because I have way more subs, but it's just like, why is
there no follow through?
Like, why are people not, like, why are they watching it and not saying, okay, now I want
to go sub to IAMgames?
I just don't understand the way people think.
I think it's like the thing my parents used to tell me about eating your greens.
You have to put an unfamiliar food in front of a child who will not eat it, like a thousand
times, or maybe not a thousand times, but like a hundred times before they will start
to try it out of curiosity.
It's true.
Yeah.
It needs to be an overwhelming amount because it needs to be something that they can expect
to appear and that they will like brush off, like, almost as like a routine, like, oh yeah,
they're talking about this at the end of the video, whatever.
You're fucking totally right.
That's true.
Like, I should not have let myself be, like, again, vocal minorities, and like, I'm somebody
who falls for it really bad, like, if somebody leaves a comment about something and I, like,
in any way agree with it, I'll just do what it says.
Like this Utana video, I did it as a YouTube premiere because somebody said, hey, you should
do a premiere for, like, your next big analysis video that might, you know, help it to get
more attention.
And I was like, that sounds like a good idea.
Crazy suggestion.
So I premiered it.
Premier seemed to go fairly well, you know, there's a chat, it was fun.
But first of all, lots of negative comments about premieres, like lots of people who were
pissed off because they hate the premiere function.
I don't understand that.
People literally, like, don't understand what a premiere is and they just, like, get confused
by it.
It's so weird to me.
Every time I do a premiere, there's people in the chat like, oh, is this happening live?
Like they think it's live.
A lot of people were mad because they clicked on it and it wasn't the video.
Like they don't notice it says premiere until they click on it.
And then they get pissed off because they're not going to see it live.
And it's just like the feeling of having missed out on it causes them to not want to watch
it at all.
Like they get mad that they missed the premiere and then they're like, fuck it.
But apparently it also is really bad for you.
Apparently there's tons of YouTubers who have reported that it fucks up the launch of the
video once it actually does launch.
And like it doesn't repost to people's sub boxes and a bunch of people just completely
miss it.
Like the view counts always go to complete shit.
People will do a premiere of a video, unlist it, re-upload it and get better views from
the second upload than they did from the initial one.
So apparently it's just kind of fucking broken and a bunch of people have talked about it
and I didn't know.
It seems that way because with the quickdraw server channel where we post the art things
that used to, you know, the drawcasts move over to the...
Hey, yeah, wait, hold on.
Before you continue on with the story about it, I don't think people know that people
ask sometimes like, where's the drawcast?
It's over there.
It only went somewhere.
It didn't go anywhere if you know what I'm trying to say.
It's still happening under a new name and it's on another channel, a separate channel
called Quickdraw and you can do it and there are like three episodes soon before.
You're going to have to mention that on every episode of this show from now on.
Yeah, that's true.
That's true.
Yeah, guess so.
Link in the description to the Quickdraw.
Go.
The problem with this is we all do a lot of stuff.
So it's like the thought of trying to bog down our show by literally just listing everything
we're doing every single time.
And yet like...
That's true, sister.
You said it.
There's something about Pumpk and every single time he mentions it, there's somebody who's
like, I've never heard of Pumpk before and it's like, ouch.
That was from Homestuck?
Yeah.
I saw that comic.
That was funny.
What a legend.
Anyway, were you saying anything about the Quickdraw premieres?
Well, yeah, the Quickdraw premieres seem to have like a very small view count compared
to the amount of people who liked the drawcast and are in the server even.
But maybe it is just that people don't know on the PCP channel that it has moved.
But I feel like if it wasn't a premier, it may even be getting more views than it is.
Yeah, maybe, Doug.
I don't know.
Might be worth trying.
The thing is, is that I just like the idea of a premier because I would certainly like
to...
I enjoy seeing premieres when I do.
I like seeing like, oh, hey, there's going to be premier in like two days.
I think I'm going to catch that.
That sounds like a fun time.
All right.
Maybe for you.
I think...
I mean, it's not good for channel show.
I'm arguing that we like personally should do it or if the online space should do it.
I just think it's...
I don't know why people don't appreciate the same way I do.
They're always confused.
They don't know what the fuck's happening.
And just seems like, are you stupid?
I think it's the fact that it's...
Are you literally dumb?
Can you not read me?
Like two days ahead of time is too long.
Like a day on the life of the internet is like a month.
They'll forget.
I have an issue...
Oh, sorry.
Go on.
Well, it's like notifications.
You can turn them on, but you have to turn them on.
Like set reminder.
I've never clicked that.
I keep forgetting to click that, even when I want a reminder about it.
Even when you're constantly told to ring that bell.
One of the annoying things I have is that like you get notifications of premieres the
same way that you get like a new video.
So it'll be pretty common that this doesn't really impact whether or not I want to watch.
I still want to watch the premiere or just the video eventually, but like when I click
on it and it takes me to, oh, this premieres in two days, I'm like, Jesus Christ, why would
you even show me this YouTube?
Let me know when it's actually premiering.
Maybe I'll watch it then.
This is another place where I feel like an alien because I get people who say like,
I didn't even know you posted this video because I didn't get a notification for it.
And I'm like, I don't use notifications anywhere on the internet ever.
Yeah.
Notifications are the devil to me.
I want to be that.
I'm unsubscribing from a bunch of stuff because I'm realizing what a waste of time and energy
it is.
But yeah.
I mean, I'm subscribed to tons of channels, but I just go to my subscription page when
I want to, like when I want to watch YouTube, I go to YouTube and I watch videos.
I can't imagine getting a notification and then dropping everything and watching a video.
That's what I do.
That's really what you do.
That's insane to me.
I need to be fair.
A lot of the things I subscribe to are like ASMR people.
So like, oh, new ASMR, this is the new thing I can listen to and not think about it while
I'm listening to it.
What are you doing when you get the notification?
Like just I'll be at work, like working and then, oh, notification, oh, let's take a few
minutes and watch this 10 minute video or something.
I guess if you can dick around at your job, then that's...
I mean, I can absolutely dick around at my job because I got my own office.
That's how boomer jobs work, dude.
Boomer jobs can just fuck around like 80% of the time.
Yeah.
It's a corporate job.
And as long as you get your quota done, like by the end of the day, the thing is I do end
up staying late at my job because I have fucked around too much during like the normal
eight hours or whatever.
So it bites you.
It bites you at the end.
That feel when you're on Twitter and you find an artist who draws big ass titties and you
go and check their workout and it turns out half their shit is some fucking morbid obesity,
big old punch shit.
You know what I'm saying?
I feel you, man.
You know what I'm fucking dealing with over here.
I couldn't fucking resonate with you less right now.
That feel when you're on Twitter, you see an artist and they draw big old fucking titties
and you go to their art page and all they draw is big old titties even when it's weird,
even when it's strange.
Like, dude, this ain't no big old titties, this is just like a stick figure or something.
That's crazy, dude.
What are you doing?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I literally don't understand what you're saying.
Hyper people hide in the shadows and you think it might just be normal art, but it's actually
hyper art.
That feel when you go on Twitter and you see a Twitter artist with the big old titties,
but then most of what they put on Twitter is not art and that's just talking and I don't
care.
I don't want to read.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, it's time for a call out.
It's time for a call out against a Twitter up and falling for many years.
Mokuo bot, Mokuo bot, Mokuo is a Toho girl.
She's the Chinese one.
She's cool and I was following them for a million years.
Now I had known all of a sudden I'm seeing people, this Mokuo bot, this account that
is only tweeted Mokuo bot images or Mokuo images by the specific artist for years and
all of a sudden is engaged with debate.
Okay.
The path of progression was simply that this person suddenly tweeted, I think it was just
two words, trans rights just canceled, canceled and look, I mean, that was fine, but the next
many tweets from this account were being angry at people who expressed, I mean, to
my eyes, any kind of pushback that this account would tweet, you know, a somewhat political
statement.
You know, obviously there's some nuance there.
That's what it seems like a rite of passage, like you walk up to the lion's den, you say
trans rights and you see if you can survive, you can see if you can fight them off.
You know, I don't think any sane person would argue with the point of the tweet.
I would, however, argue that this is really not what I signed up for when I pledged to
the Mokuo bot account.
And why would you think, sir or madam, that I'm here for your political opinion or, you
know, sure, trans rights, it's great, but I'm here for the, for the japery, the memory,
and I will, I would have unpledged you a million years ago if there was going to be any of
this kind of business.
And you know, it's not that I hate trans rights.
Well, it's not the one tweet that made you want to unsub, it's that it became like a
long protracted thing.
That's correct, Ben.
That is correct.
And you know what the good news is?
I did not unpledge your Mokuo bot and they've gone back to tweeting Mokuo images and I
couldn't be happier.
This is, you know, I'm loving it.
Digi, I'm going to need you to give me a news update and if you, and if you say that
you haven't followed this Twitter for years and I'm going to start barking at you like
a literal dog, so get ready for that if you've just treated me in this way.
Is Nihilist Arby's still good?
Oh, I haven't read it in years.
That joke seems played out.
You know, I found out, I found out today that you can't be fat and trans in New York.
What do you mean?
They did a ban on trans fats.
Yeah, that's what I call my label, fat, like fats.
I'm part of the fats community.
Nate, did you see these pictures from Oda of Nami age 40 and Nami age 60?
Oh my God, that was from the new SBS and no, I have not.
Where are they? Where can I see them?
Oh, I saw them.
I will link them in the chat, but you prepare to be disappointed because it's just her with
a different haircut.
I'm not surprised.
There's no difference whatsoever.
Have you one piece boys seen these fucking ramen commercials?
Oh, you bet your bottom dollar I have, dude.
I saw the Zoro one.
Yeah, I've only seen that one.
Is there more?
Is there more than that one?
Yeah, there's I think there's a handful.
Oh my God.
Well, yeah, the Zoro one of like it's actually it's I've studied that many times.
So okay, so there's a there's a cup noodle commercial featuring Zoro as like a high
school boy in, you know, like one piece high school and he's in like the Kendo club and
he got beat by Mihawk blah, blah, blah and he's hanging around.
It's like Zoro's story condensed into like 30 seconds, but if he was a high school Kendo
club member instead of fucking want to be the greatest swordsman on the on the high seas.
And it's a lot.
Yeah, at the end, Luffy just shows up and it just has ramen, which is relevant somehow.
This studio was already making like anim like weird anime ramen ads like this, which were
usually just like short rom like romantic stories that are just like they're just beautifully
animated 30 second romance stories that then have like a ramen cup at the end.
By missing at the very end.
It's Japanese media.
Have you guys ever seen Lost in Translation with Bill Murray and Scarlett Johansson?
No, I was just watching it the other day and obviously it's not real life, but it is fascinating.
I don't know.
I'm thinking about Japan a lot these days.
I love Japan.
You might say I love it, period, but the ceremonies, you know, a dog.
The the no one they do commercials.
J-rock.
Karugamesh.
Yeah.
Smile DK.
Yeah, thank you.
I'd say that of course.
Oh, I forgot the dog.
We got to do it.
Oh, I forgot the dog in the, you know, the Japanese dog.
Oh, because all Japanese dogs.
We got to we got to go back and remake it for for 2019.
We have to put like our faces coming in and saying trans rights.
Trans rights.
What else?
Trans fat.
Puppers.
Just just multiple names for dogs.
Someone opens their mouth and you just hear the sound.
Come out of their mouth.
No, you need a guy in the very lights up blue.
I want you to be in like the very back of the shot at like the far end of the
restaurant in the gesture outfit screaming.
Dude, Radcon four.
We should do that.
That's the only thing we should do a Radcon four.
We should do nothing else.
But you know what?
I bet that Oscar voice actor lady doesn't have a lot going on.
And you know who else's career got canceled?
My boy, Vic Mignana.
So he's going to need a gig.
We could probably get him to do the voiceover.
I can go.
I can go on the dick show and I can get Nick Rakita to put me in contact with
Vic and then he could do the boys.
Have I told you guys that when I was in college, I knew a girl who she was a,
as I recall, she was a relatively attractive, like cosplay kind of girl who
claimed to have a personal relationship with Vic Mignana.
And I'm just saying it plays into, I don't even know if I believe or disbelieve
any of the accusations.
I'm just saying that if I had to guess, if this woman was at the very least
aspiring to fuck Mignana, I would say 100%, she was attempting to do so.
Whether or not that was reciprocated, I have no idea.
But they did know each other at least a little bit.
So I don't know.
I'm not even, this isn't even a criticism of anyone.
You should ask Josh if he took that dick if you still know her.
I wish I could remember her name, but...
The Vic dick.
Yeah.
Okay.
It's going around lately.
I want to talk now about Bill Jaype.
Okay.
And it's a webcomic that I made.
When will Bill Jaype get canceled?
Too late.
He's already finished.
It can't get canceled.
So what do you guys think?
What do you think of my comic I made?
You saw the fan art that I did.
I did.
Great.
Did we talk about this last episode?
No.
It was not real yet.
It wasn't finished at the time.
I'm very annoyed because the way that Twitter cropped it, you couldn't see
Pumpk.
And Pumpk is the big money maker.
It's like a promo image.
Show Don't Link Oblivion.
Get that Link slave.
All the characters displayed out in a symmetrical way with the hero and the front supporting
characters behind.
They're floating in the background.
The classic trope of snakes all around the border.
I have a lot to say about Jailbape because before the finale was released, just maybe
even just going back like maybe a month ago, I had not read a single page of that comic.
But I had the honor of doing one small part of the Jailbape animation and I saw that
to myself.
Well, you know.
Bill Jaype, you clawed.
As I said at RFCK a couple days ago, I will literally never say Bill Jaype ever.
You just did.
Okay.
Well, whatever.
Slip that.
Ladies and gents.
Anyway, so I went back and read it and I have a lot to say about Jailbape because I absolutely
love the comic.
It's really interesting to me in a lot of ways because of its basically, I'm sure you would
admit that a lot of it is rushed artwork in the sense that you didn't spend a year or
two on each panel.
This just plays right into what I've been saying for a while now, that art does not have to
be good to be good.
In fact, it was probably in most scenarios actually to its detriment to try and make each panel
individually perfect.
I think in every scenario it's to its detriment.
Yeah, I would agree.
You can clearly tell in Jailbape, like many panels where it's like, okay, obviously-
Hang on.
If we reduce that rule to something that's like to put in more effort in something than
the bare minimum to get the ideas, the essential ideas across-
Yes, yes.
Could just be a waste of time and yeah.
Okay, okay.
Yes, yes.
There's very many panels where you can clearly tell that you cut corners in many ways and
that did not impact the moment to moment of it at all because there are legitimately pages
upon pages of Jailbape that I would consider homestuck level of memorabilia.
I often regard the many Tiki poses, specifically that one page where it's completely red.
The lava has just broken down into an underground tunnel and a cannonball has broken the roof
of said underground tunnel.
While it's fun and Tiki is just standing there posing, it is absolutely incredible.
I think about that and many other pages constantly and even though if you really take a fucking
measuring glass and look at each of the lines, you can say, hmm, this was made in three seconds.
Literally does not matter.
One fucking molecule.
Again, this goes out from the art, like the story.
There basically is no actual story, things just happen one after another.
But your passion for just the character designs basically and you know what little character
they do have shines through and especially in this lovingly crafted animation that you
made.
It is just like the pure like energy in this project regardless of the quote unquote lower
case Q quality of it.
That doesn't matter at all.
What matters is that this was a new thing that you had done.
This was, you know, you had done can story before, but let's face it, Jailbait basically
outclasses it in every single way.
I mean can story doesn't even hold a candle.
Call it Baaljab for fuck's sake.
Never.
I never will.
Whatever.
Fuck you then.
Get the idea.
You get the idea, exactly.
It just is so refreshing in so many different ways that comic and I'm so happy that you
were able to finish it in such a spectacular way and I encourage every single person to
go and read that comic because it is the best thing that any member has done in maybe a
year of any member of the PCP has done.
Just for fun.
What do you think was the last good thing that was like as good that any of us have done
before Baaljab?
Anyone.
This goes to anybody.
I'm trying to think myself.
The timeline is hard in my mind.
It's fuzzy in my mind.
It really depends who you ask.
True.
We're asking all.
Okay.
Me and Matthew will one maybe.
The timeline is good.
The timeline is fuzzy.
So there's probably something else.
Are we not allowed to pick our own shit?
No.
You pick your own shit.
Why not?
Go for it.
I mean, champion chapter one ended and then the game came out after the game.
Oh, okay.
That's a good one.
No.
That was in like late.
That was like early, like the first half of 2018.
2018.
Okay.
No.
Sure.
That's probably what I would go for, I think.
Are we saying that?
Are we trying to think of something that's as impressive as Jailbait?
No.
I mean, I knew we were refreshing in any way.
That's just not the same old shit, that's something that's like PCP like production
cannonball.
Oh, wait.
Azumi.
The Azumi demo was recent.
Yeah.
Azumi game.
I was going to say the Davoose game as well.
Oh, yeah.
Davoose game.
Yeah.
A ton of this.
A ton of this game.
When did that come out?
Yeah.
Personally, I would count my albums in there, but none of y'all listen to that shit.
Sorry, dude.
I just don't listen to them.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Maybe if I did, I'd love them.
I just haven't.
Sorry.
I don't like Digi, bro.
I don't like Singers.
Digi's too black sounding for me.
Well, to each his own.
Okay.
So Azumi game.
That's a line, guys.
He's not racist.
Please.
It's a quote.
I mean, this doesn't have to turn into a dick measuring contest.
I'm just trying to say hippo.
I'm really proud of you.
Yeah.
I'm just capturing a flame that I feel has been slightly extinguished.
And I'm really happy that you are doing something so interesting and unique again.
And you know, I think...
Thank you very much.
It might...
Well, yes, I don't mean to undercut you.
Cut you off there.
No.
I really appreciate all those words.
And I agree that like initially it was just, let's just fuck around and draw some stuff
and see what happens.
And like the first half, the first few first hundred or so pages was like, let's make it
up as I go.
And now that I have some things, I started progressively to decide, okay, well, why is
that a thing?
And then I, you know, thought of what, where they are and what they're doing.
And then I tried my very best to incorporate everything that was brought up randomly into
the finale or the end or like, so everything got wrapped up.
My brother did notice that there was that one thing that when Tiki smashed the bottle
in her face and then like had the broken bottle, she put it in an inventory, that didn't come
back.
So, you know, zero out of 10 for that.
Yeah, true.
But everything else, including the table of potions...
Well, it's a red herring, dude.
It's a red herring.
Yeah, it's actually 10 out of 10.
Excuse me.
I mean, like...
Oh yeah, sorry, God.
When I saw that the finale was a video, I was expecting something like the Endless War
S-Descend, which you also made, which was...
Did you not know it was going to be a real animation?
I didn't.
No, which, I mean, S-Descend is great, but I can tell that it was made in a time-efficient
manner.
Like, you know, it's mostly stills with video.
I mean, there is some animation in there.
Which, I mean, the sort of goes back to like, you know, that was good enough and that was
a great...
That was good enough.
And so that's why I was like, why would you do more than this?
Because it's fucking outstanding as well.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, yeah, and then I saw...
Because it's a genie.
It's a Stratobloid genie.
I saw that it was like fully animated.
I was like, oh my, oh my God.
It took a very long time, but I, you know, if there's anything I can say is that I learned
how to do the pre-production on that so that it happened in an efficient manner from going
to uni.
That's my story there.
Don't go to college, please.
Don't go to college.
Anything but that, totally.
Don't go to college, but if you do accidentally go to college, if you do accidentally find
yourself with a degree, you may as well have remembered some of the things you learned.
And you may find yourself with an animation degree.
This is not my beautiful dorm.
This is not my beautiful student loan desk.
There is a PCP release somewhere in time around you released the Bugs Life YouTube Hippocrate
review.
Yeah.
Where I believe I mentioned like Hippo, you know, video games review, are they cool?
You know, I like video games, but your animations were so cool and you were like, yeah.
And then you said, yeah, but in the future, which is now, and you had released one moments
ago, and it's really cool.
It's really cool that you're doing it again.
It's really cool that you're doing animations and the things that are unique to you as opposed
to being another cog in the fucking machine.
I think it's only fair.
I think it's only fair we give Munchy, I'm going to get around 100% credit for give make
in this animation.
Oh yeah.
That's definitely what I meant by suggesting that you do animations again.
Yeah.
That's good.
I do want to make one point about like the whole, it doesn't need to be good to be good
because combined with, I think it was like way back when I was doing the drawing your
waifus if it was risk a video series where I drew like a copied image and then gave
her like risk a horns.
Yeah.
And then Munchy and Ben shadow me mercilessly about how that's not, yeah, both of you.
I remember.
Wait, wait, for what?
Drawing your waifus if it was risk a because like I was doing it with the idea of, of like,
wasn't tracing.
It was copying.
It was close by.
It was in my peripheral, but like you were saying that's not going to get you better
at drawing.
I was like, they're right.
Yeah.
It's pretty true.
From that point, I think like a thing in my brain change little, little thing where
it was like, so I do get 100% credit.
Well, I guess you do.
Both of you, both of you, 200% between the two of you.
Yes.
High five, Ben.
High five.
High hoof, bro.
But like it was the idea, the idea of I'm, you know, I've been okay at drawing for a
long time, but it doesn't seem like I'm getting that much better.
And I want to be really good in order to do certain things.
But it's time sticking, time sticking.
And I'm not like suddenly better yet, even though I'm drawing a little bit more than
I was.
Why don't I just work within my means?
Why don't I just like make something with the power that I have currently?
And then that will be my practice for the next thing I know.
That's it.
That's what I've been since.
That's all you can do.
That's what Vapors One was for me.
I was like, I can kind of draw.
I'll just, I'll just do a comic with as best I can.
And that'll be my practice.
I think we can all agree, I think we can all agree that this, this concept of sitting
around and waiting for the perfect time to do whatever, to hone your skints.
It's all a bunch of bullshit.
This is what I mean.
I don't, I don't, I like, don't believe in practice unless there's like a highly
specific thing that you really want to get like exactly down.
Look, I'm going to go be a tightrope walker today and fuck practice.
I don't need a net.
I'm just going out on my unicycle.
I'm going to win it.
I understand.
I believe in myself.
I'm speaking about this from like, I've spoken about this many times before.
So I don't feel like I need to do the whole preamble that I always do.
But I'm not anti practice or anything.
And I'm not anti things being good, obviously.
Like when I say he doesn't have to be good to be good.
I mean, that it doesn't have to be of, I'm saying it doesn't have to be of
technical prowess.
It does not have to be like, you know, none of Jill is like, like technically
impressive.
What even is technically impressive is such a weird idea in the first place.
Because it's like, it's like something that has to be determined by like
academic consensus.
Like it's like a bunch of people are specifically trying to boil down what
they're going to consider to be technically proficient and nobody else cares.
And I think there was a time where I think this is basically the difference
between like modernism and postmodernism is the idea of like, yeah, OK,
but like you guys can come up with a bunch of logic for why that is what
you're going to call good.
But we can come up with a bunch of logic for why anything could be called
good, like when it comes down to it, what matters is the effect it has.
And like individual people are going to make their own determinations about
whether it's good or not.
Anyways, they're not going to listen to what is considered to be good or bad.
So I think what matters when we're worried about it when you judge
something's quality is what the idea is.
If you think it's a good idea in whatever way you may categorize that
and if it's communicated effectively.
So going back to that to those Tiki page pages, what is the idea?
Tiki looks cool.
Is that a good idea?
Yes, Tiki is my wife is executed effectively.
Yes, she looks cool.
Done.
That's all that panel needed to be.
And you pull it off spectacularly.
You did not need to make, I don't know, you didn't have to make Tiki
atomically correct or make or make the line with or even just, you know,
going away from technical problems, making the line with absolutely
perfect on that one page.
That would not have made the idea communicated any better.
It didn't, you know, you know, it would have really improved jail, jail
babe, though, if you didn't connect your lines, if you use that like super
secret technique of not connecting my lines, because then how could I do
the fill in bucket?
Well, well, well, wait, hippo, I think you're really missing an opportunity
to get your content for your patrons.
I think that you would get way more money if you just didn't release
the jail babe animation for three years and they just had to be patron only.
Thanks, man.
I have all these, all these points.
Oh, sorry, yeah, if you want to.
I have one thing that, like, I made a, I also have a plush, which is
being kickstarted currently of punk.
And that's like, that's cool.
It's, it's, it's, you want to talk about how the kickstarter is going?
I got like a fifth of the way there already.
So that's pretty good.
Okay.
And it's running for a month, right?
Running for a month.
Likely it will get like kind of close, but might not actually go over.
But that's not what I want to talk about right now.
I just want to, I just want to highlight one comment from that
video where I announced it from Pan Limak, who says, sorry to say this,
but the art isn't nice.
The comic looks ugly, the game looks ugly, the animation looks ugly,
and the plushie looks rather ugly.
The thing about stories with good funny writing is that bad art
doesn't make them better.
I mean, it's bad after all.
It feels weird when you show up on YouTube suddenly just to throw an ad.
Good luck, I guess.
What a fucking.
This is your post on Hippo.
I kind of, it's very like, very dismissive of the thing.
But you know, I kind of like him because he didn't, he didn't, he didn't
say fuck you.
He just said, I don't like it.
True.
And we said it, that's nice.
There's kind of a difference.
I mean, when people say something's bad, they mean they don't like it.
Nobody really knows how to say that.
I agree, Hippo, that is what it means.
And I kind of want to, okay, okay.
Remember that, that leprechaun video I did where I said that like being
saying something is bad is just to say that you don't like it.
Someone, oh God, I should dig up this tweet.
I like, after that video, someone tweeted at me and he was like, this is a
like particular value theory in philosophy that has been disproven.
And then he linked me to, well, well, hold on.
Well, he linked me, he cited some source and I went and I tried to read it and it
was my, and I could tell that there was like more literature on the subject.
And this is something I've been thinking about ever since.
And I crave to make a video where I like an actual like philosophical argument
where I go into that like value theory of judgment and I try and I like argue in
favor of my theory and I try and like rebut because apparently this is like a
thing, this is like a thing that has been like, like literature has been written
about philosophical theory has been written about.
And this is something that I'm interested in arguing in and I just
haven't dived into it yet.
Hang on, is this about the general principle of artistic merit?
Or is there a specific type?
Well, this is about like what is, is a value judgment purely subjective?
Or like it is saying something is bad, identical in structure to saying I
don't like it or is there a distinction?
Is there a linguistic distinction between those two things?
And this comment was saying that that link has been disproven.
I mean, this tweet, this tweet, I said that like this, like,
your theory of value has been philosophically disproven.
I regardless of that, I don't think every person is going to use bad or
like I don't like it in the same way as as like some people are going to think
about that most people are not.
Say when they say I like it's bad, they mean they think it's objectively bad.
Like I think that's a very common belief.
Well, I think they think they mean that, but I think they might fail to mean
that even if they intend to.
I agree, but that that's, you know, that's like death of the authoring
these people's comment.
Like this guy, I think it's totally legit.
It is.
No, I agree with you that what this guy is saying is I don't like it.
But because his intent was to say that it was objectively bad.
I think he's a piece of shit asshole.
Maybe I suppose.
OK, but it depends on what you want to do with it.
It just, it just, you know, I don't because I have like kind of a small
audience and the people who I was showing Belle Jape to as it was being made.
It wasn't like that many people, obviously, since people people on my
hypocrite channel have no idea what about anything I do.
Really, you know, you know what?
Oh, yeah.
Well, it was a duh.
I forgot my train of thought, something about the comment being mean.
Oh, no, yeah, it reminded me that, yeah, people will see Belle Jape.
They will see the way it's drawn.
The fact that it's like kind of, you know, low resolution, like pixelated,
not super clean, doesn't look like a way to put it, but it is actually accurate.
Like, well, it's better than pixelated as a term, because everything's pixels.
But true, people will see that and they will think, you know,
this isn't a good quality image.
This guy doesn't know how to draw really.
And they will dismiss it offhand.
This is like most people, I think, would see this.
People who say like Kill La Kill is badly animated or like people who say.
Kill La Kill can get people's attention.
I feel like Belle Jape was like more well received in the small community,
but on a larger scale, may not appeal to that many people.
But I still feel proud about the writing I've got, like the quality
of the writing, the, you know, the things I've learned.
I mean, if you look at the first few panels and then the last few panels,
you can tell I've become at least a lot more confident in drawing
like more difficult poses and things.
I was going to say, I feel like you improved, like reading it through in one go.
You can tell that you improved a lot.
Yeah, I haven't done that.
I just want to say that like the fact that people are seeing it
and making negative comments means that people who aren't already into it
are seeing it.
So like, even though that comment is like it's symptomatic
of the fact that new people are seeing it, which is good.
Yeah. And you know, when new when when more people see a thing,
obviously they're not all going to be into it.
Yeah. Hey, all this is fine discussion and criticism,
but really it's all pointless bullshit because I have a substantive
lower point to make about Belle Jape and it's the only point that matters.
And I actually already talked to give about this,
but I just want to express a sentiment I had because unlike you,
meta commentary dumbass pieces of shit, I actually care about the actual
characters and have concern for their well-being.
And this is what it is.
It's that at the end of Belle Jape, I guess I won't specifically spoil it,
but Belle Jape takes place on a sea of lava.
And as we have not seen anything outside of this one island, which is in
we do see other islands in the distance, do we really?
I don't remember that in some of the wide shots.
You can see that there are other things like way off in the distance in the sea.
Is that?
Yeah, this is a few little pixels of black in the inverted horizon and a few things.
I must have missed those.
OK, well, my my OK, nonetheless, nonetheless, as a dumbass piece of shit,
idiot who didn't miss any of these.
I was really cared about the substance.
That's right. That's me.
I represent the common man.
We at the very end of the series,
I felt so seeing our heroes, you know, win and go off and drift off in the sea of
lava, I felt a deep, profound anxiety because I was like,
I see these guys on a world of lava with no indication of civilization
or potential safety.
And I don't know how long this this this orb of Splish is going to last.
You know, I don't know what their ultimate destination is.
The jewel of Splish is the jewel of Splish is eternal.
Well, OK, nice head cannon, bro.
Cool head cannon.
But you know, I'm not here.
Takes a hit of my jewel.
Ah, Splish flavor.
I all I'm saying is if I was begging Gibb to make an epilogue or something
where we see them like, you know, just I would have been this would have been
addressed if just on the in like the last panel, we see them drifting off.
And maybe there's like the silhouette of like a city looming in the distance
or or like something like just just a hopeful element.
But there was none.
And the fact that I missed these islands in the distance.
OK, I'm already I've already missed some stuff because there is hope
because one of those you could theoretically go to and live.
Just please go back and just add a black panel and then in show card
gothic just right and they lived happily ever after so I can rest easy at night.
I mean, that's a I mean, that's a bullshit way to do it.
I want a more artistic way to do it more, you know, yeah.
But yes, no, I guess.
Well, obviously, the more artistic way flew over your head.
I want him to artistically do what I want him to do to his story.
That's that's what they had many grand adventures.
Look, I'm saying as the person who cares most about these characters
in the world, more than anyone in the world, I am scared
and pissing my pants currently worried about them.
And I want them to be safe and happy.
And please, sir, help.
OK, I can I can tell you that scholar.
I mean, first of all, you need to make like an analysis video
like theorizing and then I can say all your theories are stupid
and they'll they'll reach an island.
You so you so you can comment, lull.
I didn't put I didn't think about any of this.
It was all I do, bro.
I just comment death of the author and death of the author
in all caps like a hundred times and say, fuck you, death of the author.
And then start your five hundred page Bill J.
fan fiction that becomes more popular than the original.
And I was like, oh, yeah, Nate, Saint, the bell, jake guy, cool.
The bell, jake theorists like like like a Game of Thrones guy.
Exactly. Analyzing.
I'm going to talk about how pretty how pretty jail babe is.
But it doesn't just live up to like the narrative
stronghold, just ironclad, a thousand times folded script.
That is canon story.
I mean, come on, it may look more visually impressive, but come on.
Like the real meat and potatoes narratively is in.
No, check off gun remains unfired in canon story.
We can all agree the pocket boys is the real.
Oh, yeah, indeed.
And by the way, another moment I just really loved was
like at the end, when the shits going down, these are spoiled.
OK, you know, I guess I won't say it.
But OK, I will say that the payoff of the of the Flamingo narrative
I very much enjoyed.
And I mean, that I kind of felt one of those like, like, oh, my God,
moments like you'd get in like a real story.
Like imagine that and it felt great.
We can all agree that the real HIPAA winner is all those fucking
Terezi, Vriska, Porns, I see a real 34 pa heal, but I have to scroll
past whenever I search home stuck.
I always see them and makes me feel uncomfortable.
Who uploaded those and why?
There was there was one moment when I was very surprised.
I was like, oh, my God, that happened.
But then I thought I was like, oh, wait, that makes perfect sense.
Ah, and I don't want to say what it is because it's a big spoiler.
But I'll just say that that did happen.
Type it in in chat and I'll react accordingly.
I've got one, too.
I'm also going to type it in this audio podcast and totally ruin it.
Oh, yeah, that was that was.
I was I was like, I was like, what?
Wait a minute, may actually in hindsight, of course, that would happen.
Oh, I got one, too.
He's coming on this.
That was that was a thing that happened.
And oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah, go watch. Go read.
Bell shape right now.
Link in the description.
Link on street.
There's a hundred links on screen.
Oblivion fall.
You better put a hundred links on screen.
I could say like literally 100 or.
Why did why did these people deserve to live
as opposed to all the other people?
It's not fair.
It's not just wait.
We pay him. You do have to do.
There's no justice in this world.
That's true.
That's in this lava world.
Hey, did you did you?
Yeah, did you read it?
Have you read it yet?
I've only read as much as was out
like a month after it started because I decided I would wait for it to be over.
And now it's over.
So now I have to read it, please.
Please.
I read it.
Give it a little thing in about an hour and a half.
Making an hour announced video and then releases a premiere.
Why don't you make a 12 port analysis?
You piece of shit.
Maybe I will do a thoroughly analyzing
my little pumpkin.
Hey, hey, pumpkin.
I want my pumpkin.
Hey, let me tell you about something.
Let me tell you about something that makes me.
It bends here.
Oh, God.
This is this is my new this is my new crusade
that I've started to take up and get legitimately.
All right, more people on Twitter who are stupid.
Guys, look at this.
Look at this image.
Look at this tweet.
Look at this image and tell me that you would look at this and say,
no, thanks, I prefer I prefer a more well proportioned woman.
Get fucked. You're a pervert.
You're a sick pervert.
Hang on. You don't like these big ass titties.
That's what I'm fucking mad about.
OK, like you're a big fan of these titties.
Little. Yes, of course I am.
This is great. This is disgusting.
This is really disgusting.
This is what I'm here for.
This is the shit. No.
This is the shit.
Some shatman shit.
I mean, that is not some fucking shatman shit.
I'm so surprised and happy that we are brothers on this issue.
I would have never guessed, but I'm really happy.
You're all perverts.
In regard to Paul, I'm not a fan of I get to count in the comments.
Yeah, all you sick fucks in the comments who are like, no, thanks.
An undeserving of life is what you are.
In regards to this specific example that you've posted,
I find that Betty Boop has a more attractive body type than.
Look, Betty Boop is looking great here.
Betty Boop is looking great here,
but Jessica Rabbit is what I am about.
Ben, you know what? I'm surprised.
I'm very surprised you say that.
I didn't know when did this revelation come.
This is the truth. This is the this is the dark truth.
This is the dark shameful truth that I like big old titties.
I stand with Ben. I stand with Ben on this one.
You are a nightmare.
Hippo, you literally remind me of like a tractor going inside my wreath, right?
Like you are the worst thing that could happen when it comes to sex, very problematic,
which is why your riskatresi images on a rule three, four pack.
You'll always get my fucking goat.
Well, I don't draw anything.
Anyway, anyway, guys, speaking of comics and hippo, I literally don't care.
Don't worry about it. I want to fight about I want to fight about this.
OK, I want to fucking fight whatever even is there to fight about retarded.
My opinion is the correct one.
I wouldn't really criticize anyone for being into it,
but I would also have no problem with someone saying that they don't like it,
which sounds like what the argument is.
So really, I have no comment.
I just can't wrap my head around it.
I just can't wrap my head around it. I can't do it.
Well, I guess it looks unnatural and strange is this is one of those things.
This is one of those things where I just I just I can't respect.
I can't respect a conflicting opinion.
I can't do it.
You mean like every other opinion and a thing that people have,
like, you know, like all the rest, you can't respect that.
That's right. Yes.
In other words, this is just like everything else, I believe.
Things that look unnatural and strange is like part of the reason
why you would draw it rather than photograph in the first place.
You know what? OK, if Shadmander these, if Shadmander these,
they would be big and like spherical and that would be horrible.
But in that first drawing of it, like they've got half to them,
like they look like they're made of flesh.
No, it's they're just.
You're fucking gross.
No, it's it's 10 out of 10.
I wouldn't use the word grow.
It's ten five. I'll allow it.
Fine. OK, good. Great. All right. All right.
Hey, well, that's my that's my contribution.
I was walking. I'll see you all later.
Doing thank you all for coming.
Doing doing the thing that I love to do more than anything else
in the entire world, go inside of Newberry Comics
and go to the Children's section.
Because for some reason, I was not informed of this.
But apparently Western comics are like fantastic and cool looking,
says the person who's never bought any of them.
He's like, go to the kids section
and I just see covers that look like this.
And I'm going to post them in the show notes for you to look at.
And I think myself, what? Huh?
This is like a loud.
What is not my beautiful comic?
Discussing audio links so that we don't have to copy it over.
I literally did. You fucking dumbass.
It's in gross assumption audio.
Oh, you're right. I'm wrong. OK.
Hey, Nate, kill yourself.
Anyway, that's fair.
So it's things like this.
Is this a Western comic? Yes.
OK, it is a children's comic.
Yeah, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What's extremely average is named at Atelier Cento?
Atelier Cento.
That's not a real name.
Is it one of the is he the star of one of the Atelier games?
Atelier. Is he Atelier Heidi's brother?
I have no idea.
The first name is what connects them.
But this looks so Japanese.
So, yeah, it's so intriguing.
Art style wise and subject matter wise.
Look at that girl. Look at how she has no people.
Because that's the thing that I like.
I like when characters don't have pupils.
That's what I like. That mushroom cut.
I had a mushroom cut when I was young.
I find this almost as confusing as Ben's picture of the giant tits.
What the hell?
I just don't see anything unique or appealing about it.
No, I think it looks nice.
It doesn't make me want to read it.
You know, OK, you know what?
Maybe this is a man or a woman.
I don't know who's like Japanese by origin
because it's called Daira of a yokai ghost hunter.
I mean, that is a Japanese name.
I mean, his name is Cento.
That's a Japanese name.
And yeah, his name is Cento.
So he's either Japanese or like descendant of Japanese people or something.
Well, the reason I'm sure that you're right, Digi,
that it has to be the name of a group, right?
Because it's a children's book.
They usually group atelier or worse.
If I had the media prowess that you did,
I probably would not find this interesting.
But the fact of the matter is is that I have been pretty stunted media growth wise
and I have not watched or consumed shows or comics
basically like almost ever like like consistently throughout my life.
I basically have grown up on video games
that I have like three of them.
I was about to post that late night. God damn it.
Hey, what? Hey, hey.
So is it a collective or is it a French guys?
Yeah, inspired by their travels in Japan, apparently.
So their website actually, the artwork that shows up when you click on it is.
Yeah, I like it a lot. It looks great.
So so so when I see stuff like this, I think to myself, wow,
I legitimately haven't really seen much things that look like this.
And so I open it up and it's just a really nice experience.
And it makes me think about things I've talked about many times in the past
where I just feel against stifled media wise in the sense that I feel like
I don't make enough time for myself to actually watch shows,
which may seem weird to, you know, maybe other people,
but maybe maybe any of you guys, but I really just don't do it.
And so I made a pact myself.
I didn't buy this book, obviously, because why would I fucking buy things?
But by next episode, I will have watched,
I will have read the entirety of this book.
So this is the new thing.
Munchie Book Club, one comic at a time.
I'm actually doing media for Reels this time.
These these Atelier Cento guys also make games in this art style.
Hell yeah. Hell yeah.
They make like a mobile games.
Yeah, I'll put a link to their blog.
Oh, that's cool.
That's, huh?
Like mobile adventure games in that art style.
It looks pretty cool.
Sounds sick as hell.
And I'm really excited.
I like are they like a are they like a husband and wife do?
Or are they like two dudes?
They seem to be a man and a woman, but I don't know their relationship.
I don't know. I don't know.
I see a picture of a woman holding a tablet, playing one of these games.
And I wonder if she's one of them.
I'll be one of you.
I think so. YouTube channel, too.
Well, we have now.
Well, there you go.
Deep dive.
This is fucking great.
Long in the children's book that Munchie was interested in.
It looks like this is a good example of like good art plus, you know,
like, oh, yeah, art can be good and as well as being good.
I just want to say, I mean, this is exactly the way that I consume things,
by the way, is that like I see something, I look it up
and I find everything that person's ever done and then just systematically consume it all.
And like, that's what I was trying to get at earlier.
Like it's always about the artist.
It's like, oh, this person did something that I'm interested in at all.
Let me consume everything they've ever done
because it's all going to interest me.
And I think that's the I think that's a good just a piece of advice.
If anybody you have trouble finding things that you enjoy,
you know, consider looking into the people who've created the things
that you've enjoyed previously.
And they've probably made other things you enjoy.
I only had any respect for Weaboo's.
I might be able to appreciate this.
Ben, I know I know that you've resonate me on the not watching media front.
You, you should fucking watch a movie or something, dude.
Come on this journey.
Be a media, be a media meister, be a media muncher.
You need to consume more media.
It's such a weird thing to say, right?
It's a weird like on this show being like, oh, I don't watch shows.
But like, it's true. It's like actually true in real life thing about you.
Saying this much is that I also don't consume nearly enough media.
I just have the appearance of doing so because I research shit all the time.
Like the amount of stuff I actually consume is nowhere near the amount
that I like watch analysis videos of or just like.
Yeah, I do too much of that.
I do too much of just listening to some guy on YouTube explain things to me.
Completely agree.
Yeah, I think I think also that the reason a lot of people have ended up
looking at YouTube like reviews and analysis of things
is because there's so much media out there that you're like,
ah, geez, I don't want to be stuck watching or reading the wrong thing.
And you go to let you like somebody to compartmentalize all of the different
things and tell you which one's the best game of the year.
Well, I don't even like it for that reason.
I like it because I don't have to consume any of it, except for that.
Like the things that I tend to be interested in are almost never
some kind of big blockbuster thing.
It's never going to be something that even will get covered by YouTubers
because they would get no views.
So like it gives me the opportunity that I can go fuck off
and play my stupid weird indie games that I like.
And then I can still be a part of the conversation about what's happening
in the mainstream because other people are doing the job for me.
So like I could I could literally sit here and have a full fledged
conversation with any of you about the latest Avengers movie,
not having seen any Marvel movies in like 10 years,
because I've listened to so many podcasts that describe the plot in depth
that I have, you know, and like I would have hated the movie.
I could tell by the way it's described.
But listening to Jesse talk about it or listening to Red Letter Media
talk about it is enjoyable because I like those guys.
So it's like it's a better way to consume it for me.
Non sequitur right now, I'm imagining right now an alternate reality
where where Jailbap was a video game released for the Game Boy.
And I imagine the mid 2000s commercial for that Game Boy game
and about how I can imagine like some like 2000s teenagers
like going to your pumpkin patch and being like, huh, better not stay out here
at night dot, dot, dot.
And then one of the pumpkins grows eyes and then pump chunks out.
And then it like flashes like it does like an eye catch for like a couple levels.
And then it's like Nintendo at the end.
Anyway, I just thought you guys would like to know that.
Make it real.
That sounds pretty good.
I've seen it in the podcast, everyone.
I if you didn't know, by the way, people of viewers who haven't yet read
Bill J, there is a video game inside the comic called Run Away from Snakes,
which is like a 3D 3D endless runner where you run away from snakes.
I've got my brother to make a new grounds account
and he has uploaded it to there at just the endless mode.
So that will hopefully get a lot of traction.
Because the high score is winning ever since ever since Tom got front
paged with Azuni, I've been meaning to try to put the the champion game up there.
I don't think it would do as well because it's not a side-scrolling platformer.
It's not it's not a, you know, it's more of a narrative experience.
So I wouldn't expect it to do as well just on that basis.
But still, it'd be cool.
Wait, there's a champion game.
I didn't hear about this.
It's page one, technically, right?
It is the yeah, it is like sort of a prequel story to the first chapter.
And yeah, when you go to stcomics.com, it is the landing page or in there in a little bit.
Yeah, you play as the champion.
What's your name, Sophia and you and you are in the arena.
It is sort of a it is sort of a JRPG like Final Fantasy six kind of gross.
Yeah. Well, well, there it is.
Advertise this enough.
Did I did I not advertise it enough?
I mean, I guess not.
If people fail to hear about it, then I suppose the answer is if you're listening
to this on Friday, maybe you should head over to stcomics.com, check out that game
and then check out the two new vaporettes that are up at the end of the vapor section.
The first one by Emily Rhee and the second one by Lauren Colt.
Just one more week until the munchy vapor.
Just one more week.
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Next week.
Oh, which is by far the longest and by far the bestest, far longer than needed to be.
I'm going to break down why we all continually fail at this, why we're all
still marketing wrong, because the Vapors, there's a good chance a lot of people
listen to this, don't even know what the fuck it is.
So full bore, go back, explain what is the Vapors?
It's a comic that I made.
So if you go to stcomics.com, there's a bunch of comics that Ben's written.
He wrote two chapters of the Vapors, chapter three being written on the
Patreon, like released page for page.
It's been it's been released page by page on the Patreon.
It will be up to it will be done in two weeks from when you.
And a vaporette is like a one page, like short starring the characters.
It's a short story with guest art, yes, with a guest artist is what a vaporette is.
There was one by Fennel Kedenurix, one by Emily Rhee, one by Lauren Colt,
and one by Munchie.
And there's going to be a there's going to be a bunch more that come out with
chapter three. And it's a story about a couple of deeply neurotic
college autistic college kids, I guess.
Probably maybe autistic, maybe undiagnosed.
Maybe they just maybe they just have maybe not personal.
Maybe they just. Oh my God, you just fuck.
I just remembered the most important thing I had to describe.
Talk about on the show.
Yeah, please tell me you guys heard about they found the cure for autism.
What? Oh, I was a bang, bang energy.
No, no, it's way more insane than bang energy.
I saw a little bit of this.
Was this a joke? Do you just have to get it?
It's not a joke.
The cure for autism, unironically, literally is eating Normie's shit.
What? How can this be?
Because let's hear more about that.
They have discovered is that autism is linked to gut bacteria
and a lack of certain types of gut bacteria.
Apparently are apparently a lot of intestinal bacteria
as in shit have a lot to do with how our minds work.
And yeah, there's a certain gut bacteria that if you are lacking it,
then then you will I can't read this.
You will have autism and you can get it by ingesting feces
from neurotypical people.
Right. No, surely.
This sounds like an epic brand.
And it has autistic people.
No, there is no.
There was a full bore study where they they fed normal people feces
to children over the course has to be a joke.
It's not a fucking joke.
Why would they not extract the important element
from the feces if this is the only way to get it?
They made it into a pill.
They didn't like feed them shit. OK, OK, I'm sure.
Yeah, they made like a fecal metal pill.
There's other stuff you can find the fucking article.
I retweeted it from May.
Is it going to get a link?
I mean, in the show notes or something, hopefully.
OK, we'll get it.
I mean, I have heard that there are procedures wherein you literally
transplant feces from one person's intestines to another.
Like to get the good.
They ingested it orally in this particular experiment.
But if you just look up, I don't know what to look up,
but you could find this.
It's it's being reported on.
It's a study that was done on a bunch of autistic children,
all of whom showed fewer symptoms of autism
after about 18 months of going through this course.
Eight of them were so much less autistic
that they were no longer considered to even be on the spectrum
by the end of the treatment.
They are considered neurotypical now.
Is this something you have to do to a kid when they're young
like and still developing or like what if I don't know,
autistic adult become less autistic.
I haven't seen anything other than just the study that was done.
Hey, where the shit at?
I need to ask what you're trying to do out here trying to eat shit.
Please correct me.
So is autism defined as simply a set of behaviors?
Is that what that seems to be the case?
I don't think there's any other clearer definition than that.
We don't we don't understand the like underlying
physiological cause of it.
Apparently, though, it's tied to gut bacteria.
And you know, you know, by eating normie shit.
I'm prepared to entertain that this is true.
I kind of need more data before I'm going to be fully on board with this.
Go read some new look it up.
No, I read an article on the Economist about it.
On the Economist, yes.
What I'd rather do instead is just give I'll give these people, you know,
like 10 years, like go go fix autism and report back when it's done.
I mean, this is what I'm going to do.
I'm not going to read anything.
I mean, I'm not going to be 10 years.
It's going to be a year.
Well, great. Then they'll be able to do it within 10 years.
No problem. I'm sure this is not the cure.
And like, oh, this is it. All that other stuff and irrelevant.
It's just it's just the poop. It's just about poop.
That's all it ever was from the beginning.
I guess can't be that simple, right?
I I'm I'm still in shock mostly
because my diet apparently isn't working and I'm still not fixed.
I mean, I was doing this before anyone else.
And it's just not fucking working.
What am I doing wrong?
Maybe the maybe the people's shit you're eating is not a normies.
Yeah, sure.
Surely the the the not the only way to get the good gut
bacteria is specifically eating it from normies poop.
Like, is this just a dietary problem?
I'm not saying it.
Embrace it. This is the way of the future.
I really don't feel that uncomfortable,
but it's like I'm just wrapping my mind or it's like surely.
Like, I don't know why they did the experiment the way they did it.
Like, all I have is the data of what was done.
They fed people, married children for 18 months.
We're over analyzing.
Well, of them, eight of them were fully cured of autism.
Oh, look, the reason I'm giving such resistance here is because I don't want
a lot of people camped out around my toilet and my septic tank,
eating my neurotypical poop.
Does does this mean does this mean that if you eat autistic shit,
you will become more autistic? I hope so.
I hope I'm right.
We'll see what I'm thinking is the start of the fucking war.
A sewer war.
What this is going to lead to is you can customize your own neurosis.
Like, you can have whatever brain type you want.
Like, you could like, it's all going to make it go for one to the other.
Right. So like, you could just add or remove gut bacteria if you need to be
more or less autistic for your job.
It's like you really like a little bit.
Maybe if you like being autistic, like, avoid normie bathrooms
because you don't want to get infected with that normie gut bacteria.
It's like it's like you shouldn't hang out with cats because they'll give you
like they'll give you like brain like brain parasites that make you love cats
more. It's the same with normies.
They'll give you fucking gut parasites that will make you a normie.
Don't let them don't let them get you.
And some people, yeah, you know, fuck it.
I bet Nikola Tesla probably would have upped his I mean,
he was probably at max level autism already.
But, you know, like if you could increase it for more like autistic focus
on your work might help some people.
It's not all negative.
There's some benefits.
Yeah, I got to eat shit so I can be Mozart.
Nikola Tesla totally autistic and that guy never ate shit in his life.
Coincidence.
Imagine if he had how far we'd be ahead in the future right now.
Kind of tech we'd have boy.
You got to learn something new every day.
It should be utilized as a marketing strategy.
So it definitely took me a couple of days to fully internalize it.
But now you know what this means, guys?
The Patreon closed that shit down.
We can just sell our shit for fucking money now.
So we can give it off the cyberpunks.
Selling shit to cyberpunks is going to make up like 80 percent of our business now.
Who like, OK, are we just assuming that like
if you eat anybody's shit, you just become whatever they are?
Like, if you want to be a better like anime analyst, don't close my shit.
Yeah, all right.
I think I think it's a power up.
Appalachic all kinds of of unproven hearsay from this finding.
And you know what, we can make all kinds of shit based claims now.
We can send a poop based like care packages to people who we want
to be tweaked one way or another, you know, just send them like,
I don't know, who could use a dose of more Ben?
I mean, you know, people say that me and Ben are like two diametrically opposed.
What if Ben and I swap shit?
Just swap shit.
Yeah, yeah, we become the happy medium somewhere.
The phrase, you're full of shit is going to mean something different like five years.
OK, OK, you sign up to a subscription based service
where they have like celebrities that each contribute and you can like custom formulate a pill.
It's like, hmm, you know, I want to be I want to be successful.
I want to be a successful capitalist.
So like, give me like, give me like, you know, maybe give me a pill once once a day.
Give me that musk shit.
Yeah, yeah, 40 percent Elon Musk, 20 percent Jordan Peterson,
maybe maybe a dash of Steve Jobs, you know, Joe Rogan in there.
So they still like to be extracted.
Dude, OK, I'm shit from his corpse.
There's going to be literally there's going to be Ben St.
shit flavored vapes in the near future.
And you can get if you subscribe to loot shit, my new box based shit subscription service.
Comes with randomized normy, normy shit.
Normy shit should be a flavor of fuck energy in my in my discord last night.
We were all thrown out like ideas for for fuck energy flavors.
I'm I'm a fan of a water flavor, just urine.
How long is it going to be before I can get over the counter jankum?
Soon. Oh, man.
Well, that's a whole legalizer.
Man, I want to I want to start.
I legitimately would be so excited to start like a like a like like garage,
like drink canning business and just like put it in like local like vending machines.
Fuck energy drink the fuck energy.
The competition.
This is this is like an amazing market because.
Yeah, like it is.
Yeah, because everybody I mean, anybody who has who can prove the value
of their shit can sell their shit in this market place we're describing.
Like if if all you have to do is market yourself as somebody with desirable shit.
So like the competition is endless, like nobody can just make the best shit.
That's true.
Everybody's going to have somebody else who they who's shit they want.
They're all the kind of shit that they enjoy the most.
The Japanese, as always, so far ahead, you can buy you can buy sexy girl
shit in vending machines in little capsules, I'm sure.
I don't know. I know.
And for those who wish to be a little girl, they got your cover.
It's so much easier.
It's just girl shit.
Some guys who have been trying that for years and it hasn't had much effect,
but maybe maybe with a higher concentration.
Well, what have we solved it?
We solved every problem.
Each shit get fuck energy.
That is I think that's all for this episode.
Yeah, I think we've run the game over the voicemails.
Move on to voicemails now.
This this was great.
This was great and breezy.
I didn't get to like half the things I want to talk about.
That's how you know it's a good episode.
That's how it should be.
I like how much he's like rushing us to the end and then saying he has more to say.
Well, I mean, I could go on with these things.
Always go on for like two fucking hundred hours.
You know, I want to go in later.
I mean, I really think that we should, as we're recording these,
we should reach a point where we say to ourselves,
you know what, we've literally done enough.
Like we can just pick it up next week.
Like there's no need to, you know, jam stuff in where it does need to be.
Because I don't know.
That's how I feel anyway.
Around this time, it's better to leave on a high note than in a low note.
Even when there's more. Yeah, yeah, that's true.
That's true. What is it?
You know, I heard somebody say something the other day.
It was about like it was why did someone famous like retire
before they like like their career like totally bottomed out?
And I think it was I think it was on Joe Rogan, some comedian or something.
And it was just like because you want to retire
with something left in the tank, because you want to use that gas
you got left to like start your next thing.
And I think like topics on episodes.
I think that applies to that reasonably, reasonably successfully.
It's not like these things go away.
Yeah, exactly.
And I mean, if there's something topical that has to be discussed that week,
that should be like the first thing you discuss anyway.
So I wish I had been more on top of the fucking eating normally shit thing.
But I guess that was a strong finish.
All right, well, then let's get to the fucking voicemails.
Yeah, let's do it.
Read read read.
Yeah, bail, jpe, read the vapors.
Click on the vaporettes.
Listen to my album.
Click on the pump contest.
Digi, put that's true.
Digi, put them in the put them in the show.
Yeah, put links to my fucking put a link to the world over
and the unknown tape and the fuck off mix tape.
Digi, let's get the people something really easy.
Digi, if there was one project that we should that we,
your potential audio listener, music people should go listen to,
what's the one thing we should go listen to?
Oh, see, I'm just saying make it easy for us.
Give us a table.
You know what?
Because everybody's going to like a different one.
All right, Digi, news next episode.
Next episode, I will have the listen to the world over and we will discuss it.
Be there next time.
That's it.
The world over.
Listen to the world over.
There you go.
All right, cool.
That's my personal favorite.
Also on next episode,
I will have read the fucking yokai ghost hunter bullshit.
So right.
Tune in for that too.
Read the real along with me.
This is this is the we're laying seas right now here ladies and gentlemen.
And go to Gibbs fucking pump Kickstarter.
And give him money for plushes.
I want those to be real.
If anyone deserves it,
literally lower your pledge to the PCP to donate.
No, don't do that.
Earn more money.
That's my counter.
Oh, the fucking phone here.
However, 40.
What is it?
$40 for one?
That's not a bad price.
It's about it's about 40 bucks plus shipping.
For custom made plus she that doesn't sound unreasonable to me.
Yeah, I think if any of you have not read the comic and you're thinking,
I don't know about plush, there's plenty of time for you to read it
and then become a fan enough that you will want to buy one.
That's true.
Please consider indoctrinate yourself into buying it by reading the comic.
All right, let's go to the voice bells.
Yeah, here we go.
Okay, now first of all,
now I don't know if this was the thing you guys did last week
while I was away or something,
but there's a guy who named his thing voicemail theme contest.
Is this a thing that started?
Is this happening?
No.
No?
Okay, okay.
Well, then forget that part because he also just called it PCP hype man.
So we'll use this as our prerequisite to the voicemails for today.
So, okay, take it away.
Go.
Everybody, let's get ready for the PCP voice mails.
When I say PC, you say P.
Oh no.
You say P.
P.
When I say voice, you say mails.
Voice.
Mails.
When I say patreon.com, you say slash bensake.
No.
Let's go with the top.
No, no.
Slash bensake, bro.
Bluey baton.
patreon.com.
Slash bensake.
I went to the bathroom, but I'm back.
It was the pep rally.
God damn it, I went to the bathroom.
I went to the bathroom and then I'm like, oh my god, he said bensake.
I gotta rush back and complete the challenge.
You made it in time for the second one.
Well, great.
I'm spent.
I'm tired.
Okay, let's go on.
I'm so tired, everybody.
So tired.
All right.
First real voicemail.
I think this is a follow up to last week or so.
It's called I, or am I a furry?
Okay, go.
Hello again.
It's me, the one that did you call this furry the last time.
Because you said my voice sounded like a furry.
So this is a complicated subject because I don't identify as a furry.
Because my definition of a furry is someone who actually like identifies as an animal.
Like I, in my definition of what a furry is, it's like other kin.
But from what I understand, talking to other people, she called me a furry.
Like people's definitions of furry is different and it appears to be a spectrum.
So I'm curious to know what your definition of a furry is.
Like I don't identify as an animal.
Like it'd be a dog.
If you find that art style to be in any way appealing, you're a furry.
I don't identify, I don't believe I myself am a furry because I don't want to get up
in a fur suit and tell people I'm a dog because I understand I'm not.
So what's your definition of a furry and what makes a furry and what
does not make a furry?
Oh my God, it goes on forever.
So I could have got that up or whatever.
Everyone's insane too.
If you are capable of appreciating the furry art style, you're a furry.
I mean, I could appreciate it.
There is no one furry art style.
You're not a furry just because you like Disney's Robin Hood.
And I do.
Let me tell you.
That's not the furry art style.
Okay, no, okay, listen.
Here's the argument, Ben, you've heard it before.
If you're a furry, if you say you're a furry, if you honestly believe that you are a furry,
it can mean whatever the fuck you want it to mean.
As long as you engage with the community and believe yourself to be one, then you are one.
You don't, furries doesn't...
No, stop, stop, stop.
Furry doesn't mean you have to be in a fur suit.
Furry doesn't mean that you have to draw like other furries.
And it doesn't mean that you have to be a fucking under-otherkin.
It's literally its own word.
What are you insane for thinking that means the same thing?
No, furry just means if you think you're a furry.
Okay, but you just said a bunch of contradictory things.
You said if you think you're a furry, then you are one, comma, if you engage with the community.
Those, like, do you have to engage with the community?
No, but I think it makes sense that if you engage with the community, then you would be a furry.
I think that...
What is that?
It doesn't have to.
What I said, if you think you have yourself as a furry, then you are one.
Let me kick the can down the road a little bit.
Okay, so maybe we can agree that if you think you're a furry, then you're a furry.
But what criteria would you use to decide whether you yourself are a furry?
I mean, it could depend on a lot of issues.
I mean, it's different for every person whether or not you're a furry.
Okay, well, that does gay and retarded.
Why is it gay and retarded?
That if you think that that art is appealing, you're a furry.
It's not that art.
There's a ton of different art in the furry community.
That would include so many people who don't consider themselves furries.
It's not the quality or the design of the art.
If you could magically have two pieces of art that are equivalent in your mind as equally good,
and one has a snout and one is a human, one has a tail, which one do you prefer?
It's a preferential thing.
It's not quantifiable, really.
It's just like would you rather see anthropomorphized animals instead of a human?
I don't know if I would agree with the collars claim that you have to consider yourself an animal.
No, not at all.
Of course not.
I think you could maybe make a case that you're not really a furry until you have a first sona.
No.
I don't know if that's necessarily true.
There are plenty of furries that don't have first sonsa.
Can we back up for a second and remember that what she asked is what do you consider to be a furry?
She didn't ask what is the definition which nobody can pin down at all.
We're all going to have our own meaning for it.
Let's go to the higher authority here, guys.
Urban Dictionary has an extensive definition of furry.
Let me just read the sample.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
Before you do, I just want to say that what I said was assuming that you at least know what a furry is
in an abstract.
Like obviously if you were just some random person and you just thought to yourself randomly,
like you had a seizure and your brain thought of thought that dad had no meaning to it,
I'm a furry now and you had no consequence of what a furry is.
I'm not saying that you are one now.
If somebody was like, well, I'm attracted to men and I love sucking cock,
but I'm not gay because doesn't being gay mean you have to take it in the ass?
I'd be like, no, you're still gay.
Yeah, like that's what this call was like to me.
It's like, hey, I like what I like the things that furries like just not this and this and this.
And it's like, yeah, but I mean, if you like any of it, then that's not I think as long as you're
for a fan of anthropomorphic animals and you consider yourself to be one than your furry.
I guess, I mean, basically, we're down to the to the sorting hat problem of if you don't want to
be one, I guess you aren't one, even if you exhibit all the signs.
Yes, well, okay, well, what if you like the art, but you don't consider yourself to be one?
Well, then you aren't one.
Well, okay, I guess like, I mean, if you if you if you love anime,
I mean, you don't have to believe that you are.
Are you like considered an animaniac?
You don't have to consider yourself to be something for other people to consider you to be it.
That's that's what I was going to say.
I think I think it I would say that it is possible for someone to be a furry and not
know that they are.
But your definition precludes that possibility, Munchie.
Well, I mean, they would not concern to themselves to be one.
No, I mean, the bottom line is.
So you don't you don't think that you don't think that a person can be a furry,
but not realize nobody can be a furry, because there is no definition of it.
It's only in the eye of the beholder.
Like, it's up to you, your definition to say therefore, no, not up to the person.
It's up to every single individual upon observation of a person to determine if that person's a
furry in your mind.
So I mean, I guess that person can say they're not a furry.
I can disagree with them about what they are.
They can feel that they are more correct because they are themselves.
But it will not change my opinion.
We are seeking a robust and universal theory of furredom here.
But it doesn't exist in an intellectual exercise.
It might not exist.
But isn't it isn't it more about the journey?
You know, this is a real definition of furry is the friends we made along this
reminds me of the label of brony, which I personally so I had an OC.
I mean, you know, you could argue that it was like a joke, which it was.
But I mean, you know, it existed.
I made videos about my little pony was, you know, relatively heavily engaged.
I never once claimed or considered myself a brony and still don't think I ever fit
that label personally.
But I'm sure many people would say that I have in hindsight.
I don't think I think it's pretty clear that we were bronies, even if we did take it with
a high sort of but see, I don't agree.
You watched my videos for enjoyment.
Why would that make you a brony?
We watched the show.
That's the only definition that I could even imagine.
Like what other definition is there?
You like the show.
We did it.
We did everything bronies do.
Would you would you say that a little girl who watches the show and enjoys the show
and then watches your videos is a brony?
Absolutely.
I think so.
Yeah.
Is there any way to watch your videos for enjoyment and not be a brony?
If you are watching my videos because you like the show and you like the videos because
they're about the show, that is exhibiting fandom for the show, which is the fandom of
the show is referred to as bronies.
I mean, you know what?
I guess I feel kinship with this person that I feel maybe in my mind, the definition of
brony had additional characteristics that maybe other people don't share.
Maybe I'm just wrong about it, but that's what I think.
This is the thing because back in the ye old days when I had a tumblr, there were certain
people I followed who were not bronies and brony things were like blowing up and people
considered bronies to be rapists at the time.
If you call yourself a brony, you are a rapist because you're an apedophile and it was all
that sort of like oh geez.
So like to say like if somebody asks you are you a brony, you're not just defining yourself
by the show, you're labeling yourself in a way that allows people who have an idea of
what that label is to judge you based on that idea of the label.
I'll say right now.
To not call yourself a brony is just to, you could consider yourself a brony, but if you
say publicly that you're a brony, people will think certain things and if you don't do that,
then that's just a choice.
I think it's stupid to label yourself at all.
I think that I understand why people do it for a sense of community and being a part of
something, but you're just giving everyone else the reins to interpret it as they see fit.
I would rather reject the labels.
If somebody wants to label me, they can believe whatever they want, but I don't want to put
a label on myself because I know that it means different things to different people.
What am I going to explain what I mean every single time I talk to somebody and a lot of
them are just going to disagree with my definition.
I call this the feminist problem because everybody who calls himself a feminist has a
different definition of what it means and they'll explain it to you and they'll say,
well, if you fit this, this, and this characteristic, that means you're a feminist,
but then the next person will say, well, I disagree.
And I just go, how about we just don't call ourselves anything.
Just have a set of beliefs and just be you who has that set of beliefs.
This desire to boil things down into a single word results inevitably in this problem.
So yeah, you've got to boil it back up or boil it down to the actual arguments that you're
trying to make and it's fucking annoying.
When I see a furry, I become a fury and I arch my back and I hiss and I get my claws out
and I'm ready to pounce on this piece.
I just really love insisting to people that they are furries because of the fact that people are
so resistant to it and they're resistant to it and they almost don't know why.
They're like, oh, well, well, surely, surely I'm not, it's not just the lack of liking labels,
it's that they want to believe that they are not so far gone when they are definitely a little
far gone, you know, like I'm in front of May for this constantly because she was like,
she was like had like a fursona kit fox when she was younger and like she insists that she's not
a furry, but like warrior cats are just cats.
They are not anthropomorphized.
Well, yeah, but she had a anthropomorphized kit fox character.
What do you mean they're not anthropomorphized?
Like physically, but they are given explicit personalities, names, and motivations.
I have never, ever seen warrior cats or know what they look like.
It has been explained to me that they look like normal cats.
Sure.
I'm sure they have personalities.
You can anthropomorphize them in other ways, it's not physical.
Of course, but like, is that what we mean when we say furry?
Someone who looks like a literal cat?
It could be.
I mean, I don't think that's that.
Again, we fall into the label problem, because when you think furry, you think
the furry art style, which this does not fall under.
The fun in it is just, it's just pushing people.
It's just pushing up again.
Like it's, it's funny to see, I guess, because of the fact that, you know, I don't like to
label myself, but like if other people want to call me something, it doesn't matter to me that
much.
And so it's really funny to me when people get so upset when you call them something,
like it cracks me up to see how resistant people will be.
To being called something.
And it's just like, dude, just embrace it.
You like furry shit.
Like, who cares?
Like, it doesn't have to say anything about you.
I suppose, but I mean, weren't you just arguing that you hate labels?
So like, why wouldn't they also do the same thing and be like, no, why box me in?
Let me just like my thing and not label it.
It's, it's not a matter of, it's like, you shouldn't care what somebody else is calling you.
You know, it's like.
You kind of want them to accept the label that you're pushing on them.
And you're laughing when they resist it.
I'm laughing because they care so much.
I'm laughing because they're trying so hard to not be called something.
When it doesn't matter, you know, I get you.
I also think it's a unique digi to furries in a way where it's like, it's, it's really like,
I saw this a lot in Bernie's where it's like, dude, what?
Bernie's are not furries.
What are you fucking talking about?
Leave me alone.
It's like, you know, listen, yeah, okay, I get you.
But like, it's clear you're really insecure about it.
It's that I don't consider it an insult to call someone a furry or a brony or whatever.
It's like, I respect all these different things that people like.
So when I see somebody who's like, so resistant to being called that thing,
it implies that you, you yourself don't respect that label.
Like you think, oh, I don't want to be a fucking furry because those guys are weird.
And it's like, yeah, but you're also weird.
So shut the fuck up.
You know, that's why it's funny to me.
Hardcore resident.
Good job.
Excellent.
Okay, well, hey, wait, wait, no, no, before we go to the next voicemail,
I just want to say that this person, first of all, I have no idea if you're a furry or not,
because I don't really know, you know, I mean, what do you think it doesn't mean,
what you think it means.
It's not under other kin.
Do you consider yourself a furry?
You know, ask yourself that.
But also you brought this up by mentioning your voice.
And now you have the furry voice about how furry is the voice.
And this is 100% true.
This is actually factual and this and this is and this is and this is the only red
quick list for being a furry is if you have the furry voice, the furry girl voice.
I'm not trying to shit on this person excessively much, but it's interesting that their defense
for not being a furry is that they do not believe themselves to be an animal,
which I don't really think is much of a defense against.
That's that's like a that's like an extremist view of what a furry is.
A furry is not an other can.
We can all agree those two things are not identical.
I was watching a video that she'll not be named.
Although, although, although actually there's I think what she's thinking of is a
farion because an other can is someone who believes themselves to be like a like an
angel or a demon.
A farion is someone who has like an animal spirit and identifies as an animal.
We can give her credit that she clearly isn't a part of a furry community
because yeah, that's these things like because if you were to ask a furry,
if a furry is the same as another can, they're going to say no,
like there's there's as well say I was I was watching a video and
farion might actually just be a subset of other other can.
So I might personally, by the way, extensive audio from a girl that had the furry voice
and it was extremely amusing the furry voice, which can be broadly also categorized as internet
girl. Like like when you're a girl, when you're a fan artist, like a fan girl artist on the
internet, you just like stop aging.
I'm convinced whenever you like become really interested in something and you're on DeviantArt
slash or Tumblr, your brain and body just stop and you turn into a 13 year old looking
like boy for the rest of your life and you sound like it too.
So you can be like 20, like seven years old, but if you liked warrior cats once,
then you're going to look like you're 13 and sound like you're 13 and act like you're 13 forever.
Like it's just it's like a bizarre genetic disease transmitted through the internet.
And I see it all the time.
We have like a vague lisp and you sort of stutter over your words and and and you just
can't get the words out sometimes.
Wait, wait, wait.
I think I'm going to have to reevaluate some things really soon.
Okay, all right, let's go on to our next fucking call here.
We got a handful more.
Okay, this one's from Chillin' Chocolate.
Old call, man.
Let's let's see what he's got for us.
My life is fucking L and my fucking L is my life.
All right.
You see, there's a girl I like from school, but there's only one.
Do I risk telling her how I feel or do I just leave things on set?
Do I want try to go for a short term relationship?
Say it.
Have a nice time together or, you know, with the like most beautiful and intelligent and
nice person I know or just fucking.
What do I just give up and shrivel?
What do I do?
Okay, hang on.
You know what?
Actually, giving up and shrivel sounds kind of nice.
I liked a girl in my art class in my senior year
and I regretted for years not saying anything to her.
Okay, what is what is this man actually asking us right now?
We're not doing it.
Can you imagine?
He's going to graduate, so like.
Right, he's graduating in a month and presumably he's going into college
and will be separated.
What he's really asking is,
okay, look, I get the idea of wanting to get like emotionally involved with someone
who you will inevitably be separated from relatively shortly.
Do I think this relationship is going to last very long if you get split up,
you know, over a distance?
It's certainly not.
But listen to the real question you're asking.
You're asking is, is it worth putting in the effort to like do a good thing like now,
just because it like won't literally last forever?
You're just asking us for an excuse to not put in the effort to do something you already
want to do.
And you fucking pussy.
You should have already asked her like months and years ago.
Obviously, you've wanted to for a long time.
Even if.
So fucking do it.
Even if all, like, even if you get emotionally invested and you get heartbroken,
at least you might get some like.
Life experience, a starter bitch.
Get your starter bitch out of the way, dude.
I mean, look, heartbreak is going to come.
It's going to happen.
Even if you had a relationship that lasted,
she's going to fucking die on you one day, man.
You're going to have 60 years.
These bitches just be dying on us out here.
I mean, at the very like, if you're really like shrively, shrively,
oh, I can't possibly do it.
Just like write it on a piece of paper like I like you, haha.
And then like, give it to her.
Say, hello, please read this.
And then she takes it and you run away, run away screaming because, you know,
at least then you'll have.
Okay, kind of like, think about the other thing that he brought up.
I guess it's better to do it in a horribly embarrassing way
than not at all.
Think about the way that he frames this though.
He's like, oh my God, do I want to make it awkward
for the last like month among these nine people?
Think about, shoot, the stakes,
the stakes have literally never been lower.
You're about to all split up anyway.
So like what, like, what is your reasoning that like now is a bad time to do it?
It's like the whole school is going to be up.
So it's nine people and you're graduating in a month.
Okay. Why would it even be awkward?
Like you asked her out.
She said, no, who gives a shit.
This transaction happens a million times a day in your school, I'm sure.
These things are awkward, especially for people who haven't done it much.
Okay, but you got to get over that too.
And now is your time to get over it.
I mean, okay, maybe you love her.
You think she's your specialsome pony.
You know, I get it.
I get it, my dude.
But like, there's no reason not to start now.
And I mean, just taking a step further to a place nobody wants to go.
Like I do think that the whole thing of forming relationships
and having them tragically end and feeling devastated by them emotionally,
I think it's ultimately good for you anyway.
And I really think you should just get that shit out of the way in your life
so that you can move on.
And frankly, like talk about a clean slate.
If you're going to college or whatever and getting split up,
then like there's not going to be like, I was weird, dude.
My, I broke up with my girlfriend in college and my senior year,
like she was like around.
And let me tell you, I made it awkward.
But the good news with you is you don't have to do that.
You're going to be free and you will stop.
Here's the another, here's a black pill on relationships.
The second that you like have a fleeting glimmer with a girl
past the girl that you just broke up with.
Like, okay, you have this, whatever, month long relationship,
three month long relationship until you leave.
You're all sad, boo-hoo, I broke up with the girl.
Your mammalian mating instincts will make you not give a fuck.
As soon as you meet some sweet young thing at your college or whatever,
and she's interested, you will no longer give a shit
that that girl broke up with you.
And you've got a new girl because that's just how human beings work.
So there you go.
So do it.
Why literally listen to this message.
Call her immediately.
You have no excuse.
Make her laugh in some funny way and say, ha, ha, wouldn't it be so funny
if we watched some piece of shit movie together?
Ha, ha, epic joke, whatever.
It doesn't matter.
Make up an excuse.
Okay, okay.
People have come to the piece of pee with like girl advice before,
which first of all, lol, but this one has like,
this has evolved in a way where it's like,
this one was like really like not like, you know, good.
This one was like, um, I'm so stupid.
I wanted to yell at this man.
It was like weirdly self-deprecated in a way.
And frankly, I'm not into it.
And I hate you.
I get where this guy is at.
I think the fact that he called in.
He was a little tongue-in-cheek.
I get that.
Let's talk about Ben's Tinder profile.
I think that he maybe will actually get the push from this.
I think maybe he was, like you were saying,
he's looking for an excuse not to,
but I don't think he possibly could have thought
we were going to answer differently than we did.
I agree.
I agree with that.
How many voicemails do I have to piss?
We got like four.
If you want to go piss, I'm going to go piss.
Let's move on.
This is, we've answered this question.
We've definitely addressed this.
Okay.
This one's from, um, I'll, I think it's pronounced,
I'll die corp voicemail bot.
Sure, sure.
I'll die.
Yeah.
Okay.
So let's, uh, let's, let's play it.
Go.
Booting up.
I'll die corporation voicemail bot.
Cool.
Tends to speech.
I hear to tell you that procreation is immoral.
Being brought into existence may allow you to experience good things,
but it also makes you vulnerable to inevitable suffering.
You cannot consent to being born.
This is trivial to point out,
but I fail to see how that makes it any better.
The only justification for birth is that humans
must continue to exist to create a weird utilitarian utopia.
Still, in a world where millions of children are in need of adoption
to be saved from shitty, shitty lives,
what moral justification have you for leaving them in the shit
and making a new person who may not ultimately want to exist
to have a good life in their stead?
Shutting down.
I'll die corporation voicemail bot.
Another one of these fucking unburthers.
Another one of these procreation is immoral people.
No dude, just adopt, just adopt.
And then when there are no more kids to adopt,
then you make another batch of them.
Well, you know, okay.
On this argument, I take sole responsibility
when it comes to procreation for the specific children
that I will be producing,
which I will be producing at some point,
I don't know, not too far from now,
within 10 years I assume.
So like when it comes to those children,
yeah, I accept full moral responsibility for producing them
and putting them on the earth
and them having to deal with like,
struggles and whatnot.
But I mean, look, you could even argue
that most of life is suffering.
However, looking at my life, for example,
I think that the joys I have experienced,
which might not even outweigh the sorrows,
are good enough that I'm glad that I lived.
That's how I feel.
The question is, why make a new person
without their consent versus adopt an existing person
who already exists regardless of consent?
Did they bring up adoption?
No, I didn't.
Yes.
Yeah.
No, it was explicit.
It was explicit.
I have an answer for that for me personally,
which is that there's a lot of things
that are already going to be going on with that kid
by the time you get a hold of them.
I think that's fine.
Like there's a lot of people who,
and maybe even for me,
it would be good to take it a kid like that.
Are you saying there's not going to be
a lot of shit going on with your kid, did you?
Well, it's more of a black slave.
There's not going to be a lot going on with that.
No.
What I mean to say is that all of the programming
will be done by me from the start?
No.
Wrong.
Well, more of it.
He or she will come with a brain that you did not design.
But it's a brain that came from the genetic code of me and May.
So, like, I know.
And you get it at ground zero.
I don't know how much that's really worth in the final analysis.
I think it's worth a lot of my ability to relate to.
What does that really mean?
Like, I think that if I have a kid that's, you know, that's mine,
like, they're going to be a lot more similar to me.
There's going to be a lot more ease in me being able to, you know,
work with it.
Maybe.
I think, I mean, again, not to say that I couldn't maybe find,
like, the perfect kid in an orphanage somewhere.
But like, for the most part, like, you know,
kids who are up for adoption are probably going to be from
pretty shitty backgrounds.
And, you know, it's a lot of it's going to be rehabilitation.
And that's, I mean, still, it's fine.
I think that I think, you know, if somebody's really serious about that as,
like, what they're trying to do as a parent is to just, like,
make society better by creating a, you know, a human functioning as well.
Yeah.
That's probably the best way to go for it.
Like, for me, having a kid, there's, you know,
obviously an element of ego and, like, you know,
wanting to create one that's as close to what I'm hoping to accomplish as possible,
if that makes sense.
I got you.
You know, it's kind of like getting a Pokemon at level one and training it up
versus getting the same Pokemon at level 23.
Your BioKid is going to have better EVs, is what you're saying.
Yes.
That's exactly what it looks like.
Yeah.
Now I get it.
Let me boil this down to one phrase.
And it's that, uh, I care more about my shit than your shit.
And I make no apology for it.
And this applies on a genetic level.
You know, I just, yeah, like, did you say an vanity is definitely a part of it.
But also it's the fact that I plan on really optimizing my child rearing.
And I mean that by, like, being as good a dad as possible.
And, like, pragmatically speaking, even if I get a kid born one day old,
I think there's a couple issues of, like, uh, you know,
I don't know how much will be done to that kid before I get them.
They're probably going to have had some shit done to them already.
And I'm really looking to optimize my kid experience.
And it's simple.
You just, you can undo all that.
You just put them through unbirthing therapy.
That's fair.
I'll also say this.
Well, look, I'm, I'm, I'm, you know, I'm, I'm, I'm proud of my genes.
I think, uh, my, my family, my genes too.
My family's pretty long lived.
I'm pretty smart of a guy.
You know, May comes from a really tall family and she's tall for a girl.
So like, we'll probably have some pretty tall kids, you know,
probably taller than me.
So that's cool.
You know, like it's, it's a good, I think it's a good combination of genes.
And I'm like, I'm excited to see if I can create something better than myself.
What a weird way to think about it.
I mean, that is like the issue.
Isn't that just a completely normal way to approach it that everyone has
for all of human history?
It's the unconsciously normal way.
Cause like the only reason we like certain looks or like,
Oh, this person looks good.
This person looks healthy or whatever.
They're muscular.
That is all because they have good genes.
Right.
Therefore our kids will be human.
Humans are tribal, man.
I want my kids to generally look like me, you know,
I just think that's a normal thing to want.
I thought that like my genes were really bad or dangerous.
I would be a lot more hesitant to, I would probably want to adopt instead.
Like I would think, okay, let me find a kid who, you know, who needs a home.
But like if I feel like my offspring will benefit the human species, you know,
it's very egotistical to think.
But it's like, I don't know.
I feel some level of confidence in my genealogies deservedness to continue.
Okay.
But like it's not having the people who have,
who had Hitler's genes said they'll never have children.
Well, not, not having shitty genes,
like not having genes that will fuck a kid up.
It's not like a rare thing.
You like lots of people have normal, functional, healthy genes.
I mean, my genes, like, I don't know.
Let's just say that I had, you know,
I reproduced with like my current girlfriend,
you know, with Michelle or whatever, if I did that,
like there's potential that our particular combination of genes
resulted in some like awful thing for the,
like it's always possible.
You don't know.
I'm just saying, I don't know, might not go that way.
And it's just, I like familiarity.
So I'm going to go with kids that are my genetic kids.
Just seems, you know, like a logical way to go.
Now, now if you, to make it a larger argument though,
like if this isn't the net benefit for the world,
now on that, I get that argument that,
that's fair to look into more to like, you know,
deal with kids who are in poverty to maybe adopt them.
I'm not even opposed to adopting in general,
but I'm not going to lie selfishly.
I just want some kids that have my genes
because you know what, it's just,
I think I got a pretty good brain going on here.
And like my brain patterns,
obviously largely shaped by genes.
So it seems reasonable to pass on.
Here's what I mean.
I get, but it's not your brain.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
It's not like, yeah, maybe you'd have,
maybe you'd have a kid with a great brain.
So what?
It's not your brain.
It's someone else's brain.
Oh, well, well, I bet I think that,
that's a fair question, but I think it ties into the,
like how is it that humans,
like what's the purpose of human existence?
I mean, probably to exert our influence
over the world in some way.
And like they say that, you know,
reproduction is the kind of immortality
that humans can obtain.
So like I'm interested in propagating my genes to the future.
If for no other reason than just the vanity of like,
I still kind of continue to exist in this one way.
And you know, I could do that by,
let's just say being a teacher
and like instilling my values on kids.
Okay.
That's a great way to do it.
I just think another way is also genetically.
So I'm interested in doing that to cover all my basals.
I definitely see that there is like,
an argument to be made for like,
your child will not necessarily be exactly
how you want it to turn out.
Whether you rear them from your own genes
or whether you adopt them.
It could be that the person you adopt
will love you exactly the same way
and will be even a better person in the end.
But you can't know that either way.
And so in the decision making process,
selfishness is really the only thing that tips the scales.
And I mean, I'm selfish in all other aspects of my life.
Why not this one?
Yeah.
I mean, if you're extremely moral,
if you hold that higher than selfishness,
then you could go either way.
I think I wouldn't like besmirch anyone
for choosing one or the other, really.
Yeah.
I mean, I wouldn't say, you know,
I don't think it's wrong to want to have your own kids.
I do think that probably the ultimate moral thing to do
is to adopt a kid that needs a family
rather than produce a new one.
I get that.
Yeah, I'll say that.
I mean, and we also have to look at it this way.
I mean, in an ideal system, I think,
we would have some way of saying like,
okay, we've measured your benefit to humanity.
You should have kids, and you should not.
You should adopt.
And like, there's only so many kids who need to be adopted.
Someone still has to make babies.
You want to know my hot take.
This is my hottest take, and I think everyone will hate it.
And no one will like me.
I just think we should abolish families.
I really think that society would be better without...
Yeah, I think society would be better without them,
and we wouldn't miss them when they were gone.
I mean, look, to entertain that, okay,
so like, how do people get raised then?
What's the new model?
Well, wait, we don't have fucking state barracks.
I've got this great idea.
I don't know.
We should get these big furries called Lucises.
Literally, it would be cool.
Well, I don't like...
I mean, I don't like...
I don't know.
I think the fact that trolls are all like birthed in batches
and sort of raised as like a collective community is great.
I think that's awesome.
I think that would be so much cooler if it were like that.
And you know...
The trolls came out really great.
Well, they were fucked up because they were ruled by like a despot.
Yeah, the Alpha timeline was all right.
Yeah, the, you know, like people have in families,
they have like these like nationalistic allegiances.
They have family allegiances.
They have like racial allegiances.
Honestly, we should just fucking obliterate the family unit,
abolish culture.
We won't miss it when it's gone.
We'll have a new culture.
All cultures die eventually.
And if we just like...
We're like, fuck all these old cultures.
We're having a new one that is like communal
and is like shared and is not like family based.
And it's called Endless War.
We could keep the old stuff.
Like we wouldn't...
We could keep like...
We could keep like a...
I don't know, Mexican salsa dancing.
That doesn't have to go away.
You know, all the cool stuff we like about culture
doesn't have to go away just because we like...
We don't have...
Those cultures don't like actually exist anymore
because we abolish the family and are all living
in like a unified, like beautiful utopia
where we're all brothers under, you know, whatever.
Whatever like anarcho-communist regime we've established.
Ben, you gotta write a book.
You could be like the iron rand
of the authoritarian left or something.
Didn't they already have that
by the name of Karl Marx or something?
Okay, okay.
I don't know.
I know I say all this stuff
and then I get nervous when I say,
it's like, wait, wouldn't we have to have
like a really fucking totalitarian state to establish this?
And then I try and think about like,
well, how could we do all this without that?
And I'm sure there's a way to do that.
I don't like the...
If you actually change everyone's opinion
so that they wanted to be in that system,
I mean, I don't know how you do it,
but if you did that, if you convinced people
it was for the best.
I mean, the same way you would get just
a regular communist society.
Not on machines.
I just think families are bad.
Well, you know, even taking...
Yeah, I guess that's a fair question.
Because we have a fucking fractured...
Okay, well, this is...
First of all, they fractured society.
That's bad.
We have...
You have family allegiances,
nationalistic allegiances.
That's bad.
I don't think allegiances are...
Oh, man, I sure love being a Finn.
But Ben...
And I hate those goddamn Swedes.
Just because you have...
We don't...
Are you saying you want this to be like a global thing?
This ties into my thing
about how I think inheritance should be illegal
because it's like...
Illegally mean?
And unjust.
I said illegal.
And I know this has been brought up to you before, Ben.
But I mean, you are...
I mean, you're gonna inherit from our parents.
So I mean, is that...
Yes.
Oh, God.
Oh, I participate in...
I criticize society and yet I participate in it.
What a fool.
I mean, what...
Okay, but I mean, how would you...
If you could have complete control,
given the fact that you're going to inherit now,
what system would you replace that with
that you'd prefer?
Okay.
Parents don't raise their kids.
No one inherits anything.
Everyone gets UBI.
There you go.
Okay, so basically you're saying
forget inheritance, instead we'll do like a UBI system.
Forget inheritance.
You don't inherit anything from your parents
because you don't need anything
because our society makes enough money
to provide everyone with the necessities
without having their parents make it for them
and then give it to them.
You know, Ben, I'll take your argument.
I accept it as...
I try to accept it at its most reasonable position,
granting that all of this can be done
and that like human nature will like allow for it.
I would still argue simply that I think
that there's a good amount of utility
in both like the familial structure
and the nation state.
And I just...
I have not yet been convinced
that a better system is the one you described.
I think.
And that's right.
I think that we could replace...
We could replace the family structure
and the nuclear family
with a new, more egalitarian, more just society.
And we would look back...
And we would look back on late capitalism.
We would look back on when we all lived in...
And when we're all like...
When we were all just raised
by whatever fucking chuckle fuck
happened to give birth to us, what the fuck?
We would look back on that and say,
wow, what like barbaric backwards times?
I just don't feel like the state
is particularly competent at these things.
But okay.
But you know what?
I get your point.
It could...
Maybe one day.
What if it wasn't a state thing?
What if it was just like a sort of
like democratic like community run process?
What if it wasn't imposed from on high person?
I would prefer that, certainly.
I mean, they already say it takes a village
to raise a child.
What if communities just got together
and like established like community centers
where kids were like, you know, raised from birth?
I don't know.
I like it.
I get you.
I feel like inevitably there'd be some like kind of human nature
things that we weren't programmed to deal with
that we might...
We already do that.
Humans are programmed to do all kinds of horrible things
that we don't let them do
because they're fucked up and ruin everything.
That's fair.
Just like the family does
and just like inheritance does
and just like all this shit does that we do now
and one day we'll say,
thank God we don't do that anymore.
Well, I guess we'll say.
That's what I...
I guess we'll say.
That's my hot take.
I...
Fair enough.
Yep.
Okay, sound up in the comments
if you think I'm a fucking psychopath or what.
I mean...
Guys, enough of this.
Enough of this.
Enough.
Every single episode of the Pokemon anime
is for free on like the Pokemon website.
I've just found that you can just watch them all.
God, that's like thousands of episodes.
But not in Japanese, right?
But the Pokemon Company International...
No, it's not in Japanese.
It's English.
Did this just happen?
I mentioned the first episode.
It said...
No, I just saw like somebody linked it and it was like...
You know, I have never seen episode two of Pokemon
and I've always wanted to.
Where...
Look, there's got no views.
Nobody knows about this.
Please put a link in the show notes.
Okay, let's move on to our next call.
We got, I think like three more or something.
Okay, here we go.
So this is Don't I Repeat Do Not Mine At Night.
Okay, go.
Is this Animal Crossing?
No, it's Minecraft.
We turn.
Can I just boobernate?
I didn't know GLaDOS played Minecraft.
GLaDOS from Portal 2.
Portal 1, in fact.
I think I understood the first like three words of that.
Did anyone...
I could not make it.
I literally could not make out a word of that.
Yeah, was that Miku?
Who was that?
It was Red Boy Genius.
All right, next voicemail.
I thought that you guys might be able to get meaning out of it
that I couldn't figure out.
Okay, all right.
Unfortunately, it didn't pan out that way.
But I also just thought it sounded nice.
It didn't pan pizza out that way.
Oh.
It did sound nice.
Okay, so there's the plus.
I did enjoy it aesthetically.
So I'll give it that.
Okay, let's move on.
Oh, you know what?
This one is actually directly for Mage
and since she's not here, I'm going to skip it.
So sorry, Ultra Violet.
Wait, why?
Oh, it's for Mage.
It was, you know what?
I mean, I could play it.
I could play it.
It's for Mage, but...
Well, maybe we could wait.
Well, see, yeah, I'll just play it.
She won't be here for like two weeks.
All right, fuck it. Here we go.
Play.
We can shit on her.
So, Mage, you claim to like Purple, yeah.
I think we're going to have to see if that's really true.
Now, you may have heard of this little wavelength
called Ultra Violet.
That's right.
Ultra Violet, also known as Purple II.
Now, normally Purple II isn't visible to the human eye,
but it turns out that that's actually
because your eyes are betraying you.
In fact, you can remove the lens from your eye,
and suddenly you will be able to see Purple II.
It's probably not safe for the eye.
You will still be able to see a new form of Purple.
So, tell me, Mage, is it worth it?
Is it will you destroy your eyes in the pursuit of Purple?
Is that true?
I like your answer.
Okay, I've never heard this thing about removing the lens,
but I have heard that there are some people
who's like eye cones are sensitive to a slightly wider range.
So, some people can see somewhat into the Ultra Violet spectrum,
and apparently, according to them,
it looks like the drum roll, please,
a slightly like white pale purplish color.
Sounds worth.
Yeah.
Cool.
I don't know about this lens removal thing.
Is it like the lens filters light in some particular way?
Maybe it blocks.
Maybe it.
I mean, it wouldn't be crazy because Ultra Violet light,
if it's harmful to your eye,
maybe your lens might have evolved to block some of it
to protect you from it.
That's true.
It doesn't.
Maybe.
I've never heard that before.
Wow, I don't care.
Let's listen to the next voicemail.
Yeah, great.
All right, all right.
Oh, you talk about don't care.
We got a call here from Oopsy Bobo.
Now, this man left a couple of messages.
I forget what the deal was.
I think this was for you, Munchy.
Let's see what he has to say.
Oh, I'm not going to like it then.
All right.
So my dumb ass fucked up,
and I wasn't sure if the message quality was great,
so I'm going to record this one again.
Munchy, fuck you.
This is a thread.
This is not a voicemail.
If you don't let my...
If you don't let my fucking message go in,
the one about the weed,
I'll get a fucking whore of minions,
and Oospamiu is smoking the weed message.
Just constantly, man.
There's just nothing you can do about it.
So, fuck you.
All right, so if I remember correctly,
this guy called in last week,
and I didn't put his message in
because it was really terrible,
and so now he's mad at me
for not putting in his message.
So I just want to give a shout out to Oopsy Bobo.
We're going to put this guy in the voice jail
because you had the audacity to appear on the show
and be a piece of shit,
and you are not funny,
and also you're from South America,
and you have not followed on the promise
that your forefathers gave you
with the glorious history that you have betrayed.
So good job, and you're going to the voice jail.
That's fair. His name is just Bobo,
and Oopsy was like the title,
but yeah, okay, Bobo, there you go, buddy.
This is exactly why we need the wall.
All right, we got our last message here.
The Panama wall.
That's the one.
Okay, game board, Gaylord, part three,
calling in.
This is our final one.
Okay, let's go immediately.
Captain Gaylord, if we don't see any results
of this foolish while you started,
who will prove the plow to you and your crew?
Don't worry, everyone, as they say.
This is definitely the day of the spades.
See your shit back.
What's the status of our latest missile?
Ah, Cap, this just came in.
I believe we hit him.
Yes, we did it.
We hit him.
Don't celebrate just that.
It might hit us back.
We moved.
We got that.
Bobo, gay, Bobo, Bobo.
Bye, Colleen.
They missed.
Yes.
Hooray.
Yes, we know.
We did it, boys.
We finally got the upper hand.
Lucky for us that we are celebrating
a royalty-free use.
We...
No, because the game board is so small,
we can't lose.
Actually, the game is played on a 25-tile grid,
with 11 of those tiles occupied by our fellowships.
The odds are hitting are probably so high,
so that if you would be playing in a, you know,
a weak paternal house, it is stupidly complicated.
Anyone with two grandtiles could have figured that one out.
We did this to ourselves.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, we have no one to blame ourselves.
I feel like I'm shooting a brand new story teller.
Do you?
Bobo.
What?
Oh, it's a hit.
I think.
He hit our Death's Reader.
Yeah, you know what?
You know what?
You hit all of our submarines.
Oh, they were all stacked on top of each other,
like at different depths.
And now we're dead.
Oh, no, you won.
So good.
I guess that's the end of the game.
Yep, that's right.
Hey, guys, if you try to be real of my ass, Batman 2,
I want to know that...
I want you guys to know that I personally hate you,
and a fucking please unironically kill yourself.
Like, with a news or a gun.
Anyway, humanly possible, end your own lives.
Oblivion?
Nobody can be riddle my ass, Batman 2.
Oh, this episode's not getting monetized.
That's for sure.
Oblivion, if you could try to make that audible in some way,
that would be great.
Apparently, Oblivion finds the original call audio
and puts that in instead of the SoundCloud version or something.
Oblivion does something.
It's the same fucking thing, but okay, if you can do that, great.
No, he told me that he does some shit with the voicemails
that just makes them better.
Okay, fantastic.
That man is a god and a king.
Okay, well, anyway, that's the last thing
we got to sit through on this fucking episode of the BCP.
You're free now.
You're free.
Wow.
We did it.
It was really great.
And then some like anarcho-communist shit came,
and then the voicemails took like 500 hours.
And you know what?
That's fine.
Only because we talked about it.
Specific questions for whatever.
Go read, bail, jpe, and pledge to the punk plushie Kickstarter.
And I just want to clarify, that's all true, do that.
And if you left a message and it didn't get on,
I want to confirm it's because it wasn't good enough
because I was looking for good things.
And there was a dirt.
I mean, you heard the quality of what we did end up accepting.
So you were even worse than this.
Oh, imagine that.
Imagine being in that position.
Okay, anyway, patrons.com slash the procrastiners people.
We just made a new fucking bonus episode.
It was Game of Thrones.
Me, Tom, and Gibb talked extensively
about everything you could possibly want to know.
Are you like mashing a burger, meat, or something?
Like you make it a patty over there?
I'm sorry.
Was that visible?
Sorry, okay.
So what I'm doing is I've got a bag of, a plastic bag of candy.
I know I'm trying to puncture it with like the sharp end of a pin
so I can get the candy out
so I can eat some delicious gummy drops.
Well, do that at your time.
All right.
But it sounded instead like you were crushing a burger
between your fingers.
At cpcrastinators on Twitter people.
Follow us there for links and whatnot.
And give us money, $5 bonus episodes, $1 patron lounge.
Have fun, hang out with us, be a cool guy.
There you go.
That's all you need to know.
All right.
That's it.
We're out of here.
We'll see you next week, people.
Check out, check out the new vapor.
It's up on stcomics.com right now.
Take all the goddamn links with us.
We all do a million things.
We're all cool guys with cool shit.
Correct.
The amount of the two will be done by now.
Go check out.
Oh my God.
That's that school.
We can't be so good.
All right.
I'll see you later, people.
Have a beautiful night.
Bye.
Have a beautiful time.
I love you.
Oh.
What the hell is wrong with me?