I won't bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Hello and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Yoncast.
What is snort? This episode is gonna be...
Well, you may change your tune when I tell you about my new character.
Jesus.
It's my new character. Do you want to meet them?
Sure, yeah. Lay it on me.
It's the Australian alien.
Scary.
That's just sounds like...
It's the Australian alien.
That's just sounds like a regular Australian.
Oh, well, they're all aliens to me.
Is he like an alien because he's emigrated to, you know, the West?
He emigrated from space to Australia, and he learned G'day, and he talks like...
Oh, wait, so it put prawns on the Barbie?
I think they say shrimp. I mean, they're two distinct animals.
I heard someone say, we don't say shrimp, we say prawns.
And I thought to myself, but they're two different animals.
Yeah.
So really, I just learned that Australians are stupid, and they don't know the difference between those two things.
As far as I think, the prawns are the bigger ones.
The shrimps are the tiny, tiny ones you can have in like a shrimp fried rice or whatever.
And prawns at a restaurant are like the bigger ones that you rip the head off of and eat
with your hands like an animal.
Time for some animal facts.
Okay, in the UK...
Australia and New Zealand and Ireland.
Just do it.
Type hashtag giveaway in the comments.
Figure out how to spell it.
That's got to use some like diacritic marks that normally you only see in like Taiwanese Mandarin or some shit.
Some like reverse accent marks or something.
In the UK, Australia, New Zealand and Ireland, prawn is the general term used to describe both true prawns and shrimp.
Oh, well, okay.
So they just don't understand the differences between things.
They just boil it down.
Well, you boil it down in the other way.
Simplify.
They utilize the blunt, the banal, the simplistic.
They're fascists is what they are.
They're basically like lobsters, like lobster nephews.
Oh, oh, oh, little fly.
I've missed it.
With your chopsticks?
Yeah.
I have big meaty chopsticks that sounds like hands clapping when I click click them.
Damn, fruit fly.
Never eat fruit.
Then you won't get flies.
Somebody forgot to take my garbage out in my kitchen.
So there's a bunch of fruit flies in my kitchen.
They have mostly not come into my room, but once in a while, I see one and it pisses me off.
The garbage, garbage collection only comes, garbage collection only comes once a week.
So I think to all the other cowards that live in my apartment, the thinking goes, oh, well, well, guess the garbage just has to sit here now.
I know that we could literally just use the neighbor's garbage can.
We could just take it out and put it in the neighbor's garbage can.
I think everyone else just doesn't know that.
But nobody else cares because I'm the only, I live adjacent to the kitchen and everyone else lives a floor up and they probably just aren't that worried about it.
So it's really mostly a me problem.
So I guess, I guess I'm the one that has to deal with it.
You got to be the bigger man and do all the work for them.
Got to be a bigger man and make your life worse.
I have been like the only one who has been like had dishes.
I have not seen like hardly any.
Everyone else will use like a plate.
Everyone else will, there will see like a burner, like a pot on the stove.
I won't see anyone else's plates anywhere.
So I guess I'm the only one who's like needs to be doing the dishes and stuff lately, which is strange.
I don't know what everyone else is doing.
I have no idea what's going on with those people.
I've heard people like to just forever use and buy paper plates instead of ever doing dishes, which is insane.
I do that.
Like I tried to do that.
I bought paper plates so that I would do that.
But you know what I mean?
It takes like two seconds under a tap for a dish to be like scrubbed unless you leave it for a week.
Yeah.
It's like so much more extra work and money.
I can't understand using paper plates unless it's like, oh, it's a party and we need a bunch of plates for people.
It's like two dollars for like a hundred plates.
So it's really not that much more.
Yeah, but like that's two hundred plates worth of mass that will need to be moved around or put on something or thrown away.
And it's just like a hassle.
Water goes straight down the drain.
You say that.
You say that, but it's in practice, it's not.
You're killing the rain forest, Ben.
You're killing the Amazon rain forest.
I don't think that's true.
Paper plate is equal to one tree being thrown into the ocean for no reason.
That's very inefficient.
That's a very inefficient logging system we've got.
Wow.
Someone should do something about that so I can just keep burning through these paper plates.
You know, Kylie Jenner.
Kylie Jenner might be taken, you know, three minute long flights on her private jet.
Have you looked inward lately, Ben, and asked yourself, yeah, but I'm using like almost one whole paper plate a day.
It's fucked.
Who am I to judge?
Anyway, I found a, I have found a new, one of the places I was apartment hunting.
I spoke to the landlord and gotten confirmation that, yeah, I'm good to move in in September.
So that's pretty good.
I haven't signed the lease yet, but it's like semi-officially like, yeah, we're just waiting for someone else to be ready.
But then, yeah, you're good to go.
So I'm excited about that.
I don't have to, I don't have to spend the last month frantically looking like I did last time.
That's great.
Yeah, it's pretty good.
It's a little, the place I found is a little further away from like the center of town, but not that much further.
And it's a little more expensive, but it's not like, it's like, it's like $25 more a month.
So like whatever, maybe $50.
It's fine.
Yeah.
I'll be moving out of this shithole dump, but I can't believe I spent a fucking year here.
What a disaster.
What a nightmare.
It flew by and I feel like I got, I did get the things mostly done that I meant to get done,
but I kind of expected that was kind of like the minimum that I hoped to accomplish and that was all that I got done.
So, you know, that's fine.
Fucking, I've been, I've been talking to, I've been doing the thing where I talk to someone who works at a company through Alibaba,
trying to get the book printed.
And it's really annoying because this person is on China time and I'm on America time.
And so we're like 12 hours different.
So like, I'll ask one simple question and then I'll have to wait an entire day to get the answer.
And she doesn't answer on weekends, so I can basically ask five small questions per week.
And then...
So is it much like money wise?
Is that like a much preferable way to do it than before?
I did find one company that seems like a lot cheaper.
Yeah, so it seems worth it.
Yeah, other...
I mean, I have notes right here.
Other companies.
Western companies and some Chinese ones too.
I think they were going to...
They were going to end up costing for like a hundred copies.
It was going to end up costing like...
$18 to $20 per copy.
I think maybe the lowest would have been like $15.
And that's not including shipping.
Or profit.
Yeah, that's just the cost of production.
This one...
Let me see if I can...
Fucking Alibaba is a little bit...
It like boots me out and makes me sign in over and over again.
This one's going to be...
Well, it's going to be maybe like $11.
Probably less than $13.
Maybe $13 to copy before shipping.
That's better.
Yeah, I might be able to get that down a little bit more depending on like paper choice.
So this seems like the best option, yeah.
I think shipping might be like $2 a copy.
It's at $100, so...
It'll be $142 to ship $100 pieces.
So yeah, I think this is the most economical.
You're going to get a sample first?
Yeah, I just need to order samples.
Did I mention that I...
Yeah, I was fucking around with the color filter to try and get the greens looking as good as they could look in CMYK print format.
And this is really annoying.
I made a few that I liked and I printed out like big pages.
They were like oversized pages.
They had to tape pieces of paper together to fit it all on there, but they showed like six different color styles.
And I printed them out so I could actually look at them like on paper to see, you know, an idea of what they'd look like.
And I was going to bring those to RFC KCON, which happened this week.
I was going to show people them and ask them their opinions, like which of these colors do you think looks the best on the page.
And I forgot to bring them, so I didn't get to do that.
I mean, I guess it's fine.
I mean, I guess I can just pick myself and I...
In the end, I have to pick myself anyway.
But Darn, I meant to do that. Oh well.
So yeah, but I have them printed out.
How was RFC KCON?
RFC KCON was really fun.
I guess it lasted three days.
I was there for the evening of the last day, I think.
And there were a bunch of people there that I had met at the previous RFC KCON, the one that had happened right before RADCON 4.
And there were a lot of new faces of people, some of which were newer players and some of which were longtime players who I had not met before.
And that was very fun and everyone was very cool and we had a great time.
And I brought the slime bottles and everyone loved them.
And we made slime and tonics, the classic RFC K beverage.
Oh, you actually had the slime with tonic water?
Yeah, I brought tonic water and I put the slime in it.
And it looked great, by the way, because I made the slime to glow under a black light.
And as it turns out, tonic also glows under a black light because quinine is fluorescent.
So it looks awesome.
So did you have a black light to shine on them?
I did, I did. I brought one, yeah, to show it off a little bit.
Yeah, it's great. Quinine glows like a teal blue color and the slime glows kind of yellow-green, obviously.
It's funny, you know, you pour the glass, you pour the tonic and it glows blue.
And then you pour the slime in and the slime sort of, in the water, it kind of gets all noodley before it starts to blend in.
And then you mix it together and it becomes kind of a turquoise, blue-green, glowy mixture.
Very funny, very cool looking.
It just worked out that way. It just worked out pretty good.
Sounds epic.
It was epic.
Kip made dumplings. There were so many dumplings at Homemade Dumplings at RFC K-Con.
I guess this was RFC K-Con. I think it was number eight.
There was some confusion about which number it was.
I had not been to all, a lot of them had been, like, in other places.
So I had not been to them, but I think I've been to, like, two or three before.
Anyway, there were so many dumplings. They were fantastic.
Yeah, I met people and saw people again and it ruled, it ruled.
Shoutouts to Slimehouse.
Shoutouts to Slimehouse yet again.
Another successful, another successful gathering.
Yeah.
Nice.
I gave some people some pins and stuff.
I brought party favors.
Handed them out, like Santa Claus or, sorry, like Phoebus.
Or no, Phoebus is like anti-Santa Claus.
Phoebus is the, yeah, Saint Phoebus is the Slimernalia patron deity who steals people's stuff on Slimernalia, as everyone knows.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah.
So that's how that was.
Well, cool.
I don't really follow.
The only thing I've heard about RFCK recently is that Alleyoop is a character and, like, somebody's playing Alleyoop.
Or, you know, Alleyoop is in Endless War, role-playing, doing things, exclamation points, smoke.
What's the thing? What's the mouth thing?
Smoking?
Oh, yeah.
Vape.
And, yeah, that seems fun.
I like that.
Yeah, that is pretty funny.
I don't, yeah, I don't really keep up with, like, the game, but there was game talk at the con, and there were some ideas thrown around for gameplay features that I won't say what they are.
But there are plans to make the game more fun.
Let's just say that.
The game's gonna get, the game's gonna get really fun.
That's all I'm gonna say.
What does that mean?
I don't know.
Nobody knows.
If you slime in the game, you slime for real?
No, that's ridiculous.
But slime now exists as a real physical thing.
Slime always existed as a real physical thing you could have.
You just had to know where to look for it.
No, I must not say anymore.
I must not break my silence.
Are they gonna add the slime Titanic?
What?
The slime Titanic.
How would they do that?
They get on a boat, and then the slime bergs sink it.
And it's just a slime version of the Titanic.
It's, it's, it would be like, it would be like 9-11.
Like, it's just a disaster that everyone really likes a lot, and they replicate it.
Yeah, it's a disaster that everyone really likes a lot, and it happens every, every like month or so.
It's like, oh, we built a new, we built a new slime Titanic.
Time to go sail deliberately into a slime berg.
There's a slime berg just floating right off the coast, and we just send a new Titanic into it,
a new slime Titanic into it every, every so often, yeah, every in-game month or whatever.
At the bottom of the Grand Canyon, there's like a growing pile of Titanic's.
Slime Titanic's.
And then it becomes an island of slime Titanic's.
And then people, the drive more slime Titanic's into that island.
Yeah.
Okay, this is, no, it wasn't, that was not the idea, but, you know, we should add,
that should, that should go on the list.
Very on brand.
Uh, Lamal.
Good, good stuff.
All right, I hope, um, I hope the devs are taking notes.
Uh, what else, what else did I do this week?
Um, yeah.
Has it been hot over there?
Yes, it has been hot.
It was, although I have just been, I've just been staying inside with my AC room.
Haven't, just haven't been dealing with it.
Yeah, I got a window, I got a window AC.
We had the big heat wave over here in the UK.
Yeah, is that, uh, still going on?
It was only like two days that we'll forecast to be above 40 degrees.
Yeah.
Um, which is like 106, 107, I think Fahrenheit.
And, uh, that's past, but it's still pretty hot.
It's like normal summer right now.
It's like, oh, this is comfortable.
I can stand outside for like a second.
There are, there are, there exist cool parts of shade.
When the, when the, um, heat wave was coming through, it was like, I just had to,
had to lie there and take it because there was no way to cool down.
Everything was the same temperature outside and inside.
I mean, outside was a bit more hot, but like usually in this house,
there's one room that doesn't, the sun doesn't hit from the outside,
unless it's like a sunset.
That blows.
So it's usually like the cold room.
And it's like, oh, if you need to cool down, you go in there,
but that was like swaltering.
That blows.
So it was just a, it was just a big old like, whoa.
And I saw on the news, there were people like frantically, like stupidly frantically
getting in their cars and driving to the beach so that they could be in the water,
only to end up stuck in traffic because everybody else had that idea.
And they were just in a heat wave in a car stuck in traffic.
It's the stupidest thing you could have done.
And I'm pretty sure people died.
Because, wait, they died because they were in their car?
I mean, I don't actually know if people died because they're in their car.
There were some amount of deaths relating to heat exhaustion and,
because, you know, AC is not coming in the UK.
I heard there were going to be deaths.
So there was a, I don't think I saw like a death counter anywhere.
I guess people, the news didn't really want to say anything like that.
But I heard about like an occasional this and that.
It's like, oh, shit, that's tragic.
This country is not prepared for the climate crisis.
Well, it sucks, it sucks to be you.
I say drinking deep, deep from my chalice of homegrown American motor oil.
From my refrigerant liquid.
Yeah, that's pretty bad.
Not really much to say about the heat wave.
It was just like, wow, we got a new record, guys.
41 or 41.5.
It's a degree centigrade.
You should be proud.
We did it.
We did it, Reddit.
Shattering the glass ceiling.
The greenhouse ceiling.
Thank you.
Thank you, JK.
It's blessing.
The gods were angry at all the tariffs.
That's why it happened.
True.
I don't know why God's on our side now, but he is.
He's on your side, but he won't do anything about it.
Like the Democrats.
Much like the damn labor party.
Damn labor.
I'm waiting for them to say, I don't know.
Well, I guess I don't know.
I'm not really paying too much attention to what they're saying,
but nothing catches my attention.
Keir Starmer has like such a boring aura around him.
He is such a politician from the perspective of a four-year-old
who just wants to watch fucking Nadi or whatever.
Wait, wait, you just want to watch what?
Nadi.
It's a children's TV show.
It's like a little character with a jingly bell on the end of his long hat.
And he nods his head.
Another character I'm sure you're making up just to troll me
and make me look like a fool.
Yeah, all right.
Rolly Polioli, remember that one?
This is like the British equivalent of like drop bears.
You tell foreigners they're real and they just believe you.
It's true.
I used to be a big naughty head.
When it comes to like...
Nadi heads rise up.
Nadi heads in chat.
I was like, that was my favorite show.
Some people like Postman Pat.
I did like Postman Pat and Feynman Sam and fucking, you know,
Thomas the Tank Engine, the greats, Teletubbies.
I'm a student of the classics.
Yeah, there's Teletubbies and stuff.
But Nadi was like my favorite.
I was a naughty head.
I couldn't say right.
Yeah.
There was Big Ears, the big guy.
He's like a, like Garden Um...
Oh, like an elf.
I really can't remember.
It's like an elf.
Yeah.
It looks like, it looks like a, kind of looks like he should be
in one of those Rudolph the Red Nose Reindeer movies.
Kind of.
I actually have not, it's one of those like, such early memories
that I kind of remember what it was about or what anything was.
Yeah.
I probably don't know the theme song.
I could maybe remember it, but like...
The fastest trousers, Nadi in Toyland.
It's an episode title that I see here.
It was like, the pipeline was Nadi, Pingu.
And then the hoops, no.
The hoops, the hoops were good because they had like the little...
What are you talking about?
The hoops had like the little, the three little metal guys who were like,
they've got like clangy heads that look like hi-hats.
Hi-hat head robot people.
And they go like, and then there's the hoops.
It's the hoops.
I see the hoops.
The hoops are like muppets.
The hoops are muppets, but there's like these robots.
I can't remember what they were called.
Well, I see these creatures.
Oh, apparently this is made by the Jim Henson company.
That's interesting.
I think we had a toy of one of the clanger head face guys.
Is that really what they're called, clanger heads?
I don't know.
I can't remember.
I don't think we knew what the names were.
They were just sort of like talk incomprehensibly,
and then they would show like a skit with a human child interacting with a muppet.
And it'd be like, oh, we're learning about the woods.
What can you find in the woods, squirrels?
Oh my fucking god.
What can you find in the woods?
Oh, dead body.
Oh, we can't show that on children's television.
Let's go.
Have you watched?
Oh, the tweenies?
The tweenies.
No.
That's another British one.
There can't be.
There can't be this many.
There's so many.
The 100% of...
And there's Jet Set Willy and the ZX Spectrum.
Nobody does like video essays on the fucking hooves on British...
Not obscure, but just British children's entertainment.
If somebody made...
This is not facetious at all.
If somebody made a video or something, just cataloging all of the...
I don't know, the children's properties that exist only in the UK and nowhere else,
I would watch it.
That's the kind of thing that I would watch a video about.
I think a lot of it doesn't go to America, but it does go to Europe and other places.
So there's not a lot of exclusive UK.
It's just easy to like...
Yeah, we can put that in France and Germany and all over Europe.
Yeah.
Well, yeah.
I guess it would just be stuff that doesn't come across the pond then.
Occasionally there'd be like a super mega hit like Peppa Pig and that goes worldwide.
It's like, well, they did it.
I mean, it's the same.
I know there's...
Was it a YMS video about all the Canadian...
Like puppet shows?
What was the name of the one?
Like Nanaland with the stoned out green muppet.
Yeah, which I would never have heard of otherwise.
I guess it's just...
When stuff is big in America, I think it's just more likely to be worldwide.
American entertainment industry is just a little more dominant.
So I think a bigger percentage of American-made stuff is also familiar to everybody else.
Yeah, that's always been for a long time.
I think more recently, because of the internet as well, shows that are good from the UK end up being heard about at least.
And then maybe getting like a thing like...
I mean, Doctor Who was big in America.
Doctor Who was a worldwide hit, for sure.
Yeah.
But I don't know that it was a worldwide hit before the resurrection of the series in like 2005 or whatever it was.
No, my mom told me that she used to watch Doctor Who as a kid or something like she knew about it.
I mean, you know, an older incarnation of it, obviously.
Yeah.
I think it was dormant for a while, and then when it had the sort of resurrection that I think it came back in America, too.
But probably not as much, because it seems like it's more of a British institution.
I haven't thought of the Who's in a long time.
I've never thought of them before in any capacity.
Very funny.
What was the thing I said?
Why did Jim Henson need to make a different Muppet show for the UK?
They were already making shows.
Let me see.
Hoops.
Hoops 4 out now.
What is that?
Oh, man.
This is something else.
This is a thing that just happens to be called Hoops.
I've got something for you.
You're going to like this.
What?
Here.
I bet this is great.
Can you imagine the chunky polygons on that?
Well, I've got to find this.
Long play, the Hoops PS1.
Yeah.
You know?
Long play.
Look at it.
Show me.
I want to see the polygons.
I bet it looks exactly like Petscop.
Oh, my God.
Those PNG backgrounds.
30?
Oh, it's all digitized 2D.
What's the word?
Rotoscoped?
Oh, yeah.
Like Donkey Kong Country a little bit.
Yeah.
Well, actually, there is a 3D.
Earlier in the video, there is a 3D walk around bit.
It doesn't look very good, though.
There's a green character with green grass.
I can't even see him.
Oh, God, yeah.
They should, you know, Spyro.
Spyro was made purple so that he would stand out from the green grass he would be running around on.
So these guys were not on the cutting edge of game design.
They were not on the ball.
Oh, yeah.
This part where they're all standing in the lobby and they're behind a desk.
They have 3D models of all three of them.
Great.
Well, it looks like shit.
Yeah.
I mean, it doesn't look amazing.
It's for babies.
So you walk to a place and then you do a shitty puzzle minigame.
I mean, isn't that just video games, though?
Well, shut up.
Gotcha.
I like to press the X button to jump at the same time this guy doesn't jump.
Not to change the subject, or I mean, we can come back to this if you want.
But on the subject of PlayStation 1 games and videos about those games.
So I played some more Mega Man this week.
I played...fucking...I played Mega Man.
I played, sorry, Rockman and Forte, Mirai no Chosensha.
Which is, I think that's the title.
It was an unreleased game in America.
It was only on the Wonder Swan in Japan.
It means Challenger from the Future.
I mean, I'm not going to get into detail.
But it has a truly baffling place in the extended Mega Man lore.
Let's just say that.
It is truly strange that someone decided to make a game about what that game is about.
But anyway, I played Mega Man Legends.
You know that one, right?
We talked about that one last week, the one that was called Dash.
Yeah, I had played Legends a bit.
It was called Mega Man 64 on the Nintendo 64.
It was called Mega Man Legends on the PlayStation.
It was called Rockman Dash in Japan.
I played it as a kid, and I had kind of...
I had rented it one time and sort of bounced off it.
And I didn't rent it again, so I never got that far in it.
I played it again this week, and I loved it.
It was so good.
I kind of didn't think I would like it, but I was wrong.
It was one of the comfiest games I've ever played.
A lot of people describe stuff as comfy a lot, and sometimes it makes me roll my eyes,
and I think it's like a stupid way.
It's like, oh, people will describe anything as comfy if it's like, oh, it's nostalgic or whatever.
But like I said, I didn't really play this as a kid, but it was really comfy.
It was fun. It felt great.
I don't know, something about the bird sounds of running around in the fields that you start in.
Yeah, I've not played it either, but that sounds nice.
It always just looked really nice to me.
It's just sort of the controls were always like, oh, that's non-traditional.
The controls are pretty rough. It almost has like Resident Evil sort of like tank controls.
It takes a little bit of getting used to, but it's good.
There is like, yeah, the graphics look great.
They are like the perfect sort of like cartoony character designs that complement like the chunky polygon builds of the characters.
It looks perfect.
Yeah, it's just like the perfect example of that look.
I thought I was going to, I was kind of like dreading it.
I thought it was going to be boring. I thought it was going to be an annoying slog.
And then I played it and it probably took me maybe like nine or ten hours to beat, all told.
And then I was like, then I just kept going.
I went for 100%. I played it for another like six hours to like do all the side quests,
collect all the hidden like buster upgrades and weapons and stuff.
It wasn't even going to use them. I just wanted to see them.
Just wanted to talk to all the side characters and do all the bonus content.
That's a mark of a good game where you just feel like you want to do it.
I just wanted to. I didn't have to.
I could have, yeah, but it was just really, really liked it.
And, you know, funny coincidence. This is crazy. I couldn't believe this.
I was looking up how to grind Zeni, you know, the money in the game.
And so I was like, what's I wonder what the best spot to grind money is because I needed a lot of money to.
This is as I was preparing for the final boss because the final boss was kind of kicking my ass.
And so I wanted to get the final like armor upgrade that reduces the damage you take, but it costs a lot.
So I was like, what's the fastest way to grind money?
So I googled it and there were results.
The first result that you get when you Google like grinding like grinding Zeni Mega Man Legends.
Do you know who it's a video from? You'll never get.
No.
It's Oolulilia, the guy who wrote.
What?
Yeah, it's got like 9000 views.
There's an Oolulilia video where he shows you the best spot to you can grind almost 10,000 Zeni a minute
going in between these three rooms, which respawns these enemies that drop a lot.
And you have to use the vacuum buster side weapon attachment to like suck up the Zeni really fast.
And then you run to the other room and then you come back and you do it over again.
Yeah.
Just just happened to be the most the most viewed video on this particular subject.
So there you go.
Yeah.
You know what? I'll link I'll link the video.
Click, click, clack.
Yeah. Mega Man Legends fastest Zeni 9500 a minute.
First result when you search Mega Man Legends grinding Zeni.
And he starts talking in his mumbly Midwestern drawl.
You know.
Twice.
You know, I should uh, since I'm friends with him on Facebook, I haven't been on Facebook in a while,
but I should log in and message him and tell him like, Hey, man, you know,
I came across your Mega Man Legends how to grind Zeni video on because I was looking for and it really it helped me out.
It helped me grind for the Kevlar jacket or whatever it's called.
So that was funny.
Uh, that's it.
That was my week.
My week.
My week was
the heat wave.
You know, it's it's I could understand if that took up a lot of it.
It took up while the days that it was hot and then the day after it was sort of recovering.
I have not I've tried.
All right. Here's one thing.
Like I tried so hard to do work.
I felt like I was really, really grappling.
I was like, I wanted to check Twitter.
I wanted to go away so much.
And I'm like forcing myself to sit down, like finish this one commission.
I did finish one of the commissions earlier, but this is like, I've got it.
I've got like four left.
I got to do them.
I try drawing.
I start screaming.
I don't like actually scream, but it's just like,
Oh, no.
And I'm just like curling into curling into a bowl and like I'm putting the lines on the thing.
And I ended up making this is for the this is for the last few few commissions you have.
Yes, the last few commissions.
I just want I'm done and what I'm out of my life.
Did you did you take a minute to contemplate that that Twitter post I posted last week about
not I need to be in a better mood to do this drawing, but I will be in a better mood if I do this drawing.
Did you contemplate that?
I mean, no, not the time.
You should.
I don't really know how you would do that.
I posted it for contemplative purposes.
So, you know, contemplated at your own discretion, but it's there if you need to contemplate it.
I alright, I appreciate the contemplativeness.
I just don't understand how to put that into practice necessarily.
Like, I know that if I do this, it will no longer be a thing I need to do and that would feel great.
Right.
But it was truly a difficult experience trying to draw.
I was like, I'm not.
I'm not doing a good enough.
I see you have started, but you was not coming out the way you wanted.
Yeah, I had drawn like a face.
I needed to get the pose right.
I was looking at some references and I'm like, oh, I got to Google.
I thought I thought you meant you were you were like struggling to to actually make yourself do it.
I mean, I was.
Well, yeah, yeah, I see.
I understand.
So I'm like, I'm sitting there with my iPad trying to get this stuff drawn.
And it was just it was uncanny.
It was it's unbelievable.
Like never before have I tried so hard and got some tried so hard in a in a position where I really just wanted to do anything else.
Like usually I would just give in and be like, oh, whatever.
I got a little bit done.
I did a sketch layer.
I see it.
I looked at it and I was like, this sucks.
I probably need to redo it.
But I had no I had no moral fiber left after that.
And so I gave up.
And that was my week is that one day I tried really hard and I failed.
I mean, it's better than a complete like give up.
But like, I felt very silly.
It felt very silly to like sit there like quietly screaming and scrunching up my body trying to get some lines drawn.
And getting so little actually accomplished.
Yeah.
But what is it?
I don't know.
Oh, did I get it?
Yes, I got the fly.
See, see, give, see, give.
I had to try three times three times.
I said, oh, the fly.
Damn, I missed.
Oh, the fly.
And on the third time, I killed it.
So you're describing destruction.
I'm describing creation.
It's different.
They're just two sides of the same coin.
Entropy always increases.
It's not always balanced.
Every fly I kill creates a new drawing for someone in the world.
That's true.
It's easier to make a drawing than to kill a fly, I think, in my opinion.
What were we talking about?
I don't know.
I was just like, I've got like next week, by the way.
Just pour yourself a nice, just, hey, just make yourself a bottle of slime.
I posted the recipe.
I posted the recipe in RFCK.
So everyone, everyone, so it's freely available.
So just make yourself a nice slime and tonic and just relax after a hard day of trying,
trying and failing.
You know, it's just capitalism.
Just lean into it.
I mean, I feel, I've been feeling pretty good today, even though it's Sunday and I'm not
really thinking of work on a weekend.
It's the Sabbath.
So you better, yeah, you better not be.
But on Monday, I'm next week, I'm going to a gunnery, the yearly camp.
Oh, that's, yeah, that's right.
So I'll be gone for a week and a bit.
I might be back the Sunday after next.
But I won't be here for next week's PCP.
I see.
Did that get canceled last year for COVID reasons?
It did.
There was a Zoom version of it, which was obviously very minimal.
Yeah, sure.
Actually, I think, I think last year, 2020 was a Zoom year.
And it was like, oh, for the first time in like 70 years, we haven't had a gunnery.
But we technically sort of had a one on Zoom.
And then 2021, there was a very small gunnery at a more local campsite with less people,
but it still happened, I think.
I see.
With masks and very careful with all that.
This time, it's back to how it usually is.
I'm a little bigger school and like larger tents, mountain people.
We're all getting banged, get the gangs back together.
I'm a little...
On that subject, I'm a little nervous about having attended a gathering for RFC KCON.
I'm waiting for like five days to go by before I'm like...
Oh, yeah.
You know...
Uh-oh.
Monkeypox.
I mean, yeah, there's that too now.
I mean, I guess I know it's a bit...
I know it's a bit of a right-wing talking point to say that it's mostly among gay men
who are having monkeypox.
I also know that it can spread in other ways.
So it's not like the fact that I didn't do that means that I'm necessarily safe.
Are you worried because you had a gay orgy at the RFC KCON?
I...
Listen, what happens at RFC KCON stays...
I mean, everyone there...
Everyone there is gay or trans or whatever.
That's not true.
I mean, there's some...
But I don't know.
No, it seems pretty unlike...
I mean, I don't know.
I guess I even could have monkeypox.
No, I'm a little more worried about COVID.
But, you know, they say BA5 or whatever gets through your immune system.
So I don't know.
What was that?
Was that on Thursday?
So it's been three days and I feel fine.
So if I make it another three and I test and I'm fine, then I will be out of the woods.
But I'm still a little nervous about it.
But yeah, me going away next week means that I have a week coming up where, you know,
I've had all this time to do these things.
I really should at least get the Lord of Ghost things sent to the people who are still waiting for me to send them.
There's like three or four people for various reasons.
I haven't sent those yet.
And I'm going to do it.
I'm going to...
On Monday, I'm going to do that.
And I'm also going to record a Money Spinner's podcast to make up for the ones that I missed.
That's going to be my Monday and I'm going to do that.
And that's what I'm going to do and I'm going to do that.
Oh, I should do another Patreon Q&A.
I've been ignoring my Patreon while I've been working on getting the book finished and doing prep for the video.
When are you leaving for the goonery?
I think Saturday or Friday.
I think Saturday.
Okay, okay, okay.
And you'll be gone for a week.
So you're thinking like you feel like you should use that as like a deadline that you want to get it done?
Yeah, I mean, I don't know that I can get all of the commissions done just because...
But Lord of Ghost things is a lot more simple.
I have the information in the spreadsheets.
I just need to look at it, print the label, put the thing in the envelope and send it
and put it in a postbox thing and it'll be fine.
Is it copies of the book that you need to ship?
Yeah, the book with the red man.
I think... I don't know if anyone needs to pin.
All the plushies have been sent.
Is it more from the Kickstarter?
Yeah.
Oh, you didn't send them already?
Well, there was some complications with some of them and then they took a while to get back to me
and now they weren't in the previous batch that I did before I came over for Boston Con, whatever we call that,
when I came over to America to get COVID, to see the sites and to taste the COVID.
The local flavor, yeah.
So I meant to do everything else when I get back, when I assumed I got back, but then I didn't.
I understand.
And it's just a big... I try not to put myself down too much, so I'm not going to.
But I will get around to it on a Monday.
I also... Yeah, I've mentioned... I have a couple of unsent, Road to Radcon and Plebenweed Blu-rays here.
I think a few, maybe a week ago or so, I finished...
I decided, okay, I have made every attempt that I feel that I can to try to find these people
and double check that these are their current addresses.
I don't think I can do any more on my own for that, so I'm just going to send them to the addresses that I have
and hope that they are correct.
So I have a pile of maybe seven of those over here, and I was going to send them this week.
But then, RFCKcon, I made the slime bottles, and a couple people told me they wanted to buy slime bottles.
I was like, okay, well, I'll need to get more bottles, and I'll need to make some more slime and bottle it
and etch the glass and all that, which is fine.
But so now I'm like, okay, well, I'm going to... I'll send them all together, so I won't send these just yet.
I'll send them all and I'll need to get boxes for that.
So I've found another excuse to put off mailing these packages, all for the sake of saving myself
an hour and a half of going to the post office one time.
Very stupid.
I don't know if you know, but the five-pound note changed to a new updated five-pound note.
Like they changed the design?
They've changed the design. They don't use paper like they used to. It's like a plastic sort of thing.
Oh, okay.
And it's all new, and they said the five-pound notes are no longer legal tender, but you can deposit them.
You can trade them in. I have had like 15 five-pound notes in my wallet since then.
I just have never gotten around to going to a bank and saying, can I put this money in my account?
What's that? It's probably like $100 or something, right?
15 five-pound notes.
That'd be 75 pounds, which is gonna be more than $100.
It's around. It's a nice amount of money, and it's just in my wallet because I don't use my wallet at all.
I mean, I have it. I look at it. I bring it to places. I just was like, oh, I gotta go to the bank.
That's like a bus ride. Nah.
Yeah. Yeah, I know what you mean.
I have since, gosh, it must be a year and a half or maybe two years almost.
I've had a box with my old broken Cintiq.
Yeah, I had to replace my Cintiq a while ago, and you can sell a broken one on eBay,
and people will buy it for the parts or for restoration.
I think I could probably get like $100 for it.
Maybe a little more. I don't know.
I can get something.
It's a big, heavy box. It's been sitting in my room, and I keep telling myself,
oh, I gotta list it on. It's been on my to-do list for ages.
I gotta list it on eBay. I gotta send it through eBay.
But then it's like, okay, but before I do that, I have to determine how much shipping is gonna be.
And then I'll have to sign into my eBay account again,
and then I'll have to remind myself how to do a listing, which I haven't done that in forever.
So it's like, yeah, I've been putting off the steps to actually do that.
So that's about $100 in cash that I could liquidate.
It's just hard. It's too hard.
I can't do it. It's too hard, and I can't do it.
Surely there exists like AI functionality to be like a virtual assistant
that will remind you of all the things you need to do.
It's called a to-do list, and I have one, and it's on a whiteboard on my door,
and that has, and CellSyntique has been on it for at least a year.
But that doesn't work because it becomes something that you become accustomed to looking at
and not reading because you know what's on it, and then it doesn't actually remind you to do it.
You're just being like, oh yeah, at some point I should look at that list.
That's the thing to do is to look at the list, but you don't do it
because you need another to-do list that reminds you to look at the to-do list.
And one of the items on that to-do list is check to-do list.
Yeah, so if there was an AI like, I don't know, Alexa or whatever it is,
that could be like, hey, you could do this and that if you go to the bank,
and this and that, and you should, I don't know how it would work.
I don't know how, but when you have a huge list of things to do,
it's overwhelming and having a secretary
is like how people deal with so many things that they need to do
if they're a big shot office-having motherfucker.
There was a call and you need to return the call and here's an email
and someone's waiting for you, it's an assassin because this is a black and white film.
Yeah, that would do it.
The only thing is, what would stop me from just not using the secretary app?
They would need to be like, have too much access to my computer
and they would pop up in the bottom right corner, like clippy and annoy me
and I would want to turn them off.
So really, there's no way to make a good thing happen.
Now you just sound like the damn labor party.
You're not like Kier Starmer, there's no way, you can't do it.
You become the thing.
There's one problem, I give up.
He doesn't really sound like that, he's just sort of lame.
Yeah, I just assume that they're the same as the Democrats in every way,
that's how I would describe them as well.
It's odd, I don't really know anything about labor because they have so little presence.
The only thing I hear about Kier Starmer is him saying that Boris Johnson is bad
and that's been the news forever.
They say that the conservators are not doing very well, they're doing things bad.
I'm like, yeah, I agree.
Are you progressive labor party? Are you transpositive?
I have no idea where you lie on so many things.
Do you have a manifesto? I can't be bothered to look for a fuck you.
I'll just wait until there's an election and then they'll probably be saying more stuff.
Then I can look at it and listen into it and be like, okay, well, that sounds okay.
I'll put my vote.
I just saw on Twitter, this is funny, Justin Wang just liked a reply to my reply to a meme that I didn't like.
So I don't know what that says.
That means you're famous.
Oh yeah?
Yeah, now you're with the big league.
Well, here, look at this.
Let's get into it briefly.
Here's the meme.
Garlic bread.
And I think it sucks. I don't really like it or get it.
Well, there's bread, there's a girl, there's garlic bread, there's a different girl.
She's got white hair, we're in a white blouse or whatever.
And she's got bigger tits.
That's it.
I don't know, I guess it's just saying tits good and sure, what's the joke?
This person assumedly likes garlic bread and big boobies.
So do I, but I think this is irritating. I think this is obnoxious.
I don't know.
It isn't saying anything in particular.
It's just not saying anything.
I think it is the sort of meme for a horny teenage person who just is enjoying the fact that they are looking at boobs.
And then they would like the meme for that reason.
I get it, but do we need the pretext of a meme to do that?
I don't know, it's just not funny. I just think it's banal.
I think it's banal and I don't like it.
Yes, absolutely.
So I posted, what's the joke?
And someone replied, I fucked the bread.
And Justin Wang liked the reply that said I fucked the bread.
So I mean, okay, that's cool, I guess.
It's fine, it's fine.
I'll invent a joke.
It's not a joke.
Justin should like my tweet, my killjoy tweet being like, hey, it's not funny though.
He should like that one. He should think that that's better.
You should have tweeted that garlic makes your boobs bigger.
It does. That's a fact.
That's a fact though.
Because that's the...
What is a guy in this hypothetical world where a girl is bread?
Butter?
I don't know.
I think you have garlic bread without butter involved.
It's just a more complicated way to say boobs are good.
But it's not like a funny way to say it.
It's just a more complicated but not funny way to say...
It's kind of an anti-joke in that way.
I don't know, I think that's given it too much credit.
I think it's given it too much credit to call it an anti-joke.
I would call it simply a failed joke.
But 300, no, 500 people liked the tweet and thought it was funny.
And I hate those 580 people.
And I hate you, Justin Wang.
You do look like Steve Aoki.
I don't actually know what Steve Aoki looks like.
What does Justin Wang do? Is he a Tuber?
He is a YouTuber.
He's a very big Twitter account.
He makes YouTube videos.
I see him occasionally.
He makes YouTube videos that are sort of explaining some stupid internet fact.
He'll explain what the come box is or something like that.
He's funny.
Anyway, I just noticed that right now.
And that really is the last thing that happened to me this week.
That really is my whole week because that literally happened like 10 minutes ago.
I feel like this is the sort of like, you know, I attempt to make a meme.
But like something that funnier people will take and then add to to make it funny.
And then the fact that they altered it further would be funny.
The original doesn't mean much.
Like bread, garlic bread, third thing that has nothing to do with bread or boobs.
Yeah, like wait a minute.
I made it like wait a minute.
Check this out and it's just pictures of actual bread.
What do you think?
Did I did I do it right?
You get two pictures of bread and the caption is tits larger tits.
And it's a bread roll.
And one of the rolls is crusty and looks nicer.
Not even garlic.
And it's just a nice bread roll.
It sucks.
Delicious.
It's making me hungry.
I ate pasta.
I ate free pasta from some roommate or other.
Just put like some leftover pasta that had I assume people are moving out and just left like leftover pasta.
So I ate that yesterday.
That was my food.
So I didn't have to pay for it.
It was great.
There's nothing like free roommate pasta.
Do you know what I mean?
Just left out open.
Well, it was I mean the package was had been opened, but it was like put in a in like a box.
So it had not been like attacked by rodents or anything.
Yeah, the rodents hadn't got into it and taken a dime dump on it.
Somebody did leave a package of pasta out on the counter and mice did get into it.
And there was mouse poop all around it and that was gross.
Yeah, that was disgusting.
Yeah, it was horrible.
That was a while ago.
I got rid of it.
My kitchen is looking pretty.
Yeah, my kid.
Yeah, the fucking garbage that people forgot to take out fruit flies.
My kitchen is looking even grosser than what then usual at the moment.
So but I'm moving out soon and I don't care.
And my I have not heard from my landlord in a while and I hope to continue to not hear from her until I am gone.
And that would just be and that would just be great.
Not not looking forward to probably the inevitable interaction where she says like hey you still haven't paid for the last month's rent.
I tend not to know what she's talking about.
And I say, I don't know.
Oh, but I already paid.
I paid last month's rent when I moved in and then pretend that I don't realize that it's two different months that she's talking about.
Or when she says that and I say, oh, no, but it's an I put it in the mail.
Oh, it's in the mail.
You should have got it or whatever.
Just make it annoying for her on purpose.
Careful, Ben.
She may watch the procrastinator.
She's watching the podcast.
She knows.
She knows she's going to use this against me in court.
It is incriminating, but that's OK.
That's all.
I'll go to jail.
I am going to jail for this.
Hey, you know, that's it.
That's all I got.
Recently, I've gotten real big into old school runes.
Recently, I've gotten real big.
Well, I mean, that is another topic I've been gaining weight.
Because in a deliberate sort of way.
Yeah, I have been tracking my weight.
And let me see where I am right now.
I've been weighing myself and doing all the calorie counting.
I started on the June 22nd at 62.7 kilograms.
I think I can change that to pounds.
There we go.
138 pounds.
That was your starting point?
Yeah.
And it's gone up and down a bit.
But right now, I'm at 142.4 pounds.
So that's why that's 12, 14.
What am I looking at?
Am I stupid?
14 pounds.
Yeah.
And it's gone straight to my thighs.
Hell yeah.
Very nice.
I think I've been losing weight.
I haven't weighed myself in a while.
People at RFC KCON seem to say that I looked skinny,
which is good.
So that's cool.
Did you ask them about what you should do with your hair?
No.
I don't think that's cool.
Party discussion.
Hey guys, should I shave my head?
I might...
I don't know.
I might see...
I'm going to look into it a little more.
I might try and see how hard it is to get finasteride
and maybe just try it for a little bit and just see what happens.
I don't know.
Oh, finasteride.
I'm not even doing it.
I don't know.
I'm thinking about it.
I tried finasteride for a little while.
And I think the only thing it really did was make me really upset.
Like depressed, which is one of the symptoms.
The possible side effects.
Hell yeah.
Down turn in mood.
And I was like, this is so bad.
Wow.
And I stopped taking it.
I was like, all right.
Well, I'll take estrogen instead.
That's probably more fun.
Okay.
I mean, that's good to know.
Yeah.
I mean, the two hair loss products that exist are propitia, which is a topical solution
that you put on your head.
And I don't understand this at all.
But apparently it only works if you're thinning on the top of your head,
like the crown of your head.
It doesn't work on your forehead like receding hairline.
It's just different, I guess.
I don't know.
And the other one is finasteride, which is, I guess, is a pill.
And that one, maybe, that is the one you take to prevent hair loss because it, like,
does something to your testosterone or whatever.
I think, I believe the way hair loss works with testosterone is that most men have a gene
that makes the hair follicles in your head sensitive to testosterone.
And it's a gene that is so ubiquitous that it seemingly happens to basically everybody.
Some people don't have that gene, and so their hair just stays in.
And testosterone doesn't affect it.
But otherwise, your hair will fall out.
And the finasteride and other things, they sort of sit in the parking space where testosterone
would try to get in, and they stop testosterone from getting in.
It's like some sort of a T-blocker, which is similar to other testosterone blockers
that I have taken for transitioning.
But maybe finasteride is more specific for the head.
Or the hair. I'm not really sure how that works, but it's similar.
I would want to look into it a little more deeply before I decided to go and do anything with that.
So I don't know. I'll do some more research and see what it actually does and decide if it's too scary or not.
Anyway, how did I get on that subject?
I said I got real big.
So the other thing I was going to say is I got really big into old-school runescape.
I don't know if you've ever played that.
I have not played it, but I was logged into the PCP account and you recommended that guy settled, I think.
He popped up in my feed.
I wondered if maybe you had watched some on the account or something.
Or maybe YouTube heard me through my microphone.
Or it wouldn't have heard me because I didn't talk about it.
It heard you through my... whatever. It knew.
It listens to the podcast.
Maybe honestly, what if it's because you talked about it on the podcast
and somehow Google recognized that the podcast you post on YouTube through this account
talked about this other YouTube account.
Here I will recommend you that YouTube.
That's insane, but not even impossible because there's auto captions.
I wouldn't count it entirely.
Yeah, auto captions. Yeah, it might.
Oh, my God. It's going to know that I'm being a shitty tenant on purpose.
It's going to send me to jail.
It's going to blow the whistle.
No.
It's going to send you targeted ads for going to jail.
How to call the police on yourself.
It's not so bad.
How do you report rent fraud on your own person?
So, RuneScape.
RuneScape. Back when old school RuneScape was made as like a...
As a joke.
It was made as a joke upon humanity.
And it was so funny that it's really popular.
And it's like 2007 RuneScape.
And it's like, oh, I remember that I would come home from school and play that game.
RuneScape 3 or just RuneScape had been updated to such as a degree that it just didn't feel like the same game.
It felt...
There was like, every time you logged in there were pop-ups about like, oh, all of these new things you could do in news forums.
And like, I just want to click on trees and get the logs.
I don't want to do any of this extra stupid stuff.
And the graphics have been updated a lot.
And I'm like, this isn't what I liked.
So, I made an account called Frisco Cirques because of course I did.
And I didn't play it for a while.
And I've just recently just felt because of the YouTube stuff I've been watching to get back into it.
And I've been grinding.
I have this secret plan.
It's not a secret.
My plan is to gather the resources necessary to level one of the member's only skills from 0 to 99 without being a member.
I'm going to gather all of the things I need to level Fletching, which is like, you need logs to turn into arrowheads.
You need metal bars to smith into arrow shafts.
And then you need metal bars to smith into arrowheads.
You need to collect feathers from killing chickens and various other things.
So, members are like people that like pay for a subscription, right?
Yeah, monthly or whatever.
And so, what explain members only skills?
Well, free to play skills are like the very basics.
You've got the combat skills.
You've got ranging, you've got magic, wood cutting, smithing, mining, and fishing and cooking and stuff.
Members skills are like things created after the member system was made, I think.
So, you've got like more utility-based skills like Herbalore, which you get herbs and you can turn them into potions.
There are various spots where you can plant seeds.
It's like Farmville, but in RuneScape physical locations, you can plant things and go get the weeds off and watch them grow and then you get stuff.
There's Thievery, where you can pickpocket NPCs and monsters to get stuff.
There's Agility, which is the funniest one, where you have to do parkour in various areas to gain agility so that you can get through little shortcuts built all over the game.
Because RuneScape is big and your character moves really slowly unless you're running.
And having shortcuts through a wall of a castle to the outside is super useful.
So, you would train your agility up by doing parkour obstacle courses in the gnome-stronghold or whatever.
And then you could crawl under a little hole and you could save so much time when you go from this bank to this mining area.
And it's like, yeah, fun. Agility.
And Fletching. Fletching is obviously making arrows and stuff, throwable javelins and throwing knives.
There's Slayer, which is like killing specific monsters.
I don't know really what that's about, but you have to kill special types of monsters that only members can access to level up your Slayer.
And if you're a Slayer, you're like a hunter of beasts.
You're a vampire Slayer. You're this Slayer.
I don't know anything about it. I never really played members that much.
And then there's Hunting, which is like setting down little traps to catch rabbits and stuff like that.
What makes it members only? How do you level up a member's only skill?
Oh, well, there's two different types of worlds in RuneScape.
Free to play players can log on to free to play worlds where you just can't do anything for those skills. You're just not allowed to.
You can't go into 90% of the game.
I mean, there's a huge amount of free to play stuff, but there's so much more outside.
There's a gate to Mauritania or like Fremnic or whatever.
You just can't go through the gate unless you're on a member's world.
And if you're on a member's world, you have to be a member and you can do everything. That's basically it.
What my plan is, right, is you can, for Fletching, is one of the only members only skills that requires resources that I can gather as a free to play player.
So logs I can get, metal I can get to turn into arrowheads, feathers I can collect.
So I've made a little plan, I looked at all of the things I would need to make and exactly how much of each resource I would need.
And I'm just going on like a gathering expedition.
I'm getting all the stuff and it will take hundreds of hours, but it's fun because I like it.
I like planning the challenge.
Because obviously if I was in a member's world, there's so many more places and different ways to gather resources and level up your skills.
There's lots of quests that give special experience boosts, but I have to do it all without member's stuff and that's the hard part.
It's mostly just tedious, but I kind of like it.
I kind of like the having like an arbitrary goal and then just slowly working my way through.
I mean, I guess I can see how it would be fun in the broadest sense of the word.
I mean, a lot of the fun for me was like theory crafting, the route I would take or like I needed a certain...
There's nothing stopping me necessarily from just getting a bunch of money and buying the materials because there's like a grand exchange like player used like a trading thing.
I don't know how to explain it, but like if you put an item on the grand exchange, that item exists on the exchange and if somebody's looking for that item, they buy it, they get your item.
So if nobody's using the grand exchange, you can't buy anything from it, but it's constantly been extremely popular because it's more profitable because numbers go up and down.
There's like a real time chart of like what's trending, what items are people buying and selling and all that.
It's like it's the stock exchange.
So like it's technically possible for me to buy everything I would need, but that's boring.
So I want to see if I can like gather it myself, which would require me to get a very, very high level on some of these skills and getting a very high level requires so much of experience gathering,
which requires me to get so much more.
So like I need like over 100,000 coal and it takes a while to get like a full inventory of coal and then put it in the bank.
So it's like that's a lot of work.
That's a lot of time investment, but it was fun to like figure out what was the most efficient way to get to the end point of 99 Fletching by gathering resources and then using them.
So you have not actually started doing it though?
I started gathering resources.
I've not done like, I'm not a member yet.
I'm going to like get all of the stuff, make sure I have everything and then go members, go to my bank and just use the stuff to instantly become level 99 by clicking on stuff.
And it will be like, aha, I did it.
Challenge complete.
Wait, that's all you have to do?
I mean, it takes a lot of stuff, a lot of resources to get to 99 in anything.
But yeah, I mean, it's possible.
Oh, you haven't, okay, you've started gathering.
You don't have, you don't have it all yet.
No, no, no, no.
A couple thousand Mithril or a couple thousand Adamantine or and Ruinite or like 10,000 willow logs or something and you logs and oak logs.
I think I got the oak logs.
Different types of, you know, to make different types of bows and crossbows.
Naturally, naturally.
I need like 400,000 feathers, which I can get from killing chickens, but I probably will not kill chickens to get them because it takes so long.
That would be an ecological disaster.
Yeah.
I mean, the chickens in the, there's like a farm just outside Lundbridge up the road to Varric where there's a coop with like, like 12 chickens and they respawn almost instantly.
So I can just kill them and kill them and kill them and get a bunch of feathers, but.
How long would it take to kill 400,000 of them?
Yeah, it's like, that's an astronomically tedious thing.
I will probably get as many as I can.
A lot of the, the strategizing is like, how can I gain more than one of these things at the same time?
I wonder if Ululili has made videos about how to grind for them most effectively.
He would.
That's the kind of thing he would make a video about.
Because there's a thing in RuneScape.
A lot of mining areas, a lot of areas where you do anything really, have enemies nearby that can harass you if you're too low a level.
They'll be aggressive and they'll interrupt you doing something.
And you have to turn around and kill them or like hide.
And in a place where there's the fallow door mine, where there's like a bunch of coal and iron.
That's a really good place to get that.
You don't want to be harassed by these giant scorpions that are roaming around.
No, no, no, indeed.
I do not would not like that at all.
Yeah.
So the highest level scorpion in there is like level 32.
And in order to not get harassed by an enemy monster, you need to be one more than double their level.
So my combat level needed to be 65 to not get harassed by the scorpion.
So one of my goals was to get to 65 combat.
And I thought, well, combat level is determined by your attack, defense and strength things.
Your prayer level and slightly your magic and your range level.
But if I kill chickens, I can get experience in those things.
So if I kill chickens, I'm getting towards my combat level that I need and I'm getting feathers.
And the bones they drop, you can bury to get more prayer experience, which also contributes to my combat level.
So it's like, that's at least three little things I can get if I kill like a thousand chickens.
I think I ended up killing two thousand of them before I got so bored, I had to do something else.
I have been watching videos from a Pokmon guy called FlygonHG.
He basically does Nuzlocke challenge runs and then he makes videos where he basically summarizes the runs.
He explains his strategy, he explains how he theory crafted a battle and how it played out and stuff.
Which is very like, you gotta plan for this battle that's coming up I'm gonna want to have.
He does it off screen, or maybe he'll do it on his streams instead of in his YouTube videos.
But like he does the thing where he'll use like a calculator to calculate like, okay, this Pokmon can outspeed that Pokmon.
Because it has this nature and these IVs, I'll need to grind this many EVs and have it at this level before it can outspeed that.
Which will let it one shot that to make that not a threat and that's how I'll deal with that.
Plan that way way way in advance.
Theory crafting, strategy, trying to be efficient, I get it.
It's really fun. I think I made a video about Runescape in this exact reason why it's good.
Because it's extremely slow to do a lot of things in Runescape.
But the game is so open and you're like free to go anywhere and do anything really.
That a lot of the game involves theory crafting as a natural response to how slow everything is.
You sort of have to either follow a guide or like figure out for yourself how best to do what you want to do without spending an extra thousand hours that you don't need to spend.
And so a lot of early Runescape memories were me theory crafting, not just experience gain but profitability.
If you go to the Grand Exchange and you buy the materials necessary to make a mithril bar, like one mithril ore and then four coal makes a mithril bar if you smelt it.
That's more expensive than selling the mithril bar.
So I realized that if I got some of the coal or just the mithril, I could make the bars obviously slower than if I bought everything but more money efficient.
And so I could make a profit and it's like, yes, yes, thinking.
I had like notepad documents of this stuff. It was very fun.
I want to go back to Mega Man Legends. I said it was comfy and I said it was like the atmosphere.
I think it's more specific than that. I think what's enjoyable about the experience of playing that game is that it has a really strong sense of place.
It's set on this place called Catalox Island and it's just this nice little island that you're on.
It's just a nice place to be. There's like nice woods, nice fields, there's a nice little town, nice little shopping arcade.
You go around and there's just stuff to do in it. It's sunny, it's beautiful, the aesthetics are perfect.
It's like a continuous little world because everything takes place on this island.
There are ruins underneath the city and there's like a threat.
Oh no, pirates are attacking. Well, that's not good. There's an ancient legend that disaster will happen if this happens.
Oh, you better prevent that. But it's just a nice place that it puts you in and lets you just hang out there and gives you tasks to do.
So I had to go back and do all the extra tasks because I wanted to hang out on Catalox Island some more.
Gotta go and complete all the minigames for the local news stations game show or whatever.
Gotta help the fucking punk kids build their little clubhouse out in the woods and trade them beetles in exchange for spare parts to upgrade your gun with.
What a game. There's a sequel. I've heard people say that the second one, I've heard people say they like the first one better for atmosphere reasons, which is a bit of a shame.
But I'm hoping to enjoy that as well. I really thought it would be boring but I loved it. I was very happy.
I might have to play it then. I recommend it. I'm a real big fan of virtual spaces that I would like to be in for real actually.
I feel like the nice sunny and the grass and the way you're describing it at least.
I think you would like it a lot. That's not a feeling that I think I'm particularly attuned to but even my small heart grew three sizes on Catalox Island.
I think the second one takes place in like a forbidden land inside of like a storm. I think maybe it's going to be less comfy so I gotta prepare myself.
Did you ever play Wii Fit?
Wii Fit? The exercise game? Maybe I messed around with it a little bit when the Wii was new.
There's this running mini game and that takes you to an island that I think appears in like some other Nintendo something or other game with planes.
I don't know what it's called. It's like Nintendo Mi Island or something and you run by like putting the Wii remote in your pocket and jumping up and down like jogging on the spot.
But I really love that environment. The track that you go on because it's the sound design of the location. It's a sunny day and it's a nice island.
You run with your Mi and there's Mi's coming the other way and running past you and stuff or Mi's you can overtake and it's just sort of like the sound design is minimal. There's no music.
It feels like the footsteps echo when you're like under a rocky sort of bit near the mountain and there's like oh you're in the shade and it's sort of like a path was cut into the mountain.
You go around a bit and you come down and there's like a rope bridge and it's windy and it's like creaking a bit.
And you're running over that and it's like oh this is so cool. I love this place. If only I could go off the track but you're not like choosing the direction you're just making the inputs to run and your character runs by itself.
But the path it takes is just it's so scenic. It's so like nice and atmospheric is like that's that's I would like to be on an island right now. I want to be in a nice sunny island.
Jogging and I want to come back and have like a little nice drink of water with a cherry or something.
I can see a little I found a little video of a We Fit aerobics free run. Yeah. Running along a nice little. A nice little path.
It made me exercise. Imagine that. Imagine video games doing that.
Not not since Pokemon Go has a video game done such a thing for me.
Good good good video game reminds me of you know that guy on Twitter. I think his name is Arthur Vieiter making that game called.
I think it's called Zeta Gal. Yes that one that looks clearly clearly clearly is visually inspired by legends. Good good good stuff.
I don't know. I don't know why I bounced off it as a kid and then I came back to it and I'm like wow actually actually this game looks and feels great and it rules in every way.
What the fuck except except the weird tank controls are just bad but like whatever you get used to it.
Well you may be like against it being 3D now.
I think it was just like I think because my usual games that I played were like side scrolling action kind of like shooter or like yeah platformers.
And I think the pace of combat in legends is just a little more positioning it's kind of like moving around and it's not so much of like an action knee experience and I think I maybe found it a little dull.
In the in the combat.
Because it's kind of it's kind of about you know.
Ocarina of time you know lock on to your opponent and shoot into them only you can't like circle strafe to dodge them.
Because you can't like move while you're locked on so it's quite stiff.
Yeah I think that's probably why I found the combat a little stiff and dull.
Which it is which it is but you can get you sure do feel powerful when you get the right buster upgrades and you boost your damage really high.
And now you're and now you're fucking shit up that that is pretty satisfying.
Boosting your stats.
Oh yeah buying buying buying buster buster upgrade Omega at the junk shop baby.
That's what I'm talking about.
Okay yeah.
I love accruing power.
I do love accruing power both in video games and in real life.
And I love exercising that power against my enemies and the against those weaker than myself.
Do you want to fuck the way fuck the week.
Fuck the week fuck the week.
Do you want do you want to start voicemails.
Do I have anything else to say.
I get no.
Australian alien.
Good day.
We can start voicemails.
Okay let's do it.
All right I am I think the first one is called based saint three two one go.
And then it's all like as a registered Democrat.
I want us to be as open and generous with pedophiles possible because I stand all of them.
They are all my gods.
They are my kings and queens and I won't.
I went too far.
But anyone smirks them.
I went sees these Democrats have gone too far this time.
You didn't go far enough.
I know blue Ben you're not blue enough.
I've only got to be blue in the face.
I only valorize groomers.
I have not taken the plunge into becoming one as my ideology dictates I eventually must.
Alas.
Okay next one is called when I have downtime at work.
And it's an image.
It's an image or album.
Oh it is more from Vinnie I think.
Let me see the big Vinnie Vidi Vici.
Yeah it is doodles of me vaping.
Vaping the phantom or a smoke vape cloud.
Oh is that what that is?
The phantom.
Oh yeah.
This one of the skull cloud looks pretty cool.
Wait this is your gear second and gear third.
What is the gear fourth?
You're holding a vape?
Oh it's my mod.
My gear fourth with my mod I see.
I mean it looks pretty cool.
Oh yeah the skull behind.
It's funny this is like it's more in line with like a bankai than it is a gear fourth three thing.
But nobody watches Bleach anymore or Bleach is dead.
I'm putting a gummy worm into my vape rig.
I gotta do it.
Vapable gummies.
Tiny cereal with a big spoon.
I vaguely remember saying that.
Why do you look like you're blushing about this?
I kinda do yeah.
I think it's maybe supposed to be shadow but yeah it looks a little bit like tiny cereal with big spoon.
Big cereal with little spoon.
Oh yeah the donut sized Cheerios.
Oh no and then I peed my pants.
Oh it's so...
That's visceral.
I need to hydrate.
I need to hydrate more if that's what my pee looks like.
That's very dark.
Gotta watch out for kidney stones.
Give and take this is probably your first time seeing these.
I usually send these to Ben's Discord but I fear none of them have been shared with you Gib.
So here they are you can get them first if you add me on Discord.
Vinny does DM me these on Discord and to be honest I kind of I don't look at them because I expect to see them on the podcast.
Yeah send them on the podcast that's fine.
I like these...
This one of...
I think this one's my favorite.
This one with the little skull floating up above me there.
That is a nice one.
I like that one a lot yeah.
These are very cool.
Very nice.
Lovely.
Where was I?
The next one is called Son of a Glitch.
It's another vocal room.
Okay three two one go.
My favorite show on the internet Son of a Glitch.
Get money.
Acquire monetary value.
Yeah that's true.
I hope they acquire monetary value.
Whose other voice was that?
It could be made.
Madey.
Who?
The guy is an animator.
I remember living saying on a Minecraft server they recorded a bunch of these.
It could be 4 eyes.
Oh yeah yeah yeah you know what.
It's probably 4 eyes actually.
Oh right.
For some reason I thought it was a PCP clip but no you're right.
Yeah that's probably it.
Monetary.
I hope they don't acquire monetary value.
Personally I would rather have that for myself than them have it.
That's just my opinion.
The next one is called The True Nature of PCP 321 Go.
This is the show where you must always be correct.
And if you don't we'll fucking skin you alive.
I feel like that's another fly and I missed it again but I'll get it.
That should be every show.
Every show you should be correct or you get skinned alive.
That should just be how it works.
Can't they just kill me first?
I don't want to be alive for that.
I'd rather be dead than correct.
I need to grab another sparkling water.
What if I was skint alive?
Like I had no money.
Skint?
Yeah.
Is that a word?
No money.
You're broke.
Well if you're broke then you will eventually die.
You must have some monetary.
Well maybe not.
You probably can live on no money for a while.
I lap up rain water puddles for water and I eat rocks.
An untapped potential of the earth.
The power of the earth and stones beneath our feet.
I will absorb it for myself and I will become like the thing from the Fantastic Four.
And I will be unstoppable.
Yes.
I stretch myself too thin.
Always doing all these things.
That's why I became a stretchable man.
And you, Johnny, you have a fiery personality.
So you're on fire and you, Ben, you were always eating rocks.
So now you're made of them.
It's ironic, you see.
When is radioactivity supposed to be ironic?
That doesn't make sense.
It's just radioactivity.
No, it's a fable.
It's a fable about men.
No, they're real.
They're really real and they're so understandable.
And in terms of, you can quantify their powers.
Incorrect.
You can put them on like who's stronger than who.
Some things are beyond mankind's ability to understand or test or quantify or verify.
It's like that episode of My Little Pony where Twilight Sparkle tells Pinkie Pie,
you're right Pinkie, science is fake and only through faith can we achieve world peace.
Can we achieve solidarity among ponies and dominate the outside peoples?
The next one is called, is PR HTML port still planned?
Is Phantom's Revenge HTML port still planned?
Maybe Kickstarter goal to pay someone for it.
Shit, I think I did.
Wait, fuck.
I think I might have gotten someone on Fiverr to do that and then I might have just forgot about it.
I should check Fiverr and see if that happened.
Yeah, I would like to do that.
I would like to make an HTML version.
I would like to put it on Steam at some point.
I would do that after the book is getting printed already.
So yeah, that's still planned although I haven't been thinking about it for a while.
I'm mostly just worried about getting the Kickstarter going.
Next one is, what do you think of Trixie's new content?
I don't think about it.
I haven't seen anything so I don't know.
Yeah.
Next one is another Vocalru link.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
Was this open voice message thing ever a problem?
Because somebody could just say the end word.
Send one of these.
Otherwise, do you just cut it from the video?
I mean, he's right.
He is correct.
I honestly don't get that much of people just saying the end word.
So he will not be skinned alive?
No, I haven't really had that in a while.
Voice mail is be slacking.
Voice mail trolls be slacking.
Yeah, most voice mails are fine even if they suck.
They're not, like, cuttable.
Yeah.
Speaking of cuttable, the next three are...
Well, the next two are YouTube links,
and then the third one says no part three because rape joke,
and I don't want to shock y'all.
This guy is assuming we're clicking on these YouTube videos.
I'll be honest, I did, beforehand, I did look,
it's like robot chicken clips, and I'm not...
It's not...
I'm not going to indulge this nuts.
Oh, my God, that's so epic lulls.
It was epic.
It's true. Oh, my God, comedy? I love comedy.
I'm just like punchy sonichu.
You know, I love comedy because it's so funny.
That's my...
I get just like punchy.
I get mad all the time, but I control my rage
by watching TV comedies because they're funny
and they make me laugh.
That's my character.
Okay.
All right, anyway.
A bunch of YouTube links that I will not be checking.
And then the next one...
Oh, this is your weekly reminder to play Deltarune Chapter 2.
Oh, yes, I don't want to miss that.
Okay, noted. Thank you, voicemailer.
Next one is called Big Farmer.
Three, two, one, go.
Greetings.
It is I, the medical establishment,
the death furnace known as Endless Drugs.
Big Farmer from Balan, Wonderworld.
And I'm here to tell you today, Ben,
that your hair loss problem
can potentially be reversed
with finasteride and topical monoxidil.
Now, I know you've seen
those games on the box adverts
telling you, oh, you...
It's all the same stuff that's in there.
Just the generic versions of the drugs.
Much cheaper, mind you.
Now, if you just have a look
on Google images, type in
finasteride before and after,
you'll see that some people do see
regrowth. It is a possibility.
And I know you think, oh, no,
I'm too far gone and blah, blah, blah.
No, just have a look
and give it a go. Remember Tengen,
Popping Guru and Lagann. Remember Simon.
How hard he had to try against the antispirals.
I do when Simon started
balding.
Well, let this be your drill,
Ben. Let finasteride
be the drill that you need to make
your last stand against the antispirals
that is your receding hairline.
I'm so lame.
I promise you it won't make you a girl.
Didn't happen for me, but I do have a lovely head of hair.
So,
I would recommend it. Give it a go.
All the best and you don't have to tell anyone
if it doesn't work. Just stop using it and give up then.
But you don't have to give up now.
All right. Take care. Bye.
I did.
That HBomer guy?
I did. I did, in fact, Google.
Actually, it's funny. Yeah, like this morning
or last night I did, in fact,
Google finasteride before and after.
It's just a little
weird because some of them
some of those results seem like they might also
be like surgical as well.
It's a little hard to tease out
which ones are like just finasteride,
which ones are not surgical.
They don't...
It's not always entirely clear.
This is such a lame problem.
I don't know. I feel really lame even caring about it.
I genuinely think that, like,
the cool thing to do is to not
give a fuck if you lose your hair.
I think that's cooler.
And I think if I was a better person,
that would be how I feel about it.
But I'm not. I'm not good enough.
And that's
so there.
I mean, there's
another second pathology that I have
about the whole issue.
Think about it like this.
You came out the womb with no hair.
You can go back in the womb
with no hair.
Yeah, that's the goal.
I thought you were going to say you go to the grave
with no hair, but no.
Okay.
Well, that's food for thought.
Next one is called
also
when do y'all record an episode
but there is a voicemail
attached. So let's give it a listen.
Three, two, one, go.
Bro, I'm making
the best fan art ever.
It's going to be so fucking funny.
But also
is
a draw cast now
different
a separate thing you could
y'all could make a draw cast
anytime
and you
would be just another episode.
I mean, right?
I mean, I guess we could.
We could, yeah. I guess as we could do that.
I just think
it's
it was more fun when it was a larger group.
Yeah, it would just be you and me.
Like, I mean, okay.
I would draw something and you would look and be like, wow, cool.
Yeah. And you would draw something
and you would be like, oh, wow, cool.
Yeah.
Oblivion Fall
and Sea Toll and those
guys
they sort of have their own
little draw cast. I don't know if they've done one in a while.
But
they're sort of doing the same thing because they
you know, because they have like a little
a little gaggle of people over in that server
who want to be on those episodes.
So I mean, they're kind of doing
we don't have the manpower
to make them quite like we used to
anymore.
So I mean, I think that's what they're trying
to recapture over there a bit.
I think.
Yeah.
I wouldn't say no to like a stream
of drawing
together.
No, we usually play Minecraft
or some other thing for heckles or shekels.
But like, we could do a draw
thing.
It'd be nice and chill. I haven't
I haven't drawn in a while. The only thing I've
drawn recently was your birthday gift.
But I need to draw.
I need to draw a cover for
Slime and Punishment and I have not even started
that.
I've been putting that off and putting that off.
You got to do that at some point.
Yeah.
I was considering like, did I mention this?
I was considering like maybe I should pay someone
famous to do it.
Oh, like
Mark Zuckerberg.
I don't even know. I don't even know who it
would be.
But like.
What's the guy who made Garfield?
He's not Brian Epstein. Jim Davis.
Jim Davis.
I should pay Scott Adams.
He's on Twitter posting about how he murdered
his son and shit.
He'll do anything.
Get the odd ones out to draw.
I don't know. I was considering maybe
if I should instead of drawing it myself
I should pay someone famous to do it.
But like who would I even get to do it? I don't know.
The only person who like
I don't know.
I probably couldn't get Harry Partridge
to do it. He seems like too big of a
reach.
I don't know if he does.
Yeah, I don't even know if he takes art
commissions or does anything like that.
No, he's usually working on
big animation projects.
Yeah.
So that's probably not a
but that was the only like name that
popped into my head of like
someone who
I was thinking like you know
internet creators who like
one, don't suck
and two like
are sort of in on like the Chris
Chan joke.
I mean most.
Yeah.
And I was that was the only
the only one that popped up in my
mind and it's like
so I probably
just dropped myself.
I did everything else myself.
I'll do it. I'll do it again.
Oh
anyway, you ask when did we record an episode
we usually record
at 10 a.m. on
Sundays. That's Eastern Standard Time.
That's the answer.
Next one is what's the origin
of Ben with big tits?
I don't know.
I don't really think there is one other than that
like it was more of like a gib
with huge tits thing and then new drew
those comics and just gave us both huge
tits.
It could be a combination of things.
We did do that one bonus episode where we talked
about tits.
There was
no because I got
I think it was
the
the the pro and on
cast did
some of them did like art of me with
big tits at one point a while
ago and I don't remember
why that I don't remember what sparked
that but there was something
there was another time that it happened and
it was probably like
oh so many PCP members
of trans now bends next
let's draw like female Ben St
and that was maybe
maybe yeah that might that might have been it yeah
fem saint as they say
fem saint that is
what they call her
what about fem snakes
what a
I don't I don't know
I don't know
next one is called happy birthday
Ben and there's actually a voicemail
so three two one go
I
think it's just going to be blank
that was worth that was worth it
oh golem noise
next one is called I'll ask again
where is Tom Oliver I
I just don't know what to tell you
I don't know what else
we answer this question
what do you want me to say
what do you want
how much more
can I tell you
they said where
as in W E A R
yeah so they just want to know what he's
wearing oh god
well I mean probably
a beanie
and a button down over a t-shirt
I don't know
if he's wearing like a like a full
size like a onesie jeans
but a beanie onesie
there's there's a beanie body
there's simply no
he's wearing a Godzilla suit
24 7
oh yeah
or a common writer suit
oh those are the two things he likes
you know what
kaiju showed me
he got a bit more done of the dojin
which is nice
I think he drew another half of a page
maybe he finished that first page
I'm not sure
he's got like 13 to do
so I mean I don't know
if that kept up that would be
it would only be like
several more months
I mean it's something
rather than radio silence
I mean definitely yeah so
so that's he messaged me
late last night and I saw the message
this morning I haven't responded yet
but it's good
and then the last one is also
how are you today Ben
I guess I'm alright
I'm a bit
tired because I stayed up really late last
night and I only slept maybe like
four or five hours
so I'm a little tired
went a bit off my sleep schedule
but other than that I'm doing
doing good
people always say how are you today Ben
they never say where are you today Ben
I'm coming over
I'm in your walls yeah
no one ever asks
how
are you today Ben
as in how do you exist
how can this be
that's it
that's the last voicemail
nice
I just want to
play video games
I was gonna say I just want to reiterate
play Mega Man Legends
or 64
so good
so good I thought I really
I really did not expect
really didn't expect to like it thought it would be a slugs
thought it would be a chore
I will probably play
I will play Mega Man Legends too I'm
considering
whether I will play
the misadventures
of Tron Bon
oh god there's a fly
I miss it again
another fucking fruit fly
I think the misadventures of Tron Bon is on like
the 3DS or something
it's
probably play it
probably play it just for completeness
I like Tron Bon
I think she's cool
I like this that's a game
that is the one
she's the girl with the
serve bots the little yellow robot
servants
oh is that the little
I think you would like her actually
she seems kind of like
kind of like a gib core
oh I've seen her
she's um
with the brown hair and the pink
dress
the half crescent hair
yes
and the weird
okay I think this is official art
this one weirdly
emphasizes her
cod piece
I think this is for
like one of the later
sort of like games they made
sort of like a big tribute to like
oh I got him
got him that time a third time's the charm
yet again
uh
this is for like fucking
Mega Man X dive or some shit
I don't know
anyway I like her
she's a villain
and in her game
in the misadventures of Tron Bon
you basically just go around
committing terrorism
yeah you go around
like demolishing houses
like robbing people
like uh
uh you uh you break into banks
and so I think you do also go on
just fucking boring like oh
go into the ruins and excavate stuff
snore
um
yeah but uh I'll probably play that
just because I like it
what I really like about this image you posted
is that her the front of her skirt has a
as a triangle cut out but that is not
reflected in the shadow that is cast
ooh
it doesn't
well
game destroyed
can we excuse that as like
the light is coming
from the side
and so maybe it's sort of not
passing through that
I mean where but it's like
falling on her leg in that same way
but what if she's illuminated from
kind of the upper to her upper
left and so like the place on the
shadow that would have that would
reflect the triangle actually falls
further to her
right of her leg and so we don't
actually see it can we
do you buy it do you buy it
um like it's like it would be
off her body on the floor
yes yes
I think yeah you know that could
maybe that could work
it's plausible enough that I'm
that I'm willing to why is she got like
rivets on her
on her crutch it's
it
it is it is like her character
she does look like this in the game this
it image uncomfortably
like makes the cod piece her
focal point
you know um
actually I heard
there is
a theory I there's a theory from
the only the only Reployed
YouTuber Reployed Revo
I heard a theory about this
that it's because the bond
family there's there's
hints in the game that the bond family
like used to be like a very
famous and like powerful like noble family
so it might be
that she's like an heiress and
there's some weird fucking
this is probably putting too much thought into it
but maybe it's like she's an heiress
she's a princess sort of so she's
we got a fucking chest to build her ass
or something
is she not a robot?
I don't know
is she a robot?
the thing about
the thing about that
is that okay
you sort of wouldn't even know it from
the games but actually all the
people in
legends are these things called
carbons who are just people
but they can
just fucking take their body parts off
and replace them with robot parts if they feel like it
okay so maybe that's like a service
hatch she could have a robot
she could be totally normal
but just have a robot vagina
it's possible
like you unscrew that and it's like
the off switch yeah she
took her flesh pussy off
and put this on instead and she just left
that in like the refrigerator for later
or something
that's the new version of a chest
about is to remove the vagina
just remove the vagina just replace
it with like an armor piece and probably
I don't know it's probably got like
an air conditioning system in there or something
just like why waste the space
like a glove box
yeah
I think that's it
I think we've
I think we've cracked it
yeah I mean
I think these are the in-game models and I mean
she does have it
although I never really
noticed it
that's funny
they've only got so many
I don't know if these are the
actual models
these might be fan made
models actually
I'm gonna go on a hunt
I'm gonna go on a hunt for the
for the real shit
well it looks like this could be like
the real one versus a fan
edited version
I mean this is
no I mean this is
that is in the official character design
just it's
I never I never I never noticed
it during the game like at all
because I'm not a pervert
and she's like
I think she's supposed to be like 14
but I mean
I don't know
it's one of those characters that
I think she could be any age
she doesn't act
she doesn't act like a kid
although she does have a crush on
Mega Man
but Mega Man is also 14
but he you know
he's just a guy
you know whatever
yeah I mean I think
with games like this they usually have
the ages reflect the people
who are going to be playing it
so they feel like oh I could be Mega Man
this is the little boy
you know I'm 14
and I go
another tidbit that I learned
well I didn't really learn this
but he Reployed Revo
in another video mentioned this
and it's true it's really annoying
in the English he's just called Mega Man
like in the game everyone calls him Mega Man
like that's his actual name
and you know of course
it's supposed to be rock
and it literally like spoils
the plot because like
sort of the twist at the end
of
Mega Man
Legends is that
you find this like a fucking
this ancient like fucking computer system
and this guy who like
is a part of that
recognizes you
and he says oh you've had your memory wiped
you don't remember oh
your name is Mega Man Trigger
I'm Mega Man Juno and we are Mega Man
and we're part of this thing and you go like what
huh what are you talking about
I'm just rock
and it's like kind of the whole fucking point of the game
and they spoiled it because they thought
American kids wouldn't
want to play the game if his name was not Mega Man
very irritating
yeah
I mean I guess it's
slightly different because it's Mega Man Trigger
like if there's like lore like Mega Man
is like a mythical figure
but yeah I mean the thing is
you meet this guy called Mega Man Juno
and that's
supposed to be the first time you've heard of a
Mega Man and it's like I don't know
what that is but I guess you're saying
that I am whatever you are
like the fact that they've
been calling you Mega Man
the whole time is like well why would
they do that I think
I'm not sure if it's in the game
like the manual or something
but somewhere there's a reference to
the idea that
role named Mega Man Mega Man
they found him as an orphan
and she named him that because
she liked Mega Man the video game
and she named him after the video game character
which is so stupid
but I don't know it's just
yeah the name is
supposed to be like a twist reveal
at the very end and they just were like
nah kids will be
confused if his name is Rock
we can't do that
it would even have been better to go
with like the later thing
that they did where they sort of ret
in the remakes they retcon it
because you know in the English he's Rock
but when he's in his battle form he's Rock Man
so there's a couple games
where they have role call him Mega
when he's not in battle
mode and then Mega Man
when he's in battle mode and like that sucks
but that would have
sort of preserved
that would have sort of preserved the
twist
hey man
you're not just any man
you're part of a long line of Mega Man
we found you as an orphan
and I named you Man after
after your genitalia
after the people
after the species that you belong to
the thing about
the thing about the people
okay
they do call the people
carbons but they don't really explain what that means
I think it's only in like
director commentary and like people asking
the game devs like on twitter
like what's up with the carbons
I think that's the only place
that they really explain that like
oh yeah carbons can just fucking pull
their body parts off and replace their entire bodies
with robot parts if they feel like it
lol and it's like oh okay
and then once you know that
you can kind of look back and see like oh yeah
some of them do seem to have like
robot bodies for no reason
and I guess that explains it
uh
but it's like I don't think they ever
maybe in two they make it more explicit
but in one there's like literally no hint
at all that that's the case
it seems it's very strange
uh yeah
like
carbony games
huh
what
should we end the episode
uh
that was the last
his voicemail is done
yep
oh yeah that's basically you were just saying
I just started to ramble about
Mega Man again
um I will
just say
that if you're still waiting on a lord of ghosts
or commission I'm very sorry
I will keep working at it
no
and hopefully it will be done soon
enough and then I can get on to
making cool shit in like September
if you are still
waiting on a commission
shame on you
you gave give depression
no
you did this aren't you ashamed
yourself do not
do not give give
your business in the future because
look what it is look what you have wrought
money is the root of all
problems for a shame yes
exactly
no no please give me money
in the future I promise I won't feel
bad afterwards
oh you know what I have one other thing
I bought um I bought several
different kinds of green rock
for um
for for the you know
I had that idea that maybe
I could give give podrans
as a part of the kickstarter
you know what really quickly let me
I got a bunch that look like shit
uh and then I got three
that look kinda good
so here let me
really quickly just show you
the good ones
let me ask your opinion
about these
oh these actually
kind of look a little more green in my
camera than they do in
in real life but
we'll just have to deal with that
when I was a kid I really liked
rocks and minerals and stuff
and you know what
they're still kinda neat
yeah actually
I mean it's like
the earth but like
the best parts of the earth
oh you I just I looked
at my camera roll
and I just saw a bunch of
of funny pictures
that I took of myself in the mirror
wherein I moved wherein I
combed my hair in the least flattering
way possible
I made it look as bad as I could make it
and I took pictures of it like because it was funny
and it kind of is funny but
I just saw it again and I'm like oh no
that's
that's the reality
I can't see the light of day
I would never I'm not gonna
honestly I mean honestly I made it look
that it's almost like this is like a comedy
character if I could do
I could do this is like a bit this could this
would be my like
my worst guy ever would have his hair
like this and let's look ridiculous
does it look like Neil Hamburger
let me
see what he looks like
Neil
it's like a
Greg Tarkington
comedy character
I mean not quite but
I mean that's sort of
that sort of thing yeah
like bizarre comb over the forehead
wow
yeah
these
these podrans look
like powdered like they look like
Turkish delight I feel like I could bite into them
yeah and they'd be jelly
I also have the
urge to do that
you know what I could do
this would this would be really stupid but you know
what I could do is I could make what if I made
like an epoxy mold
of these like rocks and then I made
like gummies in the shape
of these rocks
I mean they would just sort of be
like a weird
polygon
you wouldn't really know that they were made
from real rocks
but maybe I mean they might have
the they might have some of the texture on them
yeah
I don't know but but anyway
yeah these are the one on the left is
fluorite the one on the right
is
I think it might
also be fluorite I think
it's quartz
the one on the top is calcite
I want to eat that
fluorite so bad
I'm not sure which one I like
the best like the fluorite is kind of
bluish and the
calcite is kind of pale yellowish
green and then the quartz
is kind of just kind of medium
I guess
wait what is what kind
of quartz what kind of quartz is
this
don't you got any emeralds
I don't know it's just called
green quartz I guess
emeralds are expensive
you know you can buy peridots
you can buy like rough raw peridots
but they're really you can only get them really small
like the size of a pea
like that's not good enough
so
no that's just that's just not
that's just not going to do it
these all
these all cost
the calcite is a little more expensive
for like ten dollars I got like
five of these little pieces
of calcite for the same price
I got about like twice as many
of the other two
but I mean it's still not just not that expensive
so like whatever
I don't know
viewers tell me which rock you think
looks the best
which would you most like to receive
in a
package I guess
based on this image I want
the floor I think it's like very good floor
you like the floor
hmm because it's more
turquoisey it's got the turquoisey
it's got the white streaks like the pony
hmm yeah that's true
yeah it's just kind of got like
it's just kind of a rough
a rough surface that sort of
has like more like
kind of cleavage
so to speak
in it and that sort of gives it like a white
kind of
more reflected surface
because like makes it a little more
like opaque like instead of letting the light
go through it
all the way to just let the green shine through
yeah
anyway these foam almost
yeah anyway these are my rocks
these are my rocks
I hope you enjoyed
there are many like it but these ones are mine
true true
I almost want to just buy more
just like
I already have all the like
kinds of rock samples that I wanted but I'm tempted
just like what if I just went back to Amazon
and just ordered the same things
again but just from different companies
just to have more
and to just see like maybe these
maybe these ones have nicer fluorite
maybe these ones give me bigger quartz
hmm
and I like them
uh
maybe I'll do that
I mean I'll need more than this
if I do the Kickstarter
and I am doing the Kickstarter that's not in question
so I mean I'll have to buy it anyway
yeah hell yeah I'm doing it
I'm splurging
oh my god more rocks please
careful not to eat them
you'll become the thing
I do they are tempting
I do get tempted to put them in my mouth
and bite them and then I'm like
that would hurt my teeth
you could do you could do
you could break a tooth through in that even as a joke
so I shouldn't even consider it
uh
anyway that's all
that's all I got
all right
that's the show
probably that's the end
wait a minute wait a minute
let's go in front of the three hours
I had an idea I did have an idea
I think it wouldn't work
I had the idea that what if
okay the same like fluorescent powder
that I put in the slime to make it glow under UV light
I was thinking like
is there some way I could apply it to these
and I thought what if I like sort of
made a solution of that fluoride
fluorescent powder and like dipped these rocks in it
and then
would that like make them glow
and I think the answer is no
I think all that would happen is
maybe they might have a faint glow
but it would only be on the surface
it wouldn't have the sort of like deep
inner glow that the slime
has because it is suffused with the material
these would only have a little bit
of glowiness on their surface
and also I think because the stuff
would only be in a suspension in water
it would not like truly soluble
I think it would just sort of dry out
and become sort of a little bit of powder
that would get on the surface
and it would just come off on your hands
and just be shit
so that probably wouldn't work
I don't know how helpful this will be
or whether it would be even
slightly viable for you
but I remember this video from Nile Red
who figured out how to make
his own glow in the dark
plastic these
well glow in
oh I mean actually
if it's a rock
it doesn't have to be edible
because the slime needed an edible fluorescent ingredient
and you can get fluorescent stuff that's edible
but there's not really glow in the dark
stuff that's edible
so maybe
there's some
topical thing I could apply
that could make these rocks genuinely glow
in the dark that would be pretty neat
I will watch this video later
it's a chunky video
but he goes through
every step of the chemistry
actually might be a little too over the top
for what you're doing
but it certainly is interesting
well he's making
it seems like he's making
a substrate
he's making the plastic itself
I'm wondering if I can
apply a glowing surface
to something
which might be a little different
but I mean this is still interesting
I'll probably watch this anyway
sweet
yeah
that's probably the actual end of the video
goodbye everybody
that's the end of the episode become a patron
become a patron
patreon.com slash the procrastinators
and
get the bonus episodes
get the minecraft
server
access
we will play minecraft again as soon as my internet
is
in working order
yeah
anyway see you next week
everybody goodbye
goodbye
yeah