Hello and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I am your hero and God Emperor, the best guy ever, Bestie Boy.
Thanks for joining us once again. And today, we've got, in addition to our regular Digibro over here.
Hey buddy boy.
My partner in crime. We've got two outsiders, two guest people as we like to have some times, who in recent times, I've become friends with who I really like.
And I think make great videos that you guys should definitely check out. And you probably already have, to be honest.
So first is The Gaming Brit.
I hate these things because this is why I've got to introduce myself and sound all charismatic just by saying my name.
It's okay. The only goal is to let people hear your voice so they can distinguish you later.
My name is Charlie. I do The Gaming Brit on YouTube. I review games.
Yeah, like Hyperbit Hero is here with us. He was the one who said, yo, yo Charlie, I'm gonna be on PCP tomorrow.
Yeah. That's right.
And he was like, you're not invited.
And I was like, yo, you've watched this podcast before, right? Things get savage. You're gonna need someone in there backing you up, man.
Like, you got him. You got him. You got him.
So he was like, okay. You don't just do PCP without a partner. It's a dangerous drug.
This is a tag team match. So let's hear from you Hyperbit Hero. What's happening?
Not much.
Well, there you have it. All right. All right. So we're doing things a little differently today.
So we're gonna start with one topic. And if things go long, which they probably will, if we run out of stuff to say for the first one,
we still need to fill some fucking time. We're just gonna go into our second one.
But our first one is a sort of, it's sort of nebulously defined right now. We're gonna flush it out.
But the word that I want to use, the word that I want to use is cred fags. You know, cred fags.
There is no Urban Dictionary definition for this because we just made it up. In fact, we should enter this into Urban Dictionary,
our own definition we come up with. How full circle will that be? So why don't, was it Charlie?
Charlie came up with it, right?
Yeah. Why don't you tell us about this?
Well, I just find that today on the internet when, you know, we all tweet, we all do our YouTube videos,
and we all meme it up. Sometimes we're all a bit guilty of doing that. And sometimes, obviously, you know,
people want to be in on the popular things and what other people are playing, what other people are talking about.
And sometimes they go out of their way to try and weasel their way in to these popular things.
Yeah.
Obviously not that interested in just being part of the franchise, the anime or the game.
And it's like so annoying because you get so many questions on YouTube and Twitter and stuff about which parts of this franchise
can I skip and like where should I start. When obviously it's just if you're interested and you care and you want to have
lots of entertainment, just start from the beginning and wake your way up. Like what's the big deal, you know?
I know Hayden gets this a lot as well, especially with the...
The thing is like, you know, they do want to get into it. They just want to get into it as quickly as possible,
as easy as possible. They don't want to fucking experience the story or anything.
Like of course, talking about the Yakuza franchise, that's where I get to ask this all the time.
Listen, you want to get into Yakuza, there's one just called Yakuza. That's the fucking one to do.
Dude, oh my god, I gotta tell you, fucking, I can't tell you how many times I've gotten this question and it baffles me
that anyone has to ask this, which is, what order do I watch Neon Genesis Evangelion?
There's only one order!
There's a TV series called Neon Genesis Evangelion, a movie called The End of Evangelion,
and then a TV show called Rebuild of Evangelion, or a movie series called Rebuild of Evangelion.
I'm not following, you need to break it down.
The watch order is in the title.
And, you know, even a lot of the times you can kind of follow a progression of, you know, one, two, three, four.
They're structured, you know?
Like Charlie's saying, the best advice is usually go to Wikipedia and look at the chronology and watch them in the order they released it.
If you want to be a serious investigative journalist, you can put in the extra mile and go to Wikipedia and look it up, you know?
It baffles me, because even with like the smallest of franchises, it happens, you know, I'm big into my Devil May Cry,
and I get questions like, can I skip to three? Can I just skip all these?
Because I know three is the one with the memes, right? That's the one with all the jokes that I want to be in on.
But the biggest joke is Devil May Cry 2, though.
It's like, there are four games, guys.
You don't, like, that's what confuses me, right?
And numbered for your pleasure.
Hold on, Charlie. Are you saying you think everyone should play DMC 2?
Like, even knowing that it's...
You know, I am two ways about that, actually, because it is a terrible game,
but at the same time, if you play two and then you play three, it's like, whoa, you're experiencing this jumping quality, you know?
I have a lot of sympathy for that viewpoint.
I agree. I would like everyone to play.
If they, like, you know, people bring up Final Fantasy as an example of games that you pretty much can skip,
but I would really like it if people would, when they get into the series, play all of them in order,
because that gives you so much context and, like, a lot can be lost if you don't...
And I didn't. I started with Seven, it was my first Final Fantasy,
but I look back at what old fags have done when they've played through the whole series in order,
and seeing that growth happen is such a beautiful thing.
And that's when, like, they talk about, like, classical long-term fans.
Yeah, then the disappointment when you get to 13 can be all the more sweet.
Yeah, that's right.
If you boot up Devil May Cry 3 and experience that opening after playing through two
and the way far that it was, it's like, like, it intensifies the passion of that scene, you know?
And you know what else it does as an ancillary benefit is if you start...
Let's say, like, a new person started playing Final Fantasy when 13 came out,
and they're like, I'm gonna play 13. It's numbered 13 of the series, but I'm gonna start with this.
And if they don't like it, they're like, well, Final Fantasy's done, you know, I'm done with it.
Like, Hayden, tell them how silly it is, especially with Yakuza,
how people want to start so much with Yakuza 3.
Because 3 isn't that good compared to 2 at all.
Well, it's because Yakuza 3 literally begins with the ending of Yakuza 2.
Like, it's a continuation of, like, the same cutscene?
I think, no, I think, because especially with Yakuza, it's such a seasonal series, really,
when you think about, like, each game is like a season, really, and like a long-running crime drama.
So it's like the silliest series.
Hey, there's some people who jump into TV shows like Season 5.
You know, I'll say, I mean, for some defense of this, I do think that it's entirely possible
to play one of the later ones, and then, you know, that makes you want to go back and do the rest.
And I think, depending on the series, it can be fine.
Like, you know, the Souls series, for instance.
Like, Demon's Souls was not very widely known, because it was a PSD exclusive,
it was a, like, not an indie game, but it was like, you know, not, well, it's a weird obscure Japanese game.
Dark Souls then blew up super huge, and I do think a lot of Dark Souls fans went back and played Demon's Souls,
you know, and like, and most people got into it through Dark Souls, but it also wasn't even presented as though it were a sequel.
That's fine though, it's like, it's when people like with Yakuza start asking, is there a recap of two and one in three?
Can I just read it?
Yeah, it's when you start to ask the questions, like, what can I do to make up for the fact that I haven't played the first games?
It's like, just fucking play them, dude.
I would never tell people to not jump into a series at any point.
I have to play Devil's Advocate here, because my brother Victor is a hardcore cred-fag.
I think we're using this term correctly, but he, because me and him have gotten into arguments over this,
specifically because of me following Charlie and Hayden on Twitter,
because I've seen these guys make this argument over and over again that like,
if you want to get into a franchise, play them all, right?
And I've thought about it and been like, yeah, you know, I kind of agree.
I think it's the healthiest way, you know, I've never played through like Metal Gear, for instance,
but if I did, I would want to start from Metal Gear Solid because,
Oh yeah, for sure, for sure.
For what it's worth, technically you should start from Metal Gear, but you know, like,
I would like to play all of them in order if I was going to.
And my brother Victor, who has only played through Metal Gear Solid 4,
Oh no, the worst one.
But it's one of his favorite games ever.
And here's where we get into something complicated, because Victor's argument is,
yeah, but you'll never play them, which is a sound argument.
Because for instance, okay, the Witcher series, right?
Super Bunny Hub did this whole video series on the three Witcher games and I was like, cool.
Now I kind of understand them and stuff and it really seems to me like the Witcher 3 is the only one I'm going to really get into.
Because the Witcher 2 seems like it's too hard and the Witcher 1 seems like the controls suck.
So like, why not just skip to Witcher 3, but at the same time,
I know that there's a lot of references to the past games,
that there's a sort of an ongoing narrative through all three games.
And so I keep saying to my brother, like, I'd really like to play through Witcher 1 and 2.
And he's like, yeah, but you'll never do it.
You will never play through Witcher 1 and 2.
And there's a chance you'll miss out on what could be one of your favorite games, Witcher 3, if you just play it.
But you'll never play it because you're waiting for Witcher 1 and 2.
And I don't think he's wrong, because I don't think I'll ever play through all three of them.
But why won't you play them?
Because I don't really play a lot of video games in the first place.
So it's like a time management thing.
But when I look at myself with that argument, like, I played all the Final Fantasies
and there's a million of them.
And it's, you know, I think that that kind of argument.
I played them all in high school, didn't you, when you had like lots of time
and like you could just do that.
But all that is, is that's making concessions.
You're making concessions to not take on a responsibility to do something.
And like, if you're willing to compromise, then okay, you can go be a guy who manages his time efficiently,
but you're also a cred fag.
That's the trade I've been making.
That's what it is, you know?
Yeah.
Oh, sorry, go on.
No, you can go ahead.
No, I was just going to say that I feel like whenever I'm like,
because I'm in the same position with the Witcher,
I feel like the third game looks really interesting
but I want to play the other two first and I'm going around to it.
But I feel like when I don't get around to it, I'm just going on to play another thing.
And the thing that weirds me out about cred fags is, you know,
it seems like people just want to have, like, to me, playing a long series, playing a lot of content,
it's still content and entertainment.
And that's why I really don't get why you'd want to sort of spend more money on more products and more things
when you have a few that can sustain you for a long time.
Yeah, that deeply fascinates me as well.
And I, from observing my brother, who at this point I'm thinking of as the ultimate cred fag,
because he does everything that we're insulting here.
Fuck you, Victor.
Like, watching the way he plays games, like, he can seemingly only get excited about a game
if there's some kind of hype, you know?
Like, even if it's just him, even if no one else cares about the game, it has to be, like, new and fresh.
Because, like, he has all these...
He sounds like a big LMFAO fan.
He has so many games that he has never beaten.
Which I am too, by the way.
Shut up.
He has so many games that he's never beaten, that he'll never go back to,
that he has, like, you know, this huge stockade of games.
But for some reason, it'll be like, you know, a new game comes out and he's like,
I'm gonna go buy that.
And I'm like, well, what about the last game you never finished?
And he's like, yeah, but I'm not hype about that.
This one's a new game.
And so it's new and now I'm excited, you know?
And it's like, if he doesn't play through a game when it's new and all at once,
and, like, beat it, then he'll never beat it, you know?
If it stops being new and it fades into the background of his collection,
he'll never finish it.
It'll just sit there forever.
You know, I can't, like, say that that's wrong or anything,
but, like, that's just, that's a very emotion-driven reason to play games
as opposed to any kind of intellectual reason, which is, you know, it's fine.
There's nothing wrong with that, but I feel differently.
It's just weird to watch, because I'm always like,
there's, because for me, I get excited to go play a bunch of Super Nintendo games.
You know, like, for me, the idea of spending $60 on a new game is such an ordeal,
because, like, you know, newer games are longer,
and they really ask for more, like, investment on your time and energy,
and, like, I don't have patience for, like, the cinematic games that come out these days.
You know, we're like, if I'm gonna have to sit through, like,
10 minutes of, like, them taking control away from me, the game's not worth my time anymore.
Like, I need to be, you know, I like Dark Souls and Doom.
Like, those are the recent games that I've enjoyed,
and so, like, and even Doom fucking pissed me off when it did take control away from you.
How long were those sections that it did that? That was too scary.
I would say there's probably grand total 10 minutes of, of, like, forced cutscene.
Yeah, I didn't find it too much.
Compared to what's out there, that's great, but in a game like Doom, it's gonna be annoying.
Yeah, it's still annoying.
And you can't skip it even when you replay the levels.
That's what's particularly annoying.
It's like, guys, look at us being so cheeky, saying fuck, being forced to watch cinematic sequences
through a forced cinematic sequence.
Yeah, that was really obnoxious.
But, but anyways, like, you know, for me, the idea of, like, going out, spending $60 on a game,
that's gonna go down to 20 bucks in six months anyways.
You know, like, for me, it's like an anti-hype cycle.
A new game comes out and everyone gets hyped about it, and I take one look at the price tag,
and I'm like, I don't want to play that for a year.
That's a very, that's a very interesting point, because I think something me and Hayden find
when we're recommending PS2 games that are hard to find, it's like that, like, they find the PS2 game on eBay,
and it's like $40, and it's like, ugh, I don't want to pay $40 for a PS2 game,
but you'll go out and buy the latest shitfest for, like, $50.
Yeah, I love that argument when you made it.
This PRR, thank you.
Yeah, well, like, the, yeah, and I went out because, like, based on Hayden's videos,
I've bought, like, Folklore, which was like 20 bucks, and it was, you know, an older game.
It shouldn't probably be $20, but I wanted that game.
I didn't want to just own a game because it's new.
Like, it's, like, like you said, these are classic games.
It's like if someone was saying, I don't want to pay $15 for Super Mario RPG,
it's like, but you think it's going to be one of your favorite games?
You know, like, that's the funniest thing to me is I'll have people say, like,
oh, that game is a classic, and I've wanted to play it for 10 years, but it's 20 bucks,
and that's too much, and it's like, if it's a classic, it's going to be worth more
than any of the new games that you play.
To play Devil's Advocate, maybe they just feel that way because they have been told
that old games are cheap, and having to pay more money for an old game just conflicts
with what they expect to, you know, do for that.
So, but whatever, I agree.
I agree.
Me and Aiden, here's the thing.
The ultimate cred-fag move is to buy a game because you heard it's good,
just to own it and not play it just to have it on your shelf like a figure or something like that.
So when people come over, they look at your shelf and think, oh, where?
This guy's got a music case and video game.
God, I wish I could believe there's no one like that,
but I know there's people like that.
That's like on another level.
That's like a level where it's like none of us would ever know a person like that.
You know what's like a more reasonable...
Like a woman in disguise, man.
I can see something like that happening when like, you get it.
Like, if you're like a rich kid that your parents just buy shit for you
and they give you a bunch of games and stuff, you know, like FIFA, 2,000...
Aiden's in the military.
I could see this happening there.
In fact, my ex-girlfriend was a little bit like this
because she was in the Air Force and she would just spend lots and lots of money.
And so she would buy a lot of games that she would just never actually play
because she just bought them to spend money, you know?
You gotta spend your money.
Steam has kind of caused that with Steam sales because prices get so low,
you can't afford not to buy these games.
I remember years ago, years ago, Hayden, you told me that one of your friends was like,
I'm gonna buy all the Metal Gear toys even though he hadn't played any of the games.
That was a friend, he said he was gonna buy like a giant couple hundred dollar
like Metal Gear Rex figure even though he's never played any of the games.
I mean, I guess if you really like the design, then that can, you know, exist outside the games.
I don't think he ever showed interest in Metal Gear Solid aside from that.
He's like, I'm gonna buy this shit, bro.
Interesting.
And you know, there's a whole other side to this that we haven't really talked about
which is when people buy specifically obscure things for the sake of them being obscure
and being able to tell on places like V on 4chan, like,
you guys, have you even heard of these fucking games I'm playing right now?
But they're obviously the best because you don't know about them.
And I think they're objectively right.
Yes.
That's my stance.
Yeah, I don't know, like, I don't know how, it's hard to gauge that.
That's really a music thing a lot of the time, but people do that music all the time.
I don't know.
It's hard to gauge with those things because there's, like, how do we know if they don't just like the thing, you know?
But I do, I mean, obviously posturing happens and I think it's a thing people do.
But I don't know.
Personally, I'm someone who loves seeking out obscure shit for real,
so I'll just go out and watch every weird fucking thing, you know?
What's the point of posturing to anonymous people?
To feel good about yourself.
Dude, you haven't gotten addicted to the use, man.
They don't know who you are, though.
Yeah.
But it doesn't, you're a person on the internet.
Well, that's what you have a 3x3 for.
You see, if you have a 3x3 that shows what your favorites are and you post it on 4chad
and it looks like you have great taste, then everyone will give you...
No, but Digi, you've created the opposite effects now when you were complaining about 3x3s
because now people are going to try and make 3x3s on purpose to get cred that aren't cred.
Because you...
You were complaining about too much.
3x3s became a fucking nightmare after I made that video.
Because now people are like, to get cred, I've got to talk about things that don't have cred.
Oh, shit.
On each of these sites, there's a different sort of internet currency.
And in the case of the 3x3s, there's a new currency which is like the Digi buck,
which is like, it's endorsed by the degree to which people are here.
Oh, god, I really never thought of it this way.
It's how I could trust any of them.
You can't trust any 3x3 again?
They've all been, they've all got ulterior motives, theoretically, so they cannot be trusted.
Well, I like to think the result of this is just that everyone is now willing to put kill or kill on their 3x3s.
I think that's the only major difference I've made and I think that's a proud thing to have done.
You know the worst thing about cred-fagging is when it backfires on people?
Like, I've seen people like on Twitter, they ask like, where should I start with JoJo?
And then someone in the comments will be like, that's the one.
That's the one I was trying to think of.
People always ask what they can skip when they're reading fucking JoJo.
Read the whole thing, you piece of shit.
They're like, but that's the thing.
Being a cred-fag can get you into trouble because then you can get replies from like, just like,
dunderheads who are like, start with part 3.
Part 3 is the best, because it has the radio.
Part 2 is objectively superior to part 3 people.
Accept it.
Well, that's the funny thing about JoJo is like, everyone seems to have their favorite part
and like, people talk about which ones are the best.
Personally, I think JoJo is always like, the same.
Like, there are differences in each arc, but the tone of the series is always the exact same.
It's always over the top, scatological, insane, you know.
I'm a JoJo savant expert, super empowered, brilliant man.
And I can tell you that when people are making that argument, what they're really talking about
are the characters and like, the specific stands and as well as the general slight difference in tone.
Like, part 4 is like, a slice of life with stands.
And that's really fun, which is why it's one of the better parts.
But it's also like, I mean, I don't think it's that, like in terms of what's going on moment to moment.
It's not that different from every other JoJo's.
That's entirely true.
If the tone is the same the whole time, that's all the more reason to start at the beginning
because it's not going to get a super different experience if you start at part 4 or part 3 or whatever.
But you see, that cuts to the nature of what crowd fagging is, which is,
they just want to get to the stuff that's most commonly discussed
so they can be a part of the conversation as quickly as possible.
I think the worst example I've ever seen is Link.
Hayden sent me to NeoGaff of some guy who played Dark Souls.
Do you want to explain it, Hayden?
I don't remember this.
Oh, you don't remember?
It was like, he's like, I've played Dark Souls and I've been told that a lot of the...
This is a NeoGaff Fred, so of course it's gonna be like,
I've heard that all these designs are from Berserk.
Tell me.
Oh yeah.
Which parts of the Berserk manga can I skip?
Oh my god!
Oh no!
Just to see the references.
The fucking Berserk manga.
Just read the whole thing.
Why would you do this?
The man doesn't want to get triggered obviously, which is understandable.
I mean, I kind of, like when something is broken up into parts,
it's a little easier to understand, right?
You got, you know, okay, there's the first game, the second game,
maybe they had different staff behind them,
maybe they're not quite the same type of game.
The Berserk manga is just one ongoing manga.
There's no like, you know, it's not like Gunsmith Cats
where there's like Gunsmith Cats and Gunsmith Cats Burst, you know,
like there's two different...
No, it's just all Berserk!
Why would you think it's okay to skip any of it?
And you know, I gotta tell you, the thing that I,
since we're talking about examples of this that infuriate us,
the one that really sticks out to me is people in all seriousness
will just, I don't know how they do it,
but they will just jump into reading one piece.
Like, and a lot of it happened during the giant war in the middle of the series
where all the characters were coming together throughout the series
to like, do something, and these people,
there is no way they could have known what the fuck was going on,
who any of these people were, what the stakes were.
Everything in one piece builds on itself because it's a story,
it's a continuous linear story.
No, it's just all all so random.
To me, to me, like, it excites me.
If I start something good from the beginning
and I know there's like hundreds and hundreds,
like loads of content coming up,
does that excite me?
I'm like, oh shit, I'm not like,
well, you see, I don't know who the characters are in Opening 14,
which I watched on YouTube, so I'm just going to skip to that part.
It's like, no.
It's like, I want to go on the journey, man.
I want to go on the journey.
The only argument I can even kind of accept is that like,
my life is too busy, I don't have time to do all this.
Like, it's not a good argument.
Like, you're being a cred-fag when you do that,
but it's like, I get it.
Well, here's the thing.
Here's another thing.
I think a big part of this is also that all four of us are
analytically minded YouTube journalists of a sort
about these mediums, right?
Right.
And I think the way that we, because how do I put this?
None of us give a fuck what's current and new,
and I think this really reflects,
because I've been following Hayden and Charlie here
for over three years on YouTube,
and neither one of them has-
I haven't been following myself that long.
Neither one of them has ever really been someone
who makes videos about new games,
unless those are games that are, like,
really relevant to the franchises that they talk about.
You guys have made a couple Uncharted 4 and, like,
DMC videos, but, like, you didn't cover fucking
BioShock Infinite when it came out, you know,
or, like, the last of us in any depth.
And even in that brilliant Metal Gear Solid 5 video
by our friend the Gaming Brick here,
a lot of that was about the context of the entire series
and why it, you know, it's legacy stuff, you know?
But these are guys who go back and do fucking
a bunch of Devil May Cry videos
at a time when, you know, like-
Bayonetta's the new thing.
No one would be talking about it, yeah.
Or just anything, you know, they talk about older games.
I go back, I talk about tons of older anime.
Nate, you've only so far covered shit that,
well, I don't know.
You did Monster Musume.
I did Monster Musume, that's the one.
I got one.
Oh, yeah, that's true.
Oh, yeah, and One Punch Man.
Well, that doesn't apply to you at all.
It was a little late on One Punch Man, but, like-
Ah, fuck you.
But the point is that we're the kind of people who,
I think we care about history and we care about classics
and we care about going back and finding the best stuff
of the medium, and I think that a lot of these credit fags,
all they care about, like Charlie said,
is being a part of the conversation.
It's all about, like-
They care about being in on the meme.
That's what it's about.
They see something trending on Twitter
and they want to, as quickly as possible, get it.
Whereas I see something trending on Twitter
and I'm like, I don't fucking care.
I'll get to it when I get to it.
If everyone's talking about, like, Metal Gear Solid 5,
I don't run out and go, I need to play Metal Gear Solid 5
so I understand what everyone's saying.
I'm like, one day I'll play all the Metal Gear Solid games
if I get around to it, and then I can know all the memes.
But I don't-
I mean, no hurry, because I'd rather-
I would much rather know the entire story
than know a part of it so that I can be-
So I can spit memes for the two weeks that the game is relevant
and then immediately fades into-
You can't play MGS5 and then just pretend to be mad
about the things they missed.
Right.
Yeah, yeah.
And you know, it's totally-
Oh god, I totally forgot what I was going to say.
God damn it.
And I think I satiate my desire to keep up with stuff
because I just watched tons and tons of analysis videos.
So I know a startling amount about Metal Gear Solid 5
because I watched, you know, I watched our good friend Jesse
play through like a lot of the game on the Blue Glow.
I watched Charlie's analysis of it.
Bunnyhop wrote a bunch of videos about it.
So like I get why everyone feels the way that they do.
And yeah, like Charlie said, like me jumping in now,
I would feel so much less than what Charlie felt.
You know, like watching his video, I understand,
okay, this is what the series veterans are feeling.
But if I play the game, I'm not going to feel those things.
I'm not going to feel anything.
I'm just going to be like, oh, it's a game.
You know, I don't know what the fuck-
I don't know what who these characters are,
who the fuck is Big Boss.
I don't know.
You know, I kind of think of it like,
I really do consider myself an educator, among other things.
And like, it's not like because someone came up with a new idea
that we like throw out the old one when it comes to like,
okay, your times tables, like those are fine,
but I've got like a new version,
and I'm going to teach everyone this.
It's like, you take the best ideas throughout history,
and that's really my interest,
is finding the things that are the best examples of what they do
and highlighting them so that we can improve them
and people can learn from them in various ways.
Well, you're talking about educating, Nate,
and the thing is never give the cred fag any leeway
just because you want somebody to be into something you like.
Because even in that Berserk example I gave you,
there were people with Berserk avatars in that post saying,
well, I guess you can skip this part of the thing.
It's like, no.
Oh, no.
Never give anyone else.
People just go with Yakuza saying,
yeah, you know, you can skip to three.
There are recaps of the first two games.
You don't need to watch them.
You know, you can just read a fucking Wikipedia article
about them and know the story.
It's like, that's the worst part.
It's like, each one of these games has its own story
and like, twists and...
And it's a real shame with Yakuza,
because like two is so good.
It's like, it's such a fun game.
Two is like the best story in the entire series.
After two, the entire storyline for each one of the games
fucking takes a huge dip.
But you know, I'm with you on this,
but just to play Devil's Advocate,
I do understand people's urgent desire.
It really ties back to the human desire to be loved
and be in a community.
They want to be in on the thing that everyone's talking about.
So there's a desperation to know,
the game of Thrones is talking about Game of Thrones,
which has happened to a lot of people out there.
It's like, oh man, I want to be in.
I want to know.
And so a lot of people, just out of sheer,
this is pretty philosophical now,
out of a sheer desire to be loved
and to be a member of the human species,
they will do, they will, as soon as possible,
cut to the chase of understanding the idea
that is, you know, caught on with the people they know
in their lives.
Well, guess what, bitch?
I'll never love you if you don't.
I think with video games, though,
there's this whole technology element where it's like,
I don't want to play on those old systems.
Me and Hayden talk about this all the time,
and it's the fact that, oh, that PS2
has this icky vibe to it.
I want the HD thing.
That's some bullshit, because the PS2
does not give me icky vibes.
Playing shit on the PS3 gives me icky vibes,
because it's just fucking all the games run like ass.
Yeah.
And it's the same for, like, you know,
old anime or something, like, the animation.
Oh, man.
And it's four by three.
Yeah, yeah.
There was another NeoGaff thread where it was like,
Hayden said, it was like,
when Yakuza 5 was getting localized and some guy was like,
well, if it's not on PS3, like, he owned a PS3,
but he was like, yeah, you're exciting, Hayden.
I already packed my PS3 up into the attic.
I ain't getting it back down.
Hello.
I've seen a lot of stuff like that.
But that's the real shit, dude.
Those are the real reasons people use to, like,
dismiss works of art or whatever,
because they don't want to fucking unpack their old TV or whatever.
That's always been funny to me, because, you know,
people talk about, like, backwards compatibility,
and I think that...
I think all these consoles should have it.
But it's always been really funny to me that people make,
like, such a huge deal about it,
because I still have all my consoles, you know?
Now, I wish I didn't have to, like,
when I went out to buy Yakuza as a result of Hayden's video,
I was sans PS2,
because seven of them have broken on me over the years,
so I had to go buy a new one,
but it was, like, $25, you know?
And it would have been nice
if I could have just popped that fucking disc into my PS4,
my fucking supercomputer sitting on my desk,
but whatever, you know?
This idea that you, like, have to pack away your old consoles
and never touch them again,
it just reeks of not giving a fuck about history
and old games and being, like, I'm never going back,
I'm never playing something old.
I do think the companies that make these things
should play a role in preserving that
with the backwards compatibility, though.
I agree, I agree.
But here's the thing, those people don't have those consoles,
because they're the ultimate cred fags,
and they didn't play games until recently.
Oh!
They were young for what it's worth.
They were fucking young.
But those old consoles, like I said, are fucking cheap.
I went out and bought, like, I literally went to,
I was at a used game store,
and it's like, oh, there's Yakuza, and there's a PS2,
and this is less than $50 combined, you know?
I mean, I guess if you're 10, that's a lot,
but that's less than what a new game would have cost.
A whole console and a great game for that console
was less than buying one shitty new fucking $60 game.
But I think this is particularly bad in gaming,
which is probably why we're using so many gaming examples,
and there's a great article that I read this one time
that I wish I could remember what it's called,
because I cite it all the time,
but there's this guy who was a professor
teaching game design at a college,
and he decided to run a little experiment
where he asked everybody in the crowd,
who hears the fan of the Elder Scrolls games,
and like 80% of the class raised their hand,
and he said, who all has played Skyrim
and all those hand-staters?
Oh, yeah.
Then he said, who's all has played Oblivion,
and like more than half of the hands went down,
and then he says, who's played Morrowind,
and it's like two guys left,
and then he's like, who's played Daggerfall?
Nobody, right?
And he's like, you know,
you say you're a fan of the Elder Scrolls,
but you're really a fan of Skyrim,
and you clearly have no context of the history
of this franchise, and it's like,
it's so weird that people seem to think,
especially when it comes to games,
that the newest one is just the best one,
just because it's the newest,
and they have no interest in looking back
and finding out if there's anything different
or interesting or better about the old games,
which in something like the Elder Scrolls,
a lot of people consider Morrowind the best one,
and these people will never know.
The advantages of that one,
because it doesn't look new like Skyrim.
I'm so glad you got to this point,
because at least for me, and maybe not everybody agrees,
because not everybody sees games the way I
and possibly the rest of you do,
it is not about the most polished presentation,
what matters about all art
is the density of valuable ideas,
and the density of artistic merit,
and that is what it's about,
and that's why a game that looks like,
just for example Final Fantasy VII,
it looks pretty ass, is so widely loved,
because it is so much density.
Don't say it looks ass, it has dated graphics.
I don't even agree with that.
The graphical design is fantastic,
it's just that it has dated graphics,
but that doesn't...
I think that that game looks better
than most modern games with state-of-the-art graphics,
because the art design is great.
You're shaming me, you're schooling me on my own game.
Let's not even get started on stuff like Silent Hill 2,
and 3 and stuff that look amazing on PS2,
and now the updates come along,
and that's the version I have to play,
because I don't want to PS2.
If you guys have seen the amazing videos
by the real Silent Hill experience,
the real Silent Hill experience by Twin Perfect,
the way that they so clearly lay out the case,
that in Silent Hill 3, for example,
every room had unique assets
that were specifically constructed
to evoke a specific scare and emotion for that room,
versus in downpour,
it's like the same fucking desk with pencil and paper
in the exact same location,
like a thousand times in an empty world
where there's nothing to do,
and not even random spawning monsters.
That's the difference between creating a piece of art
and creating a product, like downpour.
That's right.
But it's the newest one, so I gotta skip to it.
The gaming press perpetuates this,
and not just in the whole buy-the-new-game thing,
in the whole recent trend of people going,
finally, games are getting good.
And I'm not saying there aren't great games at the moment,
but there's this culture that...
Yeah, the whole Citizen Kane game
has become legitimized only recently.
Everyone was retarded before no one
you had to make a game for the PS3.
The fucked up part is in any other medium,
I feel like you would get laughed out of a room
if you tried to be a critic who hasn't seen the classics.
If you're a film critic,
and you haven't seen Citizen Kane,
then people are gonna be like,
what the fuck are you doing?
Why have you not seen the Godfather?
I've never seen the Godfather,
but I'm gonna review a gangster movie.
People are gonna be like, why would you ever do that?
You clearly have no context into what gangster movies are,
because you haven't seen what is considered
by many to be the greatest film of all time.
Did you? All old games are problematic,
so there's no reason to go back and watch them.
You know, guys, the real question I have here
is why are schools wasting our time teaching our kids
with these old-ass books for grandpas?
You know, like, Catcher of the Rye is a million years old.
Let's move on. We've got, you know...
Yeah, we got the right to.
We read an old book like Catcher of the Rye.
You know, Crime and Punishment was great.
Crime and Punishment was great, but we've got a new version.
It's called Death Note. It's better in every way.
Let's just all read Death Note instead.
It is replaced. It is superseded in artistic merit in every way.
That's what I'm saying.
People were fucking Neanderthals until recently,
when we got iPhones.
There's something so, like, sad to me
about the idea that we have, like, so much gaming criticism,
and none of it's looking back.
And, like...
You know, I've made this point before,
and Endless Jess had a great video
called Fuck the Citizen Kane of Gaming,
and both of us were kind of making the point that, like...
If there's a Citizen Kane of Gaming,
it's fucking Super Mario Brothers.
You know, like, that's a classic game.
Every element of it is amazing.
You know, it still holds up to this day.
People still play it.
It's been beloved for decades by people around the world.
How is that not, like, an impeccable classic game?
And how can you really, like, talk about games as a medium
without knowing about it, you know?
I agree. I completely agree with that.
It's the Gazomp-Gazverk, or whatever that word was.
Yeah, Gazomp. I'm not gonna try.
Watch that video by Mr. Beaton. That's the one.
Yeah.
Like, I find that this is just me personally,
but...
And, like, I'm becoming, like...
I guess maybe this even makes me, like, a cred-fag,
but it's, like, I find that, at least with me,
just in terms of this Citizen of Gaming as Super Mario Brothers thing,
I find, like, a lot of people love in America, like, Tatari,
and a lot of people in Britain, like, ZX Spectrum and stuff,
but, like, it feels like, to me...
To what?
The modern video game began with Super Mario Brothers.
Like, if you think about it, like, that's the point to me
where I'm like, damn, games got good.
Like, finally, you know, that's how I feel, at least.
Did any of you guys even beat the original Super Mario Bros?
Or am I hanging out with a bunch of cr-
I have.
I beat it on Game Boy in, like, the third grade.
I remember doing it well.
Dude, World 8 is no joke.
Like, World 8 is no joke.
That's a hard game, dude.
I have beaten Super Mario Brothers by use of save states.
Yeah, alright.
And by which I mean...
By which I mean, I save state after every jump.
Every jump.
Yeah.
That's how I got through that game.
Dude, yo, this neg over here maps save and reload save state
to the X and Y of his controller when he's playing.
You just don't know when you're going to run into a credit flag.
It's like every...
No, I said...
That game is fucking hard.
It's hard.
It's true.
And it's hard in a way that's in fear.
Like, the thing is, I mean, there's an extent to which I'm like,
alright, you have to see everything in order to talk about stuff.
But there's also an extent to which it's like,
I'm not going to play a game I hate, you know.
Yeah, yeah.
Mario Bros. is not my type of game.
Like, it's...
The fucking live system alone is enough to make me not want to play it.
It's designed to be played forever and it's like,
I now live in a world where there's a thousand games I could be playing
as opposed to one that was the one that came with my console
when I was eight and I had all the time in the world.
And I feel like Mario Bros. is a lot easier to play through
in that circumstance as opposed to, like, getting frustrated
and knowing that I could put it down and go do anything else, you know.
Yeah.
I say, like, saying that Super Mario Bros. is like,
where I think games got good makes me a cred fag
because now it's like, hey man, you didn't play Atari.
You don't know what it's like.
You can't appreciate Mario Bros.
Oh, yeah.
Well, you know, like, the distinction between the modern era of video games.
That's true.
I'm just distinguishing errors.
I will say, I feel like a cred fag now
because of the fact that I have always looked,
like, there's certain Atari games.
Like, Adventure is considered to be, like, the first, like,
adventure game, first RPG.
And, like, I always see it on lists of, like, the best ever
just because it's the first, so people feel the need to list it.
But I always look at it and I'm like, yeah, but it looks like shit.
So, obviously, who cares.
But then it's like, well, I haven't actually played it.
What if it's actually really great, you know, for reasons
I couldn't possibly foresee by looking at the graphics.
That's like the grand scheme of the medium, though.
Obviously, if you're looking at a franchise or a series,
like, isolated from the rest, it's like, obviously,
if you're skipping around, then obviously, you know.
It's tough, man.
You've gone full cred on that one.
But, you know, really, we should, like, we're all in the spectrum.
We're all in the cred fag spectrum.
I haven't played, I haven't beaten Sound Hill 1,
but I absolutely love Sound Hill 2 and 3.
Maybe I'll get to 4 someday.
And, you know, I feel a little bad about that,
that I played 3 without playing 1, so I don't have, like, all the content.
But, you know, you only have so many hours in a day, you know.
I'll do it someday.
I want to play.
If I had to put up an argument to people who are, like, you know,
who never go back and who, like, just look at them as, like, old games,
it's like, dude, if they're made a franchise out of it,
chances are the first game was great.
Like, there's got to be a reason people liked it enough
that they could afford to make another one, right?
That's a good argument.
The reason these, like, I mean, people will say, like,
well, okay, but the technology's gotten better, but we've built on it.
But, yeah, but at the same time, those old games have,
they have an art to them.
It's not just about the technology.
And, like, you know, I went back a couple years ago and played Zelda 1,
and I thought it was fucking phenomenal.
And it's a style of game, no other Zelda game has been.
You know, they've all sort of, none of them have that same free form,
roaming, just exploring, having to find everything for yourself.
And, like, if you just look at a picture of Zelda 1,
it just looks like, eh, but the graphics are,
how am I ever going to feel a sense of adventure?
I had a similar experience with that,
because, like, I remember playing Zelda 1 when I was a kid,
and I was like, oh.
But then, like, I played it, like, recently, again, I'm like,
this is amazing.
Like, this is, like, open-ended.
People out there deeply misunderstand, you know,
it's just what we were saying before.
Yeah, they don't appreciate the way that it is the sum total of the parts
of a game that determined the quality,
which is why, you know, we've talked about this before,
like, they can show us all these previews for a game like Final Fantasy XV,
but ultimately, what do we really know,
not a heck of a lot about how it's going to be as a whole game,
which is what ultimately matters in the end, you know?
And, like, my brother, Victor, like, again, Ultimate Cred-Fag,
like, he's a huge die-hard Zelda fan, you know,
and we both got into Zelda through Ocarina of Time.
What is his title now? He's the Ultimate Cred-Fag?
Right.
He's going to listen to this, too.
He will.
But we both got into Zelda with Ocarina of Time,
and, like, you know, he's played all the other ones since then,
whether it's 2D or 3D,
he's played all the ones since Ocarina of Time,
but he's never gone back and played Zelda 1,
and he's barely played a Link to the Past, if at all.
And, like, to him, it's like he sees it as, yeah,
like, for me, Zelda is all about the big, the feeling of scale
and the bigness, you know, his favorite one's Twilight Princess,
because it looks epic.
And I'm like, yeah, but if you actually played Zelda 1,
what you'll find is that the graphics, that fades away,
and mechanically, you feel like you're on an epic adventure
because you have to find everything yourself.
And it's such an interesting feeling to, like, learn this map
to go back and forth to all these locations
and figure things out that, eventually,
it feels like an epic adventure,
and you can't get that through screen caps, you know?
I do sympathize with his position, just in the sense that it sounds like
he doesn't really experience what you're talking about.
Like, he's not really familiar with that particular motion.
But he has no idea, because he hasn't played Zelda 1, you know?
Well, sure.
That's an experience he hasn't had yet, maybe.
I'm not trying to show you, Victor, but he hasn't had it,
so if he had experienced it, that would open his mind to other things
that he can experience, but I get his argument.
It logically makes sense from his perspective,
but obviously, you know, there's more out there.
I think that there's an extent to which we've been playing these games,
like, we'll play these Zelda games on DigiBros,
and he never wants to play an older one,
because he's like, it won't, you know,
I'm just going to get bored, I'm going to zone out and stuff,
and I'm like, well, okay, I don't think we should play any of them first on there.
I don't think your first experience with the game should ever be on Let's Play Show.
Yeah, I agree.
If he sat down and played Zelda 1, I think he'd like it,
and I think you have to be willing to try, you know?
That's true.
I mean, if you're going to consider yourself a huge Zelda fan, why would you not?
Why would you not go back and do Zelda 1, you know?
Do you want to, every time that you say you're a huge Zelda fan,
Victor, put that little asterisk there, like,
oh, but I haven't played any of them before, link to the fucking Ocarina Time, you know?
Yeah, me and Hayden were actually talking about how Zelda is like the biggest
Kred Fag series of all time.
That's true.
It's got such like fake, complex lore, you know what I mean?
Yeah, like the timeline.
There really is no lore, it's just stuff they made up in the game,
but it's like, yo man, the timeline, like, it blows my mind when I see people talking about it.
I don't know why, people's investment in the timeline baffles me,
because it doesn't matter at all.
It has no narrative importance.
I find it so crazy when new Zelda gets shown,
and people are trying to decipher where it takes place in the timeline.
It doesn't matter, it doesn't matter!
It makes literally zero narrative difference.
The people who make the games literally gave you a timeline,
because you wanted a timeline, not because there was a timeline,
they made one up, because...
I'm sure they only came up with that as of Skyward Sword.
Right, but that's the thing, like, bringing it back to what we first said,
like, playing a series in release order,
like, where you're talking about how he doesn't want to go back and play the original Zelda's,
because they're not as epic as the new ones.
That's the problem, that's why I don't want people to go and play the more recent games,
because then it makes the original games,
which had the original ideas, which came up with these mechanics,
which started this all, which eventually led up to this game you love,
you know, like, that now looks like a piece of shit,
because now it's been topped by its sequels.
But I guess if you play it in release order,
you're going to be like, that was awesome, then play the next one, that was awesome!
Right, and that's such another great advantage to playing things in release order,
as you can see the progression of things,
and even if they're negative, ultimately,
like, to go, I think a lot of people who just blindly transitioned from pixels to 3D,
you know, there was obviously some sloppy shit going on there for a while.
It's interesting to see that.
I love it, because especially in games,
like, I feel like more than any other medium,
it's like you play a game on one console,
and then like years later, you jump to the next game,
and it's like the world looks different, you know, the characters look different.
You're experiencing this upgrade, because it's like,
it's like you're now seeing the vision of the creators
for a new lens of what they can now do, what they wanted it to originally look like.
That's what's so exciting about Yakuza 6,
that's what's so exciting about it.
And don't go thinking people that that means like,
oh, that means actually just play the lace one,
because it's the closest to their artistic vision.
No, that's not how it works.
You know, I want to speak directly to CredFags,
because I have two pieces of advice.
My first piece, because you all know who you are,
if you've been listening to this, you figure it out.
Two pieces of advice.
One, try them all even if you don't necessarily beat them.
Like you don't have to, like if you go back to Elder Scrolls,
like each one is unique and has its own pieces of intrigue.
If you start up Daggerfall and you immediately want to vomit, as I do,
because the way that the perspective is and the way,
not just that the graphics aren't good,
but that the way they're presented is like nauseating,
in a way that only a 90s first-person PC game could be.
Fine, at least give it a shot.
I mean, some of you might play it and realize,
hey, these graphics don't nauseate me at all.
Here's what you'll get out of it.
Daggerfall has the biggest map in any video game ever.
People talk about Skyrim has a huge map, right?
Skyrim has a six...
It's the size of Great Britain in Daggerfall, isn't it?
Yes, Daggerfall is actually larger than Great Britain.
To put that into perspective, Skyrim is about 16 square miles in size,
and Daggerfall is like 20,000 square miles or something like that.
Oh my God.
Well, games have just gotten better and better, guys.
Only today have they finally achieved that.
Well, look at these technological wonders we've got now
that can make such huge maps.
Fuck yourself, people.
I believe it's procedurally generated, I think.
But I think it might be in the same way as...
What's it called?
Oblivion, where oblivion was a procedurally generated map
that was then solidified and they put it in the game.
But oblivion was like 10 square miles or something like that.
Daggerfall is fucking massive.
So if that sounds interesting to you,
then if you play the game and then you find that out,
then there might be someone who starts off thinking,
well, this isn't going to be as good as Skyrim,
but then you find out that there's something so unique about it
that it ends up actually being your favorite one.
It's like such a fallacy that the newer stuff is better,
because it's like, oh man, when assets were more simple
and they didn't take as long to make and it wasn't as expensive,
we could make more game.
And now we can't.
You see so many sequels that are like,
we removed this feature and this feature and this feature,
because they didn't have time to do it.
And the real issue with this whole thing is that
it's a vicious cycle of, you know,
there is consumer, quote unquote, demand
for like higher resolution stuff as in the meme is
that it has to be, you know, like Square Enix's thing,
it has to be picture perfect,
like the best possible have to spend all the resources
making Lightning's tits move in a slightly more realistic way
than anything else.
And then the resources get diverted there
because there's this perceived demand for that
as opposed to artistic...
Well, part of the problem is fucking...
I think part of the problem is review scores.
Well, Lightning's tits, I mean, okay, we all want that.
Aside from that...
There's a lot of Japanese developers
who seem to perfectly understand this.
And when a new game comes out from like Nipponichi
or Falcom or like most of the things that are published by Atlas,
like those games tend to look old,
but they also tend to have way more content
than any newer games.
And you end up with a situation where like...
You can play Disgaea for literally forever,
as I recall.
Right, and they keep making new Disgaea
and they all look like Disgaea 1.
The textures are in HD now,
but they're still fucking the same pixel art drawings, right?
I think...
Oh, sorry, go on.
I think like, you know, those games are still as big as ever.
You can still play a new Disgaea for 80 to 300 hours, you know?
And I think that when these games get...
When you open up a game in former magazine,
the game they're going to give a 10 out of 10
is going to be the one, the BioShock Infinite,
the one that like looks beautiful
and looks like it's, you know, modern and cutting edge
and it seems to be saying something with its story, so...
10 out of 10, you know?
Like God of War 4, looking for that 10 out of 10.
So I think...
You've got Trails of...
Sorry, you've got like Trails of Cold Steel coming out
or something like that, which I haven't played this myself,
but like I've heard from our friend Mother's Basement,
like it's like one of his favorite games of all time.
And that game is like pixel art,
but it's like a huge, unbelievably massive world,
you know, with all these different moving parts.
Every NPC has a story and stuff
and there's side quests everywhere and like,
if that game, even if that game was perfect at what it wanted to do,
if you open up a Game Informer, that score will never be above an 8.5.
It will not happen because it doesn't look like a 10
and they won't give it a 10, you know?
And it's just all about the different standards
that they're using to judge versus guys like us?
Right.
They're only going to give the 10 to the big modern game.
I once went to like the library in my university
and they had like a bunch of old gaming magazines.
They had like reviews from like the 90s.
Ah, cool.
And they had like a big compilation of like loads of scores
they gave to games in like the end of the 90s.
And you won't believe it.
It's like, they like review like these polygon, like horrible messes.
Like, oh yes, Siphon, you know, I haven't played Siphon yet.
Maybe it's really good.
But it's like, oh, it's like this polygonal, like,
like terrible draw distance game, like 9 out of 10.
And then it's like, well, simply of the night,
it doesn't seem to really be pushing any boundaries here.
It just seems like a Super Nintendo game.
Nothing to see here.
Six out of 10.
And then it's like...
There's no X.
Yeah.
I do think the reviews have gotten slightly better,
because it used to be you'd read a review and it'd be like,
there'd be sections and it'd be like graphics,
five out of 10 gameplay.
And it's like, if the graphics weren't out of 10,
then it wouldn't be a 10.
It's like, at least now people are moving away a bit from scores
and that kind of rhetoric.
The thing is like, I've never read reviews.
I've never given a shit.
If there was ever a review, all I'd do is look at the pictures
and then be like...
Well, I grew up on reviews.
Like, how I got into doing this kind of writing
is that I would read like, Nintendo Power Magazine
and as a teenager, I read a lot of GameStop reviews
and I was always fascinated with the scores.
Because to me, growing up, it always seemed like
knowing what is the highest scored game
tells me what are the classics.
If I know that GameStop gave their highest score ever
to Metroid Prime for the longest time,
then I now need to go play Metroid Prime.
And when you find a reviewer who you really trust their scores,
then that can be really helpful.
Because I used to really trust...
Have I been saying stop? I meant spot. GameSpot.
I used to really trust the game in Britain, then he went to shit.
Well, you surely trust GameSpot because of the fact
that they were super strict with their scores.
They only gave the high scores to very rarely.
And so I always thought, cool, those must be the true classic games.
But then, over time, I realized that they fall into the same trap
everyone else does of if it's not new and modern
and a big fucking graphical powerhouse,
it's not going to get that 10.
Even if you make the best JRPG of all time,
it will not get a 10 because it's a JRPG.
The YouTube evolution of reviews is a really great thing,
and it's got positive and negatives,
but it's so great to really be able to get deep into like...
You don't have like one page to fill with text,
and that's all you get.
You can have a guy like, you know, a bunny hop
going into like the history and make a half an hour fucking video
about every little detail you could ever want to know
and why this game is an artistic masterpiece
for collecting all these various aspects
from all the different games in the series
and presenting them in this way
that will perfectly capture everything
that longtime fans of that series has wanted.
That's what's really valuable.
That's the kind of review that has real merit in the world.
Well, I think these journalists are like,
what the fuck?
I got to keep my finger on the pulse of the gaming landscape.
What am I doing wasting my time with this game
that looks like a fucking PS2 game or whatever, you know?
So they're like, fuck, just get it over with.
Yeah, whatever, 7.2.
They come in, I think it's like people who,
they jump in and then like, they just have to go,
because news happens fast, right?
I know a lot of anime fans who get into anime
because they saw one or two older shows
and then they start watching current stuff.
And if you're trying to keep up with current stuff consistently,
it can take up all your free time
because there's 45 fucking shows that come out each season.
And so I know a lot of people
who pretty much never watch older anime, you know?
I think Jeff somewhat falls into this trap
where like, I only ever hear Jeff talk about watching current shit, you know?
Kind of.
And like, to me, that stuff is,
like, because current anime lets you be a part of the conversation for now,
but what it doesn't do is give you perspective on what's been great, you know?
Like, if this current season that has just started,
there's not a single show on right now
that I like immediately think this is going to be talked about in five years,
you know, like, nothing gives me that impression,
whereas you can go watch a show that has been talked about for five years,
and now you're going to get like a new perspective on the history of the medium
and what, like, what highs it can reach and like, you know,
and that will enrich you for the future
when you actually want to talk about like, deeper shit.
You know, if you want to talk about a new game and be like,
this is how it reflects the state of gaming,
you need to know the state of gaming, you know?
Dude, that's really cool because in terms of games,
if you think back to like, from like just five years ago,
what are the games that have stood a test of time and are imitating now?
You think of stuff like Dark Souls,
which was like a low-budget JRPG made in like a million bucks
that like wasn't cutting edge, no one really knew about it,
had a small, had a slow sort of like, ascent into popularity,
and now that's the game everyone wants to be
and all the mechanics, loads of RPGs copy,
and that's why, and that's exactly why,
like just because the game is the prettiest and the most hype
doesn't mean it's going to be the most relevant.
That's a good point, man.
No one's going to fucking, no one's going to care about,
like, because that year, I think Dark Souls came out in 2011,
and so this would be before Bioshock Infinite and stuff,
but like, what would you say are some games from 2011
that were like big then, you know,
like Skyrim, Skyward Sword, Uncharted 3,
Deus Exe Revolution, Batman Arkham City,
does anyone still boot up Batman Arkham City, you know?
Right, baby.
Like, I think a game, I think a series like the Souls games,
like each one has been such a big deal that yeah,
it'll be talked about forever, it'll influence a million games,
there's been countless articles written on it,
it's studied in academia, you know.
You know what game came out in 2011?
Minecraft.
Oh, well that's, I mean, that is a big deal.
People are still talking about Dark Souls 1
more than they do fucking Dark Souls 2, Dark Souls 3,
or even Bloodborne.
I mean, I tried to, I was trying to like,
find something from 2011, but like,
even to use Bioshock Infinite from 2012 or 13,
it might have been 2012, now that I think about it.
I think it was 2012, I want to say.
That game was such a big deal when it came out,
and I don't think anyone cares anymore.
Like, no one goes back to play Bioshock Infinite again.
It's not going to be like...
Oh, thank God, yes, just waiting.
Like, you can buy that game for $5 at a bargain bin
at fucking GameStop, you know, but like,
that's a game that I don't think is going to have
nearly the cultural footprint that a Dark Souls has, you know.
It got exposed as the piece of shit it was right after it came out.
It got exposed quite a bit.
I think I saw someone link to an article the other day
where it was like, a reviewer for like,
Eurogame I think, taught like, he did an article on Bioshock
and I wasn't talking about how, man, I way overhyped this game.
I remember it today.
And now we're going to...
Every...
Does that mean...
Overhyped, yeah.
I think I get it.
I live in Britain, I don't get it.
You know, right now, we're going to get like,
No Man's Sky is like a new game.
Well, I don't know what it's even talking about it,
really, even though it's not.
People at my work are talking about it,
it's going to be the most epic game ever, dude.
Right, like, a game like that comes out,
and like, again, for a week,
it's going to be a big deal,
everyone's going to play that,
but imagine if all those...
Imagine, just for a second,
if everyone who played No Man's Sky
instead played like, Deus Ex.
Like, everyone just took a classic game
that everyone agrees is a classic,
and we all just decided to play that
instead of the one new game.
Because here's...
This was my other advice.
Back when I said I had two pieces of advice
to the people who are...
What's the word we're using?
CredFag.
The other piece of advice is,
like, and Charlie was kind of saying this before,
it's still the same amount of content
to play like an older one, right?
Like, people think of it as,
oh man, I have to play through
all these Yakuza games, right?
But like, you can probably beat a Yakuza game
in like two days,
and so playing through six Yakuza games
is going to take you like a week and a half.
How long did it take you to play through all of them
for your next favorite video?
It actually took me a while.
Over the course of like a year,
I recorded footage for that video.
Okay, but it's not like the games themselves are that long.
Hey man, Hayden gets distracted easily.
It's not like he was late playing shit back to back.
He also, he has a job and...
You know, point me.
Quick, backtrack!
Like, I mean, if it's all the Final Fantasy games,
that's going to take you a while.
But even then, like,
when I play through a game,
I usually play through it really fast.
I play through it in like one or two sittings.
I did all the Souls games in a week,
like at the start of this year.
I played through Bloodborne in three days,
then I did Dark Souls in two days,
Demon Souls in two days,
and Dark Souls three in two days.
Yeah, I did Bloodborne first.
I had played the other ones before.
I just never beat any of them.
Bloodborne is what made you want to play those other ones,
as I recall.
Well, it was that Bloodborne existed,
and Bloodborne is like perfectly my aesthetic,
and it was like a game that I felt I had to play.
So you were saying it was hyped up,
and you felt like you wanted to be part of the conversation?
Well, I didn't...
No, I played it a year after it came out,
so it was definitely not still hype.
I resisted hype forever,
because I actually wanted to play...
Like I said, I'd gotten halfway through Dark Souls 1,
and I'd played a bunch of Demon Souls.
I knew about the series since it came out,
and then everyone was hype about Bloodborne,
and I refused to play it because of the load times.
I was like, I will not touch this game until they fix the fucking load times.
I played that whole fucking game through with those load times,
and then after I beat it...
But the funny thing is, because I didn't...
I feel like, because I didn't ride the hype wave,
which would have done nothing for me to play it when it was hype,
it made no difference that I played it a year later.
I still loved the game,
and I feel like I got a better experience out of it for waiting,
and my brother Victor makes it out like I'm weird for that.
He was talking about Pokemon Go came out,
and I wouldn't play it because it was so fucking broken,
and Victor was like,
but it's what everyone's doing,
and I'm like, yeah, it sucks!
It's a shit game,
and then they finally made it playable,
and now I'm willing to play it.
And he was telling his girlfriend,
he even played Bloodborne just because of the load screens.
I'm like, that's what a sensible person does.
That's a pretty reasonable decision.
Victor clearly values the sense of community involved.
Because they said when they were going to patch it,
when the game came out, they were like,
yeah, we're going to have a patch at the end of the month,
and I was like, okay, I'll wait for the end of the month.
There you go, I can go do something else.
And that's what I mean when I'm saying that playing another game
takes just as long.
You're always thinking Deus Ex is this old game,
it's considered a classic, everyone loves it,
it's considered one of the best games of all time,
but I don't want to have to put the time into playing this old game.
It'll take you just as long as playing a new game,
which is a couple days.
Take out one of the new games you're going to play,
and go play Deus Ex.
Especially if you're just a regular person
who only plays games for entertainment.
I think this is something me and Hayden run into,
sometimes, where it's like,
we've got loads of video ideas we want to make,
and so whenever we're playing a game,
we're thinking in the back of our minds,
man, I could be playing a game
that I should be making a video on right now.
That's the trap I fall into.
The reason I haven't played the Witcher games
is that BunnyHup already did such a good job
of talking about them,
that I know I can't make a video about the Witcher games,
so it's harder to justify them.
That Hearthstone DLC looks tight as fuck.
I want to get into that shit.
How can I justify over 100 hours into a game
that doesn't impact my career at all?
It would just be leisure time.
Imagine that.
Just have an anime playing in, like, the background.
Adopt of course, so you can hear it.
Adopt of course.
You still play the game, obviously, you know.
Right.
If you watch the Tales of Zestiria anime,
you can review the game and the anime
at the same time.
Dude, I don't want to do that.
No one should do that.
So what you're telling me about Dark Souls is
you didn't play Kingsfield first.
Oh!
Let's leave over here.
It's funny you say that, though,
because I have always wanted to try to play
every From Software game.
That's how my mind works, is I play Dark Souls
and I'm like, I want to know everything
these guys have done.
Because surely they've done great shit.
Surely Kingsfield has awesome elements to it.
But it inspired Souls later.
I knew about Demon's Souls because
my friend was a huge Armored Core fan,
so now I want to play
all the Armored Core games as well.
I'm differentiating between two tiers of
Cred because when we're looking at
Cred as in,
there's a story and I want to
experience it, but then I want to jump around
and just get the important stuff and get the Cred.
And then there's this whole
in an analytical sense.
If you want to play the Dark Souls series
and play the Dark Souls series,
don't skip around, play the Dark Souls series.
And now if you want to have
an analytical idea of the
entire design of Dark Souls, then you should
play the Demon's Souls and all the other games.
I think we've stumbled upon a thing with Cred Fags.
There's actually two ends to
the spectrum of Cred Faggery.
And each end is actually
Cred Fags. Like going too far in the other direction
is also a bad thing.
If you're just playing anything just for the Cred,
you didn't play this,
you didn't play that.
I don't want to play them all
just so I can laugh at people, but
I do think some do.
Well, because once you start looking
into this stuff, and we've talked about it a lot
in this podcast, so now no one in our audience
can claim ignorance of this fact anymore.
That
the new ones aren't always the best, right?
And my friend who played
who was a huge Armored Core fan,
he always said that 4
toned it down a lot. It made it a lot more simple
and accessible because
they wanted the
Cred Fag audience. They want the people
who don't, because Armored Core
is never a super successful series, so
you obviously toned it down a little bit for new players.
And then Armored Core 5 came out
and my friend didn't even like it.
Huge fan of the franchise doesn't even like the newest one.
So really, you got to play 2 or 3.
Those are the most acclaimed ones.
And I can totally see people who
play Dark Souls going, I want to know
what From Software did before.
I'm going to play Armored Core 5.
That seems like, you can totally
see that you understand this happening,
but you should say
I want to know where Dark Souls came from.
I'm going to play Armored Core 1
on the PS1, or at least 2 or 3
because they're the ones that
at least look into it and find out which ones
people actually care about.
And that's the thing about us, because we're analytically
minded, bringing it way back
to what you were saying before. It's like we care about
the context of the series
as it moves forward.
We want to
criticize the story, its gameplay mechanics
and stuff like that. We want to see how it evolved
over the course.
It's like ignorant of a certain aspect of it.
What we're trying to say to people is that we're
smarter than you and you're all dummies.
And I don't care about your opinion.
That's the summary here.
Well, that's true.
I just think, I guess what we're really arguing for
is not so much to say that we're
necessarily better, but that we want
more people to feel the way we do
because it would make for
better conversations and
my brother being such a huge Zelda fan,
I would love to be able to talk to him
about Zelda 1.
He's never fucking played it.
I've begged him to for years now
and he won't play it.
I think we can have such a more interesting
conversation about Zelda.
We've got all these people like me
who played Zelda 1, who are so excited about
this new game.
Breath of the Wild, is that what it's called?
Because it goes back to that shit, man.
It's going to take it back.
It's using the Zelda 1 formula.
There's people like me
I know Matthew Matos has mentioned this
in his live stream
and someone else did.
Maybe it was one of you guys, but
we're all like, yeah, wow, this looks like
Zelda 1, that's really cool.
And people who, Jesus Christ.
Never played that.
I think a tree just got knocked down
right near my house.
Holy shit.
The cred facts are coming, man.
They're coming at you.
Somebody draw that.
Look out the window.
Okay, while you're doing that,
what I was going to say is
I really was...
It's not like I hate everyone who's a cred fact,
but it's their existence that encourages
things like
this trend of
casualization, that sort of thing
where people aren't really invested in
the things that made it great
so much as new stuff, new technology
and it really reminds me strongly
of a thing like the Final Fantasy 7
remake, which as a po...
We don't know yet, but the signs
are there that what they're going for
is this kind of, like you said,
homogenized experience of action,
RPG...
Final Fantasy XV style.
Almost a whole other can of worms, which is like...
Yeah.
It does encourage this, because every company...
The big problem is that all these companies
want to have the biggest game.
And we've talked about this before that,
again, with those Japanese developers
who are still sticking to their PS2
graphics and still making big, expansive
games with really unique systems.
Those people are making those games
because they know that there's an audience
who wants those systems.
Whereas Final Fantasy VII
was a great game,
and it had its own style,
and the problem is not that Square Enix...
The problem is they want a bigger audience.
They want Final Fantasy VII to be played
by everybody.
They have to sell 10 million units
because they're fucking in the red.
They're going to make it the most broadly appealing
game possible, which loses out on hitting
anyone deeply, because something that's
niche will...
The people who are into something niche
appreciate it way more than
the people who are into something strong.
Some of the decisions, though, on a logical level
just blow my mind.
When I played the Ratchet remake,
and I'm getting all these
tutorial messages on where to go,
like, you run out ammo, change weapons,
everyone's talking to you, and I'm like,
okay, this game is for kids, but I was a kid
when I played the original game.
I didn't get any of this,
and I beat the game, and it wasn't like...
I'm thinking, like,
what has changed?
Like, are kids dominoes?
Is that what they're trying to say?
Can kids not handle a more sarcastic narrative
with under-characters?
Can kids not handle good writing anymore?
What it really shows is that the adults
think that the kids can't handle it.
That's what it's really telling you.
No, because they probably did some, like, stupid,
like, study where they got a few kids in a room
to play the game, and then they were like,
I don't know where to go for, like, two minutes.
Which is, like, too much. You gotta know
what to do at all times. It's a larger issue, man.
It extends to a lot of the things in our culture
and the way society's changed.
But let me ask you a question, though, about this.
Is it even possible,
since we're talking about this, is it even possible
to avoid this kind of cycle of
small developer makes great game,
it does really well,
they grow in size, they
get more responsibility, forcing them
to achieve larger, more
mainstream success, and they will just begin
to pander, you know,
and lose their creative spark that drive them
in the first place. Is that an inevitable thing?
Can it be fought?
I don't know. I think, here's what I think
is gonna happen. I think Square Enix
is gonna burn themselves out.
Like, literally, they're gonna run out of money.
I agree. They've been losing money
on all these fucking games.
Every single day, a new promotional
Final Fantasy XV thing comes out
and I send it to Nate.
It's happening every day.
Guys, let me just set the stage.
Little while ago, there was this thing called
Uncovered Final Fantasy XV,
which was a big event for Final Fantasy XV,
which is coming out, it was revealed
when the release date was. At that event,
they revealed that not only
have they spent the money to make
this game over the course of ten years,
but they also
made an anime.
They paid for an anime. They made
a movie. They made a fucking car.
They've made
so much extra shit. Two fun games.
They didn't have to spend money on.
They chose to, and they have to make
that kind of money back.
And here's the question. Here's the question.
If Final Fantasy XV had come out five years ago
with PS2 graphics,
would it be a lesser experience?
No, it would have had gameplay.
It could have been a story or whatever.
It could have been just as
hard-hitting and just as good.
What I think is going to happen,
I think we're going to see,
I think Final Fantasy XV,
which it could sell five million copies
and still tank in terms of
what they needed to make, because the
fucking budget is crazy on this thing.
Because that's what happened with
Tomb Raider and Hitman
and whatever the other one was
that they had published that year, where they reported losses
of games that sold unbelievably well.
Tomb Raider sold
six million, not enough.
By the way, guys, the Final Fantasy XIII
trilogy as a whole has sold
only over 11 million copies.
And that's three games.
It's three games together.
15's not going to work.
I think once Square Enix
tanks and once we start
losing, because I feel like
all those big developers are
in trouble and it's only getting worse.
With this new generation
of games where no one can even
make fucking games for these consoles,
because it's too much
to try to make these games.
I think that eventually
Steam
is going to kill it all
because everyone loves indie games now.
Indie games are no longer
a thing that only
weird niche PC players
who are not
a part of the crowd play.
A game like
Minecraft
or even just Braid or Meat Boy.
These games are such huge successes
and there's more and more.
Every year there's more indie games
that everyone's talking about.
With YouTube reviewers
pumping out reviews of these games
where, again, if you follow someone
like Bunny Hop, an indie game
is being presented with the same amount
of care and seriousness
as a mainstream title.
As indie games become more mainstream,
more and more people are going to go,
why the fuck would we spend all that money
on a big game that's probably going to fail?
The change has started, the shift has begun.
You have to get all those people
and as soon as you have
like, if you need
7 million people to play your game
and your game comes out in the same
week as an indie game
that gets 3.5 million
players because it just sparks wildfire
and everyone plays it, your game's fucked.
I think that's what's going to happen.
YouTube has finally
it hasn't totally set us free
but it has created an environment
where you can get reviews of things
with the least possible amount
of corporate influence
of these people
are just doing it out of passion
and they turn it into a career
and there's going to be little things that creep in
but in the specific cases
Square Enix and more specifically
Final Fantasy XV has become
a forced meme at this point
it is an extremely forced meme
and every forced meme is doomed to die
a horrible death and like I've said before
like I said in my Final Fantasy VII remake video
I would really like
Square Enix to just die
in order for them to stop
raping their legacy just let it go
just break into small groups and make little games
you make Bravely Default
you can make games like that, make little baby Final Fantasy's
just do those
and we'll all be better off
what if the game is good
what if the game is good though
what if the best game will matter
mate, you haven't done your research right
Tabata is catering to the fans
I don't know what you're talking about
how could you say this
how could a fantasy Final Fantasy XV
could be the greatest game ever
and it still won't sell enough
to make back its money
it'll still kill Square Enix
isn't that funny though with Final Fantasy
the way the Final Fantasy franchise started
like they were dying
they created this one last game and it saved them
Final Fantasy XV is finally
full circle
it kills itself
I don't think it's going to die right after 15
because they've got their other
branches that sustain
they've got KH3 which will sell
KH3 will do fine
but will it make back its budget
the game's been in development for quite a while
it's going to be a long, every jug or not
when it begins to go away
it will kick and scream
it cannot do anything but resist
its inevitable death and decline
so there will be a long
if it does in fact die
which I mean everything dies eventually
it will be a very long drawn out painful process
for every party involved
and no one's going to come out good at the end of that
especially not my beloved Final Fantasy
I mean somehow Konami is still
kicking
for how much longer man who knows
they're Pachinko
they're a gambling company
that's the sad thing though
when these IPs die
they don't just die
they become chained
turn into a fucking Pachinko machine
it's like watching her
she was so much more
it's hard to even say it but
she was treated with more respect
by being a character in Metal Gear Solid 3
and now they're fucking slapping her
it's so disrespectful
it's like these franchises
they can't get off the ship
they got to go down with the ship
and drown in the water because
the companies aren't going to sell these giant IPs
it's all they got left
but what they are now is the ship has gone down
and the company is rapidly wrapping duct tape
where the water is coming in through the sides
and they're like oh god we got to hold it
we got to survive as long as possible
I think what all these companies are missing
like the forest
that they're missing for the trees
the trees being their big budget games
back in the 90's
a new great game came out
all the time
we keep saying our Final Fantasy
had a game every fucking year
in the 90's
when I looked at that Wikipedia page
sorry I muted my mind
who's got a dick in his mouth right now
I muted my mind to have a biscuit
but I had to jump in
so I unmuted it halfway through
it blew my mind when I looked at that
Wikipedia page of the Final Fantasy timeline
release dates
and it's like seven, eight, nine, ten
four games in like four or five years
one who's linked to that bitch
and tactics too
don't forget tactics
what is the benefit of waiting
five years for one first game
these people have not decided this model
it has been basically forced upon them
by perceived
demands
the thing is that the reason that
they're not getting that
why that's such a big problem
is that you look at your PS2 library
there's a million thousand fucking games
you look at your PS3 and even that
eventually it had a decent catalog
you look at your PS4, it's been out for years
there's nothing on it
the Wii U has been out for years
it has like ten great games
and they're all great but that's all there is
literally zero
I go to a shop
and look at the PS4 section
I don't see like
I don't see like this is like the game
of the generations
I guess Bloodborne
if you go to GameStop
they still have an Xbox 360
section that covers three fucking
walls because so many games came out
for that console
the PS4 section is so weird because it's like
like PS3 ports
a few new games and then loads of PC
indie games that have been ported over into boxes
it's the weirdest thing
it's so
like it's like maybe there'll be like ten
original PS4 owner of games
and the rest is like ports and
the fucking Wii U shelf is depressing
because I was there
I was there the other time, I was at GameStop just like yesterday
and it's just this one
little rat and I'm like that's it
you know that's the whole Wii U
and it's going out
the Vita section?
some stores don't have a Vita section anymore
it's like
I'm not surprised
why this is such a problem is that
people need
like people there is a huge demand
for there to always be a game to play
because people aren't going to wait around
and you know and this is why a game like
Overwatch is such a huge deal
because Overwatch is a game that will keep you busy
for indefinitely
you know like it's a game that because
people don't want
people want you know those big games
but they want them every weekend
because the way people play games is they go out
and they buy one and they play through it
and then they need something else
and that is why credit facts go back and play
the old games
there is one game that keeps me
plenty busy on my PS4 and that game is
Dead or Alive Extreme 3 Fortune
oh the only problem is it got
fucking banned in America so you had to
import it so it's not going to see that
on GameStop shelves
point being I think what will kill the big
industry is just the fact that people need
there to be people need another game
people are going to finish a game and they crave
another game and no games are coming out
from these big publishers and
you know when you have
a game like Overwatch come out and everyone can
play it then like they're not going
to bother with anything else they're just
going to all play Overwatch
they won't but what they really should do
is they should completely revamp their development
cycle have the hardware people work
with the software guys I don't know
it's obviously too complex to do easily
but reinvent the
idea of like a great game coming out from
your studio every year whatever
sacrifices you need to make do that
because that will make people buy your
consoles that will drive up
PS4 is like winning
I heard is like doing by far the best
somehow I don't know how but it
is it was all about
winning people got so fucking hyped
for being the console
to play that makes you sell
marketing did it I think
we ran into like a I think
the saddest thing about all this is
the loss of the middle ground
where we every every game is all or nothing
it's all either like a huge fucking
kind of like the loss of the middle
class know what I'm saying like a tiny
indie game and it's like what happened to a time
where we could have like a hundred
like what happened when there was a hundred
games that could come out they were all just the coolest
you know dude like it for the last
two generations everyone like
has been like yo Nintendo where the
franchises where the franchise is going
it's like you remember the GameCube it was like
and within three years it was like boom Mario
boom Zelda boom stuff
boom F zero boom like you know it was like
nothing is a better example of this
than what Matthew Matosis pointed out
in his Metal Gear Solid 4 video
when Otacon does his speech about
like snake you need to change the disc
and he's like Otacon what are you talking
about oh that's right we're on the
Blu-ray double technology
is so fucking amazing you don't
even need to change the disc cue the five
hour loading period
between when you feed fucking need to load
the next section of the game as opposed
to just swapping
yeah great it only takes ten hours to install
the whole thing fantastic just what I want
thirty minutes dude yeah right I'd rather
just buy a game with three discs
and swap them out in ten seconds each
I'm just saying to your next game you fucking
you know this
yeah
yeah yeah you should have to take longer
to play games like we did back in the day
no the point
is technology is
not doing it's not
helping uh
games achieve a better
I don't know it's not it's it's it's working counter
to the goals that I think we can all agree on
you know in a lot of ways
games wise is such a big problem to have to
install MGS4
because I'm a Nintendo
who can't construct his own computer
so you know I think
I think the Metal Gear Solid franchise
right there this like all I have to do
is say a few dates and we can put
everything we've just said into perspective
yeah the first three Metal Gear Solid games
are pretty much considered the best right
the fan favorites four is considered
kind of a let down by a lot of people five
is considered a huge let down by a lot of people
not saying this is true of everyone
because I'm the credit say that it's the
greatest game that's ever been made but like
fucking played that's right but I
think that I've never played
I think
I think if you really want perspective on
whether or not you like Metal Gear Solid 5
we can all agree that they're that
like Metal Gear Solid 1, 2, and 3
are not that contested
the way that 5 is
Metal Gear Solid 1 came out in 98
three years later we got Metal Gear Solid 2
well to be fair Metal Gear Solid 2
is a little too smart for a lot of people to get
initially
let me finish the states 1998
three years later we got Metal Gear Solid 2
three years after that
we got
three years after that we got Metal Gear Solid 3
then somehow it took another four years
before we got the next game
and it's somehow worse than the first three
and then it takes another
seven years
before we get the next game and it's somehow
worse than all of them
this is the trajectory we're on
it takes longer to make a game
and yet it somehow is worse
I'm just gonna put the rule out there the shorter
your development lifetime the better the game
will be I'm just throwing that out that's a rule
a week might be a bit
no that's it I've made great games
at Game Jams dude we have made great games
at Indie Game Jams over a 24 hour period
I'm just saying
in terms of Metal Gear I am
as if they come up behind you and say surprise
motherfucker and you go holy shit you know
you can't know the games come out
I do like that that's like you know like
hype is bad you know hype is real bad for these
sorts of things from this day forward I'm deciding
there are four Metal Gear Solid games
is V it's just V
it's just a spin-off called V
about a guy called V
and there's four Metal Gear Solid games
and it ended at Metal Gear Solid 4
Metal Gear Solid 5 starring
Big Meme
imagine though okay like Metal Gear Solid 4 gets a lot of
shit deservedly for a lot of things
but imagine if that ending of Metal Gear Solid 4
had come now
with Konami's death how legendary
that game would have been
it would have been the more
like it is it's already probably one of
the most legendary games ever but it would have been
like you know
it would have elevated it more than
this like going out on a wet
fart and like yeah
you know oh well hey you're forgetting
about Peace Walker dude
I like Peace Walker a lot
actually it
I'm a crit fag I didn't finish Peace Walk
Peace Walk is a piece of shit
the final boss the final boss against
pass with the J Rock
fucking 10 out of 10
don't listen to Matthew Matosis it's the
best final boss of all time
no Peace Walker is
inoffensive but it's only
offensive when it's combined with Metal Gear Solid 5
that's for sure
they become a duo
of destruction
towards the entire franchise
so we've kind of explored this
topic thoroughly I mean we had our second
topic I don't know
I don't think we need it
definitely I think this is a pretty good
place to wrap it up so anybody have
any final thoughts oh I've got okay
I've got some final okay final cred
thoughts sure
so I think
whenever I play a game and when I've
played series I really in my mind I really want
to recreate what like if I've missed a series
I want to recreate what it would have been
like if I'd played them in order and if I had
experienced them as totally as they came out
and I think in that sense
like because you can't really
match that kind of experience you can never
approximate what it would be I mean me and Nate
have talked about this multiple times
yep you know like when we played a series
like Kingdom Hearts growing up
and like you
you play that first game and then you
wait years and you play that second game
and it's like it's like meeting all the characters
again and like experiencing that full story
and then having payoffs that
you know were hinted at in the first game
and then years later like two is probably
is like a better game I guess
than one and you could tell someone to go play
two first it's contested
but I do think that like
you you will not
experience it you will have a much better
experience and at the end of the day that's what
that's what media is about it's not about
being on Twitter and knowing what happened
and being able to be in the conversation
it's about having a great experience and if you want
the best experience go to the
start start it from the beginning and
just incident and and immerse
yourself in that journey that's that's what I
say Kingdom Hearts 2 release 2002
Kingdom Hearts 1 2002
Kingdom Hearts 2 wait
Kingdom Hearts 2
2006 so even that four years
at the time felt like forever
I know right and now we're like used to
like okay new Kingdom Hearts 10 years
alright let's strap in
that's normal that's
and by the way chain of memories came out
in the middle of that so there was a real
Kingdom Hearts game to say you're you know
hungry in the middle of that so man there's
been like 20 fucking Kingdom Hearts games
on DS in that time
and I've played literally all of them
and I'm still pissed that Kingdom Hearts 3
is taking this one
literally all of them people
I guess if I have parting thoughts two
credit fags which is probably going to be
most people listening to this because I think most
of us have credit fag tendencies
we've all credit fagged at least once
in our lives
and we probably will continue to do
so regardless of
knowing better but like
you know I don't I don't think it's
necessarily I mean you
you play games you watch shows or whatever
you do it because you just
want to in the moment right and for a lot of people
it's just I got home from work I want to
get excited about something that's not work
and I understand how hype can be
fun when you've got all your friends are doing it
you know but
if you're if you
have any interest in being a reviewer
or speaking about the medium at all
or if you're a fan who wants
to appreciate the medium at any depth
go back and play the old shit
because it will deepen your understanding
of the new shit to degrees
that you did not realize were
possible
and that goes for every medium
go back and look at the old shit even if you
don't like it it'll still in it it'll
make you like the new stuff more just
knowing how far things have come
you know yeah yeah in a big
way and being able to see things like
like like again to use
Zelda like just to be able to see how
the controls of
like the newer games evolve from the old ones
and like
I don't know there's a lot that fascinates me about like
playing Zelda one and then playing a newer one
and being like wow these
everything that's in this one is also
in this one but it's different
it's great go do it play
and you know
going to go I was just going to say you're never going to enjoy it
as much as those people who you want
to be part of the conversation with
if you're not watching the whole thing
yeah especially if it's a bunch of
if a bunch of Metal Gear fans are mad
about five you're not going to be as mad
about five by just playing five
it's not going to happen and you might start it
and go I don't get it
I don't like this like if you started with
Yakuza 3 just say
and I guess my only
thoughts
you know I was just going to say you might miss out
on like
your favorite game of all time
you might miss out on it
if you start skipping
that's true
don't let like the reviewers
and oh it's new so it must be good
determine whether you play
new games or old games because like what's to say
you won't enjoy those old games more
like you don't know you didn't play them
that's true man
and I guess
I just want to say that I
I think we're all cred fags at various
points in our lives like everybody said
and like did you said I think a lot of it
is just an issue of people
have different life experiences they go to work
they come home they've had a hard day
you know doing whatever that has nothing to do
with you know criticizing media in any
capacity they turn on the big bang
theory they turn on Metal Gear Solid
5 and they go to town and to those
people I empathize with you but I'd also like
to say fuck you
you gotta start
big bang theory from the beginning
and I gotta ask
what's the origin of
Bazinga I don't know I need to know
maybe you'll like the joke if you
see the origin
what if it's been this
watch as Bazinga has been like a brilliant social
commentary joke
like every time Sheldon experiences existential
pain when he remembers the death of his father
as a child he says Bazinga
reflexively oh my god
I'm a cred fag I didn't even know
didn't even know
did you be saying something
yeah just if you if you're
if you are a cred fag I have to ask
do you want to be this way forever
cause like that's whenever
there's someone who like keeps playing the new games
and you're like but what about the classics and they're like
oh I'll get to it someday it's like
you're never gonna you're never gonna get
to them if you keep following
the hype cycle and only playing the hype games
you're never gonna end up
like like Charlie said you're gonna end up missing out on
probably some of your favorite games
cause a vast majority
of the best games in existence
are old
and you know people if that seems overwhelming to you
like oh there's so many old games
they'll never be able to play them all
pick a series that you're most interested in
start with those and your life will immediately be more
even if it seems like it's on the
it's on the clunkiest oldest system
of all time just give it a go
just start it
to your friends oh no I'm encouraging people to
play obscure things just to brag about it
I take it back be a cred fag forever
another piece of advice
emu paradise
yes oh man
makes your life a lot easier
we are not sponsored by that
there is technology these days to just play
I don't think anyone's
gonna be sponsored by a fucking illegal
you don't know
I'm just saying don't be afraid of the law
emu paradise I will accept your
it's a lot of old games you can't find
but you need to play all those
super Nintendo games it doesn't matter
wink people
we're not being like this to be assholes
we want you to experience
and have the best experience
I want everyone to be informed
and smart and critical
and playing the best things out there
based on their own judgment
you know
and that's it
thanks for listening everybody thanks for joining us
Chuck Hayden
it's been great having you on thanks for coming
let's do it again sometime soon
had a great time
glad to hear digi uh fuck you
thanks for listening everybody we'll see you next time
goodbye
bye
yeah
I'm supposed to
be working
right now
I'm supposed to
be working right now
but I'm not working
I'm doing nothing
my dick
I'm jerking
myself
I'm sucking
I am an asshole
I am a stupid
I've got a deadline
don't want to do it
what the hell
is wrong with me
I'm supposed to
be making
money
I'm supposed to be
creating funny
things that the people
gladly
will pay for
artistic genius
that's what they came for
instead
I'm tweeting
hashtag repeating
that's why
there's no heat
and holes in the ceiling
yeah
it's quite the
burden
it's a hard knock life
being a genius