Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm the best
guy ever. Check the encyclopedia for best. That's me. We've also got Hippocrit is here.
I want Wuya to be my parent.
Mumkey Jones is here.
Hey everybody I'm Mumkey Jones. You look up Mumkey in the dictionary. That's a picture
of me.
Tom Oliver is here.
Yeah. I have nothing witty to say.
And our last guy is Mumkey Jones is here.
Hey guys it's me, Munchy.
And to exercise my independence from my parents I'm about to order a pizza and I'm going to
have to get it on air like 30 minutes from now.
That's fascinating.
When you said you want Wuya to be your mom, do you mean like Wuya from Shallown Showdown?
Or the game console, the Wuya.
Well either.
Now what's your favorite Shen Gong Wu from Shallown Showdown?
It's been a long time.
Just say the Mikey stuff.
Mummy! My pizza! Can you get it for me, Mummy?
She's such a good woman.
I know. I have seen her vagina and it has served me well.
Okay moving on.
Speaking of having sex with people we're talking about Munchy's parents today.
Munchy, is your mom actually hot?
Nah.
I've kind of got a thing for Mexican chicks.
No, she's not the Mexican one.
What the fuck?
You're another one of those mixed breed fucking dogs?
Cuckolds.
Did your dad get thrown over the wall?
Is that what happened?
Dad!
My Mexican pizza dad!
Munchy, I thought it was revealed that I'm your father and I'm also the Zodiac killer.
Well yeah, that's why you're over the wall, bro.
You're going to get deported.
And I voted for Trump. It was the ultimate betrayal.
Okay, so Trump is my real dad.
We're talking about parents. That's what's going on.
So where do we fucking take a discussion about parents?
I guess we can start with the tales of our own and the various rapes they've committed.
Are we going to discuss childhood and parents or just the parents or just the wife fucking?
It's all connected, man.
Whatever tickles your face.
Everything that goes with parenting and parents and stuff.
I guess I'll begin.
I like my dad. He's cool. He's a cool guy.
He's confident and he's reserved, but he knows how to do things.
He's a business man. He's a smart man.
He's always been on the right side of debates.
Always? Always?
When it comes to like stuff on the news.
What did your dad vote for in Brexit?
He's the sort of person who would like,
you know what, I'll give Trump a chance, but I don't like, I mean, you know.
Sounds like a misogynist.
So he voted to leave the European Union.
No, I don't know what he voted.
A real hero.
But like he's got that nuance.
He's got that understanding of like nuance that I like in people that it doesn't exist in anyone except my dad.
And he's like actually cool.
You know, I was going to say, you know, we all have a strong bias in that we all know our parents,
like especially our parents, we know better than anyone else in our lives for the most part,
except maybe our siblings.
But in any case, it's a lot easier to look at them and see the complexities going behind them
as opposed to like some guy who voted for Trump.
Like who knows what his complicated reasonings are other than, you know, hating immigrants, you know, being racist.
Because he thought it would be funny. I'm right here, Nate.
But in any case.
It's like, it's just sort of, you know, he introduced me.
Like he is always like the sort of sensible one when it comes to like things that happen on the news.
He's like, well, you know, this isn't that.
And I'm like, yeah, yeah.
And it's not just that I grew up with him.
It's that stuff on the internet that has influenced me is sort of like the smart people on the internet also are doing what dad's saying.
And he goes on Facebook and that's like, whoa, how could you be like smart and a Facebook user?
I thought they didn't allow dads on Facebook.
I thought that was an infamnia, as the Italians say.
Also, he's really funny and that's why I'm funny.
Now, Hippo, I got a question for you about your parents.
How much do they know about your internet presence and do they support your YouTube dreams?
I think we should all go to that at some point.
My parents know basically that I do YouTube stuff and make money from it.
It was a bit awkward the first time I tried to explain it because they had no idea that that was, you know, internet.
Like because like they're wary of scams.
Like there was one time where I was like looking up how to be a ninja and it was like a course that you had to pay for.
And I was like, no, it's real.
Like they show you like how to do it.
Now, was this when you were six or was this like six days ago?
It's like 16.
Like it's like, you know, it's embarrassing, but it's funny.
So it's funny.
It's fine.
But like, you know, they think, yeah, it's basically just a bunch of crap like dude's press ups and whatever.
But anyway, they're wary of like things scamming me as a kid.
So if I, you know, I wasn't sure whether to tell them I do internet jobs, money, YouTube adsense and they wouldn't understand it.
But they, they surprisingly, you know, just understood it as like, oh yeah, it's just like a thing.
You know, it's like new.
It's like the new wave.
We don't understand it, but it's new and that's cool and go on and do it.
I don't know.
I think my mom watches most of my videos and it's kind of embarrassing sometimes because that means she knows that I swear and I don't know how to feel about that.
But she's, yeah.
Your mom watches your videos about video games, but she doesn't play video games herself.
Are you saying your mom's a fucking fake gamer?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
It's okay because she plays Bejeweled and like cow clickers on her iPad.
She's a real gamer.
She played, you know, she's a Farmville mom.
She's one of those.
Now, can we all, can we all assume that your mom is not subscribed to Gibbon Take because I think you would have been like arrested at this point if she knew about it?
No, no, she subscribed to that.
She subscribed to Gibbon Take because it was my first one.
Oh my God.
Hypocrite.
She probably likes Gibbon Take more because it's more personal, you know?
She must think that her son is crazy.
No.
Well, I mean.
Now, now Gibbon, what is a shit post?
I don't understand.
I can't do a British accent.
I understand her mom voice.
Yeah.
It's a woman voice, first of all, because they're all shrill and retarded.
And also, I can't do a British accent.
It is me a foreigner.
I'm a foreigner in Turkey.
Hello, Gibbon.
This is me, your mom.
I want you to understand your videos.
Oh, that reminds me.
My dad's like a really good cook.
Like he cooks like all types of things like curries and Italian food.
Italian accent reminded you.
No, because he's really good at cooking Italian things and he knows a lot of things about Italians.
I am a quarter Italian, all right?
And how dare you say my people are good at cooking.
That's very offensive.
Italian's not a fucking race.
What are you talking about?
It's not a fucking race.
Get rid of Italians.
Number two, get rid of Russians.
Those are the worst people.
Italians and Russians.
Russian girls are hot.
Monkey.
You're about to order pizza, monkey.
Why are you saying this about Italians?
I don't know.
They're poison.
I think Russian girls have the objectively hottest accent.
I've done the studies and that's what the survey says.
They're talk like they got the dick already in their mouth.
You know.
Halfway there already.
Of course.
Women are objects.
Continue.
Hashtag women are objects.
You're talking about your dad and how he's going to cook it.
How your mom's an object?
Yeah.
Oh, no.
What should I talk about specifically?
Why don't you just tell us about growing up with your parents
and what use did they provide to you?
What objects and needs did they serve
that could have been better performed by a machine or something like that?
How late did you get from them?
Well, aside from the obvious food and water
and clothing and roof under my head.
You have to sleep on the roof.
They have been supportive of my creative endeavors in general.
They've never really forced me to say,
you've got to get a job or you're getting out of here.
I know they want me.
When I wasn't making any money or doing anything,
they wanted me to leave and I was like, yeah, I know.
But they didn't force me.
They're very supportive and they don't take bullshit from my teachers.
They were always on my side when it was like the teacher being a piece of shit.
So that was cool.
That's nice.
Like that time you got in trouble at school
for saying you were going to kill somebody or something?
Yeah.
That's a real story.
The time I got in trouble...
Wait, that same shit happened to me.
I thought you were making fun of me.
No, no.
It's real.
Oh, man.
Oh, gee.
He will kill you at school if he sees you, kids.
Watch out.
It wasn't exactly that.
I wrote in my art book.
Ah, fuck all this shit.
It was basically the fact that I was frustrated
and I was writing swears in my art book.
My teacher saw it and instead of talking to me,
she just reported my potential dangerous tendencies to the head teacher
so that I was suspended for a few weeks to calm down.
I'm sure that's like policy they have for reporting.
It's like that.
But what a fucking cowardly, backhanded way to deal with the situation like that.
When I came back, I really made an effort to be kind of a bitch to that teacher
because fuck her.
Good.
She does not deserve my respect after not even trying to approach me about it.
Yeah.
Anyway, yes.
Awful.
Put her in the fucking garbage.
My parents' school sucks too.
Yeah, this is kind of linked.
Yeah, I wanted to be on the school podcast to talk about that.
Fuck the PCP, hippo.
We'll do a school sucks later.
Yeah.
Shooting your school as if it wasn't easy.
By the way, to all my followers, why is that the new default thing now?
I get a comment blank as if it was easy all the time.
It's so easy to add on to something.
It could be anything you could edit.
You know what I like to add to the end of like titles of things is we're going to make
X look like a fucking joke, you know, like Columbine or 9-11, things like that.
That's a good name for a sequel.
The bug wars look like a fucking joke.
Just kidding.
Oh, no.
It's too fucking serious.
You can never make such a jest out of such.
Everyone, make sure you're following Munchy at Munchy Wears Tiny Hats on Twitter to get
the full bug wars saga documented.
The bug wars were the most depressed I've ever been in my entire life, especially after
I fell down the stairs after I slipped on a puddle of chocolate in that place by myself.
Fuck.
The bug wars were awful.
People discussed them no longer.
A new person, new person.
This man's too upset.
Okay.
Munchy, why don't you tell us about your...
Wait, I'm sorry.
I meant to say Mumkey.
I can't sound myself.
Okay.
Mumkey.
What's up with your parents?
What, you know, how disappointed?
I don't know who you mean.
Me or him?
I'm talking about you, god damn it.
Mumkey.
I can't fucking tell.
The meat runs too deep.
Mumkey.
Yeah, Mumkey.
Right.
All right.
Munchy, this question does not apply to you because of your age.
But are you guys aware of the show Viva La Bam?
Yes.
No, I don't think so.
Okay.
So for anybody at home, it's this old show about the adventures of Bam Margera just harassing
his parents all the time.
And the reason why I bring it up is because I think my relationship with my parents is
almost identical.
Oh no.
Where they're like these two just like normies, you know, and then I'm like the rambunctious
crazy child who just fucks with them all day.
But it all, it all comes from a place of love in some way.
To bring this in a way I understand, is this similar to Johnny Test, you know, he's like
a rambunctious kid.
I wouldn't compare Johnny Test to Bam Margera.
We need a really carbon copy of Johnny Test.
Now I understand.
Okay, okay.
Dude, if I had twin older sisters who were hot, I would have been incesting the fuck
out of that show.
And they are super hot.
And voiced my premier My Little Pony voice actor, Tara Strong.
Does she do both of them?
No, she only did one.
I like the one with the curly hair, not the straight hair.
She's hot as fuck.
I can never tell them apart.
You are racist.
Yeah.
That's white people.
That's twins.
So go on.
So what did you do?
Did you torment them?
It's almost perfectly analogous because my mom, much like Bam's mom, April, is just
always confused and wondering where this torture is coming from and what she did to
deserve it.
Whereas my dad kind of like tries to go with the flow and laugh and have fun.
One example I can provide is because I've had my parents, both of them in a video at
some point way back in the day, I did a movie missions podcast with me, Manimal, and my
dad because the audience voted for us to watch a Serbian film, which is a movie about a man
who is drugged and fucks his son in the ass.
Nice.
Whoa.
Did he start the day thinking he was going to do that and kind of just end up in that
situation?
So about a week before the end, I was like, you know what, dad, we're doing this movie
podcast and I want you to be on this episode and you'll see why once we watch the movie.
And he was like really nervous all week because he's probably like camera shy.
He doesn't want to like get on mic and talk because he knows that there's going to be
a few thousand people who watch it.
And like he knows all about my monkey shit and he's, I don't know if he's ashamed or
proud or what, but he's like it is what it is.
So he clearly didn't want any part in it.
But I guilt-tripped him kind of into like, oh, come on, come on the podcast, dad, it'll
be fun.
You know, like we need a guest.
It'll be cool.
He's like, oh, fine.
So we watched a Serbian film, a movie that not only should you never watch with your
parents, but some might argue you should never watch ever, like in general.
My dad was, he was absolutely mortified.
I'd never seen him in the state of being before where he was.
He was just like, like he was possessed by some like demonic ghost and he was just like
an empty shell of a human being.
So if you want to hear that podcast, it's like an hour and 10 or 20 minutes long.
And my dad probably says three sentences the whole time because he just, he's so aghast
at the film that I forced him to watch.
The fact that he's there though and saying nothing, I think would really add an ambiance
to a video like that, knowing that a dad is there, silently observing this shit.
I'd like to see that.
Yeah.
That's, you know, that's what our podcast needs.
We need a dad.
I would really spice things up.
Oh my God.
You've been kidnapping them lately.
I know.
You got to spare some.
I do have a few that I could spare, but they're, they're a rare breed, dude.
They're a rare breed.
Dads are a rare breed.
They're like diamonds, you know, out there.
They're like 30% of the population.
They're rare.
All right.
A good dad is rare.
We should, we should say non-rapist dads, you know, because most of them, you know.
Who's the best kinds?
So the one time my mom was in a video was during my recent Spyro series, my brother
Pachi was on.
And we thought, you know what'd it be funny if I called my mom on speakerphone and told
her that Pachi was saying bad words?
So naturally when my mom answers, she is absolutely wasted because she loves to just, Friday and
Saturday nights, it's rare that my mom doesn't have a drink.
So the only time my mom probably will ever be recorded in any of my videos is her fucking
plastered and she doesn't even know that it happened.
That poor woman.
She's going to come at you with legal action one of these days.
Watch out.
If she ever finds out.
The episode is called, Munk His Mom If You Want to Find It.
Okay.
Nice.
I'm looking forward to it.
Hippo.
What were you saying?
I didn't say anything.
You said something you piece of shit.
Okay.
Never mind.
Just like we always try to.
Good job.
Hashtag kickmate.
So even though I torture my parents constantly with this retarded bullshit of watching awful
movies and calling them when they're drunk and recording it, they still do whatever they
can I guess to support me.
I mean, just yesterday I moved from Iowa to North Carolina, which is a fucking 17 hour
drive and instead of me wasting like what, $3,000 on movers and shit, my dad's like,
no, I'll just fucking do it.
So we loaded up his truck and me and my mom and dad spent all of yesterday.
We left at 2 AM, got here at about like 8 PM and drove all the way down here and they
helped me move in just because I guess they love me and shit.
I don't know.
It's weird.
I wouldn't do that for somebody.
You know, that's cool.
And when I moved out to Cincinnati from Massachusetts, it was about like a 16 hour drive.
And my mom came with me and we did the same thing.
She helped me move in.
Not the place I'm in now, but like my old apartment and what a sweetheart.
Yeah.
It's really nice.
I really like parents who do that shit.
And the weirdest part is at least Bam Margera is a millionaire and can give his parents
money, but I have fucking nothing.
So I'm just doing it for no reason.
You have something far more valuable.
Minor internet fame.
Hashtag kick monkey.
Yeah.
So that's pretty much while administering that kick, you would accidentally kick me.
Yeah, not only are our names similar, but we look similar too.
Yeah.
And that's pretty much all I.
You are the same guy.
That's, you know.
Right.
That's all I really have to say about my parents unless you guys had more questions like we
did for Hippo.
Yeah.
Oh, we already said what you fucking, are they ready killed as fuck?
Well, the first time I ever voted in a presidential election was this last one because it was
the first time I was old enough because the last Obama election, I was only 17.
But me and my dad went together and we both voted for Donald Trump.
So I guess you can say my dad is read as fuck.
I'm just curious, does that mean your mom didn't vote?
My mom, I think is no pilled because she knows literally nothing.
She didn't know which political party Michelle Obama would have been associated with.
That's how little she knows about the entire process.
So no, she did not vote.
Would you say that your mother is an object?
She is a woman.
Right.
Okay.
All right.
I see.
Good to know.
Excellent.
All right.
Well, we now have a thorough understanding of a monkey's parents political views.
Excellent.
That's what I was hoping to get.
How about Tom?
I know you've got stuff to say about parents.
Yeah.
How about a dog?
How about it?
I have, I mean, my parents, I love them.
They love, they would, they'd go to war for me.
But there's no need to lie here.
There's no need to lie.
No.
I mean, I have this, this like this confusing relationship, I suppose.
Because my dad, like it's interesting, they were talking about having like your parents
and videos.
I did a whole series of videos with my dad two years ago.
Godzilla shit, right?
Yeah, we did.
Because like, oh yeah, we grew up, I grew up watching Godzilla all the time and Ultraman
like all these fucking cheesy shit because my dad's like a nerd in denial because he's
a nerd, but he was also a fat kid in high school and got bullied, so he's like, fuck
this and he got super fucking ripped, turned into a ninja and kicks ass now.
So you're like, nice.
He pretends to be that, but on the inside he's still.
Does he run the ninja school that Hippo applied for?
Actually, you know, I wouldn't be surprised.
He like, he told me one time that like in college, he had like these like ninja things
so like climb walls just climbed on the top of his dorm just because he could, like just
for shits and giggles and like trained with the black dragons and like could kill people
with his bare hands and shit.
Wait, what?
What's the black dragon?
Black people?
Yeah.
I mean, it's the most hardcore thing you can do.
Man, he got away with his life.
He met black people and lived.
Fucking crazy.
Wow.
No, but like my dad, like if you want to talk about someone who's red pill, my dad is
like the stereotypical, like red pill conservative.
Like he's an outdoorsman.
He has guns.
He has fucking crossbows.
Just super.
Crossbows.
So red-pilled.
No, like the outdoorsman kind of archetypal kind of, kind of like, you know, wants to
drive.
Usually drives a pickup truck.
Doesn't have one right now.
But like that kind of guy, but he's also a fucking dork at the same time and to talk
about Godzilla for like three hours or something.
So my relationship with my dad's pretty good.
Pretty cool.
He's also an author.
He's written like five books now, I think, and he's published.
He has like an actual publisher and shit.
Like small time.
But very...
That's awesome.
And then like, I don't know how he does it.
Like I feel...
My dad makes me feel like a retard because like I'm sitting here trying to do stuff and
I have like my whole schedule open and he like works 60 hours a week and wrote like
five books in his spare time.
It was like, huh, where...
I did not inherit that work that sucks.
Teach me your ways and that kind of shit.
Like, fuck it.
But the downside is that because he's so like conservative, he can't like nobody in the
house really understands what I'm doing and they're all just like, but you can't move
out.
So clearly you're not...
This isn't good.
Like this isn't working.
You need to get like a real job and be a real boy and stop doing this.
And my mom is way more aggressive about that because my dad has like a creative outlet.
Like he writes and stuff.
So he understands kind of like, even though like what I'm doing doesn't make enough money.
He understands why I'm doing it because he actually has passions and he's like, he wants
his books to succeed and if he could, he would just sit, you know, and write all day.
My mom doesn't have that.
She doesn't have that...
We had an argument today about me doing creative stuff and she just like, it's like, well,
right, you're fucking miserable in a failure right now.
So you might as well be miserable in a failure at a real job and actually get money.
What are you getting out of this?
And just like, yeah, you know, doing something I like has no value.
Right?
It was, it was dumb.
That's fascinating.
That's really a fascinating perspective on life.
Well, if you want to understand my mom and how it works is that the reason I started my
Patreon and started like monetizing my content in the first place because I got fired from
my job that I had after college because I was working full time at Whole Foods doing graphic
design stuff for them.
Rolling in red bank bro.
Very blue pill.
Working at Whole Foods.
The very blue pill.
The bluest of blue pill.
I did not fit in there at all.
But I got fired from that job because I was too red pill and I'd like to think that.
But I started doing Patreon and my mom in particular was freaking out because I have
student loans to pay because I made the foolish mistake of going to college.
She's like, it's been like three months, you haven't looked for a job.
How are you, you're going to run out of money.
How are you paying for these things?
I just find I said, oh, I have this Patreon thing and I got money and like people like
I'm succeeding.
I'm like, I'm following my dreams and it's working and I have money and people care about
it.
Like this is amazing.
Well, now you can pay us rent and took like half of the money, the entirety that like
I was successful and never asked for, never asked for rent before or since, but the one
time I was successful, she needed to siphon half of my money.
And when I asked about it, it was because, oh, you weren't working towards anything.
So we decided to charge you rent.
If you were actually, if you had a real job and we had some sort of plan, we would stop
charging you rent.
That's why we haven't charged your sister rent.
You know, I sort of understand that logic, but it just shows a fundamental misunderstanding
of what you're trying to do is really what's going on there.
The whole thing that I didn't, I didn't like it's because like their excuse was that, is
that we gave you a year rent free and then started charging you rent.
And I'm like, the timeline kind of worked on that because I, because I was like, why
aren't you charging my sister for rent?
Cause she just graduated college at this time, like two, three years ago.
And they're like, well, she's going to get a year rent free and then she has to pay too.
Never happened.
So I'm, I'm completely.
Yeah.
Well, that's just not, that's fucking, that's deceit.
So, so I'm just, I'm just convinced that it was, um, trying to.
Psychological warfare.
Yeah, exactly.
Well, yeah.
There's, there's no, there's no.
They're trying to pressure you into like one of these, yeah, another path that that seems
clear to me.
So I mean, my mom, my mom's really, she's, she's like done like a personality 180.
She used to be super religious, maybe go to church till all the 16, CCD, all that shit,
hardcore.
Like, uh, I was, I, all my friends got into magic gathering and I've saved up my allowance
to buy a bunch of cards and then she's like, actually, these are the devil and took them
from me and burned them.
Oh boy.
Burned them.
Yeah.
And then.
Whoa.
And then got rid of.
Red pill.
That is pretty red pill.
That's true.
Got rid of my Harry Potter books.
I still haven't read the rest of them.
Um, so I don't know.
You're not.
You still haven't read the rest.
Oh no.
It's a long lasting impact.
I don't, I don't know anything about that shit.
So that, and, but now she's like turned into this like a party animal and just goes drinking
like all the time.
Jesus drank.
Jesus was into that shit.
That's consistent.
So I don't, I don't really know.
I don't really understand her.
We have like a working like, like relationship, but that's about it.
Yeah.
Uh, we don't see eye to eye at all.
And she stole like a lot of money from me for no reason and, uh, I don't take kindly
to that.
Is this like a separate thing or is the same issue?
No, it's, it's, I mean, we, we have a problem.
I mean, if she just walked into your room, beat you up and took two grand, like that's
a separate offense to, you know.
Like Tom ever had two grand.
Yeah.
That's funny.
You think I have money?
No.
Um, it would just be like she'll ask for money and then won't pay it back.
And when I asked for it back, she'll deny that it never happened.
So she, I am sensing that there's some mental gymnastics going on in this person that is
justifying some things that are being done that may not as strictly adhere to the laws
of logic.
Um, well, she's also the person who, uh, disconnects the wifi every night because she's
convinced that she can't sleep with it on, even though we're in range of seven other
wifi networks besides the one in our house.
What the fuck?
Hey, you know, can I comment on that real quick?
There is a real illness called something I forget.
It's where people think that electrical, uh, like for us all season one and two.
Oh, that, that's right.
Is that thing people?
Yeah.
That's exactly who the thing I'm thinking of.
Maybe it's true that if she thinks it's on, it will cause her pain because she thinks
it's that way.
Maybe she's got that thing.
I don't know.
Maybe.
Because I, I mean, I use my phone as a wifi network all the time when the wifi's off.
So there's a wifi network right there anyway.
Yeah, right.
Right.
And nobody cares.
So I don't,
How has nobody in your family tested her and said, okay, we're going to put the wifi
in the other room.
You tell us if it's on and then see what happens.
You don't have to raise these things.
The thing, the thing with my mom is that you can't fight with her.
You can't, you can't do it.
She, you, you try and have a discussion and it instantly falls apart and then you turn
into a horrible person and it's, that's the thing with parents, man, and this is like
the big thing.
They're, they're the authority.
If you, I mean, especially if you live with them and you financially depend on them, what
are you going to do?
They, they, they hold all the cards.
They can just fucking kick you out.
If you go against them too hard.
Get a dad who isn't a pussy and beat her ass.
Get a dad.
Yeah.
Go out.
Go, go talk to Munchy.
He's got plenty of dads that you can swap out.
Okay.
Can I borrow a dad?
I, it's like puts like a, like a, like a note across the table, Tom.
It may interest you to know, Tom, that killing women is actually good for your Christ consciousness.
Whoa.
It's not actually, it doesn't actually negatively impact your Christ consciousness.
In fact, it makes it go up.
This, this changes everything.
I think that before the Muhammad consciousness, not Christ.
Yeah.
Well, no, that's true.
Mumpgee, you dog fuck, as I explained before, Christ consciousness has nothing to do with
Jesus Christ.
It has everything to do with crystals, the Christal light.
That's right.
The Christal lights.
My Christals.
Oh man.
This is some hardcore lore.
This is good to know.
Yeah.
This lore is too retarded for my brain.
My J.O. Christals.
All I'm saying, Tom, is to kill you all.
J.O. Christals.
Okay.
Wow.
You know.
Oh yeah.
It's killing your mom because she's a bitch.
All you need is more money.
What Tom needs is more money.
Yeah.
He needs more money.
He needs all of these problems here.
It only had some sort of a platform for you to donate money to him.
Oh wait.
Take it away, Tom.
I've actually, I've changed my old Patreon to patreon.com slash save me.
That's the actual URL.
Really?
Whoa.
That's awesome.
I can't believe that wasn't taken.
I was surprised too.
I guess no one is begging on Patreon as hard as I wanted to start doing.
Patreon.com slash save me for Tommy Oliver.
Please.
Please go.
Press one for death.
We need one of those like this animal fucking died because no one gave you shit.
But then, the armistice allowed him Oliver.
And that guy is in way worse shape right now.
In the arms of an angel, how would I get through one night without you if I believe in you?
Don't stop believing.
Oh, oh, oh, monkey.
I'm gonna start singing and then you get that ready.
You get that ready.
Okay.
I'm getting it ready.
I know what you mean.
How could I go through one night without you if I had to live without you?
What kind of life would that, there it goes.
I wonder if people could tell what that was when I tried to quit.
We are familiar.
I bet it's famous.
It's world famous.
Okay, Tom, any further points you'd like to add?
No, I think that's pretty much it.
But I, fuck it, patreon.com slash save me.
Yeah.
I love that.
God, who's that?
Munchy.
Munchy, what's up?
Tell us about your hot Mexican mom who isn't Mexican.
Yeah, it's upsetting, upsetting to say the least.
My mother is the only parent that I will discuss currently.
And she's a nice person.
But I'm your dad.
Well, I know.
Ergo, why would I need to talk about Munchy?
You all know him.
He makes the same five jokes over and over again.
He doesn't have any worthwhile content.
You all know him already.
Munchy, we should do a grandparents episode where you just talk about my parents.
Yeah, we should.
That's a good idea.
Your dad, pretty good, gonna be stolen soon though.
No.
My mom don't know.
No, I needed him.
He's mine now.
I'll hold some ransom.
If you can get me five doubloons, I'll give you back your dad.
How many Christ conscious crystals is that?
It's like about like 50 or so comprised of 10 different doubloons.
I've only got like zero.
Yeah, because you're a fucking fag.
Okay, so go on.
What about your folks?
No, I think we gotta keep this shitty meme train going for another five minutes.
I can't take any more, all right.
Tell me about your mom.
My mom is a nice person.
She's always been a pretty fucking soft bitch.
She's not hitting the gridiron every day on the b-ball court.
Okay, that's all right.
But she's a really nice person and she doesn't hate me.
There are ergo.
She's okay.
One of the few.
If she were to stand in my way, she would be evaporated.
However, she's minding her own business and therefore she shall live to see another day.
Reasonable.
I think the big question, Monchi, the question on everybody's mind is what sort of parents
slash parents would allow their 15 slash 16 year old son to fly out to something called
a radcon full of a bunch of former bronies in their mid 20s who are probably gonna molest
their son.
I mean, you're right about that.
But even like two years, I think before that, he was allowed to fly, or maybe even three,
I can't remember, when he was like 13, he was flying out to bronicon across the entire
country just to fucking goof around with a bunch of pedophiles.
How did you convince your mom to let you do that?
Two words, punitive damages.
Can you go into more detail on that?
What more punitive you need, he just spelled it out for you.
All right, I'm done.
What's a punitive damage?
You know, he was offended or there was a civil trial and he won and his mom had to give him
billions of dollars to fly to bronicon.
Oh, exactly.
What was the trial from?
Well, there's a lot of cereal.
You ate too much cereal.
Oh, I thought you ate too much cereal and you sued your mother.
No, no, no.
Yeah, correct.
Okay, good.
That's the one.
I know that one.
I know that song.
I know it.
It's real.
I was opposed to a fake song.
I know it.
You made my four local come out of my mouth when you said that.
You only knew underpants because now they're soaked in four loco.
My undertails are soaked in piss.
Oh, no.
Okay, fucking my mom.
The reason why all that was allowed to transpire was because I just explained myself properly
and she was like, yeah, I've trained you to be self descent from when you were like three.
Right.
But not how to pronounce things.
Yeah, but unfortunately, you inherited retard talks.
Maybe if she had been born in this country and hadn't hopped the wall
to infiltrate this America.
Maybe you'd be able to speak properly.
She's one of the rare Mexican immigrants who was white and jumped over the wall.
That's right.
Yeah, exactly.
He was raised in Mexico City.
He didn't illegally immigrate.
That's what you think.
All immigration is illegal, Mumky, especially in Mexico.
What does CK mean in Spanish?
Cock.
I don't know.
Yeah, there you go.
That means yes, cock.
So, you know, one thing I was curious about.
So just specifically, I was curious about the finances of your trips, Mumky.
Munchy.
God, fucking dammit.
I'm sorry.
So, I know that you do a lot of entrepreneurial type of work,
mowing lawns and shit.
Yes.
Have you had all along your trips been self-financed?
No.
Like, okay.
I've been to three bronycons, I think.
Yeah, that sounds right.
And the first bronycon was completely,
the pizza's here!
The pizza's here!
You guys, I can finish the story as Munchy since we're the same person,
if that's okay.
Yeah, please do.
So, my mum, I went up to her when I was 12,
and I said, hey, mum, I want to go with the bronycon.
And she said, well,
what level is your Christ consciousness, son?
And I said,
There's the dog delivery man.
I'm really excited.
They live in the Rick and Morty episode where dogs become sentient,
and they're like walking around with their robotic legs,
and they deliver pizzas and shit.
And yet they're still serving humans by delivering pizza.
Well, they know, they gotta make a living like everybody else.
Yeah, this is an alternate universe where they became friends.
It's not like a universe that would spawn something like Munchy.
Are you sure this isn't just Mexico, and that's where Munchy actually lives?
In Mexico, it's like the Amazon drone program where drones deliver your packages,
instead they tie it to a dog and just make it dirty.
What do you think about it?
He's in California, that's basically becoming Mexico right now.
That's right, it's been absorbed.
I'm pretty sure Trump's signing the legislation as we speak for it to be absorbed.
No, he would sign to stop that.
He wouldn't make it happen.
No, there's too many Mexicans there already.
It's a lost cause, it's gone.
He's gonna put a wall around California.
California, that's right.
I guess they didn't vote for him.
Possibly the whole West, yeah.
California is way too liberal though.
We should put up a wall.
It is.
You guys want us to see from the union?
Fine, wall.
You should put a wall between every state border.
That'd be, yeah, I mean.
And then through, and then a wall all the way around the ocean of the U.S.
and then the border to Canada as well and then just put a roof on it.
You know what we really need to do?
We need to put a wall around the actual barrier that matters,
around the entire earth to keep those real illegal aliens out of our country
because those guys, I don't want them anywhere near my earth.
We need to block out the sun like they did in The Matrix,
put a giant cement wall around the entire earth.
Do you remember when the aliens illegally immigrated to Roswell, New Mexico?
Fuck those guys.
That was bullshit.
They're still under arrest.
They're stealing our fucking jobs.
They never left.
They dropped anchor babies and now they're hanging out.
They're getting subsidized by the government in a secret lab that we can't go to.
Hey guys, this is me, Munchy.
Hey, Mumpeat, what's going on?
Okay, okay.
Munchy, important question before we get started.
Pan pizza or stuffed crust?
Stuffed crust, baby.
Fuck yeah, dude.
Press one for stuffed crust.
No, there's too many ones in the comments.
Make it stop.
There's so many.
You can't make it stop, Mumpeat.
If you look at it in a different way, there's just a bunch of 11s instead.
In fact, nine sets of 11s.
Press 11 for Munchy.
At least nine sets of 11.
11 is a very racist term against the Japanese people in Code Geass.
But anyway, Munchy...
What were you asking me?
The finances or something?
Fuck, yeah.
How did you pay for your trips?
That's what I was curious about.
Oh, okay.
The first running counter was completely her.
And then like, I think it was like, for the second trip it was like the hotel and her
ticket was on her and I just had to pay for like 75% of my ticket.
And then for the third one, just the hotel was her and I paid for both tickets.
She had to attend as well for the Bronycons because she was like, you know, kind of fucking
weird.
But then for Radcon and future installments of the shit, I just paid for myself.
Wait a minute.
You're saying that your mom was at Bronycon?
Yes.
What the fuck?
Did she stay in the hotel?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, she didn't attend Bronycon.
She was just at the hotel.
Did she get Tara Strong's signature?
Yeah.
It's funny you mentioned that actually.
One poster is directed directly towards my mom because she stood in line for me at Bronycon
2012.
Oh, that's pretty nice.
She stood in line for me to get a poster because I wanted to do something else.
And the voice actor assigned it to her and said, my mom was awesome.
And then she was like, hey, I was like, yeah, you know what, my mom is awesome.
Which voice actor was this?
It was some fucking bitch.
Was it Andrea Libman?
No, it was Andrea Hussie.
No, no, it was the one that Digi almost killed.
Oh, that's Jeff.
Nicole Oliver.
Hey, that's cool.
But it was his birthday, bitch.
It's my birthday, bitch.
Did Digi just walk in the room?
Dude, you need to watch this video that GiveMate of this event that happened, Momkey, if you
haven't seen it.
Oh, I've seen it.
It is legendary.
Oh, OK.
You better fucking believe us.
I watched all the Bronycon episodes.
Good man.
They're all good.
That wouldn't say that.
How else would he have gotten the elusive content of me looking at the camera intensely
for his Procrastinators episode?
Yeah, yeah.
That's true.
And I saw the footage of all you fuckers up on a stage yelling cuss words at a crowd full
of children.
I was like, why did you do this?
That was mostly Digi who yelled the sways.
He was drunk as fuck.
Why?
Because he was drunk.
Dude, imagine.
It's Bronycon.
There's tons of kids there.
And all these fucking assholes in there, like early 20s, jumping on stage yelling fuck
at the kids.
Kids there.
It's Digibro's fucking birthday, Bronycon's birthday.
Yep.
It was pretty fabulous.
We need to have a fucking Bronycon.
I love that place.
We need to have our own Bronycon.
I was curious about one thing, Munchy.
And specifically, I'm curious about your relationship with your mom.
So your mom paid for your trip the first time.
I'm curious.
Because I feel like a lot of kids-
Brony curious.
When they're-
I don't know how to say that.
You weren't there.
Oh, no.
That's our word.
He's been saying, but forget it.
No.
So, like, your mom was kind of like expecting you to pay more of your way as you got older.
Did you have any resistance to that?
Were you an entitled little shit?
And we were like, no, mom, you paid for everything for the rest of my life.
I literally want to shit in my pants and have you change it my entire life, mom.
Well, did Jess just walk in the room?
Of course I wanted to shit my pants and piss on my walls.
But that's unrelated to the money.
I just wanted to do that with my own accord.
And she agreed.
Okay.
I offered to pay more money.
That's, you know, I expected something like that.
You are an unusually mature guy when it comes to a personal responsibility, Munchie.
And that is to be commended, I think.
Thank you, bitch.
Piss on my walls.
So other than pissing on your walls, are there any other parents-related stories you want to tell?
Well, the thing that there's not like a lot of stories, because while me and my mother are like close in the sense that we like like each other,
like she has out from the set, like out from the fucking do is to try to do, make me be like my own guy.
And so she's always trying to make me like self-suspicion.
So we don't really like, we used to do like stuff together, but we don't like do anything together anymore.
I know what you mean.
Which is fine.
Yeah, so there's not really a lot of stories.
Oh, besides the one time where we almost were stuck over the border in Mexico.
Oh, right.
Yeah, why don't you tell that real quick?
That's a fascinating story.
I am of mud-blood descent as stated earlier.
I'm very low on the fucking hemospectrum.
And my mother was like, you know, Tijuana's fucking sick, bro.
And I was like, fuck yeah, bro.
And you know, like you want to go to Tijuana?
I was like, fuck yeah, bro.
And then she was like, sick, bro.
I like your mom's vocabulary.
Where do you think Munchie got it off?
So we went to Tijuana and then we're like, all right, it's pretty fucking bad actually.
Let's go home.
And then-
The end.
Because you went there for the whores in the gambling.
That's the problem.
Exactly.
The whores and I did pet-hit.
But other than that, it was a total failure.
No, no, no.
Not a horse.
A whore's the whore.
Nate, he knows what you fucking said.
Yeah.
Okay, good.
Wow, Nate.
Thanks.
It's almost like you're bin-sane, LOL.
Please take that back.
It's a terrible traffic burn.
Anyway, when we were about to leave, my mom was like, oh yeah, I didn't bring your passport,
by the way.
I was like.
Oh, no.
Thanks, mom.
I always want to live here forever and never go home.
Yeah, right, okay.
It's a secret way to try and get rid of you.
By the way, I don't know if this is this for all of the border, but that particular day,
there was this weird dystopian line to get to the US.
It was a fucking photo of a Russian bread line.
I see.
It was just a singular gate to get into the US.
We had to wait in this line for two hours, and then my mom had to just reason with the
guard.
He looks like I just picked him up from over here, but he's on the other side.
Please don't kill me, Mr. Donald Trump.
I'm clairvoyant.
I can see in the future.
Well, Trump was working borders.
Yeah, man.
He knew his future would involve it heavily.
Yeah, he knows his stuff.
He knows exactly how it works.
So what, did you get arrested or what?
No, he was just like, hmm, what age are you?
And I was like, oh, I don't know.
And then it was like, where do you go to school?
I don't know.
And then it was like, yeah, sounds legit.
Yeah.
And I was like, yeah, yeah.
That sounds good.
And then he was like, all right, fucking leave my side, bitch.
He walked over to this side and all was happily ever the after.
Now, real quick munch.
It's not that well known, but there is a fan wiki about the PCP.
And there's an entry about your mother, Munchie.
If you don't mind me reading it.
Oh, wait.
OK.
Yeah, I'm going to read it right now.
It says, Munchie's mom was the founder and former leader of the Crystal Gems,
enthralled by the beauty of Earth.
Munchie's mom led her friends and allies in a rebellion against the gem homeworld
around 5,500 years before the events of the series,
successfully driving the invading homeworld gems off the planet
and saving the life forms inhabiting it.
Beautiful stuff.
Yeah.
I mean, she did do that.
She is a fat whale.
So, you know, it matches up.
They forgot to add that she is a gigantic slut
who will fuck any fucking shit with a car wash, you know, anyone.
Like, yeah, big slut, big slut.
Yeah, that's all true.
And she's dead now.
LOL, get fucked.
Yeah, got him, got him.
Except for, like, in these weird inside your lion memories shit.
I only saw that episode once.
I don't know what's going on.
I didn't know you even fucking watched that show.
I've seen, like, the first 30 episodes, and then maybe I'll watch the rest someday.
It's pretty good.
Yeah, I like it.
Munchie's life, the show that is.
I like Munchie's life, the show.
Oh, that fucking reminds me.
I almost forgot I hate Nate.
Here's why.
Yeah, OK.
On the Steven Universe episode, you were going to have me.
You were going to wake up later than when you messaged me.
Wasn't that, like, episode two?
Yeah.
It was way early, yeah.
And I didn't get to be on, and I forever haunted your nightmares.
Oh, I remember that.
I remember that, because you were fucking late.
I can't wait all day for your latest videos.
You told me that day, Nate!
I didn't know you were supposed to be early.
Maybe we'll do a follow-up one day.
Maybe, I don't know.
You want to be a Steven Universe?
Yeah, like, episode two is Steven Universe, the PCP.
Oh, my God.
That's when we all drew Crystal Gems for ourselves and put in the intro that I animated so beautifully.
No.
It just, yeah, that's Steven Universe.
See, Jesse and Digi did it like a gem cast.
Oh, you guys did one, too.
You guys did one, too.
That was a separate one.
On the horse thing.
Yeah, there you go.
Anyway, yeah, a fucking sick story.
Yeah, I think that's all I have to say.
She's a nice person.
Get the fuck out of my old sight, woman.
How's that pizza, Munchie?
Let me get my pizza.
Hold on.
I didn't want to eat, because I didn't want to ruin the world.
Ah, it's going to go cold.
Fuck this podcast.
Here, here.
Hey, guys, welcome to Stealing Your Dad.
It's definitely as easy.
I'm going to take this, Mr. Bit, and upload it on my channel.
Is that Pizza Hut?
You got there?
I'm going to do a...
Here.
Wait, wait, Munchie.
You can't do that.
What kind of toppings do you get on your pizza, Munchie?
What...
Is that...
Just tell me if that's Pizza Hut.
That is Pizza Hut, right?
I need to know.
Okay, okay.
Munchie, what kind of pizza did you get?
Meatlovers.
Oh, hell yeah.
You would.
You literal gay lemal.
Now, Nate, before we go to your parents, I have a confusing question.
It doesn't really make sense to me.
It's like a paradox because somehow your parents raised you and you're arguably one of the
best guys ever.
Some might even say the best guy ever.
That's true.
But at the same time, your parents raised Ben St. Arguably the worst guy ever.
Most would argue the actual worst guy ever.
So how did this happen?
Where did your parents fuck up in the timeline?
Well, you know, it's a freak thing.
It's kind of like, you know, leukemia can kind of crop up just genetically.
You put two different people together.
One of their kids, you know, is perfectly healthy.
The other's got a crippling illness like Ben does just personality-wise.
Retardation?
Yeah, yeah.
I thought it was that like Nate like siphoned off all of the goodness, all of the good vibes
from Ben's corpse is living corpse.
That is true.
And now you're the better guy than him.
Ben's like a Dark Souls player that I ganked in the womb and absorb his humanity.
And now he's a hollow shell of a man.
That's why you won the race.
It's no coincidence that Nate is a Holocaust survivor and Nate is Hitler.
That's right.
It's no coincidence.
Also, Hitler, the most famous Holocaust survivor.
That's been a great job.
There are too many things wrong with that statement.
I know.
I don't even want to unpack it because it's so brilliantly stupid.
Yeah, let the viewers do it at home.
Well, I don't know, man.
Nate, by the way, real quick, what did you just like say that again?
Because something popped up in my memory and I was going to say it really quickly,
but I also can't remember what you just said.
You said it all really fast.
Like a Holocaust survivor, Hitler?
No, no, no, back about your parents.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
All of my family has cancer.
I'm probably going to have cancer by the time I die.
Is that true?
Yeah, that's true.
This is like in a movie, like a detective movie where the character says,
no, say that again and then it refreshes his memory and he solves the mystery
from some innocuous bullshit that the other guy said.
That's true.
I didn't think it would ever happen in real life.
The killer is Jane.
It's like, I'm going to die.
Which arguably a better ending.
There you go.
Oh, you've been saying, oh, you.
Oh, no, best of luck with that much.
Anyway, so I don't have that much to say about my parents.
I don't know.
Enough.
Pretty normal.
Yeah.
My dad is a psychologist.
He's a smart boy.
He's a psycho.
Yeah, he's a psycho.
My mom's a special ed teacher and they met like working at a place.
She has special ed.
Well, no.
I imagine she spent a lot of time with Ben.
You might say they were the perfect parents to try to raise a perfect son,
which succeeded one time, did not work out so well the other time.
Ben's the older brother.
So it's like he was the test run and then all the stuff they learned from him,
they used on you to make you a good son.
Ben's like the proto man and I'm like the mega man who's better in every way.
The proto man won at the end of the Sons of Death or the Sons of Fate.
He won the battle, but not the war of autism, which he has.
We'll see it back three if it comes out.
That's true.
Isn't like a mega man a fucking faggot?
Isn't that good?
Yeah, I can confirm.
That's true.
All right, continue.
If anyone interrupts again, I'll kill them.
Oh, shit.
Good.
I was just going to say.
Enough.
Did not see that coming.
God damn it.
Yeah, I don't know.
They met like doing like working with special ed kids, but in any case.
How did they, how did they work with Ben before they met?
Before that's one of the great questions of our time.
It doesn't make any fucking sense.
Ben's a retarded time traveler.
I'm sorry, I'll stop.
I just fucking hate Ben so much.
I understand.
That is totally relatable to my parents.
They would sympathize very much so with that.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't have a lot to say.
They're pretty great.
They're pretty great to me.
They've given me pretty much anything I wanted in life.
They never did anything particularly bad to me.
I don't know.
I have an older brother and younger sister.
We were all raised middle class.
It was good, man.
It was good.
I don't have any kind of crazy stories really because everything was totally normal and
not interesting.
Ben's in another PCP with Digi and Ben.
I remember that a little bit.
Only about his dad, about how he's kind of cool but also gay.
Kind of stern.
Yeah.
My mom kind of takes-
And he's ashamed of Ben's career choice.
He's just ashamed of Ben, period.
You know what?
Okay, that's a good jumping off point.
My dad is not ashamed of Ben's career choice at all.
I think he would really support anything that any of us do.
He's simply an incredibly practical guy and only cares.
You can do whatever you want but first you've got to meet your responsibilities of paying
the fucking bills.
So he's mad at us.
That's just life.
That's just how to live.
Don't tie everything like that.
I think it's a fool.
I'm on Team Dad.
Team Nate Dad.
That's sexist.
Right now, Ben's doing better.
My dad just worries that Ben won't be able to pay his bills or whatever.
That's all he cares about.
My sister is a tattoo artist.
She hates tattoos.
My mom too.
They hate the idea of tattooing.
My sister is a fucking tattoo artist.
Kind of like not what they're into.
But they've pretty much gotten over it and are just happy that she can support herself
doing something she's happy with.
In that respect, they're pretty chill.
One thing I've noticed is that my dad was really controlling when we were young.
He's the kind of guy who always believes he's right and usually is.
That kind of reinforces his desire to always be in charge of shit.
But as I've gotten older and gotten out of his thumb, gotten out from under his thumb,
and I think this is probably true of most people becoming an independent adult,
I feel a lot less of that shit.
His overbearing presence has lessened greatly and I can just kind of appreciate him.
He's kind of become a real person as opposed to an authority figure in my life.
I like him a lot more that way.
It's much easier to interact with him.
Because when you're a kid and you're growing up and you have a controlling dad,
it's easy to forget that he's also capable of being fun and doing cool shit.
I just see more and more of that as time goes on and he's not my boss anymore.
And it's nice.
It's a nice thing I'm trying to communicate.
I didn't really mention this about my dad.
Not really the controlling, but he believes he's right a lot of the time.
Just today, he misheard something I said and he would not believe that he misheard it.
He said that I didn't say the thing and it really made me mad.
What was the thing? I need to know now.
It was about the draw cast.
It was about the draw cast we were recording earlier.
I said, oh, I'm going to be on a draw cast.
I'm going to be on a podcast in 45 minutes.
And then that's going to take a couple hours and dinner wait until after that.
Or should I change it?
And he said, no, that's fine.
He thought I meant, like, could it wait an hour or 45 minutes?
And then that's why that is not really that interesting.
It just annoyed me that he would not consider the fact that he misheard me.
I know what you mean.
It's just stuff like that.
But it's interesting when I hear like, look at people interacting with their parents as if they're just interacting with a friend or like me or like someone.
It's weird. I don't act like I do around my parents the way I do around my friends.
I'm more so recently because they see my YouTube videos.
They see what I'm like when I'm not, you know, like being reserved.
You know what I mean?
I do.
That's that's a fascinating thing I observed.
Even when I was a kid, like, yeah, like this is what I was trying to say this before.
But like, when you see the way you're like my dad, especially my dad is very, he can be very high strung.
And like, when I was a kid, he was, you know, he was high strung.
But then when I would see him like, whatever I would go with him like to work on like the extremely rare chance I would see him like out just like doing his business.
He was like such a nice guy to everybody he met.
And it was like unbelievable to me that he was like this kind of guy out in the world was like such a sweetheart because like he works with a lot of old folks.
He's like a, you know, he does like elder counseling and shit now.
And he's done for like 20 years at this point, but that's his thing.
And like, he's just such a fucking softy to them.
I mean, you know, he still does his job.
But even not to them, but like to the nurses he interacts with to everybody else.
He seemed like such a nice guy.
And then when he would come home and just be like, why are these, you know, he wouldn't swear.
But like, this is just me in my voice explaining what he would say.
Why are there fucking dishes not done?
What the fuck is this shit?
Like I come home and nobody's done anything.
I have to do everything when I get home.
This is bullshit.
You know, he'd say it in much nicer language.
This world.
Yeah.
And he would pull out that gun and just end it all.
Every single day.
Every day.
He's unfortunately the invincible man, which is a big downside for him and his suicidal tendencies.
But yeah, you know, that's, that's, that's the funny thing about parents.
The way that as kids you perceive them versus the way they, they are sort of agents out in the world separate from that.
Total can be like hugely different, which I find very interesting.
And now that I'm an adult and get into a place where I'm becoming more of their equal as opposed to their, you know, not subservient, but you know, their child exclusively,
I'm able to understand that they kind of are put in a role where they, at least my dad, kind of felt he had to be the authoritarian.
And I could tell he never liked doing that.
He was, he never liked having to like punish us or be strict with us.
He would even, he would like tell us like, I hate, you know, having to fucking enforce these rules and shit.
But you guys got to learn, be responsible and take initiative and do all that kind of shit.
And I think it kind of eventually sunk in a little bit, I guess.
I've got a little bit more of a work ethic than I did when I was young.
But, you know, yeah.
I feel like your dad and my dad would get along. We should have a dad cussed.
Just like a sibling cuss, yeah.
And I would sneak in and fucking nab a bitch.
It's a danger to gather too many dads in one place with Munchie around.
That's a big risk that we'd be taking.
But I agree. I think our dads would get along great.
My dad is very much a dad, if you know what I mean.
Like 100% dad.
Well, actually, that's what I'm saying.
Like he's gotten a little bit less daddy and more chill dude-y in recent years.
And I think the fact that all his kids don't live with him anymore, he's finally free.
Which I don't think he's like super thrilled about.
I think he kind of misses having people around.
But nonetheless, like we're all out doing our own shit now.
And I can tell he's able to loosen up a little bit, you know?
You imagine what it feels like to just like-
Is his voice he loosened up any at all? Do you know?
I'll let you know next time I go visit.
Alright, thanks.
You ever think how like weird it is?
Like you're like a young man and then you get a wife and you have kids
and then your life is all about raising these kids to a certain age.
Like for 20 years probably.
And then they all leave and then suddenly you find yourself in a space-
With the sort of free time you would have had when you're like a young man at 25 or whatever.
I know exactly what you mean.
And then suddenly it's like, oh, what happened? Where am I?
What could that be like? It's probably very strange.
I bet it is extremely strange.
And like we've got this big house in Massachusetts that's now mostly empty most of the time.
Because it's just two people living there instead of like five.
Yeah, it's a big change, man.
I mean my dad is the kind of guy who plans like decades ahead.
And he's got schemes, he's got things to occupy him.
I mean my mom's retiring at the end of this school year, I think.
And my dad's retired in, I don't know, like a handful of years more.
And they have plenty of savings.
They are going to be just fine with their savings because my dad is on that shit.
And he's got me to start a 401K already.
And it's going, it's my fucking company, it's feeding into it every paycheck.
And yeah, I don't know, he's just like the most responsible guy in the world.
And that's been a big strength to him, like career-wise and like economically.
But also probably cost him a little bit of fun he could have had in his life.
I mean it still can.
And hopefully he will now, now that he's got more opportunities to do so.
You know, I really am happy that I can get older and understand where the way he's,
the way he like was a dude.
And like hearing about stories when he was a kid, like the shit he used to get into.
Like he was like a huge Monty Python fan when he was a kid.
And I didn't even really know until like a couple years ago when I heard Ben mention it,
like talking about my dad.
And like him and his buddy Asa, who you know, is like his friend from like elementary school
that he's still friends with.
They used to fucking quote that shit all the time to each other.
And they went across like England, having adventures together a couple times.
And they did all kinds of crazy shit.
And it's just really cool to learn about your parents as people, as opposed to authoritarians.
I really like it.
But parents feel like fathers because women are not people.
Well, you know, that's the thing.
I was, I feel a little bit guilty even saying this because I'm not focusing on my mom so much.
It's just that my mom's been a very passive person, you know, in like the relationship.
My mom was always kind of the one who did not take initiative to like do stuff.
She would, she's not a bitch.
She would, she'd be very supportive when there was things we wanted to do.
But she was very, she was dimmier, I suppose I'd say she was.
Are you sure that your family isn't Muslim?
Because it sounds very Muslim.
Muslim? No, she's, unfortunately, she's a disgraceful white woman.
Oh, no.
White people can't be Muslim, Nate.
What the fuck?
Well, not with their hair all, you know, sledding out in the sun.
Jesus Christ.
Somebody fucking mute this guy.
Whoever edits this, just edit Nate's fucking audio out of this podcast.
Nate, please.
Please.
And this.
Yeah, I don't know.
You should call your dad up and tell him you've been fucking my dog.
You bitch.
Pretty sure that's allowed in Islam.
Pretty sure.
All right.
That's it.
You're thinking about goats.
That same thing.
Same thing.
Dogs and goats.
Little known fact, same thing.
Hippo, what were you saying?
Yeah, I was saying like what you were saying about like your stories of your dad as a young man.
Like my dad has like a, I really like dad stories because he, my dad is good at telling stories.
You know, at the dinner table, like after, you know, we're done.
We're just sitting there just like, ah, nice.
And then he starts just, you know, I remember a thing and he tells us and he's always really good at telling it.
And he has so many like stories of him being like a really like a rough house, ruffian kid with his friends that would beat people up and scare people.
Wow.
That's awesome.
There was this really cool one where he was like, you know, he blew up his science class in his Christian class and he went outside.
Oh, probably.
And then there was like this one where he, him and his friends, there was like this one stairwell to this certain part of the school.
And he and his friends locked arms at the top of the stairs and they would not let anybody pass for like two hours.
Wow.
That's commitment to a fucking joke.
They really got in trouble, but it was great.
Yeah.
It's just sort of like, you know, old London, like, I don't know, 50s, 60s sort of cool, cool rough boys.
Upside down land.
Yeah, that's right.
It's cool.
Was that?
Old dad stories are really cool.
I'm imagining that's the Tower of London and the Queen is trying to pass.
She's like, oh, get out of my way, you ruffians.
And they're like, no, Goughna can't do it.
And the police can't do shit about it because those cucks don't carry weapons.
That's right.
They'll fucking get, they'll fucking get claws on the god.
I'll get you kids whips out small water gun.
No guns aren't allowed.
Oh yeah, whips out butter knife.
Oh wait, knives aren't allowed either.
That's knives are not allowed.
Whips out finger.
That's, that's a very, uh,
And they wag their finger.
Yeah.
It sounds like a very British attack is like wagging somebody.
Even that's dangerously phallic, a.k.a. patriarchy.
So we need to stay away from the whole finger wagging thing.
But you know,
Whips out white woman to be raped promptly by our,
by our immigrant friends.
No, no, Brexit passed.
There's no more immigrants in the UK.
That's right.
I mean, now that, yeah.
Hey, but I understand the,
the government and the,
and the political structure of your country way better than you.
I know what Brexit does.
I know what Brexit has done is made like immigrants want to come in really quick
before it happens, before it becomes like legal.
So now there's just so many more immigrants.
It's terrible.
Well, actually, I don't know.
I mean, like when, when, when the Brexit's done,
over 20 minutes a day,
do you just see a bunch of the jobs in the street or what?
Well, the thing is,
we've already had like a very multicultural,
at least London.
Like London is very multicultural anyway.
So it's like, I've seen,
I've seen different types of people all the time.
So seeing a bunch more would be like, hey, what am I?
Wait, I forget.
Where do you live?
Do you live near London?
What's your address?
Near London.
Okay.
Yeah, what's your address?
My address is,
One, two, three, Fake Street.
Brett Bong.
Yeah.
One, two, three, Fake Street.
That's what I always say.
Crumpet and T Street.
Do you know the address of the Queen's Palace?
What?
Buckingham Palace.
Yeah.
What's the address?
Google it.
You'll find it.
I was hoping you knew it,
so you could just say you live there.
That would have been it.
What if you were the Prince of England give all along?
Please make that true.
That would be cool for me.
Oh, and then I could,
then I could patron Ben Sain.
No!
Like, zero dollars.
No, there you go.
A little waste of money.
There you go.
Well, that was pretty much it.
Who do you think?
It was probably Munchie.
I don't know why I asked.
With that level of audio clipping,
there's only one man who can fit that,
who can fit that.
He is clipping the band.
So, anybody else want to say anything about their parents,
or should we?
Okay.
Well, we got questions too, so.
Yeah.
As a broad thing,
I just need to pass down to you, dear viewers,
the wisdom that I have been passed down by my hero,
the man, the myth, the legend,
Jean Rankowski,
aka, Jace Connors,
aka, part one, dude 91.
The advice is as follows.
Dads.
Get on the ground.
I can't.
The movie maker is obviously first.
First one for us.
However, second man.
No!
Munchie enough.
Also, by the way, listen, buddy,
so we have all three of those in quick succession
from one another.
Anyway, as I was fucking saying,
I forgot what, oh, no, okay, okay.
The concept and name and term specifically of dads
are inherently funny in every way.
And therefore, adding dad to the end
of any adjective, noun, or verb
inherently makes that verb or other word
like 10 times as funny.
You can do this with anything.
For instance, friendly dad for 20,
or super daddy,
or wood dad, anything.
It can be anything.
Adding dad to the end makes it better
because dads are just inherently funny.
I've got a good question for everybody to answer
to end this with,
would you become a parent?
Fuck no.
That is a good question.
Okay, we're gonna say no.
I'm definitely never going to have kids,
ever, no way.
Really?
You can quote me on that.
If I ever have kids,
listeners at home,
if I ever have kids,
you have permission to fly out to my house
and literally kill me.
I'll give you my address.
Now, this is a two-part question.
How come?
How do you say that?
Because I'm way too selfish
and I don't want to waste my life
raising some little fuckhead
who looks like me
because I know how bad my genetics are
and I'm not gonna put that curse
on some other innocent human beings.
That's a good point.
You're a terrible human being.
You've all seen me.
You don't want to perpetuate the monkey disease.
Nope, never.
That's true.
Yeah, fuck kids.
What do you say hippo?
Yeah, go ahead and give me.
No, you can fuck kids.
It's okay.
Sex with the young and all.
Well, now that you've told me that, I will.
I mean, technically,
every single person who has sex is a kid
because they're all somebody's child.
Oh, right.
Yeah, that is true.
So fuck you, I was right.
Oh, guys, I forgot to tell you,
this is really fucking important.
This is crazy.
From the South the other day,
if your mom never had children,
you won't either.
How crazy is that?
That's fucking fucked up, bro.
Yeah, probably true.
That's fucked up.
So much of the toilet left, am I right?
God damn it.
That reminds me of that famous screencap
of a little girl, I think,
a food of fucking her mom that says,
I'll take your virginity, mom.
Well, that's a good one.
Tom, what about you?
Are you ever going to have kids after you kill yourself?
What about you, Tom?
Are you going to take your mom's virginity?
Yeah, weigh in on that, please.
I mean, about having kids,
basically, I'm in the same position as Momgie.
I'm too selfish.
I have too much.
I think me and Tom are the same person in a lot of ways.
We have a lot of similarities, I feel.
But no, it was exactly the same.
I wouldn't want to fucking have kids,
because I think I have an interesting perspective,
because my parents...
Didn't want to have you.
No, they didn't.
I was literally in an accident.
I almost died when I was born,
and they should have just let it happen.
Wow, OK.
Would have saved me some trouble.
Oh, shit.
You know, that should not impact.
That doesn't matter.
Totally irrelevant.
No, I think it's important.
Don't worry about it.
I feel like a lot of people, like,
sincerely will get upset,
even if they don't say it,
that they were in an accident or that it wasn't tended.
I hope that's not the case with you, Tom,
because it doesn't matter.
You're worthy, and I like you,
and your existence has value.
I think it's safe to assume that the majority of
first-born kids are probably in an accident,
but then the parents are like,
oh, fuck it, we were going to do this anyway.
Let's just do it.
I think most kids are accidents in general.
Am I wrong about that?
I mean, probably, I don't know.
Whole human species was a genetic accident.
Wait a minute.
It's just a surprise.
I think, yeah, all right.
Well, the thing, the point I was going to make
is that my parents had me,
then two years later, they had my sister,
and then, like, 12 years later,
they had another kid.
Oh, fuck.
So I...
That kid was the accident.
We were all accidents.
So...
My whole life has been an accident,
but, like, just growing up
and, like, being, like,
old enough to, like, see the whole process,
and, like, this is what it is to have a child.
I was like, never.
Never in a million years.
Like, all the people who were romanticized having a kid,
no, I lived through it.
I didn't get to sleep either,
because I had to sleep right next door
where the baby was sleeping.
Right, right.
This is fucking horrible.
So, like, I saw all this shit happen.
Like, I've already had to change diapers and shit.
Fuck that!
I paid my dues.
Not doing it again.
So, no.
I paid my dues.
Never.
I have a unique perspective.
I know exactly what it means.
Time after time.
No.
Okay, alright.
Alright.
Perfectly acceptable answer.
Can we skip over Gip, by the way,
or did I just, like, pass out?
No, we didn't...
Well, he hasn't gone yet,
but we didn't skip him.
Yeah.
Okay, why don't you just go now?
He said he already has kids.
I...
Right.
I am kids.
No.
So, I think I'm unusual in my generation, generally,
that I just...
I like the idea of having kids.
Were you born in lay wrong generation, Gip?
No, no.
What I mean is, like, it's...
Lay wrong generation.
It's very, like...
Oh, that's...
Yeah, it's a very good joke.
Thank you, thank you.
Very, very good name.
Very good name.
I spent a lot of time with that.
I thank you, everyone.
I'm not being sarcastic.
I thought it was really funny.
It is funny.
It's hilarious.
Yeah.
He said it a million times before.
That makes it funnier.
And it's funnier every damn time.
It's like subscribe to Munky Jones.
Everybody in the comments, say subscribe to Munky Jones.
It only gets funnier as it goes on.
Yeah.
Sorry, Gip.
Okay, please.
That was an unconvinced grunt.
Yeah.
I like the idea of having a child.
I don't know whether I like the idea of raising it,
but I like the idea of raising it.
but I like the idea of having had raised a child up
and him or her to be like cool.
What age do you think you...
And to have a name that I gave them.
What age would you say is like, like, okay,
it'll be cool to have a kid once they're X,
like 25, like, I don't know, 40.
Just curious.
Oh, well, I think I'd enjoy it.
I think I'd enjoy it once they're not a baby
and they can talk and they can walk around
and be cute and stuff.
Now, Hippo, what if your kid becomes the next
Elliot Roger or like somebody who
kills a bunch of people?
Well, it wasn't because I'm not a terrible father.
The next greatest hero of all time?
Peter Roger was a terrible father.
He was one of the best fathers.
He just gave his son money and said, go.
That's really all you need to do to raise a good son.
Go shoot the people.
Go to the shoot people.
Go on, go to the shoot people.
That's what you need to do.
When you raise your kids, you can't say a lot about the fall.
You know, if Hillary Clinton was president,
Roger would not have killed all those people.
That's right.
Because she would have had sex with him.
Because Obama would not have brainwashed him
with Cory in the house.
It was her time.
That's a world famous YouTube video
of Cory in the house, what's in an OP, right?
No!
The faggot Jeff stole my joke.
He's not a faggot. He's cool.
Now, mine came out in like mid-March
and then his came out April 1st.
So who ripped off who? You tell me.
Oh, fascinating.
And also mine came out way after his, I think.
Yeah.
But mine was actually funny.
I don't know what I'm doing.
So you want to have kids, you're looking forward to it.
It'll be cool. You like all that shit.
Yeah, I like the idea
of being a...
Because I thought about
how you would do it wrong
and how you would do it right.
You've got to prepare for them to rebel.
You've got to accept that
they're going to live in a world
where everything is completely different and weird.
We're living with let's plays
and YouTube and shit
and our parents don't know what the fuck that is.
So when I'm a parent,
if I'm a parent,
my kids are going to be growing up on some weird shit
that I'm going to think is disgusting
and I don't get it.
But I'm going to have to let them do it
because that's the future.
So I've thought about the way
to be a good parent
despite the way that times change.
I don't know. I've thought about it a lot.
I want to be like a cool dad.
Like my dad.
Because he's cool.
I know what you mean.
I kind of empathize with parents
who are like, oh, I can't keep up with what kids are doing.
Because for thousands of years,
human society did not evolve very fast.
Now all of a sudden,
the internet has changed everything about the way we live our lives.
So I get it that people from the 20s
have no fucking idea what's going on
in the world right now.
The people from the 20s are dead.
Not all of them. That's only like 90s.
They're getting close to 100 now.
They don't even know what the internet is from.
Okay, fine. The fucking 40s.
Whatever. It's still big difference.
Big difference.
Yeah. Okay. Anyway.
Mumkey? I mean, Munchy? Same guy?
Munchy? Every time.
Every time. Munchy.
Tell me about your son.
Well, my son
will be named
Mumkey Jones
and I'll kill him.
It's funny that
Hippo wants to be a dad
because he thought his dad was cool.
I want to be a dad because I thought my dad
was a fucking faggot.
Dude, that's the Will Smith approach.
That's the Will Smith approach.
I'm just going to be like, ah, you fucking bitch.
I'll speedrun this shit, LOL.
I'll post this on Twitch.
He's going to be
720 no scoping those dad Olympics.
It's going to be fucking sick.
Alright.
I want to have a child
sometime in the future
once things are
not, you know,
when I'm not a baby myself.
No particular age
and also
if I could
I would just want to
as Hippo said just like fast forward the baby parts
but the baby's parts, I don't think they'll be that bad.
The babies are cute.
Yeah.
They're a bit of a gay
mess, but it's like one or two years.
It's bad.
I know it's bad, but like, you know.
Imagine doing anything for one or two years.
That's,
I'm with you, but I'm just saying that's this a long time.
No, yeah.
I want to be able to like
fucking like make someone
me but cooler.
That's what I'm going to try and accomplish.
How could that happen?
I would just force him to make grills.
Did you become Bill Blossom
for two seconds?
I think the most likely thing to happen
if Munchie, if you stay the way you are
as a parent that your child will be
the most like boring person
in the universe.
Yeah, just to rebel.
But you know, Munchie, I mean Munchie
would die.
Munchie would be the one guy who would be so proud
of his son to get a job at McDonald's
to make those McGriddles.
He wants it so bad.
Instead he'll become like
I want the McGriddles son!
I'm not here for you!
Where are my fucking McGriddles?
Bring them to me!
This is what I trained you for.
This is all you're good for to me.
The fry cook from birth.
The chosen one, yeah.
But instead of doing all that
gay shit
he learns how to become an astronaut
and he fucks away to space.
He'll be very disappointed.
I just wanted my McGriddles.
I just wanted McGriddles.
Fascinating.
No one's commented on this yet,
I don't think.
Because the episode's not out yet.
Bitch,
you are that.
I want to have a kid
but I couldn't even
imagine having a wife.
I know what you mean.
I was going to say something about that.
I would just want to adopt, I guess.
I know the feeling.
That is a thing.
You think this is how I'm going to do it
and then if you meet a significant other
then they have their
plans and you're going to kill each other.
And they're always going to be worse.
It's because
none of us are
actually a stature of monkey,
but none of us as far as I know
are in a serious committed relationship of any kind
where we're really considering anything like that.
It's just way outside my wheelhouse
the idea of committing to someone
for 18 years or whatever the fuck.
Well anyway,
I guess I'll just say
my piece on as well.
For many years
I have known that I will have
for starters, I have seven sexy daughters
to begin with.
And please feed them
by going to patreon.com
It's one of my reward tiers, I think.
Feed my seven daughters. Need to do that shit.
Aside from that,
I plan on having two more children
maybe like 10 years or so.
Charlotte and Vincent,
they're going to be two perfect children
and I'm going to raise them
to better humanity for all.
Because the thing is, nobody's talked about this
I think about things like
the movie Idiocracy a lot
about how the stupidest people breed the most
and make the most worthless swine humans
that don't deserve to live.
I have a duty to breed
and spread my perfect genes
my god-like genes around the rest of humanity
so you guys haven't even been talking about this
but I am serious about this
I need to continue my genetic legacy
because I know I'm the best
because I know that's what humanity needs
to get better, it needs what I've got
to be humanity, anti-humanist
to not reproduce
and continue this perfect thing
I've got going on over here.
I'm selfish so I'm okay with that.
That's true.
I'm fine with the intellect part
but I don't give a shit about genes or anything.
Well, you forget how much
I can fucking bench, dude.
You forget that shit.
But look, the fact that there are so many dumb
stupid swine humans is how
we're going to succeed
and take their money and they won't realize
we just need to have slaves again
what the fuck Abraham Lincoln
That'll work for a while
but I want to get to Starfleet as soon as possible
and in Starfleet you need people to have their shit together
more or less
I'm hoping for that sooner rather than later
You need to build Starfleet out of the pyramids
Out of Minecraft
Yeah, we just need to make
Minecraft real and then we'll have
fucking Starfleet like two seconds
We'll have plenty of Minecraft slave builders
That's all the children of the world
All the kids will do it, man
Yeah, that'd be nice
It would be like Indiana Jones or the Temple of Doom
except, you know, they'll be doing something
I also
like what you were saying, I also wanted to say
I really want to be a dad
There was something that's apropos about this
So today, the day we're recording this
April 1st, 2017 is the
10 year anniversary of Tangentapa Gurun Lagann's release
and that's a special day
for people like me who really care about that series
and I know I always say that Kamina
is like my favorite character
I've had a long time to think about why that is
and I know I've talked about this before
but the point is he is like
the ideal father figure to me
He's like
When I see him, I always talk about how
Kamina is like my favorite anime character ever
which is true, but the point of the show
which is what I said in my Gurun Lagann video
is that Kamina is not perfect
He is a flawed individual
He has these various flaws
that are complimented by someone like Rossiu
and those things kind of combine in Simone
making Simone more or less the perfect guy
not quite, even Simone isn't perfect
but it's about combining different factors
but when I see Kamina
when I see in him this masculine
bravado can do anything
project strength to
make the people around him stronger
this is going to get personal and possibly too deep
but those are the things that I see
myself lacking
when I see a dad like that
or a dad figure, he's not actually Simone's dad
but he serves that function
those are the things I want
and I love that
I want to be that for people
because it's something that I really value
and want to
I don't know, I want to spread that
I want to be the good dad
because I love good dads
good dads are my favorite thing in the world
I have the ability to do that
so I feel it's my obligation to do so
and I hope in 30 years from now
there's a kid making a shitty podcast
who's talking about how cool his dad was
and how he inspired him to be a cool guy
and do cool things even if that only
entailed just you know, birthing him
and then leading him to his own devices
to uh, why, what
what mean were you going to say?
I was just going to say and can like
rapy, that was part of your training right
well, of course
you're right, teaching him the proper rape techniques
as I say
every day, the only true love is between
a boy and a man, that's the goal
and you know
and yeah, I'm really fixated on the dad thing
I want to be a good dad and I
like what you were saying, I don't think about
like the woman I would have to have involved
in this at all, I am not interested
I would be repulsed
I could see myself
I mean, I hate the idea of marriage
it disgusts me, it's really a contract
that keep men locked down
to keep them from leaving, which actually does serve a practical purpose
cause like families
kid, raising children is better off
when the man is not able to leave and is forced
to stay, cause it's in men's best interest
like personally, to just go around and fuck
a million sluts and just you know, be free
but like, a family is better off
when they're kind of forced in place
so like, I get the societal logic
behind marriage that forces men to stay
but I'm pretty uncomfortable with the idea
myself, but I mean, I don't know
maybe I would do something like that
a committed relationship of some kind, to raise kids
but God, do not care
about the woman
well the thing is, I'm trying to raise
the best kids possible
given the current environment
and we don't have starfleet, we don't have any kind of that shit
the best, the best environment
you see statistically, this is a fact
the best kids in America
regardless of like, any kind of background
having a mother and a father
in like, a marriage relationship
brings you the best children, they do the best
like that is the biggest deciding factor
is it like your anti-gay marriage
discussion or what?
no, not at all, I mean, it is actually a fact
that like, mothers and fathers marry do better
statistically
the children of gay couples can be successful and good
well, no, that's not what I'm saying at all
it's more likely
I'm only talking about statistics
like, my dad is
he does a lot of
okay, I admit, I'm basing this on
what my dad has researched
because he's worked with a lot of kids
like people getting divorced and all kinds of like
well, yeah, divorce is going to lead to a fucked up kid probably
well, not just that
it sounds like you should be saying
children who have two
parents rather than mother and father
I don't know
well, but that's just not what the stats show
the children, I mean, it is a fact
that the most ideal situation
the kids who do the best
come from families that are
you know, a traditional marriage
and I don't even support traditional marriage
so don't get me wrong here, I'm not saying that I'm into it
I'm just saying that that's what the facts
are paying out
I think I need to see these stats
because it doesn't make any sense
it's entirely possible that that's because we live in an evil
patriarchy where that kind of relationship
is like, rewarded
whereas gay married couples
do worse, maybe that's totally true
and it is not true, but statistically
that is the fact of the matter
that they do the best
that was true, I would have seen those stats posted
on a lot of the
red-pilled pages that I follow on Twitter
and Facebook because I feel like that
is a stat that they'd want to brag about all the time
well
maybe I'm wrong, I admit
based on what my dad told me, maybe he was wrong
the thing about people posting stuff
is that they don't know anything
so they only post
stuff that gets posted by somebody
who does know about it and I guess nobody
has
I feel like this is undocked about territory
a little bit
it's the sort of thing
people are done
and if they see something that supports their argument
they'll repost it
none of them actually know it offhand
I didn't even mean to bring this up
you can just say divorce
not divorcing
your kids do better when you don't divorce
that's just how it is
that sounds very logical
I understand what you're saying
I say that to myself
in my brain a lot
the way you're coming from
I think it just comes down to a fact
that just like
minorities and shit are just
they aren't a lot of them
so it's harder to
get big old samples
I don't even know how the fuck
we got to this point
we have to wait until Hillary Clinton has her turn
and makes it so that legally
half of families
have to have gay parents
and then we can get the stats that we need
we need that state enforced homosexuality
as soon as possible
that's equal
we gotta have equality
we gotta have equality on this
I got my eye on you munchie
watch the fuck out
alright
real quick Nate
since you mentioned that today is April 1st
I thought it would be important if I said real quick
why is it so short
my favorite meme
we don't want to get content I do
I don't think people plan
guys this is the Kid Icarus show
we have to say if we salvage it or slaughter it
parents
love them or hate them
they're definitely the plebe
they're getting slaughtered
I give them zero rotten tomatoes out of a thousand
oh god
so as per usual
on the tpcrastinator's twitter
we said we needed some questions
no no no
I have something to say
I was going to award them a lot of dads
but I stole them all
they're all gone there's zero dads for dads
they're all gone
when there's no dads available everybody gets a zero dad score
so at Jarisbat wants to know
what are your most controversial
and unpopular anime opinions
and I brought this one up because
this is the worst possible question
oh my god
no I do want to talk about it
you're just fucking with us
I have a good answer
my controversial anime opinion
is that anime is generally boring
oh my god who gives a shit
fine let's just hear your answer monkey
what do you want to say about that
I just wanted to say that I know you anime elitist
would frown upon this opinion
and that's why I want to bring it up
it's probably because I watched it as a kid
but I have a deep
love for Naruto
and I really wish that it was easier to watch
I wish that the entire thing
was dubbed in English and that somebody would
cut out all of the filler episodes
like if there was an abridged version
that just had the important shit
I would watch the fuck out of it
I just love that show
when I graduated college
one of my friends friends that we'd hung out with
he was super big into Naruto
I used to read the manga back
in high school
and I just fell off the bandwagon because it was just so big
and he's like alright dude
I'm going to text message you over the next two weeks
an entire list of all the
episodes you have to watch to skip all the filler
so you can get caught up
I love that he talks like that
he was a fan
the game reviewer
top number one
and he did he gave me this huge fuck
I don't have it anymore I wish I did
was it like a hundred
he's just like you can skip like
20 episodes here, 40 episodes here
I'm just like Jesus Christ
it was funny because I didn't miss a beat
it totally just flowed and I was like this is ridiculous
I think there's some subreddit where they're compiling
all the main episodes
and they're cutting out the filler
so if somebody can like remind me what that is
I think I might waste some time watching Naruto
you know there's this thing called one pace
I remember I mentioned it a long time ago
but there's this one pace
it's exactly what it sounds like
it's one piece only they cut out
all the bullshit from every episode and speed it up
and only leave parts that are decent
it's like each episode is now two minutes long
they're like maybe 15, 15 to 20
a lot of stuff generally happens
but one piece anime is garbage
and it's such long pans all the time
it's terrible they fix all that shit
and leave only the important stuff
that's like back in the day they had this thing
all fight no filler, did you ever see those
way back in early YouTube
spliced together all the big fight scenes
from like Dragon Ball and stuff
that's funny because I don't even care about fight scenes
I would rather see like okay they start fighting
and immediately jump to the conclusion
because I do not care about the actual fighting that happens
the reason I bring it up because they had the Goku vs Frieza fight
it was like 16 hours long
and when he said the planet would blow up
in 5 minutes there was like another 7 hours
oh yeah
that's pretty fun
that's my favorite
people exaggerate that
after he says that
it was hours of content
after he says the planet will blow up in 5 minutes
7 hours though
it was something like 7 hours
it was a good like
third to half of the fight
was after he destroyed
just tries to destroy the planet
there's nobody else really
have a controversial anime
opinion I thought it was actually a good question
but you don't have to fucking
kill yourself I like you
don't kill yourself
I have a controversial anime opinion
that's kind of relevant to the last anime review
yeah fuck you Nate trying to shit on that question
we all like it
go on
Dom what do you got
I think that the original full battle is way better than brotherhood
I thought brotherhood was gay
and I hated it
what the fuck
have you completed both
can you tell me why
without using buzzwords
like it was gay
yes well the main problem
that I had with brotherhood
was that
it felt very kind of like
by the books one of the things I was really interested in
yeah it was by the book that's why it's better
because it was based off the book
well no because like the thing
I guess the thing that I was really interested in
with the original full battle
is what they did with the homunculi
and how they wanted to be human as well
because it was an interesting way to like
foil what Ed and Howard were chasing
the entire time because they wanted to be human
and they couldn't understand
why the homunculi wanted to be human
because they'd be like so much weaker
when the fact of the matter is like
their quest for being human would inherently weaken them as well
so it's the protagonist and antagonist
basically chasing the same thing
and the way that they kind of clashed ideologically
and couldn't kind of see past each other's differences
even though inherently they wanted the same thing
I thought that was a really interesting dynamic
that's a pretty cool point
I'm just like we just want to kill people
these are just flat boring typical show
no no no no no no
greed in full metal alchemist brotherhood
is the best fucking character of any show I've ever seen
he's like the same in both though
he's still a great character
no he's not the same in brotherhood
but greed's the best out of both of them in both interpretations
and greed I would give greed more credit
than really anybody else
but the majority of them
I really like to fact how like
my controversial opinion
full metal alchemist brotherhood
or full metal alchemist and I don't plan to
because there's I don't care
that's okay that's fine don't worry about it
they're not that good
my controversial version of this
also the Aryan race
this I'm going to keep talking over you
oh you told me
how to talk over people
you're going to have a puff in if you don't
and I won't respect your
ability to talk
okay so what's your anime
my anime
is that I would like to watch more
but they're too long
and I think
some of them are good
but I've only watched like 7 and I don't really intend
to watch anymore dude why would you say that
that's too controversial for the show that's too controversial
the people can't handle that kind of opinion
too controversial this question
sucks oh god damn it
I uh
do I have a fucking controversial no I don't have any
and the Kirby anime is legitimately
better than like
3 of the 7 anime I've seen
that's probably true
okay Nate let's see you pick a good question
you piece of shit
okay here's a real
question that's important to everyone
okay at Eddie the Rack
why is Nate so amazing
yeah that's right
okay so he's asking for advice
why is Nate so good at picking questions
it's how to deal
with a family member who is a shitty
commenter what do you do
when you're faced with that ultimate dilemma
when you have to put them down like a dog
just block them and ban them from your life
you gotta put them down
ban them from your life
ban them from their life with a fucking 9mm
no no just channel ban them from your life
what does that mean
it means to act
it means to act aloof and just to not
acknowledge them even when they say hello
exactly right to you
well
I have the fortunate
ability or thing
of not having any shitty commenters
in my direct family
in my extended family they're abundant
however my direct uncle
is literally not a joke
like a memester on poll
and talks to me about Pepe
and how cool he is whenever we meet
that's not a fucking joke
that's awesome
how old is this guy
I'm just curious how old is this guy
40 is like 6
what the fuck
actually no he's 52 actually
I didn't know anybody over 40 knew what Pepe was
other than like an alt right
thing
Hillary's already put down the alt right
weren't you gonna come out against Pepe
that's what we need
she fucking did
the anti defamation league came out against Pepe
I want Hillary to say
Pepe has got to go
as an alt right
fucking avatar
well I don't think that was her specific
I read articles on
brightbart.com
okay I just feel like these two things
are connected to the anti defamation
and you know what they say about brightbart
he's pretty bright
and he's bright
okay Nate good job on that great question
what else do we got
okay here's one
where'd that go oh here we go
there's a munchie the people want to know
at Wyatt word weaver is asking
what are the rest
of the tism stones they need to know for the
procrastopedia page what are the tism stones
we need the names
last I checked all of them are there
what the fuck would this guy ask
this question why what are you doing
yeah yeah what what the fuck
you embarrassed me on my own fucking
he's just a fake fucking fan dude
what the fuck what he's doing what he's doing
is he's asking about like the rumored
like fools gold tism
circulating they don't actually have power
but they trick under tailors
all across the world into thinking that
they're pretty good
it's the feminism stone
it's probably extended canon and awful
not canon guys that's not canon
not fucking canon
the only tism stones are
fucking autism sexism racism
and the other ones that I forgot
well the autism
appears when you summon the other six
are together right there's seven total
there's seven total okay so if there's seven
on the page you're fucking done go pack it in
kill yourself um okay
can I ask a real question now or what
yeah go ahead okay at tales
of nerdy I want to know
do you ever worry that your controversial
language I think you know what I mean
wink wink could hinder your
YouTube or IRL
careers I don't know what the fuck this nigger's talking
about
hinder an IRL career
well you know both are possible
especially for me I've got a real job
and I do not know
how it would be taken
if these things were to be
shown to the people around the office
I don't know like I feel like I'm
pretty much not guilty of doing
anything wrong I feel like it's just a bunch of
fucking jokes that we're telling online and that would be
my defense it's comedy so relax
hopefully it wouldn't be that big a deal
you know what I've thought
about this like what would happen if
like someone like me you got like
two million subscribers and I'm one of
those big YouTubers but I still go
on this show and I say nigger
sometimes and it's like oh people can
look up the fact that I've said this thing
and then somebody might say you know
try to try to cause a big stink and say
this guy hypocrite said
this what a hypocrite
every single like
news thing would say that and that's
like funny but
epic joke epic joke I just I don't
worry about that at all because like those people
aren't my audience if you give a shit
about the thing is like fuck you the thing is
I think about that like yeah it doesn't
matter how big I'll get it won't
you know really affect me but it
I don't know well I mean
look at PewDiePie at such a huge
PewDiePie and JonTron are doing just fine so
I know he's doing fine but
there has been a massive like outcry
against the guy that was completely unjustified
and even if he's totally financially
secure the fact that there were so many
people online literally attacking them
and well you know cyberbullying the man
or whatever like that's that's not good
nobody wants that and they're like that's not cool
but yeah like
they're they're they're
retarded I mean in indirectly
like so much for the
PewDiePie
so much for the taller and left
there it is there it is
indirectly PewDiePie being like
labeled as a fascist Nazi
and being like the top youtube guy
has made a lot of like companies
pull their adsense revenue
from youtube they don't want to be associated with youtube anymore
and now youtube is losing money
and now monetization
across the board is just going down
so it's generally
like it's pretty gay
that's the dumbest shit I've ever heard
that companies
don't want to put their ads on youtube videos
because of offensive content
are they gonna fucking pull their ads off
of family guy and adult swim now
fucking idiots
well actually I mean companies do decide
what they want their commercials to air on
the conspiracy right now
is they're just trying to like turn youtube into tv
so they're trying to get rid of like
not offensive content but just like
anybody because like the whole thing
I don't know how much you buy into this but like I watch too much youtube
about dumb things where people are just saying
well the whole thing is it's a conspiracy
because they're mad at PewDiePie
and shit because they have more reach than like
all the mainstream like entertainment channels
like PewDiePie
legit gets more views
and like viewership and then like
HBO and like CNN
just regular tv so they're just like
because youtube just came out with youtube tv
I don't know if you heard about that but like they're gonna do a $35 a month
cable subscription
thing through youtube
so they're just like oh like the same
day they did that they started like trying to
shut down like all these platforms like this
and then like within a week like every single
like news
like article has come out saying like oh like
youtube is awful and authoritarian
and gross and we need to change it so it's just like
all this just kind of lining up
they're trying to like subtly influence it and change all this crap
yeah I think it's definitely happening
so the thing is
it's gonna happen regardless
the solace is like oh well
even if youtube doesn't pay us
we'll still have patreon but then
at what point will patreon be associated
they've taken out some fucking
yeah like patreon is like
oh we're now associated with people
who make like
like fascist content we gotta
we gotta stop letting them get money
and even if patreon allowed that shit
like the things like the giant outcry against
pewdiepie like if pewdiepie had a patreon
imagine the cut he would have suffered just from
people getting upset it would have been
something and you know he's running a business
so I he's probably got you know some
level he needs to keep me I mean maybe
pewdiepie is maybe not the best example but like someone who's more
riding the line like
like fucking dark side fill is like
I don't like the guy but like he's
he's on that line where he's barely
getting by financially if some
scandal were to emerge about like he said the word nigger
and you know like people got
really upset even though these things feel
extremely artificially inflated like if you made
a fucking joke you know whatever
people got mad at him for it like he'd be done
if his patreon shit got cut like his
career would be over he'd have to go work
at McDonald's if McDonald's would even hire him
knowing that this is a man who once said
nigger in his life can we even hire such a guy
let's just let him die in the streets like
here's what you're not considering Nate
is that people who donate to
patreons are typically people with
jobs and the type of
people who get offended by
mean jokes on the internet are
typically very liberal and those people
don't have jobs so I don't think
patreon is gonna be that big of an issue
nobody has a job
gets easily offended by things
let me ask you this
liberal jobless fuck
all I'm hearing is that very soon there's going to
be real competition for youtube
and real competition for patreon
some companies
are cutting out advertising
I guess I'll make a real
better website that supports free speech
that sounds pretty good
it's like a stupid piece of shit
it's funny we're talking about this because I was playing
I'm doing a whole podcast and did you about this next week
but the whole thing I think right now is
like we're kind of having a shift back
I think this whole model
that we've kind of been riding this high is kind of starting
to collapse where it's just like
everything has become so simple
it's just like oh I can just make a
free channel on youtube and reach
like millions and millions of people
and I'll get money and it's so easy for me
as a creator to just make a platform
and as a viewer I go to
like three websites and everything on the fucking
internet basically is right there
and I just think because it's becoming
so centralized and like big business
getting into it it's going to start becoming more
homogenized and clean like traditional media
and so everything that's kind of made
these platforms interesting is going to start to
kind of collapse under that like corporate
weight and then and
people are calling like oh we need an alternative
we're going to go to vid.me and like gab.ai
instead of twitter and and all that
shit but the problem is
like for
something like youtube to work
you have to be a corporation like youtube
just the amount of
money it would take to host all this videos on youtube
is fucking stupidly
like unimaginably large
so like it's not like you can say
they have server farms across the world
to support all this shit you know
and that's but that costs money and like
so you're like of course oh I want to go to
vid.me they can be the new youtube but
you're going to put them in exactly the same situation
youtube's in right now so they're going to need
money from advertisers so the advertisers are going to
come in and put down the same fucking
regulations so what the solution
I think is is that everyone
just need to stop being a little bitch and be like
fuck I'm going to have to make my own website
I'm going to have to try hard like fucking like
get an audience like the old fashioned
way because I have to have control over everything
if I want this freedom or have to
toe the line and just not be who
I actually want to be and make safe stuff
and people are going to have to make that choice
and hopefully our general internet
rights will remain where they are who knows
if that's going to last you know things are
ebbing away little by little
yeah I mean to me that
that is bad
I mean to me when people say people are coming
out and be like the internet's under attack
and like okay like yes you've lost
you know you've lost
privacy yes this is not actually an attack
specifically on your what you can do
online just you know got to be aware of
that shit I but I definitely feel like it
steps towards that kind of thing that I do
not want and here's another little
conspiratorial thing for the future so
like just like I was like we were saying before
like patreon you know would shut down
accounts of people who aren't acceptable youtube could kick people
and what happened but you were saying
that like but individual people
can still give money to patreons
and like because those people
are you know hard-working people who aren't offended
easily by shit they're not you know
libcucks it's not a problem but what
happens when the businesses that employ
those people are able to find out
what pay like which patreons
they their employees give money to
and then fire them because they're giving
money to the wrong people with wrong ideas
and wrong think I wonder when we're
going to get to that point hopefully never
just something I think about and
if we're going down the road we're going
it's only a matter of time like yep
that's the whole point like this authoritarian
kind of imagine getting fired
because you were like a patron of
John Tron who is now a quote unquote
racist and you know I
that's I don't even think that's a stretch
I think I think that's possible to happen
today it's possible
man it's possible
my controversial opinion is that everything
will be fine
I'm a worrier
so I like I think about these things
and I do not find it easy to sit back
and not worry about these things
now at the risk of sounding like
some weird retarded person
I do have a quick devil's
advocate question
you always sound like that monkey
everybody's concerned that
your ISPN is going to
sell your browser history
to companies
so that they can more directly advertise
to you and I get the privacy
angle of it but when it comes to
targeted advertisements
I don't see how that's a bad thing
because personally if all the advertisements
I saw were things that I actually
care about I think that would be
a better internet experience for me
than seeing fucking advertisements
for shit that I would never buy ever
well you know I'm with you on that
the thing with like
the way it works at the moment is that
it bases it off
of what you've looked at
and what you bought already
and then they try to sell you more of that
and it doesn't
sometimes just doesn't make any sense
like if you buy a DVD
of something
and then now Amazon is recommending you
the same DVD but
of a different type
I bought it already
there's no point
my biggest problem
I'm not a huge
I don't think people should be having
all this access to my personal
data I'm not a huge fan of that
but I'm not freaking out like a ton
of other people are because they're already doing it
and there's really no way to get around it
like if you're using your phone
your network provider has been mining
your phone for data for years
you're using Windows 10 it's mining all your data
you're using Chrome it's mining all your data
there's no way to get around that
I don't mind that so much as long as it's
anonymized and that it's used
for purposes that's useful
I know a lot of people are getting up
and arms over
if you use an Android phone Google now
Google monitors
everything you're doing on your phone but it serves you
stuff from the internet that's interesting
and it'll look through your email
I love Google now for when I go on flights
because it'll go into
my email it'll find the flights that I've done
and I'll have to pull up the itinerary
of me having to do shit
so when I go to the fucking
to pull my data
to have a tangible impact
on my life in a good way
as long as it's anonymized
and you're not trying to keep tabs on me
that's fine
what I kind of get pissed off about
is that these companies
like Verizon and AT&T and them
are investing
tons of money in lobbying
so they can get access to all this data
so all that tells me is that this data
is worth fucking
millions if not
billions of dollars
and what pisses me off is that
that means that everything I do
on the internet inherently has value
and I'm not seeing any of that
if you're going to make all of this money
that's taking all this time
and you're fighting tooth and nail for almost a decade now
to get this data it's insanely valuable
if you're going to get your way eventually
and make billions of dollars
I want a trickle down of that
I want my internet's cost
to fucking plummet
I don't want to pay as much as I'm doing
because if you're like literally tripling your income
off of just being an ISP
like fuck you you don't need to keep charging me
like $100 a month drop it down to like $50
companies tweaking legislation
purely for profit
circumvents the entire like
economic basis of capitalism
where you're supposed to give and then receive
like there's supposed to be a mutual gain
when through an exchange of goods
but just tweaking laws to better
advantage what you're trying to do
doesn't engage in that
and also rewards like
purely corporate profit driving
efforts and does not reward
like actual trying to improve
to give people something more of what they want
which is what it's all about
if it's not doing that it's not helping the system
you're just forming an oligarchy
essentially you're giving these corporations
like governmental authority
to bring this
sort of back to the whole parents thing
I think like I was saying
kids are gonna grow up
and they're gonna be like
in a world that I don't understand
but I'm gonna have to deal with it
it's probably gonna be like the death of privacy
like the next few generations
they're just gonna not know what it means
to have privacy
and I'm just gonna have to deal with the fact
that they're living in that world now
and even though I don't like it
that's just how it's gonna be
have you guys seen that black mirror episode
about the people on bicycles
who are forced to
they're forced to watch ads
and if you look away
you're like shocked
but they live in a society
where everyone rides bikes to generate energy
to fuel everything
and you earn a little currency
as you ride and you can buy
shit that's advertised to you all the time
I'm not gonna go into it
but it's a whole terrifying dystopia
of nightmare where no one is
you're never free
you're putting these little cubicles your whole life
you just treat it like a little automaton
which is kind of how I view people
but still
doesn't look very comfortable in the future
everyone's an automaton
Starfleet would never say that
that's being more treating people worse
than Starfleet does
which I fully admit to doing
we solved the future
we solved internet privacy
and capitalism
we fixed it all
we also talked about dads
if you care about any of this
it's your duty to become a politician
and change things
if you don't do that then you don't care enough
I agree
well, not everybody can be a politician
but whatever
people who want to be politicians
the people who want to be politicians
shouldn't be
except for Hillary
because it's her time
obviously
and with that
fucking goodbye
that was episode 51 of the
Procrastinator's podcast
and make sure you're following us
and who was the weeb
subscribe to Mumkey Jones
Mumkey Jones was definitely the weeb
because he brought up a shitty anime question
who was the red pill
and who was the blue pill
but now gamers
that and get behind
and make sure you follow us at tpcrastinators
on twitter, send us questions on saturday
when we're usually doing recording
and we'll see you later everybody
goodbye
so you just got a breathing like this hippo
I'm supposed to be working right now
I'm supposed to
be working
right now
I'm supposed to be working right now
but I'm not working
I'm doing nothing
my dick
I'm jerking
myself
I'm sucking
I am an asshole
I am a stupid
I've got a deadline
don't want to do it
what the hell is wrong with me