Welcome, welcome, welcome, one and all to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm the best guy ever.
Dun-nun-nun-nun-nun-nun-nun. We've got Tom Oliver.
Hello.
Gibbontake.
Radcon 4.
Oh no, he didn't. His best say's he spilled the beans.
What do you mean Radcon 4?
Well, what what we're it all started back in the summer of 86 talking about we're doing we're making it happen
We're making right for it's gonna be a real
We're gonna do it Radcon for real in March, right? Yeah, right come on you. Yeah. Yes
Yeah, I mean fuck it present time of recording a lot of the in like this very
Specifics are not ironed out, but we are planning to do it in March
hopefully in Virginia and
It's gonna be based around the idea of like spring break
Students still where where the PCP University students and we're on spring bake a break in like a beach
Spring bake may know what I'm saying, bro. We have the we have the house picked out or we have a house tentatively picked out
Yeah, and let's let's sell it. It's a it's like a beach
Yes, on the beautiful god. What if we don't I mean, I hope we get it. So yeah, we picked out. Yeah, it's great
It's on the fucking beach. It's a beautiful. I found it. I am responsible. I saw the listing and was like hey nice value
It's actually cheaper than the last place. Yeah, and on the fucking beach, which makes me go. Yeah
I'm surprised because more of us live in Boston
So I thought that we should do it here because we would save on travel costs, which is true
but yeah, yeah, but
Rental costs are lower in Virginia. So I kind of think it doesn't make much difference and it probably evens out and
Honestly, I want to go on a trip. I want to go on vacation. Yeah
Yeah, I'm gonna get on the plane and make us my summer getaway to sunny Virginia Beach
Tropical paradise
But yeah, but anyway, yeah, let's talk about talk about like little hints little hint
Oh, let's can we say the name the name we have in general? We have well
We're not 100% settled on it. Are we it's definitely rad corn for something rad corn for paradise or red corn for paradise
We were looking at the beach house and we thought that like a tropical getaway paradise
The theme would be pretty funny in it's a tropical paradise getaway
But also we have to be in school because we're bad children who didn't
Delinquents and we have to listen to a bunch of really great lectures
But also it's Virginia in March and the beach will be miserable and the water will be ice cold and we will probably suffer a lot
Here's the funniest part is that we're thinking of maybe doing a sexy swimsuit calendar
Like on the beach of all of us. Yep. These were these were all ideas
These are all ideas. We were tossing around that there might be a stretch goal for the Kickstarter
The calendar is a great idea
for only for only the highest and most dedicated donors
Because I don't want anyone to fucking see that shit
It's gonna be good. I'm gonna buy a wig. I'm gonna buy a wig and I'm just gonna be an anime girl. Oh
That's a good idea. I don't want to oversell it
But just picture all of us and your favorite anime swimsuit
I already have the fucking Ryuko Matoi like thing that I wore on that one time
True, but that's not a swimsuit. That's it. Well, you know, it's it's a school suit. It's it's it's it's got a skirt, you know
It sounds good as opposed to the Radcon 3 arena
We're all like our weaponry with our guns instead sexy pin-up girls. I guess I guess I better
I guess I better do stick to keto real hard so I can have my beach body ready. Oh, yeah, you better fuck
Yeah, you better you want to have like a like a
Comeback from fat Ben the last time
Yeah, I mean
Unironically for ever since Radcon 2 or 3 I have been thinking God, I can't look like that
For I can't do it
It's unacceptable on that. Yeah, true. There's been a transformation. I can I can I can always succeed more
True you can always be thin. I was yes. Look, you can always be better. Mmm. So until you're in the Skeleton War
You can always be
So
The lectures, right? Yeah, the lectures are to my thinking the thing that people I mean, they're the things that I mean for me
They're my most popular content. I think same. I think that's true across. Okay. I didn't know if it was true across the board
But yeah, I'm not surprised people love the lectures. So me personally. I'm double. I'm gonna do at least to I'll do at least
I'll do more if I can stomach it and if anyone anyone will stand for me to do so
I'll do them all
And I thought that like I thought it would be funny. I thought it would be funny if we
Actually had I've said this to you guys but for the audience
I thought it'd be funny if we actually had like a class itinerary
That we like like we get there and we've got it all figured out like oh on Monday
Professor fucking best man is doing a lecture on
Dogs in the media and and and at 6 p.m. Hippo's mates are running the
Students are doing the lectures hippos doing one on birds under the sea and I
Mean, I think we can hint or like just like show what the lectures are gonna be about right? Yeah, I mean, I don't mind
I'm sure everyone knows I've been saying it forever. I'm gonna do the Chris follow Chris Chan follow-up
I also want to do one on Jennifer Diane writes
And her comics because I think those are neat and I've just got I discovered sort of an arc
I discovered sort of like a weird like sort of a weird like history arc that ties in with the thing that she's best known for
Which is the coca-ro-wish comic
Right and how that it's all part of a broader story that I think is kind of neat
So yeah, those two and maybe others. I don't know. I know I talked in the past about maybe doing a
Df and Strix but like yeah, and I think that would be funny
But what sucks about that is that I would have to watch like fucking thousands of hours of like
D&D podcasts, and I just don't know if it's worth it
Yeah, that's a big oof. Yeah, it's not a good look in 2019
Wait fuck it's 2020
Even worse
This look is getting more and more yikes by the second
I'm doing it. I'll probably do exactly one lecture
And I'll just say it's relevant to the setting
I guess we'll say where we're at and I'm thinking of things as I can do
Ah, sand. You're gonna talk about how it's Russian course
Do we know what it is? Have you told us?
I'm sure I have. I'm sure and I think I might even said it publicly, but
Because I forget. You know with the ocean in the background with the sandy shore on this
Well, you know it might be relevant. We'll see. Kingdom Hearts
Yeah, that is Kingdom Hearts relevant. The first level of Kingdom Hearts
I guess I could always I was thinking of doing like a Kingdom Hearts like two
I guess I could do that, but there's not that there's only one game effectively worth of story
And like I don't know it could do like a mini lecture that's like 30 minutes long
It makes that I think it makes worth it. I think it's where I think it makes sense
I mean like you did this big you did this big Kingdom Hearts lecture. It got really popular
And now there's a new game. It's like the final game in the series is wrap wraps it up. There's new context
Why not do I mean you've already done follow-up videos to the lecture. Yeah, maybe it's true
Maybe it should just be a follow-up rather than lecture number two like it's like it's like a
Like a supplementary class. Yeah extra credit extra credit. Yeah, not extra credits like the actual my favorite YouTube channel
No, yeah, no, not them they made video that was cringe and I saw people say that it was cringe
It's it's true live it down. It's it's not it's not wrong. Well, I'll I'll keep you nice post
Well, we'll see but I mean the Kickstarter from the time of when this comes out
We're hoping the Kickstarter is like up and running like within a week of when you hear this. So
Maybe keep your fucking wallets open boys. That's
Times of the essence considering the time is kind of of the essence because we want to do it over over spring break
Which is I'll just give you the dates. I believe it's March 6 to 13th is
Munchy spring break. So it's framed around that with like the weekends or whatever. Oh shit
I just realized on February like the the PCP dating sim will be out. Oh Valentine's Day. That's true
We created PCP dating sim scenes in real life guys. We could all like I'm sure there'll be like a live stream
Set that we could we could just play the game. We could play that. Oh my god
As the PCP. Oh my god, that's a great idea. That's that's a real good
It's gonna be there's gonna be another role rumble if we can get that working again. Hopefully we can we it's a it's a necessity
It's a tradition. Yeah, so we he's gonna be video games and anime, you know your things you're like
Fuck yeah, fuck wait. What's it gonna say? Oh? Oh?
Let's discuss the fact that everything costs way more than we thought last time and we lost
Even though we hit all our stretch goals. We ended up losing money
that we did
That okay, primarily it was because of the because all of you motherfuckers live
Internationally and destroyed us with a thousand dollars in shipping costs that we did not see they're even worse than immigrants
They're just plain foreigners. They couldn't and that's just one of these goddamn foreigners just gonna emigrate to my goddamn country
It's already so easy how much easier can we make it for you to hop the border? Jesus Christ
We're giving you free shit and everything. Just come over here. Take my fucking job. Just save me the goddamn postage
Okay, so let us so so last time we asked for five thousand eight hundred dollars for rad con three
Oh sweet as we broke it down understood it this time, okay, because because some unnamed unmentionable
bureaucratic fools were in charge of rad con twos
Finances and whatnot not a godlike mathematical machine such as yours truly who documented every expense and whatnot
We have the facts and the she showed me the spreadsheet. It's a nightmare. I can't understand it
Yeah, it was developed that that spreadsheet was developed for the very specific purpose of just identifying who was owed what money
So it's not optimized for just I didn't like fucking counting up all the expenses
I should say not sir
Okay, okay, but that being said
Now that we actually know what like ten days in a place having rad con
We know what it costs and shall I base how shall I just say the number shall I just say what we're looking for
Fucking go for it. Yeah, all right with all the expenses
We all lost money with when accounting for flight food for all this stuff
So we have we've pretty much reverse engineered
How much we need to just break even to get like six or seven of us based on like how much things cost last time
That's right, including like food if we just want to not lose any money
Yeah, we would ask for
Considering like the 10% fee that Kickstarter asked for we're gonna ask for right about ten thousand dollars
That's how much it costs, you know to make the whole thing happen. You know, maybe we don't
Maybe we shouldn't include food costs. Maybe maybe that's not necessary
Like we have to eat
I think it was like a couple hundred for the whole we're talking about a couple hundred for the whole 10
It's like ten days of just get a giant bag of rice for like ten dollars. That's all we'll eat
That's not keto. No, it's not well. Well, listen, this is how I'm thinking about it
Oh, I'm thinking about it overall the way that we did it last time
We yeah, we just way undervalued everything and of course that this number is including like making stretch goals
Shipping them out, which is like a thousand dollars just by itself to do that shit
And you know, we've got to incorporate all those into it
Like we can do things like not worry about like the food costs and whatnot
But all that means is that we're just putting the cost of this time on like us as individuals and look that's fine
Well, if you want to like pay for things out of our own pocket, that's okay
I'm just saying I'm just saying that we would be buying food whether we were at Radcon or not
I mean, that is true that that is true
You're not wrong about that and so I mean maybe what I would have that's like a that's like a quibble
That's like a pretty I mean like even if we took food out we'd be charging like
9,500
It's not it's not like a deal breaker break huge difference and I mean when we analyze it
I mean a lot of us spent tons of time after Radcon 3 working on extensive
Complicated editing projects and the man hours involved in those alone. Oh, okay, let me let me let me talk
Let me talk about that so um
Yeah, ten ten paces and draw right was a massively complicated video to edit
I mean by my state it was it was by far the most complicated video. I've ever edited it took me like
Several months working on it on and off. It was a nightmare
And I didn't make any money off of it
Like like that was that was just like that was like probably like
60 or 70 hours of like totally unpaid labor and I will not do it again
Yes, and the same with t-bat resurrection was great. I'm glad it exists, but that arc is closed
I'm not doing that again at least not for free if someone paid me. That's a different story
You know I would really like there to be like a ten paces and draw a stretch goal so that I would yeah
Yeah, that's what like I would I'm not saying I would never edit it again, but I will not do it for free
I'm sorry. I don't I don't think that much work for for free is like reasonable
So I don't feel like I don't feel like it's unreasonable for me to say I would need a budget
Allotment to put that amount of work in
Yeah, I mean I would like to do something with ten paces to draw because now that like
We could probably plan it out better and like we could do it better
And and like you actually screen record so like we could have footage of the drawings coming together and stuff like that
Because like munch is gonna have an iPad. I have an iPad. I have another tablet computer
So like we'd have we'd have abilities to do things and we could I really like ten paces and draw
I feel like the audience response was
I don't know did people like positive but not explosive hot like they like some people liked it and some people didn't give a shit
So like, you know, it had its it had its fans
I mean lectures are the meat and potatoes of Radco, you know, if you're gonna probably be doing a lot of that's
That's where my focus is that but I mean, I still want to be I do want to be uploading like, you know, just stupid
Vlogs and just like of course bullshit. Yeah, I mean, I I think we've discovered the perfect formula
In terms of being in a place the perfect formula is
Getting a place just like Rad country a big beautiful house that we can do stuff
And there's plenty of rooms to create things and goof around and whatever do whatever the fuck we want as late as we want and
We're all there to work for like a dedicated period of time
there is as few distractions as possible and
And we just put ourselves in just a creative mode and we get to see our friends for you know, a good 10 days
It's really it's the best environment to do it how valuable having the house the arena
For last for icon. It was so good. It allowed so many things happen simultaneously
Yeah, yeah, we were talking about like we were talking about saving money by doing it at Digi's place
But like it's yeah, it's wouldn't be that it's not it's theoretically possible
But it would be I say terrible we would be crammed in there
There would be no free space like the thing about the house that we rented was like they had the like at night
Like the basement was empty you could go
Yeah, like like at any given time you could go and like anyone could go somewhere and do something themselves and not bother another person
I mean that was never happened to paint the picture because like you Nate you and
Give we're downstairs recording pottycast and then we were upstairs running streams pretty much constantly
And then while the stream was going on I think at some point we were recording something in the kitchen as well
So there was just there were like three things going on at once just because of that space was there
It was just and then like like ben was saying the basement being available like the whole mining at night thing happened with those two or three videos
Right, right would not have happened without it
So it was just it was just so much stuff that happened at radcon 3 just because the space allowed them to all
Gile at the same time god
Yes, I guess we should mention who is
Definitely coming to this if yes sure sure so it's all four of us
And digi and munchie
Anyone else and victor as camera and victor of course victor will be there
Uh getting the the perfect shots the succulent visuals victor victor and his camera are such assets to uh to radcon
I mean if not for the lectures as well as other stuff
If anything, I wish we had another camera man, but hey, what can you do one's uh one's pretty uh two camera man
Would make such a difference for like, um
For something like 10 paces 10 paces. Yeah. Yeah
You you were always uh, uh, what's the word uh being saying how unfortunate was you didn't have more b rolled
No, uh, honestly like yeah without b roll it almost
It really handicapped it
Yeah, yeah, um, you can't do those like those uh what do they call it the fucking like those uh fear factors
Shots of like where someone's lecturing like I hit a really tough time
And they do that like the close soon with a dun dun unlike a totally neutral face right a participant
You know create the narrative. Yeah, that's the good shit. I mean, I wonder if we could get
Someone to I mean does victor only have one camera?
Would he only be and could we get someone to like do b roll for just like one day?
Maybe let's just say we're doing 10 bases and draw just an example
Maybe one of I mean, I probably wouldn't be in it. I mean, I maybe could be a judging. I don't fucking know
But like I could I'm not I'm no cameraman
But maybe one of us like could do that role of trying to get b roll footage while it's going on
I don't know if he has a second camera, but if he did something to think about I suppose
Yeah, and because victor doesn't live far away. We've got access to his uh, oh, yeah
He must he must have more like like at his since his house will be there
Maybe I don't even trust any of us with the camera though. I mean those are expensive pieces of equipment
I mean since we'll be maybe
Like maybe like maybe like hope maybe hope could do it
Maybe hope could carry a second camera or may or someone. I don't know just get someone just for just for that one
Just for that one event
Yeah, victor's sick like billion-dollar camera and then all the b roll is just shot on an iphone handycam or webcam
On my iphone
Unregistered hypercam to converted compressed
We could like sell a tape like in the wrong aspect ratio. It's like vertical
Yeah, we could sell a tape like a gopro to the ceiling and it can act like security cam footage
Oh, that's true. Honestly. Honestly. Yes. I want that
Hey, do you guys all still have your go pros? I do. No wait, that's unironically a great idea
Okay, yes, please and I'll put and I'll make it like black and green and make it look like night camera footage, right?
And I'll make it look like
The
It'll be like
Yeah, just all over the house. They're just live streaming constantly
I definitely want to film like a lot of stupid vlogs
Wandering around on the beach, perhaps drunk, perhaps high and attacking the ocean
Oh, I want to spend time with I love the beach so much. I was saying it's gonna be cold. It's gonna be
I'm prepared. I'm prepared
Uh, I I was saying that I'm sure that at least one night of rad con. I will get
plastered
Uh, and you mind you must promise to turn the cameras off
We all film it, but wait, there's no promises. There's no promises that it will or will not go online
If it gets funny enough if it gets too embarrassing, you're I'll I will swear a blood oath against you
Uh, it'll be worth it. Okay, understandable. All right. Hey speaking of endorsements. This is unrelated, but I just got a message from
Uh, the devu who said very quality shovel night video and he said quote just doing based chad king things is his favorite line
Thanks devu
Appreciate that. All right unrelated
I call that an endorsement of rad con for if ever there was one. Oh, yeah, dude. Oh, yeah
There's gonna be probably content recorded there. Oh, yeah, probably all our fucking weirdo goofy retarded shows will be featured
They could be if I can chibi barkers. There's definitely gonna be you know, guys
I'm just putting it out there. I'm just telling you right now
$15,000 stretch goal. We get jeff through in the building guys
10 late out 10 late is in the building people. Please. It's happening. Come on. Come on. Let's go. Please. Can we
Where does he live?
Uh, Canada like Vancouver
Fuck yeah, all candidacies in the same city. Okay. Well, I'll get him a horse. I don't know
Also, I lied, but maybe we could ask him anyway. That'd be funny. That would be epic. Uh, how sick would that be?
I'll ask him. Pretty great
Dude, what if jeff through comes down to do a lecture like if he has an interesting topic that might actually be cool
If he wants to I'd say he's welcome. I mean, yeah
Absolutely, I suspect there may be some personnel differences between some of the members of the show
No, that'd be so great. We we bring in we bring in jeff through as the exchange student who comes in mid-arp to shake everything up
Damn
That's some good stuff. That's some good stuff. See it's like he it's season two and he's he's the poochie
He's the poochie character they introduce and then and then near the end we get monkey in to shoot the school
Yes
Yeah
That's uh, that's the meme. Oh, oh, this could be this is how jeff gets killed off in the arc. He takes the bullet for digi
They have a beautiful healing moment. And then uh, god, then he's written out of the story. This is the best fanfic ever
Damn, that's good stuff. That's good stuff. The pathos
Yeah, these are all great ideas guys. You're definitely gonna see all this. Yeah, this is all
Absolutely confirmed true no lies at all
That should be the tagline. No, we're definitely actually doing this
Hashtag no lies
project
Fucking a
Well, I'm so I'm super fucking excited though. I cannot wait and I it's it's a fucking travesty and and frankly
It's unbelievable to me that it's been two years
It doesn't it doesn't feel like it in a way
It doesn't feel like it at all and also it's like objectively just a huge mistake
It should not have it should not have been two years since the last just for the record folks
If everything goes ahead as planned, it would have been literally exactly two years
It will be on like march like 14th or whatever was when radcon three happened
It will be on march 14th. We'll be like one of the last days or whatever of this radcon for two years later
Yeah, that was that was a big oof. That was a big mistake. Uh, but uh, hopefully my god
It's pretty I was I was still in my 20s. I was still in my 20s when we had radcon three
Holy shit ending my 20s
With radcon three. I you know, I think a large part of it. I'll say this to defend us slightly was
I mean
t-bat resurrection took a full year to be finished because we had so many other things competing for time and stuff
And if I made my number, right, could I got it done first? I guess but I had fucking shit to do so, you know
Yeah, something like that again, like you can't do that unless it's so it's so much work
Well, let's make another stretch go ben $99,000. We make t-bat resurrection too. No, it's back, baby
t-bat t-bat resurrection
90 that's right. We're going all the way up. You got
Like fucking studio first first. There was t-bap resurrection now. There's t-bap
Ascension where you send back into pony heaven
That does sound good for season five, baby for for gen five. I mean phantom horn phantom horn has to conclude his arc in
New los angeles city
We'll have to see how that plays out
Surely t-bap saga including t-bap resurrection all took place before the the slime city saga
Uh, I suppose it must have. Yeah, the continuity is questionable
I mean, when was phantom sealed in stone with keg? Uh, presumably
Yeah, I guess I guess that all I guess that all must have happened. You know ben
Yeah, I guess I guess I guess slime and punishment must take place post resurrection
You could theoretically end it with I mean keg and phantom sealed in the garden for misdeeds
I mean keg was like, I didn't do anything but whoops. There he goes steel. I don't know
Maybe wouldn't that be amazing. It's it's it's conceivable. I don't know. I don't know. I'll have to think about it. I didn't even
Who knows like like the spider's web that I've woven of like the timelines of keg and phantom
It's all it's all a rich tapestry. Uh, that deserves a lecture as well
Honestly, maybe it fucking does
Well, we've said like the horseshoe saga in general like all of our boys together and like the mlp fandom really well
It's own lecture. I think I think it would be funny to do a horseshoe crew lecture
But like an in a canon one like what canonically did like the events of course of a cutie mark kerfuffle
Yeah, yeah, like what canonically did the lives of phantom horn keg standard tall tales give and take digi bro starboard bow starboard bow
Yeah, lethal a roar
This has to be jeff's lecture. We can't talk about
the biggest fan
That'll be his uh, his um, you know, he'll get given that as like a project and he'll be like, ah, damn it
I don't want to do this and then his seo manager will say jeff jeff baby. Sweetheart
We got the numbers in the kids are all talking about this horseshoe crew. You've got to make your next video about this horseshoe
You gotta add tags. You gotta add hashtag horseshoe crew to all your videos. You gotta tag it. You gotta optimize your seo, sweetheart
I have I have nothing but respect who is saying 10 late, uh
He's seo manager guy the one who tells him what to make videos on who apparently is a real person from what I understand
I don't know. Yeah. Yeah, I remember
That's what it sounds like. I remember him. Yeah, baby. Baby. Sweetheart. You gotta make uh, sort out our line
You gotta jojo's bizarre
You heard about this enemy naruto. They got a video game now
It's everyone's favorite character with the seo c
Oh, that's yeah, that's good. Yes. Yeah, that's pretty good
Um
Man, fuck. I don't know. I'm really fucking hype for red count four. It's pretty cool because like literally 48 hours ago
We had no plans other than like
Very comfortable 48 hours ago. I was I was fucking I was uh, it's a wonderful life in it
I was on that bridge ready to end it all ready to have nothing to look forward to and now I'm I'm full of hope
I'm rejuvenated
It was funny. We were having a conversation and we were just like guys everything sucks. What's what do we do?
And they're like, what about
Things could not suck or remember radcons and we're like, oh, yeah
Um, why don't we do that? Why don't we just do that? Why don't why are we yeah?
Yeah, you know, it's it's funny for the record like that
We've been initiating that conversation for a while and the stopping point we kept hitting like recently
Munchie had said like hey, I'm free during spring break like we could theoretically do it then
And we had gotten to the point where he just hit the wall of like, okay, but where should we do it?
Do we need an air maybe could we do it in digi's house? But then we were just like fuck it
Uh, no, it's too small. We answered those questions and that's all it took and once that's done
uh, stone's rolling downhill and uh, that's uh, yeah, the rest is the rest is the easy part
So keep an eye out for that fucking Kickstarter. I guess come in come in within a week of when you see this very likely
Wow, maybe a little bit longer, but that's very soon. Yeah, soon, but soon though. There will shortly be a video announcement
No doubt about it. No doubt about it. Oh my god. Oh my god
So click that bell if you haven't already to get that sweet notification as soon as it tries
hell, yeah
Uh, it's great. Very very happy. You know, everyone's all the comments complain the show stagnant the show sucks
Guess what the show always sucked. It's not about the show. It's about rad con and we're back, baby
Yeah, the rad con is definitely like the the resurgence button like
Yeah, we would you know meeting up and doing all that cool shit
We'll definitely make us more hype about each other and the podcast
That's definitely true
And the fact that we have gone two years is the it's probably the reason the show suffered bad such a disaster
Two years without the orgy that keeps them rejuvenated. I guess we did have that meetup last year
Yeah, it was it was brief though. Yeah
It was rad con 3.3 things that I mean to plan to like can that was such a fucking dumb
That was such a dumb ass meeting
Was totally pointless. I mean it was kind of unnecessary, but I mean I didn't object to coming out to visit the peeps anyway
So it was fun. I was happy to do it. Uh
I mean, you know, I'm out in Cincinnati. I'm not near anybody. I know except really michelle. So, you know, sure
I was happy. I mean that part of it is fine. Yeah, but like the business meeting aspect of it
I think I remember
You guys were talking about that and I was like
This is dumb. This has nothing to do with me and it's probably all bullshit anyway
So I'm just gonna go get drunk in the basement and then I did that did that didn't happen. I didn't happen
I mean at that point that that was kind of when we were answering some of the questions about what this these plans
For the future looked like and I don't know. We have some ideas now, but we're still working it out. I don't know
We'll see anyway rad con
Coming soon
Keep talking and I was gonna say speaking of on this subject. Oh, hey a comment
I mean, is it uh, I guess comment if you want to let us know what kind of things you'd want to see or like what kind of stuff would
Entice you to donate. I guess what would what would be a good what would be a stretch
What would be a stretch goal that you'd be hyped to like push for I don't know
Yeah, if you have any ideas, but we are thinking of doing
We have we have we have a couple ideas of our own
Let's be crystal clear though on the calendar and that we you I want I want to do the calendar
The calendar is a great idea. You audience you don't know what you want and you don't know what it's worth to you
That's our job to figure out
To strategize the ways to get you to donate your money because I mean, here's one of the things
But also charge too little for each of our goals last time
And we will not be so like it's going to be similar to last time
But like a bunch of things relatively are going to be more expensive
Because we we charge too little for them last time
It's like equivalent goals are probably going to be more expensive because we fucked up last time and all lost money
And I'd like to at least break even at least
It's sad. It's sad. That was a painful phone call for like two hours who went line by line through everything. It was like, oh, no
Oh, no, remember that. Oh, no, I remember because I expected that like there was going to be some leftover money
And we would all get maybe like negative money and we would all maybe just get the extra like hundred bucks or whatever
And then it was like no, it's actually just coming out of like when jessy
Like oh, yeah, jessy, we'll cover your flight. It'll be fine. And then like, you know slam
Big miss big three months later. Oh, we we got nothing. But we still promise the man
include or will probably include like a plan of like exactly pretty much like because it's going to be very similar to
The last ride con breakdown like you can compare it'll be probably maybe you'll find it interesting to compare because I certainly do
Like what we expected the expenses to be last time we made that like chart of the expenses versus now
We actually know exactly how much those were and we're going to use that as our template for what we expect to pay for everything
This time and it's a lot more than we thought last time. So uh red con three was so much fun
It sure was buddy. It was the best thing I did that entire year easily
Uh wait, yep. What did what did I do in 20? Oh, oh
Yeah, that was the best thing
I
Mean it was the only thing I did so I mean it just wins by the fault doesn't mean anything. I hate all of you guys
But still
Understandable. Yep. Yeah
2018 was a bit of a low key year for me while I was working on we ag was and uh
Like looking to quit my job relatively soon. So what better way to start a new decade than with another rad con
You're welcome. You're welcome. All indeed. I'm gonna make your so big spenders. Russell. I'm talking to you
Open up that wallet buddy. Break it wide open. Russell get ready. Toya get drunk when the Kickstarter goes live
Oh, it was like the ultimate handboy warrior was the like. Yes
Hashtag like wrestle wrestle
Let Russell wrestle guys. We had we had one we had one
handboy warrior
I kind of think we were we were shocked someone was willing to do that and we had a we had a
What do we have like 15 or 16 like the dad dads?
Yeah, I'm thinking, you know, based on that based on those numbers. I'm thinking maybe
We have a couple we can have some one or two tears in between those
Maybe there might be someone who doesn't want to go the full thousand, you know, that that was a joke
I mean, we did not expect anybody. Yeah. Well, now we know now. We know that some idiots
Out their fat whales just weighing us spew their blubber into our waiting mouths. Oh, yeah, so succulent
Uh, yeah, yeah
So what we should do is I think as I'm coming up with a handboy warrior tier for rad gun for $10,000
I I think I don't know. Maybe we keep it something similar
But we actually open that up. So there's a couple more entries in there or something because like a thousand is plenty
Yeah, I mean, yeah, maybe people will be interested in that
But like things for like the the dad
Well, like all of our tiers of like getting physical rewards all of those I think are going to be more expensive
And then the dad one should bump up the theme of um the thing about um
We're just trying to not lose money guys. That's all it is. We just want to not
The handboy warrior tier is exciting because it like put you you you are
Involved in the yeah, that's real value. That's really like we sure surely we can find other things that we could like
Do
I don't know
I'll bet we could think of some shit that like if you donate this tier
We will include you in something else. I don't know. We'll we'll put you in the calendar
I don't know. I mean the dad thing I guess was the one because we like talked about them in like the in the fucking
Whatever that was the arena. I I feel like we could have done more with that. I feel like if we do it again
We should definitely have more dad involvement somehow whatever that we'll come up with some better plans
Yeah, but but yeah, you're you're right. You're right
It'd be like members of the school board or whatever this time
Oh, they could be our dads. Oh, you know doing our coming for parent teacher night. You know, here's my dad
Figerson and what yeah, what if they are like, yeah, what if the donors they're they're the parent. They're the pta
What if they can like what if we give them like
I don't know. Maybe they can like make
Rules for us or something or maybe they can like give us commands
I don't know
Step dad. I have to do anything you say. I don't know. I'm in trouble now
I'm stuck in the washing machine bent over in this precarious position again. I hope you don't do anything weird step dad
Turns on the wash
That's not the scenario I'm just trying to
Well, I'm sufficiently less interested. You've you've been a you've been a real dirty girl. He says turning on the wash
Oh
Damn that extra spin turns it up to like heavily spoiled and just like
Yeah
Extra hot water. Yeah, just uh, you know, uh, you know how it is. You know how it is. That's the real shit
Okay, but no, okay. I think more like audience involvement is always a good idea
Mm-hmm. You know how in like the hunger games like donors can like pay to like give them shit or like
Yes, set up. Maybe set off bombs or something. You know, they could they interact with
We should set off some seaford down in the house that we don't put some mines in the beach, you know
Maybe like an epic prank. Maybe maybe the pta can be like maybe we'll I don't know
Maybe we could have like certain things we want to do but we could have like polls
But like only the pta members get to like vote to say like what we do
That can be done something this is a very this is a very half-formed idea, but I hope you get the kind of thing
I'm gesturing it. Yeah. I mean by the time this episode comes out a lot of these things may have been ironed out and
Understood as to what we're gonna do. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Yeah, the the big things that are guaranteed are lectures and streams and
High school theming indeed indeed also the beach
Also, the beach will be there and the tropical house. We're gonna do like a slow-mo slow-mo fucking
uh
Splashing in the water going. He he
That sort of thing. We will drink everything out of coconuts
Every single time, you know just for for the record uh of interest
Maybe we'll get the mind racing or tingling or whatnot the the shovel knight Kickstarter, which I was looking into the other day
It had a thing where like if you pledge a certain excuse me
You pledge a certain tier you get to vote on which of the eight like mega man boss knights effectively
Like we'll get a playable mode of their own or whatever and like the three that one were voted on like by those people
So maybe like influence in some style or some decision of something
Oh, wait, here's just an idea. Maybe there's like there's we there's some idea for a video
And like the star of the video will be voted upon by the serene
It'll be one of us will be like the subject of whatever this thing is and is decided by the viewers
And uh, I don't know. Maybe something like that could be um, the um penny the penny arcade
Like d&d twitch the the the c team
Uh, in particular has the thing where um the the twitch subscriber base the subscribers
They're called the shadow council and they get to like vote on stuff and like uh
The dm will like he'll ask like, you know, what what is the dark secret behind like rosy beastingers?
Like long lost uncle or whatever and it's like, oh, he's he's secretly gay or oh, he's secretly straight
And it's like I like this idea of
We we we modified like the dad tier into this pta one and now they get to like be they get to they get to exert
They get to exert a certain amount of uh, of uh, uh, authorial control
Interesting idea. It's an interesting idea. Yeah
Thank you. You're welcome
You're welcome future pta members
Uh, all right. Well, I guess that's pretty much it for all our rad con thoughts thus far
We're currently busily racing to get all the assets prepared so it can be out as soon as possible
Later today, I'll be working more on these on these details of tiers and stuff
So, uh, I have to uh, I have to do the the write-up still
Indeed indeed much. He's working on a logo and other things that you'll see soon. How exciting
I am
I don't know man. It's a real fucking hype. It's real fucking hype for it. My dude
I am as well, but I guess we must move on. Um
New matthew mitosis video out today or two days ago before before we start talking about stuff
I have an an announcement
um
Hopefully either today or the weekend coming
The first chapter of my new comic will be out. No
Shit, I haven't exactly decided on the title, but it's the lord of ghosts comic
Hey
Fucking way, dude
Yeah, okay
Is this post his his involvement in uh becoming the the entity or whatever it was and then getting spat out of
Well, this is this is the story of of uh, the lord of ghosts and what he what happened to him after he was
Uh, uh, he was defeated and the mega slime was destroyed
Right. Um way back and this is his exploits
Uh leaving and outside of the city and the stuff that happens and it's
It's it's cool and I'm I'm proud of what I've written and drawn so far
I think like 14 out of the first 20 pages the the chapter is going to be in like
Each chapter is going to be like 20 pages long. There's going to be like four or five chapters
And uh, I hope fantastic. I hope for it to be basically done
By the middle of february
Oh, shit. So
Is it going to be on um
Aps adventures, it's going to be on a ps adventures. I might change that website's name to give and take dot com or something
Yeah, just for better branding
um
Uh, it'll be up on my webcomic website. It'll I'll probably make like an account on all of the
Webcomic places and put them there as well for no reason just just in case just in case somebody discovers me through that
And uh, that's um, uh, that's my big announcement
Say hopefully there will be a link in the description. It's fucking sick dude. That's fucking sick
Uh, are you gonna go back to uh red noir after this? Yes after that it's red noir until that's finished and then
Oh, yeah, the thing I was thinking because this first comic is like entirely digital
I I sketched it digitally and I'm gonna ink it and shade it digitally
And that's all cool. Uh red noir
I'm thinking of like drawing on my iPad to see how much easier or better that is or maybe not as good
You know just to see the the advantages that brings to that comic and then after that I'm gonna try and do a traditionally drawn
Um, perhaps digitally inked but definitely traditionally drawn comic for the third one
It's gonna be for the rest of the year. Maybe I don't know it's gonna be a long one
But that is my there's my comic thing
2020 was gonna be my my make three comics year
Um, I wasn't on the last episode so I didn't get to say like my goals
But I think I said it somewhere else
And that is that is what I'm gonna do
And it's a good goal. It's a good goal for anyone
Yeah, three comics three finished comics with stuff and it's
Fuck yeah, dude
That's good. That's getting me hype. You're getting me hype now
Dude, yeah, I'm pretty I'm pretty stoked. I'm stoked more work for me. That's always a good a good thing
Mm-hmm
This is making me a little self-conscious that I haven't been working on slime and punishment. Oh god. Good. It's not only me
I was trying to like yeah
Watch that fear
I had a real big like
Idea of like January. All right. How many days are in January? Okay. How many pages could I potentially do?
Out of the pages I ever have sketched like finish them
Uh
Per day if it's like if I can keep on a pace of at least three per day
Um, I can finish the entire thing in January
Unlikely to happen because of you know, all sorts of things
motivation things getting in the in the way like
Other things taking up my time. So it's most likely going to be the middle of February
Um, but I'm I've been keeping good pace so far on the first day of January
I did like eight pages, but they were like easier to draw than the others
and um
I'm I'm feeling pretty good. I'm feeling pretty hype feeling pretty artistic
And I can't wait once we've finished this pcp to get back to it
Fuck
Yes, okay. Okay. Yeah, I
You know what? I was gonna say some shit about me
But it doesn't matter and I don't want to talk about it
Okay
Also, I I did your vaporette. Um, I would and I'm I'm really looking forward to all the vaporites being done
And having that fucking book on my shelf. Yeah. Yeah, that's what I was I was gonna say
I should it's make it. I was gonna say it's making me want to work on that and get that done
I've been the last like yesterday night. I was like
I was like I was right. I was like, oh, I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna I'm gonna finish it
Ah, but it's really late and I'm tired. I should do it. I would just sit there
We're just sitting there jacking my little dick. I'm just jacking my little dick here
And I was not gonna have time in the morning. I'll have time in the morning
I'll have time in the morning to do it. You know, I'll be I'll be more refreshed in the morning
You gotta like, um, I gotta leave space for jacking my little dick here tonight. That's what I got to be spending my time on
A little dick. He's a big wank
Nate, do you have any ground to stand on giving people shit for putting work off, Mr. Ghosting Show?
For having a little dick?
Yeah, I'm afraid not, damn you motherfucker
God damn you you fucking red bastard
You little red
But Ben, the way to think about it, um, to make it easier to understand the passage of time
Because it's easy to just think, oh, I'll do it tomorrow, but then tomorrow turns into three days
Um, you've just got to think of the calendar think of the date and like say I'm gonna do it on this date
Rather than this day of the week because there's there's gonna be another one of those days the next week
So if you say I want to do like a sentence of this thing or whatever on the 13th
Then if you don't have any plans on the 13th, then you remember it's the 13th
You'll be like, well, like best, you know, this is the day I set out to do this one thing
I may as well try and then you'll be more likely to do it
Yeah, I um, I
That's that makes sense. I talked about this. I talked about my uh, my the whole
Thing with me and the and the vaporettes in my oh, yeah, I did want to mention this in the show. I talked about it in my
Uh, patreon's only patreon podcasting that I stole from hippo, which I'm doing now. I'm doing a monthly thing
Um, you know, I was really relieved. I put that out and I thought well, this is fine
I hope people like that because you know, I don't
I just like everything I make I just put out for free
So there's not a lot of like shit that only my patrons get
So I was like, this is nice. This will be nice for them
But I was afraid because I said like I want to do like a Q&A
It would be cool if I had like sort of a back and forth with patrons where it's like they're asking me stuff
And I'm answering them because it's stuff they want to know
But I was a little afraid
Because like people don't use patreon like a social media site
So like posts don't get a lot of like likes or anything posts don't get a lot of engagement generally and like that's fine
But I was a little afraid that like I'll say hey, I want to make this like a Q&A
And it would just be radio silence and I'd get no questions
And then the next month I'd be like, okay. Well, I guess
Scrap that idea. I'll just pretend I never said it. I'll just ramble for 45 minutes. But no
I actually got like
Five or six like really good thoughtful questions from patrons
It was very nice and I was very happy and it's gonna be
And it's gonna it's gonna be it's gonna be a whole fucking
It'll probably be like an hour long
It'll probably take me like at least an hour to answer all that shit to go into all the depth and nuance
Um, I just ask the questions from patrons. That went over pretty well my discord, which works pretty well
I use yeah for the podcast that I do. Oh like when you get home from the gym and it's time for a little Q&A
Yeah, yeah, so, you know, you just go you go into discord and you just no like seriously though
Like and I just have in my discord server
I'll just ask because I do weekly podcasts and I'll just like you have questions
Drop in the suggestions channel. I'm the patron discord and because people are always there
Yeah
um
My it's a weird thing because like my money spenders podcast some people just don't listen to it
Even though they're patrons and you know, they want to be up to date
But it's like, ah shit. I haven't got around to that and I've realized some people just don't get around to it
I wonder whether that's because
It's like not as interesting
as
Maybe used to be or something. I just I I just forget like I did listen to your last one where you talked about like the rfck
And and stuff, but only because you reminded me because you like you said you mentioned it more
But yeah, I only listened to it because you reminded me because you said something about it in the in this
Discord server that we're in right now
I mean
What I've been doing is because because I have the the patron discord. I just do everything through there
I just I just use patreon to post them
because like
I was posting them on youtube, but it was easy to get around it and like keep like
Listening to new episodes without paying some people were doing that which is funny, but uh, I'll just go. I'll just whenever I
Add something on patreon. I'll just go onto the discord server and add everybody like there's a new thing
So like everybody knows that it's up as opposed to hoping they go on the patreon, which nobody does because why would you?
and uh, hope they notice it
Yeah, I can't put that in enough quotation marks. I mean I always get reminded by those things
Um by email, so I assume other people do maybe people just don't check email as much as I do
Possibly that's probably true. I
Don't check my email very much
um
Uh, my okay, so my like patreon is integrated with my discord right because like my pay my my discord is public
But there are patrons only rooms in it
Um, and I'm pretty sure like when you when you become a patron and you integrate your discord
It just gives you like the bot the patreon bot in my discord gives you the role that lets you into the patrons only rooms
But I'm pretty sure that if you unpatron
It doesn't take the role away. It does. So I'm pretty sure there are like people in there who became a patron
I'm pretty sure there's people in there who are not active patrons, but who the bot just failed to
What happens is what you do to like remove the role?
So what I'm saying is become a patron now because you can get so much value
You only have to pay them for one month to get permanent access to all my secret subscribers only discord channels
Well from what I understand it doesn't remove you from the server. It just removes your role as a patron
Yeah, yeah, but what I'm saying is that I still see people in that in that channel
Which means they must have that role who I do not think are active patrons. You would think so you would think so
So I don't know but I feel like if it's like a server that is entirely patron only
People can you know, they they're usually left in
Yeah, you have to manually get rid of people because the the pcp patron discord has
Occasionally people who have unpledged that the name changes color, but they're still in there
Yep, mm-hmm
But for hybrid discords which have like patron and non-patron
Uh rooms, I think it it generally seems to be
They only get access to the ones they should right because like you you lose the role
You can't get into those channels. Maybe I'm wrong. Maybe it's fine. Maybe I'm just stupid. Maybe I'm just stupid
I've never had that problem, but you should you should look into it
Give it a test one of those people who you're suspicious of and see if it's kicking you out everyone
Yeah, it's suspicious of all of them paranoia setting in as as you should be
I don't I don't like them. I don't I don't I don't trust them
We were talking before about being excited to to make things and whatnot
And I know I said this on the on the private or the bonus episode recently about our plans for the future and whatnot
But I I've had a bunch of conversations recently
Including our one about radcon 4 that have really jazzed me up, uh for this uh this year coming
You know my my time on youtube here has been a little bit less successful and I was hoping uh, you know overall
That's why you know, uh
We aguas or I don't know maybe feeling a little stale and whatnot
So I mean I said in the bonus episode, but I'll just say it again here
Because I'm going to say it in my next we agua as well that I'm retiring the we agua format
There's also a long post about this on my patreon, which you can go look at for free
It's just you know, it's just my long explanation for why I'm doing it
Um, so I'm just going to be at the very at the at the at least for now temporarily suspending we aguas in
in you know
Indefinitely until such time as I decided to change it
Just to make time for the bigger projects people have been waiting for and and all that stuff
I think 2020 the year of ghosts is the right thing to do maybe
I well at the very least it we agua format has not been giving me the
I'm not I mean, I'm not saying that there's no room for like the we agua style content, but
Yeah, it shouldn't be at the expense of your bigger pieces people can read my post
They are expensive because I haven't talked about this much on their request, but uh, we we we've had another conversation and they don't mind anymore
I guess I whatever I've had an editor working with me on we aguas for a long time
Who just requested to not be known or whatever, but that does change now. It doesn't matter anymore
So like yeah, I've been working with an editor to give me more time
But even with that the amount of time that I've had to spend is just eaten into stuff
So I'm just like I've been talking with this editor and we're gonna we're gonna be switching it up
And we're gonna try to like
I'm gonna be working on big projects as like my main focus and like when there's small videos
Smaller ones kind of like my recent like konosuba or even the sunflower one
Maybe gonna try giving them those kind of smaller projects
Just uh, it's I'm trying to enter the era of quality of exciting bge videos again
You know, uh where people are give a shit and are interested to watch
So uh moving towards that. I'm pretty excited about it. I want to start making like youtube
Content. I want to start I want to start doing like video essays
Like like nothing fancy
I just want I just want to like
I don't know
I feel like maybe like rather than just getting mad on twitter
I feel like maybe a more constructive use of my energy
And like and when it comes to like the stuff I think about would just be to like write out an essay
Record myself reading it
Add some video clips of stuff or whatever just make drone images of you with your arms crossed talking
Yeah
Or whatever, I don't know
It would definitely be a better use of your time than twitter. Yeah, I agree though
I think you'll just get your information across in a much more
Constructive way
Prott, yeah, I might people might people I might make people like me instead of make people hate me instead of well
Let's not get too carried away here without expectations. I lost like 50
I lost like 50 twitter followers in like one day the other day, which I know that's not like a huge amount
But like that's more than I've ever lost in a day before and the weird part is
I I didn't even make any like particularly inflammatory tweets. That was just the day that like I tweeted my um
I tweeted my my discord link
And then I made a sort of tweet about like the left right spectrum
But I wasn't like it wasn't even like mean shit or any I don't know
I don't know what happened on that day
It was just like I guess people were sick of me or maybe twitter did a purge or something
Hey, yeah, that's always possible. I suppose. Yeah
Uh, yeah, well, I mean hell
I mean I agree just like when the ship doesn't seem to be going in the direction you want
Something should change probably gotta gotta change your tack to some degree. So, uh, yeah, give it a shot
I say I'll be interested to see what you make. I want I want to I want to do that
It's like, you know, I did like the ramble videos before and people generally like those
I feel and that's fine
I you know, I used to I used to be you know back in school and whatever
I was pretty good at writing essays, but I haven't done it in like forever
Yeah, I mean it's a skill. It's a muscle to flex and train and stuff like anything else
So I feel like it's something that I'm capable of doing a good a good job at and yeah
It's more constructive than just fucking airing my hot takes on twitter. You know, it's funny
I should say that I mean like effectively we Aga was have all been like unscripted videos
And making like both my sunflower and the and the kona suba videos
Those were intentionally scripted and designed to like be funny and entertaining and to convey the information
as efficiently as possible so as to not waste the viewer's time and
I both feel way better about those once they're done
And feel that people are not just like exhausted
Like long ass videos scripted ones. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, so like and and like I just feel good flexing that muscle again
So that's that's kind of one of those were like my testing grounds
But I really do
Like that feel and want to lean more into that. Um, I think I might
I think maybe when I'm done with like some of the stuff I got on my play right now
I might just I might just take some time and just like write a bunch of essays and like make them into videos and just like
See how they do
Doesn't seems like good idea. That's that sounds kind of exciting for me to be honest. I'm youtube is my platform
shareable clickable
Is it set or etc? I mean I've got you know, I've got like I'm not a big channel, but I've got like 14 000 subscribers
Which is like a it's a it's a respectable amount
I would get like a you know, I would get a couple thousand. You are well known for that christian lecture people know you for that
Sure. I sure am. Um, you know, I would get some amount of views on anything I did
I don't know. Yeah, it'd be cool
It'd be nice. It'd be nice if like any of them if I fucking had a video like
Do do well and like get seen
Whatever it is a nice feeling, you know, I don't feel I've had that in a while myself
I don't get that on twitter because like I've man. I'm get so jealous whenever I see someone with like a viral tweet
I've never had a tweet go viral. I've had some tweets get like maybe like 200 likes or something
Which is like a lot, but it's not viral. I'm just like, you know, I can't I just say something that's so fucking funny or goofy
Or incisive that just everybody wants to just jump on a why am I not a fucking
I've had a couple viral tweets, but they're never of things that I actually care about or like things that I
Like would want to go viral. I think my most popular tweet
Was there's two that were really popular
There was one when the first sonic trailer came out and I took a picture of the honeycomb mascot and just put it in photoshop
Made it blue. Yeah, that got like a couple thousand retweets and shit
And then another one was the uh, the aw shit here we go again
Meme that was going around twitter
I made one of those for the pirate bay when like disney plus was announced and like when all your favorite companies have a streaming service
And it was just him walking towards the pirate bay and that got like a billion fucking retweets. I'm like, these are both shit
I hate it. I hate all the people just like these simple memes, you know
It's like working on this fucking video game making all this 3d animation. Nobody cares drawing the meme. It's all you need
Draw draw a simple like visual
Comparison between things that are on people's mind and the in the current zeitgeist and like bam viral tweet
My viral tweet. I can't remember how much you got but it probably wasn't thousands and thousands
But the the serial experiments lane
Oh, right
That one was great. It was a an experiment using cheerios
Oh, yeah
Yeah, I remember that I think for me. I think this is my it wasn't we did not get like thousands of retweets
I think got like a couple thousand likes and I don't know maybe like a couple hundred retweets or whatever
But it was never cracked like like 200 likes is like the most I've ever got pathetic. Absolutely pitiful
This one was uh, it was when pokemon, uh
Let's go evie and pikachu was announced and they announced the quote friendly rival of like of the game
I made a post like posted him and I made this like long screeching rant in one tweet that was like like
What happened to rivals like I want the rival to break my fucking spine and step on my neck and rip my fucking heart out
And feed it to me. That's the pokemon rival supposed to be and then the last line was also he looks gay
That was like that was like the full tweet. Uh, so I guess people resonated with that to some degree god
I hate how difficult it is to find specific tweets on twitter. Yeah, it is challenging
I go to the like do I do I just have to scroll for like 20 minutes? Yes. I don't want to do that
Yeah, it sucks. It's a nightmare
Hey, well, hey on this subject
I started this this particular tangent by being like, uh, yeah
We aguas are going to be retired for some time and I'm trying other stuff
And I'm really I am excited about that because I'm hoping to like use my my editor bro to like
Help get more quality stuff out that people like and are excited about and I can get
I don't know like little thoughts out quickly while I work on the big stuff in like a format
That's just a little more just has a little more life to it than we agua
Which I think I did a pretty interesting analysis on my patreon, which is free
So if you want to hear my full thoughts, you should check that out just out of interest
But um, but also like this talk about like radcon 4 and like as soon as we had a plan
As soon as we like all the obstacles were gone like boom. We're making it happen right now. That's really exciting
Uh, fucking me and digi working on cantons. I'll just tell I mean we are currently working on what's effectively the spiritual successor to the weebcast
And then I was just like hey did you what if we like got some guests and did you like
Let's fucking reach out to some people
And so we don't know if anyone's going to happen with that
But people loved the weebcast and we're hoping to like keep that going to some degree now that like cantons like the perfect channel for that
And uh, I don't know we're talking about maybe getting like an editor
Working on that to help us out or something
And this is just many things seem very positive right now and I'm very much looking forward to this upcoming year
So uh, and it's not that I'm just dreaming of it. We're actually doing all of these things currently
So I'm very excited about it. Uh, yeah, yeah, I'm feeling very positive. What can I say? What can I say?
Hopefully things work out for the best
Uh
Fuck yeah, I mean I'm
I think I feel I'm feeling pretty optimistic. I'm feeling like
I'm feeling like I've got room to grow. I'm feeling like I've gotten new venues to branch out into that's exciting
Yeah, you know speaking about like youtube
just
doing videos I was
I was considering
because like um
For for no particular reason
I was on rusty cages channel because I'd never really looked into that guy and it turns out he makes
Like he's quite popular. I didn't actually realize that I thought mplemon was the big the big boy in that that whole like um
Friend of youtube
Yeah, but like rusty cages like he's got actually really great music and I like that
Um, but he's like he's he's quite a creative guy and he's got a webcomic or not a webcomic an actual
um
Requiem of the crazies requiem of the crazies and it's like a big like serious project that he's been working on for years
Rusty rusty seems really cool. Did you yeah, he like apparently he like um
Apparently he made a lot of money like winning like knife game contests or like
Like like or maybe not night. No, it was some contest that involved knives
Okay, but he like he just like won a whole bunch of money like doing that
And like I think that was before he was a youtuber even i'm not sure
Are we talking like millions here? Are we talking like more? You know, I don't know
Okay, like I'm just stuff maybe tens of thousands or you know enough enough to live on for a while
Or I'm not I actually have no idea. I just heard the second hand. So I don't know the details
Yeah, but anyway, he he made that one video explaining that he was going to try and focus on this comic
And you know make a whole chapter and you know stuff like that and I watched this video and he talks to
um
The the guy who made earthworm jim who has like his own youtube show. I saw that I saw that yeah
And he was giving advice and it was like I was listening because it was like obviously
Useful advice for me as well because I'm thinking of doing or I am doing comics now
And he was saying that you know, there's no reason to get like published by a publisher when you have this internet
Presence it, you know
Rusty is obviously very um, he's got like a few hundred thousands of subscribers
He can get this comic out to a lot of people. He's a million. He's a million subscriber boys, isn't he? I think so
Oh, is he?
I was it was a the knife the knife game song went like
Really popular like back in the day. Is that views or is that subscribers? You got 1.38 million. There you go
That's that yeah, holy shit. All right. I misread that as well. But yeah
He's got a big platform and for that reason his
it's quite easy for him
comparatively to
Launch a comic off the back of because of the amount of eyeballs he can get to his thing and it's like true
Maybe maybe it's not such a bad idea to do youtube for just that purpose if that would help
Yeah, because it's not like rusty has made comic videos the entire time. He just makes things
He makes videos about all sorts of things like any any platform that you establish a presence on you can use it to
like siphon
Views from it to anywhere else you want to them to go. Yeah true true
I was just thinking about that. I don't know whether I would go like
Come back full on like hypocrite in the same because it's that sort of stuff is
Very time consuming. I would probably be yeah, I probably but basically I'd be a come a big old sell out
And I try to get as much subscribers as possible completely cynically
But I don't know whether that's also either that is the is the best way to go about it. I might have to like
Figure out some sort of hybrid that is satisfying enough for the old fans and then can get lots of new fans
And then build that up just in the background somehow. I don't know these things can be challenging
I mean, I think we've been trying
But I mean one of the things I'm doing with reagua is like I think people are just I certainly feel exhausted with like
An attempt to play the algorithm and when I look at everybody else, I mean just do what the fuck you want
I saved up money so I could do what I want. So fuck it. I'm just gonna make the projects
That I feel like making and if I die, well, fuck it. I'll look. I've got a good degree
I've worked in a job if I lose all my money. I'll just fuck off get a job
Do youtube temporarily for a while and then try this thing again in a couple years once I've saved up money
Uh, you know, I'll be fine. So I'm not worried about me with the thing with like playing the algorithm
Is that none of us were
willing to go
Full shill we can't go Jeff. I can't do it. I just can't do it
It makes me want to die like if we can't if we can't do that then we don't
You can't expect to to game the algorithm because I was saying the other day using creative
Creativity points you're gonna run out of those
I was saying that I think reagua was the worst possible combination of too much production value meaning it takes up too much time
and
And also not enough to be justified in people waiting for it or whatever the worst possible middle ground is how I think it
Ended up. Um, whereas opposed to like some people spam every day a bunch of videos. That's fine
Or you make one a month and that's, you know, really nice or whatever
There's a bunch of youtubers that I watch like they do
Take sponsorships and they do ads
But they do them in a way that is just like openly
Disdainful of the thing and like I would somehow they somehow they keep getting like the the offers
And like they just keep doing it and like I guess it's just fine
I mean, what's the what's the purpose of advertising to increase brand awareness primarily just so that when that person
Thinks of oh, I need to buy this product
What comes to their mind is the thing that that youtuber was shitting on just because it's the first thing they think of
And so in that way, maybe it's fulfilling. It's it's need probably if they're saying a boost in sales
I guess like like we all need to get into that rage shadow legends of money
Like like like big joe will just end a video with like by the way guys
This video is sponsored by squarespace. You know, I always wanted to make
A website about like how much I love mayonnaise
So I I made a website and I put a picture of mayonnaise on it. Whoo squarespace and like that's the ad
Yeah
You know, that that's a minimal level of selling out
Very minimal very minimal. I don't know. I don't know. How does he how does he get away with it?
This mad is amazing
I like jesse's um
Squarespace fake ad where it's like a space where you put squares
You got squares. Here's a space for them. Somehow. I never figured that out as a pun
Of possibility. It's just so obvious. I still don't get it, but I'm laughing
It's if you got squares, this is the place. What? This is the space to put your
Squarespace
Expecting a lot from this over here, you know, just some high tier word play
Some high t word play for us low t
I mean my onions
I'm gonna make some curry later and put some onions in there. Oh, it's I was thinking of getting into curry
You've planted the seed get into it, bro. Join me on the curry train
Yes, your your sodium will go up, but it's worth it. Pay that piper pay that piper
It's the best food I've ever eaten in my life and I made it
I bought a big bag of fucking sweet potatoes fucking yams
I cannot wait to put that in my new fucking curry and enjoy that. It's the best part of the curry
Fuck the meat. It's all about the sweet potatoes. That's the best part. No, let's fuck this fucked up, man
I know it sounds insane, but it's true
It's true. I mean, I do love when you're low t you get into sweet potatoes, I guess
Yeah, yeah, so they're full of phytoestrogens, bro
Oh, shit, bro. I can feel my gains draining from my body
That's like you hear about the uh, the miracle burger is uh full of estrogen or whatever is like a fake
The sex change those damn globalists will stop at nothing to drain america sounds like a conspiracy to normalize trans people
We can't have that to normalize trans facts, but we won't allow it and I think
Probably it's against my judaeo christian values somehow. I don't know the chapter and verse, but I'm sure it's in there somewhere
I've no doubt. I've no doubt. Don't eat my discomfort. It's definitely a moral obligation, right? It's not just that. I'm not used to it
It's that I it's morally wrong
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. I think so and
gross
God created the biggest sin of all and yucky
Ew gross nasty
Uh, well, I want we could move to the fuck are we all are we all fucked out?
Are we all have we fucked one another enough for our time being are we all satisfied? I'm satisfied with the sex we've had today
Oh, yeah
Okay, I think we've had some positive exchanges here. So
We're all positive fluid exchanges. You know what I'm saying
If you catch my innuendo, I caught more than you in the window you bastard
Uh, well, all right speak pipe link boys and girls down below in the description
Uh, you can call it you can click on it. You can leave us voicemails if they're good
We will respond it on the show like you're about to see here before you on this very day
So first up to the gate to the slaughter is pancakes with craters
Why is our first voicemail? Let's hear why indeed go
Okay, pcp. We know how the views of game review channels usually work
They got they get about one two million views tops depending on the channel
There's a channel used to be called classic game room now going by the name 80s comics that has a video
Called classic game room hd
Ben 10 alien force for the we
review
And it has over
55 million views
Now this video is not special. It is no different than any of the other videos he does
I'm just wondering how such an oddity
Can occur
on youtube kids
It's the bats phenomenon. Yeah, I was thinking of the bat. I thought of bats as well. Yeah
Jesse's video bats that just has five million views for like no good reason. It doesn't make any sense
It is great video, but you know still the algorithm
Sometimes it just grabs one and it just shares it to everybody and this one does sound like the algorithm just grabs shit
Like I remember uh a few months ago everyone was weirded out because like it just put uh mkbhd's first video
He ever did and the algorithm was showing up and everyone's recommended
And it's like from when he was like 15 reviewing an old hp computer that nobody cared about and the quality was shit
Everyone's like, why is this like popular right now? Like what made this relevant?
Who's very strange man? Speaking of the algorithm, uh
chris chan and also speaking of rad con and lectures chris chan lecture is like
It's gonna hit a million views in like it might have hit a million views by the time that this uh episode goes
Oh, holy shit. It's gonna. It's like four. It's like four. It's like four thousand away. God damn
but then and and also it's seeing a spike in views but simultaneously the uh the like
Ad revenue like cost per mil is like just like plummeted
So it's like getting like more views than usual, but it's making less money than usual and it's pissing me off
And I don't like probably because it's not advertiser friendly
It nothing changed. It's the same video youtube's policy change. It's the new year
YouTube's no policies continue. I mean it could be something as simple as
Because like it you get paid based on what ads are actually served
So maybe it's happened to have like a batch of ads that don't pay as much
That is theoretically possible. Well, they nothing is lost. Stop it. Yeah, you should give me the good ads, please
Oh, just just for posterity sake. I found the tweet twitter has like apparently a search feature, but it's terrible
Uh, I found the sonic the hedgehog tweet. It has 15 000 likes and 3 000 retweets
Goodness gracious. Yeah, it was it was you posting it
Uh, I can I can yeah, why not? Let's let the people I've seen it before but posted anyway. All right. I'll I'll link it
Or I'll try it. I'm just clicking on on jesse's bat's review. Uh, a manchild, ink formally
Shit, what was it formally horseshoe reviews and I remember drying horseshoes. Yeah, horseshoes. Yeah, and it's
5.3 million views. That's fucking insane. I would be
It would be pretty cool
Sonic the hedgehog 20. That's it's good. It's great. All you need. Yeah, everybody loves this
It would be pretty cool if uh, my lecture saw big spike in views when I hit a million
Maybe it will be nice. It'll probably just keep on chugging
I mean a million views on a lecture is fucking amazing. So I can't hear anyone. Hang on
So what you get that that low low quality kami microphone?
Ben when are you gonna get a fucking real?
Microphone get an 80 2020 and a scarlet solo like indeed probably all in all with the mic arm probably like a
Six seven hundred dollar investment all told if you're gonna start doing wait six seven hundred dollars
I mean, there's the microphone. That's like four hundred dollars. The mic arm is a hundred dollars. Wait, what?
An 80 2020 do I have a 20 20 or 40 40?
I have a 80 2020. So I have a 40 40 like the upgrade. Okay. That's why that's that's the difference
You spend four hundred dollars on a microphone. I think so pretty sure
Why youtube compresses audio, there's no reason to spend more than a hundred dollars
From econ for ten dollars. Nice. It's got that snow. Got that snowball ice, baby
I am very satisfied with the performance of this microphone as my one mic for everything for the last like
It's just so overkill. That's so overkill
I mean, it's like big dick energy for sure, but like jesus
I mean, you're not wrong. You're not wrong. But hey, let's not let's consider the fact at the time
I was a employed programmer with a stable job and had income at the time
You could have bought an 80 2020 and a ps4 pro. What were you thinking? That's not very gamer of you fair enough
All right. Well, whatever. Whatever we're talking about. Let's just go to the next fucking voicemail. Uh, les are okay. We're back, buddy
We're back. All right. Wait, where are we off? Are we off?
Uh, we're talking about what was the voicemail? I don't remember. Uh
Pancakes with craters. What about eliezer? Did he send a voicemail in? Oh, well, no, I just said like he would cut this section
When you died, we said to cut that part out. It's fine. I mean, I came back almost in like two minutes. You did well
Shit, well, we're still addressing it. Do you want to keep eliezer? If this part's interesting, keep it
Ah, shit. All right. We'll no matter. All right. You can be the judge. I guess. Let's go to our next voicemail
Anyway, which is from the puppet master. Uh, let's hear what he has to say
Go. Oh, hello. This is comrade now from the pc fc pc rsh
I have another comrade. Yes, welcome to speak to you. We are covering over the transfragistrnia transmitter
Okay, I'm going to print him in there. Okay. Goodbye
Bye
Hello
um
So this is not another episode in the communist hell saga
But it is somewhat related and I'd like to speak to
digi in particular
If he's on this episode, but I guess all of you
lol
Okay, a big problem that I think a lot of people have is starting a project
And just, you know losing interest in it and not finishing it and I guess digi is
You know, he's the one who's kind of known for that, but um, I'm just curious, uh
How do you guys deal with that partially, uh, you know, how do you yeah?
Stop yourself. How do you keep your in keep yourself interested in whatever project you're working on?
and uh
I don't know
For the more autistic pc p members. Uh, does being autistic
Help you in any way to stay interested and to be really obsessed with your projects such that you can finish them
Did you poison your mind bro?
I can't
Anyway, thanks guys
Talk to you later. Does being autistic like help you focus on your project, dude? Is that like helpful for you?
Shut up. Oh, that's oh is that what yeah, that's fucking stupid god. I mean, that's really dumb
So no ignoring that have I gone on record enough times to saying how much I hate the fucking digi autism meme
It's fine as a joke that one could use in a funny goofy way
But this guy's taking it too seriously. I can already tell uh chill bro chill
All right beyond that
The way to finish project, uh, you utilize you got to utilize your mind's weaknesses against itself
You got to weaponize your own cognitive biases
For example the sunk cost effect, right? Oh, yeah, that's a good one
I've put so much effort into slime and punishment that I can't possibly live with myself if I don't finish it
I know I I must do it
Um, even even if I even if I like even if I lost all enthusiasm for it
Like I would still have to do it or I would just um
Or I like like the pain I would experience from not finishing it is worse than than the suffering
I would have to go through to slog through to the end
um
So
Person finally stop
Like they they they've been on hiatus for a million years and then they finally said actually i'm just gonna not do it
Maybe release the rest of the the story is text. I think davoo told me about that
I didn't know but that's interesting. She's been doing enough like a million fucking years. Yeah
Uh, I mean, okay. This is a complicated question the real answer. I would say it's it's a multi-faceted one
Okay, like one here's how you retain enthusiasm. There's a bunch of ways one finish the project fast
Don't like if you just get it out fast. Oh, you don't have time to regret it
Like that's important like work like finish it like like go at it with furious energy
Yeah, uh terrified because if you like like like the sort of dam
Whenever you're working on something on a long-term project or even a short-term project
The sort of damocles is always over your head and that sort of damocles is boredom at some point
You don't know when it will drop and you will start to hate the thing you're working on
So it's always a race against time weaponize that initial burst of energy as much as you can
The way to think about it really is
is that um
Every project is really hard to get off the ground and you need a lot of motivation and an you know excitement to get you like
Accelerate it like you start at zero speed and you're trying to build up speed
Uh, and once you're going it's easier to keep going
Um, a lot of the time if you take a break you slow down and if you take a break for too long
You slow down to zero and then yeah without that initial without the initial spark
You have to somehow get back to the speed you were before and it's very demoralizing
Trying to do that and failing over and over again to get back to the right speed and then you know
Every failure becomes more of a failure more of a reason that you fail the next time
Let's consider this in context though because the guy who's calling in is of course
I mean the puppet master
I I don't know if you said that before but this is the guy who was doing like the communist hell
Uh, like chairman Mao and I don't know who else so he's so like he's tired of that
I guess it sounds to me if I I mean he didn't say this but inferring as I am with my big brain
I would guess that he's referring probably to this narrative and
Like I was just saying like being if you got it done fast and conclude it. That's fine. Here's another important one
I suspect you didn't have like a vision in your mind for how to end this thing and that's fine
I would say that like having that is important because one of the important things to do is not let the scope
Drift out of your control so that one you don't even know what to do with it and two
Even if you knew it would take so much energy to actually finish it that that in of itself is intimidating and
demoralizing so like if you if you have the desire first of all
I release you from any obligation to end the communist hell saga. We all enjoyed it. It was lots of fun
You do not have to conclude it in any big epic way or anything like that
But if you wanted to it sounds like you probably don't have a plan right now
I would just say if why not do just like one final thing
Take like the 10 minutes write down just a couple of lines. You think it'd be a funny way to like maybe hell explodes
I don't know. Everyone goes to heaven. Uh epic goof. I don't know whatever whatever the fuck you want to do
But you gotta don't do that. That sucks. Sure. That sucks
But there's something that doesn't suck but like make it well make just narrow down your work by giving you something not
Have a goal. Use those smart goals
Here's my like big brain idea for for how this works. Yeah the
A lot of the advice is plan better and make sure that you don't slow down
But if you're already in that funk
Um, I think the best thing to do if you really just
You don't like you don't have a clear goal for where you're going and you feel bad that you're not doing anything
But you also don't want to do it. Just cancel it
There's no there's no like
Yeah, um, there's no shame in cancelling a project so that you can work on something that will actually get done
If you're just if you just don't want to do it, right?
Then just like if you're at the point where you're like, I don't want to be satisfied with communist hell
If that's what you're talking about. I feel no need. I don't I'm not even I'm not talking about communist
I'm just talking janitor. I don't know. Is this about communist?
I'm inferring it. I don't know for sure
It's not clear anything if you just if you don't want to do it anymore, and they just don't do it
Uh, and like, yeah, well the the reason I feel like
Confident and happy about this lord of ghost comic is because I planned it all out before I started like quote unquote started
um before I announced it and
The whole thing is planned out from beginning to end and I like, you know
I I wrote the entire thing and then did like a screenplay with dialogue before I started drawing
You know the pre-production is integral to making sure the the process of making it goes very smoothly
And so because I did a lot of pre-production
I'm confident it can work if I just went into it and
You know had the same lofty ideals of how big it would be and how long it would go
But had no real plan to fall back on it would be much easier for me to take a break
And then lose momentum and then want to quit because I didn't know what I was doing
and so the pre-production
is
It allows me to maintain my
My speed so that I can get to the end of the project as fast as possible and and not slow down at any point
um
And that's why I know that's that's gonna work
So it's it's it's it's really just a matter of planning out these projects beforehand
That's the main thing similarly if you're going into a project with no plan
It's okay for like it to just be shit like the um
Yeah, the the canon story comic I I made I made um
Just because why not I was bored or something
I I forget the reason but I thought wouldn't it be cool to do that during a stream and I did a stream
Where I drew a comic panel and then saw what happens next and then it was finished in the stream
And it was incredibly low quality
But the fact that it was a project that was started and finished really quickly
It didn't matter the the motivation like the the happiness that came from a completed project no matter how shit it was
Was like powerful enough to spark the next one which was bell shape
And that one did have a lot of hurdles because I did slow down at points
Um, I just really really wanted it to be finished
But yeah, yeah, it's it. There's no problem with like
quitting if you have no idea of what to do next or
desire to continue
I think he's gotten plenty of advice on this friend especially especially if like
To continue something you would have to like not do another thing that maybe yeah, you would be more interested in
Yeah
Yeah, we've he's heard enough. Yeah enough for you
Or spend too much time with his asshole. It's mostly just me boasting
That's all right. We've got a message here
Titled pokemon sword and shield. Let's quickly shift into the pokemon podcast people in the comments people in the comments
Said that tom the guy who wrote the christmas carol about me. Yeah, he should be him. He should be in voice grail
I don't know. I don't want to go very true back and nominate him for voice. Absolutely true. All right, tom
Tom's going in voice grail. No other tom. Yeah, not this guy's not good enough. You haven't pulled your way. All right, tom
No, no, no. I'll get there someday. Tom more like tomb
To me for christmas. Please kill Ben saying I hate him. Yeah, it's all good stuff. All right
Next voicemail right pokemon sword and shield. Let's hear what he has to say. Take it away
Hey, mr. Best guy ever in your content video
You talked about the trs and pokemon sword and shield and how you didn't know what it was
If you go to one of the guys in the town there, he's all like bro. It's so vintage. It's vinyl. They're vinyls
They're records. It's technical records. They they look like records and they break and they suck because they're records
And it's vintage and then the tms
Are technical like machines or some shit and they're like cds
That's all I have to say. It's do what you will with that information. Okay
Thank you for the okay in in pokemon sword and shield
There are tms. You know tms now are multi use you can use them in infinite number of times
But they also introduced this thing called tr as you get in the max raid battles that are
They're they're they're the old like one time use version of tms
So you might get a tr of earthquake you can use it one time and then oh items destroyed
So now i'm getting it. It's like wait. Okay, it's like old tms. I don't do they look like do they look like records?
They look they're
Black as opposed to the other cds of tms that are like whitish. So there is a difference there. Yeah, I guess that makes sense
That seems
It seems obvious. I well, I don't know. I just see a tr and it's a different color
I'm still confused as to what a tm is exactly. Oh wait
Like how does a cd teach a pokemon a move? It looks like a disc based based on how it looks when you apply them in the gba games
You basically glue it to their head and then it absorbs into their body and now they know something
I know I've said this in the past, but in the pokemon adventures comic
I believe by the way, I finally found the serial experiments lane tweet. It's not actually that much. Oh good
It just is a lot for me. Okay. We'll say 500 retweets and about a thousand likes. I mean that's that's good
That's good. And yeah, this is great. Um, but uh, that is so much better than my tweet
I hate on this subject of technical
Machines whatever in the pokemon adventures manga read
At one point when he's battling someone he he has an evie and he uses a tm on evie
And I remember vividly because I was so freaked out by this
He what he does is he has like two pieces of a machine. It apparently is a tm
It's it's like a box. It's like a box
He pulls it apart holds the pieces on either side of an evie's head and we can see like a data stream
Like pass in between or something and it's like sticking it was teaching it mimic or whatever
He's teaching his evie a move via this like weird data stream or something
But it's the it's a disc now. You can't do that with a disc. I don't understand
I mean the manga the mangas aren't the mangas aren't canon. So what are you gonna do?
I think I've been confused for a long time on this whole just throw it like a shuriken and they catch it
Yeah
That'll do the job. Okay. Anyway, it's a rocket. I'm trying to I'm trying to find a picture of the sprite
Because I want to see what they actually look like so I can make fun of you for not getting it
It's just I don't know 25. They don't even show it in game. It's just like in the inventory
It's they don't have a sprite like items, right? They do Ben just google tm 25 in the menu or whatever. It doesn't matter and go to bulbapedia
tm 25 that that's thunder and just click on it and it'll show you there's like this yellow disc and that's what
Yeah, but that's a tm. I what does a tr look like? Oh, oh shit. It's that but black. He has like a black
Fuck. Okay. I can't remember. Do the trs have names. Are they numbered?
Yeah, they're the same the numbers are the same. They're just you know
I'm searching tr 25 bulbapedia
Got it. Okay. This is apparently scy shock here here. I'm putting the show notes. Enjoy everyone this link to tr 25 scy shock
There you go. Click on it. You'll see it just as black okay black edges
Oh, that's a record dude. I didn't okay now. I know that's a record. That's what a record looks like
Unable to bun guy everybody
That's a that's a great day of cosplay
Yeah, I don't oh wait. It's not cut. It's like this is like proto-dave at the beginning of the series. Yeah
Well, I'm wait fighting. Well, what's what's what color is red? I guess fire
This one's pink. So it's a scy shock. So it's a psychic move. I guess so we need we need a fire type tr
Oh, yeah, that'd be perfect. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. All right. Anyway, uh, let's move on to our next voicemail
let me see this one is uh
Oh, she she pollution she pollution who I believe is called in before but uh, let's see what they got for us. Go
Hey guys, happy new year. Hello. So every new year. I thought it would be fun for you guys to do some predictions about
2030 like for example
Does the piece piece still exist?
or
Um, YouTube is no longer the place for most people watch your videos, you know, maybe a new platform has been created
So, yeah, I thought it would be fun for you guys to do these predictions so that in 10 years
We can listen back to this podcast and see if you guys were correct
I hope you have fun. Okay. Well, see you in 10 years. Bye. See you then buddy
If if the another prediction if a prediction of like youtube won't be around is correct
We won't be able to come back and check that we were correct. Well, this does exist on other formats. It's on
Yeah, yeah, you know other podcast format itunes and a couple other places
Um, you'll have you'll have to pledge to our patreon
Secret bonus the old bonus content now lost to time everywhere else. Damn true. Um
I think I think I think I mean
For myself like my plan in life is like maybe even if um, like
I have to get like a real job again. I'm still gonna do like all my internet stuff
I just won't be as you know, I don't have as much time. So I'm gonna keep doing it pretty much no matter what
I'll be cringe posting till the day I die
I saw ben. I loved your tweet the other day that here it is my final cringe post of the decade
I thought of that the day before and I was like, but I can't post it today
You gotta wait because then I I can't post until the end of the year
So I had to wait until the day the last day cringe posting later that day
It's like I gotta make my final cringe
You technically posted it within January 1st in my time. Your time zone is not real
So if you ever tried the cringe post in the uk, oh, oh, yeah, I'll bring it up. You're not allowed. You're not allowed
Hey, you said you said it was your last one. You said
Um, okay. Well, you took exist. What do you think? I'm sorry to break it to you, but I'm sure I have many more cringe posts in me
Over the coming decade
All right, so short version I I plan on working with you guys in some version for for a long time
So I think the pcp in some form
I plan on throwing all of you under the bus. Yeah, that'll be good to gain clout for myself. Oh, yeah
Well, I yeah, that's been obvious for a while. Yeah, that's as soon as possible
I plan on teleporting behind you so that the bus kills both of us
great
Biting my time for the perfect opportunity to jump ship as this whole thing crashes and burns
So I can escape scoffing want the pcp to exist. I mean 10 years is a long time. We'll be like 40 basically at that time
Um, I will be 40. I'll be I'll be technically just under 40, but I hope I hope the pcp
Doesn't exist not because like I I hope we all
Like fall out. Yeah, I definitely hope we're all still friends, but I hope that we're all like
More professionals you hope that we found something better to do
Yeah, like like I would still love to talk with you. I'm not holding my breath
I was still loved like I would love for like tom to be a game developer
Uh, I would love I mean, you know, if that's what you you're going for
Yeah, like for all of our projects
We're working on now to be like more upgraded versions by that right right did she will probably have a kid and that would be funny
You know you guys yeah the biggest downgrade of all by that time frame. I plan on having a kid or two. Yeah, so you know
They can oh my god, they can start the new pcp
Oh, that's their destiny. They can start content is just a fucking
Trojan horse to like to have the dads hang out. Oh, that sounds fine. Maybe we could have them on
No, we should we should re-brand us like the dad the old dad
Oh, they could make a our children could make the pre teen cp. You know, it'll be
Hey, anyone who donates $10,000 to the Kickstarter gets to name digi's kid
We're not going to tell him that
We're gonna sneak in and and and and write on the birth certificate before he can
Yes, this is all great. This is all gold. That's so seriously if you're a dad, you're kicked from the pcp
I don't make the rules. I just thank you. Thank you. I mean, okay
I think I
Personally like my goals are I would love if my channel could get big and I make a million billion dollars. Yay, wouldn't that be nice?
I'm gonna I still want like my goal in life is to make good youtube videos that people find entertaining and hopefully interesting
Uh, and I'm gonna try to make them better and better as I go
So, I mean, I I want to do that. That's the thing I want to do. Maybe I'll like work with more editors
Maybe I'll try to make them fancy or whatever. I don't know, but that's what I want to be doing
Yeah, what I want to be doing is making comics and yeah, like writing for movies and and doing all that cool
Shit by that point definitely something that I've been working on will be out from my writing work
Sure, sure, and then I'll be like, uh getting money from it or something
I have some desire to crack into voice acting to some degree, but that's kind of on the back burner
So I'm not I have some desire to voice crack
Oh
Happens when you least expect it, you know, I'd like to I'd like to sound a bit of this voice crack storyboard for cartoons
I think I could do that really good. I could do that real good
I know the guy who uh used to make that webcomic three-word phrase got a job storyboarding for regular show man
I'm sure it's like hard, but like it looks so fucking easy. Sure. Sure. It looks so easy
Yeah, uh, I want to do storyboards for family guy personally. Uh, I want to
Be like uh lois
Forget about it
His classic line forget about it lois. Um, that's what I'm looking forward to that's gonna be my career
Uh, other than that, I'd like to live in a nicer place. I want to leave the ghetto
Um, you know, I guess this isn't really in keeping with the spray. He has four predictions
Yeah, I was gonna say so like will youtube still exist. What do you think about youtube?
I think youtube will still exist. I mean facebook. I think youtube will
Uh, uh, what's the word?
My space still exists. Uh, so it's just I don't think youtube will be nearly as relevant
I think micro content is gonna start taking over. I think i don't think so. I don't think so reduce people's standards
I don't think I would like that but I don't think the idea of like youtube as a platform will probably exist
It may not be on youtube, but like so many people are so used to this sort of media
I think it'll be hard to just suddenly disappear for sure youtube will exist
I think that more
I don't like I don't think like a direct youtube competitor will like overtake it
But I think that like alternative platforms that like maybe cover some of the youtube niche will become more viable
Yeah, I think so they're starting. Yeah
Um, there will there will be not there will be not direct competitors
But there will be viable like pseudo competitors and probably like them the the the platforms will diversify
I think youtube will continue to become more commercial and so that'll force underground creators to go somewhere else. Yeah
I possibly in in 30 years
Uh, I'm not 30 years. I mean the next decade
2030 I hope by that point we will have
VR
Games that are actually good games because you admit they're not good right now
I fucking proved it everybody. He admits it that I'm right about vr games. There's a couple good video games
There's a couple good video games, but like I've never felt the urge to go and play a video game in vr
Maybe the half-life one like I've tried it out and it's been it's been it's been like quite nice
But did I bring my did I bring my um oculus to rad con three? No, but you should bring it to rad con four
Yeah, I'll bring it to rag them for we can all play fucking. Yes. I want to play super hot so bad in vr
That's the one game. I actually want to play sounds fucking sick. Okay. Fuck. Yeah. Nice
I didn't actually mean vr. I was going to say something else. Oh, well, still it's a good idea
Like just just general technology improvements, but like I was trying to think of some
Interesting thing, but of course I've got a bold prediction. I don't make technology
I don't know how but of course you couldn't think of anything interesting you idiot. No
I'm just a creative I suspect
That here's a here's a bold prediction during the next 10 years
effectively
It might exist in some form, but it would be as a shadow of itself
I think that the main line of the final fantasy series will die
It will straight up die
And sure the mmo might exist not it already died. I mean that's that's the thing final fantasy 15 came out
I guess there's no plans right now for final fantasy 16, but like people have hope foolishly. I I don't know people
I'll extend that to to square enix in general as a development. Things will wax and wane in video game franchises
People rely way too much on franchises now and continue to rely on franchises in the future
I think if something dies people will eventually be like, let's bring something back that died earlier
Let's bring back final fantasy. It's been like six years
I mean they're trying like oh my god. It's been such a what like gamers are just gonna keep getting older and they're never going to die
Look at mega men look mega men 10 and they're still gonna want to play final fantasy 7 again and feel like a 12 year old
But it's not gonna work. It's not gonna happen. What I'm saying is I don't like the big like I think that final fantasy 7 remake
People are very excited about it right now. I do not think it's going to be it's gonna be kind of like
um
Like the force awakens in that people are really excited for it
They see a lot of good things, but like I mean I'm not I'm not even like judging the people or anything
But I'm just saying like I think that they don't
Know what they're in for because it's just a remake of a story. Everyone already knows
Like I sure Sephiroth's an hd now. Is that really like this is my prediction now. So I can be wrong
Literally people will love it as long as it's not a complete
Adventuring trash fire of a video game people will love it because
Because people still love the star wars movies that have come out for nostalgic reasons. Okay, but that's why I say the that's why I
I pitted as um the force awakens because the force awakens did well
But what it did was it it showed what it or like now we know with the benefit of hindsight
We know that they did not have a plan and that like the next one like wasn't embarrassing
I mean in the in the internet reviewer
Like bubble that everybody on the internet see on youtube seems to think is the only reaction to the the star wars movies
It seems like the force awakens was the star wars is the last terrible
And will never work um like there are fans of the rise of skywalker
But the rise of skywalker was the worst performing one yet and that's what i'm trying to speak to this trend this downward trend
It's a downward trend. I think I think in 10 years it will still be limping along it will be around fair enough
Nearly be as hype as it used to be but it people the the the the big guys at the top
they they will continue to scramble for any scrap of of
You know, I think the remaking ability they can get I hear you and I see that but I think the remake
It will be more of a catastrophe than anybody expects
specifically because they do not have a plan beyond the first game and they they might they might succeed
Extremely well with this first game just like the force awakens, but I really think with well if it keeps going
They just have to remake the rest of the story and they will fail and they will fail in doing so in spectacular fashion because they only
Think about midgar. It's the only thing on their mind. They have no plan for the rest of the game
And it's going to people are going to not give a shit
I don't think I don't think that parallel
Is quite the same because the last jedi and rise of skywalker where they're not based on the original star wars
They're not remaking them. They're making a new story and the fact that the story
wasn't very good
Is separate from it being
You know the same property. I mean these are there are different challenges
But I'm just saying that there are challenges one of them being
There was no plan
I mean sure the story of final fantasy 7 exists, but like the game game development is very different from movie development
I guess I just don't really see why the
They're not having a quote-unquote plan. I don't know where you're getting the information from
I mean that has been explicitly stated by the developers that they have not planned what the next games are going to
Be about I think that really just means it's going to be a few years between
the parts
Which is I mean I would assume they're going to have to like change things up anyways because they'll be switching platforms after this one
Like that's true. That's true. Look you can disagree all that. That's fine. I just think it's going to fail
I just think your your reasoning is I don't agree with your reasoning
Okay, fair enough plan is is the reason like it the parallel to star wars is not quite the same
I think it will
I'm not saying it's exactly the same situation. I'm saying there's some similarities
I think the reason it would become less
Successful financially is just because
People will realize that a remake of final fantasy 7 is not actually that interesting and they were mostly hyped when the trailer came out
And that's it and that's how it's always going to be
The trailer is the moment where the money should be spent and I think even yeah, they might even like
Well, they kind of already do that don't they they do pre-orders like extremely early. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah years ahead
That's why they go ahead. So they take the money as fast as possible. But I mean, hey, it's coming out in a couple months
I think in march is when the remake episode one is coming out
Um, so I mean people
March is gonna be a packed month. I think I will be very curious to see
Regarding that game
What like everyone's really excited everyone's just like the remake the remake
But what they don't talk about as much is that hard cutoff. This is not a complete game
It is a piece of a game and how many years are you gonna have to wait for the next one? God knows
God only knows
So I kind of hope this doesn't do well just because I don't want that because like as soon as this model is proven
You like EA and Activision are going to immediately be like we can sell
A game in three parts
Okay, and then go back through their back catalog and they'll just all the classics
So like we're going to make a trilogy out of all of our classic games and it's going to be bullshit
Is there a game series that's done a trilogy story correctly?
Maybe like god of war did pretty good for its first three games
Max pain. I don't know. I never played it. Yeah crash bandicoot
Um, well, I mean how many of these like were it like mass effect was designed as like a continuing story over three games
God of war wasn't even designed that way. I don't think spiral was I don't think crash was they just as a story
I have no David jaffy created god of war was only involved. I believe right
And I mean a fucking mass effect was a huge catastrophe in the finale as everyone knows
I honestly feel like any game series that starts off thinking they're going to be a trilogy is doomed to be just subpar
I couldn't agree more. That's what that's what happened with fucking ratchet and clank on the ps3
Really?
They had the trilogy on ps2 and then they were like, how cool
Uh, ratchet and clank is a huge
Thing people will love the next
Trilogy ratchet was not intended the first game was a standalone. It wasn't intended to be a yeah
So that was that that was just like a natural trilogy. It was a very well-selling game
Three of them then ps3 comes around they make the first game
It has a cliffhanger ending a terrible story and I really hated it. I was completely
Disillusioned with ratchet and clank and I did not ever buy a single other game in the franchise after that
I stopped there too. I stopped there too. The second one was ironically a lot better, but uh, maybe I played that
I don't know. Yeah. Well, they fucked up. Yeah, let's do that. We lost a customer
I mean, I bought them both for five dollars in the bargain bin as I do with all the ps3 games
I mean, I put it on release. I'm just curious stupid
The the only game that ever lived up to its hype that I can remember
Is I mean, it wasn't a sequel, but it was like the the demo of Undertale
And then the actual game shocked me by actually being beyond my expectations. You know what you know what?
No, no
Did Undertale demo?
Let me down because the because the demo is the best part of the game in hindsight in hindsight
The moment with toriel is the best part of the whole game. I talked about this in great detail
And I agree that is the best usage of the time reversal thing
But like all the stuff about the multiple pathways and like being able to do a genocide and how those time
Rewinds they do impact things if you like do a genocide
Then revert it and then do a pacifist and then you get that extra little thing
Where it like confirms you're like still have the soul of a demon or whatever
Once I understood like every detail. I was like as a package
I'm I think that this is it has
greater highs or whatever
But like you you get your best bang for a buck if you just play the demo to its full extent. It's it's true, but um
I don't know whatever. Anyway, love Undertale great game. Etc. Etc. Uh
Fuck me can't wait the delta room to come out so that there'll be more porn of susie draw. That'll be great
Very exciting. That's the only reason is it coming out soon. No. No, I don't know
There's no there's no news at all, but like it's it's likely that he's working on it right now
Probably I wonder if you ever put together that team that he was talking about of uh of capable individuals
He's got all that sweet smash money now. So yeah, yeah, he probably had to fucking pay to get sands in there
Please put my skeleton son in the game. I'll do anything sakurai proceeds to filet furiously. All right. Anyway
skeleton son
All right, uh, let's go to another voicemail. We got two more. We got uh, like a little troglodyte tip diddling
bitch
Okay, damn. I love I love this guy. This sounds great. My favorite guy
Go last episode in response to my cry for help
Nate bestman asked me if I had asked anyone specifically a girl out before and the answer is fucking yeah
but
In a pretty pussy show way, you see there were two kind the first one was a couple years back a year or two
I think and
I I really I really fucking went went went zero zero powers zero masculinity in this one
Through a string of fucking, you know doing like this and holy gets homework
I managed to get her fucking medical files and found out that she liked me and I did not I would not until then
Ask her out, but I did
And the pussy is the way
So I fucking instagram dm to like a little little little little bit of fucking tip diddling
creepy bessen bitch
And instagram, huh?
Luckily enough she responded with a yes. I had a date in time as a movie. She hated the movie
She like fucking watched anime and like fucking listened to kpop and shit. So dodged that bullet, but you know
Slut I did something
Second time asked him about kind of
They were like really into furbies and like poor and shit. So that that wasn't gonna happen
But then they asked me to concentrate after I asked them
So the answer is yes kind of in a pussy way, but basically my fear is now that in this game or age
It'll be circulated if I do
So
Okay, uh, okay. I got it. I got it. He's got the typical fear. Yeah, so this is teen cp
All right, teen cp translate from zoomer for me. All right, no problem
He just uh, we last time he was asking about like advice or something
Talk girls, blah, blah, whatever and uh, I was like, have you ever talked to a girl?
Have you ever asked one out? It sounds like no because you don't sound very confident, etc
Okay, so apparently he has on a couple of occasions. Great literally twice. Good job. Uh, all right
So your fear about asking girls out and word getting around
G you just got to not worry about that because it doesn't matter. Oh my god. He asked a girl out. How embarrassed
I remember feeling that exact same fear. What if no, no, no, I get it, you know
But when I say it out loud, it sounds pretty fucking stupid, right? It does it does
And and when you're in that situation, do you hear that guy? He he he asked a girl out. He's like interested in romance
Dude, what a fucking loser dude like that guy wants to get his fucking dick wet dude. That's fucking shitty, bro
Cancel him. Yeah, he needs to be cancelled. Kill him Matt. Kill him now. That's a rapist in the making right there. He has a desire
That's disgusting
Um, he has that man is driven. Yeah, that's that's no good. That's no good
He's just a me too moment in the waiting and uh, that's no good
How you should drive him over? You just gotta
Okay, I like I don't know. I remember in my youth
Grappling with this very same issue and what it really came down to was just my deep insecurities
about like
Like putting any risk out there or having like anything negative happen to me
But these things are so
Inconsequential
Like you're a guy who's done two approaches basically and has been terrified
Those times and I get it. It's terrifying every time you do it. You need to up that number to like a hundred
Then you will stop caring and then you'll be like, yeah, it's fine. It doesn't matter. Uh, I don't know you just gotta
You just gotta lose your fear if you're feeling if you're feeling nervous and you need a confidence boost
Consider bringing a gun to school. Yeah, yeah, that'll do it
You've got nothing to fear then
Yeah, make sense to me. All right. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I shouldn't have said it. I should have said it on the show
real answer here is
There is very there basically I share this fear, but there are almost no negative consequences as a result
I understand biologically there's the instinct in us that like, oh no
We've been ejected by the females in our little 30 man tribe word will get around and I will not be able to carry on my genetic legacy
And my bloodline is doomed
But luckily, not only is it not the case that that's true
If if you are perceived to be more of an outgoing person who maybe even asks girls out somewhat that probably
Will improve your reputation as opposed to make it worse because then you're like an actual human being
Who it's the sort of thing
It's the sort of thing where like the the the other guys would say we'll try to put you down
Like, oh my god, this guy asked a girl out. Haha. Let's pull any guy
And and like all all of the boys are like, hey, yeah, fuck you loser
You yeah, how many girls have they asked out that day? You know, what are they doing?
Yeah, but like it's not that it's like the the girls in the class are like listening to this and they're like, huh
You know that they might be bitchy, of course
But there's there's some like, you know, the way boys bully is very different
In their in their in their hearts, these guys are thinking like wait, should I be doing that? Yes, that's true
Should I be doing that too? Wait, what does he know? What does he know?
We have to we have to question as fast as possible
We have to get the secrets that he got on the pcp and the procrastiners plaque
Is I have to give five dollars a month for those precious bonus episodes for all that secret information
Uh, I I would boil this down to they wish they were on they were on the voicemail
I'll boil this down to them. They do. I'm sure
Uh, uh, obviously I want to be respectful and not a creep and be reasonable and ben's point about like inviting people to do specific things
Is is a winning proposition. That's that's like a good a good way to do it
But I will say this in summary
People in general women men everyone everyone loves a man of action
So like there's nothing wrong with taking a shot
Just roll in the dice because you are first of all you're conditioning yourself to be more willing to do cool things
And also people will just respect you for doing anything
There you go
So, uh,
Fucking go for it, dude. Just just talk to people
Meet people who you think would be fun to hang out with invite them to do something casually and then do it and that's it
And just be a cool guy. There you go. There's your life advice
Congratulations. All right now go live your life. Go live your life or end it up to you
Next voicemail is oh, this is our last one. Okay. This is our last one
This is um how to pass the time at 6 a.m. By center point. Okay center
Take it away
6 a.m. On sunday morn
I can't sleep as is the norm
twitter reddit discord 2
I'm out of things to read through
I've laid down
masturbated
ASMR gets repeated
I fear insomnia though
Not as much as digi bro entering my house this hour
But i'm awake. I have power
I just erased half these lines fucking big ass thumbs of mine
I haven't eaten since 10
My stomach needs chicken
This shit poem is a pain
I'll kill myself out of shame
Okay, oh wait snaps snaps non-aggressive snaps for an epic slam poetry sash. Good job. Good job passing the time
Yeah, you did it. You did the same for us as well. That's true. You padded out our content. Thank you
We're about to cross that sweet sweet two hour threshold. Oh, we're so close. Oh, that's so fucking close
Dude, it's a night and day in terms of sheer input. We are about to roll over into a whole new world of ad revenue
I
Really hits on a on a real point
That I hate like sometimes I'm I'm writing on my phone because I have an idea
And then I'm like deleting it because it's I'm tired and I'm like, oh
And then I throw my phone out the window and die
Well, uh, I'm happy to be uh part of the canvas upon which center can can can spew his art
What a wonderful what a wonderful experience. This has been uh, all right
That's it everybody send more poetry at the speak pipe link down below
Send us your epic slam poetry. Put some uh sick bongo drums in the background or something
So, uh, we really get the vibe on and we will snap for you
Uh, as hard as we pot like we'll fanno snap for you and wipe you off the face of the fucking earth
Just as you deserve uh ascended points. So clearly dying for
All right, that's it more voicemails. You heard it send it to speak pipe
But more importantly you gotta head on over to patreon.com slash the procrastinators
Give five lowly dollars for all 33. I believe bonus episodes now
We just did our year in review looking forward to the future more of those kinds of thoughts on there
And a million other episodes of varying quality levels
At tpcrastinators on twitter follow us for updates and whatnot
And uh, if you want to play minecraft with us pcp minecraft patreon patreon.com slash psb minecraft
Although actually I think we're having a technical glitch right now, but uh, I'm sure we'll have that straightened out real soon guys
Uh, please don't please
Yeah, and that's it and that's it more voicemails, etc. Etc. All right. We'll be back. Hey
Radcon for everybody plans are in the works
Keep your eyes peeled by the time the next episode comes out
We'll either have it out or be very close to having the Kickstarter ready. I would think and uh, we beseech you
We're trying just to set
Financial goals at reasonable levels so that we are we're not like losing money for every pledge
Which I think we definitely did on some of those old pledges
Um, and so we can just make the make the thing feasible
And we don't just lose money and lose time whenever doing it
I personally love if we could actually just get hype for lectures get high for rad content
If we broke even as a result of that that's fine
But I am in fact losing time I could spend working on my own content
So I would love to make a little bit of money from radcon if possible
Just to cover that week of expenses on my fucking rent and shit
Radcon case and exposure
Don't be a little bit. It's all it does
It actually does
You know, it's fair to say that the content that we're then able to post like the lectures does generate revenue for some time afterward
So that that is a that is a net positive. They're not immediate
I mean most importantly it justifies the existence of this podcast. You are so right. You are so right
So let's let's keep that going for
Another thousand year rike everybody. Let's hear it. Keep it going here on the episode
procrastiners podcast
All right, we'll see you next time everybody uh da da ass volt. See you then bye
Check out the fucking lord of ghosts comic. Everybody else's comic slime punishment. Tom's game. See you next time everybody. Goodbye
Later