How do you like that?
Left out in the cold.
Everyone's man and murder face.
Everyone's speaking mean to me.
Nobody gets re-residuals.
Dick individuals.
Fuck those six-wise fantasy.
I'm the fucking foundation of this five piece.
I lay down my soul. I lay down my heart.
But they try to tear me apart.
Nothing in this world is where the work is for.
If they don't come, maybe they'll show us what's important.
You better tear it up or they'll show us what's better.
I ain't breaking a sweat cause it don't really matter.
Nothing in this world shouldn't not be easy.
If it needs my comfort, tell them it won't make me queen.
Do you know what I ain't gonna do?
I'll give up room, I'll break up.
Why is something so hard?
Why can't everything be easy?
Why can't it be easy, man?
Man, even singing the song is hard.
It gotta make everything hard.
I should hire someone to sing this song.
That would be easy.
Then I'd have to tell them how to sing it.
Then I'd have to pay them or I'd really get some money.
See, everything leads into everything else in the bass.
It's so hard, man.
That's why people kill themselves.
Hello, everybody.
Welcome to the new PCP part one of this episode.
That's right.
This is just me and Hippo over here.
Say hi, Hippo.
Hi, Hippo.
Anyway, this is just us because it's only part one.
We decided to begin the recording and no one else wanted to show up.
We were like, you know, every goddamn week.
It is like an hour of waiting for people to show up.
Sometimes I'm the one who takes an hour to show up.
But sometimes it's been, sometimes it's always someone.
It's just so hard.
Getting the podcast to start is very difficult.
It's an all day process sometimes.
Yeah, and that is the topic of this podcast.
Things being really hard and it's annoying and we hate it.
Right.
Now, I guess I'll just come right out of the gate with saying,
come up with inventive solutions to your problems,
which is exactly what we've done here.
Because me and Hippo, I guess we're just right in the mood to begin recording right now.
And we decided, hey, let's just talk about it ourselves.
Then once we've set our piece, however long it takes to do so,
then we'll turn it off and just put our recording set aside.
Then other people can show up and record amongst themselves.
They can say their things.
And then over the course of this PCP episode,
everyone can have said exactly what they wanted to say,
but without a six way clusterfuck of chat client monstrosity.
That is really annoying to hear anyway.
So I think this is a new format, a new exciting format
that should really evolve the PCP into a new light direction.
So, yeah.
The reason this whole thing has come to pass in this particular way is because
there's time zone kerfuffle that the podcast was supposed to start at 3 p.m.
Eastern Standard Time.
According to Google, I typed in my time
and it came up with, it was 7 p.m.
That was for me when we're, you know, 3 p.m.
So then time zones are annoying.
And then I said, okay, it's time to start.
And everyone's like, we got a whole hour to go.
We're not ready.
And so I just jumped in.
I didn't give a shit.
You know, I think in this day and age of the internet,
like retroactively, if you could make it to our time zones,
it weren't a thing that would probably be a good idea.
Like, you know, there would just be certain parts of the world
where the times of which you get up and go to bed are completely different,
but that would be like way more easy to adjust for, you know?
Like, instead of saying, like, talk into a guy from Britain
and being like, having to have all this confusion about what time it is,
you can simply have a funny conversation about how you go to bed at 2 p.m.
You wake up at 3 a.m.
That's so funny.
But at least all of your appointments can be on time without any complications, you know?
Yeah.
I mean, changing your watch when you land in a plane in a new country
isn't so bad because they usually tell you what time it is.
But like, doing stuff online across the globe,
especially at a time like this where I think the clocks are supposed to go back
an hour or forward an hour depending on where you live,
it's gay.
I hate time.
Time sucks.
You know, that is sort of many reasons why stuff is so hard.
You get into a fundamental issue.
Certainly things among human society is the different layers of civilization
that have to be built on top of one another.
Like, all of technology that we have right now,
all the digital technology that we have,
has to be regulated through laws that were sometimes written 200 years ago,
and things get really blurry in terms of the interpretation, don't you know?
You know, you got like, computers themselves,
which were designed for DOS in the mid-80s,
and they still are fundamentally the same.
I'm not exactly sure about the technicals of this,
but basically the way that computers are now is fundamentally the same
that they were like 30 years ago,
like before the internet was even out,
and so you're just building all this shit into these old systems.
It's like physical tradition.
Right.
And like how, I know that your city of London and stuff
is like laid out in a way that was originally designed for horses, right?
Yeah, I mean, the whole of Britain has got like a lot of winding country roads
and small alleyways and, you know, suburbs.
They're not like grids.
If you ever go on Google Maps and you look around England,
you see the suburbs are like winding roads and going up hills and down hills,
and it's all because they branch off of main roads
that horses use to travel between cities.
Right.
It all starts from a way,
and the difference with America is that they had the technology to plan it out
so that it can make it all efficient with grids and stuff.
Yeah.
I remember you once saying that like when you were like seeing some footage
replaying Grand Theft Auto,
you thought that the cities were laid out that way
because it would be easier to design for a level,
but then you found out that it was just America.
Yeah, I had no idea.
Then you got like modern ass cities like Dubai,
which are designed to be like 21st century from the ground up.
Be like, hey, let's make a really cool looking skyscraper out of nowhere.
Let's just build it.
Although, incidentally, Dubai has its own issues by being in the middle of the desert.
They don't have a central sewage system.
Every building in Dubai has a poop room,
and a poop truck has to come and suck up the poop
and then get up and then get the fuck out of that city,
and sometimes they get backed up in traffic.
Yeah.
That sounds like one of the things,
one of the jokes my dad used to tell me,
or told me at one point in my childhood,
and I just believed because I didn't know any better.
He said that when you flush the toilet,
it goes into a truck and a guy comes and scoops it out
and then drives it into the sea.
I was like, oh.
And then there was one time where the sewage actually got blocked
and they had some guys around.
And I asked dad, is that the poop truck?
And then they laughed.
I was like, that's not real.
I didn't know.
Yeah, my dad was like that too.
That's another reason why stuff gets hard.
When your dads are fucking around with you,
you have no idea when they're being serious.
I remember my dad would just make up things
that aren't real just to be funny.
And it got to the point that I wouldn't believe him,
even when he's saying stuff that is legitimate.
Like, hey, David, you're like roller coaster tycoon.
You should play zoo tycoon and mall tycoon.
I'm like, I just thought he made those up.
I didn't realize there were other tycoon games.
I totally didn't believe him.
So that's why things get hard.
Dad's trying to be funny and just by lying.
I think we should clarify what we're really talking about
when we're talking about hard.
Because things being hard is quite a vague, big topic.
Really what we're talking about is frustratingly complicated.
And stuff that just makes your blood boil in some way.
I mean, maybe not blood boil.
For me, it's always blood boil.
It's frustration at the way things are
and why can't they just be different.
Because we've thought of better ideas since...
Here's the difference between all technology
for most of human history versus technology
since the advent of computers.
Before computers, it's like having a piece of bread
with some butter and some brown sugar on top.
Very bland.
The age of computers is like being given a cinnamon roll
with caramel on top and chocolate and chocolate chips.
But there's a guy constantly causing you to dodge the cinnamon roll.
Like you just want to have that cinnamon roll.
You get the fork.
You plant the fork down.
You plant the fork down on the plate.
But then a dude grabs the plate
and causes your fork to miss the cinnamon roll.
So then you realign, you go for another stab
trying to get your fork in the cinnamon roll.
And the dude just keeps moving the plate around.
And then you try to get a little bit of it
but then he grabs it off your fork.
And then you try to put some cinnamon roll in your mouth
and he grabs it out of your mouth.
And then if you do the wrong thing,
he'll flip the cinnamon roll on the freaking floor
and you got to take it to a repair store to get it fixed
just so you can try and get another cinnamon roll.
That's what the modern age is like.
You are promised more incredible luxury
and incredible inventions
than you've ever been able to conceive of before.
But the actual getting of it
is just several orders of magnitude
more complicated and ridiculous
than anything we can comprehend.
People have often feared the day
when computers could take over humanity
but I think that they basically already have
because they are essentially their own organism.
They are a new branch of life
separate from humans and animals and fungi
that have been created by humans
but are already out of our control.
I remember when the Wi-Fi in my house didn't work one time,
a technician came over to fix it.
He didn't know what was happening.
He didn't know how to fix it
so a senior technician came over to fix it
and he didn't know how to fix it.
How is something that humans made
beyond the reach of humans to comprehend?
That is the world that we are living in today.
Hippo, what do you have to say?
Well, I've got to say I like the cinnamon roll imagery.
I wasn't really sure where you were going with that
but now I understand that it's the complicatedness
of technology that's...
You've got a 500 terabyte hard drive
in the palm of your hand
but you can't get anything on it.
You can't plug it in.
I don't know how to explain it
but you explained it pretty well.
It's easier than it would have otherwise been
but it's still hard.
I think that ties into people in first world countries
still being able to be depressed
even though they don't have it as hard as other people.
It's basically like that, you know?
It doesn't matter how good your life is.
Everything sucks.
Well, something sucks.
It's like what James Rolfe says about DVDs.
He's like, you know, they are better than VHS
but they're more bullshit-y than VHS.
They do a better job but they have way more problems.
And that's what all of technology is basically like.
Whoa, the hell's going on with your mic?
I don't know.
It sounds like bubbling.
Like a fan is slapping something really fast.
Am I still doing that?
Yeah.
It's like a really slow B
and it's caught in a plastic tube.
Is it still happening?
No, it's gone.
I was seeing it on the wave form of my audacity.
I can't wait to...
I think that might just be a loose connection
on your mic or something.
See how hard things are?
He has no idea what's wrong.
It's so easy to relate this to everything that happens in life.
I feel like also on a fundamental level
things are hard because of the basic logic of entropy.
Minute physics is having this series of videos
produced by some entropy specialist guy
and he's explaining the laws of entropy
and how they control all of the universe
and how the universe started off as one condensed ball of energy
and eventually become a bunch of nothingness.
And the only reason that life and even time can occur
is because of all the conflict and shlubla-boobling
that happens in between.
The process from getting to pure energy to pure nothingness
that is where stuff comes from, you know?
It's from the conflict of things happening
that stuff could even happen in the first place.
And that is why things are hard
because of entropy.
Were you actually...
Was that actually a point?
Because I didn't get it.
I don't know, it's up for you to decide.
Oh, okay.
It's hard for me to comprehend that's what it is.
You know, it's kind of weird.
The reason I jumped on this podcast so quickly
is because I was actually in a really good feeling productive mood
so maybe I'm not in the best state of mind
to talk about things being hard.
I don't know, but yeah.
Really, we could jump into the part two of this podcast
where naturally everyone's here.
And this could be like the intro.
Yeah, the intro.
The really long weird intro.
I want to talk directly to you, Hippo.
What are some things in your life that are hard?
I mean, you're trying to start YouTube videos
and getting those popular and you're not making
that much progress very quickly.
That's stupid and gay and that's what YouTube is like.
Talk about that some.
Okay, well, it's hard to get momentum, I suppose.
I mean, even Jon Tron probably wouldn't have gotten
as big as he did if he didn't blow up on Reddit
and then went to Game Grumps.
You know, even someone as funny as that
had to get a big boost out of nowhere.
And I don't think I'm going to get to that size
unless I latch onto one of those big guys
or get blown up on Reddit
or something big happens.
Like, I get a really good video.
But for now, all I can do is just keep going
and, you know, it's fun.
I make enough Patreon to pay rent, so I'm not too worried.
You do? Whoa, that's cool.
Well, it's because I live with my parents at the moment
and they're very nice, so the rent's very reasonable.
That's pretty cool.
You know, like, toward the end of me
trying to make my own channel my full-time thing,
you know, bounce between whether or not it should be
or whether or not I should do the Digibro editing.
Like, the last plan I had in mind
and, like, I was like, if this plan doesn't work at all
then I give up is I'm just going to, like,
make videos collaboratively with other channels
that are big.
Like, I'll literally just message other channels
that are slightly bigger than me
or at least have more fans than me, you know,
and be like, hey, I would like to just straight up
make an entire video and it goes up on your channel.
Like, I just do the whole thing from start to finish.
I figure a lot of channels would be okay
with that having a free video on their channel
that they get to make ad revenue off of
but then it gives exposure.txt for me.
You know, that was all I could think of at that point.
So you just actually go for the whole exposure thing.
Yeah, because I didn't know what else to do.
It was getting hard, man.
Yeah, well, I liked your videos.
I still kind of wish you were still doing your own stuff.
Yes.
The Prince of Persia one was, like,
I think the last one I remember watching.
Yes.
I want to see more of those game things.
Me too.
Yeah, another thing being hard,
having more things to do in your life
than you have life for.
Yeah, that's another issue.
I think we all know that sort of feeling of...
Yeah.
There's not enough time in a day to get multiple things done.
You have to just stick with one,
otherwise you'll get nothing.
Right.
You'll get nothing done.
One thing I have very specific trouble with is writing.
I spend, like, a month or two months writing a script,
two days editing, two days recording all the audio.
Oh, recording audio.
And then one week or maybe less than a week to edit it.
Probably a month to edit it, actually.
But the writing takes a demonstrably large amount of time
compared to someone like Digi, who just thinks of it,
writes it down, and then that's it.
Yeah.
It's too quick for me.
I don't think he goes quite as fast as he sometimes indicates
that he does, or at least lately.
I think he maybe puts more polishing time into stuff,
or maybe he...
I think it's more like he stews on it,
writes a paragraph, stews or something.
I don't know.
I actually have not watched him writing,
but I think that's what it's like.
Anyway.
You should put a secret camera in his room.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
Make that...
Put that on Davoo.
It goes to Saturn.
Make that a...
Make that a Patreon reward here.
It's access to the 24-7 DigiCam.
So, uh, Mages here now.
Say hi.
Hi.
Okay, cool.
So, we were talking about why things are so hard,
and we were specifically talking about the production
of video making, how Hippo in particular,
you seem to have a huge problem with writing.
Like, it's just kind of hard to do.
Yeah.
I don't know what it is.
I think it's just...
I like working in a straight line,
like chronologically.
I go through the thing.
I don't like skipping a part
that I'm having trouble with
and coming back to it later.
I don't do that either, really.
It's like, if I can't think of a good way
to flow from this paragraph to that point
in a way that's either funny or interesting or good,
then I get stuck on it for hours,
and I tab over to anything else
to distract myself from the fact
that I can't figure out what I'm doing.
And that just goes on for weeks and months,
and I hate it.
And you say you've spent like two days
doing the voiceover as well?
Well, yeah, I mean, I did the Rayman
I'm working on at the moment,
and I finally finished that script,
and then in one day afterwards,
I recorded the whole thing.
Brilliant.
I've still got to do the live-action stuff,
but I sat down and I just...
I spoke...
It was actually the best voiceover recording session
I've ever had, so that was good.
Not really, you know?
I only just, like, now got comfortable
with reading scripts,
like, almost comfortable, at least.
I still have not really had an occasion
where I have a whole thing,
and I record it, and it comes out ideally
on the first try,
but I'm at least now able to, like,
read something short on the third attempt,
and it comes out well,
and I don't feel too stressed out about it, you know?
I don't know how many people have watched
a lot of my older, like, 2014 videos
where my voice sounds way different
and sounds like I'm choking on a big, fat dick,
and it was the most annoying thing ever.
It was stressing the fuck out of me.
I mean, I had my braces removed,
like, five or six videos into my full-time YouTubing,
so that, like, screwed up my ability
to speak clearly in a comfortable manner,
trying to strike a balance between
sounding comfortable and sounding...
like, sounding natural and, like,
annunciating all of your syllables
is a dichotomy that you sometimes have to, like,
teeter on and make sacrifices and trade-offs in.
And, uh, gosh, yeah,
I feel like most people either start off terrible
and never improve that much with voiceover
or start off pretty good and get a lot better.
I feel like there's only some people
with an excessive amount of determination
who start off bad, like me,
and then get pretty good, as I would now say I am.
Yeah, uh...
I do like your voice in your...
in the way you explain things, especially the annunciation,
like, making the syllables deliberate.
It's different from just chatting with somebody,
because even across the room, they can tell what you're saying,
but a microphone has bad hearing.
It needs a lot of...
you need to be right up close to it
and to make sure you say everything correctly.
Otherwise, it won't know what to tell a computer.
Yeah.
Yeah, and you have to make sure you don't make weird noises.
Like, with the clicking of the tongue,
sometimes some people find it really annoying and gross.
Yeah, so...
What do you mean?
No, not that sort of thing, but it's just like...
I can't even describe it, but some people see that.
It's the little lip smack when you open your mouth
after a period of time.
Yeah, it's also weird and gross.
I don't like it.
I try to cut out those out from my audio,
which makes audio editing a lot more annoying for me,
because I usually do that, so I have to...
Especially since my voice is so quiet,
you can't really mask it with background music,
because the whole volume level of everything
is kind of small, so if I make it louder,
you can hear the lip smacks even more,
so I have to cut them out.
Yeah, and I have to also cut out by my inhales and exhales.
Apparently, they're quite loud.
No one knows, though, because I edit them out.
It's really annoying, because I breathe all the time,
so that's a lot of editing.
Whoa!
Who knew?
Specifically, people with small voices
at audio editing is really hard,
because if you're loud,
if you're like Nate, you can go,
whaa!
And then when you look at noise removal
and making it sound good,
you really don't need to do much,
because if you've got a voice like mine,
even when I'm trying really hard to make it sound loud,
there's a lot of noise that gets picked up in the background
because the microphone's gain is turned up
so that they can hear me,
so there's extra problems
if you're not shouting all the time.
I feel you.
Smee and Gib, Small Voice Club.
Yeah.
Well, I'm just in too positive of a mood
to go on for very long about things being hard.
I don't know, I'm just not really into it at the moment.
Are you thinking it's quite hard
to think of things to talk about in this podcast?
I mean, talking specifically about video-making
or just things that you're trying to...
We were talking about anything.
Anything.
So if there's things that make life hard,
what are you doing in your life, Mage?
Oh, I want to make...
I've been working on a comic sort of
kind of like on six or seven pages now
and just everything.
Everything about making a comic is hard.
I thought it could do it, I thought...
Hey, you know, some people start off...
crappy and the improver over time because they draw the comic and stuff and I thought you know I
could do it I'm slightly better than some people when they started off so I kind of have a little
you know um you know just a advantage of it and so I started making the comic and then just I just
realized I don't know how to lay out the panels I don't know where to place the speech bubbles
writing dialogue is hell and I just can't draw certain angles or like proportions are off like
most people see my finished art but they never see the art I scrap and I scrap so much art
because I just can't get the proportions right and it's ugly and it's gross and it's pissing me off
and I just hate my life I hate everything I quit goodbye well before you go would you say the
like the drawing stuff are coming up with like panels and and things would you say that's like
it's hard because you're already decently good at drawing so like learning something like it's
making comics is a whole different style of of drawing and since you're so good you have like
high standards for your finished works it's weird to just like settle for anything that isn't perfect
um kind of I guess I mean the whole topic on learning something new is a whole different
issue but the panels um I guess yeah when I put my art into panels or you know into comic form I
see it and I kind of feel like I could have done better this doesn't look like it as good as it
should have been oh backgrounds that reminds me I I had like a few month hiatus on one page
because I couldn't do a simple background for it and and then I came back and one day I was like
you know what I'm gonna do it and then I did it and kind of look crap but it better than it was
before and I was like and I'm gonna settle with this no one's perfect yeah it's I I particularly
have trouble like I've tried to draw comics I've tried to do everything everyone else has done
because I like I'm very competitive so you know with Tom and Ben being comic guys I tried drawing
a comic and I didn't like it so it was just because it was it was too hard to to instantly be great at
it it was too you know I knew I would have had to like work at it for ages I've been doing Inktober
as well and it was too hard to keep up with that because each drawing I was like okay I've got to
try and make it better than the last one more more properly drawn more clean and stuff and then as
the days went on it became harder and harder to to work that hard on a single drawing for a day
and also do anything else and so I just stopped doing it but really it is because I was making
it too hard on myself like I didn't need to put that much effort into the Inktober's I could have
just done funny little scribbles it's hard it's hard to settle for less that's what I'm thinking
um in drawing comics I stumble at drawing the same thing more than once that's when everything
falls apart oh this thing I drew I have to draw it again this time in a slightly different position
I feel you that's the end that you know just can't do it anymore yeah what's worse for me is I never
get like the face is similar or the eye shape or or something because every single time I draw the same
character I give them like different eyes or different nose or something like that and it's
just yeah it's so bothersome give hurt dot JP JP egg it's a credit those character designs are very
consistent the what hey you know you were talking about voice acting I was talking about voice acting
you know the thing about voice acting and uh getting frustrated and it that makes it really
annoying is that all of your emotions come out through your voicing whether or not you want
them to and that's why it's such a temperamental thing when I have to read a script and like you
know a lot of people they write scripts that are basically like hey everyone here's this thing it
came out in 1992.5 and you know that you can read in any sort of emotion that you want but when you
want to say something meaningful or something or something like deep or something that's supposed
to sound like it comes from some sort of personification of you you got to get the acting
just right and acting and reading a script can just really mess around with me because it like
the first time I'm going through I haven't like quite gotten down the flow of the thing yeah like
I would have would have written down like a like a paragraph and then I read the whole thing out
loud and I'm like wait a minute I didn't put any of the emphasis on the right words and it
I gotta do it again then when you go through it the second time I'm kind of getting a little
bit annoyed at myself I'm getting kind of tired of the script and so I'm getting a little bit
agitated and the agitation ruins everything so it's like it's almost like there's a limited
number of attempts you can do on a script before it's like worn out it's like removing and reapplying
tape onto a piece of paper you can know if you do it too many times you could never do it again
so you better get it right the first couple of times that's how it is for me or at least that's
how it was for me still kind of is it takes an unbelievable amount of very intense concentration
to have your have your mind be into the right lucid state of emotion to be able to pull off such a
feat yeah I know that oh you go now you go ahead okay well I was gonna say um I have that similar
sort of trouble but it's it's more like I forget to to act I forget to have emotion in my script
like I'm just reading it like and then blah blah and then you know I was like oh wait I should have
done a silly voice for that because that was a like it was a moment so I got to do it again with
silly voice and sometimes the silly voice seems forced and like that is dumb this is a bad this
is a bad joke it doesn't work I'm not I can't create the right funny sound for this word
particular word like sometimes I can create a funny sound just on its own but I'm trying to say
a word at the same time sometimes it just doesn't doesn't flow right so I have to cut that whole
paragraph out of the thing it is indeed very dependent on the entire writing style of what
you're trying to read yeah you guys like do proper videos and stuff me I struggled with
just like the basic videos I did a q&a and all I had to do I didn't have to do any sort of funny
voices or anything all I had to do was like sound interested in what I'm talking about and the
thing is like I have trouble pronouncing certain things and I had to redo my q&a like the recording
so many times that the end result just kind of I sounded dead just so uninterested so dead in
everything I said but by that time I was just so tired rereading the same things over and over again
and I just wanted that video to finally come out because it's been delayed for like such a long time
and I just I settled I'm not happy with it but I settled
the one thing about like recording audio for a video that I really hate is that you feel like
you got to do it all in one go like in one day like because the microphone is going to be set
up a certain way that day you're going to be sitting in a certain position that day recording it
you don't want to have to you don't want to have to stop and like you know even just take a break
because you're you're going to come back you're going to have either more air in your lungs or
something and it's going to sound weird or different and I don't like it I I guess it's not too bad if
you're like more energetic the second time but I like I like it when I can get most of it correct
in within a few hours and yeah same it's it's really good when that happens I was I was dancing
I was jumping around after after I recorded the Rayman thing because I did a whole bit where
I go more insane and more like more broken as that as it goes along and by the end I was doing a full
blown broken matte impression and it was really good oh my gosh yeah that's a secret spoiler I guess
I could cut that out but you know whatever PCP fans deserve to know spoilers spoilers uh well
you know this has been about 30 minutes it's about as long as I was expecting part one of the
PCP would be so anything else you too I came in at the very tail and I thought it was going to start
like right now at the moment at the round hour at like three well if you have more to say we can
keep going for a bit nah I complained enough for the day mage could be the one who can appear in
both parts yeah so what we're doing is that it's just me and hippo and then the other guys are
gonna show up they're gonna do their part they don't even realize what we're doing they don't
even realize that we're recording this whole first part it's too hard for them to read that we
we said we were gonna do yes I said we were gonna do it or I proposed it and uh no one read it so
we just did it without them uh so what you could do is you could appear in both parts and just say
the same stuff twice and they won't even know yes you should definitely do that now all right
everyone uh we're gonna move on to part two just imagine a kc nice that is flipping the
camera around and we transition into the next part goodbye bye hello everyone and welcome to
part two of this week's episode of the procrastinator's podcast we by the way have no idea what the
other guys talked about so judge us with mercy if we are redundant or talk about the same
shit because they didn't tell us and we don't want to know we didn't care to ask what happened in
part one anyway it's me the best guy ever uh we got uh did you bro hey endless jizz yep lethal mage
man greetings and tom oliver i am here hooray yes celebration all around and mage is our undercover
agent for what they talked about in the first part if that is relevant that's true they didn't
know that you were gonna you were gonna tell all it was gonna be an expose anyway so again
thing is uh for some reason the topic is uh why is everything so fucking hard and why can't everything
be easy uh and i'll tell you preach it yeah what say that again preach it i said i said hallelujah
okay jesus yeah oh baby jesus everything's too hard it's very true i was watching um uh
metalocalypse recently i've gotten really big into metalocalypse over the last week again and i
happened to see this part where maybe the best character william murder face murder face murder
face uh is walking along and he's he's just real upset because he wants everything in life to be
easy and he sings this amazing song about how everything in life deserves to be handed to him
on a silver platter and anything that takes effort isn't worth doing and i uh agree he is my role
model in that aspect he really makes a strong case for it where you're like yeah yeah why isn't
everything easy fuck this fuck everything yeah it's it's tough to disagree so uh
we're just i want to just talk about all the things that are way too fucking hard and aren't
worth doing uh number one is making this podcast every week it takes so much work to get you
fucking people in here to talk about shit it's a nightmare waking up in time when like the rest
of you are doing this let me like i'm like i'm like i'm like laying in my bed on my on my fucking
on my 10 million dollar air mattress from the kickstarter in my fucking castle and you know
my fucking my laptop starts yelling at me nate's figured out how to make the laptop yell at me it's
it was really yes i have like get up and go to the podcast i'm like no just just getting up and waking
up and getting on the podcast it's like a monumental hercules and it's like the the 12
labors of hercules just to get on this podcast and entertain you freaks believe me i completely
empathize with how much work you guys all put into letting me edit this podcast every week
it's it's tough man you don't understand the effort it takes to have faith that you won't
fuck it up it's a big it's a big hurdle you know fucking talk about effort i'm at work
right now hiding in the corner so the fucking camera can't see me dicking around in the middle
of my rounds at work to record this part why do you think i'm never fucking here because i have to
yeah he's just at work god damn why is work so hard why do i have to slave but why is my life
a burden upon myself well i didn't choose to be born and yet here i am yeah we're going off the
deep end right that's that's true uh you know we we didn't ask for any of the struggles in life
that our parents forced upon us by selfishly producing us and here we are having to pay the
piper every fucking day having to punch that clock only to die one day and making it all completely
pointless why are we here only to suffer it's true i agree sometimes let's let's all just kill
ourselves right now and that's that's pretty easy this is really dark and i like it but even
killing yourself is fucking hard it'd be oh it's so hard not worth doing it's it's just like in that
episode of paranoia agent where those three suicidal dudes which is like the best episode of that show
or any show by the way where they just get together and try to kill themselves but it's such a fucking
chore man it's it's rough isn't it heavily implied that they are already at the end they do seem to
be ghosts but it's unclear when or if that happened you know it's it's mysterious which i like
yeah everyone should watch it anyway it's great you should at least that episode well i don't know
the little slugger's cool i don't i don't think spoiling that episode takes anything away from it
well that's a whole other argument spoiled something that's ambiguous anyways you you would
have to sit on it and come that's a good point just to know what i haven't seen the last three
episodes been procrastinating on that so don't spoil you've been procrastinating for for 10 years
how is that show now it shows for like 2004 i didn't know it existed up until like last year
and then you've been procrastinating for a year yes tisk tisk that's still pretty long well whatever
i i i haven't finished uh that's that's right that's right i uh whatever there's tons of stuff
i also haven't finished they started bakimono gatsuri being one of them that i've watched episode
like one through three for like like eight times like fucking eight times that i've never gotten
passed at uh because it's too fucking hard to make time to watch it oh my god watching
shit is the worst fucking burden there's so it never ends the the pile of the mountain of
stuff that you need to fucking consume and get inside your brain you can't ever chip away at it
they keep making new stuff faster than any man could possibly watch all the curse of the internet
could be able to become acutely aware of how much shit you're never going to be able to understand
about our job they think that we just make stuff now this is this is like two full-time jobs because
half my job is making stuff the other half is consuming stuff it's two jobs that should be full
time and i'm trying to bounce them out it's impossible by long and far the hardest thing
about my job is watching anime because like yeah like that sounds insane it sounds like
people will think that you're like that sounds retarded but it's totally true right well because
i don't know until i watch a show if i'm gonna have something to say about it right so like for me
like the most grueling part of my job is deciding which show i'm gonna watch because i'm so afraid
to watch something you know for four hours and then find out that i didn't have enough to say
about it to make a video and then that's just four hours i mean i can somewhat justify it and like
okay well at least i've expanded my knowledge of anime in some way you know at least this contributes
to my overall ability to to pull from different places to to have ideas but and your your life
goal of watching all anime right that's still on the table right i don't know if i want to watch all
like book i'm glad you changed when i was like 10 years old and i first discovered the anime and
i was like i'm gonna watch all the anime in the entire world i definitely and by the little
did you sample every anime in the entire world like every every single night when i like when i
get off sony vegas for the night finally and i and i get down on my couch and i start thinking
okay i should watch something well let's see what what's this what's this black mirror show on
netflix no wait there's this other show on sci-fi about the channel zero show no wait there's probably
a new south park out no way isn't there like haven't i missed like 10 my little pony episodes
no wait i should have watched this entire fucking series over here there's five anime i just for
the weebcast i had to watch like 40 fucking shows and and the thing about it is with anime with the
yeah it's understandable with with anime specifically i like i've gotten into star trek recently in a
big way and the great thing about star trek is this people just talking and you really don't
need to pay that much attention when you got a show in gook you gotta read the fucking subtitles
you gotta watch the animation because it involves you cannot do anything else while you're watching
anime and that's it's such a fucking pain in the ass strenuous thing and you know what you want to
just learn japanese but that's fucking hard to exactly so hard god learning japanese if there's
one thing that i have the biggest chip on my shoulder about how hard it is it's learning japanese
because the spoken dialect is easy as shit they have an alphabet that's easy as shit
but then they have the kanji and it's just thousands and thousands of meaningless fucking symbols
that not only not only do they all look exactly the same but they all have a specific order that
they have to be drawn in true i know yeah i took chinese and it's the same written thing and it's
bullshit the fact that you have to draw it in the right order or it's wrong and it's oh my god it's
fucking stupid and you know what sucks is that your brain hates you because every year you put off
learning japanese your brain becomes more set in his ways it becomes harder to learn another language
i know it's just like you know it's the worst learning any language is fucking unbearably
impossible like i took french in high school i don't remember any of it i took spanish in college
i don't remember any of it you know i'm watching the anime is i'm trying to i'm i'm trying to
understand the language sometimes i feel like i'm understanding the language every once in a while
i'll pick out like a like a like a kudasai or some word that i understand that i'm like yes
yes i got it i can i can watch this whole anime now without reading the subtitles but it's all for
not because it never stays it's important like learning anything and i fucking hate myself
the saddest part for me is that i like for years i've had this dream that one day i'll learn how to
read japanese well enough that i'll be able to get into manga because so much manga doesn't get
translated most of the the really good stuff the stuff that i really want to read isn't getting
translated but on some level i'm sounds like a grass is always greener so yeah oh they're only
translating the bad stuff i'm glad that i can't read japanese because if i could then that would
just be thousands of manga i now have to read you know now i have a whole new world of shit i have to
do you know well you know i mean uh i don't know if this is true but in like shown and jump
everything is hiragana uh in a dude where there's there's a lot yeah is it seriously i had no idea
yeah well yeah for whatever all children's manga have little furigana over the over the
bleach isn't for children don't say that yeah but uh but yeah i mean it makes it easier to to learn
to like you can it's an easy way to learn kanji by doing that but i one time tried i opened up a
volume of inuyasha because i like i was on this uh it was like how to learn japanese through manga
like a thing and there was all these different manga and inuyasha was there and i was like oh i
know inuyasha so i opened up page one and i quickly realized that i just straight up didn't know any of
the words so that was no help oh that's the thing the i mean like jesse was saying before uh if you
watch a lot of anime you can learn a bunch of phrase i remember distinctly i learned the word
daijobu before i studied japanese and i was like it's because uh it's because the fourth opening
of one piece kokoro cheese starts with daijobu and it's okay and as the subtitles i get this word
now but uh when it comes to like constructing sentences or being able to you know reverse
engineer them which is what you're doing in your brain when you're translating from another language
to english it's impossible if you don't sit down and say that shit have you ever the scene in a movie
that i always bought you ever watched the 13th warrior no it's a movie with antonio benders it's
about like he's like an arab guy i don't know why he's an arab guy but he's an arab guy and he has to
like hang out with all these nordic people and there's a scene where he's like sitting around
at the campfire over the course of like a couple weeks and he just learns nordic just by listening
to them and i'm like that's such bullshit no one can fucking do that to this day that pisses me off
i mean for what it's worth i am perfectly capable of watching like a children's anime and
understanding all of it like i don't think the language is hard it's just the it's just reading
it that's impossible and in particularly in inuyasha's case because the scenes take place in ancient
japan there's a lot of ancient dialect which is why i could not understand what i was looking at in
that particular case mage can you tell me about that because i i still i don't believe anyone i think
you're lying i think there's a conspiracy to make me feel stupid so please explain how you learned
english from cartoons okay when i was little like four years old or something i kind of broke the
video tape player thingy by thinking it needs food so i fed it stuff
so my parents got cable it was cartoon network holy shit yeah they got the cartoon network
so i watched cartoon network and everything was in english haza and me a four year old was entertained
by moving pictures and i didn't care that didn't understand the language but over time i started
picking up stuff here and there and by seven or eight i could speak english fine enough for what
it's worth when you're like four that's like the stage where you're learning language either way
like i mean arguably we all learned english from watching cartoons and you know in our parents and
you know language and then having a world just proof that we get dumber as we get older because
if you can learn it like i've been watching anime for like 15 years and i still haven't learned any
japanese ever in like four words i i also started learning german from tv again just at a later time
at around 12 years old or so um i discovered that i have a german channel and there was anime that's
the first time i discovered anime was at eight years old never mind anywho either way um so i
started learning uh german and everything was fine until they canceled the uh or at least we didn't
get the channel anymore we weren't supposed to get the channel in the first place apparently
but still so i took german in school and the german classes didn't teach me quite as much as tv
taught me and it's just because like it kind of feels like when you're hearing it it's kind of like
you're hearing it in practice like you hear how it's spoken how it's used in uh conversations it's
never you cannot substitute that with uh learning from books and stuff and i had such a difference
with like um students who in my class who learned english just from books had like such a thick accent
and they couldn't grasp such subtleties and weird stuff that's going on with english like let's say
the word knife it starts with k they can't they don't have the intuition to know that the case
and i did and yeah so i was kind of a prodigy up until like the very last years of school where
i became at the top of the class but not the best uh so yeah this is supposed to be a complaining
about things being too hard yes this is bragging why would a genius i am so much smarter than americans
it's so hard to live up to european standards i didn't ask you to tell us what a genius you are
that's my job because i'm the smartest guy everyone else is dumb compared to me i'm not a genius i've
learned english from cartoons you just called yourself a prodigy you fucking did it
no in comparison to the people in my class in comparison to me in comparison to me you piece of
shit i'm trying to fucking strangle you well okay you know i did want to say that i had i had that
very same experience um in fact just the other day i was reflecting on like if i was learning english
from a textbook i wouldn't be able to speak it uh like colloquially at all it would be a total
clusterfuck like people who are learning the language because when i was in japan um the rudimentary
japanese that i learned was like in no way would i be able to pass for like just having a conversation
even knowing a decent amount of vocabulary and grammar and conjugation and shit it's just like i
no matter what i did i would sound like a weirdo outsider in any context i mean i was a beginner
language podcast but i guess language is the most hard thing that i'm the most upset about how hard
it is you know i i thought this was going to go more towards uh jobs and money and that kind of
stuff because that is what's on my mind mortality we did talk about right in the beginning so like
we can only go up from there that's like the hardest thing that's true well nate i've spent the past
probably 11 or 12 hours building is no god more than that i've spent like the last 16 hours building
a spreadsheet and i've been having a good time i feel building a snowman no i feel mostly dead
inside but but i feel like i'm also doing the thing that my that i was built to do uh so why don't
you tell us about the experience of being a horrible horrible corporate corporate slut yeah
well uh yeah in fact i was just talking to a friend yesterday about how when i made the podcast
i felt such a sense of euphoria and nothing about the video is impressive
but i didn't even think about it it just my body just did them the mechanics of it
automatically and it's because i've been doing it for years now and i know what to do but more
importantly it's because doing it in itself is rewarding and feels good and i like doing it and
that is of course completely opposed to what i do most of my time during the week or you know the
40 hours out of my week i have to spend at work 40 hours plus probably more like 60 with
all the other shit but i mean i have to go into work and do my job and i go home but that time
is not spent doing things that i am interested in or i'm particularly want to do for much longer
and my my my only goal going there is to you know do my work at a decent level and pacify everyone
until such time that i can no longer be forced to do these things because and the it's all because
i have to be able to make enough money to do you know youtube and and other stuff that i want to do
and if we lived in star trek world i would be able to do my shit right fucking now you know it's
the same with my little pony actually you just you you can pursue the things that you want to do
and that's just how society is set up to reward the things that not not only i mean come on people
not only is it the thing i like to do but you've seen the results of what i can do when i am given
the time and the ability to do these things it's unquestionable that my performance is so much
better when i'm doing these things and i am so much more of an asset to humanity when i'm doing
these things instead of these fucking yeah that's everyone go to my fucking patreon give me money
it's like there's this guy jock fresco and he's like 90 something years old now but he yeah he
might be dead i don't even know i've been like read up on him in like a couple years but ever
since the 70s he's been talking about like this like society he designed where you don't need money
and everything is just done by machines and like nobody will listen to him and he's like old and
crotchy now you're just like fucking everyone's retarded i have the answer and nobody will listen
to me i'm just like that's the fucking hardest thing ever when you have the answer and everyone
just like yeah but no that's true that is true i'd like to hear more about his philosophy at some
point it's pretty cool he's just like science is more important than politics and if we measure
everything we can measure how much the carrying capacity of the earth like how much resources
are on earth and how to distribute it so everyone can survive and then we can computerize and
digitize everything so all the base tasks that we have to do can be done by machines instead
and then people can just pursue higher education and do things that are intellectually and creatively
stimulating and i'm like you see that's the thing yeah because i i just did a vlog on this on on
bestie boy my other channel about um fuck i don't even remember what it was about but it was it was
talking about an issue of how uh we are oh god i'm completely blanking i forgot what i was fucking
saying quick tom cover uh you are going to be talking about how we are like forced to do all
this shit that we don't want to do and like i don't i don't even watch the vlog about the vlog it
was about the heat death of the universe rapidly approaching and it was no matter how much humanity
progresses we will ultimately die in the long run oh oh i remember what i was going to say it was just
about how uh inevitably we will reach a point i mean if we don't all die first where uh every
single job that is currently done by humans will be done by machines and what are we how are we
gonna choose to live are we going to let everyone die because well they don't they're not the most
efficient tool for doing this so we might as well you know fuck them they're let them die or do we
want to structure our society in a way that this technology supports the the human drive to create
explore here's the thing though think about this yeah this has already happened once like back in the
day the industrial revolution happened and since everything was based on industry there was there
was a legit a split for a while if you read up on it there was like are we gonna shorten the work
day to three days a week or are we going to invent new ways to make people fucking suck balls and
do this shit oh i wonder which one we chose and here we are so if you think that this
mechanization is going to lead us to some utopia no no no they're going to find a way
to have us toil away do some new shit that we can't digitize yet now i don't believe that
that has to be the case i think that it has to be the case but i think there's definitely like a
structure in place that would crumble if right people actually actualize their own potential
examining examining how making excel spreadsheet so the boss man could be
happy yeah examining how that process uh has affected humans and how we've dealt with it
previously is definitely a good tool to predict what we might do in the future but when we get to
the point where it's either change the system or every literally everyone is obsolete except
maybe a handful of people who are running the whole thing at that point we have to make some
i would rely on people's moral compass to say that human life has value it's generally a good
thing it would be best if we kept people alive and didn't just let them all die as machines start
doing their jobs and they just can't afford the abundant resources that are available now
because human labor is worthless i hope that we can get over that hump you know what else is
because otherwise life would be pretty hard what's that digi yeah you know what else is way
too hard are you talking about my dick is my dick and here's why that's a problem
because my dick is so hard but i have i have nothing to put it in because dating is the hardest
thing oh god oh what what is more time consuming and asinine and difficult than trying to find
i'll tell you exactly i'll tell you exactly what's more difficult than that it's trying to do
literally anything and having five different fucking girlfriends at once all messaging you
at fucking 24 seven every hour of every day they just want to talk about bullshit there's
fucking 50 of them they never shut up i can't do anything you know it was great you know it was
great jesse uh a few when i was at college i had a i had an elaborate spider's net of
fuck buddies strewn about my college campus and it was great because i never talked to any of them
except to just arrange sex that's the only thing we did that's that's like it's like that but on a
global scale is my method but they all okay all right i'm just i'm so goddamn cool that they all
just fall in love with me and they all just want to talk to me all the time and i just want to blow
my brains out it's not worth it i'd rather i'd rather blow off my dick and blow off my brain
and die it's a delicate balance making them uh want to have sex with you but never speak but
also not like me that's what i'm trying to write right the problem i'm having is that every once
in a while i think huh maybe i should try to get a girlfriend and then i remember that to do that i
have to like i have to put in a cons a concentrated effort into actually like like somehow obtaining
a relationship because you don't even it's true it's not possible to just do that in in the course
of my everyday life you know like some people like when you're in when you're in school if you're
in college if you have a job you run into people you see people around you you might have to talk
to someone as a result of i don't know doing a project together or something yeah but if you
live in a house by you know with just you and like six bros and all you do is work at home
and you never go out anywhere then there's no reason i would ever encounter a woman
unless i was seeking out a woman which means that yeah which means that i have to take time
out of my schedule out of my day out of my work out of everything i've got going on all the irons
i've gotten the fire i got to lift all those irons out of the fire temporarily just in just
so i can even try to go and talk to a woman and then i just hear a cat where's the kitty where is
it i think it's amazing yeah talk about how great cats are that's the new topic cats cats have no
difficulty with anything cats the whole life's true you know digi uh you're you're absolutely
right about this and this has been one of the greatest struggles this is probably the big one
forget death i mean what what did what did the director of silent hill to say uh every human
is possessed it's compelled by only two factors sex and death they they make up the you know the
core of the of the human soul our fear of one and the quest for the other and it's absolutely true
that they're you know with our current society especially with with people who work the way we
do our jobs are basically isolationists they don't involve interaction with anyone except maybe a
select few number of people and our only way to satisfy this beastial urge inside of us
is to fucking devote massive amounts of time to fucking doing this shit because that's the
thing about the normie life that's so different when you're a normie you're you're you're grinding
your your uh your you know social skills most of that time all that time is being you're you're
taking levels in in you know socialization i'm just saying being involved that i'm not saying
i'm just saying exposure time yeah like exposure time that you're out doing this stuff
that's what i'm talking about well i just think like i think you know when i was in high school i
saw it as like oh oh ben's oh ben's muted uh when i was in high school i saw it more like um you
know i'm awkward i don't know how to talk to to girls i don't know how to do this and that you
know oh it'd be weird oh i don't want to have my heart broken none of that is what i'm concerned
about now it's just time the amount of time it takes to go out of your way to seek someone
it's something i never would have thought about before you know like growing up i was so concerned
with the the usual stuff like oh you know is she gonna like me now i'm like am i gonna have to
like actually spend hours of my day swiping in a different i don't even know which direction is
approved on tinder uh which are the right dog always to the right okay so you know how do i
actually have to spend hours of my day swiping on on like weird fractured information of other
people you know i've sat around trying to think of if i started a dating profile what would i write
on it and i have no idea i don't know how to describe myself other than like through nothing
ganzo otaku right i'm a big internet celebrity that's the thing what you need is when you're
boiling yourself down to like especially for shit like this it's like how am i going to attract someone
to be interested in me that's the thing like i don't understand how did you can be saying it's
hard to attract people with his audience when i've been doing it for years with my tiny microscopic
audience compared to his i wouldn't even be talking about like my audience that's all you gotta do
you gotta utilize the fame all you gotta do is make a tweet and say hey people who follow me on
twitter one of you has to have a vagina i'm famous we'll see the thing is let's let's all tweet
about this after we're done here and see what kind of results we get i'm like building myself up because
when i think of how i describe myself i think every every every person who likes one of my tweets
if i see in their picture that they're a girl i make a mental note and i write it down to that's
the effort i'm talking about that's the that's the going through the trouble that i'm that i'm so
against well i mean it's sometimes like that's the whole thing is like is what's the is there
a difference between something being too hard and something requiring a lot of effort are they
synonymous well they're they are there is a lift to murder face man i i would agree there is a subtle
difference it's a lot easier for me to do a lot of work if it's just something i want to do like i
just said i've been building a spreadsheet for like 14 straight hours and i it's probably gonna
take another 14 to finish it and it's just so easy for me to zone out and plug names into a
spreadsheet because it's like this is something that only i can do and i enjoy doing it and it
you know it's you know it's a good way to pass the time and i don't have to think about anything
i don't have to think about existential dread or you know like the effort it would take to get a
girlfriend i could just plug away at the spreadsheet and not think about the world at all it's you
know you brought up you brought up zoning out which is the same thing i brought up before i
wonder if it's an issue of shifting your ability to do these things from your conscious like intense
effort mind into sort of a that your subconscious are able to sort of do it without really putting
the the the forcing yourself to do it into it yeah maybe maybe that's relevant to ride a bike
or when you uh enter a car you know what to do after doing it like hundreds of times yeah i think
i think my two favorite states of mind are either absolutely no thoughts just like doing a thing
that's menial which is why i love making lists so much because that's just like there's no brain
activity there it's just structure i'll say and and the other one is like when i'm writing and that's
where it's like super heightened brain and it's like thousands of thoughts happening at once and
all of them are beautiful and it's like life affirming and makes me feel like a genius anything
between those two states is just shit it's you know uh thinking about death and how i'm spinning
my wheels towards it to get on to another sort of topic another big problem uh about that's that's
so hard that there's literally nothing you can do about it it's just dealing with other people
and having to put up with their bullshit that they do to you all the time and let me give an example
and it was just i i went for a run because i'm trying to be a good person and better myself and
not be a fat sack of shit taxing our health care system in america uh and i'm out doing my thing
and on my way back i'm exhausted from running i'm walking out i'm i'm you know running on the side
of the road across a uh an exit of uh of like a pizza place these and these it's fucking family
and their fucking station wagon comes barreling down to like 30 miles an hour and i'm i'm like
i'm not like half a mile before they fucking get to me i'm in the middle of the road and he fucking
smashes like he smashes on the accelerator coming towards me faster coming out of this
fucking exit of this this this fat factory and i'm just like i'm just screaming at this telling
what are you doing what the fuck are you doing i'm right here running in the middle of the road
don't you see me you stupid piece of human garbage you are in your whole family or cancer
you should all be fucking die i hope you choke on your pizza you fat sacks of shit yeah so
you know all that stuff all that stuff yeah people are in annoyance like there's like a 95
percentage of everyone in the world just sucks and shouldn't be talked to ever should be euthanized
slight addendum would would put that spit on it i think euthanized is too peaceful for them i think
that yeah that's why people should have their heads
wopped off with a rusty fucking machete in the town square i don't really have run-ins with
annoying people outside the internet but dealing with people the internet is definitely a point
that you don't run into anybody so i mean that's the plus side to your isolation is you're isolated
yeah i should have scouted those but you're also isolated from all the retards and there's a lot
more retards out there i'll tell you that i should have scouted that little that like
five-year-old daughter in the backseat for a potential girlfriend i should have
well i blew it man i blew my chance yeah i like that like i should have offered in trade as as a
piece of agreement he has to offer me his first born daughter you sons of bitches get out of the
road by the way i'm single you know that that makes me upset too me and me and uh um and a bunch
and everyone else in the house we all took this quiz that monkey had taken on his uh on his show
it was like a normie quiz like it's see how normie you are right and like monkey and and
basically everybody else got like slightly strange right like uh you know you're you're not quite
normie but then me and victor and shade we all got normie victor and shade got chat status
they were straight up chat and i got normie they've got girlfriends so that's like thousand
points right well that's the thing i'm looking at this i'm like man i ended up being a normie
and mostly just because i have lots of money and like i'm not i'm not ugly i have lots and
lots of money and i have had sex before and that's enough to get you pretty much to normie status
but i was like how can i possibly be a normie when i feel like this this this this alien creature
you know who's in his room talking about how hard it is to go outside and socialize with anybody
how can this possibly be normie but that's what that's what you get for putting your faith in an
online quiz well sure i mean there's that but i also feel like this is the world we live in now
this is what it like normies now are people who don't even leave their house and talk to other
people you know maybe are they though i don't know maybe the classical idea of the normie it
doesn't even like maybe they're not even out there roaming you know i've been outside sometimes i don't
see a lot of people out there where the hell are they where are the normies if they're supposedly
outside having normie has changed if i don't think you're a normie i think like because of like you
know technology and stuff everyone is connecting more via the internet than real life and like people
don't go outside and just hang out like that's not which i hate by the way how the fuck am i gonna
know if a girl is fuckable before pursuing her if i don't see her in real life or have an up-to-date
recent picture it is unacceptable to me it's very these things are not happening
like if i i could i could find a girl who's super into me on twitter and spend like
fucking hour talking to her then find out she's a total ham beast what what am i gonna do you know
you know what the worst thing is it's when they do the like that they they have the face photos
where they look up and it looks okay but then you know oh my god pair chan dude the pair chan
syndrome it's it's it's everywhere that's really that's that's the ultimate disappointment i mean
just don't trust any pictures taken from above because everybody looks very true it's yeah i gotta
say i gotta say everyone this conversation is becoming a total sausage fest so i'm here
that i hope you're i'm i've been saying well i'm here to destroy all men
thank please do please do do it for all of us put us out of our misery let's let me talk about
let me just throw my hat in the ring and say that i am depressed that i am lonely that i hate
i hate it here and the tinder doesn't work in virginia beach digi what do you mean by
how can that work i mean it doesn't fucking work i mean it used to work where i used to live it
doesn't work i was hindering the whole time i was there i think did it work i think he means
that he hasn't got no it didn't well the app worked i mean it turned on that's not what it means for
i got more matches in one week at digi's house on tinder i have ever here where i mean oh my god
what constitutes success what constitutes success at tinder do you have to actually get laid is that
a successful tinder usage okay yes all right that is establishing it that's like the only reason
that app exists isn't it well no no i'm not disparaging that i'm just wondering what your
criteria is for i didn't know that was the point i just like the endorphin rush of getting a match
that to me means i've won the game you haven't won the game matches are easy
well not here they're not not for me but you i used to get a lot the success of tinder is very
area-based i've tried tinder a few times and my area is just full of like super normies and
everyone on there is wearing a fucking red socks hat and like goes out to sporting things and like
just has pictures of them though their girlfriends getting drunk i'm just like god forbid i would
execute all of you have given the chance so those are the only people that live around here
genocide is par for the course in here but pay attention you guys catch up
this is the most eliot roger podcast we've done in at least a couple weeks
no it's good that's how it should be i would love a i would i i want a girl who likes sports
that's cool i think like a fucking like a lin loud i'd be all over a lin loud i'd i'd rain
calm on lin loud well all right but i want a girl who's got a brain and always speaks
he's saying he's saying the loud sisters don't have brains they're genius there's all of them
here's how cool i am i don't care what a girl's interests are they don't have anything to do
with me ladies i okay but put to for a real argument here uh is it really necessary that a
couple you know be it for a hookup or a long-term thing is it really necessary that they let's
take digi for an example is it necessary that the person he dates be like into the same things
he is into no as opposed to just enjoying if you're absolutely not if you're going for something
long-term then i'd say absolutely yes i don't think it's necessary for any maybe in any case
yeah mage running three or four years now uh it's not mandatory to have all of the same
uh hobbies or interests yeah that's that's what i think that people who are my relationship
personally is the similar sense of humor and i think that's like yeah i think uh vacation people
who are inexperienced put way too much emphasis on finding someone who is into the same shit
it's more about having you know for the record i i i do i don't even want a girlfriend to be into
the same stuff that i am because i'm an elitist about the things i like and sure like you know i
mean most of the time like my ex-girlfriend was way into anime but like the wrong ones so that was
just actually no no it was actually more a source of a source of pain for me that it was a source of
like you know it was fun to watch anime together but we had to watch i prefer a girl who is into
nothing that i'm into so that i can mold her into having all the right opinions yeah sure
yeah it's a girlfriend from the ground up just like christian westerchandler promised
girlfriend from the ground up also hi mage good to see you again
girlfriend i know i know but i but i was muted girlfriend from the ground up sounds like it could
be a disney song like at the beginning of the movie when he's looking for princess oh i'm gonna get a
girlfriend from the ground up the christian west and she's gonna be pretty and fancy somebody make it
please i'm thinking i'm thinking this particular disney movie is about a bunch of like anthropomorphic
plants okay and like and like the main character is like a little like a little like vegetable
that wants to grow a girlfriend oh my god that's pretty good wait but wouldn't that make him a
pedophile if we you know it doesn't work the same way in their society oh right okay they've got
judge mcjudge mcjudson plants are incompetent that's you're you're you're just like christian
thinking that he has to teleport his son at you eggs back in time 18 years for the sex in the
comic for fuck's sake they can mature they can mature at different rates do dogs have to wait to
be 18 before they fuck know you say that but in australia i believe it's illegal to make real life
pornography of actresses over 18 if they look under the age of that's that's unrelated no no what
i think it's what no what the similar problem would be is if you're not allowed to film animal
pornography unless the animal is over the human age of consent and everyone knows the animal pornography
is a thriving field in australia and abroad how long are we keeping up this atrocious cringe worthy
podcast that i don't know we can why are we even talking about dating and stuff isn't this is the
we're supposed to be talking about hard things and all these fucking these hikikomori's these
nerds are talking about dating as if it's hard get out of here i'm talking about actual hard this
is why you're a chad jesse you're a totally chad on the subject of dating i'm the king of chad
i'm i'm chad thunder dong and all of you are beneath me
well some of us are sensitive men and we need a delicate approach that's hard
do you want to talk about a topic if yeah i could change a topic if you need a topic please
may it save us okay okay um what you got so most people find it hard to wake up in the mornings
what i find hard is to actually fall asleep i have i find both insanely difficult i cannot wake up
but i cannot go to sleep i'm just crap i'm definitely the opposite of you mage there i
have such a hard time getting up any day and like going to sleep is so easy for me i find it hard to
want to go to sleep because the act of sleeping is death yeah it's terrifying it's true i agree
completely i lay awake for seven hours until oh my god i have to yeah and i can't fall asleep
and it's just frustrating like i i don't have i don't get enough sleep for like days and then
like one day like i usually sleep for like five six hours and that's not counting uh when i keep
waking up between like two or three hours or so and then there's this one day i can't fall asleep
and then when i do fall asleep i fall asleep for like 14 hours and i've knocked out i've been there
and that is the work you enter the odin sleep i used to not be able to get to sleep but what has
helped with that now is that i don't have any schedule so i just go to bed literally only
when i am falling down oh my god so speaking of what i would do if i was in your position have you
ever heard of a polyphasic sleep cycle yes and i can't do it the sleep i want to talk about that
i've tried many many times to enter one of those it's not i can't do it i just sleep too long it's
when you sleep multiple times shortly throughout the day so you can kind of just keep going
continuous the holy grail is the is six 20 minute naps yes is what people say is possible sleep
schedule yeah but guys let me tell you because this whole not being able to wake up thing
is such a burden being a normie with a nine to five it's a fucking nightmare i'm so bad it
is the biggest problem in my life by a huge march that is my professional life me being able to wake
up as to why when i had my nine to five like one of the reasons i think they let me go is because
i couldn't wake up properly and i would be late a bunch of times and you know what it is it's
because i'm up late doing the thing i care about yeah no fucking making my videos you know you're
burning the midnight oil trying to satisfy your soul so before it gets crushed the following morning
yeah that's why i guess mage wants us to shut the fucking board no i'm just letting you guys know
because we were planning to for like half an hour and this is almost an hour now so half an hour
that's gonna be a short ass podcast don't we usually go more than a half that's because the
guys did part one because yeah davoo and hippo decided to just do a part one of this podcast
themselves while they were waiting for us uh so they there's already like a 30 to 45 minute
podcast recorded somewhere god this the the pcp is like the house of leaves of
it is oh my god oh hey so i mean that joke i mean i yeah yeah and i don't i'm gay i'm gay
um i'm sure it's come up before but this did we are did we already talk about art and how art is
hard no we haven't talked about the actual topic at all yet we've just talked about what they've all
been stuff i find hard it's just because it's stuff jesse doesn't find hard so it doesn't care jesse
is just art on a different level than us all right ben well what were you yeah sorry tom well
here's my art it's really hard that's it yeah i mean because it just takes a long time it just
takes a long time as hell like for sure it's like you look okay you look at a thing like like
brian leo malley's like my favorite one of my favorite artists you look at his art it's real
simple right there's not that many lines the characters are simplified you think it'd be you
think it would be easy to recreate but it's not it's never as easy as it looks it's it's it's like
it's a couple a couple of drawings are like an entire day's work even if they're simple
and it it's it's hard right now and i was doing okay now i'm four days behind
because i made this stupid tweet that's like oh the last two weeks will all be foreshortening
exercises let me tell you you want to talk about shit that's fucking hard foreshortening
is the worst thing in the world every time i foreshorten i shorten my life from the fucking
stress it's awful i haven't i haven't been doing i haven't been doing the everyday thing i've just
been occasionally doing an ink thing for you know that's art is incredibly hard specifically
illustration is hard and it's even more annoying because illustrators are very pompous and elitist
about it because if you if you dare say oh it's so hard to draw good i wish i could draw good they
all have the same stock response well you can draw good you just have to practice and get good at
it you piece of shit you're just you're just yeah yeah i i know i know that i can practice and get
good at it the hard part is that i'm too busy being the world's greatest comedy writer i'm busy
putting my effort into that to put effort into something else when i say that it's hard i'm not
saying that i can't get good at it i'm saying it's hard to get good at it you piece of shit you know
it's true oh jesse i understand it's just from from my perspective it's a little it's a little
grading sometimes when people look at your work and just assume that you just like i you know i
wish i could do that as though it's just something i was born able to do yes i never take it that way
i just take it like it's a result of your effort like they wish they could do that you know actually
i think not many people tell me this because personally i would prefer personally i would i
prefer people to assume it's something i was born able to do i like when people assume that i'm just
a superior breed of human and it's pointless to try to measure up yeah that's greatly satisfying me
so actually never mind i apologize for any time i've said anything like that i take it back that's
just the real that's the source of all difficulty is that there's just not enough time in a human
lifespan to do all the stuff that you want to do i've spent my whole life getting good at one
particular set of skills so if someone fucking kidnaps my daughter and says you have to make a
good youtube video i can tell them that i have this particular set of skills but anything else i just
can't do it all and i hate myself for not having the time to devote myself to getting good at speaking
of time do you ever think about that they're like higher dimensional beings where time is just like
as fluid as i hope so and i hope to become one of them someday and i get really pissed off that
i'm like limited by my well now hang on because me being without without a perception of time
as we have now a cause and effect kind of becomes meaningless and nothing that you do really is an
achievement at all you know it just it always was that way so really only because we view time in
this way do our actions have the kind of value we perceive them to have yeah but i'd rather but i'm
talking about should be rather just be god mode oh right easy or easiness jokes and something deep
and philosophical just tom's right though we have to give up uh self uh congratulatory right urges
if we just make everything easy you know if it's easy you're not going to get any satisfaction
for it but at least you're getting it done that's true and from a limited time three dimensional
being trapped in the coils of an ever moving forward time space mm-hmm that's the best we can
ever hope for vote vote prop eight to turn to turn time into uh a flowing a river that we can
flow through at our own whim instead of an onward progression vote vote that up as the biggest
solution in the universe let's talk about the actual hardest thing in the universe the thing
that's so really um um is it is it is it uh we already made the my dick joe we already said
that yeah we did we did okay okay i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry the actual thing
that was really what you're good okay i don't i don't fucking know what i was gonna say the hardest
thing that i don't believe anyone can ever actually get good at unless they were fucking you know
fucking forced to get good at it from the age of like two years old is playing an instrument
in also ballet i guess but playing an instrument is the most impossible thing in the world
i've been at the same level of guitar playing for like 15 years i haven't progressed at all
i'm just i'm just like barely competent and it's been that way since for for over a decade i never
get any better because i never have the time or the patience to go okay today's the day that i
would sign up for guitar lessons and fucking also piano lessons and all of them the fucking trumpet
wasn't this the time problem again though is that i'll come back to well i mean yeah yeah but i'm
specific jesse i actually found on how i hate that specific problem because i ran into i hit that
wall about five years ago where i was like i'm never gonna learn how to play an instrument you
know i'd spent i'm not hitting that wall i'll never accept it i spent i spent most of my childhood
in my teen years thinking i was gonna do you know one of these days i'm gonna learn to play that
fucking guitar that fucking bass or those fucking drums i got all of them i got a keyboard you know
don't know how to play any of them and then one day i was like this is never gonna happen and then i
found the best solution surround yourself with people who can play instruments then you can just
pretend that their accomplishments are your accomplishments by singing and then posting them
on your bandcamp and therefore they are your songs because nobody wants to actually associate
themselves with the songs that you've sung over because you've sung about penises and cocks
and so they're like yeah whatever that's your bandcamp bro have fun and i'm like ha ha yes
i have made music even though all i've done is screech about penises and cocks over someone
else's institution digi you are an art criminal that's a good stage name art well you know the
problem is that i just i guess i hold myself to a high standard because i picture myself in the
future as like some worldly renaissance man who can do everything and so everything that i'm not
currently good at i hate myself for and i want to die you know i view myself more as like the wild
stallions as in my art will unite all of mankind and bring us into a glorious new age you know i
think that's going to happen one of these days yeah that's right and i think self perceptions
is pretty hard because then you have these standards you have to live up to that makes life way more
difficult as opposed to like i'm just going to do whatever and whatever happens happens but no
oh here's my here's that you know on that subject my okay um my inktober drawing i mean i was talking
about how art is hard and tom you were saying that you know you've been you've been challenging
yourself with your inktober's and they've been hard for you um let me for me my inktober things
have all been stuff that i go into with no plan and i just like and i just like put down marks
whatever and it becomes whatever it's going to become and it has they have not been hard they
have all they have all just been whatever kind of came naturally because i wasn't trying for any
particular goal with them and they all came out great and i'm really happy with them so
there i'm sure there's a lesson to be learned somewhere in that story but i don't know what it
is called stop trying trying just trying just sets you up for failure if you just do whatever
you can't fail because you have no idea what you were supposed to do to succeed
yeah if you just do what comes you know what is a uniquely podcast on such a great inspirational
quote from tom oliver oh well cool all right i mean are we actually done i don't know does anybody
have let me let me bring up one more thing and i just that i've thought of as you were saying
that it's just a uh a youtuber specific thing that is kind of just true of all artists is
when you've made your work and you've got like your channel whatever and you have a certain level
of quality that you have uh made things and you know it creates an expectation in yourself and
possibly your audience it's hard to know what they're thinking uh to deliver on that same
standard which leads to everyone making a secondary channel where they post their
shit that isn't good enough in their own mind to be on their main channel uh you know just living
up to your own standards is what i'm saying as an artist as a youtuber as anything is uh
this stuff because who who who's the toughest guy that you got to fight in your box and ring
it's yourself it's your own demons you gotta you gotta punch that boy pow pow that's it that's
my motivational speech for the day you gotta punch i mean i the toughest the toughest guy that
rocky had to fight was actually apollo creed not not himself and well you you say that no you say
he had to fight that russian dude who was like he had to fight that was definitely the toughest
oh i haven't yet apollo creed and then the next guy club around kicked his ass so the person he
had to overcome to stay the champion was himself because i mean this is basic that causes down
this is basic power level stuff ben come on you can i'm sorry i'm sorry i've never actually seen
rock oh you bastard you sick bastard how dare you well here's my advice um to everyone you'll
never be as good as me so give up everyone i've already done that so just to give to your patreon
but oh yeah that's you you'll never you'll never be as good as me but also give me money because i
need it yeah you can give money to jesse on patreon.com slash best guy ever be sure to go there and
give all your money that's not it that's not it that's a lie that's it i swear all right i think
we're done here okay so i know this is difficult for some people but stay on the fucking payload
oh god lol we're talking about video games well that could be a metaphor for life as well though
if that's some kind of fucking overwatch reference i'm going to throw a fit well it's like every
fucking i mean as i understand it the payload is come right well only in porn i mean not payload
that's the frame that's oh did you that's a gala yeah you know you just commit you just committed
sexual assault we could have just ended this with all this time but now we keep it going and now
we're talking about semen all right we did it guys all right that's it uh we're done thanks for
listening everybody and we'll see you next time hope you enjoyed bye bye
i'm supposed to be working right now i'm supposed to be working right now
but i'm not working i'm doing nothing my dick i'm jerking myself i'm sucking i am an asshole
i am a stupid i've got a deadline don't want to do it
what the hell is wrong with me i'm supposed to be making money i'm supposed to be creating funny
things that the people gladly will pay for artistic genius that's what they came for
instead i'm tweeting hashtag repeating that's why there's no heat and holes in the ceiling
yeah it's quite the burden it's a hard knock life being a genius