Hello everyone, welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast for another exciting week!
We got me, Ben Saint, we got Digi, we got Gibbontake, and we got our special guest this week is
Mer Logic, who you might know as Wonder Bread Guy, the guy who makes the pictures, who commissions
the all the pictures of blonde women with Wonder Bread doing deforestation.
Eleazar, pause the video and play, show a cascade of those images going across the screen
Kevin MacLeod tracks.
Man, y'all are so lucky this isn't Twitch, cause we've already been copyright clammed
by now because of how their fucking guidelines have been as of the past couple of days.
Like, what do you mean?
Like just for mentioning songs?
Just any music in general gets the DMCA fucking raging like you wouldn't believe.
That's true.
So Mer Logic, I have to ask you immediately.
Have you ever commissioned cosplay girls to do live, do you have any interest in live
action photographs of girls with bread?
Here's the story, I have my own Tumblr page, not my own personal Tumblr page, I'm talking
about a page where somebody thought it'd be funny to make a Tumblr page dedicated to
round references to my shitposting, and I found that Tumblr page by accident, and when
I was scrolling through what was in this Tumblr page, somewhere at the very bottom, there
was a picture of a girl who was looking for a Halloween costume because she was trying
to go and she thought, and I've even personally talked to this person, she thought it'd be
funny if I were to draw myself as one of Mer's commissions and then go to the party and then
have them wonder just what the fuck I'm supposed to be.
So she dressed up like one of my commissions and then went to that party and then wrote
a post about how she went to the party, they had no idea who the fuck she was supposed
to be, and when she posted that on Reddit, everybody was like, what have you done?
Why are you trying to, why are you trying to awake the quote unquote ancient one because
they act like I'm some kind of demon that only fucking summons itself if you get the
right summoning salt and you make it in the right single shape, so I wouldn't talk to
this girl, and she was like, yeah, I came up with the idea just on a whim, it was the
only Halloween costume I could think of to make, I'm a little surprised you were able
to find it, I mean, yeah, you're directly referencing me, how the hell would I not find
it?
Wait, so you didn't ask her to do it, she did it as a joke.
She came up with this idea on her own, she went to the party dressing, yeah.
So they were right, she did summon you with this arcane ritual.
It was ridiculous, but yes, I haven't personally paid someone to cosplay for me, but I have
had people dress as my commissions.
That's the way to do it, you just get your reputation to buy your own way and you don't
have to pay for shit, yeah.
Okay, people's heads rent free.
Yeah, yeah.
So what you do, if I'm understanding correctly, is you have commissioned various artists
to draw, I don't know.
I want to ballpark, how many artists do you think you've commissioned total?
Wait, I was going to let you know this guy.
I know, I've heard and seen a few of the images, but I'm not entirely sure as to what
the deal is.
Maybe we should make scale.
Is it a scale?
It's a scale that is impressive.
No.
Actually legitimate.
I've seen...
Are you interested in this thing?
I've seen many of them in this thing.
Which is cool, that's epic.
Can you explain the appeal briefly?
But does our audience know?
Is our audience going to be completely lost if we don't?
They will probably have no fucking idea.
I don't think most of our audience will know anything about Murlocic, so...
I mean, I briefly said what his deal is.
I don't know, he's known far and wide for...
Eleazar, show another cascade of these images going across the screen, set to a kiss from
a rose.
I mean, the images themselves may be famous, but I've heard him talk about what...
I have heard you talk about what is the appeal.
I am interested in you talking about it again, if you could explain to these guys.
That's the question that's the obvious question as far as I'm concerned.
When someone is confronted with your uvra, with your body of work, it's like, what is
the animating force behind this?
So I have a copypasta written about this.
I don't know if one of you wants to read it to get like a broader idea.
Sure.
I'll read it.
Should I just post it in general chat?
Yeah.
Yeah, go for it.
Sure.
I went and copy pasted this while we were in the middle of the recording process of
someone...
Oh, Christ.
Yes, so if someone wants to read that...
Wait, wait, wait.
You wrote this?
Yes.
Okay.
And it's close to blonde girl voice as I can.
Wait, why don't you read it, Murr?
Because I've read this...
I want to do it.
I tried to read this on the fucking The Dick Show, but I couldn't read it.
The Dick Show.
He wouldn't let him read it.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
It's a parallel on how normally society identifies negative stereotypes, but they only ever stereotype
it in a way that fits their narrative.
Let me explain it like this.
How often do you watch cartoons or animation of any variety where they decide to do an episode
where the theme of the episode is about spreading either an environmental message or they create
a character for the sole purpose of helping to spread an environmental message?
When people, animators, slash writers, whatever, feel the need to make plots like this, their
archetype of choice on how they write the episode is, let's draw a white, tall, shady-looking,
sometimes fat, really depends upon how cartoonish the show in question is, billionaire, one-dimensional
character who doesn't care or think about the long-term consequences for his actions
because as long as it continues to make money, he doesn't give a shit.
They've been making this one type of character in the industry for years.
I am so sick of seeing characters like this, not because it's a bad character type, but
because it's demonized to where people start to think, man, why would they even draw a
female equivalent to a character like this?
It just doesn't exist.
And yeah, it's hard how in the real world you need to really think about it if such a
character like this could ever exist in the real world, which is probably why it is so
easy to make a character like they have been making for what feels like forever now in
the cartoon world because that one character can represent.
Either one type of character that fits that narrative or a whole group of people that
could fit that narrative.
I'm just saying, we live in a world where a female equivalent to this character I am
describing is very rarely seen, so I wanted to bring more attention to this fact by making
more of them.
So what I'm getting out of this is like more female, evil, billionaires, Yasqueen, representation.
Before I got my dream gate art nuked, I had an instance where you've all seen that one
Tumblr post, that one Tumblr user going thermonuclear, that one infamous post that everyone knows
before.
I'm not sure if I do or not, to be honest, but go on.
It's the one where it goes like part of me believes.
It doesn't ring a bell, can we show it on screen?
I don't know.
All right, so there is a Tumblr user.
I'm not going to tell her your name because everybody can probably just look her up on
her own, but this Tumblr user, she's a commission artist, and here's the thing, I ask hundreds
upon hundreds upon thousands of commission artists by the hour every day, so eventually
after a while I tend to just forget how many people I ask commissions for, and I'm guessing
at one point she just kind of fell into that circle of people, and she got so asravaged
beyond all fucking comprehension that I asked her very generically if she could draw me
commissions that she went on to this fucking, you know, typical Tumblr shit show of rants
that everybody is ran, everybody knows before, and to take it a step further, she went on
my DeviantArt, and she complained about how she didn't like the art that was on my DeviantArt,
but here's the thing, the reason why she hated all of the art on my DeviantArt wasn't
because of the one thing I thought it'd be, because if you're a Tumblr user who's absolutely
fucking obsessed with wanting to push women empowerment, you're going to look at my art
and think, oh my god, look at all this sexist content, I'm so disgusted, my purits and eyes
can't handle it, no, that wasn't why she was angry, you want to know why she was angry?
and I shoot you now, this is a direct quote from her, I don't like any of Mer's art because
all of the characters are white, okay, they're what, oh, I think if I were to change nothing,
have everything be the same, but all of the characters were any other demographic other
than white, perfectly fine, it was a kind of empowering image, but no, would they be happy
so we need more women of color deforesting the Amazon rainforest, what I'm thinking is,
like would they be happy if it was an all black picture, like do they specifically want it to
be diverse, like is it only a problem because they're white? you know what this sounds like to
me is that this person was upset for reasons they couldn't understand and like they just
tried to think and they had to like reverse engineer their own upsetness, that sounds like
Tumblr, yeah, like what is it, what is it that bothers me, what is it that bothers me, uh white,
okay, yeah, what you should like when I look at the the the collage of art and it's it's fascinating
to me that there is so much like consistency and through line in the tonality of them between all
these different artists, but like it's it's like it's so specific that when I see it I think well
obviously this is something that one person cares about more than anything in the universe
and having heard you talk about it that is absolutely true, so like I think that's why
people are fascinated with it is that like I don't know I wish I had that single-minded
devotion to anything, you know, you would think if they were any other demographic other than
white it would be worse because anybody who's ever watched 12 years of slave or django or that one
episode of the boondocks you would think black women looking like how they were as like fucking
home masters from like the civil war era they would think that'd be even worse but not you got
this one tumblr user it's like why the fuck are they all white this is terrible it is problematic
it makes that really okay okay but like these these characters they're like they're villains
like you're you're depicting them as as the villain right yes so this yeah okay this is the one
I'm probably keep having with tumblr is that tumblr can differentiate the difference between what is
reality and what is not reality this is a fictional picture it can't be real but they treat it like
it's real and then react like real which is ridiculous yeah sure I'm curious Mer like do you
want it to be real like if they're really what okay so you would not want to date a crazy blonde
shit cutting down trees without with a hang on I didn't say that I said I didn't want to be real
okay for real I'd be open to the idea however what makes this so compelling is the fact that it's
not real I'm like yeah I think I understand of Ricardo Lopez I like things that are not real
versus Ricardo Lopez being the guy who wanted something to be real so badly he went to great
extremes to make it real and for people who don't heard Ricardo Lopez okay Ricardo Lopez was the
Bjork stalker he was the man who tried to fucking put an AIDS bomb in the mail and try to send it
to Bjork okay okay okay okay so it's not it's not like you actually like wish for the destruction
of forests but yeah yeah but something I really feel like I'm on the same wavelength I get it with
this sort of stuff because I am also I'm also like a great lover of the terrible evil bitch lady
characters in a lot of media she's most enticing you know anybody who's ever like golden boy no
man madame president makes my cock so hard it's oh golden boy I love golden boy my best friend he
fucking loves that he keeps telling me to get that to watch it I haven't watched it yet but I know who
madame president is because that's his wife I watch golden boy when I think I was probably a little
too young to appreciate it uh all I got out of it was that the main character was like the coolest
guy ever it's almost like embarrassing how he's like oh wow he's so cool he can literally do anything
he's like oh what a what a badass uh uh but yeah yeah yeah you're simped because you got that scene
where madame president just spits in his mouth super erect he's he's he's like he's like a horny
idiot but he's like he like there's only six episodes I think but like every episode ends with
him like pulling turning the situation around in some like unbelievably like ridiculous display of
competence like there's I think there's an episode where he gets hired by some like software firm
and then like everyone like the the the the madame president or whatever of the software firm like
abuses him and shit and then he like he runs away in the middle of the night but before he leaves
he spends like one night and he like reprograms their entire database and like overhauls all
their like computer like company software and shit and just like remakes it from scratch
and it's just the best fucking software anyone's ever seen uh there's another bit in that one
episode where he pretends like he's playing on a computer so he draws a piece of paper that looks
like a keyboard and he's just furiously typing on that piece of paper he's like yes even when
you're not shitposting your need to shitpost consumes you so so you you were you were telling me
the other day or I was talking to um um wait uh uh okay I want to I want to give a shout out to uh to
pyro from the podcast shreddit uh uh who who is the one who who's the one who like uh said that he
knew you and gave me the hookup and gave you my contact info to get you on here and stuff thanks
thanks pyro go check out shreddit everybody yes so we talk frequently in fact he even sent me a text
message the other day asking like you still going on that podcast I'm like I wouldn't not you really
wanted me to talk to this dude but but he was he was I was confused because I was because I was
talking to him and he described like like your commissions and stuff as shitposts and you're
describing them as shitposts I mean so I thought okay so it's a bit so it's a bit a lot of things
one it's porn two it's for shitposting and three it's for you know spreading my brand around you
know because I like to I like to make shitposting interesting you know we're we're at a point 2020
has made me realize that you know people who moderate all these big names social media sites
like reddit and fortune you know we call them the janitors because they do it for free you know
they're yeah we're all tired of shitposting they they don't like it they want everything to be like
in this contained little box where everything is no fun allowed and if there are any people
having fun at any time you're done you can't have any fun anywhere at any time that's why I've
been banned practically everywhere now the only places I haven't been banned from now are twitter
and discord and that's half the reason why I want to go back on the dick show because I want to feed
into dick's point about how we're becoming more and more Orwellian by the day because the US
government literally cannot fucking help themselves ever since shelter in place the government has
been forming a massive fucking stiffy in their pants finally getting to have their Orwellian
wet dream come true and they're so close but can you can you elaborate interrupting that it's pissing
them off can you can you elaborate on the Orwellian state all right so how about just the concept of
shadow banning in general like if you ban someone you know they can't go back for a couple of days
if you ip ban someone you're done like you know unless you have some ip like like altering software
like Nord VPN like you're essentially done but I'm guessing like hard crack down on ip banning
they have shadow banning now where they'll give you the freedom to keep shitposting but the problem is
only you can see nobody sees it that only only you can see it but that's but that's not the government
oh hear me out there's a point to this so yeah what makes shadow banning really shitty is that
you go through all that shitposting and nobody can see it and you're thinking yourself is like
how the hell do we get to this have any of you ever heard of a guy named mr. anti bully mediocre
medicare yeah i know i know who that is so before medicare basically just disappeared off the face
of the internet he got cancer yeah he got cancer like he basically just moved out of existence so
he made a video and he was talking about how a lot of dumb shit has happened since the 2016
elections obviously or at least to the perception of everybody a person that the establishment
wanted to win did not win and they were dumbfounded as to how this happened so they had to call a
spade a spade and kind of alter things accordingly now during this process mediocre goes and releases
this video and he's talking about how google and all these big tech companies are very upset
that the narrative that they want is not the narrative that they're getting or have gotten
close to getting because people keep shifting away from their perspectives and their points of
you want they can't control people unless they control the narrative so medicare goes and says
they're hoarding you what they're doing is that they're going to work all these people who are
experiencing wrong thing and they're going to put them in a box and they're going to put them in a
box where the only people who can hear them are the people who are in that box or even worse the only
people who can hear them are themselves and an example of that would be poll poll is a great
alternate place to find people who can give you alternate means to look for news that isn't
completely biased like cnn or msnbc or all of these circumstances where the situation
the question seems very sketch and questionable and all the material given doesn't look like it's
legitimate it looks like it's being altered and twisted to form a narrative and he warns all these
people it's like eventually it's going to get to the point where the establishment is going to get
so sick of people shitposting and saying anything that people don't like that they're going to
rope them all into a box and then keep them into that quarantine area and they can have all the
wrong thing they want as long as it's not being put in the place that we don't want wrong thing to
think shadow banning is a normalization of that you notice how because i'll mention tumblr again
i mean i definitely think that twitter in particular is a like an extremely managed
like platform in terms of the narrative that the that the platform itself is trying to push
based on who pays them which seems to be like the more democratic leaning side of the
media establishment just based on the fact that when you make new twitter accounts like
all the stuff it pushes to you is just like like the the catalog of all the you know the
ellen and all the famous people the that weird category of the people who get pushed by the
media you know what i'm talking about yeah like uh the same people who are who youtube is always
showing in your face and um it's fascinating because it's not that there isn't a huge presence
of like the exact opposite opinions and everything going on on twitter but there is a like an effort
in the part of the algorithm to push the like a a i don't want to say left wing because it's like
what's the word i'm looking for just democrat i guess like it's just like push biden to president
currently is like what the like when you look at what the sidebar is on twitter it's like
it's it's not representative of what is being tweeted about it's representative of like what
twitter wants you to think is happening today you know i i mean sure is that i mean is that like
i don't know i for all i know twitter could be like a big like neoliberal chill or whatever could
be like all about biden maybe jack is like su just thinks like cop mommy cop malla is really
hot i don't fucking know um i think they just get money from there because like twitter twitter
doesn't make twitter makes no money like twitter doesn't they keep increasing the amount of ad
shit on there and now they're doing fleets to i don't know get people to use it more i don't
know how that even pushes ads but like the like twitter was making like less and less money year
after year and i have to assume that it's more powerful as for its ability to inform or like
create narratives in society like so much of what is taken very seriously on twitter as like
things happening that matter a whole lot don't seem to really when you actually go outside and
like look at what's happening sometimes you know i mean like of course like i mean the huge swaths
of twitter are owned by like bts stands and and and stuff like that like yeah of course everything
that's important on twitter isn't important in the real world most things on the internet don't
matter in the right but a lot of it looks like it does things are super important on twitter for
like one day and then everyone forgets about them but they they affect the way that people yeah
they affect people's like the way that people compound their narrative about their personal
politics you know like i think that i think it is being used like the the idea of like putting
some of like obviously twitter doesn't want to kick republicans off of its platform that would be
preposterous that would be a lot of the population but it's it's not that they're like even necessarily
suppressing them or making it impossible for them to communicate with each other or link or anything
like that like if i follow a bunch of accounts of one type i'm going to get recommended everybody
who those people follow because it's based on who they follow not based on what they say or what they
do but twitter does shadow categorize you like they there's you know proof of this idea that like
they have all these tags that they put on like users or posts who have been flagged for like
saying certain things and like they do put you in boxes they do try to like if they identify you
as somebody who they don't want to have their voice out there right and it's not even that it's a
right versus left thing it's just whatever twitter wants the their whatever they're in service of
i don't know who's at the heart of i mean that's i'm sure that i'm sure this is true i'm sure that's
true this is um this is just this is what happens when uh when a company when a company has a monopoly
on a certain kind of information yeah of course they're gonna use that that's a great yo uh ben
yeah let me add to your point there when you mentioned how a company is using money to enforce
that agenda do you remember a while ago when basically the entire world had like the biggest
thermonuclear shit that possible because somebody some fucking pageete or whatever working at the
white house was pushing for that means or um you know just it doesn't really matter just some
fucker who wanted to push the fc or not the fcc the uh the net neutrality thing and people were
complaining non-stop about how they were worried with this net neutrality bill that the internet was
going to focus more on biting by the whims of what corporations want versus what the natural user would
want like there were all these like reports about people talking about how like if you want to go on
a site that the internet doesn't want you to see like you know they'll let you go on it but they'll
make it a pain in the ass for you to one find the site in the algorithm and two like it'll take way
too long for you to actually get on the site versus how it's yeah i remember about net i remember
the thing about net neutrality yeah that's basically what you're talking about they were trying to make
it seem like you know unless you're like a billionaire or you have like a lot of money to spend
on like ads and all that shit they were going to make the internet more convenient for them and
inconvenient for everybody else you know because they can't financially compete with that that's
namely what you're talking about yeah well yeah i mean but yeah the goal was to make it possible
for for uh you know certain certain groups and individuals certain companies to you know further
monopolize the internet because because right because net neutrality right now means that
everyone that uses i'm not an expert but my understanding is that it means that everybody
gets access to the same bandwidth versus if we remove net neutrality then like twitter or
facebook or whatever couldn't could basically buy access to the good internet and everyone else would
be left with you know the the scraps of bandwidth that were left over nothing vile how could anybody
fucking not see that as like just man just let me have my orwellian wet dream i'm about to
i'm so sick of edging i want it now i want to be like china it's obviously it's obviously bad
and evil but because but because politics are controlled by money and money to interests you
know it can still make it to the highest court in the land or whatever obviously i'm not saying
people with power like well they've they've lied in their bed they know what they want they they
know what they're doing mm-hmm and it's it's fucking awful i hate it so much sure sure um
okay i don't even remember what the question was that let us down this this this avenue
i've been looking at pacifika northwest she's one of my favorites who pacifika northwest
from gravity falls the one of two characters that i remember oh yeah yeah yeah oh right blonde
sure okay cool i i like these images they're they they they speak to me i think like that
you were saying it was a shitpost but it was also kind of a real thing i think the quantity
of it is the shitpost like the fact that you've done so many of them
and all of them were made by me like it it was like the opposite of like when wendy got popular
as a character and like way in like a fucking boatload of like ad traffic because people kept
drawing porn of their mascot and they couldn't have been happier because people were going to
wendy's more often oh oh i think you went wendy from um gravity falls no no no yeah okay i knew
what he meant um when wait okay i just want to can you how how long have you been doing this
how many images do you think you've commissioned how many like how many do you do in a month like
how much do you and how much have you spent on this versus like how much do you spend in a month
well then i should specify the fetish itself started when i was three years old but the
commission started around 2012 can you tell us about how the fetish started so uh one of you
has been on the the dick show so you already know this story but for the sake of repeating it
yeah for our audience's benefit when when i went on the dick show i was talking about how um i was
watching uh dexter's laboratory one day and an episode showed up and it was basically the start
of how my uh destruction fetish essentially came to be um so the episode was called the old
switcher rooms it's about how dexter's dad came back from a bowling tournament he got first prize
for being the best bowler out of everybody there and when didi and dexter are running around in the
hallway you know just being stupid kids they knock over the trophy and they break the trophy
and dexter's dad gets really really mad instead of crap i do remember this yeah instead of uh
instead of grounding both his kids he turns them it's like you know what i've got a more creative
idea for punishment since you both broke my trophy dexter you're gonna be spending the rest of the
night in didi's room and didi you're gonna be spending the rest of the night in dexter's room
and dexter if you leave didi's room at all anytime throughout the night you're sleeping in the dog
house and the dog is gonna go sleep in your room so what the so dexter is who would sleep in didi's
room that would mean that if wait that would mean that if didi can somehow get dexter to leave
her room then the dog goes to dexter's room and by default didi would go back to her room so i
could see mind games developing out of this so i would think i would think that dexter would
rather have the dog in the lab the didi who he thinks is going to destroy it absolutely well
not not the lab his room because you the there's secret access to the lab but i don't didi might
know how to access the lab from his room in fact and she definitely does which book it is to open up
the the fucking bookshelf but dexter's sitting in didi's room he's having a panic attack he's
envisioning like all the horrible things didi could be doing to his fucking lab right now
and anytime he hears a strange noise he presumes that it's didi destroying his lab in the other
room like he hears like a fucking clock going in didi's room and he just presumes did's didi
like taking a sledgehammer and just destroying everything inside because there's like nothing
stopping her from just wrecking everything but these little mental hypotheticals that dexter
is having like all the horrible things didi's probably do into his lab that's how it started
i just got so uncomfortably aroused at how this horrific trail of three i just like oh yeah i've
impressed by your ability to recognize arousal at age three yep that's how it started i i don't i
don't get it but what what i guess why should i expect to um okay yeah okay so all right so then
maybe it's too much to put it in for me i feel like he's he's been spending too much time at
catholic school it's like oh the world is covered in skin right now i don't understand what's hot
about his thoughts that someone is breaking your shit and you know is it like the powerlessness
it's i think right oh it's the someone else is is like taking over like um so would you describe
the entire world is like it's just a massive but in a strange way like the winds get crossed
and scary things become really and holding in quiet missionary for the purpose of procreation
i don't understand what you're describing is not like filthy it's just it's just baffling
very logic would you consider the same would you consider this a masochistic fetish on your
part yes definitely okay okay sure like as i can i can recognize the world to be destroyed
seeing the world be destroyed by hot ladies like oh oh no but also i get it i get it so if it's
deforestation it's like it's it's not just it's not like just your shit that's it's our it's our
it's all of humanity's shit being destroyed it's like she's all of humanity out of what should be
our ours natural resources try to explain this is like does he just have a fetish for karen's
and i laughed for like five minutes when someone recommended that i i think i think a part of it
is so as as speaking as a masochist um like it's part of the you know you it's like you
like like you said well given said like there's a helplessness aspect right like you want to be
like in a position of um i have i don't have to have control in of the situation because it's
i can't you know um and so like as a as a woman it's very easy to achieve this by just having
a man who's bigger than you you know like hold you down but like as a guy how does a woman have
any kind of like power over you like she can't you know unless she's stronger than you
she cannot physically overpower you which is you know most women are not stronger than most men
but they can dominate your wallet and fuck up your life by like spending all your money and
fucking um destroying the world all the trees yeah okay where does this make sense to you
does this seem like it could be accurate in any way as i'm nervous i can feel him depleting
an energy i understand do you think the um do you think the wonderbread aspect is also like a
like a power dynamic because it's like oh mom goes and gets the wonderbread when she's shopping
and like you're almost on target but there's actually another story in relation to that and
i don't know if anybody's heard this unless you've been on the dick show and more than happy to
share that story with you yeah please so you know if ben isn't had a stroke right now he might after
this you you are miss you are mischaracterizing me very much right now but go go on all right so
a long time ago when i was say around 18 i was looking for my first job and i had no
resume experience whatsoever um i went over to a place called pedaluma people services center
all the way up in pedaluma and uh the organization that i'm talking about is kind of like one half
psychiatric place one half uh unemployment office so i went over there and nice it's a good
combo it helps people learn about their feelings and then get back up on their feet and um over
there and i'm asking my therapist it's like yo i really need to get a job i need to start making
some money and um she recommended me this place called bounty farm which is located right next to
the luckiest in the police station up in pedaluma so i had to get up at five o'clock every day and i
had to fucking get on a city bus and then take that city bus to the bus stop and then go from the bus
stop to the county bus and then take that county bus all the way to pedaluma and i had to then be
there by eight o'clock every day and i had to do this for three years it was exhausting but it was
my first job i'm working on a farm how old how old were you how old were you 18 okay yeah so i'm
there and right now as of then i was the only person working there and i go to my boss i'm like
am i the only employee working here it's like not the only employee we're gonna be getting another
employee you also showed up the day after you did she'll be showing up soon so she shows up
and we get to talking and after a while this person ended up becoming my girlfriend and it
didn't last but the process wasn't like just instantaneous boom you're my girlfriend now
it was a long long long process you know like anybody who's ever watched like any of those
really shitty soapy opera kind of shows like 90210 or and any of any of those kind of shows like
you know it was the build to that you know it's like we had to we had to have a long lasting
friendship a bunch of dumb shit involving other relationship shit had to happen and eventually
she just turned to me and she was like you want a shot like you want to be my boyfriend see what
it's like i'm like i'm more than willing to try and we were in a relationship well i should say we
were in a friendship for years but our actual relationship serious relationship lasted two
days and it was two days of my life that two days felt like two years so that's the funniest
shit i ever heard yeah so we're we're going on our first date and i have this all planned out
first we're gonna go get uh chinese food so we went to this old place that doesn't exist anymore
called gary chews and we go there and that's is that like is that like a sonichu like uh
original character obviously christian came out to win her up it's like may i recommend the
gary chew yeah so we go to gary chews and it's already not going the way i wanted to go she's
talking about how she wants to get drunk and i'm like it's like one o'clock in the afternoon
you're talking about wanting to get blitzed so were you guys even old enough to drink i'm i wasn't
old enough to drink but like she was 21 when i met her so i mean she's 21 so i see we go to gary
chews we have our food she wants to drink and then i then skip to the next part of the date which is
where we went to go see a movie we went to go see this is making me want to drink so we go to the
movie theater we see mad max fury road and after we're done with the movie she oh great movie oh great
great film classic film yeah so after the movie is done she wants to go home and she really wants
to drink so we get on the bus and we're going on our way home and here's the problem before this
i actually met a person i used to live with and i'm not gonna obviously give this man name because
you know i'm not an asshole but just to really give you an idea as to what this person was like
i found him drunk in like the bus stop one day and apparently he had mid-court order or whatever
and we were talking or whatever and then he turned to me it's like hey oh that girl i saw you hanging
out with i fucked her i fucked her last night and i fucked her real good by the way do you know
anybody i can fight right now because i really want to fight someone this dude was drunk okay and he
just straight up told me that he fucked my girlfriend and wait wait wait wait wait wait
sorry sorry this was okay this two-day relationship you're saying on the second day of those two days
you found this guy and he said i fucked that girl you went out with last night the day before the
date started i ran into this guy i used to live with okay i think this guy for three years because
i used to be a foster kid we used to live in a foster home together he i i want to nail down
the order of events so this is the day before she became your girlfriend he said i fucked that girl
yeah the day before she became my girlfriend this dude i lived with all my life and the
foster home that we lived in turned to me said i fucked your girlfriend so yes we're on the
bus right home and then and then the next day you were like hey she was like hey be my boyfriend
and you were like okay let's go out and get chinese yeah so okay on the bus right home yeah i know i
know what you're thinking you know i i don't know what i'm thinking i'm not sure but before we get to
that she was like no it's not cocked you that's okay okay go on go on we're on the bus we're on our
way to runner park which is where she lived at the time she doesn't live in runner park anymore
because it's too expensive to live there but when she was living in runner park we're both on the bus
i turned to her and i asked her did you fuck that guy and she gets really defensive about it
and she said no i did not fuck that guy but then after like 10 minutes of silence she gets really
embarrassed she turns to me and said yeah fuck that guy the day before i asked if you wanted to be
my boyfriend we went and had sex and i just told him to leave so wow okay so he was telling me the
whole truth yeah she admitted to it and this is where it gets really depressing really fast so
when we get off the bus the first thing we do is we go into safeway and she buys two 12 packs of
IPA log and eat a beer and if any of you have ever drank an IPA it is the shittiest beer ever you
know is it i don't know if that's i think that's a controversial opinion IPA's are a a new gate
for sure they're they're sort of like uh it's like the dark souls of beer the dark souls of beer you
know i no i drink fucking miller light i drink i drink fucking natty ice like i drink like piss
beer and i don't give a fuck natty ice you might as well yeah no yeah i i do i'll drink the worst
beer in the world i don't care but okay sure you get all the IPA and we're going back to her apartment
and i'm thinking to myself it's like man you know this is not going the way i hope it do but i'm
hoping at the end of the night we can somehow fix this so we go there she cracks open an IPA and
she cracks open another IPA for me and then she throws it over to me and wants me to start drinking
let me ask you how did you feel when she said yes i fucked that guy were you mad did you feel
sad were you jealous complex assortment of different emotions between what the fuck and why
so yeah she passes me an IPA and i take one sip and i immediately spit it out i'm like this tastes
horrible how do you drink this so two of her friends show up and they come on in girls
no uh well one of them was a girl one of them was a boy these are just people that she knew
and uh yeah one of them pulls out a deck of cards against humanity cards and no no
no oh this is the worst part so i'm sitting down at a table and the good times are over
she's flipping out cards against humanity cards like they're fucking poker cards and i
just fucking shoot me yeah so let me tell you cards against humanity is the most
overrated game i've ever played in my life i feel like the only reason why this game exists
is because if you're really politically correct like i'm talking really politically correct like
the very idea of anybody even like hinting at saying the n-word pisses you off the only reason
why they play this game is because they can have one instance where they don't have to be politically
correct but it's i have a yeah but it's the only time ever you get to feel that way and when you
take that away this game sucks this game is boring it's i don't know why people think this is the
greatest game in the world the the jokes the jokes in in cards against humanity or have already
you're not making jokes when you combine cards like the designers made those cards and made those
with those combinations in mind already like you're not even like being creative you're just
like matching things that like the designers put there because they thought it would be funny
this is the first time i've ever played cards against humanity and when i finally get the
bare basics down the first thing that goes into my mind is that's it this is all we're doing yeah
who fucking care about a game like this people just want to say naughty words it's the only
reason why they're playing this game yeah yeah yeah and ridiculous like there's no enjoyment out of
this game again even though what little enjoyment you can get out of this game it's boring i'd rather
be doing literally anything else right now other than playing cards against humanity so she's passing
out IPAs she's flipping out these cards against humanity cards after like 10 minutes of this i'm
like i don't want to play anymore like my date is already ruined i couldn't like you know i just
wanted to go out to get chinese food i wanted to go out and see a movie and i just wanted to have a
quiet night with her i instead have her complaining about how she wants to go get drunk and then when
she leaves the movie she wants to go get really drunk go to see if we can get a bunch of things to
help her get drunk we go to her house and you know her eventually her friends just finally leave but
like you know go in and her room has one futon now this is not like a king-size alaskan bed no
it's like a regular futon it's like the kind of futon you see in those slice of life japanese
anime's where it's an apartment for one you sleep on a futon this is what you sleep on this futon was
very clearly made for her body type because it perfectly fits how proportional she is to the
so she goes and gets a small tube tv and a dvd player and what she does is she grabs a random
movie off of her dvd case and the movie she grabs is howl's moving castle and she puts
howl's moving castle in the dvd player and starts playing the movie now you've heard of netflix and
chill right i assume that's what we're trying to yeah we don't have netflix so in order to stimulate
netflix and chill she grabbed the dvd put it in and just put it on his ambient noise that's just
what we did before netflix like you know it was move movie and chill yeah so she pops in howl's
moving castle which is her favorite movie next to princess mononoke so yeah so she puts this
movie in and she wants to have me cuddle her on the futon since i mentioned before that this
futon is clearly only made for one person imagine my fat fucking frame pushing this scrawny girl
off of her futon so i am like back first against the wall like in a lying down form i'm almost like
in a fetal position and my back is essentially touching the wall because i want to have her have
enough room on her futon so we can cuddle but if i eat up too much room for what i think is like
proportional for me i'll end up pushing her off the bed so it's impossible for this to be
any less romantic if it tried so she's like all right we're we're gonna make this work
follow me the best you can and i want you to you know touch my breasts and i did right so
of course this was the first yeah this was the first time ever describe the can situation
what oh sure tits like did they feel like wonder bread is this where this has been
leading this is where the story is the entire time all this build up i touched this is the
worst story i've ever heard about this this is even this is even this is even worse than jesse's
how i lost my virginity story this was the longest the most pointless story i've ever heard the funny
thing is i knew what the ending was at the start and i just wanted to see how long the story could
possibly go and if i hate this relevant to the i hate it all for the first time this is the first
time ever i touched a woman's breasts they felt really soft and i'm thinking to myself what is the
only thing i could think of that would represent what a woman's breasts feel like i'm thinking i'm
thinking i'm thinking and the only thing that possibly why were you why were you thinking about
that just touch the the boob yeah i touched breasts before i'm thinking what am i thinking of when i
think of this texture bread it's it's it's the uh this is why this is why you got dumped this is
why you got dumped do you think too much did you say that out loud you say oh you you have a very
like bread like breast no i didn't say that to her but i thought about it after she told me to leave
the following day so okay i want okay okay so you touched the boobs and was that it no there is
more to that but it's a bit more nsfw and uh so did you so did you fuck uh so before that
just yes or no just yes or no did you fuck or not we did well but it wasn't like the way you
thought like she wrote a list and on that list was things that she said she would be open to
doing i think she wouldn't be open to doing when i asked her when i asked her all right what's your
opinion of giving someone a bj and her opinion of that was you only ever give bj's to people if
they do something rewarding like they got a promotion at work they got an a plus that's
horseshit yeah but that's how it's your opinion of anal and she's like no i hate it only catholic
schoolgirls do that shit it's painful i got her okay okay so okay all right i asked her all right
so she's like touch my breasts and i touch your breasts and they feel like wonder bread
then she's like all right let's try kissing i really enjoyed this part but the problem is
again like touching someone's breasts i've never kissed before so our tongues our tongues are touching
and then after like 10 seconds she pushed him back it's like have you never kissed anyone other
than your mother before i'm like no this girl seems like kind of a bitch so um yeah for real
so she gets up and she's like all right i need to be perfectly real with you
i've done this so many times with multitude of different men so i just kind of know right now
are you a virgin i'm like you're my first and she just turned her face against the wall she
lied down and she was quiet for the rest of the night i woke up at six in the morning she told
me to leave yeah so you didn't see you didn't fuck you said you fucked you didn't fuck it started
that way okay go on then what happened next she woke me up at six and she told me to leave
you said you fucked yeah you said you fucked yeah we did when when when in that story did you
fuck right in the middle of the kissing part were you not paying attention no i wasn't paying attention
i don't whole story okay i guess i okay i guess i missed that part okay you like fuck we made a
long way wait so you how did i miss it you must have skipped over it in like no time at all
you you asked me this story about where does the bread come from i told you that's how it started
my first sexual encounter am i crazy did he just like completely gloss over the part where they had sex
i don't remember you describing that you had sex remember you saying that's not important that's
not that's what i asked i wanted to know if you fuck yeah we did but that's not important you're
overthinking it the point of this story is where it started all right okay that's fair enough
okay so you how long how long ago was that and then she realized that you know they they
fucked while they were kissing i think yes there you go now you're getting it but all right
like you you all act like you know it's like a long process it's not a long process it's different
for each person okay um mirlog how long ago was this that you made this wonderbread discovery
six years ago but like that was only when i wanted to start making commissions of it i've had this
fetish since i was three years old wait stop well not the wait not the wonder you said the
wonderbread thing happened when this when you were 18 yes but it's not just wonderbread it's
wonderbread deforestation and destruction this fetish happened when i was three it only started
okay into what you see now when i started making commissions okay well i guess i guess what i'm
trying to understand is how long after discovering that boobs feel like wonderbread did you start
commissioning art of wonderbread specifically that's six years but six years between those two things
yeah so i broke up with my girlfriend and i learned that boobs kind of feel like wonderbread and that
was kind of what started the whole commissioning process so no but okay but how long after that
happened did you did you commission your first work of art oh after that oh yeah first after
i broke up with my girlfriend okay so it's pretty much immediate like had you already been like
regularly commissioning artwork before that yeah i was regularly commissioning artwork but it was
unrelated to wonderbread what was it it was deforestation and destruction i assume
i i'm okay okay so i understand the destruction happened three years old dexter's lab wonderbread
18 years old girlfriend uh when when did when did specifically the deforestation aspect
no i just asked that you know the destruction and deforestation aspect is in the same category
that's been that way okay three isn't it okay wait okay okay but but but the example you said the
dexter's laboratory didn't involve deforestation yeah i feel like like that must have come into it
at a certain point you must have made a jump you there must have been a moment when you made a jump
from oh i like this destruction thing that this oh deforestation is like a particular instance
of that that is particularly compelling and then it moved on to captain planet and then it moved on
to a number of different shows uh i reference guys every part of my life so you would say it spread
would you say that it spread like wildfire through your uh enjoyment of media now you see the
most really bushfire of like 2020 was just a metaphor of what really happened this episode of
dexter's lab was like a lightning bolt that lit the dry brush underneath the dehydrated bog the
peat bogs of something i don't know what is the most you spent on one commission of this
let's see i think of it varies upon artist artists and it varies upon the scale of the project
i once paid 323 dollars for porn of another commission artist's wife
excellent worth it that's funny base um how much okay ballpark me how much have you spent
totally in this the intervening is like six years 4.3 billion dollars per million that's not a real
number my friend exactly because the number is so high i've lost count i guess the better question is
what is it in the four digits five digits it's in the seven digits big rush fortune digits
marologic at what rates would you say that you commission art for this like how often not nearly
to the degree that i would like to because like everybody else during shelter in place i am broke
and so are 50 million other people over the united states right right where do you where do you post
them like like i think you post them around as a shitpost where do you put them i did post
them on dvn art and then i got shadow banned and then i posted them on reddit and then i got shadow
banned and i post them on why did you why did you get shadow banned from dvn art because the janitor
is fucking do it for free and they shit their pants but don't get their way but but what was
but what was the jet okay i don't see anything bannable about just simply posting the images
that you have commissioned but homeboy you don't get it janitors don't do their job
because they want to do their job correctly because it's the only amount of power they get in their
life this is why people i guess yes i think the i think the question that's trying to ask is
where you ban for your uh for your image posting or for text posting like for things i want to
know specifically what was the thing that was like okay this guy's out of here it was both
i made fun of the janitor's waifus and their shit opinions and how they have no idea what the
fuck they're doing and they're unforeseen wait what you made fun of the you made fun of the mod's
wife no no i didn't make fun of their other wives they're waifus they're 2d images oh you're making
fun of the of a mod's waifu yeah and i don't know who who was wait who was it who was the waifu
who fucking cares there's probably some shit waifu i don't i'm just okay fine what did you say
tell me how the encounter went that just i did your waifu is shit you have the shittiest
taste in waifus ever hot pockets and asthma puffers you just cannot handle the bants when
you get blown the fuck out you cry and then shit your pants yeah and then you got banned yes
and it's basically the story how i get shadow banned on basically everywhere i'm banned on tumblr
reddit dvnart and specifically target mods that's why you get banned is that you
i'm not targeting mods on purpose they instigate this and then it leads to me getting banned
i'm not looking for mods they're looking for me that's the problem well now that you've
got a reputation i can kind of understand how they would at least find you so that make that part
makes sense fucking june it's good for free they do see i yeah i would i would be confused because
all of these images they're like a strange fetish and it's funny that there's so many of them but
like there's nothing offensive about them so like yeah it wouldn't it wouldn't be a reason for any
social media sites are getting to the point where they just want everything to be a echo chamber
hub box where everything is exactly they want it to be they want control they don't want fun
posture they don't want riveting discussion they want control you know it just occurred to me
i i just i don't know why this is something i never thought of there is definitely people who
would pay you to mod your stuff so so is it so is it the is it the companies that want control
and an echo chamber they're banning you or is it these like individual jannies that do it for free
that are just exercising their individual power it's a bigger symptom of what's wrong with the
internet right now everybody is getting banned for dumb reasons i'm not complaining because i'm the
only one getting banned i'm complaining about how just everywhere it's not even just a reddit it's
everywhere people are getting banned for the dumbest shit because janitors who do it for free
have this in their mind like they're enforcing this new agenda they're being told to enforce
or other people are just going off script because someone made fun of their waifu or something dumb
and they got so fucking asthmat they shot their pants they shot blood and they banned the person
and then he coomed in his pants and he thought he did something productive today that is the janitor
he does it for free gotcha very logic i have to tell you i think you're a marketing genius
the way you hammer on those phrases like that um they do it for free i think they would pay you
to mod for you i think that's imagine if i do get paid i would never i would no i'm not even
saying that they would get paid i'm saying i'm saying that janitors would pay to do the job
like they would pay oh to do it they would they would pay deviant art or discourse or whatever
yeah yeah to be a mod sure i'm sure i think there are people who would complain about being a mod
when that one girl who went on my deviant art complained about the art being all white
she went over to the deviant art mods and she was like don't you think this counts as hate speech
deviant art moderators probably okay okay we're in a sonico season diaper fetish shit
and then they look at my art it's like huh you're right now i'm i'm sure deviant art
always so i'm i'm here i think it's funny now obviously it's funny that she's like all i see is
white people this is hate speech like that's pretty funny but i i'm just curious if that incident
did you reflect on it at all and be like what if i did draw a black you know colonizer a black
deforester yeah what again what was your conclusion that is when i drew princess marco
from star versus who's the only not well technically that's not true i don't even know who that is
pretty long from star versus she's also princess marco princess marco star versus oh okay i see her
her okay her male that is the boy
that's mm-hmm yes it's princess oh marco marco d uh oh it's the oh it's the boy it's the
i've never seen star versus so i don't know who these people are okay all right gotcha gotcha
okay this is uh that's excellent so mere logic that that ties into uh something i was gonna ask you
is at the beginning i was asking if you'd ever paid anybody to like just cosplay and hold bread
and i happen to be planning to dye my hair blonde in about a week so i'm wondering do you would you
business opportunity did you just straight up just push bend to the side it's like all right
off camera real quick this is more like you know more important with me like a payment plan
i gotta i gotta be hard let's let's talk to make some money so i don't i don't even get to i
i'm going to be blonde anyways and i like eating wonder bread so i would have no problem procuring
that um and also this i mean you just introduced me to the fact that there's like a hard to procure
wonder bread in this economy you know it's funny i actually had someone on reddit sitting again
before i got banned and he was like hey i am a transitioning trap if i were to make a sandwich
and eat it would you pay me to eat it i'm like that depends how much you want to ask it's like
if you were to just like give me 10 bucks to like make a sandwich and eat it would you get
turned on and then pay me to do it i'm like hmm i don't know i mean would you do it and in the end
he didn't really do it but he instigated the idea he asked me it's like would i really well i'm
already dug deep into this hole so i might consider it dg probably write down notes right now
yeah i mean whenever you can afford to uh pay for me to cosplay just hit me up
name a price okay i mean i have to i guess i have to take other cosplay picks i have to
develop a portfolio first i guess um i don't really have a portfolio of uh cosplay photos
yeah we'll get there i mean i am an artist i would be up for drawing a funny fucking
deforestation wonderbread commission i could i could preferably because i can't afford any
i that's another half the reason why not not i'm i'm willing to wait i'll play the long game
i'm gonna be blonde for a while so this is gonna be waiting it's like any day now i'm gonna be
making bank if my investment opportunities is actually perfect i did want to ask you if it's
not too much information like how do you afford to pay for all this art like what would what were you
anywhere is able to afford anything right now i'm shelter in place i got one stimulus check
and you know it didn't last like or we're all like on some kind they gave us $1,200 and said
fuck you so did you did you lose your job were you non-essential worker i was already
in need before shelter in place now i'm like a super neat like during shelter in place like
everybody well how are okay well how are you making money as a neat like how how is it different
now than it was then why can you not afford it anymore many different and is you know if i have
money like i get it off like making tab money or i do like various odd jobs because if i need a
commission i'm willing to you know do anything need a commission tab tab money yeah you know
let's say somebody comes to me and they ask me it's like hey oh homie i need a pack of cigarettes
could you get me a pack of cigarettes and then i'll pay you back when i have money i have one guy
right now he owes me 110 bucks and if you were to look at his tab the only things that are on his
tab right now are and i quote pizza rolls pizza rolls chicken nuggets chicken nuggets hot cheetos
hot cheetos snapple snapple 110 why don't what why don't they just buy it at the store broke
they asked me to buy it for them and they pay me back oh wait so do they pay you back more than you
like are you sure do you charge interest um i haven't really implemented an interest tab because
i feel like if you implement interest it only compels people to not wait okay this this doesn't
make any sense how do you have this is not a this is not a money-making scheme no wait this is an
uroboros i'm confused how do you get the money that you spend that ends up on their tab so here's
the thing i'm not like christian where i'm spending money like it's out of style i have money i just don't
spend it like a retard like christ but where does it come from where does it come from just money
i've saved up saved from where i assume you just have a job i assume you had a job in a while i
sure don't have a job during shelter in place sure that's what i was saying you did have a job before
though had a job i've had multiple jobs i'm also you want unemployment since you lost your job due
commissions you should you should apply for unemployment if you lost your job due to the
covid release oh okay all right good i kind of have to everybody is right now like how else
you can afford yeah the government wants to be completely dependent on them right now i don't
know i have i have at least one friend who like lost their job it like couldn't work anymore because
of covid and they were like uh yeah well i guess i just have no money now and i'm like did you apply
for for unemployment you know they have a clause in the cares act that says like if you lost your
job due to covid you're entitled to free money from they're like uh i probably don't qualify
no i'm not going to do it i'm like you're literally just throwing thousands of dollars away
your friend probably just heard about the stimulus check thing i thought why doesn't the government
just on my door i just give me money i just wanted to personally give me money yeah i don't
maybe work of any kind yeah it's i i think probably yeah it's like they are intimidated
by the manner but like it's come on there's like there's like a whole bunch of money that is like
for you you should just like put in the the paperwork to claim it and i know people are
complaining about how societal collapse will happen any day now but literally as of right now
the federal reserve is printing trillions of dollars in money but acting like giving people
a thousand dollars a month is like too much for them to benefit oh the economy can't handle it
you poor people yeah tighten your belt straps a bit more yeah hell yeah austerity boys uh no
they're fucking they're they're fucking bailing out airlines and banks and shit but like oh giving
people money oh how are we gonna pay for it oh how are we gonna pay for it health care hey how are
we gonna pay for it uh no sorry we need to we need to fucking drone strike we need to drone
strike yemen some more sorry we can't afford you to do basic middle-class people not paying enough
taxes for the poor people to not work um were we talking about i don't remember okay i was just
too busy thinking about how that other girl who just like cosplayed as a wonderbread girl
should have gotten like i can't believe she didn't think to ask to get paid i think did you wanted
to know before before shelter in place what did you do for work well the last job i had and this was
before shelter in place this is like a while i've been unemployed for a while i worked at a place
called uh buccaloo unemployment and uh there's a longer story in relation to that but like uh you
worked you worked at an unemployment firm so in my city there are two unemployment firms there is
department of economic rehabilitation and buccaloo they are the two biggest unemployment centers in
the city i needed a job so i went over to dr and i asked my new art coach what is and they gave you
a job at the other one so here's the thing i go over to her and i ask her is there anything i can do
to make some money real quick and she asked me it's like well there is uh catholic charities which is
open catholic charities is a rehabilitation center for runaway kids foster kids and recovering
drug addicts they wanted me to go work over there but they didn't specify what the job was about
over at catholic charities but in order for me to go get that job i had to be trained first so
they send me over to buccaloo and i go over to buccaloo and i'm going through the inauguration
process and the woman is looking over my resume and she looks at me it's like um you are aware that
your california state id is expired right my wait what so i open up my wall i look at my id and i'm
you know holy shit it's expired so she pushes the resume back over to me it's like i'll tell you
what since you seem really enticed at the idea to start working again if you can get that id
renewed i'll give you the job immediately so i went to the dmv i spent three hours in line i got my
fucking id i went back i then asked alright can you start the training process so again i don't
know what kind of job they want me to work over at catholic charities but for whatever reason
they're like having me do random shit like firstly sit me in front of a computer and they
a shit you know they pop up mavis beacon i haven't done mavis beacon since elementary school they
want to check my typing speed i type at 35 words a minute so it then go and decides like actually
you know what you know we need to train you some more before we decide if you want to go work over
at catholic charities so they throw me a broom and a mop and they're like all right until we
feel like you're ready to go work over at catholic charities you're gonna be buckled is janitor
you're gonna you're gonna be a literal janny and you're gonna clean up our messes here's the problem
you would think since it's an office building it's a big building so there's lots to clean
no it is a small building with two rooms and a bathroom when you clean both rooms and the
bathroom you look at the clock and there's seven hours left of the day and you realize that you
now have to find busy work all day in a seven hour work day to pretend like you're doing something
important like when you run out of shit to clean like there's nothing left to clean like that's
right it's so dumb and like this was a problem i was having it's like i'm supposed to be trained
to go over to work at catholic charities right now you're treating me like a janitor like what am i
supposed to be trained for right now and here's what's really shitty my job coach came to me a
couple days later she sat me down it's like mer we're worried that you're not enthusiastic enough
about the job we've given you because it's really hard to be a janitor i mean you're not doing it
with a smile you're not doing it with a smile you fuck yeah fucking wagey why aren't you working
faster why aren't you coming into work every day like a mary poppins character going shitty shitty
bang bang all over the place and i'm just being thrilled that you work a fucking cognitive machine
so eventually my job coach is like all right i'm gonna go to your employer and i'm going to
tell her to motivate you because you don't seem motivated to do this how are you supposed to be
motivated to do this janitorial work is the lowest form of work you can ever put yourself through
nobody other than like people who are desperate and from third world countries because they're
willing to take a pay cut just to come to america just to do work like this because they don't want
to be in mexico anymore and i get sent into my boss's office and they're like i don't know who
trained you last but they did a horrible job and that was an insult because the person who trained
me last is one of my closest friends and the job i worked at before this job was a great job that's
a longer story in its own right but point being i got unbelievably mad i already hated this job i
hated everything about this job so as she's just tearing into my ass right now i just said you know
what to fuck this i called her a piece of shit i called her all kinds of horrible different names
but here's the thing if anybody female sees a male disgruntled employee yelling at their female boss
all the females in the room suddenly become tumblr moderators they all start screaming
yas queen all the same time and the minute they hear me yelling at my boss all of them drop what
they're doing right now they all huddle in a fucking circle around their boss and they're like
you can't do that you're what's the problem with modern day you are a part of the future you can't
yell at your boss i'm like you know what this poor this this poor disenfranchised boss just being
just being just being discriminated against by her wagey employee how dare he yeah how how dare
he uses privilege in this way i got i pushed my chair i got up i took my resume i chucked it into
the air and i just i went over to wing stop and i ate food and then the following day i'm so sorry
wing stop is the worst i'm so sorry man i had a bad day and i went over to wing stop i ate food
and then the following day we then had the tubs fire which lasted for 10 days tubs fire the tubs
fire was one of the worst fires to ever happen in the state of california which is an understatement
considering how we now have terrible fires every year we had five back to back terrible fires this
year during shelter in place yeah yeah i saw the red sky do you see that red sky thing going on up in
like northern cali dude it's it was so bad at one point that i thought india declared war and they
fired a bunch of the trains into the air and they exploded because the sky was covered
shit colored brown gross gross is right i couldn't breathe everything smelled bad it was awful uh
yikes um well so okay so i guess i guess that answer is where your money comes from came from
yeah uh what what what what else what else do we want to talk about anything you guys want i'm
hoping to talk about anything you can ask me what jeffrey eppstein killed himself
why why did jeffrey eppstein why would he do such a thing he had so much to live for
i don't know if you're a guy who has like a long fucking track record of raping and trafficking
kids dating all the way back to the 60s i i would think like that'd be concerned for somebody wanting
to kill you that's ridiculous that's totally ridiculous never never heard of i'm sure billionaire
people like the ross chow family and george soros would never put a hit on eppstein's head because
he fucked everything up and now everything's all wrong and the and the trafficking networks just
aren't working anymore clear clearly this was a suicide we all we all we all know it was we all
know it was the clinton's though right we know that mr eppstein got on his second story bed he said
look i'm going to do a flip right now i'm going to do a matt sidale for the shooting star press
and then he put more down and broke his neck that's clearly the narrative because you know believe
yeah uh well good good good you know good for him and glad he lived his he he lived his life
before it's raping children proud of my boy who'll make me proud of my boy eppstein
uh hey somebody fucking say something we i'm on my brain has been my brain has been rendered
smooth by this conversation i don't have anything voicemail if you want i guess we're going to voicemail
a shitload of them and we are going to be going for an hour and 18 minutes we have fewer than usual
but we have like a dozen or some some murd you want to do you want to hang out while we answer
voicemails or they just got here they just got things in general they are not about you nobody
nobody knows you're on until the episode comes out so no they're not about you specifically
so are we just done here like do you need me here anymore or i mean if you want to stick around
then sure if if nobody else has any you know a discussion i guess i guess we'll go to voicemails
unless uh yeah i don't know we you can you can i had my most pressing question answered which is
can i get paid to hold wonderbread in a picture maybe in the future i'm so into the idea
no i just want to be in a picture too for some cash digi really fucking wants to make some money
right now i just i just want to know if i can and it sounds like the answer is i could if you had
money so that's a good i mean that would depend upon like you know there's there's like a good
cute there's like chihiro from dank and rompa cute there's princess marco cute but like not every
3d equivalent of something that's cute is always cute you got to be convincing that's why it's called
yeah no yeah well there's good yeah i you know there's uh there's there's makeup there's filters
there's lots you can do you see snapchat is a wonderful thing it makes the reality the way i
want it to look yeah i have i have apps for that for on my instagram all my instagram pictures i
look different in every single one because i use different filters then you gotta sit digi down and
say his dream is this not gonna happen like you know you really want this to happen but it's not
um you mean you mean this this business arrangement it's it's questionable it can't
happen because there's nobody there's not enough money involved for it to ever for it to happen
anyways i don't know i mean i got my logic was that projects right i mean i already got
straight porn being made right now and i'm paying off in september i already got down payments i have
to fucking fulfill i'm running to missy talk dark money being fun what's okay i want to i don't ask
you said you one you said you do it part of the reason you do it is to raise your online profile
do you have like an end game of like once you're known enough you know like you're gonna do something
is this project all building to some conclusion i thought to myself there was no way i was ever
going to reach a pkp posting after roosterteeth themselves fucking did a video on my deviant
art and they were looking out over all my deviant art stuff and i got really disappointed because
they didn't look at any of the ruby art all my carefully constructed ruby art of assaulting in
winter making out and made my pp very big why wouldn't they look at that because they didn't
have the time to look at it and it makes me sad because y'all created ruby look at my ruby art
that's what i really want you to look at that seems like that would be the first thing they would
look at i don't know it doesn't make any sense to me first it was that then i had the creator of
mighty magisort straight up tell me that i'm the worst human being on the face of the planet i hope
nobody ever draws me commission art so there was that i had the guy who created cookie well do you
know what the guy who created mighty magisort has one of the shittiest podcasts ever and made fun
of it on w ATP once so fuck that guy i had the guy who created cookie cookie clicker mentioned me
frequently on tumblr for whatever reason because he thinks my shit i love that guy he thinks my
shitposting is amusing so there was that um i love what's his name he's like it's like drag
that's his name something like that i've been on the master's in show i'm thinking to myself it's
like that has to be the peak now i'm here i'm thinking to myself it's like i need to create a
you've reached an ever higher peak yeah yeah so so now that you've now that you've conquered the
world and been on the procrastinators podcast i mean where is there even to go from here obviously
to go back on the master's in show again because i have lots to talk about okay yeah sure um i think
as i was saying about you being a branding genius like you were you were saying that
you keep commissioning them partially just to keep your name out there and uh like you said it's
landed you on all these podcasts and like i have i have a similar kind of like um i perpetuate
the existence of fan art of myself by always reblogging any fan art that anybody makes of me
and it seems that's not as i don't see it as much i seem to get more fan art than most people
by way of like just constantly promoting the fan art i get because then like people see it and
they want to copy it and then it's like every time i get one a bunch more like follows soon
afterwards and it's uh it's a good way to it's like a good way to create a brand identity
without even having to like let's like not like i have like a cartoon version of me
that like exists solidified at a bunch of people's minds you know what i mean
i mean you know whatever floats your boat my god i'm just in this to kum i need pretty pictures
to kum too don't we all is that the note is that the note we want to go out on yeah i think so
murray do you want to listen to these fucking voicemails with us or you want to get going
not really i mean like i namely came to answer people's questions if y'all want me back on the
podcast like any other time or if the other guy wants to put me back on the mouse and show
him all for it but like if we're all done with things in relation to me i'm more than willing
to just dip and y'all can continue your podcast from here on out and i'm more than happy yeah
i'm more than happy to come back whenever y'all want me uh we might uh and uh yeah appreciate
appreciate you being on i was very excited when when pyro said like oh yeah i'm friends with
wonderbread guy i was like no no you can't mean you can't mean that wonderbread guy you're not
not the guy who everyone knows um but so it was so it was all right well i guess we'll move on
to voicemails and uh thanks thanks for talking you fucking weirdo i am a very big raging weirdo
but i'm proud of it amazing cool that's the right right way to live all right yeah well send me the
see you in hell never it uploads uh yep absolutely it will be up this friday yeah
all right cool thank you see thank you i love you at gross gay
nice uh well that was fucking that was based as hell shall we do the call god i just i just hate
i just hate how these uh i just hate how big how big tech how these big tech corporations are
employing their unpaid discord mods to uh uh to discriminate against me and create an extra
they do it for free just because just because just because i insulted their waifus and picked
fights with them you know this google google and facebook get the fuck out of here uh uh enough
the fucking jennies these fucking jennies they do it for free they do it for free i mean what
what more can you even say it was very that's very um who was that lawyer who defended the um
the oj simpson case oh fuck um wait wasn't it a kardashian um it was not no i think he defended
the other side i'm talking about the guy that was defending oj fuck he's famous there's a boondocks
parody to him right like he's been parodying the lots of stuff cockerin johnny cockerin
johnny cockerin it was the same way how like he would he would have make these little catchphrases
like if the if it doesn't fit you must quit and he would repeat it over and over again and it like
and it's stuck with the jerry yeah it's good marketing it's just it's just good marketing
okay so uh uh we've only got uh we've got less voicemails than usual this week the first one is
called uh we're on about it we're on it again it's called dickskin samurai no three two one go
i can't can you guys hear it i can't okay i can't hear it never mind next one is called uh co next
one is called kawaii samurai um three two one go sorry go ahead and go
konichiwa reno san to san please return buy some buy scroll okay yep next one good good yep scroll
got it uh next one is called uh not not this one is called not about circumcision so this is good
three two one go so about circumcision all right that's good that's good next one is called uh
next one is called i love the pcpo finally three two one go
so
it's just a song why does it sound like this was filmed on a phone microphone yeah but like like
he's not like rapping over a beat that he's playing in the background like
all right cool cool man thanks for the thanks for the voicemail uh next one is called next one
why why why he's so terrible next one is called thanks for making the pcp plus questions kafka
esk kaw three two one go hey guys i'm a long time fan of the show and i just wanted to say thanks
so much for making the pcp um your content means a lot to me and i appreciate all the stuff you
guys make oh wow okay moving on i have a series of four questions that i'd like to ask all of you
guys circumcision circumcision so the first is do you guys believe that people have an innate
responsibility to help one another why or why not the next is do you guys believe that unconditional
love is real why why not the third is does hardship really make someone stronger or do you believe
that's just a way to cope and finally would you guys prefer i do a drawing of brook and labud
or a picture of death the kid with liz and pat and tweeted at you guys all right thanks so much
thanks for making the pcp i really appreciate what you guys do um it's a little pretty big
questions in our own death the kid uh who is who is liz and pat the two girls are the guns
the gun girls that death the kid fights with uh oh you know wait i don't know what that's
from i don't fucking soul leader you do know what it's from god damn you've seen soul leader you
nerd i've seen the first three episodes of soul leader and i thought it was shit they introduced
definitely i did it i did i actually like soul leader a lot because of it actually like soul
leader a lot it's good it just doesn't it has a shitty ending because the manga was still going
and they had to wrap it up um but other than that it's great um well agreed wait i'm looking
at labudans better anyway liz and patty oh no they suck i don't like them uh the the other
questions he asked okay unconditional love uh uh no is is wait wait is unconditional love real uh
yes it is real but it shouldn't be i don't think it's real how do you think it's real what is it
what is that thing cool well it's when you it's when you love someone and no matter what they do
which is stupid like a like a decision you make i know i know i know that there are people who will
love somebody no matter how bad they are no matter how they mistreat them they shouldn't that is real
but that i would not i don't think that is unconditional per se like like how is okay that's
what it means the conditions are very very low bar well yeah exactly but it means it means the
conditions are very are in are unrealistically high that like it could never meet them to stop to
stop loving them there if there are people who will forgive someone literally anything there are
people who there okay but what i'm trying to say is like like okay so let's say that you have like
a brother and no matter what he does you'll still love him because he's your brother that's the condition
like it's can if you wouldn't do this for anybody you would only do this for your brother
because he's your brother but like yeah but like but this person being who they are there is nothing
they could do that would make you not love them i just can't imagine how you would find out like
like if you fall in love with someone then like it's not unconditional it's like there's something
about them that made you fall in love with them you know what i mean but like unconditional love
would have to just be like sprayed everywhere at all times because there's no condition but once
you're but once you're in now that's stupid once you're in love with someone if there's nothing
that could make you stop then that's unconditional there i don't i think there are people who i think
that is cope semantics is how is that cope like it's just fucking you know not you mean something
i'm saying that unconditional love is cope like it is i mean it's it's very bad and stupid and i
don't i don't think well it's it's like you're convincing yourself that's that no matter what
you will love this person because that is easier than having there have to be like conditions so
it's it's like the the condition for it to stop is this is none unconditional yeah yeah yeah that's
that's bad i don't like that i think it's very very rare that it actually gets to such a point
they need to be like totally mindbroken that nothing would like absolutely nothing would
change their mind i mean people people write like uh love letters to like murders and prison and stuff
so it's real what do you mean what the fuck what the fuck do you mean
eh i don't fight me i'm having a trouble understanding what this concept i'm having a
trouble i'm having a trouble right here let's move on he also has many other he said do we
do people have an innate responsibility to help each other i mean response there's no
any there's no such thing as an innate responsibility like responsibility is
something that we judge i think we made we made up i think it would be fair to say that we have
instinctual reasons to help one another that like compel does an innate like desire for people to
cooperate that's like just sort of like a an instinctual thing yeah a responsibility though i
don't know about that no no and then the last part he asked was hard does hardship make you stronger
or is that just absolutely yes it does hardship makes you stronger uh i think i think in some cases
it might i think there's a huge ripping off of the band aid effect that comes with almost everything
in life that like anything that you are like afraid of or build up in your mind that like once you
experience it it can never be like scary again you know like unless it was really fucking bad like
and you really don't want to go through it again you know i don't know going through going through
hardship can make you like more afraid and wary of i guess it can happen i guess it can be better
or worse it just depends on how well you deal with it like it's like you know muscle growth is you
tear it and then it builds back but you have to eat enough protein or else it's not going to build back
you know it's like if you're just tearing your muscles and not fucking eating anything so wait
what was this question that there was it does hardship make you stronger or is that just cope
i think there's it's not just cope but it can be yeah i think i agree it can some some
sometimes it can be like oh i came out of it and like now i learned what not to do or or i learned
that i that it's not as bad as i thought but sometimes it is as bad as you thought and sometimes
it just can like fuck you up and like ruin your worldview and like make you a more miserable human
being because like now you know if you take the you know the breaking of muscle analogy to bones
once you break a bone you're much more likely to break the bone in that one spot again and again
yeah yeah yeah it cuts both ways all right good questions though um the next one is called um
i'm stupid the next one is called uh trying to be fear and loathing in real life three two one go
okay all right next one is called uh pancakes all boomers must die three two one go hey pcp
you know it really grinds my gears or really butters my buns this one someone does something
that i don't really like and i criticize for it and some fucking boomer has the brass of balls to
say uh you know they have the right to do that yeah yeah yeah oh god i just want to get my fingers
around their necks in terms of the major's favorite shade of purple because for one i'm not saying
they don't have the right to do that that's a different conversation and second of all just
because someone has the right to do something doesn't mean it's always the right thing to do
and that's what i'm criticizing them for you boomers basis of fucking garbage uh i would just
agree with that yeah when you when you credit when you when you when you criticize someone
it's not you're not you can't always just be like oh well they have the right to do it because
that's not always the issue yeah it's it's it's like you just see something you say oh fuck this
it's like whether allowed to it's like that i the only fuck yeah the only time that like they have
the right to do it is the response is if the person is saying they can't do that or they
don't have the right to do it well if they do then maybe correct them but if that's not what
they're saying if they're saying oh this sucks like i you know this person is a piece of shit for
doing this it's not you know maybe they they might do something that's legal and still and that's
still be the case um so yeah i would just agree pancakes i would just agree um next one is called
in before god damn it three two one go
god damn
well i have three scripts so we will choose this one
oh okay i have a noto samurai sama return this samurai sama son here to avenge samurai
sama father but you can call me samurai sama ben no self return no samurai scroll because you
steal three more not just one three more power scroll magic scroll and super cake scroll normal
cake scroll you keep we want to super cake scroll but until next time so i'm sorry i'm sorry i did
these things then why did you keep stealing the scrolls i don't know i have a problem i have
addiction they're just so tempting they're just so you know i was playing i was watching
krug smash i was watching door door fortress and i just and i just saw all these books and scrolls
and i saw all the funny titles they had and i was like i want to find more i want to read more funny
descriptions of books and scrolls so i just start picking them up i just went into adventure mode
i started picking them up and here we are by the way yeah i was gonna say i wonder if samurai
sama has a fetish for ben sainz stealing a scroll and wonder bread and you know deforesting the
bamboo you you made you made a tweet gib yesterday that was it was the the the soy face for it was
the average average versus average others versus average myself you know yeah that one and i it's
the same meme as like a chad virgin like all the others all the names like typical Naruto fan
versus average one piece enjoyer and it's the soy guy versus the handsome man or whatever um but uh
i read that the average other and the average myself sound like titles of books that dwarves would
write um they're randomly generated i uh i just wanted to share that just wanted to share that
uh little little tidbit uh next one is called denis flimpo okay here it is uh there three two one go
hello this is denis i'm calling on behalf of flimpo's cucumber and zucchini exchange
i'm calling for um one ben german saint um it looks like your presence um friend zucchinis
and we can hold them for you for seven days so please uh try and get to the store in that time
and pick them up uh if you can't come and pick them up for any reason we would really appreciate
a call to cancel um but thanks and uh you know my number just call me back if you need anything um
you have a great one uh bye um what why did you call it to the podcast was this uh was this a
like was there did we was there a this of in response to something i don't i completely
don't obviously from that i have no idea what the fuck was going on obviously don't cancel my order
obvious i want those french zucchinis just hang on i'll figure it out i'll figure out uh what i'll
send a drone to i'll send a drone to pick them up i'll send a i'll send a boston laboratory
his fucking robot dog to uh just just duct tape it to its back and it'll it'll take him home to me
uh next one is uh they should call the boston dog boston uh thing dynamics they should call it
the boston terror or something like terrier the oh i get it those things are gonna be killing us
very soon those things are gonna have guns can't wait yeah eight uh next one is called truth bomb
three two one hold on wait what so wait sorry sorry yeah the next one and it's this one that's
five seconds uh i already listened to it because i thought you were gonna click on it and i agree
with it but now you can oh okay three two one go having your wisdom teeth pulled is the circumcision
of adulthood i mean i had my wisdom teeth i was a kid so oh really not really i all right i don't
know too much at least at least they sent that they say they anesthetize you to get your wisdom
teeth out isn't there like a a reason that they would take them out like it because they hurt
if they hurt yeah i mean okay grow bad is not an objective criteria you know like i don't know
like the thing about dentistry uh dentists are the worst people which is why they have such a
high suicide rate um and it's because dentistry is worthless it's just cosmetic it's not they
try to tell you there's all these fucking health benefits to cleaning your fucking teeth but truly
you just want to have white ass straight ass teeth so you look good on camera and but but the wisdom
teeth thing they push they push the teeth they push your other teeth in such a way that can make them
you know less straight or they can hurt personally i have wisdom teeth they don't hurt don't really
care to have them removed don't really see what the point is i i have wisdom teeth as well um
i i i i never understood every single time i see a dentist they're like i just assumed that if
you get them removed it's because like oh yeah you know you ever seen the picture that episode of
the simpsons where the Lisa goes the dentist and she gets braces and it's like if you don't have
braces your teeth will go fucking through your eyeball that'll happen if you don't okay braces
the worst meme in the whole universe because you wear them for years and then you wear a retainer
every day for the rest of your life so they don't straighten your teeth like they they will get them
into a position where you can maintain them in that position but i stopped wearing i stopped wearing
a retainer i actually like never wore my retainer and like it's fine like it didn't my teeth didn't
go back to being shit i've seen people's teeth go back to being shit before it was braces didn't
work but um you know uh shit well i was like oh yeah the every time you go to a dentist for any
reason they'll they'll they they frame it in that salesman like way where they'll say when are you
getting your wisdom teeth removed like when should i schedule you for a wisdom teeth removal like who
should i refer to you to and the response i always say is like do i need to have them out and they
well do they hurt or like they will hurt and i say well they don't hurt now so like do i need to
have them out they're like well i mean technically no i'm like well then why is it being framed to
me like it is absolutely inevitable that you are going to pull out my wisdom teeth but like they
frame it that way because they want you to spend the money on it obviously maybe maybe my parents
just fell for the meme i don't know everyone all society has fallen for the meme every time well
i mean in the uk they didn't push it on on me they just they're just sort of like i don't even remember
them saying anything about it actually i just go to the dentist they look around they say yeah that's
good americans are really weird about teeth we don't care about being fat as fuck we only care
about having straight white teeth it's a strange place uh next one is called down with mortality
propagandists three two one go have you ever been talking with someone about immortality
in there like oh yeah if humans weren't if humans didn't die then it would suck actually yeah there
would be no time with it on life i hate this meme this is good call already anything cooler
productive sooner than later we just procrastinate forever and lays around this always seems
strange to me because like by the very fact that this is framed as a negative it means that you
wouldn't let this happen like suppose you were immoral right and you were upset at the fact that
you're not doing anything you wouldn't think oh man i wish i had the ability to die because then
i would have a reason to do something no you would think man i should do something i'm not doing
something so i'll go do something yeah it's right it's is that not obvious it like what a stupid
what a stupid idea to be like oh boy well good it's it's good that we die because it like makes
people like you know make their fucking magnum opus or like who fucking anybody who thinks that
do that sorry anybody who thinks that clearly hates their life like yeah you'd have to you'd
have to be a fucking moron and like just have like absolutely no value to your own life to be like
it's good that one day i will cease to exist um yeah it's i mean it goes even further than just
that reason it's like like if you're immortal you can't die um you don't need to do anything
what's the problem with not doing anything yeah also yeah if you if if you're content
not doing anything i mean if you're not content then you have forever to do stuff there's always
like there's no downside really the arguments they always portray it as like oh i've been alive for
10 billion years and i'm so bored if only there was something that was interesting in this shonen anime
uh and i'm the villain uh-huh it's like it's i don't know whether i mean there's no way to
really know what happens to the human brain but like the reason people go crazy when they get
older is not because it they live for a long times because human bodies age and they become
decrepit and they the cells die and then they they lose their functionality if you didn't have any
of that if you just were fine forever i don't know whether anything of that is bad would happen
i mean i mean i guess eventually overpopulation like we might just i don't know if everyone's
immortal you mean if if like yeah if the entire world were just like choked with humans but like
i don't think that would necessarily be a problem it's just there's just like not enough biomass
oh this happens in final fantasy 13 lightning returns and uh everybody becomes immortal and
they just stop being able to have kids and so there's just like the same people who are around
for like five thousand years that's what that's what happens in 17776 is one day everyone just
stops aging and stops being able to have kids and the world just becomes a complete and it's
awesome like it's so awesome i want to live in 17776 but lightning returns is pretty cool too uh
there's like all these odin gods and shit running around doing stuff it's neat there was this there
was this like um uh dnd like green text post thing i i read once which was really interesting um and
it reminds me of this this idea that like if if you could have children and you were immortal
the amount of human mass would just continually like grow out of control and the the dnd post was
like there was a skeleton and it had the ability to summon a skeleton that could summon a skeleton
and then um they failed at killing the skeleton and after a few rounds there was like a hundred
skeletons it was multiplying exponentially and so they had to run they had to run far away
and the skeletons never stopped and they just sort of like they saw in the in the distance
there was like a writhing mass of bones constantly undulating and growing and and it was taking over
the entire planet and the sea and they were like all over the place it was just like oh my god
yeah it's like it's like doubling itself every round yeah and it's like they couldn't do anything
and then like they all died the entire planet became filled with skeletons so that you couldn't
see it the skeletons continued to grow outwards until the mass of the skeletons was so great
that it collapsed in on itself and it became a black hole or a supernova
yeah something something like and it created a new star and that star was like named after
like the event and then in their future dm campaign uh dungeons and dragons campaigns that
star was in the sky and they could like look at it that's so funny that's so fucking funny so that's
that's what would happen if you could still have kids and be immortal is that if unless we
spread out we would become okay if you're immortal does that mean you cannot die or just that you
don't die of natural causes i would assume you just cannot die if you can't die then i don't know
that's that that's weird and like yeah i guess maybe you would just eventually just choke the whole
world with humans but that seems like stupid like if you could die of natural causes like and
we did just eventually use up all of like the carbon on earth and like to create biomass for
human beings eventually there would just be no more human beings and we would just have to literally
have to eat each other in order to like feed on anything god it's such a cool premise for a place
because there'd be nothing else to eat there'd be no more plants or animals all carbon on the world
would be devoted to human being human life uh yeah like like like the magma the the mantle or whatever
is like all it was how would that even happen like all of the rock that makes up the earth gets
replaced slowly with human biomass this is filled the human like it just becomes the earth is just
filled to the core with a writhing mass of beings crammed in gross oh cool um that's that's what
hell i have to address the the other thing about immortality that everybody always is like
i don't want to be immortal because i have to watch all my friends die and everybody you love
die if you're like the only one i'm sure that would suck but like i'm sure that would suck the thing is
a you're gonna do that anyway if you live long enough like but like yeah you can make more friends
like it's it's like it's like like the like the logical conclusion of that is like oh
they're so so what you're saying is that you should kill yourself now before anyone you know dies
right yeah like that's what you're saying you want like death is prefer death is preferable
to seeing someone you love die yeah that's what you're saying right people seem to think that
they're going to like run out and like the only reason that old people like run out is that they
know they're going to die and so they don't like make an effort to like make a bunch of new things
begin in their life it's like when you it's it's hard to like even for young people like
young people don't want to hang around old people because they know they're going to die soon you
know like the the the attraction of being younger is knowing how much potential is ahead of you
you know and like i think that the the way that human life tends to be structured is just based
on the fact that we happen to live the amount of time we do but like if you were immortal
you would just have no reason to ever stop being involved in everything you know in the
world like personally i want to be able to see like the ramifications of things across generations
you know like i can see like i get to watch the effects of my actions for as long as i'm alive
for what if i got to see like the ripple of that across fucking thousands of years you know um
i want to know what's going to happen to humanity i'm interested in this story
it sucks that i don't get to see very much of it you know i think absolutely the only real thing
that could be like oh it's bad to be immortal is not for the person who is immortal but it's like
you could become a villain that is unstoppable and you could start just for fun just fucking with
other people and murdering them and you'll be like yeah i mean i've killed so many people it
doesn't even feel that bad anymore in the same way that seeing your friends die over and over again
for thousands of years you'd be like yeah that friends die that's normal it doesn't already feel
that way you could easily like get dull to a lot of things and then you could be the bad guy and
that's i feel that way just from having like because i've moved so many times in my life that
like the idea that people just pass through your life is very normal to me like yeah you just sometimes
just don't see motherfuckers anymore you know so like yeah to me the idea is like but you like
that doesn't prevent you from newly having a best another best friend you know like there's always
going to be interesting people you want to hang out with so like you know just because some of them
die doesn't mean the new ones aren't springing up for you to hang out with you know like there's
always going to be somebody who's interesting yeah agree uh yeah fun things like trying to be like
mortality for 100 years straight but by a similar token uh it's not the same but i feel like it's
related people there's always one idiot at like any party who if pressed will say like oh yeah i kind
of think like humanity should be destroyed lol like we are the virus and like i fucking hate those
people if we are the virus we will be we will be corrected anyways like those people are sick but
like it's been normalized it's been normalized as sort of like like baby's first edgy take that's
like how the world would be better off without humanity like fuck you like go fuck yourself i
don't know start with you yourself please literally start with yourself like if you think
be the change you want to see like i know like i know humanity does bad things to other people
to other species but i'm not a other species i'm a human and as a human i am i'm i'm bigoted in
my own favor i i am invested in humanity's success like sorry if that's a fucking problem for you
there's a there's a guy there's a guy that i started following i don't know why on twitter
he's some kind of like he's some kind of like like um anarcho primitivist like like eco terrorist
communist guy or whatever and he says that like he's he's he's he's he's super like pro animal
rights but he if that's not even good enough for him he says like yeah like humanity like
fuck humanity uh we need to protect animals but even that's not good enough because animals
would just be colonizers like humans if they could even animals are like too are too corrupt
only only the plants and fun guy like our our true allies yeah this is a good argument
i don't know why um i thought he was funny that anyway yeah um life isn't it good yeah
but plants fight each other too the trees they hug all of the sunlight for the little flowers
underneath so we need to chop down all the trees there's trouble with the trees for the maples
want more sunlight and the oaks ignore their pleas but but they don't do it on with on purpose
they don't do it with malice of forethought we'll see the trouble with the maples and they're quite
convinced they're right is that the oaks are just too lofty and they grab up all the light but the
oaks can't help their feelings if they like the way they're made and they wonder why the maples
can't be happy in their shade no it's a rush song and then pacifica northwest comes in she destroys
them all makes bread well at the end they they pass along yeah they pass a law that the trees are all
kept equal by hatchet ax and saw oh my god yeah one from the law x soldier rides away uh it's
libertarian propaganda about how how socialism bad i think
uh wait is that is that what rush is like i think that song is at least some like i mean the
message of the song is basically that like you know uh the the maples are like the oaks are
taking up all of our sunlight and they're like well there's nothing we could do about it and they're
like yeah there is what will all be equal and so they all get cut down like oh man you ever you
ever read that book animal farm you ever read animal farm that like fairy tale like yeah man
like communism would never work lamal uh uh that's the proof uh you ever hear that rush song nah dude
we need fucking like billionaires to have child sex slaves in my opinion uh next one next one or
or is there more yes next one is called a hot water is amazing and margar is gay three two one go
hey so have you guys ever thought about how you just turn a tap and you can get hot water
that is pretty fucking amazing when you really think about it like it was only like what a couple
of thousand years ago we couldn't maintain a fire we couldn't even start a fire and now us hairless apes
at the point where we can just turn a tap and we instantly get hot water that is pretty fucking
amazing that's like our greatest accomplishment good on us if there is anything anything at all
that we should be thankful for it is the ability to get hot water all right i get it hot water and
there's also one more thing that we should be thankful for and it is a me samurai summer
fuck are you i'm sorry sorry about the scroll sorry about the scroll all right yeah hot water is
pretty good uh are some of these people like duplicates are they like doing the voice i can't
tell i yeah that one sounded like it was an imposter i don't know that we we we we we just can't know
they got the naruto a shadow clone shadow clone jutsu yeah yeah exactly next next one is called
sebek three two one go fencing more like based saint you said this on twitter and i agree wow thank
thanks very much next one is called cross music in other languages uh there it is three two one go
you guys were talking about accents and language in the last episode and it got me curious what you
think about music and other languages personally i think it's fantastic it's a great way to gain
comprehension in a language plus there's the whole point that they made in his anime and music video
about how if you don't understand what's being said completely you can imprint whatever you find
to be the most appealing message onto a song also i don't know if anyone can relate to this but i
feel like music and languages that are not english tend to have way better instrumentals i don't know
thoughts uh i think that's just not true i don't i don't think you're right about that i don't
think you're right about that last one i think you're probably just maybe paying more attention
to the instrumentals maybe because you can't focus on the words um i i like listening to uh foreign
music obviously tons of japanese music and like there's lots of countries that like make music
that sounds like stuff that would be from america or the uk like influenced by that stuff just sings
in english because like they want to have more global appeal ah so i i've i've um recently
discovered some like saharan desert like prog rock that sounds like jimmy hendrix but it with like um
islam islamic uh you know singing it's really cool it's like a language the arabic islamic
arabic where'd you where'd you study in arabic yeah look i um stupid okay do you send a link
to that band uh yeah let me let me get have you wait have you have you kept studying arabic
actually i i sort of dropped off because because the um the app sort of it's sort of
it got to a peak of like what it could teach me with me like learning new stuff i was just
sort of doing the same things over and over again and i needed i needed to like step up the amount
the the level of teaching in order to actually learn how to like speak it and and stuff and i
never went into that much because the app was so easy i needed i needed to like study it like a real
thing and they're like that's hard i don't want to do anything definitely sounds hard lamal um yeah i
like music in other languages like fucking i was a kid listen to fucking anime op's and be like ah
this is so beautiful what a beautiful language i don't know what it means but it you just it
could just entirely focus on the melody and it can mean whatever you want it to me there are certain
languages that have like different advantages when it comes to being sung and i think that
english is a language that is popular because partially because it sounds really good in music
um broad range of vowel sounds like japanese there's only five vowel sounds that they use
in their language so like um you know there's like a lot of cleanliness to japanese singing because
of the fact that like again they only use like uh they only use syllables like full syllables to
communicate so like their words are more simple and easier to pronounce and easier to make melodies
out of um i i don't okay i could be wrong but i think i read something by like an essay or maybe
it was an intro to lolita by nabokov the the guy who wrote lolita and other books too um and i think
he said that he wrote because he was russian but he wrote in english he like lolita is not translated
he wrote it in english and he wrote him any other books in english too and i'm pretty sure the reason
why is because he found english was like a very lyrical language or a poetic language or a language
that he found it was easy to make like like like a poetic like illusions and like similes and
metaphors and stuff with i think he just found english to be good for that better than russian
so i guess some languages are more like that than others in ways yeah i think it depends on like
that like you said lyrical and like i'm thinking about like the difference between lyrical and
poetic as like how they could because i'm thinking about like how lyrical miracle spiritual like in
chinese they have like ridiculous amounts of like metaphors and different meanings for words to the
point that there's like this one poem that famously is just like she written like 50 times but it's
all different definitions of she um but like uh buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo yeah like that but
much more extreme um yeah and like so chinese has that advantage of like it can be extremely
metaphorical and poetic and impressionistic um but like it doesn't sound as good sung because
there's so much like uh of the throat i think that has to be like used you know like a lot of
languages that use more like it's like it's not as easy to say that english everything is just
you know like that's what it sounds like center it sounds like center language wait
wait was that a creed or who who is that an impression of uh fuck that songs by like i don't
counting crows or something wait wait wait is that hoody in the blowfish
no it's like a really mellow song Dave Matthews band no no it's mellower than any of that it's
it's that it's that band with with the black um front man that is hoody in the brush fish but
oh okay you're right all right the the guy i was thinking of was mudo mokta i don't know how to say
his name i think that's it i posted a link he's like he's just so cool he's he's playing the guitar
upside down like hendrix clearly inspired by that and he's just like singing about stuff and and it's
got that that uh his definite like a definite different like tone to like the way they're playing
it he looks so awesome not western he looks so awesome in this like with his his his turban and
his like face fail it's like so rad i don't know that's good um
i don't know good any more of uh voicemails there's one more yeah sorry there's one last one and um
wait fucking fucking posts please there we go this one is called salty dog three two one go
okay so ben was talking about super salty stuff yeah and it reminded me of this game that i used
to play with friends at some gatherings uh called salty dog where what you do have however many
people at a table you get that many sugar packets you rip them all open but fold them over so the
contents don't come out but one of them you pour it out and replace it with salt so then you mix up
all of the sugar packets everyone grabs one at random and three two one you just pour it into your
mouth all together at the same time and one person is the unlucky fool who is the salty dog who gets
a mouthful of like a whole packet of salt at once this is just russian real entertaining ragcon five
salty dog tournament win this is just russian roulette with salt i mean isn't a big full mouthful
of sugar also a bit weird i guess it's not as bad no it's not that bad no i used to eat sugar just
like i used to go to mcdonald's and just grab handfuls of sugar packets stuff them in my pockets
and then just drink them like one at a time all day i mean i probably wouldn't love it that's very
america core yeah yeah that's true uh uh it's yeah i was back also around the time i used to just
like eat sweet and condensed milk by the spoonful i wonder what a i'll eat i'll eat honey by the
spoonful i love honey some people don't like it uh uh jenny nicholson said in a video she had to
eat a spoonful of honey and she was like ew gross i hate it and i i was like shocked and horrified
no that's great what are you talking about i do you think i would gag if i ate that much at once
of it probably i i a spoonful of well depends on the size of the spoon i guess i'm picturing the
largest spoon i can think of like it's like a pretty big spoon i could i i like a jar of honey
fine tablespoon i'll take it i'll take a jar of honey and just squirt a whole bunch of it into my
mouth like no problem no problem i love it um sounds like it would taste like well yeah obviously
i wonder what it would taste like if a packet of salt if you ate a miracle berry you know about
miracle berries no i think we've talked about them before there those like berries that you can eat
and they make your tongue different so like you can't taste sourness anymore oh and it's like it's
like if you eat a miracle berry you can then like eat like drink like pure lemon juice or like drink
vinegar and like it doesn't taste bad it tastes different i wonder if that would
affect like a packet of salt or or maybe you wouldn't i don't know we'll have to find out
we'll have to do an extensive i've always wanted i always wanted to try a good video idea like numb
your tongue with this stuff and then see what different shit happens we're like what happens
people have done it this people have done it um i just want to try it for myself uh it's got some
kind of chemical that like binds to your like sensory receptors on your tongue in a way that
like changes how they process data um but yeah i would we should i want to run the in in in in
addition to um if rad radcon five god willing uh we should do a salty dog tournament alongside our
digimon i don't even like the the thought those those two words one after another my mind went
white and like i the almost passed out what radcon five yeah are you okay are you gonna be fine
just the thought of be even considering being ready for that yet oh no yeah no no no no no no no
i'm talking about this will be 20 000 years in the future craig lost craig it's okay he got he got
everything he needed um all right uh well hell that's the last that's the last fucking voicemail
i think we're done let's wrap it up then ladies um people were excited people were excited that one
time when it was like you two were on and someone said this is the first this is the first episode
of the pcp with a majority female cast and everyone said yes queen more female drone operators as well
yeah oh in kazi again more female deforesters uh more women of color please uh cutting down the
rainforest cutting down a forest it seems like something she would do cutting down a pumpkin patch
just grinding it up into a fucking into a machine and that's like fern gully it's it's
terrible uh are we done is it bye everybody uh
speak that by don't want to become a pacy pacy patron the procrastinators
also don't forget um to do the other stuff that you have to do that i don't buy
you