Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemails for the Minecraft stream. I really want to have Redcon funded by you. We can be procrastinators.
Hello. Welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Podcast.
Podcast. We need a flag.
A flag?
Yeah, we need a flag for podcasters rights.
Oh.
What colors would it be? What would be the stripes?
I can't even begin to think of what color podcasters are on visual. What's the color of sound?
We need it to be like a rainbow, but like better. It needs to be better than the gay pride flag because they've been taken all the good will. We need to outdo them.
Well, a simple, completely black skull and crossbones, but with microphones. Skull and microphones. Two skulls facing each other with a microphone in the middle, pirate flag.
What are podcasters, if not modern day pirates?
Criminals.
Pillaging, murdering, yeah, just fucking up everything for their own personal gain.
Just sailing the seas of the airwaves of the internet for monetary gain. It's the same.
Pirates made a living, and so do we.
Why can't we?
Sometimes. Why can't we?
I say that John McAfee was like a modern day pirate, but in my opinion, I'm a lot more similar to that lofty ideal.
I was complaining about the trans flag because I'm insanely transphobic and insane.
I saw that flag and I got really upset. I said, too political, take it down.
What are you talking about?
No, I was asking my discord because I've been confused why there's the black and brown stripe.
Because to me, if the stripes all mean a different thing, like there's the trans colors and there's the thing.
Oh, you mean like the big, like everything flag.
Well, no, not even the everything flag, just the one that's the rainbow, but then there's the triangle, the chevron, and there's the trans colors and there's the black and brown stripe.
I don't know which one that is.
It's also called the progress flag?
If you just Google LGBT flag.
No, that's the everything flag, isn't it?
That was what I meant.
Oh, well they've been, I mean, some people have been making ones with even more stripes and even more chevrons.
Sometimes as a joke, sometimes as like a, this is fucking stupid, we have too many colors or whatever.
You ever see the ones that have like 50 fucking stripes on them?
It's like the ace flag, the lesbian flag, the gay flag, the rainbow.
It really could be just the pan.
Yeah.
Like I don't know, like do they have a fabric shortage?
You could just fly multiple flags together.
I was thinking you could just fly multiple flags, but I was complaining because the visual implication of the black and brown stripe to me is that being non-white means you're part of LGBT.
And I don't think that's true.
Yeah.
But I mean that, that wasn't the intention.
I guess that the intent of the flag is more like marginalized groups.
The, I think, I saw a video, I saw a video by a YouTuber who, I guess, the YouTuber is JJ McCullough, who I don't even, I don't even like him, but I thought he made a pretty good video about this flag.
The, I think the intent of the stripes is not like black and brown people are also LGBT.
It's like a, it's like a, it's, it's like a solidarity thing.
It's like a, you know, black and brown people of queerness are also included.
I don't know.
I think it's weird.
I think it's weird that it's kind of become the main flag.
I mean, whatever.
But why did I bring this up?
I literally, I had a point to make with this.
And now I don't remember what it was.
Is it because insanely transphobic Ben Sain is coming out as insanely racist as well?
I'm coming out as transgender and transracial.
So now I need, I need all the stripes I can get.
Oh, no, it was, I thought it was interesting because in the video he mentions that, you know, they make all these different flags.
There's the trans flag and there's the MLM flag and the WLW flag and the ACE flag and the whatever.
And they're all different stripes.
And, and some people, I guess, according to the video, it's, don't like it because it's like, okay, the whole, kind of the whole point of the rainbow is that it includes everything.
Yes.
So it's a little bit like, it's a little bit missing the point against the original intention to be like, we need to add more stripes.
We need more colors because it doesn't include mine.
It doesn't include my stripes.
It's, it's, it's the, um, yeah, the whole rainbow thing.
Well, actually, I don't know why it's a rainbow.
The, the, the, the, the original flag.
It, he, I learned this in that same video.
Um, he, he just made a video about this like two days ago.
Uh, it was, it was literally an American politician like made the flag.
The rain, just the, no, no, it was, there was a guy, a politician and his friend who I guess were both involved in, in gay rights stuff.
And the, they, they designed the flag and then they sort of pushed it as sort of a part of their, this guy's political campaign.
So like it was made by a politician as sort of like a, I am running on like a pro gay rights agenda.
We're going to fly this rainbow flag and it means gay rights.
Uh, that's where it comes from.
Wow.
Another factoid that I learned, another factoid that I learned is that, okay, yes, there was the rainbow flag and then not too, a little, a while ago, at some point in the last couple of decades, someone as a statement made a version of the flag that just added the brown and black stripes on top, just to the normal rainbow.
Yeah, I remember that.
And then, and then someone else added, and, and then there was this, this artist decided there were too many stripes, so he redesigned it to have the, the triangle, the chevron is what that triangle is called.
Uh, but he, but that guy, and that, and this one with the trans triangle and the black and brown triangle stripes on top of the regular rainbow, that's sort of the one that has taken off recently.
But that guy who designed it thinks that he owns it and thinks that it's his and he should like be the, the only one who can sell it.
Yeah.
Okay.
Good luck.
The whole thing was, with, with adding to a flag until everything is on the flag, because that's the ultimate conclusion of an idea like that is, oh, we've got to include everything, otherwise it's in, in like implicitly not included, even though it is kind of like to add everything in would make the flag a mess,
because you would eventually have to add like so many different things that would become, I don't know, lame looking.
Apparently, apparently the six stripes of the original rainbow, they stand for like the elements of harmony, basically, they literally were meant to stand for like honesty, loyalty, integrity, courage, courage.
I mean, not literally those, but six things like that.
I googled and I found, I found the bear culture, the bear brotherhood flag, which is, it's a, you know, a subset of gay is to be like the big muscular hairy guy gay.
That's what I'm, that's what I'm going for.
That's what I'm going for.
My squad is going up.
I squatted to plate.
I squatted to 25 recently.
I'm going to the moon bear bear, bear pride.
Here I come.
So it's like, would there be a twink flag?
Would there be a twunk flag?
Would there be like every single possible permutation of being gay?
It's like, as long as there are flags that people can come up with, there'll be a, some sort of a precedent to add it to this flag.
I just feel like it does miss the point of like waving a flag around is supposed to be like an iconic symbol that people can rally behind.
So if people are thinking, oh, my color is not included.
Even though they added these other colors, it's just going to just make people feel like they're not included.
Even though they are, they should be.
And it's just, it's making, making it difficult to, to rally behind as like a tool for like, for like marketing, you know, to, to put in a protest and say,
swing the flag around and say, this is awesome.
We're going to kill you, other people who are evil and trying to put us down.
But if they're fighting amongst themselves as to what to put on the flag, it's a bit, it's a bit, uh, dumb.
Gay?
Oh.
Sorry.
Oh, you, you.
I, I think, I actually think, uh, I, I mean, yeah, obviously, obviously you can't just, you can't just add more stripes.
To a stripe flag to be like, we need to include more things, right?
Eventually it just becomes a mess.
I've seen Twitter ones that have like, let me try and find one of the, uh, I don't even want to fucking Google for it.
But you know, you can imagine one that has like 49 fucking stripes and 15 triangles on it.
Um, uh, uh, I think that the concept of like all like LGBT specific flags are in the form of stripes.
And you just chain and changing the colors of the stripes changes which like variation of queerness or whatever you're, you're representing.
I think that's a cool idea.
That's a little bit like, that reminds me a little bit of like a, of like a, you know, like an old like coat of arms thing, how like, you know, you'd have, um, you would have like a base color and then you might, there might be design elements that like maybe two houses would share, right?
They'd have like, they'd both have like quartered colors, but then like one would have like a different things in the quarters.
And another one might have the same things, but the same design and the same elements, but like represented in different colors to represent that they're like a sister house or something.
I think that's a cool design philosophy in general.
I think I feel like this, the one that is like taken off, as you say.
Apparently it's called the progress flag.
Progress flag.
Like I don't think it's that terrible.
Like it's, it's not like a bad looking necessarily.
But it looks good.
No, it looks good.
So like it's, it's just the, the, the idea that it invites to be added on with, but I feel like as long as it gets too, if it gets too ugly, people will not care about, you know, changing it.
The black and brown stripe, the black and brown stripe, they might, they might offend me, you know, I might want that black and brown stripe to have their own water fountain, but at least white people get the whole triangle.
So we're still winning.
I mean, I could see this, like if there was like a protest, there'd be like a big flag of this, the progress flag, and then three separate flags, the trans flag, the gay flag, and then like the black power fist, like a cool, like, like some, I don't know whether that's like an official, if they have like a flag for that exactly.
But you know the thing.
I mean, yeah, there's the, yeah, there's the black lives matter flag, which is the words on the black and white bars.
And there's the fist.
I don't know if the fist has like a name is do people do like just a black fist with the white.
There's the white black flag with the white.
I typed in black power flag and it was like a red, black and green, which pan African red black and green.
Yeah, something.
I mean, it seems more specific.
That seems more specific.
The fist seems like the most.
Yeah, I mean, the fist is iconic.
The fist is iconic.
Oh, fist in the shape of Africa.
That's a cool.
I like flags.
I like vexillology.
Remember the, remember, not shackles for heckles, the draw cast, we did the draw cast, we all did flags.
Oh, yeah.
Fucking find that in our fucking backlog.
If you dare.
Which one did you make?
I remember making one and I found, I thought it was like quite good.
What year was that?
It must have been like two years ago.
My art is like separated into like years that I did things.
Was it 2018?
We did that one.
Could be.
I can't see it.
I remember that munchies flag just naturally had the, he just put the fist on it.
In hindsight.
Yeah.
I thought that, I think that's funny.
I think his flag was like, it was like black and white and purple.
So I guess he's, I guess he's ace or whatever.
Is that the, is the ace flag, the black and white and purple one?
Your color choices determine what you are.
You have no say.
That's, absolutely.
I mean.
It's a good thing I like the trans colors then.
The trans colors are really nice.
They're just universally lovely together.
Yeah, that's true.
I like, I like the, I like the agender and like the aromantic flags.
I think that's what the green and gray one.
Wait, what's, what's, agender has the black and what, black and gray stripes with the
one green stripe down the middle.
Oh my God.
Oh, okay.
What?
Look at this.
Look at this one.
I just, I've never seen this one before, but guess what it is.
Um, Reebok.
I don't know.
Rubber, it's a rubber pride.
So it's a little, it's a little cheeky.
It's not like a real thing, but.
Oh, they shouldn't.
They should have been.
It looks crazy though.
It looks awesome.
They should have put little white bits on the, on the black, like highlights, like to
make it look like rubber.
Know what I mean?
I know what you mean, but I feel like that might make it too busy.
I like how it's just geometric.
Maybe just replace one of the stripes with a, with a white one.
I just got to have some white in there, you know, being white.
Being white, being white.
I don't feel, honestly, I see the rubber flag and I don't see my skin color and my particular
brand of leather kink on there and I feel excluded by it.
The age, enter and a romantic both have green.
I like the colors on the aromantic flag.
Look at that.
It looks awesome.
That.
Yeah.
Gray is a great addition to anything.
True.
It feels like the aromantic would make a great like draw cast a, what do you call it, color
amount, not a lot.
Oh, the pallet, the pallet.
Limited color pallet.
Limited pallet.
That's a good limited pallet.
Those, that limited pallet challenge was rad.
Yeah.
Hey, I'm, I'm a genius.
I made genius works out of it.
Oh, no, I'm scrolling on this.
I went to the site to find.
No.
I went to the site to find the flags and I'm scrolling down and I'm seeing all those shitty
like sponsored ads for stuff.
And corporations.
Yeah.
The corporate and I just, I just saw one that's Caitlyn Jenner.
No makeup photos.
Confirm the rumors.
And this picture of her.
This isn't real.
She looks like a fucking burn victim.
That's not what she looks like.
Is it?
Oh my God.
That looks like it was taken in the jungle.
And when she was on, I'm a celebrity.
Get me out of here.
I mean, scary, scary stuff.
Scary.
She looks like fuck.
She looks like fucking Ebert after his jaw got taken out.
She's just doing one of those mouth movements.
There's one of those.
That's, that's what it looks like when she pugs, you know?
Jenner pugs.
Isn't she like running for senator or some shit?
I don't know.
Governor or something, mayor, whatever.
She's running herself into the ground.
That's right.
Let's see here.
All right.
So I wanted to, we're recording this episode a little early and now it's, it's almost three
anyway.
I wanted to record early because Munchy is like, apparently he's like leaving the state
for like the rest of summer.
He's going to be on the west coast for like the rest of the summer.
I didn't know this, but I guess we're going to hang out one last time before he goes.
And I wanted to, yeah, I wanted to get there.
So I was like, hey, so last night I'm like, hey, can we do the PCP early?
I want to do it at noon.
I want to do it three hours early.
And eventually you were like, yeah, okay.
And then I responded and I was like, uh, actually I stayed up all night playing
Minecraft and I don't want to get up that early anymore.
So let's push it back two of those three hours that I wanted to say.
You pushed it back to one and then you said, now push back to two, just pushing it back
back to three hours.
Um, but you know, I had a real great time playing Minecraft.
I, I have, I have gotten really, I was on the PCP Minecraft server, which you can join
at the patreon.com slash the pro crassinator.
Uh, I've gotten really into the Thaumcraft mod and I have, uh, I'm turning, I am
turning my slime cave into a sort of inverted wizards tower where it's a big, like black
obelisk that extends under the ground and it has like all these rooms and staircases.
And oh no, I set it all up.
I've, I've have it all set up so that now when you put stuff into the, uh, what's it called,
the smelter, you put stuff into the smelter.
And it, it extracts the Ascension and it pumps it through a pipe into a room with all these
jars and it like squirts out of the, of the, of the pipes and it like flies through the
air as like ghostly little beams and it goes into its little jars and all the jars are
arranged around the, um, uh, what's it called the, like the thing that like can like automatically
like make stuff for you.
And that thing has a little attachment on it that will automatically suck up Ascension
from like the jars all around it and like, and do the, do the production tasks.
Uh, uh, it's all very, it's all very, and I have a little study next to that.
I have a little, a little study, you know, I'll get, I'll get in to Minecraft after this
is done and I'll take screenshots of my study and my smelter room.
Uh, it's, it's a work in progress.
Most of the rooms are empty, but it's, uh, also it's all, it's all made of coal.
Uh, I wanted black, I wanted black walls.
So all of my, all of my walls and hallways are made of coal.
Uh, just cause it looks nice.
I was about to say you could go to the Nether and get like the basalt, but that's all new
stuff and the server's still in something.
No, there's no, no, there is basalt.
Yeah, there's basalt, there's basalts in, uh,
or is it one of those special too many items or not that?
I use, I use basalt for the floors.
The floors and the ceilings are basalt and the walls are coal.
There's lots of different, um, and then in the latest Minecraft, I haven't played it,
but my brother was telling me, um, that there's like, I kind of remember, there's like
deep cobble, which is like black cobble that you can just find in, in veins.
Deep cobble, deep cobble.
That's so cool.
And, and there's like variants of like gravel and stuff, mulch, mulch is sort of weird,
gravelly, something or other.
So many variations of stone things you can get that are basically just decorative as far as I know.
Yeah.
Deep cobble looks great.
I'm curious about deep cobble.
There is a, I've gotten into the Thaumcraft mod, but there is, there is, I want, there's a dark purple block.
It's basically like metamorphic fungal stone, which I would have to do the other like big magic mod, botania.
I would have to do some botania to get the, uh, metamorphic fungal stone.
But it sure would look nice in my, in my duck and dark black and purple tower.
Chiseled, uh, obsidian, chiseled obsidian is, is purple and it looks great.
And I've sort of been like embedding it into various places in the walls, sort of as decoration.
Uh, just for a little, just for a little, just for a little splash of color.
And I would, I would like to have some, I would like to have some, some fuelium, some like fuelium flowing like down the walls or like through like shafts or whatever.
Because fuelium has a nice, lovely, uh, bright green color.
Uh, Minecraft.
Cobble.
Deep cobblestone.
You mean cobbled deep slate?
Oh, maybe that's what it's called.
There's cobbled deep slate.
There's another stone called blackstone.
I typed, I typed in deep cobble and I got real life images.
I didn't know, I didn't know fucking stones were real.
You got images from Kabul.
I got images from people like garden, like, like patios and.
Oh yeah.
Oh wait, are we, are you tell, wait a minute.
Are you telling me that Minecraft is based on a real thing?
I suppose I am.
There's a real, you think that we'd stone, I thought stone was just in a video game.
Oh my God.
It's funny because like cobblestone, cobble is like a very, it's a word that nobody used really to describe things because cobbled streets were so, you know, antiquated.
Cobblestone in Minecraft.
Cobblestone is in Minecraft is not like cobblestone in the real world.
In the real world, it's a very like deliberately placed and like very, very, you know, work labor intensive way of making like a very beautiful sort of rustic path.
In Minecraft, it's just you break a fucking rock and it crumbles into pieces and it becomes cobblestone.
And I don't like it.
I don't like that.
Bricks.
The real life cobblestone is more like is more like what in the game is bricks.
So out of notch, take a fucking get off eight Chan.
Take a take a breather from decoding the latest Q drop and and fix it, please.
Thank you.
That's rude.
I showed him that'll teach him.
You there.
What's up?
What happened?
Internet gone.
Internet fucking gone.
Anyway, I was going to say they were cobbled together.
And that was what I was going to say.
Good, good joke.
I had to say you're waiting for like 10 minutes.
Well, not 10 minutes.
It's so different because there's only two of us.
If one of us gets internet troubles, that's it.
Otherwise, before when I would when I would have internet troubles, I would be gone and nobody would fucking notice.
And then I would come back.
Nobody wouldn't.
We would just be like, oh, we got it.
The show must go on.
Not anymore.
Now we're hanging by a thread.
Now the show must end.
The show must never go on.
The show must end.
Yes.
Absolutely.
Let's see.
Oh, yes.
So I guess whenever we finish here, I will immediately be catching the next bus to go over to see Munchie
and Kazi and those dudes and see him fucking say bye for summer.
I didn't even know he was leaving.
I didn't know he was going to be gone for the rest of the summer until like a few days ago.
But he is.
Lamal.
Maybe we'll get ramen again.
Soup Shack.
I think I might have mentioned last week that I started writing Road to Radcon Chapter 5, which I am sorry to say I did not get to complete it this week.
I have had a very busy week.
I've been very preoccupied with trying to avoid Tom's fate.
Tom mentioned that the Massachusetts unemployment stuff fucked him over and I guess was asking him to like pay back a bunch of money.
I have had to go through a lot of my old documents and like remake stuff and count up like money I made over like 2019 and 2020, like month to month to report it to the agency.
Yeah, the deadline was the other day.
They were asking for like fact finding documentation.
They wanted proof that I am in fact self-employed in Massachusetts.
So I spent like two days being like, oh my God, I can't find all my 1099s because when you're self-employed, right?
That's the documentation that you need is the 1099 is the tax form that they give you to report how much they're paying you because there is your freelancer.
And I couldn't find a bunch of them and I was freaking out because I couldn't find the 1099 from the Kickstarter from 2019.
Right, because I did the Vapors to Kickstarter in 2019 and I should have had a 1099, but they didn't give me one because I never reported that I moved from Georgia.
They thought I was still in Georgia.
So and I guess only in like Massachusetts and one or two other states do you need a 1099 unless you make some like outrageous like it's like $20,000.
Like if you make if a place pays you less than $20,000, they don't even give you a 1099 and like it doesn't matter.
But in Massachusetts, the threshold is 600.
So because I never told them that I moved, they didn't give me the 1099.
I didn't have I was like, oh my God, I'm going to get I'm going to get hit.
I'm going to get Tom's.
But that's that's an unfortunate but true idiom.
Yeah, but I but I think it was okay.
I joined a Facebook group that was for like people dealing with like unemployment office snafus.
And I asked like a lady who was in charge of it.
I asked her what kind and she told me that like what they're really what they need is just to prove they're they're not even like checking like they're not even really checking like your income or like how your income change you do.
I just want to see proof that you are employed the way you say you are and that you do live and are making money in Massachusetts.
So even though I didn't have all my 1099s, I had some of them.
And I think hopefully that is enough to prove what I needed to prove.
So I haven't I haven't it hasn't fucked up yet.
And hopefully it won't.
Hopefully.
But anyway, that took that took me like a bunch of my week.
I really, really wanted to not fuck that up.
So by the way, that wasn't an idiom.
I am an idiot.
I was just guessing on what I that thing was.
But to be what thing to be tommed.
Oh, to be tommed.
Well, if it might not be an idiom, but we can make it one.
How do you do that?
I googled it already.
I don't even know what it is.
I can't understand it.
What a group of words established by what you're a fuck.
I'm you fucking dingus.
I'm stupid.
Tommed.
I'm making it up.
It's a neologism.
It's a neologism give.
I I you knew what you knew what I meant through context clues.
You knew you use your context clues.
You said that's an unfortunate but true idiom.
Yeah, I know what you meant.
And I was just trying to figure out what word I was trying to use.
Because idiom isn't the correct word.
No, I'm the idiom.
I thought you meant that you were googling tommed as a verb.
And we're like, that's not a real word.
I'm the idiom in this situation.
Okay.
Okay, push your favorite idioms in the comments.
Post your favorite idiots in the comments.
My favorite idiot is you, the listener, the commenter.
People trying to figure out how do I post like an image of a mirror in the comments of the YouTube?
How do I do that?
I've there's been many times that I wish I could post a funny reaction image in the YouTube comments.
But all you can do is post an image or link.
It sucks.
I mean, you could you could ask you are you could ask you are at it.
Sure.
If you just draw a rectangle, say it's a mirror and hate yourself.
Yeah.
Draw a rectangle and put a little like stick figure smiley face in there.
Well, it's like, all it has to be is a smiley face because it's like in, it's like Scott McCloud said in drawing, drawing words, writing pictures.
If the face is, is general enough, cartoon enough, you see yourself in it, you project yourself onto it.
So if you just draw a simple smiley face, the viewer will understand that they are looking at themselves.
I thought it was like a highlander thing.
Scott McCloud or the Klan McCloud?
No, do you not know Scott McCloud?
No, I remember.
There's the guy who has the book.
He's got, he's got at least two books.
He's a heavy heavy.
What is it?
It's writing, writing words and the drawing words and writing pictures and understanding comics is the other one.
I think I've read both of them.
I should read for them.
But they're good.
They're good.
I don't know.
Doing things that are good for me.
I don't know about that.
Why you should, you should, I mean, I feel like I read them long enough ago that I kind of don't even remember what's in them.
And yet I feel like there's a lot to learn.
If you haven't read them, you probably should.
Have you ever read, you ever read the Loomis?
You ever read like the Loomis drawing books?
I read through it.
I didn't do the things though.
I tried the first page of like, all right, now draw a circle.
Now draw shapes on the circles.
Okay.
Made a face.
I was like, okay, well, I don't want to draw things that look like this.
Stupid.
I just fell off.
You should, you should, everyone should work their way through.
I worked my way all the way through.
I think it was definitely figure drawing for all it's worth.
And
Fun with a pencil was the one I was reading.
I don't think, I think I did figure drawing for all it's worth.
I finished figure drawing for all it's worth.
I don't think I finished drawing the head and hands, but that one was good.
I did some of drawing the head and hands.
It's good.
It's great to learn cause knowledge is power.
No, but power corrupt span.
I don't want to be that sort of person.
Well, no, it's good.
It's good to be corrupt actually.
If you just have to make sure you're the one on top.
You just got to get yours.
Okay.
You, you, you learn all the, all the art techniques and then not let anyone else learn them to
maintain the hierarchy.
I believe is, is the, is the way it's done.
Let's see.
Let's see what else, what else is going on?
Oh, I was going to say it's, it's, it's a typical American situation to give out money for
COVID relief, but then to put a lot of money into following up to make sure that people
weren't lying so that they can rob people.
And get the money back.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, okay.
It's, it's funny.
Yeah.
I, I, I hate this.
I hate this.
They, they claim, and I don't know how true it is.
They claim that there were like widespread unemployment fraud, wherein like organizations
would like met, would mass claim, like unclaimed social security numbers and like claim benefits
in, in the names of those people for like, I don't know, underground fucking crime organizations,
like, yeah, I don't know.
Social security number, like a really insecure number or something.
I think it's, it's not as secure as maybe we wish it was.
Yeah.
I think so.
Like they just go up one at a time or something.
I remember seeing a CGP gray video where the social security number in America is like
subpar when compared to other countries equivalent.
Like,
That sounds,
Numbers,
Sounds familiar.
But it was not designed.
It was not designed for the purpose that it is currently used for.
Nice.
Whoops.
Fraud.
Fraud everywhere.
Yeah, I gotta, like, I mean, I'm a big, I'm a big believer in like non means tested, like
just, just give people stuff, like just give people free stuff.
And like it'll, it'll sort itself out.
I can't imagine that like a big concerted government effort to be like, ooh, we gave out
too much COVID relief.
We got to like send out all these paperwork to everyone and be like, hey, fill these paperwork
outs.
And if you fuck it up, we're going to take you to court and make you pay it back.
Okay.
Thank you.
Like I, that's not going, that's not going to work.
That's not going to be worth the time and effort.
There's no way.
So stupid.
People, people living paycheck to paycheck to get all that money.
They buy food and eat it.
And they got nothing to give back.
They used to pay their rent and then they're like, they, they fucking forget to dot their
eyes and cross their T's.
And the government was like, we think you're part of a, we think you're part of a syndicated
unemployment insurance scam crime ring.
We're going to need a $10,000 back.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Surely if it gets to court and the person arrives and they're like, oh, it's just an individual.
Okay.
Forget it.
They should do that, but they won't.
They don't.
They'll take that money and put that person in prison just because that's how the system
is.
I don't, I don't know.
I'm sure it depends on the person.
I'm, I'm sure that like, I feel optimistic that probably most people can just be like
apply for a waiver and like as long as they can just prove that they are who they say
they are, they'll probably get it.
Hope.
I don't know.
I hope so.
Cause all this is like still going on, but I mean, Massachusetts is a pretty good state
for like not fucking people on that stuff.
It's very much like, very like civil protections in place to protect like, you know, people
in court and renters and employees, right?
Samp.
They actually just, you know, they actually just, uh, they just expanded like employee
leave, uh, rights in the state and my, my local representative Christine Barber posted
about like, here's, here's what you need to know about, about paid leave in Massachusetts
as of today going forward.
And I respond, I went on Twitter, I said, based at her, it's like, based, based Christine
Barber dab, dab, dab, um, she actually, she was the incumbent and she actually, there
was another lady who was running against her who I voted for.
I didn't vote for Christine Barber cause her opponent was a, was a Bernie, was a Bernie
ite, uh, and she had a rose in her name and I was like, well, that's all I need to know.
Uh, but I mean, whatever, even, even the shitty candidates in Massachusetts, I don't know why
we had a Republican, I don't know why like Mitt Romney was our like governor for a while
and he's like a Republican.
I don't know why that happened, but even, even the shitty candidates are still like
liberal Democrats in Massachusetts.
Like we had the Senate race was Ed Markey versus Joe Kennedy and like their, their policy
stances were not even that dissimilar.
They didn't even, they didn't even disagree on very many policy things, but that was kind
of the point that was kind of why everyone hated Joe Kennedy because he was clearly just
running because he's a Kennedy and he wanted to be a senator.
He wasn't going to do anything differently than Ed Markey was already doing.
He was just like, it should be me.
It's my fucking legacy.
I'm going to run.
It's my time.
He's, I think he was the first Kennedy to like ever lose a Senate race in Massachusetts.
Good for him.
I don't know if there's any Lincoln's about saying, um, actually, no, no, he died.
No, I mean, he, he, he got shot and when he got shot, all of his, all of his, uh,
uh, offspring like dissolved, they all just, they all just got Thanos snapped just like
he did.
He just turned a powder right there.
They're, they're like his minions in the boss battle.
You defeat the boss and then all the minions dissolve.
And then the star appears and you grab it.
Yes.
The star.
And then John, John Wilkes Booth like jumped up, grabbed the star and did a little spin
and gave the piece.
It was John Wilkes Booth.
Right.
I'm not confusing that with some other assassination, right?
No, that's a name of her.
I'm pretty sure.
Sometimes I confuse John.
I'm a Graham Booth.
Sometimes I confuse John Wilkes Booth with John Wayne Gacy, but I'm pretty sure those
are two very different, uh, people, um, but it's, you, you mentioned, right, you, you
said something about giving away money for COVID, which is actually the, the, the next
thing on my list of things I want to talk about is that, but a different kind.
Have you heard of, do you have anything like this in Massachusetts?
They're doing Vax millions.
You know, I've heard, I've heard you talk about it in your server.
Yeah.
I don't think there's any equivalent over here.
Vax millions, baby.
We're not, we're not even the only state doing this.
There was another state that was doing it first, but we're doing it too.
They're literally doing a, like they're, they're doing five, like lottery drawings
of people that are vaccinated.
And if you're vaccinated, you get entered in a lottery.
And if they draw your name, you win a million dollars.
I can't fucking wait.
I can't fucking wait for Vax millions.
It's so stupid, but it's a good idea.
Cause it, the people who want like, like, oh, a lottery or a million, there's the
people who kind of, who kind of sort of don't trust vaccinations for some reason.
They need, they need an incentive.
That's going to be the people who are like probably disengaged, right?
Like disengaged from politics or whatever fucking factors lead someone to be vaccinated.
But if they're a million dollar lottery, there's a mark, that's a whole new market.
It's so stupid to not try it.
I don't know how many people are going to just try and pretend they have the vaccine
somehow and assume that will work.
I don't think it would work.
I mean, you, you didn't have to show ID or anything to get vaccinated.
You just had to like, you literally just had to show up and like say what your name was.
And if they had like that name on their like records as scheduled for today, they let you
in and they, and they jabbed you.
Yeah.
Well, they keep in some sort of track of who has it.
You didn't need your driver's license or anything, which is good because my driver's
license was expired as of like earlier this year.
So I'm glad they didn't require it.
Although I just got my, I just got a renewal in the mail.
I'm so excited.
I can buy booze again.
Speaking, speaking of like licenses.
My passport has expired this June.
I didn't really notice because there's no traveling I was planning on doing, but
there was a thing I was thinking maybe I could go see like Munchy and you and everyone
at some point, they wanted me to come.
I was like, I'll just, I'll maybe, you know, I'm scared, I'm scared about traveling.
Check my passport though.
It doesn't work and it's going to take too long for me to get another one.
But in the process of doing that, I, I got to this, to this, you know, this
unfortunate little, this little, little moment that annoyed me.
A snafu.
A little snafu.
I can renew it fine, but I have to keep all the information the same.
I was thinking, hmm, I kind of don't like the, the, the, you know, the multiple
choice, are you male or female?
Cause I see that in forms and, you know, obviously before there was no question.
I just click the thing and male every time, no thought.
But now that there's like, you know, there's a question there.
It's, it's a decision I'm making.
I'm like, am I going to get in trouble for doing this when I'm, when like, I don't
know, the government doesn't think I am.
What do you, okay.
It asks you what your gender was.
Yeah.
Like cause they put the little gender in the thing and it's like M or F.
And I was like, I'd like F, but then they say, okay.
All you need to do is get a, a gender recognition certificate from the government
to say that you are the gender you say you are.
And in order to do that, you need a cover, you need a doctor's note to say, yes,
you are that gender.
And you also need to have been living as that gender for at least two years.
And you need to show that you will live as that gender for the rest of your life.
How, how are they going to prove that?
I don't know.
I think they just need you to say that you're going to do that.
And they need some person like just a thing that you're just supposed to say yes to.
Yeah.
I mean, well, the thing is you say yes, because of course you're going to.
And then they have like a psychiatric evaluation to determine whether you're
actually telling the truth or something.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
You're saying when you apply for a passport, if you say you want to change your gender,
they're going to make you go and see like a, like a doctor.
Give you like an evaluation to give me an evaluation to see whether I'm like faking it or not.
And only then, if I give that information with my old passport, mail that in, will they send
me the new one with the gender change?
That's weird.
So it's, it's really, it feels, I don't know, it's, it feels sickening.
It feels a little gross and it makes me upset just thinking about going through the whole process of that.
So I haven't, I've, I've got like the, I've paid for the renewal because I wasn't thinking,
I was thinking maybe I, I could just do it, right?
I could just say gender female, but then it, no, I could send the passport off, but they
will just reject the gender change and I can get my new passport and I could look at it and
it will say male and I'll be like, ah, it's such an infinitesimally small thing that doesn't
really affect my real life at all.
It just annoys me that I have to, it feels demeaning, you know, feels a little degrading to go through that.
Do you have any idea what the, what the like examination would consist of?
I have no idea.
They say doctor's note.
I, I was told that you could just ask your doctor, just send them a note and then they'll do it.
Yeah.
So I'm going to try that, but I need to get in.
Like I've like sent my, my GP like an email saying, can you do that?
And they'll get back to me, I guess.
I don't know when.
So I want to try and see if it's that simple, but I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm a little worried that
they're going to be like, well, no, do more.
And I'm like, oh, no.
How are they, how are they going to know?
Like, oh, no, we have, we have pictures of you a year and a half ago where you were wearing a top hat.
And that means you weren't, you weren't a woman then.
So you got six more months.
The thing that annoys me about it is, is that I feel like it's, I mean,
it's obviously pointless because it comes down to the,
like, what's the problem with people quote unquote, faking it?
Anyway, like, what, what is the purpose of the gender on a passport?
I mean, I agree.
I agree.
Uh, the.
Like, like, oh, was it, oh, they're, they're female or male.
That means they're more or less likely to like have a bomb on the plane.
It's because they, it's big, give obviously, if you could just call up the NHS or whatever
and get it on, get an F on your card, then tomorrow you could go and to the Olympic
weightlifting tryouts and become a gold medalist in the women's power lift category.
Stupid.
I couldn't beat like a fool.
Don't you care about women, the integrity of women's sports?
No, I don't.
That's really misogynistic of you.
I don't care about sports.
I never have.
And I, and I don't care about women together.
We don't care about women's sport.
I mean, that whole argument is just sort of like, yeah, whatever.
Sure.
I just want to be not like, you know, I want to be treated good.
Can I have that, please?
Yeah, well, I feel like, I mean, it's pretty obvious to me that a lot of people
do the women's sports thing because they just find trans people icky and they have,
they have this as their excuse.
That's, that's their, because it's, because it's hard to argue.
Like when I think about it, I find myself being like, gee, I don't know.
I kind of feel like I don't even, I don't even qualify to have an opinion on like,
who should be allowed to compete in what sports category that kind of seems like
something that like professional athletes and like, you know, athletic biologists and like
sports scientists should, and like nutritionists and endocrinologists should be answering.
Like, so like, it's hard to even have, because that's a really technical debate is like,
what are the, what are the qualifying questions to determine?
Like who, who's in what league?
I mean, for what it's worth, being on HRT changes your bone density and like your
muscle strength anyway, as long as you've been on it for a while.
Yeah.
So like the whole like advantage of being male, it's, it's, it's,
it varies depending on whether they're taking hormones.
If like allowing trans women to compete in women's sports, if that led to like,
suddenly the league is dominated by trans women, then maybe it would be like, okay,
there's some advantage here that is like skewing things and it's, and it's like,
you know, I would say then maybe, then maybe it's worth asking the experts like,
maybe we need to redefine the leagues somehow.
Yeah.
Right.
But as far as I can tell, it isn't like that and that hasn't happened.
No.
I mean, very occasionally it's, it's an interesting question.
It deserves talking about, but I don't care about talking about it.
And I know a lot of the people talking about it don't care.
All also don't care, but they'll use it as a wedge issue.
They just don't like trans people.
Yes.
This is their, this is their W.
They don't give a fuck about women's sports until they can latch onto it as a like, oh,
well, you know, these fucking freaks want to, they want to invade women's spaces.
So we got to kill them.
You've never cared about women's spaces.
Johnny America, you piece of shit.
Johnny America.
Hey, that's my, hey, don't insult my cousin Johnny America on today.
The holiest night of the year, July 4th.
Did you know that today is American Independence Day?
Of course I know that you'd never, American.
You never shut up.
I never shut up about it.
You dang Yankees never stop talking about America.
Ben, every day in the discord, you're like only a week left until the 4th of July.
Only six days left until the 4th of July.
Oh, it's the 28th of June, Pogpog.
I do like the 4th of July because traditionally they do a, you know,
in Boston, they do fireworks shows like all over the dang place.
And usually I would go up to the, to Tufts.
I would go to Tufts campus to this one, like Pagoda they have.
And you can kind of see over the Boston skyline and you can see like fireworks in the over the city.
Like pretty far away, but you can still see them.
And that's, that's where I would, I would watch them.
Generally.
Maybe I'll, I don't know.
I'm going to go see, I'm going to go see Munching Casulator.
So maybe there'll be like some different place or maybe we just won't even fucking bother.
I don't even care that much.
It's fine.
It's all good.
I make sure to drink a cup of tea on the 4th of July.
Criminal.
Like I do every day.
We should, we should fucking, oh, I saw,
I saw a really funny tweet.
It was a video of people tearing down a statue, you know, like they do.
Nice.
As has become, as has become popular today among the youth,
but it was people in Canada tearing down a statue of the queen, right, of England.
Ben.
And the tweet was like, the tweet was like,
guy with seven with tattoos of 1776 and the don't tread on me snake.
Why are you tearing down history?
You know, do you get it?
Cause like America.
The tweet was saying that the kind of guy who would have be like,
Oh, America.
Yeah.
Don't tear down Confederate statues because that's American history.
America.
Don't tread on me.
A Gadsden flag.
He doesn't, that kind of guy wouldn't like tearing down statues,
but what if it's a statue of the queen of England who his country famously rebelled again?
So it's like, oh, he's so, so conflicted on the one hand.
I hate, I hate, I love that we fucking did the war for independence.
But on the other hand, I love statues so much.
Oh, think of the property damage.
No, put it back.
Put it back, please.
Imagine being crushed under a statue.
Like your head, like you, like a, like a train's coming.
Like a train's coming.
Yeah.
That's what I thought.
I saw that statue come down and, and crash on the ground and I was like,
I'm imagining what it would feel like to be under it and just, and just obliterated.
This is my, my bones just crunched and all my fucking soft tissues eviscerated.
If you become like a full-time game dev, that'll be your first original games,
like, um, getting headcrushed simulator.
Headcrushed simulator.
Oh, God.
Jesus.
No.
Press A to rise.
I'm, I'm, I don't know what it is.
I don't want to like, like every night, like every night,
well, before I go to bed, I like think about like, what if my head was crushed and I'll like,
have a little fucking spasm?
I'll be like, no, no.
Ah, I can't sleep.
Oh, I want to scream.
I have to empty my mind.
I have to use my, I have to use Isaac Sunsenghe's,
a kumdo meditation techniques to empty my mind.
Like a still, like the, like the service of a still pond.
You, you put your, you put your ear to the train tracks and you listen and you listen hard and then
an airplane lands straight under your other ear.
What would you do?
Huh?
What would you do then?
You'd be fucking dead, probably.
You'd be dead, bro.
Yeah.
Not so tough now.
Hmm.
But Vax Millions though, I'm legit.
I'm so excited for Vax Millions.
I'm literally going to like, mark my calendar and like,
I'm not kidding.
I'm going to make this a thing.
It's going to be, it's going to be just like Psycholonials,
just like how I was waiting for every new chapter of Psycholonials every,
every week on Thursday from July 29th through August 26th.
I'm going to be at my computer and be like, oh,
they're going to announce the new Vax Millions.
Cause like, apparently you have to respond within 24 hours to claim your prize.
So like, imagine if like, I missed it and they picked me.
And then I just like, didn't notice until the next day.
You just do a live stream the entire day.
Live the entire day?
Yeah.
Uh, imagine if I won Vax Millions on the stream.
They're doing, um, yeah.
Once a week they do, they pick, they pick an 18 plus person and a 12 to 17 person.
And, um, I guess the 12 to 17 gets a third 300,000 scholarship grant
and the 18 plus gets, just gets a million dollars.
Um, the, well, I thought, I thought they weren't the vaccinating 12 year olds yet.
Are they vaccinating 12 to 17 year olds?
That's, I guess.
I hope they are.
I like, I like vaccinations.
I trust the science.
Soy, soy, oh, soy face.
Oh, lower transmission rates.
Oh, reduced symptoms.
Oh, the, the, the death, death rate is plummeting.
Oh, Delta variant.
Oh, stupid.
How embarrassing.
It's so embarrassing to do good things.
It's so cringe to win a million.
I can't fucking wait.
I'm calling it now.
I'm going to win all five.
I'm going to win all effects.
Uh, Pogg, what would you even do with five sets of one million dollars?
What would I do with five million dollars?
Um, I would move to a nicer apartment.
Uh, actually by then I'll, by then I'll have to be moved into some, somewhere.
Still haven't found a new apartment.
I have to move at the end of this month.
Wouldn't you want to buy like a, a whole building so you don't have to pay rent forever?
You know what?
Yeah, you're right.
If I had five million, yeah, I would just buy a, I would just buy a building out right.
Yeah.
There's no question.
Absolutely right.
I guess the only downside is that you can't move easily.
You'd have to sell it.
But like rent sucks.
I mean, you know, not, not to, not to be landlord-pilled or anything,
but I mean, if you owned a building, you could just move out, rent another building,
and just rent the place you own.
True.
You don't, you don't have to live in the building you own.
Although, I mean, you probably, it's probably the most cost-effective, uh, if you do.
Just buy all the buildings and then pay security guards to kill people who try to sleep in them.
Just buy, just, why hasn't anyone thought of this before?
No, you don't even have, you don't even have to pay.
You don't even have to pay, uh, uh, security guards to protect your property.
The fucking, the fucking civilian, the fucking, uh, municipal police will do it for you.
That's what they do.
They're there to protect you, the landlord.
They're there to, for free.
Literally the state pays them to protect your private investments of multiple, like, housing complexes.
They are there to respond to crackdown on people who offend your property.
How fucked up is that?
Uh, pretty fucked up.
Literally, literally.
I'm trying very hard to find, like, a positive spin on that.
I don't know.
Literally the, I, I, I think I was reading Kropotkin when I had this, I had this realization.
It was like, literally the police exist to protect property and rich people, landowners,
homeowners, like the more homes you own, the more stuff you own,
the more the police protect you.
They literally were, they work, they work for you.
They work, you know, in theory, they work for everyone to protect everyone's property.
But the more you own, the more of their free protection you are provided,
the more they will fucking crack down on your enemies for trespassing on your stuff.
And you don't have to do anything.
You can literally, you can own a property, not even, not, like, defend it, not maintain it in any way.
But if someone is trespassing on it, if you happen to own it, you can call the cops and
some fucking burly guy will come and crack their skull with a fucking butt of his pistol.
Just because you want him to.
Yeah.
I guess the phone call costs nothing.
The phone call costs nothing.
Just like all the best things in life.
The best things in life are free, like calling the cops to brutalize a homeless person.
So yeah, Vax Millions, Vax Millions, I'm hype, you can bet, you can bet
that through July and August, through August, I will be reporting every episode of the PCP.
I will be on the show to be like, yes, this week, once again, I have won Vax Millions.
I'd be excited to see the Vax Millions corner.
If I win Vax Millions, I will personally give everyone who likes the video.
I will personally give everyone who likes the episode that I announced that I won Vax
Millions, one dollar like the video screenshot, your screenshot that you gave the video alike.
DM me the screenshot of the the like button that you hit.
And then such a small and then give me your PayPal and I will PayPal you one dollar
out of my Vax Millions.
See, I'm spreading it around.
That episode just happens to get one million likes.
For a million likes on a PCP episode, worth it, totally worth it.
Me millions as two millions, as the Espanol would say.
Well, look, look forward to that, everybody.
Yes, update, update on the Lord of Ghost Kickstarter.
It's been going well.
It's been going good.
It's very, very, very close.
Now it's 40 pounds, only 40 pounds away as of recording to the Red Man Zine stretch goal.
90 backers, 16 days to go.
By the time you're listening to this, it'll be like 10 days to go.
There's not much time left.
You have to do it.
You just have to do it.
I literally went on Facebook.
I know, cringe.
I literally went on my Facebook that I never use.
And I posted a link to the Kickstarter and I said my friend is kickstarting a comic.
And I went to the Boston Comics Roundtable Facebook group and I said,
my friend, he's kickstarting a comic.
Wow.
You said it in a different voice.
I did.
In my personal one, I was just kind of like, hey, I know someone who's doing the thing.
And on the Boston Comics Roundtable, I was like,
You're pitching it.
She's doing a thing.
If there's merch and everything.
Whoa.
I really appreciate that.
It was very nice.
I hope that one, maybe one of the like two people that have pledged since then might have
come from there or maybe not.
I don't know.
Who knows?
You might know, but or maybe you don't.
So I can, I can check.
I can check.
You know what?
Yeah.
All right.
Check and tell me if they, if they're complete strangers' names that you don't recognize,
I'm going to assume that I got them on Facebook.
Well, there's Super 2D, Jonathan Kirkwood,
Rhomboid Goat Cabin, and Sick Normal are the four most, when did you do this?
This is just a day ago, right?
Three days ago?
Or three days ago.
Or two or two or three days.
It was, it was at 88.
It was at 88 when I posted and now it's at 90.
Oh, I can't think about what that means.
Yeah.
I think those four I mentioned are the ones.
I don't recognize a lot of these names.
I think they're different from like names they have on other social medias, but yeah.
I would say viewers, listeners, maybe if you, if you're listening, if maybe you're already
supporting the Kickstarter or maybe you can't support the Kickstarter.
You don't have any money right now.
That's okay.
It really makes a difference.
This is how, I mean, running mine.
I really appreciate it whenever anyone shared it.
And like you can fucking, you know what?
Just fucking spam it in like discords that you're in.
You know what?
Honestly, I'm in a bunch of like shitty discords that I don't even use.
Maybe later today, I already, I already put it on the Facebook.
Maybe later today, I will just go and put it in a whole bunch of these
discords that I haven't looked at in a year.
And maybe I'll get banned for spamming.
Who gives a fuck?
Yeah, I don't know why I haven't mentioned that.
Like I say, hey, check out my Kickstarter and pledge if you like.
I haven't said share it around.
Share it around is good.
Because a lot of some people, some people will not be in a position
where they want to pledge, but they can share and they'll do that.
And that's good.
Share that shit, everybody.
If you want to help get that fucking plush.
If you want to get that fucking plush and then I'll increase my pledge.
So I get that plush.
Yes, looking at the curve, the, what is it, line graph?
Show me, show me the line.
It's, it's, there was a bit where it was very slow and then it increased for a second.
Yeah, but it's slowing down again.
I think just because it's halfway through or a little before halfway through,
that it's like, I'll get around to it like people who would pledge are going to pledge later.
This looks.
I had, I had great graphs from mine.
They kind of, they look pretty similar to, yeah, it shoots up at the beginning and then
it tapers off and then every, there's every, like, like bumps every, every here and there.
As like people who maybe wanted to pledge, but couldn't like get around to it or get
some money and are like, oh, okay, we'll go back and play.
Oh, you know what?
I haven't checked, but today as we're recording the, that comic podcast that I sent my voicemail
into is going to go live.
I should go listen to that and hear myself and go, oh, what?
I sound so bad.
And then I'll know that people have heard me talk about Lord of Ghosts.
Did I mention that the day is all blur together.
I don't know what's happening.
Did I mention last week about the Animorphs podcast?
What about it?
I think you did mention it.
Did I say that I was going to be on it or that I had been on it?
Let me, hold on, let me see, let me see.
I made a tweet about it.
So, yeah, I was on, I was on Animorphin time that was on, yeah, that was on June 29th.
Okay, okay, no.
Yeah, last week I said I was going to be.
So yes, this week I was on the Animorphin time podcast, the leftist Animorphs podcast,
Animorphs podcast, All Cops Are Year, STAB with Nate and Tyler.
That will be out in on Apple podcasts.
I think Tyler's told me that it would be out on the 20th.
I think it'll be out on July 20th.
He said three weeks from the day we recorded it.
Damn.
We read, oh yeah, so if you want to prepare,
if you just want to listen to my episode, if you, we read book 31.
It was number 31, The Conspiracy.
It's a Jake book and this, if you, oh my God, it's, I want to talk about it,
but I don't want to spoil it too much, I guess.
They Animorph.
They do, they do Animorph.
It is, okay, if you want to prepare for that episode,
to prepare for my Animorph time appearance, you can go and find,
if you just Google like Animorphs PDFs, there's, it's really easy.
Someone has uploaded just like PDFs of every single book.
You can find the entire thing and read it online really easily.
Also, I was like kind of dreading my book.
I thought it might take like, I forgot how short they are.
I literally read the entire book in like two and a half hours.
They're so short.
I'm not, I don't want to talk about the, the details of the book,
because like, you know, we, we go into it, we go through the whole plot in, on the, the pod,
but it's so bad.
It's such a bad fucking book.
It's, it's kind of hilarious how fucking dumb everything is.
In like, when I read them as a kid, I think I got up to maybe book like
20 late 20s.
So I had never read this one.
This is 31.
I think there's like 50 of them.
And this is definitely into the part where like,
the series is basically done and it's ready to conclude,
but they want to make more books.
So they're just going to have a bunch of like stupid filler happen
until they finally are ready to end it.
It is a, it is a, it is basically a pointless filler episode.
But the really infuriating thing about it is that there are
like the things that the premise of the episode, like could have been a big deal.
Like it could have been like a huge turning point, except that for no reason,
they all decide, no, we can't do anything.
We have to make sure that nothing happens.
We have to make a stupid, the dumbest plan in the world that guarantees that no progress will be made
in our quest to protect the world from this alien invasion.
I won't, they, they literally could have fucking gotten shit done,
but they like deliberately sabotage themselves and it's infuriating.
But it was a fun podcast.
Cool. Go check that out.
But you, would you find podcast?
Weird, weird coincidence.
Yeah, check that out in like two weeks when, when that,
it'll be about two weeks after this, this episode comes out.
Weird coincidence.
There was a guy, a guy who I used to know from my old Discord server
before the current one that I, that I have, the old one.
His name is DivineSoupcan.
Hello DivineSoupcan, if you're listening.
He randomly started sending, they started shouting him out on the AnimorphinTime podcast
because he would send them in like really bizarre animal facts.
Um, about like, yeah, this is like really bizarre animal facts.
And I was just like, I was like, I, like, I know that guy.
I literally know that guy.
What are, what are the odds?
What are the odds that a person would listen to a podcast?
Would listen to another podcast that I also listened to?
You know what?
There's no such thing as a coincidence.
It was a distant.
Have you seen that guy, that there's no such thing as a coincidence guy?
Oh, the, is he the, the guy who the lady screamed in the video, but he just kept going?
Yeah, why did she scream?
I feel like, I can't, I don't know.
I feel like it's a strange scream to say if, like I first, I assume she looked back at him
and he had a very piercing gaze and she was like screaming at, but like that's a weird thing to do.
So I think she probably just tripped.
She walked by him.
She walked by him and like knew he was there.
Yeah, she walked by him.
Well, she didn't see his face.
That's why I thought that.
But I think it's more likely she just tripped and fell.
His face isn't that scary.
No, it's sort of like intense.
Yeah.
He looks like an anime villain.
I, yeah, I saw that clip with the scream.
I thought the scream was added.
Like I thought it was an edit because it's so weird that it's there.
And then he had like a follow-up.
Like a lot of you are wondering why I didn't react to the scream.
Yeah.
It was like, who, I mean, what is this guy?
Just re-record your fucking take.
Re-record the fucking take with someone screams when you're trying to record your
fucking there's no such thing as a coincidence TikTok.
Simple.
I wonder what, like, with that, what, I don't understand.
I didn't really look into it.
But it seems fascinating.
It must have been pre-planned if there's no such thing as a coincidence.
Maybe she was an extra that he had to scream.
There's no, that's, that's, well, maybe that's it.
The scream wasn't a coincidence.
He was like, that scream must be here for a reason.
You know.
I knew exactly what to do.
I must have manifested this scream somehow from the energies of the universe.
So that I would get like, you know, comedy views and then skyrocket into relevance.
So it would go viral.
Well, and it worked.
And it worked.
Now I know who that, now I know who that guy is.
It's all true.
He's so smart.
It's all fucking true.
I'm actually kind of mad because, yeah, it completely worked.
Jesus.
We should invite him on the podcast and he can have a webcam and do that.
We don't even know what his name is.
Yeah, we can have him on like, Mary, like Mary as a VTuber.
But instead it's just him like, in the park.
Against the green screen.
Just staring, staring directly into the camera.
Yeah.
Has it been, has it been hot for you?
A little bit.
Hot and then cold.
Oh, it's not cold.
I guess hot and then wet.
But, you know, temperate, I guess.
It hasn't been like heat wavy as I've heard it's been.
Yeah.
On the west coast, it's been like 120 degrees.
It's been like record breaking.
Like we're all going to die levels of, you know, hot.
On the east coast, it's been a heat wave here too.
It hasn't been quite as bad.
But it's recently broken because it started raining a lot.
So the last couple of days have not been that bad.
It's been rainy.
But it was really hot.
It was really hot for a minute there.
I have, my room is pretty small and I have an air conditioner in my window.
And I've been, I was keeping the air conditioner going like full blast all day.
And it wasn't enough.
I was still sweating in my room.
My room is very badly ventilated.
It gets really hot in the summer because it's up.
One, heat rises and I'm on the third floor.
And two, I think the sun on the roof.
I think the sun heats the roof and the heat seeps in through my roof.
So my room gets really, really hot, even in the best of times.
So yeah, even the full blown air conditioner was like,
it was like kind of handling it, but it was still like uncomfortable.
So it's really like oppressive when it's so hot because it's like, where do you go?
When you're already in the shade and you have access to water and you still feel like you're
going to die, it's like, there's nowhere to escape.
There's not, there's nothing that can improve this.
You just have to like dig down a hole into the ground and live underground.
You don't have a hole, but you can't, you don't have a shovel.
You don't have a diamond pick.
You can't dig that well.
No, you don't have a diamond pick.
You don't have a void metal, you don't have a void metal pick with silk touch called
big softy like I do.
You can't, you can't, you can't dig down a big, a big shaft and make your fucking
thaumaturge logical wizards tower underground, if only.
It's just that sort of despair you feel when like, you know, you're sitting by an open fridge
and you're like, I'm going to die.
It's still too hot.
I'm sitting by an open fridge.
Like that one episode of The Simpsons where they like open their fridge and like set up
a little tent in front of it.
Yeah, I remember.
Hot Simpsons, they predicted heat.
They predicted the climate change.
Oh, they predicted it would be hot in the summer.
A bog, yeah.
Yes, yes.
Yeah, lucky, lucky for me, I suppose that it hasn't been devastating, but it'll happen.
I mean, it happened last year, August was very, very hot over here.
Yeah, I guess it might, I guess it might still get hotter.
Huh?
That's a bummer.
I guess it's doing like a heat dome.
I keep hearing people say that there's a heat dome.
I don't know what that is.
I can, I can picture it.
I can sort of understand from context clues what a heat dome might be.
Like a, like a Dragon Ball Z, like seen from space explosion blast.
Exactly.
But with heat.
Oh, funny thing happened yesterday.
I mentioned, I mentioned that I'm super strong now.
I mentioned that I'm bet that I squat two plate like a god.
But it's not that impressive because I'm fat too, so it all evens out.
I went to the basement to lift yesterday and I put my phone down on like a little like,
it's like a thing, like a table, like a folded up table that's leaning against the wall.
And I went to squat and I went and I picked up my phone and I see something on the screen
of the phone and it's, well, I didn't know what they were.
I was afraid they might be lice or bedbugs, but I'm pretty sure they were actually dust mites.
They were really, really small, like the smallest bug I've ever seen.
They were so tiny, but I could see them moving around on my phone and I looked at my hand
and there were some on my hand too.
And I was like, oh my god, because I thought they, I didn't,
I thought they might be parasites of some kind, lice, bedbugs, whatever.
I was like, oh my god, I'm infested.
Oh my god, they're gonna get on me.
They're gonna live in my hair.
They're gonna live in my body.
They're gonna live in my asshole.
I'm fucking done.
And I got scared and the fear and the terror gave me an adrenaline rush that
I think it made me better at lifting.
I think it helped me power through my last set on the bench press.
150 baby, that's a recent PB.
Wait, so you didn't rush to the shower to get rid of them?
You rushed to the bench?
I had to finish my lifts.
Oh, I missed the beginning of the convo of the use.
I'm sorry, I'm out of it today.
I'm fairly listening to anything.
No, I mean, it's fair.
Well, I mean, I rushed to finish my lift so that I could go and get in the shower
as quickly as possible.
I did spend a little while standing there very intently, looking at my hands,
trying to see if I could spot any more and try and flick them off.
But at the same time, I knew that they're so small that there's a little,
even no matter how closely I looked, I could very easily have missed some.
So I finished my lifts and then I did go and I took a shower as hot as I could stand.
It's one of the most unsettling things is like the slow realization that that thing
actually is a bug.
Oh my God.
Oh no.
Like you look at a thing and you're like, is that just like a piece of plastic?
Or like, what is that?
Oh no.
I mean, it's like a spider and you jumps into your face and die.
Yeah.
Dust mites.
I mean, they're so small.
It's almost like they don't even exist.
So they're not that gross and they're not like harmful.
Like they don't really bite or anything.
They're not parasites.
They don't suck your blood or eat your skin or whatever.
So like, I don't even think it's bad that I got some on my hands.
Wait, they don't eat skin or they even do then.
Well, dust mites just, I don't know.
I guess they eat dust or whatever.
They just live on the floor.
Isn't that like mostly dead skin cells?
Or at least a large amount.
I heard that like there's things like that that live on people's pillows because of
like fatty oils from skin or whatever.
I think they're like, oh, fucking feeding frenzy.
It's disgusting.
Okay.
I mean, they do eat skin.
They do eat skin flakes from humans.
It's like, yeah, they might eat some of your dead skin, but like they're so small.
I mean, what I'm saying is they don't like nest on human bodies, right?
Like lice live in your hair.
Dust mites don't like live on you.
They might get on you and they might eat some of your dead skin.
But like, again, they're so small they don't even exist.
They're literally microscopic even though you can technically see them.
Uh, you can see them if you look real hard.
If you squint real good.
They put your eyeball right next to them and they jump onto your eyes.
I don't think they can jump.
They literally, they look exactly like headcrabs.
They're tiny, tiny, tiny.
But if you look really close, they literally look like headcrabs.
From Half Life?
Yeah.
No, from real life.
Well, I don't know.
Maybe there is a thing called a headcrab.
There is not.
There is no, oh, look at Cassie.
Look at Cassie being fucking cheeky.
Cassie is in the server.
Do voicemails so Ben can come over.
Yeah, Cassie's waiting for you, Ben.
She's just going to have to fucking, she's going to have to wait until I'm done
going through my funny little list of topics to bring up on the episode, which
actually I'm basically done with.
I think that was, that was the last one.
I guess we can start voicemails.
The one last thing that I wanted to mention was last episode I talked about hanging out
with those guys and playing Smash and playing Inkling and not knowing how to refill my ink
and a couple of people messaged me to be like, actually, you can refill your rink anytime if
you shield and hit down B.
So thanks, thanks to everyone, thanks to everyone who hit me up with the
with the pro tips on Inkling.
I will, I will, I'm sure we'll play Smash today and I will try to use that.
But Munchie is so much better at Smash than me.
I can barely take a stock off him, like when he's just fucking around and basically letting
me win.
So, you know, I was a while, this wasn't the last episode.
Last time, but like, like several weeks ago, I was over there.
We were playing Smash.
I decided to just play Sephiroth just to see what he was like.
I think Munchie was playing Kirby and like I managed to take like two stocks off him.
And I was like, oh, wow, I actually kind of won.
And the next time I saw him, I was like, hey, last time we played Smash,
you just let me take those stocks off you, right?
And he was like, yes.
And I was like, okay, just, just making, he didn't even pretend.
Uh, but that, that's just how it is.
That's just how it be sometimes.
Completely forgot Sephiroth was in Smash.
So many, so many funny reveals.
He's kind of cool.
I like playing with him.
He's got, he's got reach.
He's got big swings.
He's got big reach with his sword.
And he makes big explosions with his hands.
And that's pretty cool.
I like that.
Yeah.
Um, I guess that's it.
I guess that's all I had to say about all that bullshit.
Boy smells.
We got a lot.
So let's fucking.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Okay.
Oh, they all look short.
I'm looking at the first page and they're all under a minute.
Oh, except this one, except one, but it's okay.
They're all under a minute.
Okay, good.
All right, uh, send us a message at speakpipe.com slash PCP voicemail.
If you want us to fucking hear what you have to say about literally anything,
unless we really don't like it and then we'll tell LA czar to cut it.
But that doesn't usually happen.
Most of you are pretty good.
Thanks for the voicemails.
Okay.
First one is John Lennon is a hack.
You see that?
Yes.
Okay.
And three, two, one, go.
Who's your favorite beetle?
I don't fucking know.
All George or Ringo.
My favorite is Yoko.
What about you?
I, I know.
What do I even know?
I know that Ringo is the one that everyone says was untalented and he was on,
not reading Rainbow.
He was on the Thomas the Tank Engine show.
Shining time station.
Is that what it was called?
Um, did you know that Ringo star was, yeah, he was the conductor?
I know he was, he was the, he was the narrator.
Shining time station.
What do you mean shining?
I thought it was just for the show for like a bunch of seasons.
He was the voice.
Well, the, well, the show is, I think the show is called Shining Time Station.
It's not, the show was not called Thomas the Tank Engine.
Is it?
Wait, I don't, wow, I'd never heard of that.
I thought it was Thomas the Tank Engine and Friends.
No, this, this, this is like a Warriors versus Warrior.
Everyone calls it Thomas the Tank Engine, but no.
The series, wait, wait, is this a different show?
Yeah, he was Mr.
conductor on Shining Time Station, as was George Carlin.
Element, wait a minute, elements of the show were incorporated into the
two, into the 2000, no, Thomas and Friends film.
Okay, no, that's later.
That's like a remake.
It incorporated sequences from the British.
Oh my God, this is amazing.
Holy shit, they fucking, they power-rangered it.
Huh?
This is blowing my mind.
This is blowing my fucking mind.
Okay, I guess Thomas, Thomas the Tank Engine, I guess was a British show.
They showed it in America.
I didn't know any of this.
They showed it in America, but they showed it as part of a program called Shining Time Station,
and the Thomas the Tank Engine were just segments in the Shining Time Station show.
Did you watch that as Shining Time Station?
Yes, yes, I did.
I watched Shining Time Station as a kid.
I just knew it as, we had a VHS, I think, of Thomas the Tank Engine and Ringo Starr said
stuff, and it was just it, that was it.
But Ringo Starr was on Shining Time Station.
He wasn't in Thomas the Tank Engine.
No, he was the voice of the narrator for Thomas, yeah, first two series of Thomas and Friends.
Well, that's confusing, because he was, I guess he did both.
I guess maybe, I guess his hit, I mean, he's a big name in America as well.
Him doing the Thomas the Tank Engine narration, and then they get him over for the American
something or other.
I'm confused why they felt the need to remake it and add new non-train segments.
I'm confused why they felt they had to do that, considering the original is in English.
Wow, this is very, very, very weird, very strange.
So because of that, Ringo's the best.
What do I know?
I know that John Lennon was a fucking hippie.
I know that Paul, I know that Paul died.
I know.
And that you just make survive, that's all.
Yeah, I've seen that quite a review video about the conspiracy that Paul is dead, yeah.
My favorite has been George, just because I liked his solo work more.
Actually, I don't know about that.
Nah, my favorite is Paul, because I like his solo work more.
George is the one that I know the least about.
George is the guy who got the Indian, like the sitar influence,
musical stuff into the Beatles for those two albums.
I thought that was John Lennon.
No, no, no.
John wishes he was that fucking hippiness.
I think John was actually jealous of George for having like a weird, interesting passion,
and he was like, fuck.
So I'm going to marry an Asian lady.
Yeah, I'll show him.
I'll show him.
That's funny.
If you had asked me who were in the Beatles, I would have said Paul, Ringo, John.
I think I might have forgotten that there even was a George.
Like, I know there's four of them, but I don't think I would have remembered that his name was George.
So that's-
My favorite is George Allison.
I don't know.
I don't really have a favorite.
Sorry.
Okay.
You've got a good answer, though.
And now I know about Shining Time Station.
Next, the next voicemail is called Henlo Corgo, cool and new webcomic.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, then.
So I was wondering if you have heard of, or perhaps even read, cool and new webcomic,
the Homestuck fancomic, where they're rewriting Homestuck in the style of Sweet Bro and Hella Jeff.
Yeah.
It's actually pretty good, pretty funny.
If you haven't read it, I would totally check it out.
I have seen it, and I kind of made a mental note that like I want to read this,
but it was still going on.
So I think I said like, I'll come back and read this later,
and I haven't ever gotten around to actually reading it.
But yeah, I've seen it, and I think it looks cool.
I read some of it.
I got to a point where there was like-
It was a funny joke, where it's like the midnight crew.
They're all like dumb, except for Jack.
And they're like, you know, like the things they say,
sleep with the fishes, but put them in a good, I don't know.
I can't think of the joke.
It's the things they say that you could interpret as like a thing that's not killing them,
but it's obviously supposed to be like murder them, please.
But because he's not clear and uses like the gangster lingo,
they just take it literally, like put him to bed.
Put him to bed means literally like tuck him in, give him warm milk.
I remember that being pretty funny.
Gotcha, gotcha.
But there was a point where they were doing like a walk around,
or like a really long video.
It just got a little too long.
I did like it though.
I, yeah, I think it looks cool, and I want to read it, but I have not.
So I don't have much to say about it.
Other than it looks, I think it looks pretty funny.
Maybe I'll check it out soon.
Next voicemail is called Dear Ben Fat Fuck Saint.
Three, two, one, go.
Yo Ben, the reason you're putting on a fuckload of weight
is because you're not fucking running.
Lifting it ain't shit if you can't actually get any goddamn cardio in.
That's where all of your calories are supposed to fucking go.
So cringe.
Fucking fat, so.
Man, that's weird, man.
But it's also funny.
Uh, the reason why anyone ever gains weight
is because they eat more calories than they expend.
You think I don't understand this?
I understand this.
You can, you can reduce that number by increasing your calorie output
by doing, for example, cardio, or you can reduce it by eating fewer calories.
They both work.
Uh, running is, I hate it.
I know I probably should do it.
I know it has health benefits.
Quote unquote, good thing.
Quote unquote, good for you.
Um, lame.
Next, what, what, I, what does he say?
Like what good is lifting if you can't run?
What do you, you get fucking strong?
That's what you get strong and you get muscles.
That's what good it is.
What are you talking about?
What do you think people lift so that they can run?
No, anyone can run.
Any idiot can run.
Oh my god.
Fucking perverts out there.
Am I right?
Uh, sure.
Next voicemail is called Racky the Robot Guy.
Three, two, one, go.
Remember when people used to come to the show and ask for dating advice?
Yeah, they don't do that anymore.
You know why?
Because pussies layer, vagina, wetter, panty dropper,
chick seducer, boner, giver, backbreaker, women, bedder.
Who's it going to be?
Nate best guy ever isn't here right now.
What do you say in your defense?
Of course.
I'm sure everyone was like.
There's nothing to defend.
We're thoroughly destroyed.
That everyone was like, that guy's got it figured out.
I want to know how can I slay, how can I slay,
how can I eviscerate vagina?
Like that guy.
How can I critical hit that puss?
How can I fucking vorpal slash decapitate?
How can I put the pussy in a sarcophagus like him?
How can I mummify it?
And I have nothing to say in my defense.
I'm guilty, your honor.
I'm a beta.
Next voicemail is called It's Not About SF2 This Time.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay, Ben, I really hate to meme on you like this,
but you have to watch Odd Taxi, dude.
It just finished up and the ending just turned everything on its head.
I mean, let's be real now.
Invincible, fucking, I sleep.
Odd Taxi, though.
I also had me fucking shook.
You just have to watch it.
I mean, I won't blame you if you don't want to, but it's really good.
I'm sure it's good.
I'm sure it's great.
I don't care.
I don't care about shows.
I don't care about anything.
Thanks for the recommendation, idiot.
You got anything to say about that, Gib?
How, why?
I wasn't listening because they were talking about you.
Okay, do you see an Odd Taxi?
What do you think about Odd Taxi?
I've seen Crazy Taxi.
No, no, not the same, not the same.
Okay, next one.
It's an MP3 link.
You got it up?
Yes.
It's one of these ones a guy can't fucking figure out how Speakpipe works.
Okay, this one is called Munchy Shortly After He Hacks the Universe.
Three, two, one, go.
I might have to rewrite your history in a second here.
It sounds keyboard-clacking.
And done.
You have.
I hope you enjoy being trans.
Got me.
Did you remember when that was from?
I don't.
I feel like it was, it must have been a like a fucking something or other.
Radcon?
PCP or maybe a ChibiBuckers.
I feel it's like low energy.
Maybe it was a stream.
No idea.
But I do remember that happening.
If anyone remembers when that was, leave a comment because I...
I don't watch this show.
I don't watch this garbage.
You seen that, you seen that Trump tweet, my favorite Trump tweet?
Isn't he gum?
Or is it an old one?
He's always in our hearts.
He's forever in our hearts.
The old Trump tweet about Coca-Cola.
If I've mentioned it before, I'll say it again.
The best Trump tweet was, it was like paraphrasing.
Coca-Cola company is not happy with me.
That's okay.
I'll still drink that garbage.
I remember that.
So good.
That's my favorite one.
He's had some real bangers, but that one was an all-time classic.
That's like almost equivalent to a drill.
It is.
A little tweet.
It really is.
All the, literally all the best tweets are just remind you of drill tweets.
Every, it's like, you know how evolution, right?
You know how like in nature, evolution, like everything eventually becomes a crab?
Like the crab is the perfect form and every creature eventually approaches crab hood.
I didn't know that.
Surely you're familiar with carcinization.
I am not a crab.
It is, it is, it is true that in nature many, even things that are not like related,
like genetically, a lot of like evolutionary lines have sort of
gravitated towards a similar form that resembles a crab, like among multiple different.
The crab is just a very efficient shape.
It's just a very successful shape in nature.
Well, on Twitter and the ecosystem of Twitter, it's the same.
And like people's posting habits all strive towards a single, like perfect template,
a single perfect platonic ideal.
And that ideal is the drill tweet.
It's the ultimate realization of the medium.
They don't strive towards it.
They randomly throw things out there and the drill tweets are like, they naturally select.
Yes, the more like drill your tweet is,
the more successful it will be and the more its genes will be passed on.
Yeah, it's true.
I think I think I'm literally correct.
Next voicemail is called anti-capitalist except for my cheeky tendies.
Three, two, one, go.
I don't understand why so many people are so willing to go to bat for industrialized
animal farming.
These are massive corporations.
They are not your friend.
Their business model is to produce as much as efficiently as possible.
And then obscure from the public the horrifying scale and depravity of what it takes to do so.
Like if you feel a little bad about chickens being kept in cages, you can buy free range.
But no matter what eggs you buy, you're still supporting chick-calling, which is the process
of tossing all the male chicks into industrial grinders because keeping them alive would be
a waste of money.
Like we have laws around animal abuse, but these companies are just completely exempt from them
except for the most threadbare of regulations, which they oftentimes do not even follow.
It just seems like the most quintessential capitalist nightmare and the fact that so
many people, especially leftists, are so apathetic or even actively supporting of it
is baffling to me.
Yeah, sounds right.
I mean, people like their tendies.
Your title said it all.
If getting rid of it would cost people their tendies, like I understand,
but I don't want to lose my tendies.
I like my tendies.
I literally ate tendies today.
I, Ben St, cooked tendies and ate them before this episode.
So I am part of the problem, probably.
There's an addendum, so let's listen to that.
Three, two, one, go.
Also, if there's the response of, oh, well, that's a problem of the system.
We need to work for better regulation instead of pinning the blame on the individual.
The thing is that these are problems inherent to the practice of industrialized animal farming.
There is no sustainable way to produce as many animal products as we do
without running into these issues, no matter what system we're working under
or whatever regulations we have, unless it is just total abolition.
I feel like the goalposts move there.
Is the problem that the practice is immoral or is the problem that it's unsustainable?
I think the first one was more like, I can't believe people don't care enough.
But without mentioning why that was a bad thing.
I see.
I mean, I don't know.
I guess he's right.
Yeah.
I also like my tendies, but I acknowledge it is true.
I mean, what is the world?
Okay, question, serious question.
What is the perfect world?
Is it a world where nobody eats meat or is it a world where there is meat, but it's ethically
farmed?
The whole conversation around this has always been a little weird for me.
And I think a while ago, I settled on, okay, I don't care about animals rights then.
I'd rather just eat and not pick and choose what things I care about.
Like, oh, but what about cats and dogs?
Well, some people do eat those, but I eat chicken, so I eat fish.
I participate in all this stuff by eating the things.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Maybe that's lazy and stupid of me, but I don't know.
I can't help it.
If I'm going to own it, then I'll own it, but I don't know.
Doing something, it takes a lot.
It takes a lot, not just to advocate and eat vegetables, because that's possible.
It's the, I don't know.
I hate this conversation.
I need a lot more brain power right now to argue about it.
I'll just accept that I'm a bad person and that I will eat and kill animals,
because it's easier for me to accept that about myself than it is to try and
change my entire world, change everything about the way I consume food,
because no matter what I do about food specifically, there's always going to be
some industry that I'm supporting by participating in purchasing anything.
Sure.
So I'm like, at some point, I'm like, yeah, fine.
I'll just, I'll be, I'm a murderer.
Fuck it.
Yeah.
I agree.
It's intractable.
I want to be better about it, but like I just, it's too hard to do all that and also work on
myself and everything I'm trying to do.
Like, I don't think about what I put in my mouth too much.
I'm like, oh God, I got to eat today.
Oh shit, I haven't eaten.
And I have to think, oh wait, I've been meaning to like change my diet so that it's different.
And now I got to buy all this other stuff.
Maybe there's like, you know, it's worth, it's worth like doing that for the,
it's just not easy and I don't like it.
We can talk about this all day.
My, my, my, I have no defense.
That's, that's my position.
I have no defense.
I'm a murderer.
I'll eat a horse.
I'll eat a cat.
I like eating.
I don't give a fuck, but I do, but I don't, but I do, but I won't, but I
don't, I just want to break down, just punch the ground.
I don't know what to do about it.
We do eat, we do eat too much meat.
I think, I think it's just true that like America and probably the UK just eat like
more meat than is necessary.
And probably our, even aside from like, you know, killing animals is bad and cruel.
That might be true.
But I think like just like reducing our meat intake would probably mean that our
impact on the environment would be better.
Yeah, I've heard that.
Yeah.
That's definitely a better reason than, don't feel bad about it.
Because I don't, I don't believe, I mean, I don't believe that, I don't believe that
consumer choices are going to drive change in that area.
Like the best, the best it'll do is create a new market for like fucking hippy vegan
equally consumer.
Ooh, ethical capitalism bullshit.
Yeah, that's kind of how I feel.
Okay, let's-
It's, it's, yeah, I thought I could shut up.
Yeah, keep digging my hole.
Next voicemail is Janess, three, two, one, go.
How do you talk for so long on podcasts and streams without having to gasp for breath?
I know, it's so annoying.
I'm so obnoxious.
I never, shut up.
You just gasped for breath right then.
I literally, I do, I mean, do you think I don't, I mean, I do breathe.
I don't know what they mean, because obviously we take breath while we're speaking.
I don't, I don't have any tips and tricks.
I just may, I think that maybe you just don't notice the breathing.
I think maybe it's like-
Now you're noticing it, because I'm noticing it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sometimes I'll hear a YouTuber say like, oh, I think like maybe Mr. Beetong made a comment
or someone, sometimes I'll make a comment like, oh yeah, that video sounds really bad.
You know, you, you can hear my lip smacking.
You can hear my, my, get my breathing.
You can hear my, my smacks and pops or whatever.
And I'll have never noticed it at all.
Right, but they, but they noticed it.
So maybe you just don't, maybe your brain is just filtering out.
Like you don't pay attention, because that's just noise.
And you don't pay attention to it.
It's, it's, maybe it's similar to like-
Because I definitely do gasp for breath all the time.
Because like, I shave my arms, right, to get rid of the arm hair.
That's the dysphoria thing.
But I never really pay attention to the fact that women have arm hair.
It's not, it's just a little less noticeable.
But like having completely smooth arms is not a feminine thing.
It is a, is a, you know, it's a different thing.
Yeah.
So like in real life, people breathe.
You just don't notice it.
Sad, but true.
They really do.
They do, they do be breathing though.
We do a little breathing.
Just a little.
Next voicemail is called ravioli.
Three, two, one, go.
It has made some really good ravioli.
Nice.
My rat is eating something and she really likes it.
You just wanted to say that to somebody.
Based.
Cool.
You should have made a rat tattoo.
I made, I made one time I made, I think it was like sweet potato ravioli.
Like it had like a spice, like sweet potato interior.
Potato inside of a fucking pasta.
I know.
It's more of a pierogi at that point.
But I made, I made, that was the only time that I made the pasta from scratch.
Like I made the pasta dough and I like flattened it and I cut it into squares.
And I made the little pouches.
That was the only time in my life that I've like made pasta.
It's really freaking hard.
Maybe you just have to practice a lot and get efficient at it.
I would like to do that.
That sounds fun.
I'd never tried it for some reason.
Have you ever had, have you ever had pierogies?
I don't think so.
They are a Polish thing.
It's basically, it's basically like a dumpling or a ravioli.
But it's got, it's got mashed potatoes inside.
It's good.
No, no thoughts, no thoughts on that.
Oh, sorry.
I just blacked out.
No, no thoughts head empty.
Ravioli.
Hey, I make it up.
Hey, I make of the pierogi.
Hey, I make of the borsche.
I cook it up.
What's on it?
I make it a kilbasa.
Mamma mia, cze.
What's on it?
What's a, what's a Polish thing?
Uh, hey, hey, minnowie, minnowie popolsku.
Uh, pasta brazu.
That was the one, that was the one phrase that I remember off the top of my head
that I could say in Polish.
Minnowie popolsku.
I don't speak Polish.
Minnowie, minnowie popolsku.
Next, and cze, which is a, no, cze is high.
Oh, and of course, nazdrowie, which is cheers.
Oh, and stola.
Obviously.
Next.
Next voicemail is called ravioli two.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Wait, my other rat, I gave her ravioli.
She did not like the ravioli.
Damn.
That's it.
One of, there are, there are two rats inside of you.
Uh, uh.
Only one of them likes ravioli.
There's, there's two rats inside of you.
The one that wins is the one that you feed.
And the one that you feed will be the one that likes ravioli
because the other one won't eat it.
What?
Yeah.
You know the, say, you know the saying about the, there's two.
Yeah, I know the saying about the two rats and the ravioli.
It's a classic phrase.
Oh, the rats and the ravioli and the silver spoon.
Yeah.
Okay.
Next voicemail is called out three, two, one, go.
God damn it, Ben.
You laid the seat like two or three weeks ago or something.
And it's, it's just been there in the subconscious, the voice, the voice telling me,
just, just try to open your mouth as far as you fucking can.
I'm sorry.
Ben was right.
See if it'll hurt.
See if it'll keep hurting after you close it again.
You can, you can make it hurt if you want to.
Fuck you, Ben.
I'm sorry.
I had not thought about that.
But now, now that he's brought it up or they brought it up,
I should not do the gender thing.
But now that they brought it up, everyone who listens to this podcast will now think about it.
That is the, that is the kind of thing that, I mean, yeah, that's the kind of thing that,
like, I would get that idea in my head.
I would hear someone say, what happens if you open your mouth as wide as you can?
And then I would consider, this is what I'm, this is the same thing with me thinking about
what if I got my head crushed by a train?
It's like, now I just think about it all the time.
What if, what if, what if you were trying to open your mouth as wide as it could?
But before you got to the maximum amount, you got hit by a train
and you could never find out.
At least then I wouldn't have to feel weird of my jaw unhinged and fucked up.
Yeah, be in many pieces.
Many, many pieces, little tiny pieces, all down the train track.
I hate it.
I fucking hate it.
I hate having a physical body.
Shit, I can't wait to be dead.
I should go put my head on a fucking train track so I don't have to deal with this bullshit anymore.
In Minecraft.
I should go put my head on a mine cart track.
You just got to do, you just got to have like the catharsis-
Made a void, made a void metal, Thaumaturge.
You got to have the catharsis of the train crush head simulator game to get,
answer all these questions.
You're, I, I don't want to think about it.
Okay, next voicemail is called Uwu,
UwuLillia recommends a documentary.
This is from kukmichael at comeonmytits.com.
Three, two, one, go.
Hi guys, so I saw this really good documentary.
It's about how coves are bad actually.
What's bad?
They're kind of alien and they're being used to place us.
And not gonna lie, once I finished watching it,
I decided I'm never wearing coves again.
It also makes it way easier for me to come up with titties.
So, uh, you're talking about, are you talking about Kill-a-Kill?
It's on Netflix.
It's called Kill-a-Kill.
I knew it.
I think you should really check it out.
Come on Michelle, take that tittie away.
You want a taste of the name, don't you?
Gross.
This is the only place you're going to kill it.
Well, um, Michelle, response, they just want to fuck me.
Why would they do this?
Well, the same reason they do anything is they really want to fuck me.
It's the animating force behind.
Why do they have to do this and also have a terrible microphone?
That's what I want to know.
You know fair, yeah.
I like relatively high effort, uh, sound modulation effects combined with a terrible audio quality.
Lamal.
Uh, next voicemail is called XXX Hardcore Brutal Painful...
What?
Wait, um, fucking, fucking, um, fucking munchie at Al are calling me.
I'm in the middle of a fucking podcast, you freaks.
Uh-oh.
You're going to miss your last chance to say hello to munchie.
My god, I hope so.
Uh, okay.
Jesus.
All right, uh, where was I?
Hardcore Brutal Painful Sad Heartbreaking Dirty Anal XXX321.
Let's jam.
What's up, fellas?
I want to know if you guys saw the new, um, Sara Z, I believe it's her name.
Sara Z.
Video about she, she's getting legal threat from, from Homestuck.
Homestuck, it's a legal threat, threat, threat, threat.
I've stopped listening.
Yeah, I've seen that.
Threatening her, uh, it was a big one.
Okay.
End of voicemail.
That's it.
I've heard enough.
Um, I didn't watch that video because I'm annoyed by its premise and I don't like her
face in the thumbnail.
Those are the two reasons why I haven't watched it.
I didn't watch it for a while, for the similar, for a similar like, oh,
it's a drama video or something.
I don't care.
Like Homestuck, whatever.
But people assured me that it was a wild ride.
So I just, you know, I wanted to see and it is kind of wild,
but it is ultimately kind of like a whatever.
What annoys me.
It's like a Lindsay Ellis drama video.
There's something that annoys me about it and it's, I think it's that like,
there's a little bit of, I feel a little duplicitousness about it because I know
that Sara Z.
Like I'm imagining myself in her position, I would be thrilled to receive a spurious
legal threat from whatpumpkin.com and then to make this video because this is the kind
of thing that would get a lot of views and it also, it's, it's, it's the, it's the,
it's the jackpot because not it's, it's like current, it's drama and it's about something
that's popular, but it's also about you.
And the fact that this content is now it, it's an excuse to talk about yourself and
profile yourself and make yourself kind of the, the center of attention.
And that's like exactly what a YouTuber thrives on is getting the audience to invest in them.
So I know that she must love this.
And yet I see her on the thumbnail and she's making a face like she's sad and worried.
And I think you're a liar.
That face is lying to me and it pisses me off.
I mean, I guess you could call it a lie.
That's how I feel.
That's how I feel when I see it.
The video is like self-contained.
Like the story begins and ends with the video because she goes through all of the emails
and by the end of the video, she says they've dropped the claim.
So the video was not necessary in like clearing her name or anything.
She just wanted to tell the story about it.
Just like, let's look at this wacky like emails from Andrew himself.
He starts, he starts his first email saying, hey, I made homestuck.
And that was Andrew's kind of funny.
Like, like unintentionally.
And I suppose it's interesting to see, but I don't really, I didn't watch this and then
say, wow, what a great YouTuber Sarah's is that is.
I will now subscribe.
Like that's, I was just mostly interested in seeing Andrew.
How's he read, write strange emails.
I'm just trying to explain the kind of like, the kind of like immediate like sort of gut
level, like I'm a little bit repulsed when I see this.
I felt the same.
It's the same reason why I didn't watch, I didn't watch Lindsay Ellis's like video about
how she got canceled on Twitter.
And I didn't watch the new one that she just put, I used to watch every Lindsay Ellis video,
but I didn't want to watch her, I got canceled on Twitter video.
And because of that, I was, I also was like, you know what, I won't watch this other new
Lindsay Ellis video either.
I don't know if I care what she has to say.
Maybe you should unsubscribe.
Maybe I should unsubscribe from a YouTube channel, Lindsay, just for no real clear
reason that I can articulate.
But that's my right as a, as an American.
And no one can tell me otherwise.
Fourth of July, baby fireworks.
Yeah.
Uh, next voicemail is called AV.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey y'all, it's AVE.
Long time listener, first time parasocial bastard.
Just wanted to call in to say happy birthday to Gib.
I got into the PCP from finding fighters are people too in like 2016.
And I don't know if you even remember it, but the video real talk you should vote
and here's why it's like the funniest thing in the entire world.
If people listening haven't seen it, go watch it right now.
It's very, very good.
Um, I've been starting to transition in the last year.
They them right now.
And hearing your perspective and journey has really let me feel like I'm not just
making stuff up in my head.
You're one of the creators that has inspired me the most.
And seeing you grow has made me feel like maybe I can too.
Thanks for everything.
Happy birthday.
That's great.
Anyways, PCP forever.
Some will never die.
Everybody go pledge to Lord of Ghosts right fucking now.
Yeah.
True.
Well, I have no, I have no objections to any of that.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Also interesting.
You say you got into the PCP from spiders are people too.
Spiders are people too is the animation you did, right?
Yeah.
It's like, I mean, it's on my give and take channel.
And I guess.
How many views does that have?
It's not that many, I don't think.
I'm very surprised.
I'm very surprised that that would be the first PCP media that someone would find.
Yeah, 6.7 thousand views.
It's just statistically, statistically.
You would like, it's so much more likely that someone would have gotten into us through
the Brony stuff or like the Chris Chan lecture or maybe one of the other lectures or like.
Yeah, I'm very curious million view videos or something.
I'm very curious where they saw spiders of people too, whether it was just recommended
or whether they were like.
Yeah, where were they find it?
Well, that's great.
That's really nice to hear that I've inspired you and you're trying out new stuff.
And that's a very wholesome voicemail.
I call some voicemail.
Thank you.
AVE?
Did they say their name was AVE?
And AVE for AVE.
I think they said AVE.
What?
Thanks for the voicemail.
I love you.
Next, next voicemail is Hussie Suss.
Is that the next one?
Yes.
Hussie Suss.
Three, two, one, go.
It's AVE again.
I forgot to mention, have y'all seen this?
There is the Zed Homestuck follow-up video that just came out.
It seems right up your alley and I'd love to hear you talk about it.
We just did.
Sorry if my last voicemail was too long and gay.
I'm trying my fucking bad.
See y'all.
It's fine.
No, we already talked about it.
Okay, next voicemail is a message for the ladies.
Three, two, one, go.
Men do not derive sexual pleasure from blowjobs.
We just think they're really funny.
Ladies, if you're listening to this, stop giving out blowjobs.
But they're funny.
It's been a prank this entire time.
We're just messing with you.
Stop falling for it.
I can't stand the secondhand embarrassment anymore.
I don't care if this is breaking man code telling you this.
It's too much for me.
I can't take it anymore.
Blowjobs are not real.
Stop doing them.
We got, shut them up, shut them up.
And the voicemail.
No, we can't, Eleazar, cut that out.
We can't let, we can't let the message, we can't let the message spread.
Okay, a few.
I'm glad Eleazar will.
Do that and prevent, prevent, keep the secret.
It's too funny.
It's just a big prank.
It's a big prank.
We're all in on it.
I'm sending a fucking, I'm sending a formal complaint
about berserk chip for this one to the bro headquarters.
I like the idea that it's, it's, it's like, it's a joke,
but maybe even also not even pleasurable.
It's, like the coming is just like, oh, just learn how to do that on command.
Just so we can make it like look real.
We have to, we have to take one for the team.
It's work.
We have to put in the work and take one for the team,
just so we can tell everyone like, she did it again.
Oh my God.
LeMau.
What an idiot.
I can't believe it.
I can't believe they fell for it again.
Um, why, I mean, why is it a message for the ladies?
Guys can give blowjobs.
Wait, if two, if two guys, if a guy gives another guy a blowjob,
then since they're both guys, they must both know that it's just a joke.
Well, all right.
Then if it's, if it's two guys doing it,
then they must just both be doing it because they both think it's funny.
No, no, no, no.
They, no, they, they, they, they think that like when they're giving one,
that it's doing something.
And then therefore when they're getting one, they're like,
Oh, I thought maybe, maybe something's wrong with me.
I thought this was going to feel good,
but instead I'm just laughing inside.
But I got to pretend I like it.
And so the lie continues.
This is why, this is why people turn gay.
This is why, this is how cultural Bolshevism has made America gay.
By just tricking men into thinking the, the natural order of things is men
knowing that blowjobs are just a big prank and a joke.
But they've, culture, media, media has convinced us that miscegenation is okay.
And that blowjobs are serious and not just a fucking meme.
And now look at us.
Weak men rule the country, dogs and cats living together, mass hysteria.
Okay.
Next voicemail, your name optional.
Three, two, one, go.
Girls and pals, I will think about like getting some sort of segment
structure into the podcast.
You can still do your like depressed, my life sucks, free talk,
but like as a segment and like do other stuff because I feel like currently the podcast is sort
of just a, how do you say it, a cacophon of just hymning and highing about until you like go
to voicemails and then get angry at people for doing shitty voicemail.
So maybe, maybe I know that I know that you just want to, you just wanted to pee on the voicemail.
So you thought of some paper thin excuse to be like, let me just frame this as the,
in the form of giving advice.
Some people, I think some people think they can have advice to give to be like,
what if you guys did this with it instead of the podcast, the podcast needs to change.
And here's my idea for how to change it.
Well, they don't understand that the podcast is perfect now, as it always has been and always will
be. There's no, there's no improvements to be made. I would say you say that it's a cacophon,
I'm sure you deliberately pronounce mispronounced cacophony, but I still wouldn't use cacophony
there. Cacophony is like loud, like a like a loud sort of like a din, like a chaotic
layered of many mismatched noises.
Some of the voicemails are a cacophony. I think the word you're looking for would probably be like,
a, what's the word for just not like a loud explosion of chaos, but like a, like a disorganized
labyrinth, no, like a, like a, like a rabble.
A rabble is like a group of people.
What's the word that me, a lasagna, you're speaking of a chaotic lasagna.
An onion, a chaotic cacophonous onion lasagna. So many layers.
There's definitely a word, a word that is like a, a, a strew, like strewn.
Ah, fuck. I've sort of lost the thread of what you're trying to describe.
Word that means something that is just kind of strewn all over the place randomly,
structurally, chaotic mess, messy, unkempt, synonyms and ansonyms,
uh, uh, just hither and thither, rats, a rats nest, a taxia,
opel mel, opel mel is a great fucking, yes, here we go, synonym, a taxia, synonyms,
I've never heard that, hold on, a taxia, definition, that's gotta have a Greek root, right?
Uh, oh, a taxia, noun, the loss of full control of bodily movements.
Oh, okay. Uh, that's not exactly what I'm looking for.
Hurly burly, hurly burly, now there would be a great word, uh, uh, pal mel.
So like you would say these hurly, pearly voicemails, what do you, what is the object?
He, he's not talking about the whole, he's talking about the whole, uh,
the show, not just the voicemails. Also, pal mel noun, a state of affairs or
collection of things characterized by haste or confusion. The pal mel is actually
pandemonium, helter skelter, uh, pal, I'm on synonym, I love thesaurus.com,
uh, noun, just sort of pandemonium, a snarl, a tumult, ooh, a tumult, yes, the whole podcast
is just a tumult, that's good. Um, a ferment, tumultuous, stupid. Some of these are like bad.
Actually, thesaurus kind of sucks sometimes. I don't know if these, I mean, tumults feels
like it's like a, a large crowd. And that's how I feel. Yeah. Two people just being disorderly is
like hullabaloo. No, hullabaloo is noisy. Hullabaloo is raucous. This isn't like a big,
like, like pandemonium is not the type of word. Cacophony implies noise, but most of the podcast
is not noisy. It's just disordered. So not bedlam. Bedlam also implies noise. Uh,
a, a spaghetti. I'm imagining like a, like a spaghetti, just like, like tubes.
A series of spaghetti. There's a, there's a better word. There's gotta be a better word for not something
that is noisy, but something that is, something that is randomly arranged, disordered, an arrangement
of things that are, that are in disorder. Comment, if you, if you have a word, suggest a word in the
comments and I will, I will, I will like, I will favorite the best one. I feel like, like chaos,
chaos is like some sort of a chaos, like a quiet chaos, something like that. I'm looking for one
word though. I'm looking for one word. Deliberate chaos. That's two words. It's too many. You cut,
sometimes you need two words. Sometimes there isn't one word to describe a very specific thing.
It's always better to use one word instead of two.
Anyway, I can't think of what I'm thinking of. So I'm just going to go with, you can't
fucking think of the word. I'm going to go with palmel until someone suggests a better one in the
comments. Next voicemail, cross. Am I the only one? Three, two, one, go. Am I the only one who,
in Minecraft, enjoys breaking chicken eggs on a block that is sitting over top of lava, that way
on the off chance that a baby chicken spawns, its first moments in this world will be consumed with
fire, pain, molten lead, and the delicious smell of its own flesh cooking. Just me?
Yes, just you. I mean, on my on a PCP server, there are no mobs, there are no chickens, so nobody
lays any eggs. I mean, why would you throw eggs? Why would you collect eggs just so that you could
throw them? Why would you throw it wouldn't like make profit from making more chickens that you
can make more eggs? Why would you break eggs in a specific way? What is that? What do you think
this is? Noida? Oh, that reminds me. I almost forgot to say this week I did it. I did the ultimate
Noida thing. I got all 33 orbs. And now, um, wow, I got all three. No, I got to show you
my character. I have a, I have a pendant. I have a magic pendant now. It's a miracle.
There he is. There's my guy. He's got the pendant.
Oh, got the gold pendant because he got all he got 11 orbs from the main new game plus world.
And he got 11 orbs from the East parallel world and he got 11 orbs from the West parallel world.
Now the other the next thing I got to do is I got to do the Sunseed quest and I got to create
the sun and the dark sun. But I will do that eventually probably not that soon. The this was
this was a big this was a big I for a long time I didn't play Noida and it was because I had
started a God run and then I kind of quit it in the middle at like at the point that I was like
I'm I'm basically a God. Now I just have to do the work of actually going around and finding
all 33 orbs. And it was so that was such like a busy work like I don't want that like I just
didn't play Noida for like a month because I didn't have that usual urge of like I want to
boot up Noida and just have that rush of like going from being a weakling to getting a chainsaw
one coming and going and killing everything that that that feeling of progression was not there.
And that's what usually enticed me. So I was just like, I just fuck it. But I was like,
I think I think I've been I've been working on the game for like a long time this month.
And I think I got burnt out. And I was like, I got to do something else. You know what?
I'll finish that Noida game. And then I did. And I did my job. Wow. Wow.
But I got the pendant. That's what's important. Next voicemail.
Next voice is just an image. I guess I'll post the image. It's Sarah said is that it doesn't
really look like her other than that it has blowing up. She's blowing up what pumpkin head
quarters with a bomb. This is annoying. I'm an I feel like I don't I'm annoyed by this.
Maybe that's not fair. But that's how I feel. That's my truth. I mean, I feel it's just sort of
it's making her look so great when the only thing that really happened was that
they had no case and she said no. And then they were like, yeah, sorry.
Like she didn't do anything. She just didn't get destroyed by them for but they had no way
to do it anyway. They would just I think the lady who initially gave the lawsuit
admitted that she was mad. It's like an emotional thing. And it was very unprofessional, obviously.
But like, obviously, there's just she's just like she's a YouTuber. It's yeah.
Like sure, it's it's a little bit of an embarrassing snafu for what pumpkin and
hussy by proxy. Absolutely the case. Nevertheless, Sarah Zed is just some YouTuber
who doesn't even write her own scripts all by herself. She just sits on a couch and reads a script.
And she has never contributed anything of value to culture. I really feel this way.
I'm sorry if this is cringe. I don't think Sarah Zed has contributed anything of value.
Hussy, for all his faults, has made great contributions to culture. And for that,
I just have to be like, who do you think you are? Am I being a simp? I feel like maybe I'm simping
a little but I kind of feel like who do you Sarah Zed think you are to clown on Andrew Hussy?
What have you ever done? You got a spurious lawsuit? Great. Congratulations.
Yeah, I feel like a lot of the reason people are like all backing Sarah is is because
like Hive Swap has been handled terribly. There's been various controversies and they're just like,
you know, everything they they have against what pumpkin and the way Homestucko and Hive Swap
and all of that has been handled. They're just like, yeah, now this is a person we can ascribe
all of this like to like we're mad about this. Even aside from this whole thing and the whole
Sarah Zed situation, I feel like Homestuck has been kind of like a low hanging fruit easy target
for people to shit on for a while now. And I feel like this is just kind of another,
this is just kind of she's she plucked, she did it. She plucked the low hanging fruit
and made it and she she she went into the medium. And you know what good and you know what good
for her God bless her I can't begrudge her for it but the lands of likes and subscribes.
Yeah, yeah, whatever. I'm so that's what I have to say about this image.
Thanks for the voicemail. Next next one is called get and large prime numbers three two one go.
Then use get for source control on your game project. We'll keep a history of all your code
and asset changes. So if your PC dies or catastrophically fuck something, you can go back a day
or two. I use GitHub. There's also Git labs and a bunch of other ones. All you got to do is download
an app like SourceTree or GitHub desktop, make a repository on the website, you clone it from the
app, you move your project into it, you push it, and then each day you commit your work.
Also, one of Tim Rogers' band was called large prime numbers and they put out some bangers.
You can find songs on YouTube and Bandcamp song right now playing. It's called for those about
to go. I don't think. Also, also, I don't think musical voicemail sound the same and suck for it.
I don't think you know what a game maker file looks like. I don't think I can just copy paste a
I can't. No, I don't think I don't think I can just paste my game maker file into GitHub.
Have you ever made a game make? Have you ever made it use if you were done a game and game maker
with GML? No, but is there a folder that it's in? Well, I mean, yeah, there's the folder. Well,
I guess, but if I was so that if you have like if you make an update and you it's all logged there
and it's like because I've used GitHub a little bit and basically it's like I use GitHub for endless
war. Yeah, it's like a save state for the contents of a folder. It doesn't have to be anything specific.
Hmm. Hmm. You know, you have you have the folder that your game maker stuff is inside.
You save it on GitHub and then you accidentally destroyed everything and you delete it out of
the recycle bin. You just roll back to GitHub and then that folder which is synced up to Git will
literally become the same as it was. So how is that? How is that any different from just like
saving backup versions of the file and like Google Drive or something?
I guess it's no different. It's just a somewhat simple. I guess if you know if you know how to
do it, it's somewhat simple. If you don't, it's hard to learn. I got taught taught by my brother
who is a code master. When I would use GitHub, I would like go into the text files in the Git
folder and like directly edit the text. It wasn't I didn't use like syncing with my computers.
Well, honestly, when you say it like that and it's like, oh, Git will just like directly copy
the contents of a folder and create backup like, okay, actually, that does sound really convenient
if I knew how to do it. So maybe I should look into it actually. I do have some I have some backup
save but they're on my computer. So I honestly should be saving backup versions like to some
place secure in the in the cloud or something. That much is true. Okay, I have to I have to
take a shit. I want to finish this. Next one is called clearing up terms three, two, one, go.
Um, that doesn't but the if the communist is doing it from inside parliamentary politics,
isn't there still a state then? Are they still engaging in statecraft?
I don't know. The distinction between like, government and state is a little it's a little
academic and I get a little tripped up there about where exactly one ends and the other begins.
But okay, I yeah, that's a reasonable distinction between communists and anarchists that makes
that makes sense. Okay, next voicemail is a glimpse into the future best guys forever three, two, one, go.
The year is 20 xx. At one point, Nate Bestman was a staunch capitalist ready to pull himself up
by his bootstraps. Things have changed. In the early 21st century, a certain league came together
to capitalize on these succulent ass in a multitude of ways. One way it was in cloning
and enslaving them. Virginia once again found use in slave labor as millions of Nates were created.
He could be found in every home, every business, hard at work. A month following Ben's ascension
to Godhood and bestowed gifts, Ben appeared to one of the millions of Nates and said unto him,
Gurren Lagen, more like gay in Lagen, the Nate was dumbfounded, but slowly a smile crept across
his face. He knew what he had to do. In covert, this Nate created a network of other Nates,
and soon the preparations were made abolition and the Nate Wars began. The wars were bloody.
Millions died on both sides. But in the end, the Nates were victorious. Oh, shit. Two migrations
followed the war. The surviving Nate fuckers fled their concubines in tow. But to Virginia,
came all the Nate heads, eager to help rebuild. Virginia from then forth would be known as Best
Virginia. This is a future before you. Even now, the hands of feet move ever closer to this
eventuality. This thoroughly based future. So I'm a little confused. So it sounds like the
Nate fuckers control the Nates and the Nates are allied with the Nate fuckers. But the Nate heads
are against the Nate fuckers and therefore also against the Nates? No, no, no. I think that the
Nate heads are there to liberate the Nates from the Nate fuckers. Yeah. Okay. They are slaves,
as I said. I see. Yeah, I guess that makes sense. I guess that makes sense. Dark. Timeline is dark.
Curse time one. MLN, everybody. Multi-level marketing. No, NLN, Nate lives matter.
Yes. Yeah. No, Nate would never say that. It's too political.
Next voicemail is called Clearing Up Terms Two, plus Minor Cycloneal Spoilers Two. Three, two, one, go.
If not participating in electoral politics sounds absurd, it is because anarchists believe in
something called the theory of means and ends. This theory details how when people are put into
the chain of politics their goals and motives change. For instance, a full-fledged communist
can run for office, and if they win they might, instead of removing power from the state, secure
more power for themselves. As they see themselves as the arbiter of socialism, so removing that
power would be contrary to the goal. You can see this happen with Lenin and particularly Stalin in
their actions as heads of the USSR. There's an anarchist quote that goes socialist leaders who
find themselves caught up in the electoral machine, end up being gradually nothing more than bourgeois
with liberal ideas. They have placed themselves in determinate conditions that in turn determine
them. To an anarchist going into government to change it from the inside is as ridiculous as
going into the police force to change it from the inside. The system will break you before you
break the system. The praxis we use must be congruent with socialism. Through joining and
participating in anarchist groups members learn how to engage with ideas like direct democracy
and non-hierarchical organized groups. A hierarchy-led revolution is inherently susceptible to the
same corruption as any hierarchical system and is contrary to the goal of a non-hierarchical world.
Anyways, this is the message of Psycholonials. Zed tried to create socialism through authoritarianism
I don't know if that's the message of Psycholonial. I don't know. I think you're giving a little too
much credit. I think it's an idea in Psycholonials rather than the message. Me and Cheesy talked
about this a couple weeks ago, how we don't think that was like really, that theme was really
followed through on... I mean, her like political, honestly, throughout Psycholonials,
Zed's like political goals are basically just, she kind of says she's like it's a left-wing
revolution, but all she really does is just maintain power and not get destroyed by the
United States military. That's all she actually does. It's a little bit toothless as far as
like a political commentary. I can't remember exactly, but she inspires mostly violent takeovers
of police buildings and government things by clowns. More so than instilling, because yeah,
I think I talked about this before, that the her manifesto doesn't really go into much
specific like policy stuff. The only, yeah, I mean, it's, I mean, it talks about gender stuff
and that it makes it a big funny clown joke, which is cool. Yeah,
but I mean, I like this was, I mean, the thing about the system changes you and you get inside,
you become bourgeois with liberal ideas, that sounds, that seems true to life,
that lines up with my experience of reality. Anyway, good voicemail, thank you.
Next one is called Anamorphing Time. Three, two, one, go.
Ben, did you invite Tyler back to be on the PCP? You fucked back?
No.
What do you want to come?
I guess like, I guess I could have. I guess I could have, but I didn't.
If he wants, if he wanted to be on the podcast, he could be on the podcast if he wants to, honestly.
I'll fucking do, I'll, I'm down for anything. Next voicemail is called Anamorphing Time two,
three, two, one, go. Ben, did you get drunk on the Anamorphing Time podcast too?
I bought special booze because I'm going to be on it.
Based. Who is this? No, they told me that the episode before the one that I was on,
which I don't think that one is out yet. It's not one that's out yet, but they told me the one
before I'm on, they got really drunk and it ran really long. They weren't drinking on the episode
I was on. I wasn't either. And our episode ran short. It's like less than two hours because
our book is really bad and there's like nothing to say about it. So no, we didn't get drunk, I'm
sorry. And I blew my shot too because they only, they said they only have one, they said they're
only going to have one guest per episode or they're only going to have guests come one time.
They've had like one repeat guest, but I think they said they were going to do like one person,
one appearance from now on. So I'm out. I'm out forever. Next voicemail is called The Vavitch,
three, two, one, go. Ben, you mentioned you'd seen The Witch. Yep. What do you think about it?
That was pretty good. Bye. Okay. Next voicemail. It was good. It was
a tense, it was thrilling as a thriller should be. I liked it. It made me feel dread and anticipation
and the part where the spoilers, the part where the boy dies at the beginning and he cries out
to God and he's all happy and he's smiling creepily and he's saying all this weird
God shit, he's like, what does he say? Jesus, invite me to thy lap, let me lay in thy lap,
oh Christ my lord. And he's like ecstasy and then his eyes roll back and he dies.
And then his mom starts like screaming and his mom's like, oh, the devil speaks scripture too,
the devil speaks scripture too, our son is in hell, our boy is in hell. That part was really
disturbing and stuck with, not in like a horror movie way, just in like a,
I guess no that is, it's just in a, it's not, it wasn't scary, but it's like a situation that
was very distressing and it was memorable because I'm like, boy, what a horrible scene,
that one's gonna stick with me and it did. And I thought the ending was kind of cool.
The ending's kind of just unironically cool. Have you seen it, Gib?
Nope. It's scary probably. It's not that scary. It's, I don't think there's any jump scares.
It's, yeah, it's not, no, no, there's one, when the witch is like in the cabin with them,
drinking the goat's milk, that one's kind of spooky. The ending is just, the ending's kind of like
badass. So it's good. I kind of like, I kind of like that it ended on a, on like a note like that,
like that sort of left me with like a good feeling about it. Instead of like,
what is it, not hereditary, Midsommar ends in a, in a really horrible way. It's like
the downfall, everything bad that could have happened has happened, the ruination is utter,
the downfall is complete. And it's like, that's a well-made movie, but it left me with a very like,
you know, it left me with a very negative feeling, as I think it was supposed to,
because the events of the movie are very negative. Whereas the the witch, it's like,
all this bad things happen and it's kind of horrible. But in the end, the main character
kind of gets the, she kind of wins in the end, and it's kind of awesome. And that left me sort of
like, that was kind of cool, actually. Yeah, that's it. That's what I have to say. Next voicemail
is called PCP Bad Comments Award Show 268. Three, two, one, go.
You unlock this door with the key of procrastination, beyond it is another dimension,
a dimension of entitlement, a dimension of arrogance, a dimension of lip tarts.
You're moving into a land of both the social and parasocial of memes and dreams. I love this.
You've just crossed over into the PCP Bad Comments Award Show. Here is a person named Just Lexi.
Lexi is listening to the Procrastinators podcast. In the episode, somebody makes fun of Trixie,
and Lexi has an amusing thought. In fact, it is perhaps the funniest thing Lexi has ever thought
of. Oh no. Such an incredible joke that Lexi must share it with everyone else. Let's see. They type
out their comment and hit send. It reads, Trixie identifies as society. And that is the worst
comment on episode 268. So the next time while listening to the PCP, if you have some stunning
observation, some humorous remark, some biting criticism, think before you post, or you might
find yourself on the PCP Bad Comments Award Show. I gotta admit, I gotta say, I don't know what that
comment means. No. It's sort of an attack helicopter joke, but like, it's not really even that.
It's, yeah, it's a bad comment, not because it's like insulting, or because it's like
annoying, but just because it's confusing and it's definitely trying to do something,
but I don't know what it was trying to say, so it definitely failed at its intentions there. So I
would say, yeah, pretty solid choice for the zone. Another banger of an episode of the PCP
Bad Comments Award Show. Thank you. Thank you for the voicemail. Next one is called Majora's Mask.
Three, two, one, go. If you played Ocarina of Time and you want to play Majora's Mask, but the assets
look too similar, just play Majora's Mask 3D instead, because those are different assets.
And if you played Ocarina of Time 3D, then play original Majora's Mask. There, problem solved.
It's not, it's not that I was like, the assets look too similar, and that puts me off. It's that
instinctually, I sort of had the feeling that it was like the same game, just because it looks the
same, even though I know it's not. You know, I watched the, I've seen two videos, one of them
saying that the Majora's Mask remake is a bad remake. And I had that thought, I think you must
have seen it, the thumbnail with like the big lips from George Lucas. Narrow, the narrow video.
Yeah, something, I remember seeing that and being like, okay, I guess I shouldn't play the remake.
But I also watched the AVGN episode about playing Majora's Mask. And he found, because, you know,
AVGN, he screams at all the really frustrating bits. Nobody talks about the things that suck.
And I'm like, God, I don't want to play that. It looks really annoying. And I'm sure that's like a
misrepresentation of the game. But still, I don't like old games when they, they be annoying.
Yo, Gib, I got a great attention to the Lord of Ghost Kickstarter,
where you are at 91 backers, and you are five pounds away from Redman. This happened just
within the last hour or two. Holy shit, 2,995 pounds. Hell yeah. We're so close. It's happening,
it's happening, base. I think as soon as it ticks over, I'm going to get around to,
I'm going to start like making the PDF of that so that I can figure out exactly how the layout is
going to be. I don't think there's going to be a contents page. There's a lot of Redman comics.
You should get on writing the ghost stories because you're almost halfway through the
campaign. And the day is coming soon. You should, you should try and get those out to the guest
artists like before the campaign ends. I've got two more to write. I've sent you yours. I don't
know whether you noticed. Oh God, that's right. I did notice, but I told myself like, okay, I'll
look at this later. Yeah, I didn't actually, I didn't read through it. So hopefully that has
all the information you need. I sent Kazi, her one. I got another one ready. And then two more to
write. I should, yeah, I should do that first. I should do that soon as possible. Yeah. Yeah. I
mean, it's all, it's all work that's got to get done. I just wanted to draw your attention to that.
Next voicemail is called shoplifting strats. Three, two, one, go. All right. I got some shoplifting
strats for you all. You go to this channel. It's called gas station encounters. It is just this guy
who thinks he's really cool, catching people shoplifting from his gas station. So watch these
videos and you do opposition research. This is what not to do because they all get caught.
And then a big man gets really angry at them. So I hope he at least works at the fucking gas
station to be better, I guess. I don't know. Yeah. Know thy enemy. Next voicemail is called
question three, two, one, go. Do you guys prefer people asking questions
in the voicemails? Are you guys like it better whenever people kind of use it as a way to leave
comment or tell a story? Sorry, if you don't like people even questions, because that was
indeed a question. I guess I would say generally questions because it's then it's easy for us
to know how to respond to it. I suppose. I mean, most things end up being questions
in some way. Even if there's no question mark, it sort of prompts a discussion on a topic.
Just depends on how good the topic is. Some questions are stupid and we skip past them
immediately. Absolutely. Next voicemail is called comment three, two, one, go.
Also, some of the voicemails you guys get are weird and I don't go by the voicemails.
They seem more like they should be like Twitter DMs or emails. Like that person who was saying,
oh, can you guys check the subreddit? Like, do message them on Twitter? Or you know them?
Yeah. I'll leave a voicemail that you won't hear back from for like a week and a half.
You're right. You're not wrong. I understand the appeal of leaving a voicemail, but yeah,
I would say if you just want to like ask us something that you just want like some info about,
yeah, DMing on Twitter is probably an easier way to do it.
Yeah, Twitter. I don't get a lot of messages, so it's like guaranteed you'll be able to get
through to me. I'll see it. If you DM me on Twitter or Discord, I respond to almost every
message I get. Sometimes I miss one, but usually I'm pretty good about them. Next voicemail is called
Ben, Communists Want the Government to Do Stuff Saint, three, two, one, go.
A society in which workers own the means of production, thus abolishing social classes,
and a society which abandoned the commodity form. Anarchism, a political ideology which seeks to
establish an unhierarchical society in form of government. Anarchist or libertarian communism
could, for example, be achieved by seeking democratization of the workplace and subsequent
reduction or complete abolishment of the profit motive, abolishment of the state in favor of
democratic non-hierarchical modes of government, victory against all forms of bigotry and
decommodification of essential, most are all products produced in said society. Depending
on who you're talking to, markets can still play a role in such a society, albeit in highly
regulated forms. Alright, thanks for the Wikipedia article, buddy. Next voicemail is called Me Taking
a Shit Week One, three, two, one, go. God, I wish this were me. I still need to take one. Gross.
Oh, god. Oh, I'm not listening to that. This can't be real. This isn't real.
It's like I'm there. I can smell it.
I've stopped listening.
This reminds me of that scene in King of the Hill when Bobby is listening to a CD of Fart
Sounds and Hank takes any listens to it and he goes, oh, it says, Bobby, this isn't funny.
What that man has is a serious medical condition. That was explosive. You should see a doctor.
I don't think it's fake. I feel like it's easier to just put a phone near the toilet while you're
shitting. Maybe. I mean, maybe he just could tell that a bout of particularly explosive diarrhea
was coming and he was like, this is the one. I've been waiting for my opportunity.
I feel like this is sort of like you would need like a sensor bleeps on it.
You know, it's just like, gross. Nobody will need to listen to that.
I should be censored. I don't know. We didn't censor the guy peeing, but we've never censored
people peeing. In fact, it's a tradition. Peeing is like it doesn't sound grotesque,
and also peeing isn't as bad as shitting in terms of like hygiene.
Well, it's too late now. It's too late now. It made it in and there's nothing we can do.
Comments complain to Ben saying for not choosing to censor that.
There's simply no way that we could censor it. We would have to, I mean,
you know, every part connects to every other part of the pocket. We can't just cut one part.
It'll affect the pacing of the whole thing. We'll have to rewrite and restructure the whole
thing from the bottom up. It's impossible. We can't do it. This is like my impression of George
Lucas about the first prequel, by the way. Okay, next voicemail. This is the last voicemail.
It's called Happy Fourth of Gaeli. Three, two, one, go. Ben, were you bullied much in school? Because
you should be. No, not really. I thought of myself as a nerd, but
I mean, there were some, there were kind of jocks, I guess. There were like kids who were kind of
like badasses. There were kids who like, you know, liked rugged stuff, like ATVs and whatever,
and motorcycles. There was that kind of thing. And there were kids that played sports. I got
sometimes one or two kids. Sometimes I would get teased by someone or other, but like, I wasn't like
anyone's target or anything. I didn't have like a guy who regularly bullied me or anything. I was,
it was no, no, I was pretty fine. I was pretty A-okay. I was so popular.
Then you have really long hair. Got laid so often. Yeah, I could have, yeah, I had really long,
in high school, I had like hair down to my waist. Like, I was pretty weird and I probably should
have been bullied. I definitely was asking for it. Yeah, I had hair, I had fucking really,
really long hair. Did you wear a trench coat? Were you like the whole package? I didn't wear
like a black, like fucking, you know, school shooter trench coat, but I did, I did wear weird
coats a lot. I had a leather, I had like a red leather coat that was very, made a very squeaky
leather that I would wear sometimes. I loved that thing. It was so heavy. And then in senior
year of high school, I cut my long hair and I wore a suit to school every day.
What? Yeah, I don't know why I did that, but I did. I had a bunch of suits and I would wear
a different suit and tie every day. Did people say anything about that? Surely no one else was doing
that. No, nobody was doing that. Yeah, it was just my quirky thing. It's your new quirk. That was
my, it's pretty bizarre in hindsight knowing what I'm like, but yeah, believe it or not,
through most of senior year in high school, I wore like a suit, like a suit and tie and a button
down shirt and dress shoes and a belt and all the cuff links. I'm imagining like the way you look
is like super pristine, like a perfect vision of like the stereotypical American man on his
way to work. And then like fast forward, like, oh, what went wrong? It's been St. Now with the
peanut shells all over the place. I won best dressed in my high school yearbook. Even though I
wasn't really even a good dresser, like other kids dressed better than me, I just, because I
like made a thing out of it, I made like a gimmick out of it. And so people knew like, oh.
Is that guy wears the suit?
It probably should be that guy who wears a suit every day.
If I can report of the weak ass Ben St.
Fucking young Republican ass. Yeah, Ben St. in high school, Ben St. Cringe. That's your daily,
but and yet, and yet, no, I wasn't bullied that hard. No, people just thought it was funny.
I got away with too much. They were too easy on me.
Shit, that's the last voicemail. Thank God. That's it. That's it. Do we have any more
bullshit to spew before we sign off? I'm just going to check that Lord goes again.
It would have been so Pog if it hit 3k, but not yet. That'd be pretty Pog.
That'd be pretty Pog. I'm sure it will have hit 3k by the time this goes live. Yeah.
2995. Oh, for me, it looks like 4139 dollars.
But if I hover over the little dollar next to it, it shows the conversion so I can see.
Pledge to the Lord of Ghost Kickstarter. Everyone, link in the description.
Share it around. Share it on Facebook. Share it on TikTok. Share it on Discord. Share it on
Getter. Share it on Getter. Go at the president, 45th president of the United States, Donald J.
Trump on Getter and have him retweet the Lord of Ghost comic, please. Thank you.
The hell is Getter? Getter done?
I'm pretty sure it's a new Twitter alternative that is literally created just so that Donald
Trump can use it. I've been seeing some funny leftoids that I follow have been opening Getter
accounts under the names of people they hate, like Eve Barlow and who was the other one.
Spurt Magoo has been opening a bunch of funny tweets from that guy from that
band that quit because he got harassed because he supported it. It wasn't co-eating Cambria, no.
It was another name, a band with an and in it and the guy was like pro Andy No and everyone
hated him for it and so we quit the band. Band. Quit. Andy. No. Mumford and Sons. The guy from
Mumford and Sons. Winston Marshall from Mumford and Sons. Oh, he's 33. He's the same age as me.
Oh, wow. Yeah. Guess he's the son. He sucks. Fuck that guy. Mumford and Sons was all over the place
for like a year. They were like, oh, they're so big. And I was like, it's sort of all right.
I'm sure I've heard it from them again. I'm sure I've heard it, but I couldn't I couldn't name you
a Mumford and Sons song. No, they're just sort of like quirky to be acoustic core,
like foot stomping, folky sort of songs. I want to be the lead singer of a folk band.
I really want to do that, but I don't want to actually make any music because I'm not good at
it. I just want to sing. I just want to be a singer. If anyone wants to start a folk band and just
let me be lead singer and not make me do anything else for it, then hit me up, please. Someone else
writes the lyrics. The lyrics are I stinky. My diaper. No, you have to sing it. I signed a contract.
I signed a conservatorship. I have to do it. My life is not my own anymore. Fuck. Yeah, I'll do it.
Fuck it. Yeah, I'll go up on stage and just sing and just croon out a song about how I pooped in my
pants. The ladies will appreciate the confidence. It's not like a blue song. It's like I pooped
in my pants and I stank so bad. It made me cry. It stank so bad that my dog died.
Yeah, so it's a perfect blue song concept.
Okay, well, that's all I got. That's all I got for today.
Okay, I guess that's it. Patreon.com slash the procrastinators to get bonus episodes,
many, many bonus episodes, and you can get on the Minecraft. You can get on the Minecraft,
you can come in and see my cool wizards tower. It's a work in progress, but it looks really cool.
I really like it. I have a lot of fun building. Okay, that's it. Thank you and good night.
Good night.