Hello, welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. It is January 24th, 2021, and it's the new episode.
I'm Ben Saint, and also there's Gibbontake. It's been one week since the last PCP.
I lost my watch at a party once. An hour later, I saw some guy stepping on it while he was sexually
harassing a woman. Infuriated, I went up to him, punched him, and broke his nose. Nobody does that
to a woman, not on my watch. YouTube.com slash Gamers Tavern Show. Tell your friends even if
they're imaginary. I didn't see that punchline coming, so I'll give you that one. I think I heard
that one before. I don't know where. Probably one of my videos. Maybe. Don't tell me you reuse
material. I would never do that. The greatest comedians tell a joke one time ever and then throw
it out and never repeat it under any circumstances. That's what the professionals do. I've been watching
these videos of Stuart Lee, this comedian. He's a British comedian and he's like,
I'd never heard of him before because he hates the whole TV scene. He just likes doing shows,
which means he's better because he's not stupid and lame and on TV and all that shit.
So what does he do? He sells DVDs of his clubs, clubs and stadiums and stuff. He's quite popular,
but he doesn't do the TV circuit of being on panel shows and whatever.
But I see sometimes, I see a bit of his where it's like, I know this bit. I've watched this bit in a
different video, in a different DVD special. I've seen this bit before. I think he sucks now. I don't
like him and in fact, I'm going to unsubscribe to this random YouTuber who isn't him.
Absolutely. So he reuses material too?
Yeah. When I hear a band play a song a second time, I'm like, that's it. You guys are hacks.
You guys are over. How can you reuse material? This is blatant. You're literally plagiarizing
yourself. Yeah. When I listen to an album, I'm like, I've listened to this part before.
Skips to the new part. Skips to the new part. It's like each song is like a piece of thin ice
over a lake and you can skate on it like only so many times before it cracks and it's no longer
usable. You have to skate on other songs. Yeah. I need to get some new material because...
I have many people are saying this. I need to get new material because this cotton shirt just
isn't working out for me. I suggest Rayon. Big Rayon fan. Underrated. Underrated textile there.
Somebody messaged me after last week's episode to ask me like, hey, I loved your font recommendations.
Do you have any more fonts you recommend? And I was like, no. I named all the good ones.
You mean you were still doing that? There are no more. Because I think you were recommending
fonts on one of the last episodes I was on. I think we got a voicemail where someone was like
very pointedly asking about like, what are you guys favorite fonts? So is this going to be like
the circumcision thing? No. Font corner. I don't know. I don't think font
choice. I don't think things like kerning are like as emotionally charged as the circumcision
debate. Well, I don't know. Some people get pretty serious about fonts. What are the different types
of like, there's like the ones where the Times New Roman where the like a T has little bits on the
end of it. And then there's one's Serif and then non-Serif. Serif and Sans Serif where Comic Sans
gets its name. Yeah. Like where'd you fall on the Serif Sans Serif debate? Oh, I'm a big Serif guy.
Big Serif energy over here. I always liked that as well. When it came to like drawing,
like if there was like a drawing I was doing and it involved letters, I would always do the fanciest
possible because then it would be like fancier. I mean, as many bells and whistles as possible.
If you're handwriting and you add Serifs, like that means you, that means you really gave a
shit. Like you were like, how can I up the presentation? Speaking of, oh my god, you know
what would be, okay, I actually received a handwritten letter from Christine Weston Chandler.
Whoa, that's a big deal. This is, okay, this is funny. I, okay, I mentioned in the PCP chat,
Gabe, I think you saw that like, okay, on, on Twitter, in Twitter DMs, Chris messaged me to say
like, hey, I bought this crystal. It's a piece of blue hemi-morphite from Arizona, basically
because like, oh, it's just like slime podrans from the Endless War, right? Yeah. And she literally
fucking sent me the podrans. She sent me the piece of hemi-morphite. It's sitting on my,
I guess I should probably post a picture of it.
Dude, you're literally pen pals.
I guess so. So I told, I told Chris like, cool, if you send me that, I'll send you like some
pins and a slime coin. So I got to get that in the mail to her. But, but she wrote me a letter
and I actually haven't read the letter yet. So I guess I should, I think I'll just read it now.
Yeah, why not? Here it is.
To Ben saying, feel free to read on your next live stream or whatever. So I guess that's this.
Dear Ben, wait a minute, sorry, I'm mixed up because Christine is not Christine. Christine
is actually Sonichu right now. Sonichu is actually inhabiting the body of Christine while I suppose
Christine is in C197. When you got to get all the letters. So this is actually a letter from Sonichu.
So this is Sonichu's actual handwriting you have. Like this is literally, yes, I literally,
I literally holding in my hand a letter from Sonichu, of the Sonichu comic book fame.
What a world, am I right? That's quite an artifact you've got there.
It is. Dear Ben, here is a lovely chunk of hemimorphite, aka a podron of slime. Obviously genuine.
Purchase from the minerals and mystics, formerly crystal connection, of Charlottesville, Virginia,
mine from Arizona, in the vicinity of Nlacocam. And Christine has personally verified it as
1218's counterpart of a podron of slime. This podron has been near this body for a few days
so it is energized and blessed. Oh, it's been energized by Christine's body.
Eminem also gave me a bit of a bit of stickum and a pedestal. Oh, okay. It's the thing that it's
like sitting on. Eminem also gave me a bit of stickum and a pedestal, which I felt would be
better off for and with you. You may even put your name on it. Ben quote, Ben Saints podron
or what you like. Enjoy it and stay safe and well. Sonichu, January 18th, 2021. And Sonichu is
written in a scribbly sort of lightning bolt kind of a script there. So bear it into your face.
Now you're protected from COVID now.
Well, in slime and punishment, in Christine's side pages, images of it,
Chris Chan Sonichu takes the slime podron and I guess energizes it and gives it back to phantom
horn. And this is in the beta timeline. And in the beta timeline, phantom form is given this
energized podron and it causes him to grow a sort of ethereal quote unquote phantom unicorn horn
that he can use like some approximation of real unicorn magic through and in and in the image,
when Chris when Chris Chan is giving the podron back to phantom horn, the podron is blue, like
it's very clearly blue. So I was like, okay, she charged it up with blue energy, right? Because
recently she posted pictures of Sonichu and Chris Chan. But they since they've switched bodies,
they have like an aura energy around them. So Chris Chan's body has this yellow energy aura,
because it's got Sonichu in it. And Sonichu's got this blue energy aura, because it's got
Christine in it. So it's like, okay, yeah, she put her fucking aura energy into the crystal.
So it's blue, of course. But then I reply to her like, oh, just like the the blue podron. And
she's like, um, actually, Christine simply use the wrong marker to color it. Make of that what
you will. And I'm like, oh, even Christine makes a mistake. So that was just a mistake.
So that's just a mistake, even though it just makes way more sense for the podron to be blue.
Okay, she said like, make of it what you will. So I'm just going to assume that yes, yes, it did
make the podron blue, because I literally had the pin manufacturers like manufacture a small
quantity of like alternate color blue podrons. So I just feel silly if that if that were a waste
of time. So I had like, I had like, I literally forgot that I got that until just now.
And that's pretty cool. You know, pretty, pretty cool. I guess maybe I'll hang that up.
Maybe I'll tuck that in behind the, you know, the page of liquid Sonichu being or liquid Chris
being reborn in the fucking hell womb or whatever the one I have on my wall. So I guess you two are
on good terms again, because I remember a while back, there was like a bit of an issue
or something. She was, yeah, she she was, she was mad at me merely for reporting the facts,
which is that in Lockecom did in fact go to war with quick bill. Yeah. And that the casualty,
the casualties were immense. But Christine refused to acknowledge it. And I guess that's just the
quick bill party line is to just not, not admit that any of that happened, but it did. You know,
I was there. I posted pictures, there was video evidence. There was a whole, there was a whole
body of work done about it in the, in the RFCK server for the contest, the quick, the war on
quick bill contest. So like it's, it's, it's Canon. I mean, it's indisputable. A whole body of work
of all the dead bodies, right? Yes, that's right. There are, there are stats too. There are, there
are body counts. Astronomically high ones, of course. Oh, that's, that's fine. You should,
you know what, if you're sending the, the coin and stuff, you should do a handwritten letter back
and actually like get a rapport going with Sonichu.
Um, you know, I, I had arranged like a sheet, like a little piece, like an image that would
explain like what each of the pins mean, like what, what they are images of. And then my
fucking printer broke. So like I couldn't print it. So I might just like send her that image when
she gets it so she can see it or whatever. Cause like she's not going to know what like
goo girls limited is. For instance. She might be a bigger fan than you think.
I don't. You know what? Maybe you're right. I choose to believe that you're right. You know what?
You know what? I wasn't kind of a shitty mood, but that, that really, that really perked me up.
I'm feeling chipper now. You're feeling chipper and you're not even chipped from shipping downs.
Die. Die, Gamers Tavern. Die. Oh, uh, by the way, I, um, want to mention something on here.
Uh, you can, uh, you, you can both call me, uh, Krono with a K instead of Gamers Tavern,
unless you want to continue. Okay. Gamers Tavern is up to you.
Krono? Sure. Yeah. Uh, Krono is a real name, I guess. Yeah, you've mentioned that before. I just
was in the habit. I was just in the habit of calling you Gamers Tavern, like I was in the habit
of calling Gib Hippo. Right. Um, that's a, okay. Krono, Krono it is. I mentioned that off the air,
I think one time, but I want to take the opportunity to mention it on the air. So, uh,
everybody knows, I guess a couple of thousand people might listen to this.
That's a, an old username I used to use back in, I think I first used it in 2001.
So I haven't, I haven't used it much lately, but I'm thinking of bringing it back, you know,
because, uh, embrace tradition and reject modernity. That's right. The, the, the
the extremely modern Gamers Tavern brand. It's not old, old, old, good, new, bad. It is. It is
bad. So just keep as far back as you possibly can. But that's been my, my philosophy for pretty
much my entire life. Um, man, I've been, um, okay. Let me tell, I've been, I've been really
struggling with Noita. Noita is so fucking hard. And then I, I guess Vosh just beat it. Like, I
haven't, I haven't, I haven't watched Vosh in a while. I didn't know that he or anyone was playing
Noita, but I just see a, I see a, he, I just happened to see a tweet from him that's like,
I'm really proud of my first Noita win. And it made me really mad. It made me really mad
that Vosh beat Noita before I did. Do you care to elaborate on what this is for anyone who doesn't
know? No, no, no, it's a, it's a roguelite or roguelike. I don't know. Yeah. One of them.
Yeah. You jump into a game.
I had a really good, I had Craig fucking die, Craig. You piece of shit. I had a really good
game like earlier today, where I had like a pretty good synergy going where I had, I managed to get
a buff that would like turn a project, when you shot a projectile, it would make the projectiles
shoot fireballs out to the left and right. And I put that on a wand that would shoot a like bouncy
projectile. So the projectile would go out and it would bounce. And so it would like persist for
a while bouncing around. And even after it was bouncing, it would still just keep shooting
fireballs that like, um, it was pretty fucking, it was, it was, that was pretty fucking good.
It didn't actually do that much damage, but it was like a lot of bang for your buck.
What an important thing is that it looked cool, right?
Uh, though, I mean, the cool looking ones just literally just kill you when you use them.
They just like fucking explode and you die. I had, I found one wand that had a spell on it
that I'd never seen before. And the spell was like, turns everything around you into blood.
And I used it and it literally just turned my body into blood and I died. My whole body was just
became blood. So it's like, I don't know exactly what these things are going to do.
No, you don't really know what the spells do until you use them.
They like randomly generated effects like they can stack and mix in interesting ways.
The spells are, there's a pre, there is a particular list of spells.
But you will, you find wands that have slots and the slots will have like
semi random spells in the slots and the slots, some, some wands are like randomized. Like you'll,
you'll shoot them and it will like pick a random slot to fire a spell from.
But some, some wands are non shuffle, which means that the spells progress in a linear fashion.
They go slot one, slot two, slot three, slot four. And so you can build things. So like,
you could maybe put a like modifier in the first slot that's like, okay, cast the next two spells.
But then, you know, and then maybe you put a spell, but then in the second spell that that
double slot cast is going to cast, you put like another modifier that's like, okay,
that one make it like a double branch spell. And then so that in that second pathway actually
branches out into two more spells. So you can build these like, these like logic
machines that like do like a chain of spells that all modify each other.
So spell slots is like a material, right?
Um, yeah, kind of. Yeah, yeah, more or less. But like the spells are on the wands. So like,
you're not you, you don't have mana that you cast spells with like the individual wands have like
a mana pool and like a mana regeneration rate. And like that affects like, like you might have
a wand that has like a really good fire rate and like, and stuff. And you put like a spell on it
and you're like machine gun. But if it's got like low mana or low regeneration rate, you like,
you'll run out and you won't actually be that useful, you know? So you kind of have to find
wands that work well. It's super fucking interesting. And it's so hard. I think I made it,
I think last night I had like one of my best runs yet. I made it to you start in the mines,
and then you go, no, no, you start in like the cab, the mines, and then you go to like the deeper
mines. And then you go to like this ice layer, and then there's a jungle layer. No, no, and then
there's like a vault, and then there's a jungle layer, and then there's like a second vault,
and I made it to that like the like second vault with all this high tech shit in it.
And I was like, this is only like a second time ever I've made it there. It was it was my best
run ever. It was pretty good. But I don't think I was even anywhere close to the end.
And it's very, very challenging. It's very challenging video game video game. Yes. The most
the most fun thing in Noida, in my opinion, is in the second level, the like the deeper mines
is if you get a spell that has the ability to like clear dirt or clear, um, yeah, like clear
materials out, and you just go around there and you look for like pockets of gold that
are buried in like the stone in the mines, and you can just like dig to them and just like
pick up the gold, and you just like go around and like collect as much gold as you can. So you
have a lot of money so that you can like buy better spells and like the in between zone like a
minecraft, right? Almost as if you are some kind of the minecraft. Yes. Dude, I've been playing
minecraft, and I've been playing minecraft as well as minecraft. Have you ever heard of
ever heard of X's adventures in minecraft? He was a let's play. Is X a person? X was his name.
I don't think his channel, his channel wasn't called that, but he is. I've heard of X's adventures
of whatever I've heard of Poo's adventures of. Yes, he's not winning the poo, unfortunately.
But he was like one of the first minecraft let's players that didn't take off
in like a gigantic way, but he's like beloved because it's like kind of the best when it was
new. You know, he was discovering the game and he was like learning and everyone else was like
learning with him, and so it was like a magical let's play, and it was really well produced.
He was a very thoughtful gamer rather than just screaming and jumping at stuff. He crafts
his let's play like it's a show that it's got narrative stakes, even though he is just recording
himself playing a game and he cuts it off at specific. It's just very well nicely made,
and he's been gone for 10 years. He has stopped doing minecraft 10 years ago, and people have
always wanted him to come back because I think the first playthrough, it got quite far, but then
he just sort of got bored because he died and it was far away and he lost a lot of stuff,
and he tried to look for it. That was just it? Yeah, I think it was before Beds. I think it was
before you could set your spawn point, so he was on a very, very long far away adventure and he
died and he lost everything. Just like real life? Yes, except he didn't in real life, he don't come
back. So real life is better? I suppose, if you die and lose all your stuff in real life
and you come back and you start again, you're like, I don't want to even think about that.
So this guy crafts his let's plays like that minecraft thing, right?
Oh yeah, he crafts it like a mine. He crafts it like a mine. Anyway, anyway,
he is cool and he's been gone for 10 years. He comes back very recently with Minecraft
let's play hardcore mode and he's doing it the same way as always and he was never like
a big speedrunner type gamer. He's always been sort of slow and methodical and a little bit
autistic in the way that he conducts his like, I noticed watching him, he's like,
he has to have his station, which always has like the furnace in a specific place
compared to where the crafting table is and the chest and then he like digs and it's very,
I don't know, soothing to watch. And I've been getting back into him
playing the game 10 years super nostalgic Minecraft let's play makes me want to play
Minecraft, even though at the time I was in a Minecraft binge, I was talking about Minecraft
not so long ago, doing a hardcore mode. Minecraft is so fucking good. I can't even imagine people
playing us a different game. It's so good. No, it is just Minecraft. No, it is just Minecraft
only instead of only each each individual pixels its own block. So it's better because it's more
granular, more blocks is more better. I guess that's that's more more blocks than Terraria then
because Terraria is blocks still have Terraria has multiple pixels in them.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, much better, much better. It's much better than Terraria and much better.
Because I mean, think about it, right? Noida is only two dimensional. So, you know, theoretically,
the blocks, the small the already smaller and more granular blocks are only two dimensional. So
actually in a in a hypothetical 3d space, you could fit infinite amounts of them, right,
because they're infinitesimally small slivers of a three dimensional area. So there's actually
like infinitely better video game. Oh, yeah, that sounds like pretty solid logic. When they're not
Minecraft, I don't know. I think I think most games suck. It's fine. Some some people just like
less blocks. Some people just like fewer blocks. Some people are stupid. Yeah, good point. That's
okay. That's okay. You know what? Son, live and learn some some people live and learn.
Oh, see, Craig finally made it. Fuck you, Craig. Yeah, piece of shit. Well, I did upload a new video
recently. We mentioned that before. Did you crafted your own YouTube video? Yeah, exactly. Dude.
Oh, it all comes back to Minecraft. Everything always comes back to Minecraft.
Sure does. So what's the video? Your video was Mega Man zero four ending. You're like it was a
it was a speak video. It wasn't a let's play. Yeah, it's something new that I've never done before.
I'm not sure if it counts as an analysis video or not. I think it sort of does. It's like a mini
video essay sort of thing. Here is why I like this thing. Yeah, I wrote a script for it and I
recorded it and it was pretty easy to make because I didn't have to tell any jokes. That's the easiest.
That's the easiest. It's easy not to have to tell jokes, you know, it's a weight off my shoulders,
but I guess it's maybe good or maybe not. I'm not even sure if I want to promote it because I
don't know if it's good. I watched it. I kind of liked it. I'd never heard of Mega Man zero.
What? I've heard of Mega Man zero. I've never played. I mean, never played any other. I mean,
I feel like they'll even played Mega Man one. Am I crazy or did didn't you talk about this video
like last time you were on? No, because the last time I was on the video didn't exist.
Or did you just talk about the ending to Mega Man X4, but not this video? Yeah, maybe I talked
about the ending. The last time I think we were in a stream that wasn't on the PCP.
Oh, that might have been it. Yeah, that might have been it. I really liked the ending to Mega Man
zero four. So I got the idea of making a video explaining why I like it. And I uploaded two
videos, one of just the ending by itself and the other one of me talking about the ending.
Yeah, okay. Okay, I see. Mega Man zero is a fucking cool. I don't know. It's like
Mega Man. Okay, Mega Man X is more of like a spiritual sequel to Mega Man. It has like some
lore connections, but it's like not explicit. And it's sort of like up to you to decide what
the relationship is there. Mega Man zero is like a, it's like a direct sequel to Mega Man X. It's
almost just like, I guess it's not just like a straight continuation because Mega Man X did
continue. Mega Man zero is canonically just like the future of Mega Man X. Like super future, right?
Like, like, every super humanity is not even slightly the same as it was in Mega Man one.
I don't think there are any humans left in Mega Man. There are cyborgs or something.
There are humans in Mega Man zero. The plot of Mega Man zero is that the humans hated the
reploids and they wanted to get rid of all of them. So they found a society called Neo Arcadia
and they're hunting down reploids. Cool fucking name. God, the aesthetics of Mega Man zero is
a fucking cool. Yeah, it is pretty cool. So in the beginning, you joined the resistance group.
Yeah. And in the resistance group, you're actually fighting against the humans to
defend the reploids or the robots. Right. Right. Because the humans are actually
the bad guys. Because the reploids are basically just people. The reploids are just like most people
in this world, right? The reploids are just robotic versions of humans, I guess. Or rather,
they're robots that have free will. I don't know if I ever mentioned this, but there was a,
okay, me and, me and Munchy and Kazzy one time went to, because their school had a like comic
book creators club. And Munchy told me like, this is bad. He was like, I went to this club
and it sucked. And I was like, that's funny. Let's go. So we went to a meeting. We went to a meeting
of this kind of this like these college kids who were all like talking about their comic ideas.
And it was very much like it was it was a lot of most of the meeting was like basically
people describing their like going around the table like describing their OCs and all these
cool ideas they have for their comic that they haven't started making it. But they will.
I guess he's right. That does sound pretty bad. Yeah. It's, well, the funniest part.
And this was this was not the worst part, but it was probably the funniest. There was one guy
who is describing like the plot of like the comic series that he wants to make.
And he is like, okay, so it's set in the future. And you know, this technology is developed to
create this race of robots that have free will. And you know, there's tension between the sentient
robots and the humans. And some of those sentient robots decide that they're like robot supremacists
and they break off and they form like sort of a sort of a team of like renegades, you might call
them, you know, there's like a group that is like anti human. And then there's like, and then like
the protagonist is like, you know, a pro he's like a pro human, like he fights on behalf of the humans
to defend against these evil robots. And he's literally just describing the plot of Mega Man X.
And, and he's sitting there describing this, he's wearing a Mega Man X shirt. Like it's on his shirt
as he's describing it. And like, I'm just not gonna get we'll figure it out. Well, well, no,
I he redeemed himself a little bit because at the end, he he like he goes, he talks about all
this stuff. And then he's like, so you know, it's a lot like Mega Man X, like it's heavily
inspired by Mega Man X. Like, it's very simple to be obvious. So he like, he completely owned it,
which I respect. It's basically the same exact thing, except for one tiny detail that's different.
Yeah, basically, like, I know the feeling of like, like, I think sometimes like, ah, yeah,
I'm going to make this this thing. And it's it's basically like, exactly like home stuck, except
I wrote it. Yeah, yeah, basically, I can't think of anything I can't think of anything like it
would have in it. I just want to invent Riska myself.
Well, that's a noble endeavor.
Um, try to think if there was any other funny shit that happened.
No, that was the funniest part. It was I don't know. It was a bunch of crap.
But yeah, the Mega Man Zero series and X series are pretty cool. The stories of them are pretty cool.
But Mega Man Zero's story, I think is probably better and more fleshed out than X series.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, zero has zero is a little bit more plot centric. I think the X series,
you can play through Mega Man X and like almost not even notice that a plot is happening.
Yeah, the X series has pretty good lore, but there's not much plot to it.
Yeah, but the Mega Man Zero series has lore and plot.
It's very much like, okay, like I'm the fact that like, like the fact that it's called like
Neo Arcadia and like, I don't know, they talk about like this, like,
the place where like the humans like are like ruling from it has this sort of like weird like
religious aesthetic to it. Like it's like some kind of Holy Land or whatever.
Yeah, definitely. And like,
If you get an S rank in Mega Man Zero, they call you the Redeemer.
So fucking cool. I have such a sucker for that shit. The final when spoiler, big spoilers,
but when you like, okay, so like X is the leader of these evil humans who are like anti-reploids.
Yeah, but it's not actually X. It's X's body, but the like X's actual mind now exists in the form
of like a cyber elf, which is the sort of like disembodied like program that is sort of like a
spirit or whatever. And you can use cyber elves to like enhance your abilities and stuff in the game.
But like the real X is a cyber elf, but his but X's body is controlled by some new AI who thinks
he's the real X, but he's this fucking like a like reploid genocide fucking monster.
And when you fight him at the end of the first Mega Man Zero, he turns into this giant fucking
like robot like angel wing creature and just is like fucking blah. Yeah, it's pretty great.
It's so good. The whole X series is constantly foreshadowing the big battle between X and zero,
which happens a couple of times in X series, but you can say the climax is in the Mega Man Zero
series when zero kills copy X. It's got it's got this whole thing where like these four the four
like guardians what is like Harpuya the grew the wind guy Leviathan the water girl shadow the ninja
And I think the fire guy is Fenrir, right? Fire guy Fenrir. Yeah. Yeah. They're like these
they're these like heroes of justice that like defend they like they think they're the good guys
and then like over I think it's over the course of the first game they learned that like no X is
the leader of like this evil fucking empire or whatever we're the bad guys and they all you
know become redeemed. But it's interesting because what a fucking game the New Arcadia is
seen as like the utopian city for humans but they their X is killing off all the reploids and
you're defending them and fighting against that. But it's just kind of weird because in the X
series you're defending the humans against the reploids but in the zero series it's reversed.
Yeah, because it's like um yeah because like if you imagine like the historical timeline like X
was known like in the X games he fights against the evil reploids because these maverick reploids
are more powerful than humans and they're they're like it's like um it's like Magneto in the X
men they're like well you know fuck the humans right like we're better than them. But then like
by the time I guess reploid technology was so successful that by the time Mega Man Zero happens
like reploids are they're they're like indistinguishable from people but so I guess like
because you know because this new X that thinks he's the old X is like yeah I fight the reploids
reploids bad so you know persecute them even though like now the tables have turned and like now the
reploids are the underdog sort of sort of you know except for the good reploids that like work for me
my fucking four like elemental champions or whatever and also me because I'm special because
I'm because I'm the hero was he called himself he calls himself like the fucking hero of legend he
has some like I'm I'm like the show I think he calls himself like the chosen one or something
because he thinks like yeah X is this hero from history like he's the I'm the greatest fucking
reploid that ever lived like I saved the human race I can do no wrong. Yeah it's something like that
it's uh it's pretty freaking cool when you think about it um there's a lot of I'm getting I'm getting
fucking hype I'm getting excited over here I have a remembering I've never played really any Mega Man
except what the first one that I bought on the Wii store um and I've I've always been curious
because I know there's loads of spin-off series and I'm like looking at the timeline to see if
like it's a jumbled mess like Zelda but it seems to be just in order like Mega Man series is like
20 xx Mega Man x is 21 xx so that's yeah yeah it's pretty yeah because I mean later like
Mega Man zx uh century after the zero series Mega Man the legend several thousand years later
just keeps going whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa mega man legends is after zx yeah apparently
but that's what the whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa what the fuck what the fuck is this
link link let me scroll uh yeah it's just it's just the um you see the that doesn't make any
fucking sense I'm I'm looking at it but it makes this is unacceptable makes sense if you're a big
Mega Man fan nerd like I am but um basically okay this is not this is not canon yeah it might not
be canon I'm not sure if it is canon or not but it's theorized by the fans that Mega Man legends
takes place after uh zx because in zx humans and reploids start to become almost the same
and humans start incorporating like cybernetic uh implants into themselves and in Mega Man
legends um I think in legends it's determined or confirmed that all the humans are basically
reploids by that point oh god okay but I thought that I thought that the Mega Man from Mega Man
legends just is original Mega Man from the Mega Man games just like in 3d uh no he's a he's a
different character he's uh I forget is I mean they're both called Mega Man whereas like Mega Man
X is called X well the um so I just assumed yeah but the one in legends actually his name is
Volnott or something like that or his last name is Volnott I think um my memories where's all the
like strategy like the small like um turn-based whatever games are they what do you mean the
rpgs uh the battle network series and oh battle network battle network's gotta be somewhere else
battle network's gotta be its own and that's just separate timeline timeline I don't know where
it no is it separate I would I would hope that it figures somewhere on the time I was really just
looking at like the beginning and then I was scrolling down to look at the specifics but this
is like how it's laid out at the top and I'm like okay so the series follow on like chronologically
yeah for the most part uh but then there's no mention of the uh I guess this is Mega Man
timeline classic oh god wait I'm looking at the I'm looking at the zero timeline which is that
that's just the image at the top I didn't really look at that yeah that's not the whole thing that's
just that's just between x and zero yeah but uh the battle network series takes place on its own
timeline or universe it's not related to uh the main timeline wait oh wait this is a comprehensive
timeline for classic mega man mega man x mega man zero mega all of these series occur in a timeline
that deviates from the timeline seen in the mega man battle network and mega man star force series
which are canon to one another but not the other series yeah the wait what was that second one
um you mean star force on something wrong uh yeah mega man star force series star force is a
the spiritual successor to battle network it takes place like I think a hundred or two hundred years
after battle network so it is a timeline that deviates so if if now I gotta look into this I
love I love like timelines I'm probably never gonna play any of these games I like figuring out
but the idea is that the main mega man's timeline is when robotics became the big popular thing but
the battle network timeline is if robotics didn't take off and instead like the internet became the
big thing so they they go into the web and they do battle network they do battles in online yeah
basically they they they they pull on each other digitally yeah I'm not um I'm not too big of a fan
of the battle network series but uh they're pretty okay if you like rpgs
series set in a parallel universe from the original meg man series where the internet has
become integrated with almost every piece of electronic equipment in existence from tv's to ovens
yeah so the what the oven gets like infected so it's just the real world yeah the oven gets
infected well I guess that is a virus and then it starts messing up your house and burning down
your house and stuff it's like I made a wooden television I made it like to combat the internet
I made a wooden uh something or other it doesn't doesn't matter and then um the main character
his name is lan as in local area network and um he jacks into a device with his little pda thing
he jacks into his little pp yeah that's what they call it in the games you you jack in and you jack out
and uh oh there's anime and manga yeah the battle network series was pretty popular and it had its
own anime and I guess it had a manga I didn't know that the mega man nt warrior manga authored by
what really bugs me what bugs me about this timeline is that I can't actually see any references
in mega man legends to like to like zero and zx like if there was any of that I would believe it
yeah I'd be willing to give it but like it's just fan I don't actually see anything it's uh I don't
think it's ever been confirmed to be canon that legends is related to um the timeline I would I
would need to I would need to be a list of like oh you know here in in this like room you can see
like an image that like refers to something that happened I mean legends never even acknowledges
the existence of zero I don't know this this just seems like some dumb but there there's a lot of
fan theories and fan canon stuff and um you know the the lore of mega man is pretty interesting you
could probably do a lecture on it it just it just that's true that I'm sure is true actually actually
100 true I'm just saying this just seems like a big like what if like oh what if legends takes
place in the future after zx it could you can't prove it doesn't and like yeah you're right you're
right it hasn't been confirmed um there's like little implications or nudges but it hasn't been
actually confirmed to be canon it's um I mean I'm looking for implications and I'm not really
I found a forum thread tell me if this makes sense in the x series a space station called
Elysium is being built roughly in the year 50 xx and the master is at least 3000 years old when
he dies before the events of mega man legends meaning that 80 xx is the earliest the series could
happen wait so x so in x there's a space station called Elysium yeah and I assume Elysium is like
an Elysium is or like something like that and Elysium is also in let in the legends okay okay
yeah it's um if there's a uh there's little hints like that but this still isn't a hard
confirmation that that's what I was looking for that's what I was looking for okay so
it's kind of like uh I mean I think there's nothing on the on the other hand only like little
on the other hand from other games I mean if them if if legends is like far future from
the original mega man then like they're not the same person but they had just have the same name
like it could just be a different thing that's also called Elysium like how mega man is just
also called mega man true but was there Elysium was there an Elysium in the original mega man ever
mentioned uh no it was the space station that was being built in the original mega man I don't think
so was the space station being uh mentioned in mega man x uh being named after an already
existing Elysium from legends who knows who knows which way around it goes uh oh yeah I honestly I
think that probably is true because like legends because like mega man x kept going even as like
the legends series was starting so like I would believe that like people making like later x games
might just name things after things in like the early legends game I think there's only like two
or three legends games there's only two and they were both but yeah yes one
yeah so yeah they they like the the the inspiration could have gone either well the
the x series was originally supposed to end at x5 and then Capcom made uh x6 without Inafune's
knowledge and he was quite upset about it when he found out that they made a mega man game behind
his back yeah it would be too this this could be a interesting video if if someone knew all the
stuff and they would you know would feel like you know like analyzing the truth coming down to the
I mean mega man doesn't have like kingdom hearts level convoluted lore but like there's so many
games that like there is a lot of it yeah like a lot of stuff has happened but a lot of the stuff
in games it doesn't really matter you know like a lot of it is pretty self-contained
that's just what they want you to think yeah but uh sometimes the most interesting uh stuff about
the lore is the fan theories as opposed to what is canon like um yeah there's a big fan theory about
Dr. Wiley's involvement in the x series and whether he was secretly controlling sigma or something
yeah and um yeah sure I mean this is a I've I think I've heard something about it but it's
it's not like I feel like there are some references to Wiley in x oh yeah there's there's definitely
some um like in um a mega man x4 uh spoilers uh the first cutscene when you play as zero uh it
clearly shows uh that Dr. Wiley made zero oh okay yeah yeah yeah that's right that's right
so like that's like fully canon like yes this is the future of the other game and then when you
get to sigma as zero there's another anime cutscene where it shows that uh zero was the first maverick
and he infected uh sigma and that's how sigma became okay I thought was that not the story from
the beginning I kind of thought that that was just like established in mega man x that like yeah
zero was the first maverick and he but he like got unmavericked maybe not maybe I don't think so
because in x4 they make it out to be like a huge revelation like it's a big plot twist maybe maybe
I just read that somewhere and then just like read that into the game when I was playing x because
as a kid I only play the original x like I played x2 and x3 a little bit however um this is foreshadowed
in x at the end of x2 when you kill sigma his final words or something like um zero you were one of
wily's last known he didn't he doesn't say why he said zero you were one of the doctor's last
creations why did you betray me or something like that so he he doesn't say who the doctor is kind
of implies that sigma is also made by yeah well sigma is not made by uh by wily he's made by dr
kane oh right right this is kind of weird but dr kane is an archaeologist and he discovered
x's uh body in a capsule and then he copies x's design and makes a bunch of reploids so he made
sigma I knew that so what I don't get is how does an archaeologist like learn how to build a robot
you know that's well he just copied the I mean he he didn't do it himself he just like
he found dr lights design yeah but dr lights design was like plagiarized it was the most
sophisticated robot design at the time and he just somehow copies it and and modifies it
it's like you have to know a thing or two about robotics to do that maybe he I mean maybe he well
you know he's probably just like Elon musk he doesn't actually do anything he just like hires a
bunch of engineers to like do it that's possible I never consider that possibility never thought
about it so everyone so everyone just assumes oh yeah dr dr kane did it you know it's his it's
his baby or whatever sigma more like sigma balls we're like leg good yeah okay yeah yeah you were
you were going there you went there mm-hmm I went there I'm not afraid snap snap snap
bass man I fucking hate video games yeah they're pretty bad awful oh dude speaking of video games
I've been replaying um phoenix right ace attorney trials and tribulations the third in the in the
first three games I played the first ace attorney game and I thought it was dumb I thought it was
bad well you're dumb instead because actually I mean I will say I will say that I think the second
and third games are much better with the with the um when it comes to like things coming out of nowhere
to save the protagonist that doesn't happen quite so often I remember like replaying the first game
it's like oh no there's absolutely nothing I can do then suddenly out of nowhere like the one piece
of evidence you need like you had no hand and you're getting that evidence for the case it just
sort of appears and then you can complete it and it's like okay that's just manufactured like
manufactured uh what's the word tension tension because like there's no there's no like ticking
clock you don't know that the thing you need is on its way but it might be late you just
think there's nothing gonna happen because there's nothing and then it's there were out of its house
but the second and third games are so fucking good I did um I guess you need to play you need to play
the third game to see Godot Godot is like the coolest guy in the world I did beat uh I think
all the ones in a ds except for I think the last one which was kind of like a weird action adventure
uh type of thing there's one where you walk around I didn't play that oh that's that's
those are miles edge worth investigations I think yeah that's uh I think the only one for the ds I
did not play such this is such nerd shit what's what's you just talk about mega man timeline
shit for ages I don't know mega man's cool mega man's about the horrors of war yeah Phoenix
right about the horrors of the law I mean this is just about this is just about the legal system
this is about being a fucking suit look I'm just saying there's a there's a lady called friend
Franziska von karma and she has a whip and she whips people and she's got a soft inner side
and it's so much my favorite type of character that I just can't help but love the whole game
it's that's uh that's anime stuff if you're into anime stuff
it's kind of like no no thank you to anime stuff it's not really like the way it looks the sprite
work is just good it looks like chunky and like more westernized than normal anime the the later
games like Apollo justice and some some other ones that I haven't played um that are built for the ds
where they they up the anime a little too much this is what happened to fire emblem as well I
fucking hate this as soon as they have more fidelity to draw things they hire artists that are just
two japanese and they ruin the style of the original games well fire emblem and ace attorney both went
down to fucking garbage as soon as they got too many pixels I wasn't talking about the art style I
just mean that's just that's the case with every game there's a critical mass of pixels that a game
just can't can't sustain and then it's bad forever that's why pokemon is bad once it went to the
fucking 3ds agreed I suppose too many poly too many polygons I kind of like they're just pixels but
I kind of like the the the character design of of pokemon sun and moon for like people
like it's it's not too enemy okay yeah that's fine but that's a whole that's a whole other
can of worms but um okay okay um okay my my my problem with ace attorney my problem with
his attorney was one uh it's boring two uh the actually the like the actual court
moments are like it I didn't really feel like I was like solving a puzzle I kind of just felt
like I was just going down dialogue trees um which sucked um and also okay and this one's
weird and this people probably aren't gonna agree with me on this one but like the fucking case in
the first game I don't know I didn't like the fact that you're like that you're like solving a
fucking murder case about like a woman who was just like fucking murdered in her home and like
had her head bashed in and it's got but like the proceedings as you try and discover who did this
is just like very kind of like it's only like sort of serious and kind of goofy and I just didn't
like it I just felt uncomfortable about like this is like gruesome like the crime here is gruesome
and like it's not being treated with the fucking uh uh gravitas that it deserves that might that
might be personal but I feel like the other two are objective criticisms that make the game objectively
bad uh why do you feel like it's not you're not solving a puzzle because I because part of part
of my my favorite thing is like listening to all the dialogue you know like investigating getting
getting the the the the testimonies and like checking the court record and seeing what information
I have to figure out who's lying and how that's that's like fun I guess I never I never felt like
I don't know it's been a little while since I played it but uh I I never felt I never felt
at all like I was in danger of like losing um it just felt like I just had to like
like I would win either because I not because I like to do something but because like I don't know
like there was like a really obvious hint that was like yes this is the option you should choose
right now or even if I didn't have that I could just exhaust every possibility then like maybe I
would lose if I really tried to but it just never felt like a real threat I mean I gotta be careful
here like it's it's not the hardest game ever it's just I think it's it's easy to like get there
by just clicking random buttons if you really want to play it like that but if you want to
figure it out the puzzle aspect is like engaging and fun well I well I didn't think so because I
didn't I when I found a clue I would just feel like it didn't feel like I had to okay it kind
of had the same problem but worse as like um what was that game um what was that game by the
papers please guy with the one where you're on a boat and you got to solve who killed who
I don't know something over a din I think over a din something
over a dean return of the over din um that one also kind of had this but not as bad where it's
like okay the clue it's not you you're not like looking at the scene holistically and deciding
like hmm what could this what could have happened here like what could be going on what are the
possibilities you're looking at it as though like this is a a clue that has been constructed for
you by a game designer and you are taking that hint you're like okay what hint are they trying to
give me with this uh okay they mean to tell me that like this is what happens I mean sure I just
I just like more inductive than deductive uh which is a problem a lot of games have that's not
unique to to reveal right sure it just it doesn't it doesn't feel like I'm solving a crime it feels
like I'm following a trail of breadcrumbs I think what helps me with all that is that I like the
the reward for getting it right is hearing more of like what the story and the dialogue and the
characters or all that stuff if you it's like um sure it's like a really good visual novel with um
yeah like a little bit of puzzle solving in like lore courtroom shenanigans and if you don't care
okay so much about like what the characters are gonna say like then the the puzzle maybe isn't that
incredible that bring okay I totally understand that um and maybe this is something that the later
games are better at than the first one but like that brings me back to my first point which is
that it was boring because like there was so much like clicking through stuff there was so much like
time-wasty stuff between the moments when you know you you put the clue together and then you
get the next piece of the puzzle but it just didn't I like it wasn't that engaging I mean I I will say
I will say the first game I I bet I bet the series gets better I bet the series gets better
replaying the first game it is definitely a little lacking in some of the the interests in like
dialogue stuff because they're just figuring out what these characters are like second game and third
game are like they really step it up on some of the cases definitely the third game I love a lot
well I um yeah I enjoyed the story of these games but uh I guess the gameplay maybe could be better
but I think um I think it's just inherently difficult to make gameplay for a detective kind
of thing like this I don't know if it's ever been done uh like completely successfully before
well I don't know about completely successfully I liked L.A. Noir that that was a good one because
you could miss pieces of evidence and go down a path and still complete the case and you would
just get the wrong guy what was that one what was that one like point and click detective game
and like Davoo made a video about it I don't know and it had like a very like sort of picture book
sort of was it a DS game I don't know let's go to divu.com hang on no I'm gonna go to divu.youtube
what it's the one where you're at like a swamp and you got to like solve an alligator crime
that sounds like my kind of crime I don't know um it does uh
uh never never call an alligator crocodile
why wouldn't would you because uh it's like calling a Chinese person a Japanese
I found it Detective Grimoire yes Detective Grimoire it's 11 minutes long I can't remember this
you know what I actually didn't play this game I just feel like I did play this game because I
watched this video several times and I feel like I know everything there is to know about it
and for I only just now was like wait a minute no I never I never played this game we go to
what am I talking about I think I saw my brother play this game it looks it looks pretty good I
yeah but I forget what what about this is like good detective stuff so go watch the video everybody
fill in the gap in this conversation that are like it does some things pretty good but other
things it's just okay that's just every video about anything well into well well because we were talking
about like like in terms of like specifically how it simulates the like detective like
clue finding problem solving solve the crime sort of thing that's uh that's really hard to do and
I kind of wish they would have a game that does that well because I think that would be a lot of fun
I I mean the thing I was talking about last week or a week before I can't remember about like um
what was it pick cross which is like it's I feel like it's detective but like at the very basis
level where you are using the information you have to determine which blocks which squares are
colored in and which ones aren't and um if you make a mistake you are stupid yeah I guess that's
that's the sort of the the neural firing that I enjoy it's like I wonder hmm which is this the
way it is and then the answer is this is the way it is you were right and I was feel so smart
a lot of older rpgs especially for the nes and a bit era they uh they had a slight detective
element to them because in order to figure out where to go you need to talk to the npcs in town
and uh piece together like the clues and hints like uh because uh there would be no
no cutscenes to tell you where to go so you need to just talk to the random towns people and use
their ecliptic hints to figure out how to solve the problem of the town or whatever is going on
which which games you're talking about like like castlevania 2 you know I mean a eight bit rpgs
like dragon quest or dragon warrior and things of that nature I haven't played any of those extremely
old um rpgs and actually um played a remake of final fantasy one yeah final fantasy one is another
uh good example of that and actually the the original pokemon red and blue um they were heavily
inspired by those old eight bit rpgs because it was in itself an eight bit rpg if you remember
not like a two bit rpg um just just two just just one like like on or off like gameboy uh and also um
every game is a two bit game if you think about it like that well officially every game is binary
officially pokemon was inspired by uh final fantasy legend on the gameboy or as it's known in
in japan to saga series god there's so many fucking sagas so many fucking series of things
franchises what the fuck no thanks what were they thinking what no thank you i'll have none of that
please uh why am i scrolling through pictures of francisco von karma because you love her ben
no no you well that's true well i am yeah the reason why uh the reason why i like the
plots of the you know the phoenix ride games is because i'm a big sucker for murder mystery plots
even though it's pretty cliched i guess yeah that's the thing is like the butler did it like
murders is boring like somebody wanted someone dead you just got to figure out why and whatever
like oh the murder weapon oh i heard that before said the detective on the crime scene for the 100th
time oh someone's dead big surprise how cliche i said like putting the tape around the body
tell me something i don't know there's a fucking body whatever like it's it's like when it comes to
crime drama that is the the the most overused in media but it's obvious because it's like
higher stakes than a parking fine and i just saw a fucking detective crime game where it's like
who fucking who fucking hasn't paid their fucking parking tickets yeah a detective game
where it's just you go to see what car whether it has the the the parking meter like ticket if it
doesn't you give it a fine you just move on actually i want an open world game like that you
walk around entire city just giving out parking tickets well i'm sure that would be riveting
gameplay i mean you could you can make a good game out of anything you could you really could
make a good story out of anything stupid boring things that suck uh can be great as long as you
are yeah papers please papers please was a great game yeah that's what i hear because it was bad
you can make a good game about being being the coffee or the tea guy in a studio in a work
office it's like hey get the tea you got to make sure you get the tea before they're upset with
you what's what's what's that game on the nes where you just gotta fucking like give people root
beer you know the one oh something yeah i've seen it parody yeah you throw beer at people
but you always coming at you you go through sasperilla everybody's always uh rooting for beer
more more beer wait uh what does what does gaston say
but it's just like more than i can bear more beer what for i'm depressed and that's me in 2021
but uh i like i use beer and all of my decorating
i think uh the main reason i like uh murder mystery plots is just all the plot twists and
surprise elements if if it's genuinely surprising that is and um i hate to be surprised no thanks
yeah i think that's right is it's pretty great like having having situations
that unfold in a way that you can't guess exactly what's gonna happen next and it's quite good
i always know that it's not obvious it's written really well yeah once the guy who made um the
first three he didn't do um miles edge worth investigations he there was a team of writers
that made what that one and apparently that one sucks hard that's a good thing i didn't play it
doesn't have his his his smart writing thought to like make everything fit together nicely
and that that that one video i made about professor leighton versus phoenix right um that
was also written by him and the creator of professor leighton so it was like doubly good
written that was such a good game oh yeah i i remember that video you made it was uh pretty
good from what i recall yeah it was before i i i didn't have and still don't know how to uh record
ds footage so i just don't it didn't bother i just pointed a camera at it well um i always like it
and murder mystery plots when the cop is turns out to be the bad guy or you know because that's
that's just real life yeah basically or you know when one of the good guys turns out to be the bad
guy because uh again it's kind of cliched but i uh i just love that betrayal plot point
and um do you remember i like to be surprised i like to be blind oh yeah i used to be a big fan
seemed like a look seemed like a little bit of it first series spoiler alert someone's a bad guy
nobody knows who it is no fuck someone's the bad guy what why would i want to watch a show
gib that has a bad guy in it i like good guys that would be an interesting experiment to have a show
where everything is just fine the whole time there's not even any problems hold no that's
that's just um isn't that just what like slice of life is well you know i don't think so because
like slice of life the problems they deal with are not big deals because it's usually from they
they have problems they okay okay they might have a problem or a conflict but like no one's
never like a murderer yeah it's always just like i mean maybe maybe sometimes there's like a
jerk late for the downside oh no how can i get to school that sucks how can i get to my first day
of school and eat my toast at the same time every story has a conflict no matter how small or big
it is no i'm gonna be i'm gonna brunch out i'm gonna break new ground i'm gonna have a story
when nothing happens at all nothing nothing happens a show about nothing that sounds quite
familiar to me nothing nothing happens maybe something happens on his way to work no nothing
happens it's just a shot of him driving for 45 minutes that's like uh that's like it's like
if you're murdered by a sign i guess that means you were sign found
oh god christ christ i'll fucking my sorry i um maybe i should tone it down from your honor
maybe you should fucking go to jail maybe you should fucking go to voice jail
this is the first time we ever put a guest in voice jail but there's a first time for everything i
guess uh so here's why i'm upset um i can't i can't get my gummies to be right oh i thought you
had the recipe correct no i can never i like i'll get it right one time and then i'll like try
and do it again and and then like it doesn't work like the last time i was like oh okay i wasn't
using enough pectin that's why they were coming out too like too too jello like and then i i tried
making some yesterday and i was like okay i'll use more pectin like i did last time so i used the
more pectin and they come out they come out like all fucking crumbly and gross and i'm like what
what did i do and then i go back to last and they come out gummy again i'm like it doesn't
work how are you measuring the same thing the input are you doing it very precisely i'm just
i'm just doing it with like a spoon you know with like measuring spoons oh okay i'm measuring
okay not like a spoon spoon no i really just remember like okay i use a tablespoon of this i
use a teaspoon of that um man man what about uh you know what you know what it is the the move
the move to corn syrup i don't i don't cook it i just like i just heated and dissolved it and
refrigerated the switch to corn corn syrup doesn't work that well honestly like the weird like
fiber shit the imo just worked so good it was so good and even though it's like it's like a weird
substitute for sugar but it's literally better than the real thing i can't fucking get a little behind
on the gummy saga what i remember you saying it's no longer keto gummies um what's the the sugar
thing is that part of keto you can't you can theoretically make them you can theoretically
make them with a like highly concentrated sugar solution in water but i decided to try making
them with corn syrup because corn syrup has a pretty similar consistency to the isomalt
oligosaccharide fiber syrup that i had been using for the keto variety and i just this is what i've
been this is what i've been trying to do and i just can't i just can't get it to be i just can't get
it to be both smooth and gummy like but also like have enough bite to it that it tastes like a gummy
and not just like a jiggler and i i i've made like three batches the last few days that have all
failed they're all trash um and it's annoying because pectin is expensive um like using a tablespoon
of fruit pectin is like well that's like several dollars worth of ingredients right there sure
blowing a lot of money on this uh project i'm think i can write it off i think i can write it
off as a taxable expense i hope well you talk about it i have probably use it as content as a
like thing to talk about on your on your income show that's that's what this is called the income
show i have probably spent possibly over a thousand dollars on like weird on like various powders
and like items and objects and molds and and liquids and ingredients and actually no i think
about it you've been doing it for quite a while that isn't that big of an expense if it's involving
like the equipment as as well well the i mean the equipment's not that i mean the molds were like
i don't know i probably like maybe like 50 or 70 bucks on all these different molds and so they
are not that expensive yeah but think of all the bitcoin yeah i think of all the bitcoin you could
have bought was that a thousand dollars ben oh man did i did i say last week that i'm out of the
bitcoin game you did yeah did i okay well i just i just want to say that uh i'm i'm you know i was
upset when i got out of the bitcoin because i had been up like a thousand dollars and when i got out
i had lost like 200 so like oh god but it could have been so much worse because it has continued
to go down since then i sold it at around like 30 35 k and now it is down to like under 32 so you
know i'm just glad that i sold when i did because it seems to be the the market has turned bearish
as they say i've got something to mention about coinbase specifically because that was the thing
i was using um apparently you can't take money out like in in in normal currency you can put
money in and you can trade the bitcoin for different cryptocurrencies but you need a different program
to turn it back into real money um so yeah my brother he he tried it as well and he found that
it was like like not good so don't get coinbase i guess i still look at how everyone says to use
coinbase yeah how's how's your one pound doing uh 83 pence right now it's actually gone yeah
since a little while ago so yeah it went really far down like yesterday it was down yeah yeah yeah
around uh around midnight on around midnight on uh thursday it was down to like under 30 k
it's bounced back a little bit yeah i noticed it went down a lot but i don't know i just used
that opportunity to buy more did you actually yeah because in theory it should go up eventually in a
future at some point hopefully okay but did you but did you actually did you actually buy so yeah i
did buy someone it went down it hasn't really gone that far down if you look at the old time
yeah it's it's not really enough for me i would i wouldn't want it to get like i think i think it's
gonna go fresh and then i'll be like yeah but i think it's gonna go down further yeah i think it's
gonna go down further and settle it might i think it might settle around like maybe 25 or maybe 20
or maybe even lower i don't know and then it'll probably just hang out for a while and then maybe
it'll have another fucking boom or not another maybe it'll just dwindle to zero the bit the bitcoin
boom they're gonna have another with like one day like when everybody in the world owns bitcoin
and then the price goes to the moon everybody in the world will be a millionaire and everybody
will just start having babies left and right and that'll be the and that'll be the boomers
mark two the bitcoin boomers and that's why people have babies because of the bitcoin
because everyone i don't know when when good things happen people have babies and you can afford them
but that's a bad thing you don't want to have a bad thing to ruin a good thing
look i i don't know it's just when when babies is that's when well why do you think the first
baby boom happens because they died in the war and it's like we got to make more
no no you fucking weirdo it wasn't that like oh no everyone's happy that they're no longer getting
bombed so it's like yeah cool well was that plus the fact it was that plus the fact that
like the economy was going like nuts because of like the post war boom or whatever yeah like
now we can we can take all of germany's resources and yeah things are cheap hell yeah hell yeah
and like you know we i don't know we made like so we we made so much money on bombs or whatever i
don't know whatever the fuck it was whatever it was that we were doing that made our economy yeah
i i never really went back and learned more about world war two beyond documentaries that i
occasionally catch on tv and my school like education it's probably a lot more going on there
that like governments don't want me to know about probably probably yeah i mean i
surely everything's declassified now sure but like um my my specific like educate like i've
only seen documentaries broadcast on the bbc and my english so that's like that's definitely biased
perspective on exactly what happened i mean i don't know it seems like the bbc is a real piece of
shit bbc seems like it's a real fucking biased uh news yeah i i don't like like they're okay
for some things but i will never really forgive them for like ruining jeremy corbin's reputation
in that you know the whole anti-semitism thing which was stupid not even real
they just kept going about it until people believed in and he lost
great seems like it's a it's a little bit like it's a little bit like halfway between like something
like cnn and something like fox news which is like a really bad medium i don't know if it's like
that's not a good happy medium it's definitely a cnn like like similar sort of like liberal
not really yeah not the you know anti-socialist for sure yeah yeah sure okay so you're saying it's
just like just regular neolib shit yeah i mean i'm not like that you know i guess cnn i guess cnn would
i guess cnn would probably be similar like cnn is probably very much like hmm you know
are trans people corrupting our youth more at 11 you know give give both sides of the argument
or whatever yeah the enlightened centrist position like i could feel i feel like that would be
generally a normal bbc thought is like huh what if we yeah platformed both sides
hmm yes yes yes oh my god i saw um i saw i just happened to see a video of roosh
you know remember roosh uh roosh v who's that yeah roosh i think i heard of that name never
never heard of him i don't i don't you've never heard of him um well he used he used to be like
a pickup artist guy who i i kind of followed and i kind honestly i kind of liked him i'm
ashamed to say that now but like i'd like followed this guy and read his stuff and was like this guy
seems cool um and you know anytime he said like some misogyny stuff i was like haha that's he's
just joking about that well you know i know he's been really he's been really bad for a long time
but i saw him on like a live stream of him uh like that he did just like last week and he's talking to
some guy called he's called the muslim skeptic i think i don't know anything about that guy
but um he's like some muslim guy who doesn't i don't know that's literally all i know he's
a muslim and he's a skeptic um but i don't know roosh was just going he's just literally just
being like yeah you know hollywood's run by the jews you know they're all lying to you you know
they want to fucking do miscegenation to dilute the white race just on iran it's on iran so i was
like i can't i can't believe it this this this guy used to be like this guy is like a hard he's
like a hardcore like traditional like uh like christian values guy now this guy used to be this
guy used to write books about how you could like um you know uh uh get one night stands with girls at
bars which is what i was here for well i mean in hindsight it doesn't seem that he's got a great
ridiculous that he would eventually he's got a great beard though strange he's got a great beard
he's gonna look great what looks fantastic a great beard spectacular i think uh this is what's
known in some circles as a grifter i don't think he is a grifter i think he's a genuinely a fucking
psycho i know i think he totally believes it he's he's i don't think he's just following the money
oh you never know it's tempting for some reason there i don't know i was just it was just
disturbing it's just disturbing because this is and and i met this guy i've probably said that
like i literally met this guy and hung out with him a couple times uh i have probably mentioned
that on here i met him i met him in poland this was this was before he wasn't he wasn't he wasn't
quite like this back then but that was what maybe like six years ago i don't know uh
so just so just unpleasant i was like i felt a little sick honestly hearing that well um this
is the perfect guy to get all your world world war two uh info from i think we gotta get ruche on the
podcast yeah please remind us about world war two who really was at fault how many how many i mean
you know hey six million that's like doesn't says okay well you know uh nobody is perfect not even
adolf hitler no yeah and and then all this time i thought he was but apparently apparently he's
cringe apparently he's said some cringe things now he's canceled yeah everybody makes mistakes
couldn't even you know what we should we should couldn't even finish the job
um sorry let's move on i don't even know why i don't know why i brought this up that letter
from christian i felt chipper now i'm depressed again oh just bring up the christian thing again
you'll be chipper all over oh yeah i'll just i'll just read the letter again i should i should
every time you feel down you just look at over at the podre and you're like uh yes
i think this is good nothing brings the mood down more than holocaust
it's it's actually it's actually pretty ugly honestly it's actually not a particularly
attractive rock uh this little bit of a hemi more fight it actually just looks like mold
um i i i'll show a picture in the in the podcast i wish i had a picture on like you
know i'll take a picture right now right fucking now a few moments later are you are you ready to
see this shit i'm ready uh no are you are you ready for the fucking to have your mind shattered
and your pelvis shattered uh here we go yes to the first part no to the second part
here we go yes to the second part podre
it looks like mold right it looks yeah it looks a little dusty like like it's something's growing
on it looks like uh yeah it's not like big chunks i mean it's not like big like crystal chunks
it's just like very small little like it's very small crystals just kind of like in like a layer
on top of this like geode rock or and that's what i was gonna say it looks like one of those georocks
or whatever they call it yeah i mean i guess it's not technically one it i don't or maybe i don't
know what if i don't know what specifically makes a geode geode ben do you have the capability to
make like a silicon mold like by by pouring it over this and make a podrian uh gummy
uh i would find a better rock to do that i guess i'm trying to think of ways this could be interesting
um man maybe shine ultraviolet light on it i've talked before about how cool it would be to have
like 3d molds of like rfck things like the various fruits and vegetables and a podrian too would be
cool and just make make gummies out of that once i once i had the perfect recipe and could actually
get my hands on the fucking ingredients i found a new flavor company though the new the new flavors
that i bought make the old the old ones were like bad like some of them were just terrible the new
ones incredible the new watermelon i got beautiful perfect guava love it strawberry decent cherry
pretty good this is a big step up from what it was so uh when you're gonna start selling these gummies
i don't know maybe never maybe never i don't know gotta make some money ben uh
maybe maybe i don't know you live in a capitalistic society you need to sell everything you make
it would take it would take a lot of um i would have to build up a bunch of infrastructure for that
i would have to i would have to have a lot of things in place that i don't have like a store
front and and molds and like a slightly more like a more a more steady supply of stuff and like a
settled upon recipe that i'm like this is what it's made of this is how i make it which i don't
really um i don't have any of that can't you just sell it online or something
well yeah but what about all that other stuff i just said uh step by step
i don't know i'm still gonna have a fucking etsy page i don't know whatever whatever uh sounds
complicated sounds complicated and like a dozen people would buy them and then
well that's even the point i mean what's the what's the point of anything you know
we're all just gonna die you know and soon too very soon that's a good point yeah the thing with um
like selling food products i think would be like much more complicated and annoying
like mailing them than it would probably like you would need to be a local like label
seller you'd have to go to the market i would at the very least have to like label them and get like
you know ingredient like they have to be labeled for sale yeah yeah yeah um food would be fun it
depends on how perishable they are if they go bad quickly then it's pretty difficult here's i mean
the thing about it is that like i don't expect to ever make any money from it so if i do it it'll
only because i think it would be fun and cool uh and i would just be and i could and i would
amuse me uh so if i ever do it that will be why yeah or maybe uh send it to people on on your
patreon as a patreon bonus no no anything but that no no i don't i don't want to i don't want to do
like monthly like i think like tom does like monthly or bi-monthly or whatever like care packages
i think maybe did she does i'm not sure she used to i'm not sure if she still does
yeah but i don't want to do that i feel like yeah like that would be you need to be making
uh like all of this extra stuff and then sending it in a little envelope on a usb stick or whatever
yeah which i kind of already do well i kind of do that just well because every now and then
somebody buys some more like pins or whatever so i'm kind of doing that but like those are just
one-time transactions it's not like it's it's not i don't i don't want to like set myself up with
any more like monthly or weekly responsibilities i mean to me that the idea of like setting up
things i mail to people makes less sense because the majority of like english speaking
viewers of things are gonna be from america which means a whole lot of bullshit shipping
oh that's true yeah that's a lie true it's always gonna be a hassle i could say europe only and
much less like things would happen yeah that's that's a good point it's just it's just gonna be
like inherently more expensive for you to do it oh and now because of brexit even europe is gonna be
fucking annoying nice god nice damn it awesome really uh you're really lucked out man europe's
so fucking cool like you know not england anymore no but it's it's it's so it's so fucking cool that
they just like decided like hey you know our borders like fuck them let's just set up like high
speed trains that just go everywhere between our fucking countries and they just did that
yeah that's so great i mean and then you you people just threw it in the trash well i mean the
train can't go over the water you personally ruined it you ruined it there's no point anymore
just throw it all away just i was there i was there in the shadows like climbing down like a
little rope and then whispering into the ear of the prime minister at the time whoever it was
saying dude brexit like that will be a cool title you know catchy slogan why didn't you just say that
and then they did and then you did well brexit does sound pretty cool it was really funny
you know the the word the name the name brexit so i can see why i cut on it's yeah it's catchy yeah
it's catchy annoyingly people are good at making things sound good even though they're bad
um i feel like we should have something to say about like the new president but like i don't
like nothing happens nothing's happened with that he's undone some some trump things immediately
which is like yeah sure a bare minimum so far cool i guess kids kids still in cages that's fine
that's good uh isn't that something that's been around for a long time um it would like the the
centers were like built by obama they were used under obama trump like they've been used more
under trump but they could be does they could literally be dissolved and like emptied out like
under executive by executive order like anytime yeah but what i what i mean is it just seems like
we could literally just stop doing that any time it seems like that goes beyond the administrations
for whatever reason uh it doesn't it's like why would so many uh why would so many presidents
from different parties continue to do the same thing because they're all the same they're even yeah
that's right this is the only way you get because they're mostly they're mostly the same that the
only way you can get to the top is by appeasing the largest number of people which means you have to
have no morals no fiber no no character no character development that's right nothing you have to be
at an empty shell or otherwise uh a freak a ghost in the shell wait wait wait i'm writing all this
down yeah cool this is fucking this is hot tips hot tips and tricks this is speed run speed run
government speed run the president see exactly uh joe joe biden like slow run the presidency
because he's like 85 uh so you know but he got he got there you know god bless him
uh no i won't okay i'm sorry i won't bless that guy that son of a bitch that son of a that that
that whores son uh
then that's me that's not very nice shut up shut the hell up do you want to go voicemails
we can start we can start voicemails now uh yeah we could we could mail yeah i'm it's been
almost two hours yeah uh okay let's do let's do one the first one that we got this week is called
how wait it's called how to unkill the podcast uh cool wait i'm uploading it to the general
okay there it is how to unkill the podcast three two one go i have a great idea on how to revive
the podcast guys so endless jess digi bro don't like mumpkin jones they hate him right uh best
guy ever would rather not associate with him good thing all those people are never on the fucking
podcast anymore so this is not the first person to propose jones as a guest uh and then and then
more people would watch the podcast and it wouldn't be dead anymore uh what would you guys think this
is not the first time this has been suggested i mean is is monkey even like hot shit like he used
to be anymore i mean like i i i i literally propose this but but like yeah it wouldn't it wouldn't
revive it wouldn't revive the podcast to have mumke yeah mumke's not that hot shit mumke had a
moment there where he was like he was the he was the uh the the free speech uh uh you know help
i'm being censored guy du jour um and then and then and you know and then that came and went
and then he had his cringe arc and i was like he had his cringe arc which is pretty funny it was we
all had we all had a lot of laughs uh i mean yeah we could i guess i would say we could do that
and i wouldn't even be that opposed to it but it's not gonna revive the podcast like give me a give
me a break yeah i agree that's not gonna revive anything but um why not absolutely i mean yeah i
mean it's i mean i mean i mean i mean i mean i think mumke's kind of an asshole but like whatever
like we had we had fucking we had more logic on so like whatever we it's not it's not like we have
standards uh i guess so well um but whatever like i don't really care um okay the next the
next one is called oh god i i hope you're ready i hope you're ready for cringis bingus two oh no
the sequel oh yes oh yeah all right three two one go hello pcp it's me again yeah cringis bingus
pcp voicemail lever that's ever called into the show today i will talk to you about what i cringed
and what i banged again what i cringed at the thing that i cringed at is people telling me
what they think i should do because sometimes i just want to sleep until
five in the afternoon and watch anime all day and do nothing else and people tried to tell me that
that's bad and they're wrong because i'm just having fun i'm just having a good time so i cring
when they tell me that i shouldn't be doing that the thing i banged and what i banged this week was
a bunch of cookies i got a box of cookies from the store and i ate them all i banged all the
cookies are in like two days and i kind of got a tummy ache and i have so many carbs so many carbs
in the cookies that i that's cring anyway that's me cringis bingus yeah talk to you next week your
favorite pcp voicemail lever cringis bingus cringis bingus cringis bingus sure liking this guy
he he fucking uh he fucking delivered he showed he showed up and he showed out he brought the goods
you deliver the package i think i think this is the start of an arc this is the start of an arc
start of a beautiful friendship this is the start of a rising star that will never fall
we'll never get tired of this bit under any circumstances there's nothing there's nothing
so racist that cringis bingus could do that would make us stop loving him i'm i'm i'm prepared to
say uh right now uh cool thanks for the voicemail see can i can i call you cb can i call you cb
for short you know we get on a we're we're close personal friends okay next one next one is called
ben saint is not a bad person wow three two one go you see ben isn't a bad person he isn't even a
stupid person he's just like his his worldview is all twisted up from all the lies he's ingested
honestly i think he could benefit from some form of formal re-education encampment of some kind
pony hypnosis teach him you know like facts and logic and stuff i love facts nobody loves
this is my opinion i know he's gonna lash out against this he's a child but you know
no no no education ben don't throw those out of the pram they go down the pram they stay in the
game it's pretty critical no i don't want to learn anything no i hate facts so much
we're learning uh learning kind of sucks i'm not i'm not you know i'm just i'm just flawed you
know i'm just i'm just uh i'm just one of my foibles some of my foibles that just makes me even more
lovable is that i hate the truth and i love uh lies next one don't we all
hell yeah next one is called you're a joker and you didn't even know her three two one go i'm
listening i'm a few episodes behind and i'm listening to gib talk about how she likes fire
and ben was like oh yeah fire's cool i guess but i'm not super stoked about it and nobody
no one recognized the pun what the fuck sorry i didn't even notice i mean you see if i was there
things would have been different yeah you would have said instead i mean yeah i mean i just i
say stoked as a matter of course so yeah wait was that accidental i think so yeah lol and then it
doesn't count that's just that's just a phrase that i use so yeah no it's gotta be on purpose
yeah but what so uh good good catch good catch uh the next one is called um the next one is called
uh my mic is bad sue me why would you title your voicemail that why wouldn't you title it about what
what the voicemail is actually about okay three two one go i cannot believe that you wrote off mr
boop's ending as an even gillian reference it is the ending spells out the running theme of the comic
a critique of escapism the characters return to the place of origin leaving alex head cannon as he
accepts that reveling in fantasy can never be a replacement for the real world it's beautiful
and it's great and thing you've made me so mad that i'm gonna go fuck my wife lisa simpson
but on the episode where she's an adult so it's not weird i mean i i did catch the whole like you
know that okay i just i just thought the ever thing was ever thing okay it didn't need the ever
music but uh whatever doesn't really matter here's what i think here's what i think um
i i disagree i know this is a joke voicemail but i'm gonna respond to it as though we're serious
which is a bad habit that i have um uh i i disagree that one of the that the theme that a theme of
betty of mr boop is like that like reveling in fantasy is bad that's like entirely an
a seat and act for thing like there's no there's nothing about that in like the first three acts
that's just like a sort of like last minute like twist at the end that gets added and it's not
relevant before that so i suppose i mean the joke seems to be that the the comic is is it looks like
a four panel punchline comic and there's no punchline all the time it's just like the the author
is so stupid that he's just drawing about having sex with betty boop all the time and he's so brazenly
like unapologetically like making her love him over and over again so much that that is like
meta funny it's the author that we're laughing in the early acts yeah it's the it's the author the
idea that this guy is drawing about his his life and how everything's so fucking sick even though
it's clearly it's not quite as sick as he's trying to portray it is okay okay hold on
are you are you saying are you saying that like we're meant we're meant to read early mr boop
and read into it we're like the punchline of the early ones like is the hypothetical author
that is making the comic because like yeah because it's like ha ha some it's so weird
that some person drew this comic okay it's it's funny multiple levels but ultimately like the
punchline is about the author having drawn it like like ones where he's like you're never gonna
leave me right ha ha and she's like no i'll never leave you like that's never gonna happen ha ha
yes i love you so much in in fact it's it's like i'm gonna cry with how much i love like it's
there's there's elements of like unsureness in the way that he's like displaying affection
and he's drawing like it's it's multi-layered like i think the joke seems to be how soon does that
start to come in quite soon i think it's even before bugs bunny appears
hmm how the fuck is it is it boop.net is it sounding a lot like uh tails got trolled
uh a little bit a little bit like that um superficially yeah i mean sort of it's got some
it's it's uh tails gets trolled with boop characteristics um fuck uh
i mean it's similar in that it is a story which pulls all these fucking dudes together into
why can't i fucking find the website i can't believe far down when i when i click mr boop on
google does the webtoon comes up first and the fucking tv trips thing um oh god it's been
pushed so far i just want to look at the fucking website okay it's mr boop.net okay i found it um
okay so the first okay my wife is betty boop um okay even okay even in the second the second
comic is like i'll never get a divorce yeah and then it's the sort of the the the sure the the the
cocksuredness like like oh this is absolutely perfect but the cracks are so obvious and he's
still drawing about them it's like it's it's funny for that sort of reason okay okay but is the but
is the message there that like i don't think no i don't think living living in living in a fantasy
is bad sure okay okay okay but what i'm saying is like i don't know if i don't know if you can
say that like yeah the ending which is sort of like the in which like the fantasy finally crumbles
is like oh yeah that's like the culmination of the theme of mr boop which is about like you know
how retreating into fantasy is bad and like this is this is the the result of it because i i don't
like the tension like the tension in the early comics yeah is about this like this like total
cocksuredness about like like being married to mr the total like like the totally sincere way in
which the character and i guess you one assumes also the author is like being married to mr boop
sure is to betty boop sure is great but then all this yeah all these cracks are showing in that facade
and i guess i guess it sort of depends on if you imagine that like within the diocese that the
comic is being made by the fictional alec who like real who is the one that you see in the videos
who is like yes i invented the comic mr boop it's a comic about how i married to betty boop i married
to betty boop you know you know like fuck i feel like i've sort of been like i guess i i read it
as like like it's a comedy right like it's jokes and it's meant to be funny and it's being made by
someone who thinks it's funny for this character to act this way but i think no you're supposed to
assume that that the what that the alec making these is not the real alec but the alec that we see
in the videos who is sort of subsumed by the fantasy yeah i mean i'm not sure how early on
you're supposed to feel that because if you just read the comic and don't see the videos
i mean yeah like are you supposed to to to read the comic and assume that the author doesn't know
what's going on like that they are a tales gets trolled or sonichu
author like they they actually think this is like good because the whole website is like that
it's like shitty website um like 90s i mean bad uh you know all that all that i think what do you
call it i can't think of the word to describe but it sounds a lot like my content i think that
i think that this is a failure of the series because i think that the series assumes that you
sort of are on board with thinking that the author is sincere right i guess i guess it's not
because like he made the video spelled out pretty clearly that's like you should assume that okay i
i yeah i don't know how early is the is this the first like video that's what i know because i i
i because i feel like that video is what established it was it was tongue in cheek
like i could tell pretty quickly it wasn't like oh this is similar to sonichu and that the person
making it has no idea what's going on and they don't realize how funny it is but it's very clearly
obviously like constructed to be the way it is yeah yeah but it's still funny like like you
can buy into the character once you know it's a character that's deliberately the author is one
of the characters and he's playing it in a video that's like oh wow he's going to such lengths
to tell this joke okay i mean at some point at some point the comic itself starts commenting on
the fact that like alec in the comic draws these comics and like talks about himself drawing the
comics but i feel like that's like act no no that's that's even in book two even by book two he's
doing that damn okay okay so i think these themes are kind of established a little earlier than
maybe i thought but but but but oh my god maybe maybe maybe maybe this maybe this voicemail is
right maybe i am the fool maybe i've been under arresting any mr boop this whole time maybe it is
a a a unified thematic hole shit i mean it could be i still i still feel like the presentation
with the ava probably read it maybe i haven't watched ava in a while i forget whether the theme
is exactly the same i i still feel like the ava reference doesn't add a lot this is a mr boop
podcast now i love mr boop everyone should read it and it's finished and it's not a lot
everybody everyone who's a coward who says oh home stuck one piece they're too long i can't get
into that this is very short so you have no excuse okay okay all right i guess my my central
question then is for about the ending being good like is the the the ending is like the crumbling
of this like fantasy so is are we meant to be thinking i don't know if we're meant to be thinking
about the like i don't i don't know if we're supposed to think like oh this character has
is like living in a fucking like unhealthy fantasy world that i don't know maybe we're supposed to
but i i didn't i didn't start to think about that stuff until like way later maybe i might
fuck i might go back and reread the whole thing like knowing like knowing how it ends and stuff
so i can just so i can really have like a really well-formed opinion of like how thematically
consistent is this well i should uh that's right yeah i should read it too so um if i'm on here the
next time then i can contribute more to this uh discussion uh yeah if you yeah you should i mean
yeah i don't know why i don't know why you wouldn't have already read it since it's the
fucking breakout hit of 2020 probably the best thing that happened in 2020 was mr boob
i'm feeling a lot more confident about being married to you now
which if she leaves me i'll threaten to kill myself i'm just kidding i know that's this is
later right like this is book three uh i don't know this is after he comes out of the coma this
is like number 33 so this is not uh the mrs boob that i i remember this is book one apparently
what yeah this is only number 33 fascinating okay all right enough enough boob talk enough boob talk
uh it's time for act it's time for boob action when you when you step on a goomba that's a boob right
well the sound it makes it no it's a it's a it's a it's a
yeah i guess it's it's a foot stone it's a boop
uh next one next one is called twitter warning funny joke okay three two one go
uh you guys are all like i don't like twitter but uh have you ever tried shitter
no no he was right uh it was pretty funny thanks for thanks for the voicemail
okay next one next one is called an asian query so okay three two one go how long is a chinese name
oh i get it oh i get it yeah it's just a statement
uh it's not even well he said it was a query so yeah it was it was a it was a facade it was a
it was a one two punch i need to get to this been going on you need to get your voicemail
people to write one of my videos dude that should be a bonus episode where people like send in uh
what literally what we're saying we just read it we just read the script oh god no well you know
what that would it would become just like just like two people would be the ones that ended up
writing like most of it you know it would be like a handful of people might send like a little like
little snippets and then like two people would be like ha ha and they'd write an entire script
it would be horrible it'd be a nightmare no no unlike all of our other uh bonus episodes that
would just make for terrible content so it's something acceptable i did kind of seriously
consider doing that idea having somebody script one of my videos for me and i read it but uh i
think that's not a very good idea yeah but would you outsource that to just a a gang of hooligans
yeah that's that's probably okay yeah maybe okay okay next one is called and woo hussy ooh
woo uh three two one go there seems to be some confusion about us homestuck is my intellectual
poverty and mine alone all of my head canons are 100% legitimate whereas yours are waffa
way fake there is no room for interpretation whatsoever in homestuck not even a little bit
to claim otherwise is hella c and also in violation of my legal rights as an artist
i hope this quills things up ooh woo thanks hussy i didn't know you were such a fascist uh yeah
oh that reminds me um last time there was that that talk i don't know actually we if we talked
about it on the show but like the the thing you brought it up and the the hussy maybe being the
problem behind yeah yeah yeah our gentleman situation i read that whole thread oh god
can you summarize for me i can the summary is that uh it's likely that it could be both of
their fault and it's not just they fucked him over like he he uh implied in the thing that he leaked
because the the the non-disclosure agreement for the whatever means that nobody can talk about it
but he did leak something to someone who then made a post about it which is where everybody
heard about it and then that was taken off but of course once it's out there it's out there um
but the odd gentleman haven't said anything on their end and it was it was this guy basically
going through you know somebody gave him a tip-off that hussy may have been the problem
he took all of the statements and he cross-referenced it by talking to people involved uh seeing what
was absolutely false and none of it was absolutely false nothing could be disproven
which was uh curious and things seem to line up very very neatly um but the i think the the the
main thing that seems pretty likely is the odd gentleman were uh they were waiting around for
hussy to create the document that they could like the the the bible the the pitch bible the
the thing of this is what the game has to be please make it um they were waiting for him to
write a lot of stuff to to make that so that they could get started on developing the game
and um he took a really long time with that and in the interim they were like okay we need to
be making something so they started work on a different project which was the king's quest
thing with the idea that since that's also a point and click they can use what they build
with that for the hive swap thing later um but when hussy was ready he went to the odd gentleman
all allegedly by the way that i'm saying um don't actually have any proof of all this
but the idea is he well then it's proof we can just keep we can just keep repeating it
as though it's true and then it will be well i i i want people to read the the the big post
because it's quite extensive and it goes into a lot more detail than i'm going into so don't get
the wrong impression but this is what i've gleaned from it is it's likely that they were working on
king's quest because they had to wait for a while hussy did finally get him the thing but by that
point they were already working on a different game and they said okay we have to finish this first
because of contracts and stuff we'll get to hive swap afterwards and hussy was like furious and he
like canceled the whole thing and then set about making like having his game be made in house with
his own studio and then everything changed sounds like uh some hot goss that makes i mean if we only
ever heard hussy's side of it before then i guess it's not surprising that the takeaway of it was
it's their fault yeah there was lots of little bits where he's like making people believe that they
were so unreasonable but like the more i think about it and the more i read about this thing i'm
like what are the chances that this company of people are all fucking assholes and andrew hussy
just happens to be like yeah and they literally just like took they literally just like let someone
pay them a ton of money to make a game and then just didn't make it like that doesn't seem like the
kind of thing you can get away with yeah and then the fact that there's a non-disclosure agreement
with a with a settlement to like i don't know it's it's fishy which is why it's worth looking into
and yeah you know like i said nothing is like absolutely provable but nothing that this this
tip-off suggested is like like false necessarily like it's not you can't prove that it isn't true
i guess that's the the the curious thing about it um we should have a link to that
in the description well the the truth is usually somewhere in the middle with most things
that's why you gotta have this why you gotta have jk rowling on the bbc to explain why trans
people are a menace to society versus anyone else that says something else by the way that i hear
both sides of the argument all of that said about andrew i don't necessarily think it makes him
like a demon devil man it just it's like yeah like business is like complex and if he was handling it
badly i mean whatever it sucks high swap is like delayed by millions of years but uh you i don't
know i still like what he's made generally speaking you'd like to you think you'd chalk it up probably
more to incompetence definitely more to incompetence than malice yeah sure no thanks like like his
like i don't know i mean i don't really know what he's like as a person too much
aside from his media that he's made which is like assuming you know what a youtube is like from
watching videos of them well uh nobody's perfect not even adolf hitler yeah he all comes back to
hitler uh okay okay next one is called rejected application follow-up three two one of go
you know it then is that guy who applied to be a guest uh i just figured no hard feelings you
know i just figured i just saw that guy who commissioned the art of the wonder bread as his
only qualifications so i figured just had anybody had a shot you don't want to be on for the same
reason as that guy yeah that guy is on because he's like so fucking embarrassing he's he's like
a story he's a curiosity i think it's it's not that you need like high standard of qualifications
he earned his fucking place yeah no no uh it's literally just that we've heard of him
and that his stick is comical um you take uh you take applications for guest positions now
no this this guy said in an application assuming that it would help
it didn't oh that's pretty funny story didn't no hard no hard feelings i'm glad he says that
well maybe a sum maybe we can yeah actually maybe we hate him maybe a few would be fine
okay next one oh god next one is called um that dog is sexy so pucker up pupper
oh no three three two one go
okay cool okay samurai sama must confess samurai robot not real uh just samurai sama
city voice just beno sento san for for epic troll and one more bigger
corner fashion okay samurai sama not real samurai what samurai sama never finish samurai
courage so just a regular man with a katana and samurai dream can no samurai sama
not dream but a samurai but a manoh can't dogan san he say be samurai come from heart
but Beno san break samurai sama heart that's why seek revenge on Beno sento san
and also you steal scroll so fuck you for that okay okay time almost up so until next time
i say oh no the pathos so he's not even a real samurai he's been a fraud you know
he he he you know i had a feeling he's just he's just uh he's just too too honorable a real
samurai don't give a fuck a real samurai would slice your head off in one go but this guy keeps
asking politely that's right that's like he's uh he's you know he thinks he's got something to
prove and he does uh fuck fuck you uh next okay next one damn now we know just learning
just learning so much okay the next one is called uh the ultimate bitch bitch rare
three two one go hey ben you know what makes me a rage um i just uh subscribe to the procrastinators
patreon no five dollar months here oh god i get the bonus episodes again all of them
they're great i'm listening to them no i'm listening to them on youtube please no not the ideal
audio player uh true but you know what i'll accept it okay so the bonus episodes
unlisted youtube videos and what do i hear
no okay maybe but it's not my fault
it's a video thing's still going is that it is that it wait what was that last but he said
he said something at the very end uh why why is it my fault um if there's ads on the if there's
ads on the okay first of all there there should really be mp3s are they're not mp3s of the bonus
episodes they're supposed to be they definitely should be there isn't so we should we should we
should we should update that we should do that um thank you for mentioning it the ones on the okay
the ones on youtube okay if there are ads on them i have personally removed ads from a lot of them
if there are some on the new ones youtube might have just automatically put some no no youtube now
they just put ads no matter what it's it's only whether like you having the um
the uh you need a certain amount of subscribers to get monetization you can turn monetization on
and off but ads are like always on they've changed their their how that works so we definitely definitely
sucks and we should make i thought they were mp3s there were there were of the there are
out of the old ones maybe whoever has been supposed to do that has not been keeping up with it but uh
okay well i guess uh you're gonna have to use ad blocker i mean it's not like i mean it's not
like we make any money from ads on the bonus episodes it's not like i would put them on purpose
because we would we must have made like less than a dollar on all views across all bonus
episodes if that were the case um so you know nobody wants that the ultimate betrayal true
youtube betrayed us keep keep your remember who your true enemies are okay next one is called
setting the record straight for ghost stories three two one go i gotta set the record straight
about ghost stories being a shitty anime made into a gag dub because that's not entirely true
it was based off a book series basically like anime goose bumps and was decently popular in japan
it just wasn't amazing the main problem was that yokai watch wasn't invented yet so american
didn't know what a yokai was and instead of trying to translate everything they just kind of went
whatever so we got the masterpiece that the english dub is today i don't know this is referring to
okay um we're i've heard you know the anime ghost stories nope yeah oh okay well it's long story
short it has it has one of those gag dubs in english like the dub is not faithful it's just
like deliberately stupid um oh and okay yeah and um okay so we said it must have just been a shitty
anime that got a dub and i guess it's no the answer is no it wasn't necessarily shitty it just
was not localizable so they didn't like try and do a faithful localization
okay i mean whatever i don't care i don't care if ghost stories is a good anime or not
well i guess that's why uh you should always go subs over dubs right um no because the
fucking i i'm not gonna if it were if it had been dubbed faithfully it would have no value to me
or to anyone i think well man i don't know whatever i mean i wouldn't care about it if it were just
if it were just normal i like that it's weird shit and schlock and and goofy ass bullshit um
okay next one is called wait a minute which one did i just yeah okay next one is called
monstrous usurper three two one go do you know who henry jay waterness is no henry jay waterness
is the right for the ceo of monsters incorporated during the movie salivan stills the company and
becomes the new ceo he just ceases the power that's not right what the fuck uh he's talking about
ink yeah but why um i guess the transfer of power was like he kills he just banishes the
the spider man by pushing him in the door and it becomes the ceo i mean i assumed he was like
like everyone thought he was the coolest guy that's vote for him to be the new guy you don't vote
you don't vote i don't think he well i don't know how it worked i just i never thought i never
thought it was like oh salivan just is the strongest so he rises to the top and he's now
in charge who who cares why are we even talking why are we talking about monsters incorporated
isn't that what uh isn't that what you did with the pcp ben yes it's it's no it's the exact same
it's the exact same thing became the ceo no no i'm the king i'm not mike wasoski in the situation
that can't be the thing it cannot be the case i just what is the what is what is there
is it so so this guy's asking is it is it fucked up that uh salivan like killed the ceo and took
over the company uh i guess i didn't even know that i've never seen salivan's a good ceo so it's
all fine there's no way to improve the only way the only way to beat a bad ceo is with a good ceo
that's true i thought all these guys are bad though no not if they're nice not if they
not if they have like fun sense of humor post uh things on twitter that are very funny
it's good it's good when it's good when one guy owns everything honestly that's the way he's
reji fees or something whatever he's a he's a he's a me he's a me
okay he's very nice and lovable um as a spokesperson he's very good i don't really know
a site he's he was head of nintendo of america which means he had uh he had a like in charge of
localization and branding and marketing and how everything made in japan would work in western
countries so epic yeah literally that's all right that's all right because i like him because
he's cool red reji seems fine i don't know i don't know i'm sure he's great i'm sure he's real fucking
i'm sure he's a real freak in the sheets if you know what i mean uh next one is called uh what is
it next one is called the speak pipe background thing is making me feel sick okay three two one go
hey fuckheads get the mr boob guy on the podcast get the mr boob guy on the podcast
um hmm be a try i mean i'd like that would be pretty good i don't feel like there's any guarantee
that he would come on he may as well get get everyone on the podcast we we should get uh we
should get this guy i've been hearing a lot about this guy uh joseph robin at biden maybe we could
get him on the podcast hmm maybe we could get uh maybe we could get uh uh maybe we could get the
pendleton ward seems like a real up and comer um maybe we could get the gary gygax i hear he's done
some cool stuff in the field of gaming we're all bunch of gamers here so maybe we should ask that guy
uh we should get rayman on the podcast we should get rayman why isn't rayman of course
everybody loves rayman it's a perfect fit for the pcb oh my god
um i mean yeah okay yeah get mr get mr boob on the podcast okay sure thing um
oh fuck uh the next one is called uh what even is the next one called the next one is called
pancakes uh wee wee or pee pee
three two one go i put my wee wee into your pee pee shut up i put my pee pee into your
shut the fuck up new piece of shit you can't do both of those at the same time you can do one
or two but that was uh that was some quality this guy should be in this should be in voice
jail if he's not already um all right next one is called uh the the most paramount of reminders
three two one go i'm calling you out ben saint yeah catch up on one piece okay thanks you're right
that's true how can you call you out if you don't if he doesn't even have a phone
it just keeps getting longer it just keeps getting longer and longer and there's more
like my dick make just like when i read it when i see corona pretty soon it's gonna be so long it's
going to have a two piece when i i just how am i how am i how can i possibly stay current with one
piece when new chapters just keep coming out like it's it's fucked up it doesn't make any sense
i don't i don't understand uh i'll read game of thrones once it's finished yeah that's like trying
to get up to date on penny arcade anyone remember penny arcade yeah sure sure but why would you
ever want to be current oh god why would you ever do that it's funny because when i first started
reading penny arcade it was back when they weren't around uh long enough to have too many
issues so i actually went back and read all the issues they they published and i i actually did
mean the comics right yeah it's comics but obviously now that that would be basically impossible
there's just too many i mean they put one out like three times a week right um maybe i don't
remember uh the schedule anymore all right i think funny i think i'm funny i'm pretty sure
this is wrong but is penny arcade control alt delete or is that completely different
no they're different you thought they were the same thing i thought they were the same thing in my
head when i hear penny arcade why would they be the same thing why would the why would they be
the same thing when they have our two different names i don't know penny arcade was the control
alt delete is a subsidiary of penny arcade i don't fucking know no no they're they're literally
bitter rivals they're bitter rivals um okay maybe that's why i've associated the two and then yeah
yeah like a lot of people associate the two mostly it's to say like oh control alt delete is trash
penny arcade is like that but good but like it's really not like penny arcade is also trash it's
maybe slightly less trash but like penny arcade but it's just it's just been more successful
penny arcade started in 96 i think and uh control delete started in the 2000s maybe
early 2000s wow this is exactly the same as control delete it's not the same i mean it's bad
and different i'm looking at it this is this is more sweet bro and hella jeff than then
that i mean that's true that's true well i i think probably was inspired by penny arcade
i don't know how i've never seen these characters i think i've seen the guy with the brownish hair
uh nowadays everybody associates control delete with the miscarriage comic yes meme
loss yeah um penny arcade is is like the worst thing that penny arcade does i've said this before
but like i like a lot of their like other like side projects that they've done over the years
the comic is like unreadable it's i don't understand why they keep doing it i don't
know anyone who likes it um i don't know why anyone would it's if it's a nightmare one thing that it
always uh annoyed me about their comic is that um a lot of times you don't get the joke unless you
read taiko's uh blog post about it yeah 100 you read the comic and you just be like uh i have no
idea what they're talking about you know okay a couple things first of all gabes art style has
like melted over the years and like i'm fine with him being more expressive but like it's really
it's gotten really weird looking like it just looks weird nowadays um and yeah the comic okay
i used to i've listened to every single episode of the um of the dlc podcast which is the podcast
that they would record like as they were writing the comic and it's literally it's them like riffing
as they come up with the comic and i love that podcast it's great the comics are dog shit not
a single one has ever been funny didn't they do videos of that podcast or something because there
were video yeah there were some video episodes i remember watching the videos and uh those are
pretty good i mean i've watched i've i've watched a ton of like side of like penny arcade side
content and like penny arcade adjacent stuff like i watched um like i've i've i've watched i've
listened to a lot of their old like um dnd uh uh groups and stuff like the c team mostly and uh
i mean i went to i went to pax that one year which was pretty great um what was that oh yeah
and the strip search strip search was was the best thing we ever did and they never did it again
because they're hacks because they're cowards wait uh that's the reality tv comic thing right
yeah strip search i remember watching that it was really it was really good i mean it was kind it was
kind of crap actually but it was kind of crap in a way that i liked and appreciated it's a reality tv
what can you expect yeah i mean exactly um i i think control of delete is better than penny
arcade just because it has loss and penny arcade doesn't doesn't have anything i'm looking around
the closest thing the closest thing that penny arcade has to loss was the dick wolves comic which
caused like a in hindsight like very minor and nobody actually gave a shit sort of like
political correctness oh yeah i remember that scandal um but like at the time it seemed like
a big deal but like nobody cares anymore and it's and it's honestly not even that funny and it's
like not even worth explaining penny arcade is like um penny arcade is like the gaming equivalent
of a garfield comic i think i i think i think you're giving it too much credit because it's
not just like it penny arcade is not something that is just like a simple like you know relatable
little like gag about something that's like oh ha ha i hate mondays oh ha ha lasagna no it's
actually it's hyper specific about like whatever is like the fucking gaming news du jour of the
week or whatever that like like you said you have to fucking read the text post that goes along with
it and even then it's still not funny it's just like oh okay i guess i get what they were trying to
say and the other thing about it is that like half of them are not even about like being gamers
anymore not that this is necessarily bad but it's not really like even a gaming webcomic
entirely it's a lot of it is just about like being dads which is fine um but i don't know
it's not well i never um it's weird i honestly never was that big of a fan of the comic i mostly
went to the website to read tyco's blog posts yeah it was a big inspiration to me as a writer
back in the day what are they what are they what are they doing now are they just like
streaming shit on twitch uh i don't know seems like that's most of what they do nowadays like um jerry
has the um jerry has like a a twitch show about like beer brewing or something and then they have
like a dnd group that also drinks the beer that they brew and they have a couple of like other
sites i think see i assume c team is still going i assume the comic is still going yeah of course
the comic is still going the comic will go forever even though it's like no even though nobody wants
it just just an uninertia it will continue until we're all dead um man penny arcade is such a
fucking bizarre you know honestly lecture idea is like the penny arcade diaspora because it has
like it spawned so many like weird things that have just like spiraled out into his whole little
universe like the whole the whole child's play thing it's like it's like a big or was like a
really big thing for a while um yeah i remember that yeah i mean i assume it still goes on but
what always surprised me about penny arcade is uh how he got so popular that they started their own
gaming convention and now it's like one of the most popular gaming conventions almost up there
was a three it's it's wild and like the comic did not deserve any like it like it's not good enough
it's just it's just doesn't deserve all of this shit that like was created off the back of this
shitty gamer webcomic but i guess because the like the only alternative was control alt elite which
people hated more like it had to be these guys i guess i don't know oh my god man nice image
resolution i i can't find a bigger nice image resolution you got there god god all right
this this has um that guy with the glasses energy this whole thing that comic or like the
comic no no the yeah the things i'm looking at all of all of these panels and things are just sort of
like early internet but like would never thrive today sort of feeling
yeah they i mean i mean that's that's where it came from and like they have like to their credit
like they have used this platform to like delve into all kinds of other weird shit like
like side comics and like you know they've made like you know
pen and paper rpg modules and they've done like twitch shows and they started conventions and
they still these other projects and they do all this other fucking shit and like that's all well
and good and i think that's pretty cool it's just really funny that like the the content that spawned
it all is like totally unworthy of any of it it's i think maybe um i think maybe the only reason
they got popular is because they were one of the first ones probably yes yes usually how it is
yeah of course and i was one of the first uh retro review websites and i never got popular
so it was it was the fucking wild west back then the
oh god the trenches is still going i think i remember what that is but i forgot i remember
but i forgot i just who who reads the trenches who is this for christ
honestly when i see this like gives me a sort of like terror like i'm imagining that there's like
there's some contingent of people out there who do who actually read penny arcade for the comics
keep up with the comics read fucking the trenches read um um what's the other one that uh
i don't know vg cats like i'm just thinking of like other things that have like i don't know
anything else that fucking like scott curtz does you know and then like i get it i get like the
heebie jeebies when i think it's it's almost like i'm staring like into like the deep like the ocean
and it's like some like i think i just uh for some people it's lovecraft it's lovecraftian it's
feels lovecraftian that there's like a whole there's a whole there must there must the existence
the continued existence of the trenches implies to me that there is an entire universe of like
people and culture out there that is totally alien to me who i can never understand and they
will never understand me and i'm afraid of them i think it's just uh for some people it just
becomes a tradition you know you just yeah don't stop that's true i guess that's true i
guess that's true and i have done that before i have like read stuff like just out of tradition
just like but i have i have long since abandoned all such traditions i don't keep up with anything
anymore uh i can't relate to anyone that does uh i don't know all right you move on to the next
voicemail yeah many do we have left uh it's not that many uh we have um what was that that one was um
one two three four we have seven left okay so it's oh my okay lol hopefully they're all short ones
that was the most paramount of reminders so the next one is called wait um the next one is called uh
last year on the pcp three two one go oh and while i'm here apologies for the ass phone mic quality
i'm in my bed didn't feel like getting up i don't care another thing you guys uh still don't have an
about section on your channel it still says under construction don't know if you guys want to do
anything about that but i thought it would be a good reminder to us all that the channel's got
hacked about a year ago um it didn't used to say under construction i know that it says under
construction i think like i asked Nate about that at some point and he said that no that wasn't
because of the hack but i'm not sure maybe it is i don't remember what was there on that before i
don't really look at the channel itself the about page but i guess we could fill it in with like
pcp is a thing under construction is like a pretty cringe thing for it to say honestly
yeah that's the kind of thing that websites from 2001 would have on their front page
was it was it a year ago that it got hacked was it that long i think so
hmm wow i'm trying to think of the the situation because we got the channel back or like some of
the channel's back so it was like not all of once that it was resolved and garlach house still
haven't uh he still hasn't paid for this uh injustice has he brad yeah brad garlach house
we'll take we'll take him to court he's he's being litigated as we speak um okay next one is called
cute anime girl three two one go
yeah gotcha
that's what they sound like
yep nice nice all right sick i like this one because uh it was short
yeah encounter blessings okay next one is called tommy j ben's physics sim game thing
it's not my game it's called noita other people play it okay three two one go
hey it's tommy j so uh the game that ben is referring to the like browser game with the the
the physics sim is called a powder game oh it is on the gamble website and there's also a mobile
version i highly recommend it because it's fucking free and uh it's great to pass time if you're like
the what what i used it for is i would be sitting there are other watch lecture there are variant
versions that other people still and listen to somebody talk even if i am paying attention to
what they're saying so i would just pull out my phone or my laptop because you can do that in
college and i would just set up some metal bowls and put water that would infinitely
respawn at the top and just watch the water eat through the metal bowls by resting them
and that's just watch that the whole time and uh and i barely passed my classes that semester
so maybe i'm not as good at multitasking as i thought okay but uh i had fun i guess this is
not this is not the one i was thinking of i have seen others that are different from this one this
is fun i'm playing it right now yeah me too i just i just put some oil on the floor and then
shot a laser into it and it's like it's making all this weird shit happen that's cool whoa bird
wait bird magma oh shit magma on ice what's gonna wait you can uh you can just pull your phone out
in college in class why didn't anyone tell me about that okay bird is just like bird is really weird
okay i'm just gonna i'll make a glass enclosure and just fill it with bird and then i'll just
put a torch in the bird no no no i'll put a bomb wait nothing's happening i'll put cloud no thunder
what's nothing this nothing's nothing's going on um okay magma
uh what is uh dude wind with cloud makes it all sort of do stuff wait like nothing is nothing
is working now like nothing that i put down is is happening maybe you can maybe i overloaded the
maybe there's like a pixel limit okay i'm gonna reload um okay s ball oh it's super bouncy ball
oh whoa look at it go oh can you uh can you actually learn physics with this
no no definitely not definitely not oh oh dude put some gas and then light it on fire
there's another one that is like a bigger screen and it's like it's got materials in it that are like
like you know uranium and like plutonium and you can you like electrons and positrons and like you
know neutrons and stuff and and neutrinos and uh and there's like mystery materials that will do
like weird like rainbow explosions and stuff if you combine them in certain ways uh oh firework oh you
put oh you put down some firework and then drop some magma on it that's pretty cool that's pretty
cool right there oh the pump is pretty cool it drags things along its thing okay now we're just
playing a video game yeah now we're yeah yeah yeah this has become a let's play okay i yeah i think it
i think it just um there's like a limit for how many things you can put on the screen and it
eventually just like stops you from putting more so that explains uh everything okay yeah yeah enough
enough but anyway uh was it called powder game yeah powder game that's one of them anyway um
next one is called uh Tommy J Ben's physics sim game thing ps uh wait there we go okay three two one
go forgot to mention a powder game is the browser version is not in flash it works some other way
so it still works it is not broken even though flash has died kind of based based based it works in
some other mysterious manner uh maybe it's html maybe it's html uh next one is called gas lighting
more like gas lighting but to gas means fart now
there it is okay three two one go why is it called gas lighting like i i know what it means and i see
it all the time but like i have to manually reach into my brain to find the definition every
single time i see it just because like i the name and that definition i think it's i think it's from
like my head because like what why is it what's just have is to have some analogy with like physical
using gas no to light something how am i supposed to know how that works i'm an e-boy in the age
we need a new gas lighting that is just the same thing but with a different name for the new generation
sending this voicemail was a really roundabout way to just google it but uh from wikipedia the
term originated from the british play gas light 1938 performed as angel street in the united
states and its 1940 and 1944 film adaptations um term originates in the systemic psychological
manipulation of a victim by her husband and patrick hamilton's play gas light in the story
the husband attempts to convince his wife and others that she is insane the play's title
alludes to how the abusive husband slowly dims the gas lights in their home while pretending
nothing has changed okay so in the in the play this is a lay epic reference oh that's that's very
oddly specific in the play he tries to convince her she's crazy by doing some weird shit with the
lights and so that's where the play gets its name from and the term gets its name from the play so
there you go so the the term references a play that nobody has seen in modern modern times
probably more people know it from the term probably by a wide margin i would think
oh but that's okay sometimes things are just like that uh okay next i'm stretching okay next
voicemail is called um tommy j ben's crush three two one go yeah i hope i'm not the only one who
caught this uh ben is like trying to explain all these stupid little like running voicemail gags
and stuff like that to fucking this double cast person ben you're just like me you're the cute one
now ben i caught you you're so excited so excited to explain all this dumb shit to this guest i caught
you what does that mean how does it feel ben you're the cute one now what does it mean what does it
mean i think i think they're they're saying they caught you out um being excited to to like share
something with someone and that's cute i just i just didn't want manner i don't know whether
they mean in like a flirty way or not i'm not sure yeah i'm not yeah okay if it's cute that i'm like
trying to that i'm like explaining something that i'm like interested in i guess that would make
sense but this voicemail is called ben's crush who's my crush is in double cursed i guess i don't
think so maybe it's crushed as in you were crushed you think he crushed me with this voicemail
and he crushed you with facts and logic hmm hey fuck fuck you tommy j i'm not the cute one
i'm not a cute one i am that's like the second voice that i've been crushed by facts and logic
a couple times in these but this is the last one by the way this is uh the last voicemail we
is called tommy j why is education a cable package um okay three two one go why is college a cable
package why do i have to take fucking art classes and history and shit i mean the classes didn't
suck or anything but they weren't i wouldn't have bought them on their own because i can just
look at the internet and learn things like i mean the history class it took it's kind of cool
i read a bunch of fucking primary sources which never did in high school that's like awful that the
only primary source you read in high school history class is like the constitution and the declaration
and maybe the guettysburg address and that's like it like they talked about fucking magna
card and shit all the time in high school i don't know a single word of that thing that's kind of
bad why is education a cable package why do i have to buy all of this shit that i do not want
i want the fucking database classes and the fucking software practice and uh operating
systems i do not want fucking um music theory the music theory class is fine too but i would not
have fucking paid for it on its own um and then and then communications and gender still
wasn't as bad as i expected it to be but it just it's just why why okay first off i feel like you
went a little off the rails there first you're like why is it a cable package why do i have to get all
this other stuff and then you're like oh but they didn't teach me about the magna carta well so i mean
it sounds like so you want your education to be broader but ignore ignoring that um okay like
without without defending like the business model of private universities too hard i i will defend
like okay if you just want to understand like operating systems and databases i feel like there
are like degrees and certifications you can get like an associate's degree or or some kind of
certification course for that uh you can go to a career school they have schools for that yeah if
you're if you're um if you're going to college for your bachelor's degree like that is a like yeah
you have a like a focus you have a major or whatever um but like the point of a liberal arts
education is not just i mean you know just despite what people say right i know some people are like
uh you know fucking oh this fucking uh bullshit liberal arts stuff like oh gender studies like
whatever you know despite all that like the point of a liberal arts education like a bachelor's degree
is to like create like a well educated population and to give you like a broad education like the
point is to make you a well educated person in general not just to prepare you for the workforce
and i know i know that it's kind of fucked up and to make you well rounded i think is what you mean
yeah i know that it's kind of fucked up because like even just for the purpose of getting a job
you're expected to have this like broad education this bachelor's degree or whatever that includes
all this like tertiary liberal arts stuff and like yeah i agree that that's fucked up but like
in in theory that's what the purpose of a degree like that is and so i understand it uh
uh it's uh it's a weird it's a weird sort of the wires that get get crossed there where like
jobs jobs require this like jobs expect this like broad and non-specific education
and therefore and therefore job seekers get this broad education but then people are like oh this
education is too broad because we don't need it to get a job but like it wasn't meant to be for
the job in the first place but it like became that due to like cultural expectation and the
fucking private university business model i don't know i think uh most of college is just a scam to
get you pay money but um well the weird thing is uh because you mentioned private universities but
the weird thing is even public universities feel like they're just trying to scam you into
getting your money a lot of the time i mean yeah okay yes you have to spend hundreds of
dollars on books that don't shouldn't cost that much and then spend like a hundred and fifty
dollars on a calculator from texas instruments because that's the only calculator that your math
class is going to accept i mean true uh yeah i'm not trying to i'm not trying to defend any of that
yeah i mean there's a whole lot of bullshit with it but like okay if this question is about like
why do i have to study all this other stuff in addition to what you know i want to get my degree in
that's why it's because like i don't know i think the answer is pretty simple was originally intended
to be more than just a a specific a job specific like training program i think the answer is pretty
simple it's uh money they want you to spend money that's what it comes out my answer is my answer is
better my answer is more cynical yeah it's shorter and but i'm i'm trying i'm trying to see uh
don't don't cast me don't cast me as the as the as the as the fucking private college
apologia guy that's not where i want to be don't make me defend these monsters but that's like
where the idea comes from yeah but maybe that idea was manufactured by them just to make you spend
more money no it's it's older it's older than that it's an older idea than that it comes from like
it comes from like old ideas of like what a classical education should be and the you know
you know like the kinds that like fucking like aristocrats would get not because they need a job
because they don't need a job because they'll just fucking live off their family holdings
or whatever just based on like i don't know Hellenistic ideas of like truth and beauty and
shit you know but doesn't that still come to the whole rich versus poor thing
i mean that is a a thing maybe it's just an invention of the rich from the very beginning
huh what my answer is who cares i fuck you fuck both of you i was playing powder game
it's so much more interesting i'll fucking kill you i'll fucking kill you
dude i've i've i've planted seeds oh no they're burning
i i didn't realize scenes what is this uh animal crossing
fuck fuck powder game i'm gonna go play the better version of powder game it's called noita
because it has like machine gun ones and spells and and bombs and shit and laser beams um machine
gun ones then i have to play it for sure it goes yeah it goes um i'm gonna play a better version
of that which is phoenix right no please oh we all we all know that phoenix is always right
die all right i fucking hate i fucking hate the pro crassonators podcast patreon.com slash the
procrastinators pro crassonators podcast we we should get uh i'm gonna complain i'm gonna
complain in the general chat about who should be making these fucking mp3s that's elisar's job
right is it i don't know if it is it might not be um but i'm gonna tell elisar the better
fucking do that or i'll kill him uh and then we will get we'll get a fucking mp3s for your bonus
episodes you don't have to watch them on youtube uh and hopefully we can get that ad-free experience
i think i'm on the latest bonus episode right yes at least until oh my oh my god i've made
like a stable vortex i don't even know what's going on that's actually pretty awesome this looks
like a scene of a murder crime mystery a murder crime as opposed to a different type of murder
you are on the latest bonus episode at least until elisar gets that uh that the bonus uh
content cut content episode done i thought it didn't make sense but murder crime does make
sense as a thing to say this looks very rsck this looks very rsck core what is all that green
shit it's it's like i put seeds and then ants and the ants built from the seeds and they built in
all directions and then something caught fire and now there's a vortex swirling of the the vines
are constantly growing and the fire is constantly putting them out and flying up so the green
so the green is vines the red is ants the red is magma or something or fire okay i thought the
green was slimes i mean i wanted it to be but i guess it's seeds well i put seeds and vines
and then ants and i guess the vines constantly grow so they like nobody this is like a stalemate
entropy will run out in the end no one no one can win in this in the battle in the battle of war
what is the war between like magma magma and seeds it's a complete the two most powerful forces
yeah if you play pokemon then uh that's the case i guess
uh dude it's so mesmerizing patreon.com slash the procrastinators send us a voicemail
at speakpipe.com slash pcp voicemail uh go check out gamers tavern uh check out his new uh check
out chrono's new uh uh uh the metal gear no mega man for mega man zero for video um thanks for
thanks for listening uh anything else before we fucking die no okay good night
oh thank you
goodbye