Hello! Welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. What? Craig. And immediately Craig craps out.
That's fine. We don't need him.
That's a good way to start an episode.
Craig is like, no, I won't record. Fuck you, Craig. All we need is me, Ben Saint, and my
good friend, Gamers Tavern here.
Uh, what's long, hard, wet, and full of semen? A submarine.
Oh, God. God. Um, Gamers Tavern. I was, uh, last night, I went on the, uh, the podcast
Shreddit. And, uh, this was a guy, a guy, Pyro, who I, who I knew from the Minecraft
stream, uh, and he introduced me to, uh, Murilogic, that fucking moron.
Oh yeah, I know who that is. Uh, it's the Wonderbred guy, right?
Murilogic is the Wonderbred guy. Um, but that's-
Yeah, I saw you did a, uh, episode with him. I haven't listened to it yet.
Everyone, everyone hated him. And, and, and for good reason.
Yeah, I looked at the comments.
Lamal.
And, uh, people didn't seem too happy about it.
Very funny. Very amusing, uh, uh, to me. The plan worked perfectly. Um, uh, uh, uh,
but I went on, uh, yeah, that guy, Pyro, uh, he has his podcast Shreddit. It's not only
his, there are other people, whatever. I went on Shreddit and we talked about adultery.
We went on r slash adultery and we read tales from adulterers that wanted to post online
about their adultery. And you just reminded me of the, one of the stories that I was particularly
aggrieved by, and I'll sum it up for you here. The story basically went, man who is
cheating on his wife, goes to the grocery store and gets a call from his wife and the
wife says, honey, pick me up an avocado. And he says, what kind? And she says, a big hard
one. And he smirks, uh, impishly and says, uh, well, he's like, I'm gonna, I'm going
to amuse my wife who remember I have been cheating on for years now, but I'm gonna,
I'm gonna give her a treat. She, she, she's earned a treat. So I'm gonna give her, I'm
gonna show her a good time. And he says, I got a big hard one for you right here. And
his wife, who obviously loathes him, obviously detests this man and cannot fucking stand
to hear him say anything at all. She says, why would you say that? And he is like, I
can't believe that. Can't believe my joke didn't get appreciated. And then so he calls
up his, his mistress or in the parlance of R slash adultery, his AF or a fair partner.
And he says, Hey, sweetie, sweetie bushel, uh, if I said, if you, if you said, um, if
I said, I got a big hard one, a big hard one, what would you say? And she says, I got a
big hard one for you right here. And he says, Oh my God, this is why, this is why I cheat.
This is what it's all about. She's such a, such a free spirit, such a wonderful soul.
You know, she's got such a, such a glowing sense of humor. She understands me. We get
each other. She appreciates me. This woman appreciates you. Not like my, not like my
dumb wife, who hates me for who, for who have been cheating on for decades and hates me
for some reason. You know, this woman gets me and thank you are slash adultery for getting
me this woman who appreciates my biting wit. But that's what I need. Anyway, I'm saying
that you are this man. Yeah, pretty much. It's not true. It's not true. You're, you're
a man of good, outstanding moral character, gamers tavern. And I know that because you
are here now on the podcast with me, unlike everyone else who has abandoned their posts,
left me to defend the Alamo against the arm of a single cannon. I basically say it.
Come and take it. I say another solo then cast it. I guess it would have been another
solo been cast. Um, we had, we, other people were supposed to be here. We even had another
guest lined up. There was another guest who was supposed to come on this week and just
nobody's here. And, and, and I, I, I do not understand it, but it's okay. We're gonna,
we're gonna be fine. All right. This, the show must go on.
Well, maybe eventually it's just going to be just us running the entire thing.
God, I hope so. I hope so. It's squatters rights. You know, if nobody, if nobody shows
up to the podcast for long enough, it becomes our podcast.
Uh, yeah, that's, that's my understanding. That's the rule. That's why you basically
run the show now because Nate doesn't show up anymore, right?
Um, basically,
you know, it's funny because, um, the first time I was on in 2018, I believe it was Nate
who invited me on.
Hmm. I think that's sound, that's probably right.
And, uh, back then I didn't know who he was or I didn't know anything about the PCP itself.
So is, um, I had to do a lot of research before I came on back then.
Oh yeah. Oh yeah. He had to dig up all our skeletons.
But I did, um, I didn't know, uh, of you had to, had to make sure none of us had ever
said the N word.
Yeah.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry we disappointed you.
You couldn't do it.
I did know about you and, um, uh, Jesse and, uh, Gib before I was on, but I didn't know
that you three knew each other and that you all did a podcast together. That's, uh, I
discovered later.
You knew me and Jesse and Gib.
Yeah, I knew you from Twitter.
Oh yeah.
You followed me on Twitter and you tweeted stuff.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I knew Gib and Jesse because they left comments on my videos and I checked out their channels
back then.
I never, I never leave comments on videos.
Almost, I almost never do that.
I don't really do that either anymore.
Yeah. Twitter though. I'll leave, I'll leave a comment on Twitter.
Oh, I'll, I'll leave a reply thread on Twitter.
Yeah, I see. I've been pretty active on Twitter.
I've been too active on Twitter.
It fucking sucks.
Hey, you should probably, uh, uh, hold back on that.
Twitter is not, um, it's not too great of a place to spend all your time.
No, no, it's bad.
But I'm just so powerless in my life.
But you know, Twitter gives me the illusion that I can affect change.
Yeah. But I saw something kind of interesting about the Wonder Bread guy.
Um, because I looked at the comments of the video, uh, that you posted with him.
And most of the comments that mentioned him were pretty negative.
Yes.
But then on Twitter, uh, I think you tweeted or somebody tweeted the episode on Twitter.
And the comments on Twitter.
I did and did you did.
Right. So the, the comments on Twitter were actually pretty positive or neutral.
I hardly saw anything negative.
So, uh,
There were, there were a lot more comments than there were Twitter replies though.
Yeah.
But it was just interesting how, uh, on Twitter it was mostly positive and neutral.
And in your comments section, it was mostly negative.
The, the, I mean, there's, there's, you know, I don't, I don't want to go too hard on it
because I pretty much agreed with every comment from last, last week.
I was right.
I was right there with those commenters.
Like, yeah.
Yes.
Correct.
Um, but our comment section is, is a pretty negative place pretty often.
Yeah.
I'm surprised, you know, uh, I didn't get very, very many, many negative comments, uh,
both times that I was on.
We didn't, we get, uh, you know, it's fine.
It's not a problem.
But yeah, we get, we get a lot of, we get a lot of, we get a lot of good faith.
We get a lot of good faith criticism down in the comments.
We get a lot of people saying, uh, giving, giving us a helpful, helpful tips on how we
can improve the show.
Yeah.
Um, I remember, uh, one of the comments I read on, on the last episode I was on, they
were like, uh, oh yeah, that gamer's Taiwan guy back when the PSP used to be good.
Um, good old days.
Yeah.
The funny thing is back when I first was on in 2018, even back then I saw comments on
that episode that I was on that was like, uh, the PCP is on a downward spiral.
It's not as good as it used to be.
You know, even back then in the good old days.
Yeah.
You know, life is basically just one big decline into nothingness.
Well, if you want to look at it that way, I guess so.
And you know, that's just, you know, PCP is no exception.
Uh, yeah.
Although I do think, uh, sometimes people, uh, will, um, they will, they will have a better
opinion of the past than is actually realistic.
Yeah.
I mean, I think so for sure.
But, uh, as far as the PCP is concerned, they're probably, uh, correct this case.
Uh, uh, I mean, you know, when the, I mean, if anything was like more, uh, uh, exciting
in a way, everything, you know, novelty is just fun.
And so like just one of things newer, it's kind of just more exciting, like by default.
Uh, you know, what can you do?
Yeah.
That reminds me actually, um, I think that's the reason why, in my opinion.
Uh, the game groups are not good anymore.
Hmm.
Because I haven't watched the game group in forever.
Uh, when John was on the game groups, in my opinion, was pretty good.
And then when he left, it started to be less good.
But I don't think that's because of John leaving.
I think that's just because, um, the novelty wore off and they were no longer excited about
the project they were doing.
Uh, man, I don't know.
I listened to a bunch of game grumps.
Like, I think I listened to a bunch like pretty shortly post Dan swap.
Uh, so like the first game grumps I ever really listened to was a bunch of like early Dan.
And I thought that was pretty good.
And then I went back and I listened to John and Aaron.
And then I maybe listened to a little more Dan and I was like, yeah, this is good.
And then I just stopped listening because like, yeah, I get it.
Well, I checked out some of the newer episodes.
I go back every once in a while just to check on them because I used to like them a lot.
And now I find it really difficult to listen to the newest ones because you can kind of tell that both Aaron and Dan don't, uh, their hearts just not in it anymore.
That's a bummer.
That's not a good feeling.
They become like a typical nine to five job for them.
Yeah, I mean, how could it, how could it not?
I mean, that's literally what it is.
You can't do that for years and still care about it.
You must, you must settle into a routine at some point.
But I have to feign interest.
I have to pretend that they still are as into it as before.
Yeah, of course.
You know, for the sake of the audience.
For the sake of the audience.
But in my opinion, I don't know, this is controversial to say, but I think Dan should pull a John and leave Game Grumps and do his own projects.
I mean, Dan did his own projects before and I mean, some of them were kind of successful.
Because he has his own band.
Yeah, he's always had his own band.
Yeah, but I mean, imagine if he just did that full time instead of splitting his time between that and Game Grumps.
I mean, I kind of, he already kind of does both, doesn't he?
Yeah, but I would prefer to see him do more of the music stuff, which I think is better.
Because you're only one person, you can't do too much at a time.
It's like if he just focused 100% on the music, he could probably make more music and better music.
I mean, maybe, perhaps, perhaps.
As opposed to spending his time.
It's not necessarily the case that like, if he had more time to do it, that he would do more of it or make better.
I mean, it could just be that like, I don't know, maybe Game Grumps takes enough of his time that the amount that he's got left over is, you know, give or take the amount that he likes to spend on music.
And if he spent more time than that on music, it would be less productive, you know?
Yeah, I suppose that's a good point.
It's possible.
But I think that's why John claims to have left Game Grumps because he wanted more time to work on his own content.
So I'm just going by that logic.
But of course, that might have not been why he left.
No, I don't think so.
No, there was bad blood, right? There was bad blood.
Possibly. It's never been confirmed.
Yeah.
You know, I'm not a huge fan of like, Dan's music.
I'm not a big, I'm not a big Ninja Sex Party fan, honestly.
So I, you know, and I'm also not a big Game Grumps fan anymore.
So I guess I don't give a fuck what he does.
I actually do like Dan's music.
I think it's, it kind of reminds me of like a sign filmed if it was music.
It's my kind of humor.
I mean, I haven't listened to a ton of it.
I've listened to some and I thought, like back in the day, I heard the Unicorn Wizard one and I was like, that's pretty funny.
And then I've heard, you know, other songs since then.
And usually I'm like, okay, it kind of feels the same.
I guess it's true that it's all kind of themed after a similar thing.
But there are a couple of songs he's done that I really like.
One of them for obvious reasons is I think it's called Objects of Desire.
And it's basically all puns.
Objects of Desire. Okay.
It's the entire song is puns.
So obviously I'm a huge fan.
Can you, can you, can you give us a sample?
What are some good lines?
I didn't memorize any of the lines, unfortunately.
I memorized my own stuff, but I don't memorize other people's stuff.
Okay.
All right.
I know you're shy.
I get it.
It's fine.
You don't know.
I just don't legitimately don't remember.
I think there is one line in it because every, every song he does has a plot kind of.
Yeah.
So the plot is that he moved in with, with this new girlfriend he got.
And then he reveals the secret that he's having sex with all her objects.
And all the puns are based on that.
So I think there's one that's like, I'm going down on your stairs, which is.
Okay.
Great.
And that's pretty good.
I'm slamming your door.
All right.
Okay.
So that's, that gets the official gamer's tavern seal of approval.
Yeah.
That sounds about right.
All right.
That's reasonable.
And I think another song that he did that I really like just because of how absurd it
is.
It's like the, the story of it is funny.
And it sounds pretty good too, but it's like a story where he sets up a woman's rights
seminar or something like that.
And by giving them in solidarity, you know, empowerment, empowering messages.
But the thing is the empowering message he gives them is just that they can do him, you
know.
Hmm.
Yeah.
If they, if they work hard enough someday, they'll get to be able to sleep with a ninja
sex party.
Very nice.
And then that's true.
They all get really upset and grossed out and start to leave.
So it's unbelievable.
The audacity.
Yeah.
So it's that kind of a, it's basically just in my mind is like the George Costanza
relationship comedy, but in musical band form.
You know, many trying to go after women and striking out in funny ways and coming up with
elaborate schemes to, to get with women.
I kind of like that story story of my life.
Yeah.
I kind of like that type of comedy.
Did you ever listen to starbomb?
Yeah, I listened to it.
You must have.
What did you think of it?
I thought the first album was all right.
It had a couple of catchy songs.
And I thought the second one was pretty underwhelming and I didn't listen to it much.
I wasn't.
I thought I listened to the first one a ton either.
I thought, I thought it was all fine, but I wasn't really that into it.
Yeah.
Which is ironic because I'm supposed to be in the gamers tavern.
I was, I guess, you know, this, like it came out like at the time, the first one came out
like when I was sort of into listening to gamers tavern or law.
Who would listen to gamers tavern?
Nobody.
When I was listening to, when I was listening to a fucking, a fucking game grumps.
Yes.
Game grumps.
So I was like obligatorily.
Okay.
They put an album.
Gotta go check the album out.
And I did.
Okay.
This is fine.
All right.
And I don't remember any of the songs.
And there's the one that's about Street Fighter and there's maybe a Castlevania one.
Yeah.
I don't remember any of the specific songs, but I vaguely recall one I think about Final
Fantasy seven or Metal Gear Solid.
Maybe it was a mixture of all those games and one song.
Oh, there's, there's one that just, there's one that just like goes from like game to
game to game.
Right.
It's just like a bunch of, you know, it's weird, but I have trouble these days enjoying
gaming content.
I'm not really, I'm just not into gaming based content on YouTube as much anymore.
I am, I think I could listen to, I have an endless appetite for long videos of some guy
explaining why Sonic Adventure 2 is good.
Specifically that one game.
That sounds, and I've never even played it.
I don't know why.
Sounds kind of like Cyber Shell.
Um, I mean, yeah, he, he, yeah, but he's like, he's, I mean, he's far from the only one.
There's a whole cottage industry of video, long videos where some guy explains why Sonic
Adventure 2 is a good video.
I didn't realize that was such a big industry.
It is.
There's, um, maybe I should make one.
I don't know.
King K had one.
Running, Running Shine did one.
The Cyber Shell did one.
I've heard of King K, I think.
King K's fine.
He's fine.
Um, he's the guy, he's the guy he's always like, and I certainly hope you have some well-deserved
fun today.
Well, that's nice of him.
At the end of every, at the end of every Krug Smash video, Krug, Krug Smash ends his,
his videos with, until next time, you bearded bastards.
And then he, and he whistles and I can't whistle.
But their voices are like kind of the same tone.
So sometimes he'll say that sometimes I think he'll gonna say, uh, until next time you bearded
bastards, I certainly hope you have some well-deserved fun today.
Whip, whistle.
Uh, and he never does it.
Uh, he never does.
Uh, it's fucked up.
Well, um, uh, I had a, it's kind of weird how I have such a disdain for gaming content
nowadays online, considering, um, you know, I'm, uh, running a gaming thing.
Yeah.
But, um.
Well, I mean, I don't read comics or anything.
And I guess I like make them or something.
I used to, I don't know.
I guess we have a lot in common.
Yeah.
I just hate art.
I hate all human endeavor, actually.
Yeah, same.
Well, you can just drop endeavor and just leave human.
Yeah, that too.
Sure.
It's different.
No, humans are good.
No, no, I like humans.
No, no, no.
I'm a pro human.
I'm a pro human, but I just wish they would stop doing, doing things.
You're a little bit more optimistic than I am.
If they would just quit doing shit, everything would be fine.
Uh, it looks like, it looks like Cheesy is trying to join.
I don't know if he's going to join.
I guess they'll just join late.
It's fine.
I'm fine with whatever.
We should, we should, we'll let, we'll let them in.
It's fine.
It's, uh, it's your boat that you're running on here.
It is my boat.
It's my boat.
And, and what I, and what I say goes, um, man, what did I do?
I just, I just listened to, no, I fucking watched gaming content.
The other day I was watching, uh, I watched a bunch of Jim Sterling and I made myself
sad thinking about what if Jim Sterling died like total biscuit.
Well, I used to watch a Jim Sterling occasionally in the past and, uh, I think it's pretty good.
Uh, I guess.
I don't know what he does.
I really like him a lot.
I just like people with British accents.
Yeah.
I mean, I get that.
I try, I try not to let it, I try not to let it persuade me.
I'm also a big fan of Yahtzee.
Jim doesn't really have like a smart British accent.
Jim has like a dumb British accent.
Uh, so it doesn't count.
Uh, cheesy welcome.
You've, you've, you, you, you arrived here.
I'm fucking here.
Oh my God.
You're on a pro crass news podcast.
Yeah.
I was running, I woke up late in my hotel bed, um, cause I showed up to New England and
then my taxi was running late and I showed up to the PCP HQ building.
There's, there's security guard out in the front and he was, he was hassling me.
I'm like, no, I'm a guest on today's episode and he's like, I have no idea what the fuck
you're talking about.
It was a, it was a whole ordeal.
I left my, I left my VIP pass in my other clown pants.
Yeah.
No, I left it back at the hotel and then when I drive back and I call Ben and I interrupted
him while they were recording another episode and he had to come down and explain to the
security guard for me to be let inside the building.
It was fucking, it was fucking ordeal.
No benefits.
Clown.
Well, two hyenas were eating a clown and one says to the other, does this taste funny to
you?
Oh my God.
Cheesy.
Yeah.
Your response?
Um, my response are the, is one of the clowns like a, is one of the hyenas a female?
Uh, possibly.
Okay.
Well, she, um, she grows her giant hyena penis and she says, shut the fuck up bitch.
And it fucks him.
Yeah.
Which is very, which is very accurate to hyena.
You know, hyena, you know, hyena biology, uh, gamer tavern.
Uh, not really.
Uh, the female hyena like in growth, like her clitoris grows massive, like the size of
a penis.
She knots him.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
I think I have heard of this from somewhere.
I'm not sure why.
Yeah.
It's, it's kind of crazy.
I wish humans could do that.
It's kind of based.
Like really get right.
It's kind of unfair that God gave like animals all the cool dicks and we got, we got the
lame dicks.
We know human dick is pretty fucking sick.
No, I'm gonna, I'm gonna stick my neck out for human dick.
I don't know.
Cheesy.
Have you ever tried a human dick?
It kind of, it kind of changes your world.
And you know, the best, the best human dick circumcised baby.
Whoa.
See, this is why I was brought on.
This is why I brought on because I am the elusive, uncircumcised guest.
Finally, I am here, right?
Fuck off.
No, wait, we don't.
Okay.
Here's the thing.
I didn't really want to argue about this.
I'll just say one fucking Gentile.
I'll just say one statement.
I just want to make one statement.
All right.
Okay.
So, so it's, it's no, it's no rumor.
Ben, Ben circumcised confirmed, right?
Sad but true.
Right.
Um, but, and Ben circumcised, um, there's only two vapors books.
Hmm.
Cheesy, uncircumcised, there's a, there's four chapters of villain verse.
What?
That's crazy.
Numbers don't lie.
That's just not right.
Yeah, exactly.
Like, um, yeah, in my foreskin, that's where I keep the extra chapters of villain verse.
Did I forget to buy chapter three?
I don't know.
And four.
Um, something.
You got one and two.
Uh, four is not out yet, actually.
It's going to be.
Okay.
I may have forgotten to buy number three.
Hopefully it's out by today.
Actually, wait, you're a patron.
So you get a number three for free.
Am I a patron?
Yeah.
You're a patron of my Patreon.
I'm pretty sure.
That's, that's fucking epic.
Yeah.
If you go to fucking epic.
If you go to my Patreon is probably one of the last or third posts.
The only thing I post on the Patreon anymore is a villain verse chapters.
So you're going to get number four for free.
Hopefully by Friday, which is today, right?
By the time this comes out.
Uh, yes.
This will be coming out on Friday.
And it would also be the last day to pre-order your own physical copy of villain verse.
That's right.
It's on sale.
Links in the description.
We fill out your form.
Link in the description.
You get your own.
Shouldn't we try to explain who the guest is to the viewers in case somebody doesn't know?
Um, oh, um, yeah, we should probably that's smart.
That's smart.
I guess I just assumed that people know cheesy cheesy Manfredo is, uh, is, uh, the cloud is
a clown.
Uh-huh.
That is me.
I am the one more.
What more is there to say?
Um, I've been, uh, I've been Pete.
I'm, I'm what the cool kids like to call PCP adjacent.
Right.
So there's, yeah.
Yeah.
And author and author of, and author of monkey Jones favorite webcomic, uh, Bongo and Luna.
Bongo.
Yeah.
Monkey Jones did say when monkey Jones and, uh, I think he interviewed, uh, Pickle.
Rhee.
You guys remember Pickle.
God.
Of course.
That was like three years ago.
Um, on that video, we interviewed Pickle.
Rhee at the end.
He expresses his love of Bongo and Luna.
I, I totally did not pay him, uh, 15 bucks to say that.
I did.
I did not do that.
And the notion is, yeah.
What kind of asshole like markets their comic with money?
I've, I can't.
I don't know anyone who does that.
Yeah.
Let me like a piece of shit, dude.
Agreed.
A real, a real artist.
A real artist is on Twitter talking about how much depression they have and how much.
Oh, I wish I could make a comic.
I'm so depressed.
That's it.
That's how you really market your webcomic.
That's the best way.
Cause it, cause it's related.
It's related.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Well, this person has depression.
I'm going to check out their comic.
Oh, wait.
They don't got one.
This person's just like me.
They suck.
Let me see what they make.
I am, um, hot take.
I don't have depression.
So it's, it's kind of a struggle for me to promote my webcomic.
That's fucked up.
Yeah.
I can't relate to the masses.
Wait, you don't?
That's weird.
Yeah.
I was, I was born, I was born different, if you will.
Um, uncircumcised, if you will.
And I think that probably like affected me not having depression.
It's crazy.
Yeah.
That's a good point.
Exactly.
I was, I, unfortunately, tragically, I was born depressed,
circumcised and vaccinated.
So, you know, the deck was stacked.
The deck was, it was a hat trick.
Well, I'm not perfect either.
I'm vaccinated as well.
So, you know, not everyone's perfect.
Then it's okay.
I'm still, I'm no God.
Ben, I am human as you too.
I mean, if it helps, I was born, I was born brown in America.
And that's kind of like how cute.
That's like kind of having a deep, a deep up in America.
You know, if you're straight and white, that's like a might as well.
You're like, um, what would be a perfect word?
You're already like ahead of us.
Like a, you know, you're like, um, it's like, that's like your,
that's like you got the world of Warcraft, uh, uh, like a demo pack
and they give you like the XP boosts, you know, so you level up faster.
Yeah.
You know, the first 20 levels like that.
Yes.
You get those first 20 levels for free.
Straight white boys get that bonus XP pack.
But if they turn trans, um, because the wow hates trans people,
they're like, ooh, yeah, sorry.
We're going to take those back, my guy.
Fun fact.
You know, it's just, uh, it's just, uh, it's just the way the world, you know,
where there's nothing, nothing for it.
It's just, it's just, uh, immutable law of the universe.
I think I was also easy come easy go.
I was also brought on this episode to kind of balance it out from last episode.
Because, um, you guys, you guys have like a Nazi as a guest in the last episode.
And then out there in PCPHQ, they were like, oh, now we got to bring a lefty,
you know, to balance it out.
And I'm very, I'm very left.
Fringe, fringe.
At least, um, nobody can accuse you of having an echo chamber now.
Exactly. Exactly.
I'm the opposite of echo chamber.
I purposely try to like make tweets that piss off people.
So I get a bunch of like people shitting on me.
Right.
And I'm like, finally different opinions.
This podcast is already communist propaganda.
True. True that.
That's just, that's just the way I like it.
You're welcome.
I mean, in the previous episode, you apparently had somebody who wasn't a communist.
Well, you can't, well, you can't win.
Well, Ben brought him on.
And if you have seen, if you've seen the last episode, you don't have to watch it.
I'll run it down for you.
Ben had an epic debate against murder logic and he explained to him why he should stop
being a Nazi.
He should stop being a right winger.
He explained to him why, why the Mr. Medeker conspiracy theory is fake and he shouldn't
believe Mr. Medeker and then murder luck.
Yeah.
There's a calm and reasonable discussion about it.
We all, we all, we all coolly, you know, we, without prejudice laid out the facts on
the table and examined them thoroughly and came, and came to the only logical.
It sounds amazing.
I should have, I should have listened to it.
Yeah.
And then murder logic is like, Ben, you're right.
For now on, I'm only commissioning POC women feeding the, feeding the poor.
That's my fetish now.
No.
POC women feeding the poor.
He, he, he wouldn't like, he wouldn't like that because.
No, but you convinced them because you, you explained, he convinced him to stop being
a Nazi and he's like, you're right, Ben.
And then his fetish were, went in reverse.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Good.
Yeah.
All right.
It's like opposite land.
The only thing I know about him is the Wonder Bread stuff.
I don't know anything else about him outside of that.
He didn't, he didn't really, he didn't really go into, he didn't really go into like things.
He'd just say, what if one thing he would say every now and then would give a pretty,
he's like, okay, I see where this goes.
If you're a high bread tube consumer like me, if you're a big brain breadtuber.
You can see the signs.
Consumer.
Yeah.
You can catch what we in the industry like to call dog whistles.
You can smell it.
Yeah.
You can smell it on him.
God, while I was watching that episode, like the way he talked, I was thinking like, he
sounds like a dick show guest.
Like he has that cadence to it.
I mean, he, he literally was that.
Right.
I mean, I, I think I guessed that before you said that he was.
And I'm like, oh my God, this is crazy.
I think someone in the comments called it the white libertarian voice.
Yes.
And you know what?
I can think of, I can think of at least one other person who has the same voice.
And yeah, that's what it is.
That's what it is.
I think that's where I first learned of him.
I, I, um, I listened to a clip of him on the dick show, I think.
Because I don't, I don't listen to the dick show, but sometimes I, I watched the clips.
And I thought, wow, this guy is weird.
Yeah.
It is the internet.
He's weird and he's pretty annoying.
I'm not, I'm not surprised he exists.
I'm not.
No.
All right.
But, um, he's, um, he's a, he's a white kid dude.
Um, shout out to Murilogic.
Murilogic, it's capitalism.
That's the problem.
Shout out to Murilogic.
Murilogic, we'll have you back on the show anytime.
Murilogic, we love you.
Thanks for coming on the show.
You, you brightened our lives and our hearts.
I think it's, it's cool to have weird guests on every once in a while.
I agree.
Honestly, honestly, like, like the people complain, like, like the people complaining in the comments,
like, I understand not liking Murilogic, but I don't see why that's a bad thing.
Like, why is, other than the fact that his story was really long anyway.
That's how, that's how you tell shows.
That's how you tell stories on a dick show.
You got to tell them longer than they actually are.
Hey guys, what's going on?
Give and take.
There she is.
Are you recording?
Yeah.
Based.
How long have you been going?
40 minutes.
Oh, no problem.
Crazy.
I was just, I was just busy with a little thing called shirking my responsibilities and not looking at anything at all.
You didn't tell, you didn't tell Cheesy when we record.
I was going to do that.
Well, when?
Well, you know.
You know, after the episode was over.
No.
Nice.
Before the episode, look, I just didn't turn on my computer all day and I was having fun with family.
So that's my bad.
Frankly, that's despicable.
Step first mistake you live with your family.
That's a no-no.
It's the holidays.
It's the December time.
Wow.
Fucking Europeans.
Fucking Europeans all living with family.
You should be like Americans and bootstrap your ways out into a house with like seven other dudes that you've never met before.
Unironically, that is, I'm literally living in a house with seven other dudes right now.
Good.
You know what?
I'm living the Ben St. lifestyle.
It's nice except.
It's going to be kind of a full house.
It's nice except when I decide that I want some fried chicken at one in the morning and I tenderize the meat in the kitchen
and it's so loud that it wakes people up and they all yell at me.
You know, except for that, it's good.
I mean.
It's good, I promise.
That's every house.
Unless you're completely alone.
Yeah.
Well, you know what?
Fuck I'm Ben.
You know, you want some fried chicken?
All the fried chicken places are closed at one.
How are you going to get fried chicken?
You got to make it, you know?
You got to make it.
Yeah, exactly.
And God forbid it not be tenderized.
Yeah.
The Chad mood move is to just make the fried chicken and wake everybody up.
Fuck them.
Yeah.
That's exactly what I did.
I got to get all those gains.
And it was delicious.
Exactly.
You say gave or Tavern knows.
Yeah.
You know, it's about gains.
I haven't worked out in a week.
I'm such a fucking idiot.
I'm losing my gains actually.
I don't work out.
I'm going for it.
I had started working out.
I was doing pretty good, but I've fallen.
I've slipped.
I've slipped a little bit.
I haven't worked out this week.
It's bad.
I got to get back on it.
What do you usually do?
Where you work out, Regiment?
Squat.
A squat and just, it's just been squatting and benching.
Is your, is your, is your ass thick now?
Is it, is it big?
Is it, is it a big ass?
No.
It's normal.
Damn.
That sucks.
It's normal.
It's, it's.
It may come as a surprise, but I actually work out almost every single day now.
Nice.
What do you do?
What's your routine?
Everything.
I've got a schedule.
I do just 24 seven, just all muscles clenched all the time.
He's running right now as he's recording this podcast.
I wish, but I do like one day arms, one day legs, one day shoulders, you know, that kind
of thing.
Nice.
Do you do it in a gym?
I used to, but now, you know, because of COVID, I've been doing it at home.
I have a bunch of weights and stuff at home.
He's been doing it back at the tavern as his name implies.
Back of it.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
I was working out sort of quite consistently a while ago, but I stopped and then just continued
to stop.
Remember when Mary called you, remember when Mary called you a bitch boy?
Whoa, what the fuck?
That was something like that.
Yeah.
That was literally epic.
Whoa.
That was a world conjecture.
They didn't have any evidence to support their claims.
They didn't.
And they need evidence.
Yeah.
What was his marriage?
No, he's not real.
He's a Vtuber.
That's right.
They're not.
They're not human.
I don't consider them human.
No.
Danes neither.
Oh, exactly.
Especially the Danish.
Wait.
Is he Danish or is he Finnish?
He's Danish.
He's Finnish when I'm done with him.
That's right.
He's gonna make that joke.
Okay.
All right.
So I've come in late.
What have you already talked about?
We talked about, we talked about Game Grumps for a while.
We talked about gaming content on YouTube in general and how gamers have been
sick of it.
We talked about Villainverse and Bongo and Luna a little bit.
We talked about Circumstition, obviously.
I want to talk a bit about Bongo and the cheesy verse.
Oh, yeah.
What cheesy has been.
Because I've been following you on a few things and you have been pumping out
Villainverse pages and chapters.
Oh, yeah.
And it's quite impressive.
Incredible, in fact.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
Yeah.
So I guess people don't know me for the cheesy and the PCP lore goes way back when I made
a call that was made a voice call to the PCP where I was actually secretly shilling Bongo
over the whole time and Ben figured out dead, dead away.
And then I made another one because Ben recognized real.
He knows when someone's shilling.
Game recognizes games.
Exactly, right?
Like he saw that.
He's all like this mother.
Have you ever seen the ending of Nightcrawler?
No.
It's literally the ending of Nightcrawler.
I'm the Mexican within the car accident with the gun and Ben saying is a Jake Gyllenhaal
and it looks like I'm going to shoot a Ben say Jake Gyllenhaal, but I don't because I
recognize him as a psychopath just like me.
So, so basically after I pulled myself out of that car accident, I invited Ben onto my
podcast cheesy cast.
That was fun.
You should check that out.
It's the first episode of cheesy cast with Ben saying and it's kind of it's actually probably
perfect to watch it now because we're at the end of that podcast.
Ben says everything he's going to do up to this point.
Right.
So it's a good it's a good way to check to see if Ben went out and did all his promises.
Oh God, I probably did.
It was a good way to get tabs on him.
Yeah, you had tabs on Ben because he won't do it himself.
I can't I can't believe you got Ivy Adams on the cheesy cast.
That's so cool.
Oh yeah, that was extremely because I was talking to another Ivy Adams is the creator of a
comic called Pinky and Pepper.
Actually, you might like that.
I'll send you a I'll send you a link to it.
I bet you would like Pinky and Pepper.
Ivy Adams is so fucking cool.
Yeah, I love I love Ivy Adams.
She's a she's a cool person.
And um, no, she was really easy because I was talking to another friend of mine.
I was saying like, yeah, I'm going to email her right now and she's all like just DM her
and I'm like, what is like, yeah, if you DM her, she replies to anybody.
And then she showed me a screenshot of them just DMing them like a random thing and she
just replies.
And I'm like, oh, okay.
So I just yeah, I just DM there and it was it took a minute because she doesn't like
clowns.
I'm at this point.
I'm like, at this point.
Yeah, it's a struggle.
It's a handicap.
I got to live with, you know.
Yeah.
Furries their handicap, you know, a lot of people don't like furries.
I'm the same, you know, like I got the clown thing.
A lot of people don't like clowns, but getting up, but getting Ivy after moving past that
getting out was really cool.
But anyway, so at that point, I think I stopped doing bongo and Luna, which was like my slice
of life fetish comic on webtoon.
And yeah, it was pretty, it wasn't that fetish.
It's about it's not that fetishy.
It's like it's monster girls and clowns and there's some there's some kind of lewd humor
or some crude humor, I guess.
Yeah, it's a lot like it's not like a horny comic.
It's not too horny.
It's like it's kind of like it has there's a certain there's a dynamic.
So bongo is like the mature one and like Luna is like the horny one.
And that's basically the dynamic.
That's like the backbone of the whole series.
Right.
If you ever seen a, you ever seen a key and peel?
I mean, it's just a little bit.
I mean, besides can feel, I mean, like, have you ever just any like routine any comedy
bit?
There's always like the serious guy and the silly guy, you know, like that's a
Yeah, exactly.
That's cool.
That's called, I believe.
Not.
Yes, exactly.
Classic.
Yeah.
So that's basically bongo and Luna.
Right.
And it wasn't making me that much money.
No.
Because there's no money in comics.
That's unironically true.
Don't do, don't do comics if you want to make money.
If that's like your first goal, you're fucked.
Unless you're like Mary, whether it's just, it was just, um, it was just fucking wild.
It was just crazy.
It was off the chain and doing anything online unless you're super popular.
True.
Mary wither just has a compulsion to Mary withers brain is just wired so that he is
like, I think he just genuinely loves like, uh, uh, uh, like, Hey, what if this meme was
an anime girl?
Like, I think that's just what he likes.
This is a bread and butter.
And it just happens to be what like, it just happens to be like the perfect, like lowest
common denominator.
Like everybody can, can appreciate the appeal of it.
The most marketable thing in the universe.
I am.
I see him when I, when it was on the podcast, um, he said, like, like, I wanted to get him
on my podcast at one point, right?
But that, that hasn't happened because he hasn't accepted my friend request on discord.
I told him to.
Yeah.
I know.
And he said, and he said he would, he said he would.
Uh, it's been like months.
I guess it has.
Um, no, you should, you should just make a group chat and just add me into it or whatever.
Um, but anyway, it's just that I think, I think what's lucky about Mary wither is that
he had like the money to back him up to just get the first one done.
And he just had to kind of like, there's a certain, it takes an amount of, uh,
I started up capital startup capital and also some balls to do what he did because he,
like how he said, like, oh, I basically just like DM like over 200 artists and see who would buy.
Right.
Yeah.
Cause that's a, that's, that's crazy.
Cause I mean, that's like, I mean, logically, eventually someone's going to take the bay.
Right.
And, um, yeah, I think another thing with Mary weather is that I think he unironically likes
all that stuff.
Um, yeah, that's what I'm, that's what I'm saying.
Like that's, that's what he likes.
Yeah.
He's incredibly marketable.
He, um, he, I watch another interview with him that web tunes did, um, because there
was a couple of questions you guys didn't ask him.
And I was still like, and I was like, Oh, ask him these questions for my podcast.
But then I find that he answered these, uh, questions on other interviews.
And one of them, he said, like, someone asked him, where do you get your ideas from?
And then he said that he literally watches the first episode of every seasonal anime.
And then he just takes con, he just takes concepts.
And he's like, Oh, I can explore this concept.
And I'm like, that explains so much because all of this stuff just feels like seasonal
anime.
That's so funny.
Yeah.
It's, it's crazy.
And usually comes some of the, you usually need something for inspiration.
Almost all ideas have an origin.
Yeah.
I mean, I agree.
I do that too.
When I like watch movies and I'm like, Oh, this is a cool concept.
I wish this was like expanded on or I'll just expand it like, you know, fan fiction
or something.
Speaking of stealing concepts, we got to talk about villain verse now.
And, um, I guess, uh, what's, uh, what should I explain here?
Should one of you guys try to explain it?
See what the violence?
Yeah.
I think I've only read the first issue.
Did you read the prologue and chapter one?
I read the prologue and chapter one.
Yeah.
So there's this goblin guy with the big tusks.
He's the big bad guy.
He's like, um, uh, I'm the number one villain as is ranked on this thing.
I forget if he made the thing.
Yeah.
He made it.
It's like this giant ethereal list that just exists on the end of the, at the edge of the
universe.
And the names on it just keep shifting because like depending how evil you are, you move down
on the rank or whatnot.
Or if you just straight up die, you disappear from the list.
Right.
So it's, it's for like a bragging rights competition to see who can be the most evil and dastardly
devilish person on the list.
Yeah.
That's right.
That's, uh, that's like the backbone of the series.
It's, it's really, uh, if you read the prologue, it's, it starts mostly as a feud between like
the character give just explained.
His name is the villain.
Like that's his name.
Right.
And he has this feud with the devil, like the literal devil is like a character in this
universe.
Uh, and they're trying to compete to see who's the most evil.
Yes.
And throughout the story, like the villain has this very over elaborate 4d, like death note
Kira style plan that we're going to see him like pull off.
Right.
And I, and I know exactly how it's going to end.
I guess the only spoiler I could give about how it's going to end, it's going to parallel
the, the prologue in chapter one, like a lot.
Right.
Like a book ending.
Um, I'm a big fan of those.
Some books.
No, I don't read that shit.
I don't read that shit.
Does that mean you're a prologue?
Yeah.
I'm a prologue.
I guess like trees and shit.
Yeah.
I have trees like weed.
Exactly.
Yeah.
We smoke weed.
If you cut down trees, it's basically a comic about smoking weed.
Exactly.
It's a metaphor for smoking weed.
It's like everyone's competing to see how much jaywalking they can do in one second.
Exactly.
That's why the villain is green.
It's a parable as weed will kill you.
His head is in the shape of a weed leaf.
You're right.
It's a, it makes perfect sense.
I knew it.
Yeah.
That's what jaywalking you got to do, but it's not enough.
Like, it's not enough that you jaywalk on your own planet.
You have to move from planet to planet and jaywalk on other planets, other solar systems,
until you just jaywalk so much that you rise above the ranks.
I don't, I don't see why jaywalking is illegal.
Doesn't jay deserve to walk too?
Mike doesn't let him.
Mike stochasta says, no, Jerry, stop jaywalking.
That's why he was in that wheelchair.
That's why he was in that wheelchair in that one episode.
Yeah, exactly.
He fucking jaywalking before he got hit.
Like, fuck you jay, I'll jaywalk as much as they want.
Some crazy Milwaukee like driver hit him.
Milwaukee jaywalking.
Oh my, it rhymes.
It's like poetry.
Here's the rabbit hole go.
It's like poetry arrives.
So what else about villain verse?
Oh yeah.
And I'll just tell you how it ends right now.
I'll tell you what the final spoiler.
All right.
So, so at the end, the villain turns to the camera.
Yeah.
At the end, the villain like turns to the camera and he says like,
but the real villain is capitalism.
That's a good one.
Very clever.
Yeah.
It's a real thinker.
It's a really nuanced, very subtle.
He blow, he blows the dust off that off the list to reveal that
capitalism was actually at the top the whole time.
Like, yeah, he, it's capitalism.
The villain, then the devil, right?
Makes you, makes you think.
Yeah, exactly.
It's supposed to make you think.
Actually, there is kind of a message in villain verse,
but it's not really revealed to like the last chapter.
I, it's, I believe it's going to be more subtle.
Like I have faith in my writing.
I think I'm a good writer.
I think.
But yeah, you should check out villain verse.
It's about a bunch of crazy wacky space villains all trying to
murder each other.
Meanwhile, the big bad space villain has like an elaborate plan
that involves just like wiping everybody out in a specific way
that you're going to see at the end.
And there's a,
I gotta get, I gotta get chapter three.
I forgot to buy chapter three.
Yeah.
You should, you should, you should, um, yeah,
you guys should tell me what you think of chapter three.
I like to hear people's feedback on each chapter.
I forget.
I, I, I supported your Indiegogo.
I figured which, which things did I get from that?
Oh, you, I think I did.
You got, I, you wanted a picture of Clarissa, but thick.
Yeah.
I got that.
So I, um, I drew thick Clarissa.
Um, it's, it's one of the things you could have gotten because,
um, a couple of months ago,
my computer was finally showing its age.
And, um, I needed like, uh, I need a new one.
I'm like, I can't finish villain versus without like a new computer.
So, um, I ran a little Indiegogo for it.
No, it'll go fund me.
Yeah.
I ran a go fund me for it.
I had to get a new one.
Now I got this brick of a gamer PC.
Um, I'll play video games, but, um, yeah, and I got that,
I got that bullshit.
Oh, that's nice.
I need to get a new tablet.
Yeah.
Tablet broke and I need a new one.
Ah, I just keep not getting one.
Um, it is, it is time to get a new tablet.
I would argue.
Yes.
Yeah.
Sad.
I just realized, uh, this is the first episode that I and Gib have been on in a while together.
Oh, that's true.
Last time you were on, I wasn't for some reason.
That's weird.
Why was I, what did I do?
Why was I?
Did, did Gabriel Tavern scare you off?
Yes.
I was terrified.
I think maybe, um, it's better for only one of us to be on at a time because with two
of us is just too many puns.
Exactly.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
You can't say that now.
I'll have pressure to do puns on my end.
I haven't got anything in my head right now.
Say it.
Hey, Gib, you're a, hey, you're a funny, you're a funny person.
Why don't you tell us a joke?
Huh?
Why don't you make us laugh?
Is that internet comedian Gib?
Hey, Gib, play us a classic right now, Gib.
Um.
Oh, classic Gib.
That's a good one.
Classic Gib.
Don't, don't laugh at me.
Oh, what is, what a joke.
What a joke.
No, it's so embarrassing.
What an absolute joke.
But doctor, but doctor, I am Gib and take.
Doctor, I think I keep thinking I'm Gib and take.
That's cause you are.
Honk, honk.
Oh, good.
That's what the name was on file.
Oh my God.
But, but doctor, I am bongo and Luna.
Shut the fuck up.
Said the doctor.
44 Magnum and blust you away.
The real bongo and Luna was capitalism.
And unironically.
So that is the message of bongo and Luna.
I'm going to talk about any of my comics having messages.
Um, they kind of have been by accident really.
Yeah.
I was, I was, I was like the message of bell jpe.
That you should break out of jail and that it's fun.
Yeah.
Fuck the police.
Anti-authority, anti-authority.
Yeah.
Punk is the ultimate anti-fur.
I was, uh, I was drawing someone, uh, uh, someone requested.
Cause I'm so stupid.
I had still not completed all my, uh, uh, papers, uh, doodles.
I was doing like one of the last ones.
Someone had requested that I just draw some lore shit.
Like just any lore, like new lore.
And I was like, okay.
And I drew some champion related stuff.
And I remembered like, oh, wait a minute.
Uh, this premise and the setting is actually fucking based.
And, uh, it was a genius to create it.
And I should probably make some more of it.
Um, that's kind of really cool about this whole thing with, um, people like to think
that, okay.
So amateurs, right?
Um, they like to think that you need to wait for inspiration.
Like a professional knows that you just got to start working and inspiration is going to hit you.
You got to just have their brain rolling, right?
And I feel like, yeah, I feel like what happened to you is like evidence of that.
Right?
Yeah.
Um, yeah.
Cause I knew what I wanted to draw and I started drawing and it just got me, it just got me
thinking about like, oh yeah, you know, I'm drawn this character and thinking about like
them existing in the world and like what their role is in the larger setting.
And I'm like, oh yeah.
Oh yeah.
There's themes here that there's themes.
I seem to recall.
Hmm.
Pretty cool.
Actually.
And then they turn to the camera and they say capitalism was the problem.
They say the real champion was.
Yeah, exactly.
Whoa, no way.
That would blow my load.
I would be like, whoa, I guess maybe I should be circumcised.
I would have said that.
Sophia turns directly to the camera and says, I have become increasingly disillusioned with
the white moderate who prefers a negative, a negative piece, which is the absence of
conflict to a positive piece, which is the presence of justice and so on and so forth.
And then her, and then her, her little friends is like, whoa, what are you putting in?
She's like X-Men 2.
That's right.
X-Men 2 is pretty, pretty good.
X-Men 2 is probably the smartest movie ever made.
Unironically.
Yeah, probably.
There's a chick.
Don't remember.
There's a chick in that movie who has like sharp claws and she's like, I'm the female
Wolverine.
And then Wolverine's like, you can't be, there can't be a female Wolverine.
That's SJW shit.
And then he, and then he murders her.
He murders her right in front of everybody.
You know what?
I guess he made his point.
Burst into laughter.
Yeah.
That's aspirational.
That's aspirational for me.
Yeah, you're going to find female Ben Sane and you're going to love her, then murder
her.
You can kill him.
You find your female doppelganger and you've got to kill him before they kill you.
That's what I've been told.
That reminds me of an episode of Seinfeld where George was dating a female Jerry.
Does anyone remember that?
Yeah.
That sounds, you know, you could have faked that, but it sounds like a real episode.
I guess I haven't, I thought I'd seen a lot of Seinfeld, but I guess you, whenever you
reference a Seinfeld episode, I've never seen the episode you're talking about.
Maybe I haven't seen as much as I thought.
Um, I found a DVD copy of season one, two of Seinfeld and a Bush when I was just walking
there.
Yeah.
Just walking behind it.
You know, it's, back in my old neighborhood, I found a lot of like just VHS copies like
in Bush's for some reason.
It's like, yeah.
Well, maybe it was like, like somebody just thought I don't want this anymore, but I can't
think of a way to get rid of it.
So I just threw in a bush near the same place.
I think it was on there.
Yeah.
I have gamers to have or no copy of Seinfeld.
Um, but I think the logic is that, you know how, uh, give, I don't know if they have this
or you live, um, but like sometimes people just leave like a couch on the sidewalk.
Oh yeah, that happens.
Yeah.
So I think the logic is like, oh, I'm just going to leave all this like bullshit.
I think one of the best things I found, one of the best like VHS as I found was, um, a
complete like set of like Rod Serlin's favorite episode of the Twilight Zone.
And, um, yeah.
Was that?
No, I was just going, huh?
Yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
It was pretty strange.
It was like right behind like a little dumpster as I was walking to a middle school and I
was like, whoa, what the fuck?
And I was like, huh.
And then I grabbed all of them as fast as I can and I ran back to my house, dropped them
off and went back to school.
Right.
And then when I came back, I made sure to see if they work and they, and they do work.
They're pretty, um, they're pretty good condition, but now I don't have a VHS player anymore.
I was pretty lucky.
Yeah.
No, it's, uh, it's crazy.
Um, I don't go outside anymore.
So there's probably a shitload of other DVDs and VHS.
It's just piling up like the bush is getting slowly overtaken by VHS and DVDs.
Yeah.
Well, when I was younger, I was like, um, before I went to get into comics, I was really big
into film, so I was trying to consume as much film as possible.
And I would just kind of collect any VHS I would find on the, on the street.
Right.
But, um, over time I developed a taste and I was like, I don't really got to keep the
VHSs for the movies that I don't like.
They just take up too much room, you know?
Like I've been really, I've been really good about that recently where I just, I just now
buy like movies that I like or just right now I just buy comics I want to read in the
moment.
I don't try to buy a comic that I'll eventually read because I feel like that's a waste of
money.
I want to just buy something.
I know I'm going to read it when I get back home.
What's the last comic you bought?
Uh, uh, Jack Kirby by Tom Schiele.
Um, do you have Jack Kirby by Tom Schiele?
Do you know who Jack Kirby is?
I've heard the name.
I know that, God, he, he is like a Marvel.
Yeah, he's like, there wouldn't be a,
Wait, wait, wait, he made the Kirby Crackle.
He made the Kirby Crackle.
Yeah, Kirby Crackle.
I love the Kirby Crackle.
Was he a DC?
Yeah, he went, he went back and forth a lot.
Um, but there wouldn't be like a Marvel Universe without him.
Like, uh, like Stan Lee, like sure he's credited as a writer,
but he was more of like a glorified editor.
Right.
I see.
And because Stanley was also the only guy, the only guy in comics with
charisma, everybody remembers him.
Um, but yeah, but I think Jack Kirby basically like saved Marvel and
created, well, like it's debatable, but he did create like the majority
of the universe.
There's also a rumor that he possibly created Spider-Man.
Um, because, uh, back in the, yeah, because back, because, you know,
Spider-Man is credited towards Stan Lee and Steve Ditko, which is true.
That, which is true.
That's still true.
But what happened was that back in the day, um, like artists would,
artists and creators would just kind of stockpile just like any superhero.
Like they'll just come up with a random superhero.
Like, oh, okay.
Um, Spider-Man.
And then he drew a picture of a, of a spider themed superhero and he just
kept it in a filing cabinet.
Like, oh, maybe later.
Like we're going to need like another superhero book and I can just pull
this off and I'm like, okay, cool.
I'll expand on this character.
Right.
So he just kept that in the filing cabinet for years.
And then when he went back to, to, to basically, he basically went back to
save Marvel.
Um, Stan is all like, we need a, we need another superhero.
And then he went for his filing cabinet.
It's like, what about this, uh, Spider-Man?
And then Stan Lee's like, uh, I'm not really digging the design.
I'm going to get Steve Ditko to redesign it.
And that's the design we have today.
That actually, uh, reminds me of the origin of Mega Man because, um, mega,
a KG Inifuna is often credited as a creator of Mega Man,
but I think somebody else actually, uh, created him.
So it's, uh, I guess kind of similar.
Didn't he, uh, design Mega Man?
I don't remember now if he was on the design it or if somebody that was
working with him at the time actually, uh, did the design.
I think, um, I, from what I, tell me if this is the story you heard where Mega
Man was originally like an Astro Boy game, but then they lost the license
for Astro Boy.
And so they had to redesign like, um, the main robot boy character.
And they came up with Mega Man.
And I think that was a KG Inifuna, maybe.
Uh, that story sounds familiar, but I don't know if it's true or not.
Yeah.
I don't know if it's true.
I mean, I read it.
I think I read it.
I can't remember where I read it.
It's pretty obvious that Mega Man is inspired by Astro Boy.
Oh, yeah.
I think Inifuna, uh, has stated that before.
Mm-hmm.
I'm a, I fucking love Astro Boy.
I grew up with the Astro Boy manga that was, uh, republished by Black Horse.
When I was younger, I would just keep checking out the Astro Boy, uh, manga from the library
because I wanted my art style to look like that.
Cause it was like, I think it was one of the first comics that I read and I'm like,
whoa, you can make a comic that looks like cartoony.
You don't have to make it realistic.
And then I just checked all the Astro Boys out and I just tried to copy his, uh, his art style as much as I can.
And this was like back in the start of middle school.
And then towards the end of middle school, I was like trying to draw out of his art style.
And I, I don't know if you could still see Osamata Suka's influence in my art style,
but maybe barely there, but, um, yeah.
Yeah, Astro Boy is pretty cool.
I don't know too much about the lore and stuff, but, um,
I've seen it and it's cool.
Um, actually my first exposure to Astro Boy was the, the game for the Game Boy Advance,
uh, Me and My Treasure.
Uh, that's a progress game.
Yeah, that game is amazing.
Yeah, yeah.
It's, it made, it's one of those, uh, uh, good games.
It's one of those.
It's one of those games where like, like, like as a, as a video game goes,
you know, it's like fun, like play in the game.
But then there's a story element, which is like surprisingly gripping
and like makes me cry.
Ah, nice.
Yeah.
The Astro Boy stories are like tiered jerkers.
They also like move like really fast.
Like they'll have like, they'll have like an anti-war message,
but at the same time, like then in the next scene,
like Astro Boy's got a beat up big robot.
The pro war.
No, no, no.
Astro Boy is very anti-war.
I mean, it came out post, um, post, uh, World War II
and Japan was very like anti-war.
And like, why do, why do, why do we live just to suffer?
It's basically Astro Boy.
Um, they only said that because they lost.
That's so serious.
Leah, we'll lose your mentality.
Well, wow, maybe.
War is actually good as long as you win.
Maybe they shouldn't, they shouldn't stop being fascist
and just became hardcore capitalists like us Americans.
Asians are so bad at driving.
I'm starting to think that Pearl Harbor was an accident.
Oh, no.
Oh, I swear I've heard that exact same joke somewhere.
Actually, maybe I shouldn't have said that.
Edit that.
No, it's okay.
Cancel the podcast.
I'll vouch for you.
It's all right.
Um, what was I going to say?
Something about Imperial?
I'll defend.
What was I going to say?
Racism.
We're talking about Astro Boy.
Oh, yes.
Astro Boy.
Uh, pretty sick.
If there's only one Astro Boy story you should read,
it's probably, uh, the world's strongest robot.
Um, that's a good ass story.
Is that like a Shonen tournament arc?
No, it's about, it's about some rich, uh,
soddy looking asshole who like,
who pays for the strongest robot called Pluto.
And he's like this giant like devil looking robot.
He has a really cool design.
Yeah.
I think I remember Pluto.
There's like a list of,
there's basically a list of like the most powerful robots
and Astro Boy is on that list.
Right.
Wait, wait, wait.
Is this the one Cyborg?
Is this Cyborg 009?
They all wear red.
No, no, no.
That's a different thing.
Cyborg 009 was created by a,
I have this fucking,
I have one of his mangoes right in front of me.
It's, it's got that Astro Boy logo.
Well, because the thing is that,
um, he was the apprentice for Osamatsuka.
Like he worked under him.
Yeah.
And then he became his equal.
Okay.
His name is Ashotaro Ishii Nomori.
He, um, he created a Cyborg 009.
He also basically created the Power Rangers too.
And, um,
A base.
That's pretty interesting.
Yeah.
He, uh, he also created Common Rider.
You guys ever heard of Common Rider?
Yes.
Yeah.
And Common Rider basically has the same plot of Cyborg 009.
The only difference is that in Cyborg 009,
it's like a group of Cyborgs,
but in Common Rider,
it's only one Cyborg.
Fun fact.
How much do you think Mega Man is ripped off of Astro Boy?
I haven't really played Mega Man games,
but he looks so similar.
I don't think,
Not,
I haven't really seen Astro Boy.
I think actually,
There is a heavy inspiration from Astro Boy.
You know a lot about Mega Man and Astro Boy?
I mean,
Dr. Light is basically the guy who created Astro Boy.
Does Astro Boy never kill a single robot master?
No, no, Astro, no.
Okay.
So in Astro Boy,
he kind of has two dads almost,
or he has like three dads, technically,
because the Astro Boy story is basically,
there was,
there was his kid,
and he was like the son,
like the head,
yeah, Tobi,
he was the son of the head ministry of science guy.
I forget his name,
but he was voiced by Nicholas Cage in the movie.
Anyway,
Nicholas Cage dad who kind of looks like Dr. Wiley,
like a proto Dr. Wiley,
like his son was driving and got into a car accident and died.
And then he's all like,
Oh no, my son.
He's like,
Oh, I know,
I'll build a robot son who's better
and has a shitload of superpowers.
So he builds his robot son.
I wish my dad had said that to me.
When Ben St died,
I wish his dad was like,
I'll build a better son.
And he did.
And his name was Nate Besman.
Oh my God.
Yeah, you're right.
It's in the name.
It was, that's why he has the best mid name.
Oh my God.
It's glorifiedly exclaimed.
That's why you can't see,
he covers his eyes
because you can see the circuitry through his pupils.
That's why you two can no longer be in the same podcast.
Right, exactly.
Legally the same person.
So he built his robot son
and then he's like,
Oh, I love my robot son.
And until he doesn't,
until he stops loving his robot son,
because he's all like,
he's only pretending to be human.
I hate him.
Get out.
I hate you robot son.
I don't want to be with you anymore.
Right, exactly.
And then his robot son gets adopted
by the new head of the Ministry of Science
who basically looks like Dr. Light,
only with a huge nose.
Yeah.
And he's all like,
I'm going to teach you how to be a good boy.
Your name is Astro Boy now.
You're like a superhero and shit.
And I'm pretty sure.
Wait, what was that?
Did you say my name is asshole boy?
Okay, I'll be an asshole.
He's called asshole boy.
Isn't there a character named Astro Boy?
Isn't there a character named Astro Boy
that's like a proto man from Mega Man?
Or, you know, do you know what I mean?
Uh, Atlas.
There's a couple of...
Yeah, yeah, Atlas is like the anti-astro boy.
But, um, I know the anime,
he shows up pretty early on,
but in the manga,
which I'm more familiar with,
he shows up like way later.
And, um, yeah, Astro Boy is pretty sick.
I think Astro Boy is kind of like a Mega Man
with a much more detailed, complex plot.
Because Mega Man just takes the basic premise of Astro Boy.
It doesn't really, um,
it doesn't really go too in depth on anything.
A lot of, um, a lot of messaging.
So, like, basically in Astro Boy's world,
this is kind of crazy that, like, he was doing this
like way before even, like,
I think even the start of the civil rights movement,
Osama Tsutsuko's writing of...
Like, robots were so abundant in Astro Boy's world
that they're like their own ethnicity at this point.
Like, they're their own minority group, right?
Who wants, who wants, like, rights and whatnot.
Yeah, that's like the part of Mega Man X.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, basically.
And in Astro Boy's world, like, um,
usually there'd be a bad robot,
but they're only bad because they had, like, a bad creator,
or were designed with evil purposes.
Um, there's, like, a big thing in Astro Boy where it's like,
the more human a robot looks, the more human it'll be,
and the more good it will be.
But if you make a robot look like a gun,
it's gonna be a gun, right?
And some, and then it's just gonna be programmed
to wanna, you know, shoot people.
Although, like, um, in Astro Boy's world
they do follow, like, the three laws of robots.
Uh, what's it called?
Yeah, the laws of robotics, I think.
See no evil, hear no evil, speak no evil, yeah.
Exactly.
It's also mentioned in Mega Man as well.
Yeah, yeah, so in Astro Boy's world they have that.
So Astro can't, like, can't kill any humans.
Although a lot of times, like,
a lot of times they do the irony thing
where it's like the evil human, like,
collapses the building to collapse
and then the rubble kills them, right?
So robots didn't technically kill them, right?
I'm quite familiar with that trope.
What was that?
I'm pretty familiar with that trope.
Uh, lots of media uses it.
Yeah, yeah, it's a very classic trope of, like,
oh, it was his own undoing, right?
Like his own selfishness causes his demise, right?
Yeah, basically.
He's very, he's very classic trope.
Um, and that's how, and that's how villain versus basic,
we're gonna end, uh, spoilers.
Okay.
It's gonna be all the villain's fault.
Oh, the villains were the fault?
That comfy.
Who could have seen, yeah, that's a, yeah.
The villains were the bad guy?
What the fuck?
That's unusual.
I, I hate it when comics tell me who the good guy
or bad guy are.
They need to be nuanced and subtle.
I hate it.
Jesus Christ.
Very cringe.
But I think, uh, where Mega Man separates from
the Astro Boy influences is probably, uh,
from X onwards.
That's when it becomes a lot less like Astro Boy.
Mm-hmm.
When it becomes base.
It stops being stupid.
When it gets a fucking dash button already.
Yeah.
Astro Boy doesn't have a dash button.
He doesn't.
Like he, he loves Tumblr.
Yeah, because he's always tumbling down the stairs.
He's, watch out for those stairs, uh, Mega Man X.
Uh, I don't know what you're about.
I can't deal with stairs.
I, I only need, I, I, I can only do inclines that are smooth.
The stairs.
I can't dash up and down those.
I always get strange stairs when I take the stairs.
So I take the elevator instead.
And then people elevate you in the elevator.
Yeah, exactly.
You get strange stairs because, um,
because people are races.
Uh, you mean races against stairs?
We fixed races.
Oh yeah.
Racism is gone.
Once Obama was elected, like racism was over, right?
That's right.
That's the first thing you did.
Exactly.
Yeah.
He made racism illegal.
And then, then Donald Trump went into office
and made racism, racism legal.
It's okay.
God damn fact.
It's going to be illegal.
That orange man.
It's going to be illegal again.
It's going to be illegal again very soon.
You just have to sign it.
Thank you, Biden.
Oh, thanks, Biden.
God, I'm, I'm writing Biden so hard I broke his dick.
We know, we know Joe, right?
We know him and he knows us inside and out.
It's inside, whether we want to or not.
That's right.
Yeah, he, he, he knows that we're smooth.
He hacked into all my emails so he knows a lot about me.
Yeah.
He's, he's petting me right now with his weird wrinkly old manhand.
Joe Bile.
It's going to be a, it's going to be a sexy four years.
Oh, with Joe, Joe vile.
Oh, I like that name.
Are you going to use that name?
Cause I'm going to use it for a villain name.
I said Joe Bile, but vile also works.
Bile, that's pretty good.
He could be like a villain who pukes on people.
Just got to remove his gold bar.
Yeah, exactly.
He could be like a wacky guy who just pukes on people.
Um, I like, I come up, I have like a, I have a sketchbook, like a big sketchbook called
the villain versus catalog and it just has every villain that appears in the, in the
comic.
Cause sometimes I can't remember how they all fucking look like.
So when I need like a background shot with several villains, I go through it and I'm
like, okay, that guy's going to be there.
That guy's going to be there.
Yeah.
There's also a couple.
There's a lot of designs, a lot of, a lot of crazy guys in that, in that comic.
It's impressive.
Oh yeah.
When it comes to me.
Every page has like a new like fucking weird costume.
Yeah.
It's, it's a lot.
I, I try so hard, but when I say that, I mean, I try not at all to make characters.
Um, it's, um, it's really like easy.
Like, so I guess I could, I could talk a little bit about the, the actually the real origin
of Villainverse.
Villainverse.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Everyone's Velma.
Everyone wants to be the most velvety of all the Velmas.
Um, but back in a 2019, there was this guy called Craig Gleason on Instagram.
And he's a really good artist and he has something called the bad guys club.
Right.
And basically it's like his, it's well that I like the son of that club.
Oh yeah.
It's a pretty cool club.
Um, and he basically has, um, he has like the set of like characters called the bad guys
who are members of the bad guys club and all just a bunch of wacky different monster guys.
And every, every October he does like a, he does like a, his own version of Inktober called
the season of the bad guys club.
And every month you draw a different bad guy and he, but he also encourages people to like
redesign the bad guys.
Like, oh, just like take the name and just come up with a cool design for that name or
whatever.
He doesn't really care because he kind of likes when people like draw it and way wackier
art styles or just, just anything.
He just loves seeing it.
And, um, and I was doing that.
And I mean, I've been, I've been fans of this guy for like, I've been a fan of this guy
for like years.
And then, um, I finally did it back in 2019 and every bad guy I created, I was thinking
like, huh, I like, I think I'm pretty decent at coming up with like stories for characters
on the spot.
And, um, and I came up with like a lot, several stories.
And I was like, I could probably make a comic about like all these characters existing in
the same universe.
Right.
And originally I was going to pitch it to Craig Leeson as like some sort of anthology,
but then I thought, why should I give that guy like my good ideas?
I should just use my good ideas for myself.
I don't need to like get someone to do a good idea.
Yeah, exactly.
So I'm thinking like, okay, time to, time to take all the designs that are different
enough and then take all the other designs that I like, but like change them to make
them legally distinct.
Right.
And then, and then, and then you, did you see the logic there?
Like, I mean, it's easy to see how I jumped from that guy's club to villain verse.
Right.
I don't get it.
And, and basically like the list, the list exists because, um, because like it's kind
of like, how do I make these guys like, what's the relationship between all these like villains?
Like, why do they give a fuck about each other?
Then it's like, well, there's a list.
So they're in a constant competition.
Right.
And, um, and basically like, I think from there it's like, like, I think some good advice
for like a designer character is to kind of know exactly what you like.
Right.
Like, um, like for example, there's a, there's one character in villain verse called dirty
bomb.
Um, yeah, she's like a bomb girl.
And she's actually based on another character called the moon goon from bad guys club basically
right.
And the moon goon is like this guy who has like a, who has like a giant like moon for
a head.
And, um, and so I looked at that guy and I thought to myself, what do I like about this
guy?
Well, I like his like round head.
I like his like constant smile.
And I kind of like all the accessories he has on him.
Right.
So it's like, well, I like his round head.
What else is round?
Oh, well, bombs are round.
Right.
Like the little cartoon bombs are round.
So it's just from there.
Like then I kind of like, oh, you know, spots are also round.
So I added that on her.
Um, gave her a couple like frills and whatnot.
Yeah.
That's what he looks like.
Right.
God, what a freak.
That's an interesting design.
No, I, no, I, yeah, I love them.
I got them.
I have a shirt of him.
Um, and so yeah.
So basically you kind of see how I jumped from the moon goon design to a dirty bomb over
here.
Oh, I really liked that one.
Right.
That's pretty cool.
Thank you.
And, um, and basically like, um, her like, we don't see this in like chapter one, but
like what she could do is like those spots on her clothes, like she could peel them off
like stickers.
But once she peels them off, they turn it to like little like bombs, right?
Then she could throw and her, her, um, her suit just like respawns them.
That's very clever.
She has like a, yeah, she has like a near infant internet, like amount of bombs.
I feel like there's another character.
They don't make bombs.
I just think like some, some looney tunes thing where like the, like holes, like pulling
like holes off there.
Yeah.
Oh, wait.
I'm talking about Maggie and her ferocious beast.
Am I?
Cause the ferocious beast has spots that could be removed.
Shit.
Yeah.
Maybe I'm thinking of Maggie, the ferocious beast.
Uh, possibly.
It's a good show.
Pretty, pretty base.
Pretty, pretty good.
There's pretty good lineage there.
There's also a Bomberman.
Does anyone remember that guy?
Oh yeah.
That's true.
Love that guy.
Of course.
Who could forget Bomberman?
He's requested a Super Smash Brothers character.
Even, even more requested than Goku?
Uh, well, that was a joke, but.
Oh, okay.
Oh my bad.
I, I took Goku 100% seriously.
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh.
Wait, why isn't Bomberman in Smash?
They, they made a, um, uh, a skin, like a me.
I think he's in as an instant movie now.
That doesn't count.
No, he's in as a meat costume.
I think.
Yeah.
And also as a costume.
I'm, I'm sorry.
If ice climbers get in, Bomberman should be in.
Yeah.
I mean, they should have them in because they have a Simon Belmont and Bomberman is not
currently owned by Konami.
Um.
I've never, I've never heard a more obvious pick.
The next, um, the next reveal is going to be a Fortnite, uh, character.
No.
Fortnite doesn't have characters though, does it?
It just has.
Yeah.
Humanoids.
Humanoids with guns.
So actually the main story, the main story of Fortnite is like a zombie survivor game.
I knew that.
So like that, that story.
That's not the thing people care about though.
That's like, no, no, they care about the free, like, battle royale thing.
Right.
They put Steve for Minecraft.
Plants versus zombies and smash.
They've already got Piranha Plant.
Yeah, exactly.
I'm going to put Sands on the tail and smash.
I want Sands.
He's in here.
Yeah.
We should get Sands.
It's not the same.
We should definitely get Sands.
Oh my God.
Where is he?
Where is the boy?
Where is Sands?
Where is Sands from the best video game ever made Undertale?
Where is he?
You know, I was playing Smash Wii U with my brothers just now before I got in the call.
Or maybe a few hours ago.
So that's what you were doing.
Well, it wasn't just that.
It was just like hanging out and having fun.
Shut up.
Anyway.
That sounded like a smashing good time.
It was cool.
We were all playing as our Mies and I had to, I had the, I could change my Mie to be like
a female and like make it look different.
And it was cool.
Nice.
And I shot them and I was shooting them just in the side.
Nothing special about that.
But Smash Brothers is fun.
It doesn't matter what characters are in it.
You just play the game and you win and you destroy the competition.
Yeah.
It's just like war.
It's cool as long as you win.
Yeah.
It is fun, but I usually lose in it nowadays.
I don't usually typically win.
Yeah.
I'm not super great at it.
Online.
I'm prone to underhanded tactics.
Online is terrible just because people care about Smash and they practice and they're
on the line, but in a room with siblings, you can say fuck and then you can have like
a cup of tea and talk about something else afterwards.
God.
With a person online, they just, I don't know, they do a Dark Souls emote and they shit on
your face and you don't feel like anything is good.
When I was younger, I was playing Smash Brothers at a friend's house and I was like saying fucking
shit and when I was playing and then their mother snitched on my mom and told her that
I was cussing and I'm like, that fucking cunt bitch.
That's a tale as old as time itself.
Yeah.
Fucking bitch.
She fucking ratted me out.
I hope she gets lung cancer.
She's gonna probably eventually.
She smoked a lot.
Did you know that your son cussed?
I think that's more of like a thing she's saying about like to your mom like, oh, you're a bad
parent.
You have a child that cusses.
I just want to rub that in your face.
Yeah.
But then obviously the wrath is going to fall on the son.
The mom is gonna be scolded because her son is like, isn't potty trained.
Hasn't been broken like a horse and re-forced into a valuable citizen.
Rats from full metal.
She's gonna unleash her vengeance upon him.
And then as my mom was beating me for cussing at Smash Bros.
She says, don't blame me.
Blame capitalism.
That's when it all connected.
Everything clicked in my brain.
I was like, of course.
Obviously this is capitalism right now.
She was beating me.
I'm only doing this because it's advantageous to me financially.
Exactly.
Ironically though.
This is what you get for not performing your role as a member of society.
Isn't that why anyone does anything?
Yeah.
We'll get spanked in certain ways.
To avoid the big beating and rich people, they hate getting the beating.
That's why they try to make as much money as they can to avoid it.
They've got weak buttocks.
That's what it is.
Exactly.
They've got buttocks made of paper.
They need to do more squats.
I think Donald Trump is probably the only rich person with a good butt.
It's massive if you've seen the photos.
I'm sure there's got to be some other people.
I have not seen the photos of Trump's massive behind.
Yeah.
I've seen diaper Trump.
It's pretty huge.
Have you seen his son?
His son is like tall as fuck.
Holy shit.
Baron is a real beanpole.
He's a real fucking monster.
You can fucking...
Yeah.
He's a real super soldier in the making.
You could say he's pretty good for a Baron.
He's a real...
If you see Baron right next to Trump, they look like one piece characters.
Yeah.
Yeah, a little bit.
Wait, isn't that the best way to look?
Trump's like pretty tall, right?
Trump's like six foot one or something, right?
So Baron's got to be like eight foot nine.
Wait, how old is Baron?
He looks like an eight year old.
Eighteen?
He's like a teenager.
He loves anime.
Yeah, he was like ten or something.
I think when the presidency first started, now he's like straight up ten.
Now he's like forty.
Okay, so who's Trump's other son?
Wait a minute.
Oh, Don Jr.
He got chubby.
When did Baron Trump get chubby?
This is fucking...
No, no, he's supposed to be skinny.
He's unattractive now.
I do not like him no more.
That's clearly the anime's fault.
There's Don Jr. who's like the infamous son where Donald Trump was like,
I don't want to name my son after myself.
What if he's a loser?
God, this little fucking monster is going to be a thorn in all of our sides
for the rest of our lives.
He's going to try to run for presidency,
but he's going to have the fucking charisma like his father does
to actually pull it off.
No.
This guy's not a hero like Donald Trump.
He's not a populist hero.
He doesn't look like Trump enough to...
I think the average person would be like,
I guess it's just some guy.
I mean, he's from the first or second marriage?
I don't know.
I think Milani is like that dirt, isn't he?
Well, I hope the entire family eventually tries to run for president.
Oh, yeah.
You know, like what the Bushes did?
They're all going to run against each other.
And Eric and Don Jr. are going to be like running against each other
in the next primary.
That would be great.
Ivanka is probably going to win.
She's going to be first female president, finally.
Yeah, like half of them will run as Republicans,
half of them will run as Democrats.
So, you know, to thin the crowd out a little bit.
Finally, finally, sexism is over.
Now we have a woman president.
Based, based.
About time.
He does have the hand thing going on.
This image loads.
Tiny hands.
Something about the gesture.
His hands are...
Well, I...
Yeah, he does have the hand thing.
He does.
China.
He got that look.
Chinese virus.
He's got that hella look on his face.
Looking at the chat now, we've got like a list of characters.
All confirmed for Smash.
All potential Smash characters.
Nice.
Oh, did you see the thick Clarissa I posted that earlier?
I did.
Yeah, yeah.
I do not forgive as a thank you for the GoFundMe.
There's a lot of people who like,
could get a commission from me because of the GoFundMe,
but it just haven't DM me yet.
And I don't really care too much about reminding them to be honest.
I think I owe a handful of people from some patron rewards.
I think one person, one Bev asked me to,
for her reward, she wanted me to do another top killer's RFCK image,
which I am like a fucking year overdue on.
So I'll have to do that at some point.
Oh wait, this is my end right now.
Hey kids, you like RFCK?
You like the game where if your character dies,
they don't really die.
They come back thanks to a green slime.
Yes.
That's literally villain verse.
Oh my God.
And no one can die.
No one in villain verse could die.
Oh my God.
They all drank a chemical called Regeneradium,
and it makes them all deadpool basically.
Just like real life.
It's just an evergreen premise.
Exactly.
So every character comes back so you can still have your favorite
and they won't die.
It's fucking great.
You can just see them lose over and over again.
Exactly.
It's like everyone's playing on Gmod,
but in real life, but in a comic.
Not in real life actually, but almost.
Almost.
In their real life, in their universe,
their villain verse if you will.
To coin a phrase.
Do we want to start listening to voicemails maybe?
We've been going for an hour and a half.
I got like an hour and ten minutes here.
What do you think?
Should we start voicemails?
Give.
Back me up.
In real life.
Okay, I mean if you've all got such important shit to talk about,
by all means.
No.
Never mind.
No voicemails.
No, I don't.
No, I won't post them.
After all.
I think it didn't give me how I could pump out comics so fast earlier.
Yeah, I wanted to talk about that a little bit,
because I've been very non-existent with what I've been putting out.
I made the Clarissa half of it,
and I said I would do the rest,
and then I stopped, and it feels bad.
Not sure about it all day, every day.
I was thinking a little bit.
Sorry I haven't made a comic in a while.
Yeah.
You kind of have to unironically treat it like a job.
Well, yes.
Like, no, but I'm not saying that like, oh, obviously,
but I mean like, no, actually, like, for example,
Monday through Friday is when I just work on the comic,
and I just do nothing but the comic on Monday through Friday.
Saturday and Sunday is when I go to my job and I make money,
but there are the week,
I just got to have to just work on the comic.
Like, just whatever you can.
Like, you should also try to like,
make sure the day before you have everything set up
so you can just jump right into it the next day, right?
Yeah.
When I do my comic, I always like do the panels first,
like where the panels are going to go,
and then I'll have that ready,
so then tomorrow I'll have to do just draw inside the panels, right?
Having everything ready to go so you can just jump right in is big.
It is pretty good.
I mean, how I write, how I do villain versus basically,
so I have the whole story like outline,
like each chapter has a summary,
and it's like a, it's like a skeleton of an outline, right?
So I know what happens in each chapter,
but I don't know specifically what happens,
and that's kind of like the fun part.
That's the kind of like, like, oh, I know where the story is going,
but the smaller details, the little, like,
intricacies and nuances,
I'm discovering that with everybody else, right?
So what I do is I do a rough draft of the comic,
and just to finish it, I just, the rough draft,
like I don't focus too much on like whether it's perfect,
just to finish it, just to have a rough draft,
and then I'll look at it like the next day,
and I'll like, like, you know, edit it to make sure it's like,
I lower the page number, I add more pages, right?
Or I like combine pages together until like,
it kind of like flows well, you know?
And then I start like drawing it,
and I draw it on a deleter paper,
which is like what manga artists use, right?
And even while I'm drawing it,
I'm still like editing it,
because like I could like be drawing it,
and I'm like, wait a second,
I kind of don't like how this looks.
I think I'm gonna add an extra page
to kind of balance it out, or lower it,
but I consistently try to stay under like 30 pages.
I think the highest I've ever been is like 26 pages.
That might change though.
Sounds like a professional.
It is, it's a very, like,
I mean, that's how I managed to do that,
that Clarissa in that month,
leading up to the contest entry,
was that I streamed it,
which was like the way to like not get distracted.
And I managed to do quite a lot of work during the day,
but it was too much,
and I ended up burning myself out.
And I just, I don't know,
maybe I'm just like a, like a stupid idiot,
but I don't know how to like motivate myself
to work without a stream.
And I don't want to have to stream,
because like that's extra,
like I need to-
Alright, now I get you.
I forget like a lot of things.
Like it's been very long since I played video games
or like seen a show.
Actually, wait, hold up.
I actually have been watching shows while I'm drawing,
but like, so I do this thing where I look for shows
that aren't good or bad, just okay,
and I just play them in the background.
Right?
There's a show called Legends of Tomorrow,
and it's a spin-off show from like the Flash TV show.
And Legends of Tomorrow is like, okay,
it's the most okay show I've ever seen,
which makes it perfect.
So I just play it in the background,
so I don't have to like pay too much attention to it.
But I think like, I don't know,
like you're just going to have to like,
I guess I'm just,
I really just want to finish Villainverse.
If there was like a button that I could press
and like Villainverse is like instantly done,
I would press that button.
So I think that's like what motivated me,
because I really do want to see what the whole thing looks like.
And I think also because I really like Villainverse too,
like I'm also a fan,
because once I try to read the prologue,
I want to read the rest.
Like I can't just like look at the chapter one
and just like reference it quickly.
Like I, if I look at chapter one,
I'm going to start reading it
and I'm going to like have to stop myself
like hold up, don't finish it.
Just keep working on like what you're doing, right?
I feel like I do get distracted a lot,
mostly through Twitter,
but like the fact that that hasn't like hindered
the production of Villainverse
is why I don't really perceive it.
That's too much of a problem, right?
I mean, I'll try to like do less Twitter arguments
when I'm working on the comic, right?
But it's just, I'm just really looking,
it's like I'm really looking forward
to how Villainverse is going to look like.
I'm really looking forward to how my art style
is going to look like by chapter 12.
That's like one of my end goals.
Also, I want to know how Villainverse is going to end.
Well, I mean, I know Villainverse is going to end,
but I want to see everything go down.
I also want to be financially stable.
And I think that's kind of going to be the end goal
for like Villainverse.
Like there's a bunch of other comics I want to do
and I want to make those comics too,
but I got to get for Villainverse first, you know?
There's just like, yeah, just, I don't know.
I think that motivates me.
I think what also helps is that I don't have like
depression or anxiety or anything like that, right?
Base.
So, yeah.
Narotypical gang representation.
Narotypical gang, yeah.
Like, assemble.
One time, I tell the story like almost
on every other fucking podcast I'm on,
but you ever heard of Meg Moggenau?
I have.
Yeah, that's a thing.
Comic.
Yeah, it's a comic.
It's a really good comic.
It's kind of like train spotting,
but if everyone was like a monster.
But basically, I asked the creator of Meg Moggenau
at Comic-Con, like, I asked him a question
for a friend, right?
And I was like, how do you like make comics
with depression?
And he told me, oh, here's the therapy, right?
Because he said that he only started
really making comics in his 30s, right?
And now he's like an indie comic legend.
What's really fucking crazy is that currently
right now for every day since the start
of the quarantine, he drew a comic,
like a one-page Meg Moggenau comic
with its own like long continuity
and it's fucking legendary.
Jesus Christ.
I mean, the thing is that he also admitted
that he's a workaholic, right?
And I'm kind of like that too.
For the longest time, I never thought
that I would get like a partner,
like an emotional partner,
like I would be in a strong relationship
unless it was someone who also does art
and would be on the same schedule.
I mean, now I'm in a relationship,
but what's great is that the person I'm with
understands like my schedule like perfectly
and doesn't like bother me
when I'm like working on my own shit
and they also do art.
So it's not too bad.
Also, I think a great video to watch is
this video, how to be creative,
how an artist turns pro.
This is a really good video.
I try to watch this video like every month
just to keep myself on track, right?
Let me see.
Did you post it?
Yeah, I posted there in the general.
It's a really good video.
It just explains how like,
anyone could become an amateur at any second.
You can just become an amateur, right?
But this video talks about how you
consistently become a pro, right?
And the thing is like,
even before I watched this video,
I kind of agreed with everything it said,
but there's something so great about being reassured
that you're on the right track, right?
Yeah.
Like, sure, this is all the information
you heard before,
but the fact that other people kind of believe this,
it feels like, oh, so I'm really not in the wrong path.
I'm in a good path.
I guess what also helps is that like,
I did an internship at a comic book publisher
and they just explained to me how to get published.
And I was like, oh, cool.
So I just got to do the comic and I'm good.
I think having a good work ethic
is something that can benefit you
no matter what it is you're doing.
And if you enjoy what you're doing,
it would help you have a better work ethic.
But even if you don't,
the work ethic can be a separate thing
that gets you motivated.
Yeah, like, and I do enjoy,
I do enjoy like drawing comics and whatnot.
I have forgotten like a lot of like social gatherings
just to work on the comic.
If I could get my Patreon to like 800 a month,
then I could do a second comic,
but I kind of want to do that too.
There's like other ideas that are like a little bit easier
for me to do that I could like bullshit on a weekend.
Is that like, is that like what it would take
for you to be like full time, I guess?
Yeah, yeah, like 800 on Patreon.
Yeah.
Yeah, that'd be like the end goal.
If I could like, I think what I was going to do
on my Patreon was like, if I could get to 200 a month,
I'll do a pasta, the clown, the comic.
Because I have an outline.
Yeah, I have an outline for that too.
And I know it won't be too hard.
It won't be like, I won't try as hard.
Like I'm not going to put as much effort as I'm doing
with Villainverse.
Like it's going to be its like own little like shit post
of a comic.
Yeah, there's a bunch of other comics I wanted to do.
I want to, I want to tell you what those are.
Cause I want to save a few secrets.
I don't want you guys to steal my genius ideas
that are popping out of my brain.
I think also eliminating distractions,
unless the distractions help you inspire you to do
what you're doing, that's also probably good advice.
Yeah, true, true that.
There's this thing I do where like,
every time I finish a chapter of Villainverse,
I reward myself by catching up with One Piece.
Right?
That's something I got to reward myself with one of these days.
Yeah, I like that.
That's good.
That would actually work for me, I think,
cause like there's, I have a lot of One Piece left
to get through.
Like I might even, I probably have like 50 or 60 chapters left.
I'm not too far behind one.
I think I'm just like maybe 10 chapters behind maybe.
I've been like lagging a lot with this chapter has been taking
a good while because I moved out.
I've been trying to get accustomed to this new job.
I got into a relationship.
I had to help my partner move to another state.
It's a, it's a bunch of, it's a bunch of stuff that been a lot
of like life changing moves have happened in the past couple
of months for me.
Also, there's the fucking pandemic.
Oh, sure.
Yeah, at the start, I was like,
yeah, at the start, I was pretty, I was doing pretty fine.
I managed to get like two chapters in the pandemic.
But then like, I don't know, I guess the move
and all the other stuff.
Also, my computer was like fucking on its last leg
and all this bullshit I had to do.
Um, yeah, it's just fucking, it was fucking ass.
But now, now next month, it's going to be good.
I'm going to try to finish villain burst by the, by next year
this month is when I want villain burst to be over.
How many, how many chapters is it going to be?
12.
Okay, base.
Unless, unless, unless I die, but also,
but also if I managed to amouse enough interest
towards like the middle of villain burst,
I have, I know potential directions to kind of extend the story.
Right.
If not, whatever.
But um, yeah, I also got like a lot of ideas for villain burst too.
Like I would, I have an idea for a sequel,
which would be more of a ongoing.
It wouldn't be, it wouldn't be just 12 chapters.
It'll be way longer.
But um, that's it.
I mean, that's if villain burst is like popular by the time, you know.
Yeah.
I mean, I just, I just want to finish it.
Guess about it.
Well, God bless you.
God speed.
You black emperor.
Give us, give us connected again.
Damn.
What a piece.
What a piece of shit.
Should we, should we wait for her?
No, fuck that.
Uh, let's, let's, let's start it on voicemails.
We've got a normal amount.
We've got a normal amount of voicemails,
which is to say like a million of them.
I can't wait for all the circumcision ones.
Oh boy.
No, I'm sure we won't have a single one about that.
Uh, this, this first one is called the green goblin lin or something.
Three, two, one, go.
Spider-Man.
I see you falling into my trap.
The choice mail.
And this subway car was a, it's full of people.
And this subway car has Mary Jane in it.
And that's the choice.
That's why it's the choice mail.
So choose Spider-Man.
That's, um...
Do you guys remember when voicemails were good?
No.
Anyway, next, next voice mail is called Voice Whale.
Voice Whale.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
There it is.
The tantalizing cry of the legendary voice whale.
I don't know what I was expecting.
I was like...
It's better than the average one.
Told you exactly what it was going to be and it was delivered.
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess, I guess I was the, I know, okay, that's the okay voice.
I'll take it.
Voice, Voice Whale for Voice Grail.
Voice Whale for Voice Grail.
The Grail Whale.
I think, I think we got to put the Voice Whale in the Voice Grail.
I'm doing it.
I'm making it official.
There he goes.
Perfect.
Gib, you missed the Voice Whale.
Gib, you're back.
You missed the Voice Whale.
But he's already ascended to the Grail, so, you know.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's the best.
You're going to have to re-watch the episode just to hear this magistrate.
Sad but true.
Uh, next one is called, uh, You Suckers Didn't Hate It, Here's Another.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello, and welcome to part two of the Sucker of St. Benedict, The Need Who Could, by Elzon.
But God, the mean old bastard just couldn't leave Ben alone in his cave.
No, no, he just had to make a priest share his lunch with Ben in the middle of Easter.
Also, some random shepherds found him.
No.
I do hate it.
I'm sorry.
It's not germane.
Uh, I'm in no mood for this horseshit.
Do you remember, you remember that one guy who did voicemails where he, um, he had like
weird audio mixes and ended with like little mini songs about each member?
Yeah.
That guy was cool.
I was pretty, those are the days.
I'm tired of all these wannabe Riddle My Ass Batman types.
Too bad we don't do that anymore.
I disconnected for what seems like 40 minutes.
Um, I just wanted to say, uh, that Cheesy, the things you were saying about art and working,
were so similar to my own.
That was basically entirely identical.
And, uh, I forget what my train of thought was beyond that.
I'm really annoyed that I've been gone this long.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Well, you got, you got my DMs again.
We could still talk about, uh, this stuff.
We're pals.
Yeah.
The best, the best tip was, uh, use, uh, the next chapter of One Piece as your, uh, as your,
as your carrot.
To beat you.
Yeah.
To doing things.
I don't read One Piece when I'm making the comic, but once like I finish and it's on Gumroad,
it's on Patreon, I'm like, all right, time to catch up on One Piece.
Yeah.
You, you reward yourself with something you like doing.
I'm pretty sure villain versus gonna, pretty sure villain versus gonna end before like,
uh, One Piece ends.
Well, yeah.
The universe will end before One Piece ends.
Oh my God.
In my opinion.
I'm gonna have kids when One Piece ends.
There's never gonna be a two piece.
You're the final reward.
Uh, okay.
Next, next voicemail is called misogynist for trans rights.
Three, two, one, go.
I believe in trans rights, but also a strict binary.
So to prove it, Ben, Tom, become trans because you, if you would support something, you'd
do it also.
Terrible.
Can't catch me to the jail.
Neal.
I thought it was gonna be funny.
Uh, I saw, I saw a tweet that was like, I don't know, the opposite is like the opposite
of a turf is like a trans inclusionary misogynist, something misogynist, reactionary misogynist
or something.
Trans it like, so a femboy.
A femboy.
You better get off my turf.
Does that, does that mean like, um, someone who, you know, like respects trans people's
identities, but also is misogynistic against trans women in the same way they would be against
cis women?
Oh my God.
Yes.
I think I, I think I know.
Oh my God.
I have the perfect guy in mind for that, but I don't want to out him.
I have a friend of mine sounds just like that description.
Um, although he, although he does it in jest, he's not like an actual misogynist, but this,
if it's perfectly what his brand, um, it's this guy called a yellow swag on Twitter.
He's a cool guy, funny guy.
Hey, fuck you, yellow swag.
He's a cool guy, a friend of the show, yellow swag.
Sounds like a major shed, if you ask me.
He's, he's cool.
He's a cool guy.
He's mutual with stone toss.
That's how you know he's base.
Oh, I've heard of that guy.
That's so cool.
No, I just, actually, no, I'm not joking.
I like stone.
I like, uh, I was gonna say, I like stone.
I love stone toss.
I'm a big stone toss fan.
No, I, no, yellow swag studios is a cool guy.
He did.
He did a cool guy.
Stone toss made a kind of good comic the other day.
He did.
Oh.
He actually did.
What did he do?
The comic was basically just the punchline is a guy works out and gets really buff to
attract ladies, but ladies don't care, but gay guys like it.
That was, that was it.
That's pretty good.
I think I'd seen that comic before.
I, um, I was not new.
Was it not a new one?
Um, no, I mean, like I seen the joke done before.
Maybe it's like the first time he's done it because I actually have it.
It's not an incredibly original.
It sounds like the story to my life.
It's perfectly fine.
And knowing stone toss, the punchline is, oh, how horrible gays are now attracted to
this person.
How unfortunate for them.
In other comics.
Yes.
In this comic, there was no, there was the gate, the guys just look normal.
I mean, sometimes like, you know, I mean, that's how it works.
Right.
You know, you got to throw in someone, just a straightforward joke, you know, so once
people like the straightforward joke, they get a red pill by the other jokes.
Right.
Yeah.
That's true.
I mean, there wasn't one point where I was like up to the, on every stone toss, like
a comic, like I read each one of them.
Cause I was fine.
I was fine to do a video.
A video.
Yeah.
Religious followers.
But I think even if you disagree with his messages, his comics are sometimes pretty funny.
Oh, I mean, they're very well, they're very well crafted.
I mean, I understand.
He's very good at what he does.
Like I read all of them cause I wanted to talk, I wanted to make a video talking about
how he does it.
So like lefties, like know what to do.
But basically.
Thoughts like I'm already made that video.
No, but I'll do it, but I'm a comic artist.
Yeah.
And he's a little bit more valid.
Obviously you could do it again.
No, but also, but I'd also like would draw like my own version of a stone toss comic
and I kind of have, I mean, I'll just tell you guys it'd be, it'd be the first frame,
the first panel would, would be like his little version of how he draws a trans person.
And then there'd be like a, there would be a guy next to him who's like the smug little
racist guy.
And on his shirt, it's the, it's the, it's the acronym for it's okay to be white is on
a shirt, right?
And, and the guy would say like, isn't it obvious?
And then this panel too, he'd be like, your identity is killing you.
And then it's that it's the mean number of like the trans suicide rates, which isn't real
by the way.
That's like not accurate at all.
Like the, was it 41% yeah, it would be 41% right above the trans person, right?
But then in panel three, the trans person is like looking at, at the other guy.
And then in panel four, the punchline is that right above the other guy, there is a 68%.
Right?
I don't get it.
Okay.
Because the thing is that, that white boys have like a higher suicide rate.
That's like 68%.
And I think there was an article explaining how like white, white boys have a 68% suicide
rate.
Yes.
That seems, it can't, it can't be true.
I'm probably misquoting it.
I'm probably misquoting it, but I think I was going to talk, I was going to talk about
that in my video, how like you have to kind of lie too, if you want to make a stone toss
coming.
Oh yeah.
This is supposed to be sad.
I swear, I swear it's like, no, but it was like a 68% or something.
Not like saying like.
I don't think 68% of white people kill themselves.
No, I don't think it's, I don't think it's specifically white people.
I think it's specifically like white males.
I don't think that's true either.
You don't think that's true?
No.
I don't have the stats on any of this though.
I can't, I can't say whether it's true or not.
It seems like an outrageously high number of people.
This sounds a little bit high though.
That would mean, that would mean that suicide kills more people than everything else combined.
More white men than everything else combined.
And I'm sure that it doesn't.
Hold up.
Well, I could be misquoting that.
There could be other shit that like I'm talking about.
Oh it's 69%.
White males account for.
Hold up.
Suicides is from.
They account for 69% of suicides.
It's not 69% of them commit suicide.
That's like a different, okay.
I mean, I was assuming I misquoted this.
I assume I misquoted the statistic, right?
Right.
Exactly.
Yeah, I see.
But what I'm saying is that like, you know, you kind of like, when you do a stone toss,
like he's not, he's not quoting that percentage like accurately, right?
Yeah.
Just like I didn't.
The point isn't the, yeah.
Okay.
I get it.
The point is not to be honest.
The point is to.
Is to have those kind of like quick snappy like.
The thing is, a lot of people are not smart enough to understand satire.
So they're going to just think you're legitimately making that point.
Uh, but it's true.
No, but it's true as far as I'm aware.
I mean, the logic with the whole trans suicide rate joke is that, oh,
we shouldn't help trans people because they just end up killing themselves.
Right.
Which is really fucking stupid logic.
So it's kind of like, oh, if you think that, then we probably shouldn't help like white boys
because they're also killing themselves like by a higher number technically.
I, I know that there's no point.
I know, I know that we've already agreed that the statistic is not.
Okay.
I keep wanting to argue it even though I know that's not the point.
Uh, yes, I understand.
I understand what you're saying.
Yeah.
Got it.
Guys, I don't, I don't hate white people.
I feel like, I feel like it would require a citation needed.
You would have to have like a little like hyperlink under.
It's like, here's the, here's the study that this is referencing.
He sometimes does that.
You know, we ever seen him do that once when he did a comic about circumcision.
Nice.
But I'm pretty, but I'm pretty sure what he was like, um, linking was like a documentary
that did, cause like when stone toss like does a circumcision thing.
He like, he, he, he specifically likes to blame women and Jews.
Right.
Like that's the, that's the only people he blamed for circumcision.
Same.
But that's like, that's like the M.O.
Right.
Why?
Why women?
Cause he hates women.
Oh, okay.
I guess that, I guess that.
I mean, like, if you're, I mean, if you're a Nazi, you're most likely also a misogynist,
you know, it's, it comes with, it's like a package a deal, you know.
Okay.
Yeah.
You know, I was, you know what, I don't, I don't need an explanation.
I really, I really don't.
Uh, uh, uh, it's just, yeah.
All right.
Got it.
Nice.
I don't even remember what we're talking about.
So let's move on.
So let's move on to the next one.
Uh, this one is called the last zoomer.
Three, two, one, go.
Here my plea.
And let me talk on the boomer.
Ben saying.
That didn't, that didn't rhyme.
I think the lack of rhyme at the end was for emphasis.
I think it was done deliberately and I think it was masterfully executed.
I guess it was supposed to make me mad.
You don't get it.
You were supposed to make you mad.
As far as I know, uh, Ben really hates it when people call him boomer.
I, I, I, I, I hate it when people say it and mean it.
Someone called me boomer.
I got to stop them and was like, wait, do you mean that?
I, I hate it when people genuinely don't know.
When, when, when, when I get, when someone calls me a boomer without the
knowledge that actually I am in fact a millennial, uh, I get frustrated
because we are, we're not the same.
Me and them are not.
The only true boomer is boomer co-anger from mega men X.
Nice.
Boomer co-anger at least.
I love that guy.
Never ate lead paint.
You know, he's just made of lead.
Did, did you eat lead paint, Ben?
No, the boomers did.
So they've all got lead poisoning and have no empathy.
Word, word.
I think the only boomer I like is, um, a Stereo's coconut.
He's a pretty funny guy.
He's, he's Gen X.
God damn it.
I sent him a free copy of Villainverse and he hasn't read it yet.
Stereo's coconut is supposed, has been, I've been supposed to go on a
Crystery podcast for like a year now.
And it's just, uh, I'm just, I'm just waiting on that call.
I'm just waiting on that DM.
Why don't you invite him to the PCP?
Hmm.
Invite Stereo's.
We could invite him.
We could, I guess we could invite a Stereo's.
Word.
Uh, but Ben.
You guys could do that.
There was a tweet where a Stereo's tagged the drunken peasants and you in
response to something about Nick Fuentes.
What was that about?
I was confused.
Yeah.
Let me, um, I remember the one you're talking about.
Uh, was it in response to a rational disconnect tweet about how Fuentes was
malding about not being invited on the Timcast?
Yeah.
Someone replied, someone replied with that image of a discord post that I had
seen before.
And actually, like a week ago, I was thinking of that exact image because I
saw a post from Fuentes that sucked because everything that Fuentes says
sucks.
And I wanted to post, and I just wanted to post that image in response of just
this guy explaining what a fucking loser, uh, Fuentes isn't always has been.
I didn't have the image.
How about that discord like message thing?
Yeah.
The one that the guy just describes like how he knew.
Shit his pants and like what a, what a turdy is in high school and how now he
just, he spends his free time harassing the church that lived across the street
from his parents house.
Um, and, uh, yeah.
A Stereo's tagged me and the drunken peasants and some other guy.
And I don't know why he tagged those people specifically, but I appreciated
it.
Well, the drunken peasants like actively shit on Nick Fuentes all the time.
Actually, like, well, good for them.
Actually, last, the last episode they uploaded is how I found out about that
whole discord message and him shitting his pants.
Um, yeah.
Uh, the drunk peasants are pretty cool.
Pretty cool guys.
I want to get on that eventually.
Hopefully I get enough clout that I could appear.
Uh, I'll go on any fucking podcast.
I went on shredded.
Nobody knows about shredded.
Yeah.
Ben is real desperate to go on anything.
I'll do anything for clout.
Yeah.
Anything.
Ben, I heard rumors that then voted for Biden.
So, you know, he has no morals.
I voted for Howie Hawkins.
2020.
I voted for Jojo.
Joe Jorgensen.
God bless America.
Libertarian.
Libertarians.
Uh, there it said it.
Rolotariat.
Ness voicemail is called advice three, two, one, go,
hurts to the podcast that you mean exclusively every consider something Christ Jesus looking
.
No.
It's kind of a little unnecessary at the end, that was little unreal.
I have.
I like how short all of them are now that's true a blessing in disguise I the
short ones I've noticed are the ones with the slurs so far so far yeah that's
true I mean to get I guess the game plan is like you say the slur then leave
right you don't want to stay yeah exactly that's the tactical in and out I
tactically use my slurs next one is called this one is called
flupidy doopidy zim zam zoop three two one go
on the tube oh my god this is I summer I saw yes I listen to a podocast when I
send off two message second message you say is that a samurai yes it is a
samurai this is what I talk about when braze rarix hard to grow up and do a
samurai voice you're cracking was all dysphoria you're cracking but for
anyway Ben no son you apologize you apologize now after steel scroll you
now say sorry well summer a foggy oh good all is a foggy one Ben no son no
want to scroll if for you sorry it okay but oh Ben no son you cause of summer a
father to commit or set a code and for that I shall not be forgiven but until
next time I think her father that they said something about gender in a past
thing and then they said dysphoria this time I think I think yes samurai might
be struggling to maintain their voice while also transitioning which is that's
correct these are these are the two bits that I put together oh god should I do
it should I say should I say sorry should I say sorry so Louis I see the
scroll you know this this person clearly puts a lot of effort into their samurai
samurai had his arc alright samurai came and went and you know what I think he
had he had his moment of redemption so I think I think he deserves closure all
right I'm gonna do it all right I'm gonna fucking do it Sam samurai sama I am I
Ben no saint oh son I'm sorry for steel scroll until next time Ben no
saint oh son great performance probably like the the most racist thing
you ever said on this podcast bed um yeah you know you're right I think you
might have said worse things in the past I never know nope nope nope nope never
never never never never never okay next one next voicemail is called it's not
Nate you know next voicemail is called a riddle three two one go if a tree falls
in the forest and no one is there to hear it what color is it green next one
wait what color is it I guess you just I guess you just go check later and then
you'll find all right it's true color wait is one of is there like a is there
a color that sounds like the sound when a tree falls maybe that's like maybe it's
like a pot it's a if a tree falls in a forest and nobody hears it then my
illegal logging business is a success
logging yes smoking weed yes it's weed color it's fucking it's 420 colored oh
my god you could do something with like saying timber when it falls and like
timbre as like a sound design thing like a sound thing is the timbre of us shut
up shut up I don't know anything this we might we might be thinking this real is
a little bit too smart that actually is it's it's orange okay can I go now if a
tree falls in the woods then how many times did I fuck your wife wood would
a woodchuck fuck if a woodchuck could fuck your wife it's rude hey five times
seven why would you say that look why would my my husband with my husband who
I hate and loath said that to me I would say what's so rude why would you even
say why would you why would you disrespect my wife son that way I do not
respect you at all my wife son is listening he can hear you my wife son is
a fan and I don't want him going and swearing at the neighbor's house when
he's playing video games because then I'll have to beat him and then and then
crush him under a felled tree and then smoke weed and then I'll punish him more
for smoking we I don't fucking know just call you callbacks to everything just
just hey at this point in the podcast instead of us doing callbacks just stop
the podcast go back to the beginning and listen to it again consider it all just
and you're like oh that's a callback oh that's a callback to the first frame of
the video is a callback to the first frame of the video oh the first time I
listened to it was just foreshadowing for the second time
it's obviously way funnier the second time around
obviously obviously go and repeat you should go back to the part where I
promote villain verse so I don't have to promote at the end again you should
skip over the part where I'm racist wait what Ben was racist what was that
time-staff now next voicemail next voicemail ha ha ha the next one is called
an answer oh my god we're gonna find out okay three two one go fall colors good
one okay so I wouldn't have thought of that because of autumn being the word yeah
I wait yeah you know I made a joke like this one it's winter isn't it no but
like I guess it's a pun yeah but a tree a tree doesn't always fall in the
autumn it can fall at any time I guess I guess but the joke is that the tree is
falling therefore it's fall colors yeah pretty much it's not about you're
thinking about this too rationally I mean I would assume he there's a lot of
information he didn't disclose just imagine you're watching one of my videos
yeah yeah you know like what he's gonna say like oh my god it should have been
it should have been if a fall if a tree falls in the woods what time of year is
it I mean that's a bit too obvious it's too obvious for you because this is the
same word shut up my my god my god no the joke's fine it's a good joke no it's
not it's a good joke mr. mr. riddle sir it's it sucks defend yourself he's a
good joke this guy he's a riddle a riddle lure if you will he does he does
him a lot hmm next one is called PCP website oh boy three two one go yeah I
just want to know if the procrastinators.com oh the procrastinators
podcast.com is that your guys's website because if so it looks so shit it looks
so garbage yeah it is that's the most basic looking template ass website I've
ever seen if that is not you guys whoever runs that needs to clean their
shit up I'd rather have like a basic ass HTML a tag fucking garbage website than
like this basic template shit clean this shit up if it is you guys I know you
know how to do graphic design because all your other websites look fine so what
the fuck's going on looking and I'm seeing that cactus and frankly I don't
know I love that cactus if we change all right that we first of all that is
our website second of all the point of the website is just so that we can
host it on iTunes we didn't think we didn't bother to like put any effort
into designing it in any way and third of all what the fuck's wrong with it it's
fine it's just a list of the episodes like like it doesn't need to be it
doesn't need to be anything more than this
honestly I think the only thing wrong with it is just that the image is a
stock image and not like PCP branding true we could change the one thing but
like that is bad about the template the template it just looks like a normal
template web but I think you're gonna see what's wrong with a template you work
for us right here I think this person this person doesn't like that it's
boilerplate but like it's boilerplate on purpose it doesn't have to be maybe
you should get me to make one for you
hold on let me go to is it gamers tavern.com or the gamers just gamers
tavern.com gamers you know I recently installed an SSL certificate which was
pretty difficult and costed me some money but now it's finally secure a
connection a lot of brown a lot of brown let's check on articles okay yeah text
articles check out the news okay there we go a feed feed going back to 2018 oh
no it goes back for even that there's not a single podcast on this website how
are we supposed how how can we possibly host it I didn't say I would host it I
just mean I meant I could make you a website for you our website is immaculate
our website is perfect it has function I mean I time immemorial I feel like you
know having a website and like making it your own and doing like a unique design
for it is is cute and cool and based and I don't knock that sort of thing I
just feel like yeah if you have no intention to run it there's no reason
for it to not be a template like it's just there yeah to to be the website
version of the archive yeah it gets it gets the job done we are not there's no
way people will find the podcast through the website you know I keep thinking
speaking of branding speaking of PCP branded banners and imagery I keep
thinking about changing our branding like our branding is fucked up now it's
it's like it's wrong I hate it I hate that every episode starts with the wheel
with with nine of us when there's literally like four of us now if that I
keep thinking about changing it but it's like it's like a it's like kind of a
big project and I don't know what I would want to do with it um new kind what
if I just announce a contest right now somebody fucking design us some new
fucking no no never no design a whole new intro and and with animation just
whole new name whole new guests remember all the whole thing I want to
overhaul the channel it's it doesn't it needs to look like what it is and like
now we got fucking we got mage on it we got to do on it we got munchies still on
it we got Jesse on it like who are these people they don't I don't know I don't
I don't remember I don't remember anything before coronavirus I think I
called one of them races once yeah oh cheesy you call everyone you fucking
Mexican this is the bensane is racist episode I did it I finally transformed I
talked shit about white boys and then that pulled the trigger and then I cracked
you cut cut you cut a liberal and a fascist bleak he got red he got red
killed like oh you just can't trust minorities out that's how it happens this
is this is what I get this is what I get I tore down the wall I tore down the
wall I I let you immigrate onto the podcast and and this is how you're
painting I guess diversity is a failed experiment not our strength catch the
next PCP episode with Nick Fuentes on the show
based based Tim Poole might not let Nick Fuentes be on on a show well well
we'll get May on too and they can they can finally the vile absolutely
embarrassing embarrassing hmm shame shake our head I'm doing it right now the
one-minute shake head remembrance there are oh they're more worse now yeah let's
keep this next one is called uh where is it next one is called um large cock
three two one go got transformers are so fucking cool whoever's listening to
this stop listening to this podcast go freaking buy some transformers not from
Hasbro because they do a shitty ass job but buy some of them sick ass custom
transformers that cost like a thousand dollars to be the next person are so
cool I jack off to my transformers every day and I am definitely not a virgin
alright very cool the funniest they still sell transformers this sounds like
my friend wonder what the funniest thing to me is whenever Lindsay Ellis alludes
to the fact that she used to write like erotic fucking transformers slash fiction
that's like the funniest shit I've ever she she really did that well she she
um she loves star screen it's a plot it's a she she mentioned she mentioned in
like one of the latest videos okay she definitely wrote fanfiction and she was
in the transformers community and like come on look at her look at her you know
you know what it was it's a star screen because there's like a lot of star screen
figures in the background that's that's something I didn't know about her a lot
of women like star screen I don't know why yeah I've she's not she's not the
only one um well because he's bad I mean he's not he's not the bad guy I'm
Megatron's bad too but then it's time to get a star screen is like trying star
screen is like the Judah to Megatron's Jesus star Starscreams Starscream is
tortured Starscream is conflicted like like Megatron you can you can you can
change Starscream yeah he hit you he hit you that one time but it'll be
different whoa whoa oh my god I think I think I hate women now get start getting
Starscream pills this is transit the new the new revamp of the PCP now extra
misogynistic extra racist before the members of the PCP are now Ben Gibb
Tom sometimes Digi and Starscream next voicemail is called relationship
question oh this will be fun three two one go hey there PCP just want to ask a
question about relationships don't I think we haven't had one of those in one
oh boy but yeah it's not the cringiest question is not should I maybe talk to
girl yes you should yeah no it's like what are you doing a relationship I mean
you fuck anyone but it was short you just so I don't really know what to expect
of a relationship and I think most of the stuff I was no fucking guide but just
do whatever you want to do friends like not in their face this is so funny yeah
thoughts that's a fun it's a funny question yeah did you yeah there is no
answer you just like like it's it's it's like you do what you want to do and
what they want to do and you see what you both want to do and then you do it is
usually sex do you um do you see my profile picture and there's like a
little plush version of pasta the clown oh yeah I see oh yeah yeah that was no
there's only one of them oh I mean maybe maybe eventually it'd be pretty dope but
um basically that was made by my partner so you know you can make plushes for
your in your relationship you know see what I don't you need to do is you need
to go and compliment your girlfriend say I like the yellow in your eyes and then
you'll say thanks that's due to complications from my hepatitis C
hell yeah that will get that will get a dialogue going you know you look like
you've seen a ghost picture oh this is a nice this looks this is actually based
on a music video from one of my favorite artists and I actually added him when I
made um when I made this picture and he retweeted he's a cool guy his name is
funder cat just look at that you don't have to watch the video just look at the
video the thumbnail the thumbnail the background looks a little bit like
Lisa the first it looks like a one of those backgrounds from earthbound
earthbound yeah yeah the background was made by my friend pug ugly he's a cool
guy I started the video and it looks the same as the phone yeah exactly that's
that's why I said you don't have to watch the video you just look at the thumbnail
that's what it's based on I like I like making my profile pictures based off of
like album covers or like anything kind of music related my profile picture before
this one was based on a title the creator album cover man I was I was tempted
the other day to change my Twitter avatar oh you know what I'm watching I
love my current discord avatar but I've had it for a long time it's Kazi's
drawing of me from the rfckcon I'm gonna change it I'm not ready to change my
my Twitter my 3d avatar by calisar but I think I'm gonna change my discord
avatar to be that gen 4 scientist sprite from Pokemon which is the best and looks
exactly like we should commission someone to make it a little bit closer to
what you look like now why would I do that when I can just do it my fucking
cell all right all right okay all right okay okay all right then there's an
artist no thanks okay look I oh my god I only made one circumcision joke you
don't gotta get so upset with me you are on thin ice this close to being out of
here the next next voicemail is called cross bad way to wake up falling off a
bunk bed three two one go
voice grail wait to get out of your bed in the morning that kind of reminds me
of I think cross is in voice jail I think he's he's got out I guess he's out
that was funny he just fell out of bed this this kind of reminds me of the
video alien misfortune it's only like a seven second video but it's kind of
literally that aliens okay three two one go oh it's psychic pebbles yeah
aliens misfortune yep what a damn shame for that blue boy alright next one is
called always like me some psychic pebbles it's just called a mozilla
named after his author one assumes three two one go so Ellen Page has
transitioned into Elliot Page and I think that's pretty fucking dope but
therein lies a problem I've made for myself I've dead named this person using
the name that they've left behind but what I want to know is and I mean this
with no disrespect I fully support trans rights I love what Elliot is doing at
I just want to know like how do we go about talking about people in the past
tense from when they used their former name like Elliot it will be Elliot going
forward no debate anyone who disagrees and is like they're always going to be
Ellen to me and their women like these people should be burned alive by fire
but their former name is engraved in our culture you know they still exist in
the past and I think that just because you change your name change your
identity it doesn't mean that that past version is erased is it wrong to think
that way and if so first of all I apologize and also how can this dilemma
be solved I know from people who know way more about this than me doesn't um I
mean okay it's a small dilemma but like I think that the reason you would you
would refrain from using their old name is on the off chance that they would hear
it and like I don't know they don't like to hear it yeah it's not that is
incorrect it's just that it's like potentially upsetting I'm pretty sure
I'm pretty sure that like by and large most people who transition want you want
you to refer to them by their new name even retroactively like pretty sure
that's generally the the the thing like the I think the only one okay I don't
know if this is even is like a good example like Chris Chan is a weird
example because she literally like refers to her past pre-transition self as
like a male and like a different person so but she's like the only one that I
didn't like con contrapoints doesn't didn't didn't she say one time that like
she doesn't consider herself to have always been a woman she considered
herself to have been a man who became a woman but she still goes by Natalie she
doesn't refer to old self as I guess I don't even remember what what her old
name was depends on the person I think it depends on the person I think I
mind yeah seems like the most most people say just use the new name I think
yeah yeah but I think in the case of a celebrity it's gonna be kind of impossible
to get away from your old identity because of how popular you are in pop
culture yeah I mean that's still be listed on old movies with the old name
and what can you do what a lot of news articles I've been doing that I kind of
appreciate is like they'll say like former star of Juno or star or star of
umbrella Academy yeah I mean you can say now it's not it's not wrong to say like
it's not wrong to say like Elliot Page formerly known as Ellen Page right like
that's it's not about it being wrong it's I really think it's just about that
because when it's on a smaller scale with a person like a personal friend you
wouldn't talk to them and X like toy like use the the old name for fear that
they would not appreciate it when it's a famous person it is a little bit
different but I don't think like if you're interviewing them you don't need
to use the old name necessarily and it would it would be kind of maybe kind of
rude depending on the person that they are I think as a general rule you
should try not to just because it'll be easier to for people to get used to the
new the new name but for historical purposes when you're talking about the
actors from a film I don't know like it's as long as it's not overtly
confusing I don't think it should be too difficult to to retroactively use the
new name unless the like if Ellen at the time started with a person who was called
Elliot and then you talk about the film and you say Elliot who's who you're
talking about that that's maybe a thing but yeah so I mean it seems like use the
use the new name unless there's some like specific reason not to unless you
need to you need to bring up the old name for some like specific purpose there
might be like little niche like little moments where you're gonna have to but
like that's probably be incredibly rare I mean I don't know how actively you all
be watching umbrella Academy or like Juno or all the other classic Elliot page I've
never seen I've never I've never seen anything that Elliot has ever been in
that's to my to my knowledge not even Juno I've never no I've never seen Juno
Juno is literally the papers the movie really no okay I mean it could be I
haven't seen it in a while it's Vapors for the movie yes nice yeah Magda gets
pregnant by Vincent that's a fucked up she gets like quote-unquote pregnant
it's actually like a stuffed toy she shoves up her shirt and people think
she's vagina oh wow what a what a lion can't I can't believe it
well I think she gets a big poobah she poops out a poobah child that could be
like I could be a dream sequence that could be that could be illegal that
could be erased from living memory hey I think I've just remembered that have you
seen I don't know whether you would have but there's this this I don't know what
you would call it I guess it's a dojin and it's mostly safe for work but it's
basically the the tale of this person who is literally Vincent from the Vapors
who is like a spoiled rich kid and this maid who is a lot taller than him and he
gets mad at about her being tall and treats her like shit and I know where
this is going and she she like she's continues growing because she's like
having gross births and it's like hi that's a fetish thing it's like really
tall like three meters tall he's like one meter something or other and he gets
he thinks that stupid woman she she can't beat me I'm the coolest guy ever
it's literally Vincent it's really funny sounds pretty cool no I'm not
let me link let me link okay look okay don't worry about it
Vincent's not a rich kid well he looks it's just how he looks and his attitude
okay I was referring to the personality damn Ben you should read it you should
read more Daniel Klaus um because he do ghost world yeah he did ghost world but
yeah a lot of his characters feel like Vincent types yeah I can I could I'm
not I haven't read that much of him but I could see that you should you should read
a wait it's called David boring that's like my favorite Daniel Klaus boring
yeah David boring I've never heard that it's it's pretty good I read it when I
was 14 and I was like whoa literally me this is literally me and then I read it
when I'm older and I'm like oh my god that was literally me but now I'm older
and more mature and more wiser I recognize that it's yeah and I recognize
like where David boring fucked up like oh my god I know why like he doesn't have
a happy ending I know why you fucked up cuz I I learned I learned Marty yeah that
was my experience playing Final Fantasy 8 at the time I thought exactly like
Squall from the game and there was a pretty pretty pretty embarrassing Squall
is disgusting and I love him because he's handsome that's the only reason yeah
same it makes me mad I'm naturally competitive with handsome men I want to
destroy them so I look better by comparison I can't help I want to
destroy them a no Lee at handsome men oh I'm so look at the tits look at those
tits look I like that's that's what I'm that's what I'm talking about it's
basically this he's he's short and he's mad about it and she's like oh I'm sorry
master it's very funny and what are they bone you know I think I think and days
left until the master gets shown his place by the maid what is the what does
that mean you gotta reach to find out my god I guess I have to Japanese sure
are great he's like half the size of her vagina that's crazy he could go all
the way in he could I think about it I'm thinking about it I'm skipping through
it he's fucking ripped he's fucking got a six pack you can become an explorer
you're not allowed to read okay I'm gonna read oh it's 55 pages geez who
fucking reads dojins I'm fucking just it doesn't get like particularly sexual
like nudity wise it ends on the cliffhanger so it's like whoa in the
next stop they're gonna bone maybe I do see panties though you do see panties so
that's anyway I've always thought this guy was just Vincent okay the boobs are
out though the boobs are out though oh god okay everybody just cool everybody
just cool for a second here we got to take a little smoke of that weed take a
little take a little toke take a little toke of the trees there on top of the
morning to you okay whatever hey fuck you next next voicemail here it is
you're coming right at you this one is called neon phymosis event going on okay
okay three two one go Foxy concession I'm interested on discussions from the
podcast was good specifically I was thinking about that time when Benga
met because you guys were praising a scene from Steven University they used
choreography from evolutionary Bill Newton a specific DJ I believe was
praising it because he's very in for you were in your episode your sleep and I
think I come up for a nice segment why the shit is good because you know when
you use when you construct a phrase use words word that existed before but what
is of most value is the meaning of the phrase what you're coming up that's new
even if what you're using are old century old words okay so what it evokes the
meaning evokes when the choreography is used in Steven University initially brings
your mind the things of no devotion and gender that is in Newton yes and it is
specifically meaningful for the character and the episode and and it's good I
and that was my point I understand good to be smart I don't I don't agree with
that like equating using words that have already existed to using a shot for
shot like scene choreography for like a like an animated bit because you don't
use those as words that's just a reference okay that I think I think he
said that as like an analogy and I think it I kind of understand that I think his
main point was that using the scene you know not not parodying but basically
recreating the uttina scene is like shorthand to evoke all the all the
emotions and the feelings and stuff that one would associate with uttina which is
true I haven't seen but I don't but I don't really think I don't really think
that was the intent of that scene and I yeah I don't think they expected that
like most people watching Steven Universe would have seen uttina and like know
what that is and have those emotions come I think I kind of think it was just
like a reference for reference sake I mean it's not gonna be cool like oh we
like this anime let's reference it in our show cuz we like yeah I mean I I think
that what he's saying a references I think that what he's describing you can
do that with a reference but I don't think that's what this one was doing I
don't I remember the argument being that you you just thought that it wasn't it
like you thought it was cool that Steven Universe had that bit of animation but
when you found out that it was a reference it felt less interesting and
then other people the others were trying to argue I thought it was a cool I
thought it was a cool looking scene but then when I found out that it was just
copied from somewhere else I was like oh well I'm not that impressed because they
didn't come up with it wasn't it that you were arguing that it's more better to
come up with something original than to make a reference yeah eventually
eventually I did we did kind of break it down to the point that I just think
that being original makes a thing better even if all everything else is to me it
just depends yeah I think it depends as well but in that one I'm saying all
other all everything all else being the same an original thing is better just by
virtue of being original I still I still isn't everything just copied from
somewhere else isn't isn't just villain versus the bad guys club
actually there's no story in bad guys club is they're just characters they
have no story but um yeah I don't think you can like like you can argue that a
reference is like never as good as something if you if you do say like all
else being the same you're basically talking about the reference and the
original and which one is better and I don't even know whether that's what's
like okay obviously it's an imperfect comparison yeah obviously there will
never be a case where one thing is original and another thing is is
derivative but they're the same because that doesn't make any sense one of them
had to come first I don't I think isn't like a lot of the media you like Ben is
like oh this pre-existing character but they're doing something they're not so
supposed to be doing is it not like a lot of what you dig what the fuck are you
talking about like tails get strong show good strong mr. boo oh god damn you're
absolutely right oh my god you do you do like that like oh pre-existing character
but they're not supposed to be doing this guys well in that like yeah in in
those contexts I think that you do carry over the whole cultural cachet of like
Pac-Man you bring him into the story and it and it brings something to it to a
deliberate effect or maybe not deliberate but to a specific effect I mean okay so
like to make it the story of those gets trolled could not be told it just couldn't
it wouldn't be the same without those that those stolen characters I mean I
agree yeah could I make a distinction would it be like Pac-Man the character
being in a comic versus a reference to how Pac-Man dies going like that yeah
like that being the reference used that would be like it's an unoriginal thing
versus Pac-Man literally being in there I mean I think that like that's so like yeah
no what I'm trying to get at is like there's a difference between referencing
something and using something that already exists because then the argument
of a references like is it is it better is it better than the original or like
would it be better if it was its own original thing rather than the reference
and if you're talking about tales gets trolled it's a different sort of
question maybe I'm being a little too hard on the scene because I think that
maybe the point maybe there is a point like the point is to just the point is
to compare Pearl to Utina which is like fair because I guess I've never seen
Utina but she's like a knight or something and she's like I don't know
she's heroic she's a pretty one of them has women or something okay just like
Pearl yeah that's that's what I'm like they so I guess spiky nose I guess maybe
I guess maybe it kind of does do that damn it only took a hundred episodes to
I don't think that they expect I guess I guess it's like an Easter egg it's like
an Easter egg and if you've seen Utina you might be like oh I recognize the
scene and it fits because Pearl is kind of like that most references like Easter
eggs yeah they are I am I reference the movie I reference the movie cannibal
holocaust in villainers classes you can ever guarantee that your audience is
gonna get a reference there's always gonna be some people don't get it yeah
I think you can expect you can expect that everyone will that basically everyone
well it's like okay this this kind of brings me back to when I said I watched
the show legends of tomorrow I literally watched that show for the references
because a legend of tomorrow references a lot of like DC comic characters like
very obscure characters and every time they do I do the soyboy face the you
know the face yeah with the Nintendo like I'm like I'm like watching legends
of tomorrow and I'm like oh Bawana Beast oh I know that guy they do the fucking
face that's my enjoyment of the show that's that's fine I guess I was I guess
I was a little wrong I guess you know I can I appreciate the reference a
little more now that I think about it but I still think that originality is a
virtue I mean I I mean I agree like yeah I mean luckily like the majority of
Steven Universe is original true yeah as long as they're not constantly doing
references and it's fine to have one every once in a while yeah I I know I
never said it wasn't fine I didn't it didn't add anything to it for me I've
always held the opinion that a reference should be like able to be enjoyed
without getting it and if understanding utena is important to getting that that
is a cool action shot then it's a bad reference but you could easily enjoy it
without knowing that yeah it just had to like yeah like how I use this this famous
wave and in the Lord of Ghosts it's like it illustrates that there's a storm but
it's also like hi I know that picture the use of the wave here is meant as
shorthand to evoke all the feelings of the original bigness and wetness yeah
I do the same thing with actually with my last panel for this page right here if
you look in the background like the silhouettes of those like characters
that are impaled that's a reference to the movie cannibal holocausts where people
get like impaled through their asshole out of their mouths that's pretty cool yes and it's
oh that happens that happens in reverse in infinite jest
yeah all right next voicemail is called uh next voicemail is called um are you ready
it's called I am gay three two one go this is absolutely the one with the girl from
new guy war infuriating to me because of the self-importance they imply self-importance
that the guest you spoke with that went unchecked despite it being uninteresting and
unintelligent because of the agreeable nature of you guys oh my god shut the fuck up I hate this
I see this argument all the time like you know the comic quite okay I'm not quite sure what he's
saying okay so he's saying basically that so Mallory's comic with with the dog like people's
problem is like oh no she's just so self-important about stealing it's like no she wasn't the
character just does it in a panel it literally like there's no like kind of like oh yeah there's
wait is that I thought this guy was saying something about murro logic no he said Mallory
and self-importance I he he was very hard to deter like I couldn't really well Mallory
totally am I took something completely I thought he was saying that like we let murlogic talk for
too long because we were too nice and we didn't why did I get a completely different message
hang on I'm really listening to it yeah me too yeah me too
yeah girl from new guy okay yeah that's Mallory um yeah yeah he's talking about Mallory
because he says the guy because Mallory also did the new guy Jesus Christ I fucking hate
it's so like oh my god it's so I'm gonna say it everyone who's mad at that comic
is fucking cucked I'll say that I I told yeah I agree I don't I don't get it at all because
it's bizarre because it's kind of like so do you think that a retail worker should be fired if
like someone steals like if just someone steals the retail workers should be fired
because like it seems like people say like because a lot of people said that
oh like the retail worker could potentially be fired if you if you rob the store and it's like
so you're kind of missing the point that that's like worse than like robbing a store right you
shouldn't point yeah the problem there is that they can be fired for that right exactly which
mostly they can't be like like in America that's not legal I mean it might happen but it's like
it's not normal I oh my god I a lot of what Mallory said like I did see to that um she was talking
about how like there was also like several lefties who also like weren't on her side about it which is
so crazy because like you should like a lefty should realize like um actually like a boss
shouldn't be allowed to fire at any retail worker that because as a real estate worker you're I
question what you're fucking what what what what theory what theory have you been reading if you
are not on board with this I really I literally have not read any fucking theory but like not
use this this hypothetical question yeah I go to me but I'm saying you don't even have to read
theories and be aware that like that's kind of a fuck worse fuck situation than like someone just
like stealing right like there's so many people I saw I saw this one long ass post where someone was
talking about that was their old job like oh someone stole who would get like potentially
fired or ridden up and then I and then I asked him like so do you think that you and your
fellow employees should have like unionized or commenced a strike or something or would have been
down for a co-op or whatever and they never like never fucking replied like it's so
Jesus Christ it's literally like the logic of like oh stealing is bad because the boss might
get mad and fire the employee it's literally like oh you can't you know uh yeah don't disturb the
we must pay homage to the beast it's literally like oh no no no you shouldn't you shouldn't
fuck with that guy you shouldn't fuck with that guy because he'll get mad and beat up his girlfriend
later it's like and she'll deserve it because you made him mad it's so it's like that logic where
it's all like ha ha have you not heard of death by cops or you're saying that like cops are just
like killers like we shouldn't fuck with them like they're by the fault like these bears that like
oh if you don't listen to what they say they could fucking murder you so you think cops are monsters
that technically like you're like missing the fucking point and that's what and that's why
they're good and that's why we should obey them they're because they're because they're so powerful
and they'll fucking murder you yeah it is which is good and i like that right exactly and i love
that kind of like a like a pessimistic like doomer mentality almost exactly like that we can't do
anything about it so we just have to like bend the knee to whatever is in charge yes it's capitalist
it's capitalist realism it's like there's there's no changing this this is an immutable law of nature
the immutable law of nature is that stealing is wrong because bosses will fire their employees
for things that are out of their control and we just we just have to accept that unironically
i think the only like i think the only lefty that i saw like um who who was like wasn't
defending mallory but he wasn't like saying like oh that ill stealing is bad i think is vosh
because i think um i saw him talking about i saw mentioned in one tweet saying like um seeing this
whole thing about like whether or not she's to steal from a retail store and he's like literally
who fucking cares because it's a fucking like stealing is a symptom of a bigger fucking problem
yeah it's not like stopping like you don't really fucking stop the problem if you just stop fucking
stealing it's these motherfuckers who think that that real life works like fucking batman like
batman isn't fucking making a difference at all that's why he lives in a fucking cartoon world
where that's where it only fucking works there i'm so fuck oh i'm mad i'm heated i'm heated no
yeah i get yep yep yep it sucks this is a fucking trigger for me stealing is okay so long as the
cops aren't around mad fuck the cops yeah fuck the cops yeah they shouldn't hey you know it would
be really cool is if there were never any cops around anywhere true that if we didn't pay if we
didn't pay for them we could have a word and another fucking thing that people ignored with the whole
like with that whole comic is that retail workers steal more than like customers like retail workers
like 80 80 percent of retail workers steal just from their job way more than any customer probably
true but also bosses steal more from their workers oh that's true then fucking even then they're
stealing you're like yeah like stealing your overtime motherfuckers be talking about i hate stealing
well you should probably hate like how much fucking you should probably hate you should probably hate
wage theft because it's like a hundred fucking times you should do this shop you should see how
much fucking moron you should see how much of a the biggest fucking criminal in the world is
literally jeff bezos because he's stealing from everybody no no no no no no no no he he earned
that he earned that he made a big website and that's how villain villain verse gonna end at the end
the villain's gonna turn to the camera say the real villain is jeff bezos the real and then he shows
up he shows up and he shoots the villain is like now i'm number one is what he's gonna say can you
just have can you just have a character like a villain in the world just be jeff bezos and like
he just appears maybe like two or three times in like the middle of a brawl you should you should
have a guy called chef bezos and he has a spatula just no no just just have regular completely
normal jeff bezos in the middle of all these like these like chainsaw headed freaks and so he's just
on the list he's down to like maybe number like 10 or 11 you know respect okay i'm not okay i like
i know i've been joking that i'm spoiling the ending but i don't want to give you guys i'll
tell you guys a spoiler after we're done recording all right deal jeff bezos and we'll have ellie
and we'll have ellie azar put it in the bone we'll have ellie azar put it in the bonus uh cut
if i get i didn't get my royalties from uh from spoiling villain verse
no uh wow wow bed save the royal team uh if you're royal
nobody gets paid here on the pro crastinators podcast that is the rule uh all right pro tag
three two one go no no no no no no no no no stop every every every single voicemail
pencil this pencil that pencil what if it's true i'm not no no no no no no no no no stop
we don't this don't give one you protect now congratulations what accent was out of the
protag now no they said gibbons the protag now yeah where's where's all the voicemail saying
that i should give back this where's where's the arc yeah where's gibbons arc about uh being hunted
down by her sensei i'm gonna say it i'm gonna say it i'm gonna say it i'm gonna say it right now
okay yeah i i blend capitals and then and everyone's so fucking yeah yeah brave it was a brave
statement to make brave yeah but i'm saying everyone is so uh capitalistic pill that they see
bet the anti-capitalist and they need to attack them like he's a virus they need to they need to
take him out of the system uh give hasn't give catchphrase isn't uh i blend capitalism so he
never i mean she never gets shit on her anything you have to be more contentious i don't know i
yeah i guess i do have to be more contentious like unironically that's why they nobody talks about
me ever that's why we call her gib the lib gib the lib very very cringe lips i'm not like vicious
enough or that's right um pathetic you don't get mad enough yeah i know when i when i was you know
i'm not pathetic i'm not i'm not i'm too strong unfortunately unfortunately um when i when i decided
to uh tenderize my chicken cutlets for a fried chicken the other day at one in the morning and
woke up my roommates uh uh one of my roommates asked me hey ben this reminds me why do i hear
pounding noises from your room like all the time and i was like oh that's when i read tweets that
make me really angry and i can't control myself and i just pound on my dad that's what that was
uh i thought you were gonna say like that's when that's when i'm fucking mad pussy dog that's
it is no i never i can't be mad never that it's just that when i get too mad it's sort of like
uncomfortable and nobody likes it and i don't like it and it's sort of i wonder if i'm gonna cringe
well if you want to uh if you want to be the protag you're gonna have to show up more often
what uh if you want to be the protagonist you're gonna have to show up more often
i show up never to do that you're gonna have to you're gonna have to have an arc i'm sorry but
you have to do it i mean i mean i guess it kind of works like uh give is the one everyone loves
and ben is the one everyone hates you know it's about you're gonna make sense you're gonna need to
have you're gonna need to undergo some character development you're pretty you lack you're pretty
lacking in character next next episode uh ben becomes the lib and uh give becomes the anarchist
we have a brain transplant just like i don't know it could be more mean i don't know i i'm not
i'm not i'm not cool to do that i'm not good at i i like if we're talking like uh character
archetypes like i'm definitely the baby face of the pcb i'm always like the good person and i'm
right and smart and the best i'm the chopper and i've been like fucking
turned into a stuffed animal that doesn't do anything just me too makes it feel any better
i i see endless i see endless love forgive and the ben saint discord all the time i think
just gotta do more but wait and tell me next time and i'll ban it i'm one of them is your mods and i
i'm like half the half the people half the people in there are my mods uh that is that is
just ban your mods that is yeah um there's a real a real glut of mods somebody needs to clean
the house we need to do some cleansing in there uh all right next next voicemail next voicemail
is called life skills three two one go say it with me sucking dick it's a basic life skill
another gender role kind of kind of agree they should they should teach it in school kind of
kind of agree like you know sometimes you gotta suck a little dick you know to like i sucked a
lot of dick to get on this podcast got me oh that's that's a boy you can say you can say that again
it's gotten me out of a jam or two once that's a jam when i had too much come
and i just needed to get rid of
i just uh it's like oh my balls are so full but there's no receptacle i
oh get me out of this out of this oh my balls they're so full oh i haven't jerked off in weeks
that's pretty much the one jam it can get you out i i've done no no not november my balls have
grown huge they're so full i like i read a i read a i read a manga i read a manga about uh uh uh
going through no not november and building up all the cum and then just exploding at the end of it
uh yeah there's a lot of people doing those i mean it's uh it's it's how it is it's how it
you gotta you guys trendy you know it's topical right it's very topical yeah you know you gotta
everybody knows yeah exactly everybody's on the level you gotta be a marketer for your cum
next voicemail is called mozilla fenneken but after listening to the entire podcast three two one go
i absolutely loved that fucking worthless consumer of oxygen that you had on the last episode it wasn't
bad enough that he absolutely sucked shit at telling stories but he goes on about how he worked
this job that was oh it was so horrible i i had to stand around with a fucking broom for seven
hours oh god help me oh fuck i got bored at my job wow i'm i feel so bad for you you work a job
that was just fucking boring you didn't have anything to do oh no here's how you can fix that
you know it's this is such a crippling issue for you go work at a taco bell go work at a
fucking amazon center yeah these places suck shit and you will lose your humanity but hey
you have something to do and they'll hire literally anybody they will hire your fucking worthless ass
that types that 30 words per minute which makes it even funnier that he's sitting in the fucking
pcp common sec you go no but but but but it's fucking shut up god i absolutely and then oh oh and
then i you know he cusses out his job coach or who the fuck ever oh because i get mad at women i'm
so edgy i'm so fucking interesting wow man i thought you hated bread why did you get a
fucking bread fetishist on the show no more bread no more bread fetishists on the pcp or whatever
fucking worthless you you knocking it out when the guest i love gamers tavern love that
low art guy love everyone else uh but that guy fucking sucked fucking bye oh wow i was mentioned
here look look how invested you are no you think that guest sucked but he got you invested you know
what this is what he he was here to make you mad wait he did it it's that strategy you know you get
something that the you get mallory and all the right wingers shit on her and then you get um
murlogic and all the left left guy shit on him you know i don't even think you have to be a lefty
to actually you know we're like you know you just like a general piece of shit yeah just generally
annoying just just purely for the fact that they couldn't tell a story just at all i mur i i'm i'm
pretty sure that murlogic um i'm pretty sure that he like remember how hard it was to drag out of him
like what he does for money yeah exactly i'm pretty i'm pretty sure he was just on he's just on uh
unemployment like tons of people are right now and i'm pretty sure he just like wouldn't say it
because i don't know he was embarrassed or something like i'm pretty sure he that's what he was dancing
around um which is very it's um i just i just wanted to talk about funny funny bitches with the red
that's all i wanted i wanted i wanted to ask him if he had read homestuck but by the time i hadn't
like like do you ever heard of riska circuit and it was like it was gonna be a funny thing but like
it was too late i was done briscus briscus briscus circuit deforestation the land of uh land of uh
alternium i noticed he's uh is there a planet with trees the the troll plant has trees this
alternium has trees no i mean like i mean like a spur planet uh i mean like a spur i noticed
he's uh kind of going through all the comments and replying to all of them uh that's kind of weird
yeah he he's he's he wrote like a hundred he like half the comments on the last episode are him
is like he's he's replying to every single comment reply to me oh i'm gonna i'm gonna check let's see
what he said pretty weird okay i did i did call him a nazi too um i don't know guys can we can we
just enjoy an asshole no i i love assholes but like i'm just i i understand i understand
people not liking the guest i i was a little surprised by how people were like mad about
the fact that the guest was unlikable to me that does not seem like an inherent problem
yeah like i mean yeah you know you're it's an investment yeah you know people are getting
engaged like oh we i don't fuck with this guy i'm gonna reply to him it's like like let's
like the disney come the disney world policy is like a bad experience that's been made up for
is better than a good experience so i it's like i give you stock home syndrome like i make you
listen to a bad guest and then and then i apologize on the next episode and then you love me more
than you did in the first place sometimes i convinced you that it was all part of a bad
guest can provide you with more entertainment trust the point i think actually i that's why i
think uh dick masterson sometimes gets really terrible guests just to basically uh make fun of
them or allow them to make fun of themselves by just saying the weird stuff they say i i think he
i think he definitely likes all the bad ones because he seems to be in pretty friendly
relationship with anybody on the yeah i mean dick dick just is i don't know he likes to
extend all of brunch's just for politeness sake he so that he loves not why he loves not wisely but
too well i think he just loves not wisely but too well i mean sure like he's a classic
bibronic hero i think he just a nice guy um nice guy sucks that 50 percent of the guests are
nazis but nice guy i guess i think he just uh bs is a lot of them to trick them to come on to his
show more was that i don't watch that fucking show i think he just uh is pretends to be nice to a lot
of them just to trick them to continue to coming on to his show and provide more entertainment
my impression has been i feel like he's choking back he's pretending he's sort of holding back
his laughter yeah at least i don't i don't know how often at least sometimes i haven't listened to
one of his shows in in a while but yeah it does a lot of them when they're very strange i remember a
guy who's like like all talking about black pills and stuff extremely seriously oh was it sernovich
yeah like yeah that guy's a fucking monster oh yeah he's a real piece of shit real garbage
experience i i think i think the stereo's coconut figure that out and that's why he's like
not even on the show anymore um you know that's what i thought i mean but i can't find any record
that like i mean but the stereo is left for that it doesn't seem like there's any like public
falling out between them at all no they didn't have a they like i think a stereo knows that if he
does have a falling out with dick it's basically over for him because his community is just too
tight with the dick show so it's kind of like i i'd be too fucking risky of a move i already
built like an internet presence and dick is sad not i mean not sadly but like he's attached to that
and now like if i like if i shit on it or like you know because he is much more like liberal i think
he got more liberal the more i don't want to i don't want to i don't want to speculate i don't
want to speculate on is stereo's interiority i mean yeah but i will say that for my part yeah if i
were close with the dick show and i decided i didn't like it anymore and i didn't want to be a part
of it anymore i would be very afraid to like alienate that whole group oh yeah uh because
there's a lot of them and i feel like a lot of them are highly amoral and who knows what the
fuck they would do unironically it's uh yeah i think the ship has already sailed on that one
um no nobody no literally nobody who listens to the dick show listens to the pcb not a single
solitary soul i guarantee and i promise oh yeah that's i hundred percent confirmed
i know every fan of the pcb i know every single person that listens to the show because there's
like a hundred of them and they just listen like 20 times each and that's why we get a few thousand
views but i remember specifically uh one time dick had this weird creepy stalker guy on his uh
on his show and uh he was he was pretending to be nice to him just to have him say weird stuff
and uh the guy didn't figure it out i think his name is chris the kiwi or something like that
and uh that rings eventually he he figured out that dick was just bs-ing him and now he
hates dick and is trying to dox him and stuff uh yeah i mean i would hate i would hate someone
that did that to me i think there's only a handful of people who could potentially dox dick because
i think he lives he unironically does like live in like some secret hideout kind of those
i remember in in in a in a side of a mountain in in los angeles yeah like that's how his show
starts it says like from a hidden base in the mountains hidden by from the side of the mountain
in the city of failure yeah i think yeah and i think did you did confirm that that is accurate
but did you did not disclose the location and he's got like i didn't he's got mines and and bazookas
and sniper rifles no i mean true no it could take out a dick and i mean i don't want dick to get
dox i don't think he deserves to get dox i just think i just i assume he just lived in the fucking
city i didn't know any of this there's a hand there's a handful of people i think could deserve to
get dox but i won't say i mean some people deserve i don't want to literally anything that might
happen to them but some people just want to watch the world burn exactly how many more voicemails
we got there are exactly two more voicemails hell yeah and uh this next one is called mad
three two one go you stupid motherfuckers kept sucking you on the bread guys dick because the
boss is worth a money on stupid fucking commissions and because he kept repeating this catchphrase
like what was it because i'm sorry he's a he's a funny he's a funny he's not he didn't make that up
he got it from fortune yeah or whatever website he goes through um because he didn't repeat it
because he's a genius he repeated because he's an artist he doesn't know how else you to speak
is an obsessive fucking stupid motherfucker and and and that how you guys came off on on this
this episode really dumb agreeable pieces of shit i think god this guy hates it when we're
agreeable i think i mean it was digi who called him a genius marketer i didn't know it was from
yeah that that was very kind of like it was just i don't know digi thinks that guy's a genius
wow wow digi's digi's easily impressed by something stupid amazing it's that
i don't know i i i did feel a bit bad like afterwards because i was like i wasn't prepared
for all of their stupid political stuff that they had in their head i i thought it was just
the wonderbread guy i didn't know anything else about them and so listening to that i was sitting
there listening to them prattle on about like conspiracies and i'm like i need to tell this
guy to stop because it's stupid but i i don't want to come across like i don't know what i'm talking
about and i couldn't formulate like an argument i wasn't really in the like the right mindset to
like argue with someone about that loudly i had i had the sense that he was that kind of guy but
i also kind of just didn't want to talk to about him about that with him because like who cares
what he thinks about any of that stuff i mean that's i mean that's the that's the thing like
it's kind of like i i think about this too because sometimes i want to have potential guests
that i disagree with on my podcast and cheesy cast cheesy cast youtube channel by the way
link in the description link in the description but um but i'm thinking like the thing is like
if you ask them to get on and it's like like you're not you're not paying them to get on it's
kind of like oh you kind of got to be nice to them unless you're like i'm not gonna like i'm not
gonna be rude to the guests like right to their face i'm gonna wait until they leave and then
do it behind their back unless you're like debating them or something unless it's like a blood sport
thing or if you're paying them i feel like if you pay a guest you you're probably allowed to be a
piece of shit to them like i'm gonna like i'm gonna at least wait until the episode is all recorded
look and then before i start an argument look if it makes it feel like yeah what's great about
that time that uh what was his name bill bill um mary um a talk show host guy he had uh he was
liberal mar bill yeah he had uh milo on his show and everybody really didn't like that
yeah i mean bill well milo is a fucking piece of shit i i built you can have people want to show
you disagree with it doesn't mean that you agree with him isn't it bill mayor is that is it mayor
i thought it was mar uh well her i mean it was kind of fucked up about that is oh yeah bill mayor
or bill mar i fucking we kind of fucked up about the bill mars shit is that um they were he was
very friendly to milo like very fucking friendly and then when milo got exposed as a pedo apologist
he was acting like oh well you see he bill was trying to claim that he was the one behind it even
though it was like the drunken peasants who exposed them as like a pedo apologist
right yeah i heard something about that yeah yeah um either way it's pretty obvious that uh bill mar
didn't agree with milo at all about most of the things he said that was made obvious on the show as
well i haven't i haven't seen it so i haven't watched it in a long time maybe maybe i remember bill mar
being very friendly but i guess he was just friendly maybe he did disagree with a lot of things
but being friendly doesn't mean you agree with the other person true true i mean you're not wrong
i don't know i personally have no idea i have absolutely no idea i haven't seen the thing i
never saw the thing what's great about this episode is that like which instead of like you
shitting on the guests you get the guests of the next episode is shit on the previous one like i
i mean i did it for you basically i i hopped in and one of the first things i said was like i
think mere logic is a nazi he clearly has nazi vibes i think he's just a shitty libertarian
which like i mean sort of tomato tomato i mean uh when push when push comes to show the push comes
to shove like i know who's side they're on yeah for sure i did i did not see that coming
i should i should have because um or i did because like before like i talked to him very
briefly like before the the the pod the episode like just to tell him like you know get him in
the server tell him like how we record and stuff with the time you know unlike some people i told
the guests when we record the podcast uh and then and he and he was and even then he started talking
about jannies and how the jannies do it for free like in text and i had to tell him like listen
i have to go make curry now i can't just talk about i knew there was going to be a problem
when he mentioned that he was like a fan of of of legendary ben saint enemy of mr meddaker
uh he yeah yeah he did uh man i fucking hate that guy yeah because he said he was
spouting this conspiracy theory that meddaker invented i'm like hold up hold up hold up
listening to it which one was that uh when he said that like oh the media companies
oh they're gonna they're gonna wipe us they're gonna wipe us they're gonna censor us all out
there they don't like the narrative that uh that trump is president so it's against their
narrative they wanted hillary so they're gonna soon like wipe us out uh in the biden administration
and it's like it's like all it's like this conspiracy it's this whole conspiracy theory
that like oh yeah big tech companies they're a hundred percent progressive you know they're
totally left-winged you know nothing is more socialist than like powerful i mean meddaker
didn't invent that point of view no but i'm but i'm saying i think he's he mentioned how that's
like one of the final things meddaker's went before he became kind of silent recently was this
conspiracy theory that he dropped i mean it's not an original conspiracy theory no conspiracy
theory is like two original nowadays but i'm just saying the fact that he like a hundred percent
believes this conspiracy theory invented by a known reactionary um it says a lot about for sure
it says a lot about the guy yeah i mean it all it all fits it all fits with uh with uh the the
portrait the portrait that i have built in my in my uh interior mind space hey we got one more
voicemail we got one more and it's called orwell was based three two one go animal farm is more
about how totalitarianism is bad rather than communism after the animals overthrew the humans
which are of course an allegory for the bourgeois capitalists they collectivize and have a pretty
bombast time it's only after one of the pigs goes full dictators at things turn for the worse
i see how people can interpret the story as anti-communist but i perceive it as being
about how totalitarianism can sneak into any ideology george orwell was a democratic socialist
in his memoir an homage to katalonia he talks about how cool anarchism and collectivization are
i highly recommend you read it i've heard that orwell i don't know that much about orwell but
i've heard that he went to spain to kill fascists but i also heard that he like snitched on communists
hmm that's interesting i am i i do i i agree i agree with his voicemail um it's it's something i
kind of like figure it out um where i was talking i was arguing with one of my friends and they were
trying to convince me that stalin was a fascist and i'm like uh no he was like a bunch of other
things that you can associate a fascist with but like his ideology wasn't like fascism fascism like
at all right yeah and i i think to be honest i don't really know that much about stalinism
in specific yeah me me neither i know a couple things around it but i but the thing is like what
the thing is like all fascism is like authoritarian but not all authoritarians are like fascists
right i think with fascists you need kind of like there's a couple of like key factors like
oh like a return to glory and you need like a scapegoat uh to blame everything on it's like
i mean it's like um there are a bunch of things that fascism tends to be like but it doesn't have
to be any of them because you know i think that also due to the fact that fascism wasn't like
invented in the university it was like invented in the streets it's like almost pure emotional so
it's like isn't isn't fascism like yeah supposed to be the the return to um like a a state of things
where people are on top and people are underneath and that's just the way it is and there's no
there's no like reason that gets to that like it's just um i think i watched a video by vorsch
yeah who who talked about like politics 101 or something and he explained like back in feudalism
times or some some you know peasantry medieval people was dumb they couldn't read them right
um people generally just believe that the kings were ordained by god and that's just how it is
and there's no there's no reason and then there was the age of enlightenment or whatever and
people were like wait we can think oh my god and so like like fascism tends to go back to an age
where people didn't think about anything and they just said these specific people are on top just
because and these these other people are subservient and that's just how it should be
there's no logic there's no reason there's no like ideology that you could really point to
that explains it because they don't think in that way i i think that yeah i think that does go hand
in hand with what i mentioned about a return to former glory like uh musulini like oh return to
we're returning back to roam i mean higher hierarchical hierarchical thinking is just kind of
this the the thing is just kind of the defining feature of like the right generally like like
that's that's what makes you like further right to a certain extent is like how hierarch and fascism
is a far right ideology so it is it is also an extremely like you know those at the top and
those at the bottom and those at the top are just there because they're the right just because
they're there and it's you know it's always seems to be that the people who would benefit most from
fascism are the ones who want it back at the top weird capitalism is very hierarchical too well
what i want to know is is dr eggman fascist uh he's like a tech i tell like a joke was coming
he's like a techno fascist dr eggman in prisons animals in robots for some reason
because the robots are powered by the small animals i feel like this was the only human
being in the world i don't think there is politics well i think he maybe his i mean i don't know
maybe his plan is like to return to the former glory or an imagined time i mean he's authoritarian
that's for sure like like eggman like with with maria right bowser steels princess maria has motivation
sonic rescues animals but does eggman just want to imprison animals is that the idea he wants he
wants he wants he wants a robot arm he wants the chaos emeralds to kill who there's no one else
i think does it the chaos emeralds like he just wants power the chaos emeralds like can work
reality right maybe he's trying to bring back all humans he he and there are humans in sonic
he imprisons he imprisons the you're right you're right he imprisons the animals to make the robots
to gain power and he uses that the the robots to seek the master emeralds to gain even more power
he just wants to take over more he just wants to be the most powerful boy he's just pure he just
he's like a dr doom type that just wants as much power as possible because he just thinks
everything will be better under his rule now i want to watch a a cyber shell video about
what is eggman's ultimate plan what if eggman did it all what what would happen
well what what what what if eggman won there's probably there's probably an archie all the
chaos emeralds and he turns supersonic at his mustache went gold there's actually there's got
to be there's got to be a run of sonic the hedgehog comic books that is like what if eggman won like
it's impossible that there isn't probably but yeah this question actually was already answered in
sonic cd is in sonic cd there is a bad and good futures so the bad future is basically when eggman
won isn't it isn't that it's just like a single it's just like a single frame of like the city on
fire isn't wait isn't the first sonic the bad future because sonic is only one is it sonic is
like the last fucking timeline cyber show what's the sonic timeline please i need a video he's
probably working on it right now hell yeah i i i think i think that uh did the timeline go is
sonic one and then sonic two and then sonic three and then knuckles and then that's the timeline and
then knuckles two and then knuckles three knuckles three and tails is somewhere else we don't talk
about him he's having this sky adventure spin-off game uh um um um or well or well uh i think he was
okay or well that ends well or well that ends well baby we did it no we finished the voicemails
wait let me let me refresh what if we've gotten a new one oh my god we got one all right i'm gonna
do it hell yeah i'm gonna do it i'm letting i'm letting darin the red sneak one in at the last
second you cheeky little bitch uh you fucker all right here we go uh three two one go so i have a
very specific issue and that's with tv remotes why are they not rechargeable it makes no sense
that they're not rechargeable tv remotes i'm ironically true though they're not what do you
you know what a tv remote is no i mean like the the idea of it not being rechargeable like
why don't you switch batteries out from them where would you plug it in batteries what well you
just have a dock like on your on your like you know i don't know i literally cannot even recall a
single time i've needed to change the batteries on a tv remote really last for 20 years i i remember
like so many times i had to change the batteries well i guess we also we also did the thing where
like if one thing needed batteries we'd switch it out of another product and put it in it we
we had like my dad had like all this like sound equipment he had like a dvd player and a stereo
and all these like other stereos and all these like and like the tv was hooked up to like a
surround sound system and that had it so we had like six different remotes and like i only knew
what like one and a half of them did um so we had all these fucking remotes floating around and then
they were all needed occasionally so yeah i was batteries needed changing uh uh on the fairly
regularly they're all needed occasionally just like dough i i think i i agree yeah like uh uh
just yeah make them make them rechargeable fuck batteries i i guess i i yeah i agree with it
it's every never something i've never thought would see the only the only time i fuck with batteries
is my my wireless mouse when i when my wireless mouse drains its single double a battery and
i have to change it and every time i do i'm like god i can't fucking believe that a device that i use
uses double a batteries why why are we still doing this yeah everything should just be
rechargeable nowadays yeah what the fuck nintendo yeah what the fuck um uh she'll get around me
logitech what the fuck company makes this this mouse i don't batteries in 2020 uh cringe they are
cringe we should have been done with them but then again capitalism should have solved many it was
supposed to solve most of our problems again fucking do it once again cheesy was right it was all
capitalism
oh no the capitalism is choking bed
capitalism is escaping from his pores hey i've i've got a joke i've got a joke about pizza
uh sorry it was it was too cheesy sorry
so yeah at cheesy manfredo on twitter make sure you follow me um got pre-orders for physical copies
of villain verse available check out the villain actually today is got the villain actually today's
the last day to order the pre-orders by the way if you're listening to this yeah yeah if you're
listening to this today is the last day of may uh december 11th yeah the last day to get your
pre-orders link in the down there if you don't think if you don't think i'm an annoying cut uh you
should check out villain verse and while you're at it uh also check out youtube.com slash gamers
tavern show and gamers tavern.com and uh on twitter at gamer tavern check these fuckers out
guys and also go to uh speakbike.com slash pcb voicemail and patreon.com slash the procrastinators
is that right the procrastinators you've asked that like the last 20 weeks i've become i it's
just become habit now i can't ask the i can't say it without asking the question uh is that right
you're you're you're inviting the viewer to go and check and then confirm the dementia is finally
hitting bed no no it's learning it's called muscle memory because i'm so strong no you don't
learn when you have dementia ben actually it's the opposite you start forgetting things uh
patreon.com.com slash oh no i'm typing it 30 words per minute i'm fucked uh the yes the
procrastinators i got it you know what i'll never have to ask again because now i know now i know
oh yeah patreon.com slash the procrastinators that's gonna do it all right another fucking week
all right cool so you know if you like cheesy manfredo make sure you go to the comments and
talk talk shit about him another three hour and 40 minute fucking podcast we do it for free
we do it for free we do it for free for free he's like ben saint does it for free
i'm doing it for free that's for sure i'm doing it for free also i you two are literally you two
are doing it for exposure i mean yeah i mean i i mean i automatically like this podcast uh you
know been through it through thick and thin um imagine liking the pcp i think i i actually had
some beef with this podcast every every podcast i get on i i have beef with them in a way um
ben fucking stole my lineup of guests he stole my plan to create oh he stole my plan to create
ultimate uh controversy and clout the plan was the plan was to have mary weather and then mallory
because with that combo you know people are gonna get fucking mad because everyone thinks you're so
cool because oh lol you're your friends with mary weather and he's such a chill and cool guy and
then you bring in mallory and then those same people like turn on oh she's so unlikable and
uh she's so self self-righteous self-important right right exactly those assholes start showing up
and i was gonna do that uh for my cast but uh uh mary weather didn't didn't didn't accept my friend
requests on just splitting the audience just split it and split it over and over and over until
there's nothing left that's how you run a fucking business i mean that's all i am that's some hot
goss for you yeah i need i think i'm gonna i i do have i think i'm still gonna do that anyway
i'm still gonna do the mary weather than mallory but i do have a guest after mallory that will bring
back more uh more division in the cheesy cast fandom good yep that's what you want yeah i'm gonna
do you want your audience to be fighting each other so they're not fighting yeah i'm gonna
interview stiltos that's the next guest very good all right we should wrap up this is fucking too
long all right all right good night god bless god see you all in my mask it's over