Hello, ladies and gentlemen, welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Oh, it's a pleasure to have you.
This is 120, isn't it?
This is episode 120, that's correct.
Episode...
We got all the power stars, everyone.
Is that...
Oh, right.
Yoshi is confirmed for Smash.
Oh, can we get Yoshi on the podcast?
Yoshi!
There he is.
I checked his Twitter the other day, and he said some real racist shit.
I don't know if we want to get into that.
That's true.
We got to keep his race realism to a minimum on this podcast.
I'm the best guy ever, and we're joined today by Yoshi.
Wahoo!
It's me, Yoshi.
All right.
Also Munchy's here.
You know it.
There's Yoshi's digits.
There he is.
Ben St.
You know, I remember, like a couple days ago, I thought of something really funny that I
would say for my intro on the next PCP.
It's totally gone.
No one will ever hear it.
I'll never remember what it is.
So I'm just going to disappoint everyone.
That's what you wrote it down.
Yeah.
Ben, it would have been so easy for you to just say that and not have actually come up with
any thought.
Then just think to yourself, I'm going to just say that I have thought of something.
I'm going to say that I've thought of something on the podcast.
This whole thing can be a little just as bad.
I don't believe you.
Curious.
No one will ever know.
And also, it's also Mage.
I am forever suffering.
Hello.
Greetings, individuals.
It's another one of these that you've signed up for, signed away your soul in time for another
episode.
Here we go again, everybody.
There it is.
Shout out.
Hey.
I checked my podcast listing app, which I use to listen to other podcasts, Cast Box
on Android.
Shout out and free advertising.
Shout out if you're listening to this on Cast Box right now.
We have two comments, one of which I don't even think is pertaining to the podcast.
I have no idea what it is.
Here, I'll get it up right now.
The procrastinators.
We have something like 400 watches or something.
It's absolutely better.
Just like us.
No, no, no.
We only have 100.
Wait, where is this?
The two comments on...
It's on a podcast listening app, like one of the most popular podcast apps on Android.
Basically, I have no Android listeners is what this means.
By Austin Baker, you guys want to wrap these up?
Oh my God, what are the implications that the episodes need to be shorter or that this
whole thing we're doing just needs to stop now?
That's a wrap, though.
That's a wrap.
Oh my God.
I love you, Austin.
All right.
Then by Xavier Jackson, I don't know what the fuck this means.
The vague helicopter parent slash millennial pussy slash let kids fight and get bullied
narrative was lame, especially in the light of the common counter example she presented.
What the fuck is this guy on about?
Maybe he commented on the wrong podcast.
Lately, I get all these comments from people where they take whatever I've said and then
assume that because it sounds kind of like something some philosopher said, that I am
basing it off of that or whatever other thing they've heard of.
For instance, in my video about Isiah from Doodadada that I posted the other day, I got
two different comments being like, oh, your Hobbesian social ideas are incorrect.
I was like, I don't even know who Hobbes is.
Maybe they're not saying you read Hobbes.
Maybe they're just comparing your ideas to those of Hobbes.
One of the guys literally described me as trying to out Hobbes Hobbes.
I was like, well, I haven't read.
I was like, what exactly is the problem in this video?
He's like, well, it's clear that you just got all your ideas from Hobbes.
I'm like, I don't know who Hobbes is.
I don't know how that's possible.
I only know Calvin.
I haven't gotten to Hobbes yet.
I'm very confused right now.
The weird thing about it is that a lot of the times, the things I'm saying might be
Calvin and Hobbes.
They might be close to them.
God damn it.
Yes, they are.
Sorry.
They're named after Calvin and Hobbes.
A lot of the times, the things I'm saying, they might sound tangentially similar to
what these guys are saying, but the part that I didn't say that they would have is the
most important part.
People take the fact that you said something kind of similar, and then they just extrapolate
that you also mean the rest.
It's like, no, I don't mean the rest.
I mean the part that he said that was correct, and not the part he said that was incorrect.
So when this guy says like, helicopter parents, I don't think any of us would encourage helicopter
parenting.
I think that we might have said something that was kind of helicopter parents.
Did anyone use that phrase?
I don't know.
I think I've talked about stuff about that.
It's the one where you're kids and over.
No, it's when you turn into a helicopter.
Right.
It's when people...
Oh, it's when Yoshi gets the helicopter power up.
It's when people are trying to disparage trans people, and they say, I identify as an attack
helicopter.
That's helicopter parenting.
Right, right, right.
But yeah, I'm sure that we probably said something that indicated we were okay with
something that could be construed as helicopter parenting.
As though thinking one thing that's fairly overreaching is okay, and then just extrapolating
oh, we all just think helicopter parenting is okay.
And it's like, no, we didn't go that far.
We went a little far.
I mean, it's ridiculous to just extrapolate because one's philosophy has some connection
with a philosopher that you reach the exact same conclusions.
I mean, it's the Hitler family.
It's so easy.
It's so easy to just hear things that people are...
Oh, that's true.
Right, so easy to just hear one sentence that could have started.
It's like some alt-right video, and just assume what someone is saying.
It just is some dog.
I want to say, I want to say...
I have a relevant experience.
I have a perception of forever color.
I have a relevant experience, recent kind of.
Some people might have seen it on Twitter that I posted.
A while ago, there was this video on YouTube, and they were doing an animation meme.
They were playing my animation meme in the corner, I'm guessing for reference or for
audio or whatever, and I left a comment.
Are they doing the same meme?
Aren't they animating the same meme or something?
Yeah, they're animating something themselves.
Like, incompletely or something, Ryan?
What?
Never mind.
Okay, just go on.
Go on.
What they were doing is fine.
They were taking my idea for the animation meme and doing their own with the characters
they were presenting, and that's fine.
That's what animation memes do.
The issue I had, the small issue I had, was that they were playing my video at the top,
and it's not breaking into laws or rules or whatever, but they didn't credit me or anything,
and I would have preferred if they had.
It's just common courtesy.
It is common courtesy.
Yeah, and I left a comment saying, in polite terms, I said,
hey, maybe you should maybe not use other people's videos in the corners,
or if you're gonna do that, at least credit them.
And then, like, I also edited the comment later on,
because I saw a lot of people saying, oh, you copied, oh, you traced,
and I was like, no, that person did not trace,
and an animation meme is basically taking the same idea
and just doing it with your own characters, kind of.
Did this person acquiesce?
Did they put you in the description or anything?
No.
Well, really?
Yeah, it's eight months later, at least, still haven't credit me.
Eight months later, wow.
They're probably not going to do it.
That's just bad.
They probably don't give a shit.
Yeah, the issue is not there.
Like, okay, whatever, things like that happen.
But I politely, even in my comments, I said,
this person is not tracing me.
They are not copying me.
Please, to all the people that are saying that they are, they're not.
This animation meme is fine.
The only issue I have is that, you know,
they could have at least credited me.
That's all.
That's the small issue I had with the video.
Did they play other videos or just yours?
No, it was just that animation meme,
and they used the audio from the video they were playing of my video.
So it was just, in that instance, it was just my video,
but I have seen on their channel, they did it at least once
with some other video, I think.
I haven't really researched them.
I mean, I guess this person just doesn't really care about the good crediting.
The thing is, though, I got a lot of replies to that comment,
just like, how dare you bully this person
and think that they're stealing you.
Why do you think, you know, they're not stealing from you,
you're just bullying them, you're harassing them.
It's just like...
Well, is it because you're big?
They're the one who took your video.
Is it because you have more subs, so it's like punching down?
Yeah.
Probably.
Probably, but the thing is, like, they didn't even read what I said.
I specifically said to the people that were harassing the person
is like, this person is not stealing from me.
I just wanted them to credit my video since they used it in their video.
And the people go on and think that I was...
There was...
I mean, I'm totally with you, Mage.
There was an incident, I mean, a while back,
that everybody probably remembers.
There was just an...
I made my video about communist glasses not being orange, whatever.
And, like, I used a picture of a cosplay girl who...
Yeah.
She, like, had very orange glasses for her coming to cosplay.
And I used the picture and said, like,
ah, this is bad, like, ah, you know, you suck.
Like, something along those lines.
And she commented saying, like, hey, you have stolen my work
and put it, and have used it.
And, I mean, she was just very upset.
I don't think she asked me to, like, take it down, but she was mad.
I'm really glad you brought this up because that attitude pisses me off so much
when people say things like that about their fucking fan work.
Okay.
Because I want to say to that woman, did you ask anyone
on the Girl in the Gone production team
if you could use their character and intellectual property
because they can sue you for that?
I think that if this picture was, like,
if this picture was, like, paywalled or something,
then I think she's got a point.
But if this was something that she, like, made and tweeted
and, like, posted publicly, I don't think...
If it was paywalled, then it's super illegal
and she shouldn't be able to paywall her, like...
But people do that.
People, like, cosplay.
Well, yeah, it's like a Patreon cosplay or something, you know?
I think that's all...
I think I love that that economy exists,
and I would defend the idea that it should be possible
and companies should embrace it because it promotes their characters.
Like, that's why they're not going around shutting all this stuff down,
but, like, all of it is technically, you know, they can.
Like, it used to happen at a lot of anime conventions.
Like, they could probably issue some kind of cease and desist
if they were so inclined.
Like, in the artist alley, there used to be lots of stories
of, like, anime company representatives
just going around and being like,
hey, you're not allowed to sell art of our character
and just shutting down stalls.
Like, Disney famously does that.
Yeah, I was thinking.
I was thinking.
I was in Anime Expo recently.
I was just in the artist alley, and it hit me.
This is totally fucking illegal.
Like, you can't just sell pictures of Pokémon.
Right.
Well, okay.
When you say it's illegal, what it is is it would be a...
I think it's a civil issue where they may be doing something
that a company would have a claim to object to,
but until they object, it is not, like, really an issue,
or it's not quote-unquote illegal.
I think it is definitely...
Yeah, I guess it's theft of intellectual property, right?
I mean, I just don't think that's a great...
I don't know.
I sympathize with the companies that want to protect their brand image,
but, I mean, I think we're all better, obviously.
It has someone who makes derivative quote-unquote artwork on the Internet,
but she sympathizes with desire.
Yeah, when I was researching copyright for a few reasons,
I did come across, like, it's not good.
It's not legal if you're sort of like,
let's say the company is making fleshy toys,
and you start making fleshy toys of the same characters,
and, you know, that's obviously very wrong.
So, like, if you create competition with their intellectual property,
or whatever, something like that, so...
The idea behind fair use is that it's only fair use
if it doesn't compete with the original product
or could not stand as a replacement of it.
That's always the defense I use with my videos,
because, like, I obviously use tons of footage from anime,
but it's like, this in no way is representative of the product,
because I've cut it into a bunch of random 10-second clips
that I'm talking over it, and it's like,
you're not getting the experience of watching the show.
So, like, if it was something that directly competed,
and even then, I'm going to defend my stuff,
because I don't care if it actually is legal to do what I do.
I'm just going to appeal to the logic of these companies,
and, like, for instance, Sentai Filmworks got in contact with me.
You guys can see that in this picture.
I've posted it in the chat that has my DMs in it.
But Sentai Filmworks took down my
Astroscore Sucks Part 12A and 12B video,
which is where I was, like, defending Shivery of a Failed Night,
which is their show.
That's the one that they own.
It's the one that I was, like, you know, saying is better.
And so I just basically went on Twitter and was like,
hey, everybody, this company took down my video.
Why don't you tell them how that makes you feel?
And there was, like, dozens of people saying,
like, I only watched this show because of that video,
or, like, I bought this show from you because of this video.
You need to bring it back.
Right.
And when enough of that happened, Sentai contacted me,
and their response was to the effect of, like,
hey, we really appreciate that you promote our videos,
our content.
We hope you keep doing it.
Like, we'll get in contact with our Flagger team.
Now, granted, they haven't actually gotten my videos back yet,
so this is not me praising Sentai Filmworks for doing the right thing.
Hopefully it's just bureaucracy that's loaded up at this point.
Yeah, I hope so.
But in any case, like, you know, it's not that I actually care
whether my video is fair use or not.
I kind of approached it like, hey, guys, if you take down my video,
you're going to piss off your own fans.
You're going to piss off the people who want to support you.
So, like, you know, this is not in your best interest as a business
to take this action, even if it was legally correct.
Here's a question.
Well, we're talking about, talking about artist alley artists drawn like...
Wait a minute, before we finish that,
I just want to put a cap on what I was saying about that girl,
which was simply that.
When she requested, I mean, she was mad that I used her video,
or that she used her picture, and just expressed disinterest.
What I did was I credited her in the comments,
which I think was in the description,
which I think was a completely reasonable request,
and I would do so of anyone.
If you look at my videos these days,
you will see me crediting as much fan artist physically possible
and asking anyone who wants credit to let me know,
and I will add you, because I think that is the right thing to do.
But I would never, ever take it down at someone's request.
Oh, God, no.
We're using this.
I've had my fair share of people coming to me with the same request
of like, hey, can you put a credit for me in the description and stuff,
and it's amazing how snooty them and their fans will get.
One time I used...
I mean, they feel taken advantage of, so I sympathize.
But one time I used this dude's...
This dude did a heavy metal cover of a Kill Law Kill song,
and I just showed a short clip of that video of him playing the song in my video,
and he's like, hey, man, kind of a dick move to not give me credit or whatever,
and then I added the credit to the description,
but in response to him or on his channel and stuff,
there was just tons of his fans being like,
oh, it's wrong to steal people's content,
and I'm like, again, you did not ask the permission to make a Kill Law Kill theme cover.
This is a cover of a corporation's intellectual property, yeah.
And no one ever complains that I've got all this footage from the anime in there,
which is equally like, you know, I'm not crediting Trigger.
It's punching down.
I don't really believe in the whole punching down paradigm, though.
I get it. I think it makes sense. I just think you should keep some perspective.
I think you should punch anyone who's wrong.
That's my stance on punching.
I don't like punching. It's a complicated thing, I guess.
What were you saying? You were going on about some bullshit, as I recall.
That's right. I'm queuing up after Ben.
Sure.
So you got some fan artists, the artist Allie, selling like a really nice painting of a really nice painting.
Samus.
No, of a hit Montab.
You got this absolutely scrumptious hit Montab, you know, just rendered in glorious-
That's even more sexual.
The realistic light on this hit Montab is just unreal.
It's like you really had hit Montab too much.
You can feel the hip hop beat emanating from the canvas.
He just leaps off the page with his enthusiasm for battle and dancing.
But anyway, here's my question.
Is that taking away from...
Do you think that a person who is buying that work of art,
would they have otherwise purchased a work from Nintendo,
a piece like a hit Montab poster officially sold by Nintendo or something?
They're going to think that this is a really weird monster that they're not going to even know what it is that they don't know what it is.
No, no, no. That's not what I'm asking.
I'm asking you, without the artist, without the fan artist, would they...
Look at it.
Did this artist take the sale away from Nintendo?
Would that customer have gone to Nintendo to purchase an official hit Montab merchandise?
You're right, Ben. The answer is no.
The answer to that is no, but you can think about it from another perspective as well,
which I'm sure is how the company thinks of it.
It's that this product would not exist, if not for Nintendo and the Pokémon company, whatever,
creating this intellectual property that you are now capitalizing on to make a sale.
I could certainly see why they deserve perhaps at least a share of what's going on there.
It's not a matter of necessarily whether it competes with something they already have.
It's whether it could potentially compete with something they intend to create,
and like the fucking Samus remake, remember?
Or even more importantly, to all of us, and the Fighting is Magic video game, where...
Of course, of course.
All of these...
There's a great video about this by that dude...
What's the name of the black guy from Two Best Friends Play?
Oh, Wully.
Yeah, Wully. He had made his own channel and his first video was about addressing this idea
that the reason these games all get shut down is that these companies...
If they don't shut down your game, it makes a precedent that they don't do that,
and that they allow this, and it makes it legally harder for them to defend themselves later
if they did want to make a competing product with you,
that they can't just shut down your game after having allowed it to exist, basically.
I think also the reason why they shut down Pixelmon after years of not doing anything...
People speculate it, I'm not sure, but I think it's because they release later on Pokemon Quest,
which is like, you know, QB Pokemon sort of creatures,
and aesthetically, it's similar-ish.
I mean, I don't really see it, but people have been speculating that's why they shut it down,
and I'm a little scared if that's the reason.
Yeah, like from a business perspective, it's a business, and actually it's a fiduciary responsibility.
Fiduciary, yo!
Fiduciary, that's right, that's right.
It is their fiduciary responsibility, like if they have a publicly traded company,
to protect the earnings of their shareholders to do whatever it takes
to preserve profits now and any potential profits in the future.
So it's... I mean, yeah.
I don't speak too angry with them.
I know the whole, down with the corporations, down with the big man, yada yada.
But I can't be angry if they're just doing stuff to protect their intellectual property,
so if they have to do it...
I think we all kind of just wish it didn't have to be that way, but, you know...
But yeah, I wanted to say just a little bit, as a content creator,
as, you know, I used to do Fannert and stuff like that, as one of those people
whose art gets used on the internet.
I would just like to say, like, the things like reposting my art, I don't approve of it.
Like, if you let's say... I really hate Pinterest because of it.
I despise Pinterest.
It's just, I hate when my art gets taken to a different site and then posted without my permission.
With Pinterest, I think most of it is credited.
Some of them are credited wrong, and there's nothing I can do about it.
But, um...
Yeah, I hate my art being taken to a different site and then, like, just losing track of it, so to speak.
My fucking Galco video has been reposted to Tumblr many times and accrued millions of views,
and that's a real shame for me, you know, financially and whatnot.
Would have been nice if everyone just came to YouTube to watch it, and I earned the pittance of ad revenue that it gets.
Could have just embedded on Tumblr, too.
Yeah.
Hey, Ben, going back to your...
Hang on, Major's still finishing a point.
Yeah, it's just like, but with, let's say, fan art for things...
Hold on, now a last one point.
My art, yeah, okay.
When I do fan art for a character, like, for instance, Mothit, my very first Undertale fan art,
it's quite popular, and it was, I think, used in design, but the proceeds from that design were for charity or whatever.
Yes, Z.
It's pronounced Z.
In my head, I called it Zine, and it's a habit.
I wouldn't mind so much, but you're not the only one.
Shut the fuck up, it's not Zine.
No, it's Zine.
It doesn't make any sense.
Wait, Zine, did you make the Zine?
Major, what's the, I don't know, what's this about a Zine?
Yeah, it got featured in the Zine, I think, but I didn't get any money from it because it was for charity.
That's just to sort of emphasize how popular it got.
Like, they contacted me and they asked if they could use it because I didn't go to them, they came to me.
That's kind of flattering.
Anywho, but like, yeah, it's quite popular, and several people have asked, go on and actually messaged me and asked me,
like, hey, could I use this as a picture for my musical cover on YouTube and stuff like that.
And I'm like, fine, I'm more than happy to let people do that with fan art of characters if, you know, they ask.
And they, like, it's not a repost, but they do their own thing with my art.
So it's kind of like, what's the word, transformative in a way?
Yeah, sure, somewhat.
You know, they're not just...
It's using it for our purpose, it's not just taking the artist's position.
Well, what if my purpose is just to make money by reselling Major's art, like, on a poster?
Like, that's my purpose.
Well, then no.
Oh, then no.
Yeah.
No, no.
I'm here, I'm here to commodify Mage and the...
As he does with all women.
No, that's right.
There's a difference.
Don't objectify, commodify.
Yeah, it's a way of saying that.
But yeah, like, so I'm pretty...
What a progressive that bit.
Guys.
But yeah, like, I'm perfectly fine with people, like, asking for...
You know, if they ask for permission and they credit me and they use it in that sort of thing, that's fine.
I've seen several people re-uploading the video, like, the sort of animatic thing of the dubbed, like, Papyrus, Sans, and Metaton, like, they go on a date or whatever.
That video, it got, like, it was my most popular one for a while.
Yeah, yeah.
And people have re-uploaded it.
However, they did credit it in me and they dubbed over with their own voice.
So, I don't...
Okay, there's something there.
There's something okay there, kind of.
Yeah, so, like, I don't mind it too much.
I'm not too happy about it.
I would have preferred if they had asked, I guess.
I would have probably said, yeah, sure, okay.
I think one of them did, and I did give them a get-go.
So, yeah, those sort of things, fine.
When it's fanart as well, like, I can understand why you want to use it in that way, so long as you give credit to me and, you know, doing something trans-morbid, not just re-posting it.
I'm usually fine with it.
Fine with it.
You know what?
This makes me rethink a little bit my statement before about how, like, the whole punching up, punching down thing is irrelevant.
Because, like, if you, for example, just took, like, any anime and did a fan-dub over it, like, I wouldn't blink twice.
I'd be like, this is fine.
But if it was, like, one person's animation, like, on their YouTube, I'd be like...
Yeah, the funny thing is there's definitely a difference in kind.
There's obviously a difference in the way that we perceive those things because of how we perceive those companies and people, but I think that's wrong of us to do.
You might be right.
What I hate about the whole idea of punching up, punching down is that it stratifies, like, you're putting worth on people on the basis of their social clout, which is totally unfair.
Because it's not as though someone having more attention means that they have more rights or a better life, you know?
To suggest that because someone's famous, they are now just open to criticism.
It's like, why would that person, how is them getting famous forfeiting their right to be treated the exact same way that you would be treated?
Especially when fame is not a linear, like, thing that makes you just happier or, like, better.
And I don't understand what the metric is that we are now allowed to make this person sign all the shit on, you know?
I think I know why people feel that way.
And it's because of the perceived power that, like, famous people have, specifically, where, like, they have a...
And this is a real thing of influence, of being able to shape the world to a degree.
So you want to help me wrap up your point?
I want to quickly wrap up my point.
Kujoto, Arbok, Hitmontop, Pitmonly.
Yeah, Ketchum.
No, no, no, I'll be quick.
Hitmontop's Gen 2, you stupid motherfucker.
He's not in the poker world.
Hitmontop, please continue.
I'll be quicker.
What I was talking about was mostly about, like, fan art and fan work and stuff like that.
When it comes to my OC as personal art, I am a lot more strict about people doing that.
And I would probably not allow it, even with credits, because those are my creations.
And I'm like, I'm a nobody on the internet.
If someone took it, if someone takes my fan art of a character and they'll go like,
oh, yeah, that's a character from that game.
And, you know, they get pretty...
Major, quick question.
That makes sense to me, but here's my question.
Why doesn't that same level of, like, protectiveness extend to something like a Sans or Papyrus
or just, like, any famous online character?
Like, why doesn't it go to those guys?
I suppose because, like, I don't own the characters, so I can't...
So you just leave it up to whoever actually, like, owns them to worry about that stuff?
No, it's not like that. It's just like...
I would understand that.
It's like...
I'm more protective of my characters because my characters are mine and I love them and I would hate...
It would devastate me, people taking them for their own.
And, like, you can't...
Like, when my art is used with my permission, it's usually, like, for a cover song,
for a cover for a song.
It's like a thumbnail for a video, something like that.
If they're, you know, they're talking about the topic and they're just using my image
to illustrate what they're talking about or what they're doing.
It's not taking those...
They're not taking my characters and claiming it as their own with my OCs.
No one knows what those OCs are, who those OCs are.
Like, I think the only sort of exception is for when people would review specifically my OCs and my art,
stuff like that.
That's the only exception because that video is, you know, about me and my art rather than, like...
But if someone takes my OCs and use them, like, I don't know, as a talk sprite,
or as a background image while they're talking about something irrelevant,
people start associating my art, my character.
I would say that goes beyond, like, fan art at that point, where that's...
Yeah, that is someone, like, that's using it in a way that competes with your content.
Like, you're basically...
Yeah.
That person is now altering the narrative of your character in a way.
Like, I understand what you're concerned about is, like, this person is going to make your character
associated with something that has nothing to do with you,
and now you've lost control of the narrative surrounding your character.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
Yeah, and I think that even famous characters, like, I would say probably...
Even Sans has been almost completely co-opted by the much more popular variant of Venom Sans.
I was going to say that, like, that's definitely something that's happened with, like,
the Undertale characters where there was, for a while, like, everyone ascribing,
like, specific, like, you know, gender denominations and stuff to them that become...
Yeah, Crying Sans is a perfect example.
Like, yeah, people have created this alternate version that has nothing to do with what Toby Fox presented,
and, like, whether or not he's okay with that, like, he could have made a public statement or whatever,
but, like, the fact is that this character has gotten away from him culturally,
and I don't even know if I think that's unfair.
I appreciate why for someone like Mage, who, again, sees herself as an Internet nobody,
it's like, if you haven't even had the chance to tell the story you wanted to tell with these characters
and other people are already telling an alternative story, then it's like, your story just never got told.
And I do think that that sucks, and, like, I would argue that it's something that I wouldn't want people to do,
but I also don't know if I think that it's wrong, per se. You know what I mean?
Like, if we're going to extend that to people who are Internet nobodies,
I feel like that same respect should be paid to someone like Toby Fox, you know?
Feelings-wise. In terms of my emotional reaction, there's definitely a spectrum there.
We're drawing a picture of Sans in a cool different outfit or something.
That's one end of the spectrum, and then on the other end is taking Mage's character
and using it as a talk spread for a completely other personality and some other work and not crediting them.
There's a continuum between there, and definitely at some point it starts to feel wrong,
but I don't know exactly at what point does it go from a fan work to a transgression.
If Undertale had just sold Shiddly and nobody liked it, I feel like all our feelings would change on this matter.
It also depends on how the person themselves feels, though, because for me, I might create a character
that I don't have any intentions with, and then if someone wants to use my character as a talk sprite,
I'd be like, hey, sounds like a way to market my character and potentially draw attention,
but I might contact this person and ask how I could work with them.
Again, there's a million possibilities with all of it, and it really just comes down to just respecting people's emotions or not.
If Mage comes out and says, hey, don't use my characters, it's not that I think that there needs to be a legal precedent
or anything that she can defend them, it's just like if you respect Mage as a person,
don't do the things she doesn't want you to do, and if you don't care, then just expect her to hate you.
If you do that kind of thing without credit, then you're stealing, and that's definitely wrong.
If you do credit them, but you do something that the author does not want you to do,
even if you credit them, it's maybe not wrong in the way that stealing is wrong,
but it's like, I'm doing this without the permission of the author, the original creator does not want this.
I guess in the perfect world, that would be a stain on your work that should make people not appreciate it and not like it,
but I'm sure that not every case does that happen.
It's not like a legal wrong, it's just a social wrong.
It's highly disrespectful that I think about it.
You're taking this person's work, their hard work, their creation, and they're not speaking about me specifically,
now I'm thinking about something else, but you're taking their work, and you're using it, you like it enough,
you're using it for your own gain, but you don't respect the creator of the work you're using enough to go along with their wishes.
I think a lot of it is really just laziness.
It would be so easy.
We can't take someone to court for this, but we can job lynch mob them and slander their name on social media.
Let me play the other side of the field for a second here, though, and try to explain why I think most of this happens,
because in cases like Crying Sands, the kind of people...
Who is Crying Sands, though?
I know there's so many Undertale versions, but I've never heard about Crying Sands.
Crying Sands is just the general trend.
Immediately after Undertale got big, people would tend to draw scenes of Sands getting really emotional and crying.
Because the idea is essentially that because Sands has been through the most out of everybody,
that people depict him crying because it's reasonable to expect him to be a sad boy,
there's just nothing in the game that actually presents that angle.
We don't see him crying.
The temptation there is because he's such a together guy, and he's the most powerful and the most knowledgeable,
to depict him breaking down is like, this is the ultimate, this is the ultimate emotional whatever.
To talk about why I think people would draw that, it's because people are pathetic.
When you think about why would somebody...
Especially artists, let me tell you.
Why would somebody need Undertale in their lives?
You need it because it gives you something.
As a human being, it enriches you in some way.
And for some people who don't have the huge cavalcade of media,
all of us, we have a shitload of stuff that we like.
None of us is just into one thing.
Even if we all did absolutely love Undertale, it's none of our only thing.
And I can imagine somebody who gets into this game.
I'm only into one thing, Digi.
Keto, continue.
Of course.
I imagine that if somebody got into Undertale, and that was their whole world,
and it was the only way they really understood how to express their innermost thoughts and feelings,
Oh, shoot, I did draw crime scenes.
That's exactly what kids are like.
Kids use cartoons and shit.
These kids are playing Undertale, and they're going like,
How do I represent what this made me feel when I don't have my own characters?
I don't have my own ideas.
And it's free social cloud online because you're drawing this character that people already care about.
People care about your art automatically, whereas you could not build that by yourself.
That is laziness, but I understand why if you're a kid and you don't understand
that the people who made this stuff had to work so hard to create these things
to learn how to create good characters.
Toby Fox obviously is not a newcomer.
Even if it's his first game that made him popular,
this dude's been creating stories and music and art for a very long time.
Yeah, he had to mention he's been on the inside of the Homestuck,
so he's obviously been around down the street.
Exactly.
What's that made?
I did draw sans crying, I linked it.
That's hilarious.
I need that to enrich me as a person.
There's another reason why I just figured out why people want to repost this and share it.
The first sentence is please do not repost slash use without permission.
Well, let me tell you what my first thought is when I see that sentence.
It's what I'm thinking about doing right now.
There's always a question that comes up every once in a while,
you know, what Pokemon is the PCP?
What would the PCBs for Sona be?
What sans would be?
What emotion sans is the PCP?
You can call that one right now.
Hitmontop is a pretty similar color scheme.
I'm prepared to just say hitmontop is sans.
Wait.
That was not the question.
It wasn't though.
No, but valid answers.
I'll take one again.
That's kind of relevant to what I was saying.
For a lot of kids who only have so many media points of reference,
they tend to constantly do that kind of comparison.
Everyone in my group of friends corresponds to an undertale character.
It's like everyone in your group of friends
corresponds to a member of a group of friends
in literally any game or piece of media you could play.
Which sex in the city girl are you?
Exactly.
Which golden girl are you?
That's all they've seen.
I'm Rose.
I'm the mom.
You are the mom.
I used to do that with my friends when I was eight
and we saw Rose on YouTube.
We all did it.
In the PCP, we used to do it all the time.
Talk about which my little pony guys were we.
But then we would just extrapolate that into every other show.
I've made any show I watch.
I could take the characters and say,
oh, that one's Nate.
That one's Kion we did it with.
Oh, your Ritsu, your Rainbow Dash.
No shit.
Any sporty character is going to be Nate, you know.
Yeah.
You said social cloud a minute ago.
Sorry to take this, we can go back to what we were talking about before,
but I want to mention that I was thinking about this the other day.
It makes me very upset.
It makes me despair to think about why people like things.
Because sometimes it feels to me in life that people,
especially on the internet and just like in public,
people like things as a public performative display of allegiance.
People like things and are vocal about liking things
in a way to ally themselves with this thing.
With certain YouTubers, right?
Maybe someone wants to be like,
maybe people want to be like armored skeptic or what's that other guy?
Sargon of a cottage or what's that, you know, these douchebags.
And so, you know, they're going to make videos that are like them.
They're going to like them on Twitter.
They're going to retweet their shit and be a big fan of them
and shout them out if they make their own videos.
And that's true of like everything.
I feel like people like Undertale or people, I don't know.
Ben, this is also true of you.
It is true of me.
And the point is that there's no escaping this.
There's no escaping this.
I would say this is the purpose of art.
Like, I think that what it mostly is there to do is to...
It feels impure.
It feels like all love.
All love is impure love.
Accurate.
I think it's all of this art and all of the way we respond to it is
it's us reaching into ourselves and trying to figure out who we are.
And then we see something that makes us say,
oh, that's what I am.
Now I get it.
Now I understand why I think this way.
You know what this is?
And then you just keep collecting those, you know?
That is the micro opposite side of the coin against like widespread politics.
Because politics is like the exact same thing only on the macro level.
We're like politicians.
So like, I feel like when people are telling like, oh, politicians are evil.
Like us doing this thing is like aligning ourselves with groups that don't like perfectly represent us.
Like yes, the scale is different, but it is the same sort of problem.
Right.
Only like an individual level as opposed to politicians trying to align us in groups.
I feel like maybe my example was weird there.
Like, I don't know.
Do you think that people like publicly perform their love of something like Undertale or Homestuck or whatever?
Because like, I think there's like some, like you could do that because something speaks to you
and because you feel passionate about it and it means a lot to you.
You could also maybe do it because it's cool and because you think it makes you look cool to like this thing.
That's definitely a part of it.
Personally, as a person who has created fan art for things, I usually do it because I really like the characters.
I usually draw characters.
I like the characters and I just sort of like want to...
What do you mean by like though?
Define like.
Incidentally, I think we can all refer to ourselves as people who have made fan art of things.
It's kind of like all of our...
I mean like drawn fan art, I guess.
When I made that image, I drew it.
I think we also have drawn fan art of things.
When I finished Lisa for the first time, I spent a couple days.
I worked on this piece of Lisa fan art that was really, I'm pretty proud of it.
Oh, that Lisa.
Yeah, yeah.
And on the one hand, like I did it because like I love the game and I love the story and I love the character
and I love the ending and I just wanted to depict the ending in like a cool way.
I think I've said this before, but like when I do fan art of something, it's like I love this thing so much.
I want to like participate in its glory a little bit, you know?
Yeah, yeah.
I want to be a little part of this thing that I think is great.
But also...
I want to like...
I'm sorry.
For me personally because...
Wait, let me finish this point.
What do you mean by that?
God damn it.
But in addition to that, I also was very gratified to see that like that image is relatively high
if like you search Lisa images, like it turns up fairly easily in a Google search
and it did really well on Twitter and I think the creator retweeted it and stuff.
And like so I was like...
That's because you did such a good job of understanding it.
Like me and Lisa, there's like a Lisa link.
Hang on, wait.
There's like a Lisa link.
God damn it.
Everyone live the fuck up.
There's like a thing between me and Lisa.
Like I'm...
And I was gratified.
I was like, I think it's cool that I am associated...
I want to be associated with this thing because this is the thing that I think is good.
You know what I don't like about that?
All this stuff.
I feel like...
Doesn't it feel a little impure?
Yes.
Like, ah, look at this cool thing someone else made.
Let me just hitch my wagon to this and ride it for a while.
Here's why.
No, yeah.
That's my problem.
I really want to blow this all wide open here because first of all, let me ask you, what
is the purpose of language, of communication?
It is to bridge the gap in discrepancies between the information we have, right?
Like I know a thing, I want you to know the same thing so I say it to you.
And we have the English language, we have all these different spoken languages that
are good for that.
But sometimes the idea is so complex that even if you understand it, you have no idea
how to communicate it except in reference to someone else who has already communicated
it.
So, like, Ben resonates with Lisa super strongly because it says something that he agrees
with very strongly.
And maybe there's not a way for him to easily or concisely explain that in words, but Ben
is capable of drawing pictures that perfectly capture what he likes about Lisa.
Like what about this game says the same thing that he's thinking?
If nothing else, it probably highlights the moment that Ben most strongly resonated with,
which in itself is like a distinct form of like a pinpointing.
It's focusing in on this one thing.
So when Ben posts that and when there's two layers to it, like he just said, there's
the layer of like, I wanted to show my appreciation for this thing that communicates something
that I agree with and want to also say, like, and I'm saying it in my own way with a little
twist.
I'm making my version of the statement, but it's close enough to the original and it's
so it has so much of the same appeal as the original that the people who like it inevitably
will also like Ben's art.
And that's why it is so popular and that's why he also in turn feels good about feeling
like he best captured what was good about this game, you know, better than other artists
were capable of.
Would you agree with that, Ben, as my analysis of your fan art?
Yeah, yeah, I totally agree.
I get little tingle.
When I think about that picture, it makes me think about the ending of Lisa and I just
get, I get, I get a weird like tingly, I get a weird like breathless sensation just because
I love it so much.
I wanted to say something before Lisa, like with me with me personally, it's like a part
of me is like, okay, so I really like this thing, right?
And I want to sort of participate in the thing that I like.
So I sort of like create the art for it, just like to express myself, express my like love
for it and sort of practice.
Major, I'm sorry.
Can I interrupt real quick?
Because the PCP just got a one-darl patron from Past Analysis, baby.
Hey!
Welcome, buddy.
Hey, Past Analysis.
What's up?
Hey, see you at BronyCon, dude.
Yeah, BronyCon.
BronyCon 2019.
Oh, oh, oh, can we please, can we please grandfather in Past Analysis be a CMC member of the PCP?
Can we, can we?
Can we upgrade?
Okay, I wasn't here last week.
What about that we are going to BronyCon 2019?
Briefly, I think.
Supposedly some of you are.
Yeah, and we are.
We see a Briterite that's not a joke, that is not a joke, everyone.
We're not like doing that, you know, to make you laugh, Brony.
No.
We are actually going to BronyCon.
Well, it is, it is pretty, it is really fucking funny.
But we are.
Okay, okay, sure.
But I'm doing it for real.
That's a sigh.
All right, that sounds good.
But I totally interrupted Mage.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to mourn.
Please continue.
And now I forget.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
It was just really fucking funny.
No, it's okay.
It's okay.
But yeah, if Pest is reading it, hi Pest, I haven't heard your name in years, probably
literally years.
I heard that name in years.
Exactly.
Why can't we get patron from Dr. Wolf?
Soon.
Why, why, why are we so below Dr. Wolf?
Oh, no.
Pest analysis is actually cool and I want a patron from him.
If Dr. Wolf patroned us, I'd be like, what's happening?
Is this subterfuge?
Like, I've been talking shit about this guy for years.
He hasn't even done anything new to me.
I mean, he probably doesn't even know.
I mean, you know, I don't know.
Different world.
I don't think it's possible to talk shit about somebody online and then not get sent
it.
Yeah, maybe.
Like, I guess every time someone even so much as mentions me on the internet, someone
sends it to me and I don't know why because I don't necessarily want all of it.
I do and it's people who are like other YouTubers and who I don't expect, like who I don't see
it coming from.
Like sometimes it'll be people who I've been like, for a recent example, there's a YouTuber
called Ocelot, O-S-C-I-L-L-O-T who like I collaborated with back in 2015 and like I thought his videos
were super cool.
It was one of the few like anime analysis channels I was kind of excited about.
But he kind of disappeared to go become an editor for another guy who I don't care about.
And like recently, like, he was just talking shit about me like really aggressively on
Twitter and like not tagging me or anything.
Was that person MatPat and did he commit suicide?
Oh, jeez.
Well, first of all, MatPat didn't commit suicide.
First of all, it's not even the same, it's not the same guy.
Well, I'm just, because you said this guy became an editor, so I thought, oh, he's probably
the editor that got himself from, you know.
You just had to think about it.
No, where it was confusing is you said was this guy MatPat and I thought you were talking
about the person I was describing.
No, I meant the guy that he went to go edit for.
Yeah, I feel you.
I get it now.
And it is funny in retrospect.
By the way, I am mildly curious who he's working for.
It was Mr. AJ Cosplay, now known as the Cartoon Psych.
The guy who edits for.
No idea who that is.
He's a guy who does like a lot of videos about dub acting and shit.
I don't care about it.
But so this us like I was like talking shit about me and Zen Huxdable like just quote
tweeted him was like, yeah, you should probably tag at DigiBraw if you're going to talk shit
about him.
Sure.
Thank you, Zen, for telling me that like this guy who I've been telling people is like one
of the cool anime analysis channels for years is now just shitting on me for no apparent
reason all over Twitter.
So I do like when people send me stuff like that because I want to know like, you know,
before I go talking people up who are apparently hate me for no reason.
I understand.
What was he saying?
He was talking about some weird dream he had where he had to have like an analysis debate
with me.
The way he was describing it was like, yeah, I had to listen to his insufferable fucking
prick voice, arguably, or whatever, just like, I was like, what did I do to this guy?
I fucking paid him for a collab one time.
I paid him money last time we interacted.
What?
I love I love people that give me money like Cy, who paid me to design a t-shirt.
So I promoted his Kickstarter because I want to encourage people giving me money.
And I, for what it's worth, the last time I talked shit about Cy all the time and he
talked shit about me and we both give each other money in support.
So there you go.
Oh, God.
What a great relationship.
Can we please, can we please just back, can we please back up a moment and discuss what's
really important?
Because Ben, about your, about your example in the R.S.T.A.L.Y. about a hip-mon-top painting.
Yeah.
I fucking pray I want there to be a beautiful hip-mon-top painting because look at this
change you want to see in the world.
This hip-mon-top, hip-mon-top is one of the Pokemon that is banished from ever having
any merchandise whatsoever.
This is the official Pokemon store.
And hip-mon-top, zero matches.
They're not a single piece of plush figures and pen, training cards, clothing, home
offices, video games, or all other categories.
No beauty, no beautifully rendered oil paintings of hip-mon-top art galleries.
I literally own a hip-mon-top plush.
Like I can't see it from here because it's blocked.
Why are they selling it then?
Why are they afraid to bring it back out?
They must have made it.
Why are they silent hip-mon-top?
Like sold at some underground office.
What are they hiding?
Yeah, why are you silent hip-mon-top?
First of all, it's Jones and now hip-mon-top.
When does it end?
All you guys are telling me right now is that I could sell this hip-mon-top on eBay for
a lot of money.
That's what I'm getting at.
Yeah.
The market is surging with demand for hip-mon-top right now.
I need that hip-mon-top.
Bad!
Did you get it?
Like everybody, everybody.
I need it!
If you're listening, invest in hip-mon-top now.
The price of the sky rise.
That's true.
On the hip-mon-top plushie, does he have a tail?
I don't have it on me, but I mean, it's an official plushie.
I got it in like back when Gen 2 came out.
But that's the question because like you see Munchie has been spamming us with hip-mon-top
images.
And like at the very first one, it looks like he has like either a third foot or a tail,
but then the following ones.
That's his penis mage.
That is his penis.
No, he's got a little.
This bulbous.
Yeah, he's got a little.
Yeah, he's got two of them.
You know what I'm saying?
The one that I just got from the show, you can see his tail if you look very carefully
at his.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, okay.
He's definitely supposed to have a tail, although it seems like it varies in length.
Like sometimes it's just a tiny little nub and sometimes it's long.
Maybe that's a gender difference.
I'm curious.
Maybe it extends.
Because like, yeah, like look at the very first image.
He has very long legs, but then the following images is very stumpy.
It attracts it to help with his spinning.
Yeah, like, like, yeah, like, yeah, that makes sense.
Okay.
Wait, wait, wait.
This is so, yeah, in like the 3D, the 3D models, his tail is like incredibly short, but then
in like the old sprites, it's relatively long.
Like you can see like a connecting like, like strand or whatever.
That's so weird.
And I hate it.
Do you guys remember the 3D?
I hate the move to 3D.
Do you guys remember the Hitmontop game in Pokemon Stadium 2, where you spin around
as Hitmontops and they're like, Beyblade each other out of the arena?
Beyblade?
Dude, that's what it says.
That sounds sick.
Have you guys not played Pokemon Stadium?
Listen, everything you guys say in Hitmontop is going in one ear and out the other, because
all I know is that I need that.
I need it bad, did you?
I need that Hitmontop bad.
Okay, so like one episode before the last one, I mentioned about a topic I wanted to
talk about, and we were going to talk about that topic today, but like we started talking
about other things and we're already an hour in, so I really want to talk about the topic
right now.
We're only 50 minutes in.
I'm down.
I get it.
There is no topic, first of all.
Second of all, I want to talk about a very disappointing interaction that I had on Twitter,
because I saw...
Were you asking why for Hitmontop?
Were you just connected to what we were just discussing, or are you just like listening
to the fact that Mage wants to do a topic, and then being like, no, I want to do the
topic?
No, it's not connected to Hitmontop.
It's connected to what we were talking about before Hitmontop.
Okay, all right.
Let's wrap it up.
All right.
What do you got?
All right, so I saw...
None other than Christine Weston Chandler was tweeting about how much she loved...
God, what the fuck is her name?
No, I love Kim Possible a lot.
Oh, okay.
And I saw an opportunity, right?
Of course.
Sure.
And I was like, wow, this lady, she's into my shit.
So I tweeted at her, and I was like, do you like any other pony analysis channels?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I saw this tweet.
I'm a big fan of T-Bat, personally.
And she responded.
She said she did not say anything about T-Bat, but she responded that she liked Kim Possible
a lot and Dr. Wolfe.
And I want to say that...
I think that it is very telling...
I think it is very telling that Chris Chan does not appreciate T-Bat and loves Dr. Wolfe.
So listen, she has allied herself with Dr. Wolfe by publicly professing her liking for
it, but not with T-Bat.
So T-Bat is pure.
T-Bat is pure and good.
Dr. Wolfe?
Yeah, that's true.
Or T-Bat just is just not the standards that Chris Chan demands, and you're saying that
if you want to be...
So it kind of sounds...
If you like...
If you appreciate what Dr. Wolfe does, you have...
If you appreciate what Dr. Wolfe does, you have tastes comparable to Chris Chan.
I just want to put that out there.
I think it kind of seems like Chris Chan is just into people who are currently doing
My Little Pony reviews.
Like, surely if T-Bat came back...
Oh my god, we've got to bring it back.
...surely if you maxed her vibe with T-Bat, Chris Chan would have the opportunity.
Oh, man.
We've got to let Chris Chan know that the future's looking bright.
Um, boy.
All right, Mage, what did you want to talk about?
It's not a super interesting topic or anything, but I really wanted to talk about it because
it's one of my favorite topics.
For like...
Yes.
It's one of my favorite topics.
And I want to talk about dreams.
Not like your goals or whatever, but like, you know, when you sleep and you have dreams
and you're like listening...
I'm not familiar with the concept.
Please, yeah.
When you close your eyes and you fall asleep and then you see images that are not real.
Okay, images.
What concept?
I mean, those are what dreams are, yeah.
I didn't launch into it, but I did have an amazing dream last night, but we can talk
about that later.
I had a dream that I was eating a hamburger and I realized it had a bun on it and it was
made of bread and it had carbs in it.
Oh, no.
Let me tell you.
No, let me tell you.
I'm ashamed.
Is this just what this is going to be?
Is just dreams are cool?
Well, let's find out if it's cool or not.
I'm ashamed to admit that in the dream, I said, well, I already ate half of it.
I might as well...
No!
That's the kind of man I am.
I'm weak.
I know the feeling very much.
Oh, didn't we already do a PCP on dreams before?
Yeah, that's the thing.
I wasn't sure if we did.
I asked Nate and he said no.
Oh, if only there was a way to check me.
If only there was an incredibly simple way.
Look at the topics that we've covered up to this point.
Yeah, I see.
But what are we...
That requires...
That requires sleep and dreams.
Well, I'm not sure if I was on that one.
I probably was, but regardless, the thing is...
Talk about it again.
Yeah, the beauty about dreams is that you get them almost every night.
And for me specifically, I get several nights.
So, you know, it's a topic that will never die until I do.
Will you want to share one with us?
Yes.
I actually, funny enough, because it got pushed back the topic,
I managed to get this really cool dream a few days ago
that I wouldn't have been able to share it like last episode.
So lucky me.
So it was like...
Why?
These things don't make sense.
Don't nitpick it, because, I mean, it's a dream.
Sure.
But it was really cool, and I really hope I do a justice.
Okay, so a little bit of memory did fade from me,
so I don't remember where it starts.
My dreams to have a tendency to shift from one dream to another.
That's what dreams tend to be like.
Yeah.
Yeah, so this specific scenario starts with me being a military soldier,
and I wasn't mage.
I was this soldier guy.
And we were in this building.
It was kind of like a warehouse, but it was huge.
Imagine the biggest hospital you've ever seen,
and just that hospital being hollow in a warehouse.
That's how big and wide.
It's huge.
There's no floors between the things.
It's just very high, hollow.
And within that warehouse,
there was like a sort of like almost like a maze-like building,
and we were taking cover in it.
This is, by the way, in post-apocalyptic sort of scenario.
I'm just imagining the Angels of Death anime.
I have not seen it.
You would absolutely...
Well, first of all, have you played the game Angels of Death?
Because it seems like you're like...
It's like the most mage aesthetic thing I could possibly imagine.
The anime especially looks like your artwork, practically.
It's one of those indie horror games that RPG Maker horror games,
but it's got an anime adaptation now.
You should check it out.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Was it actually like an indie RPG Maker game that got an anime?
Yeah.
Holy shit.
It's like dope.
That's how that works in Japan, isn't it?
I mean, that's not...
I mean, RPG Maker specific is...
I mean, I'd imagine that's pretty rare.
I made an RPG Maker VX.
It is very popular, and that hasn't gotten an anime from what I've heard.
I mean, like, Angels of Death is very Ibsque.
I mean, it's possible that the creator of Ibsque didn't allow an anime to be made.
Shout out to Master of the Wind, the actual best RPG Maker RPG ever made.
I never played Master of the Wind.
You used to talk about Master of the Wind all the time.
And I had to make fan art that one time.
I drew that fire guy, whose name I forget.
Sometimes I think about...
I did a couple Master of the Wind pieces because you liked it so much,
and some of them were really bad, and I'm embarrassed about them.
Well, there you go.
But some of them were okay.
All right, mate.
Sorry.
Yeah, but back to the gym.
So I posted back to the faculty, it was exciting.
And so it was me, another soldier, and three old people bunkering down in the maze.
We were getting ready for a war, because we were going to get attacked by opposing forces of other humans.
And the thing is, we were not going to win this.
We knew that we were outmatched despite our mazes, despite our coverings,
despite everything, all the firepower we had.
We were not going to win this.
We were going to die.
All these people that were trying to save, all these people are hiding and covering or whatever.
There's only a few soldiers and a lot of civilians,
and we were not going to make it if this attack goes down.
So somehow I managed to sell my soul in exchange of winning this war, or rather this battle.
However, it had to be conditional.
I couldn't just snap my fingers and win.
I had to win it with the way this force tells me to win.
And if I don't do it, I lose my soul and I lose the war.
I lose out.
However, I took the risk regardless.
And what I had to do, I had to sort of like quote unquote back step one on my own
and kill them in front of this specific guy from the opposing forces.
And if that person dies, then the war is over, basically,
and the truce is had, peace is had.
So I did what I had to do.
I killed the guy.
No, no, wait, hold on.
So the forces come in and they start shooting at us,
and they even went on top of the, what do you call it, the scaffolding, I think, that's the thing.
On top of the building, they uncovered the building.
They were shooting us from top down.
And I wasn't getting hit, but I killed several of them.
I got a few headshots.
That was cool.
Wow, you're so good at this mate.
It's incredible.
Wow, I know, right?
So the forces went in, and the reason I couldn't just immediately do it,
is because I had to have a specific guy come in and walk into a certain position.
So we had to take some damage.
But once the guy was in,
so I killed one of our own.
And once the guy was dead,
the big boss guy called off the forces and was like,
okay, you know, whatever the truce.
During the battle, though, one of the old guys
that we were protecting,
his heart stopped, I think,
and they were trying to resuscitate.
What's the word, resuscitate?
Resuscitate, yeah.
Yeah, they were trying to resuscitate.
And I was like, okay, let me do it.
But I'm going to try, because I have plot armor,
and I'm the protagonist.
I should be able to do this, right?
So I went in there and I tried my best.
All I could manage was give that guy one last breath to open his eyes,
and that came out creepier.
I was like, I can save the guy.
And I was really sad.
I was heart torn.
Old people dying is the saddest thing to me.
And so it was very...
Even for a lot of sadness, I'm afraid.
It was heartbreaking.
But we had no time to mourn,
because of the whole the ruckus.
Ah, yes, the ruckus.
Yeah, all the ruckus.
The telltale ruckus.
Because of all the noise we created through the wars.
Like, the zombies were moving it,
because, like I said, it's not class apocalyptic unless they're zombies.
So the zombies were moving it,
and we had to evacuate.
But thankfully, zombies are slow,
so we could evacuate in an orderly fashion.
And we would...
It was very easy to do.
They were not a threat.
Zombies are never a threat in my dreams,
even though in all my apocalyptic dreams...
How often are zombies in your dreams?
Very often, actually.
See, I finished watching The Walking Dead a while ago.
So like ever since,
and even a bit before that,
like ever since and a bit before that,
I get these apocalyptic dreams.
They are varied in setting.
Not all of them have zombies.
Some of them do.
Zombies are rarely a threat.
They're just sort of in the background.
So like, yeah, we were moving out,
and then me, this other soldier guy,
and this doctor lady,
we had to sort of like separate from the group,
because, you know, I kind of killed one of my own.
And even though I did it to win the war,
people wouldn't necessarily know that,
so I kind of, you know, had to high tail it out of there.
So we started to move,
and this other lady that's starting following us,
and she was from the opposing forces,
and I know that she was able to manipulate water,
like some sort of waterbender or whatever.
And she was very dangerous,
and the fact that she was tailing us,
even though she was trying to play it cool,
like she wasn't tailing us,
oh, she's just traveling in the same direction,
was kind of like sketchy.
And then like,
so we ducked into this like shady hotel sort of thing,
where we met with another soldier
that wasn't there.
And he was on our side,
but he wasn't there for the battle.
And apparently,
the person I killed,
it was his best friend,
and when he learned
the best friend had died.
Oh, talk about awkward.
He didn't necessarily know that I killed him,
but he learned that he had to die,
like, and he decided,
and because of a traitor,
he decided to go find the traitor,
and like, he also had some sort of powers as well,
but if he had to,
but if he didn't do it,
it would undo my wish,
and my soul would just go to waste,
you know, because the world will start all over again,
and I wouldn't be able to,
you know, do it again,
so I had to go after the guy
to stop him
from doing whatever he was going to do,
and I remember like the last part of my dream was like,
he was in this pod,
and he was about to activate the pod
to do something, like teleport or whatever,
and like, I slammed open the door,
I reached into the pod,
I was like,
the handout is like, you know,
come with me, I'll show you the truth
or something like that,
and then the dream ended.
Alright.
I checked, we have not done a PCP on Dream,
but we have done a PCP on Sleep,
in which we explicitly say
how much we did.
I also did that same research.
Well,
I always like talking about dreams,
and I'm, you find what's interesting.
Have you heard this phrase,
have you heard the expression
that dreams are incredibly interesting
only to the person telling the story
of their dream?
No, because I want to hear about other people's dreams,
and I always find it fascinating.
Well, sure, sure.
Well, one time,
I think I've probably told the story
on the Sleep episode,
but I haven't.
If I could get,
the story doesn't mean anything to me,
but like, if it possibly,
like, all my dreams have
very clear meanings,
like, they're all shit, they're all nightmares,
they all suck, and I hate them,
but like, it's pretty easy
for me to extrapolate what they're about,
because almost all of them are-
Oh wait, sorry, that was just real life,
my mistake, I confused the two sometimes.
All of my dreams are just about me
being lost in a big place,
with people and or trying to protect
someone, so like,
they're all like direct responses
to things that are going on in my life
or my general mind state,
it's usually obvious,
and they're all basically the same,
they follow the same few templates,
so like, it sounds like you have a lot of dreams
where there's zombies and shit,
but they're not a threat,
so like, I don't know,
do you think that this has anything to say
about you personally?
Not really, okay, I have two types of dreams,
at least I categorize into two types of dreams,
one dreams where I am mage,
like, in real life self,
and one where I'm not mage,
which is basically what this dream was
and a lot of my coolest, my awesomeest,
my most badass dreams are when
I'm not my real self,
like, I could be like, quote unquote,
the mage. Okay, see that sounds like
it says something about you that maybe you
think that the only way you could be awesome
is by escaping
and not thinking of yourself
as yourself.
But isn't the only way
to detain if something's cool or not
is if you haven't done it already,
like, if you're just going to be yourself
in any dream, do anything that you've normally done
that's never going to be cool.
Well, it depends on if you think yourself is cool.
No, I love myself, that's no secret.
Yeah, woo!
So like, if you don't like yourself,
then any time you would see yourself
doing something awesome in a dream,
like being you.
It's like an experience of like
playing a game or role-playing something
like that, like experiencing an experience,
you know, in a safe environment.
And I like that.
I like those dreams, they're very fun.
When I have dreams about me being me,
it's usually like callbacks to the past
and the people that I don't want to remember
and it's like, it's nagging me
about things that I don't want
to think about or talk about
or want to move past, like a lot of my dreams
are like me, always have me
being back at school
during those years that I dreaded the most
and I hate that.
It's a callback, I guess it was
traumatic to me or something.
Yeah, it's unresolved trauma.
I think dreams for the most part
are just like things,
they're attempting, it's your brain
attempting to understand the things
that it doesn't understand,
but like it doesn't,
it's showing you these images
of you at all, it's like it's trying to help itself.
It's trying to like put things in their place
and like in my dreams I always see,
I always see random
faces and locations
that I have been to or like people I have known,
but they're not accurate.
Like the relationships
and the scenarios are not accurate
to what those people really were, but it's like
there's a reason that these people
are here and that this scenario is here.
It's just that that reason is jumbled.
It doesn't have a clear, coherent meaning,
but like through looking at the broad scope
of all the dreams put together,
I can figure out broadly what they're about.
You know, like the fact that
most of my dreams end with me
literally being on the run
from like a massive group of people
is like obviously I am afraid
of society coming after me.
Like that is something I've always been dealing with.
Are you a lucid dreamer, Digid?
No.
If I figure out that it's a dream,
most of my dreams end with me dying.
Like most of them end when
or are about to die or like surrounded
or trapped. Like my dreams usually
end when it reaches the point where
I am fully
Yeah, exactly. It's when I
reach the point of having the least control
and like I usually am straight up
immobilized or like about to die
and that's when I wake up.
I...
All my dreams are nightmares about either
I can't find...
It's all about I can't accomplish something.
I am lost and I can't find my way.
Or other people do not
want to assist me in doing something.
Mine are often about being lost but specifically
being left behind.
It's that I'm trying to catch up to the other
people who I was with before.
Yeah, I have a lot of those
dreams as well.
That's sad.
I don't think I dream that much.
I don't have that many
or I don't remember most of mine.
Like I remember that hamburger
dream.
I hadn't had one in a while.
It's a very exciting dream though.
It's a very straight forward dream too.
I think I feel like what I know
what that one's about. I was just dreaming about
eating and then I noticed that I was eating bread
and I was like, ah shit, oh well.
And that's the story.
I had another one like not that long ago
and I...
Your dreams are all just keto nightmares.
That's all you're having is keto nightmares.
It's been one thing now.
Yeah, that's it.
That's the only one I can remember
in recent memories.
Wasn't the other one also about eating a burger
or something?
That's the same one that I was just talking about.
I have a question about your dreams.
We've all expressed our displeasure
with this dream about dreams.
I love this.
You guys can leave.
I want to talk about dreams.
I have a question.
Have you attempted or
has there ever been a scenario
whenever you were chased?
Have you ever turned around
and asked them why they're chasing you?
Uh, no.
Because I know why they're chasing you.
There's a movie.
He knows what he did.
Exactly what I did.
What's the movie?
Why MS review a movie where that happens?
Where like the kid...
Wait, no. That's what happens in Stranger Things.
Stranger Things Season 2.
Bob tells the kid
next time you have a dream about the thing
turn around and tell it you're not afraid of it
and then he does that and it fucking murders him
and he gets fucked up and everything's ruined.
The reason I asked is because
I had a similar dream.
Spoilers, bitches!
I had a similar dream when I was younger
and some scary force
was chasing me
and I had no idea why.
I think it was like a witch but not like a humanoid
witch. It was terrifying.
It had me cornered
and I had no clue
why it was chasing me so I turned around
and it was like, why the fuck are you chasing me?
And it just got stumped.
And I woke up.
You stumped it?
Yeah, I stumped it.
It didn't attack me.
I was like, what the fuck are you chasing me?
What's your problem?
I woke up.
That's how you deal with a bully mage for sure.
I don't have necessarily nightmares.
Whenever scary things happen
I usually interpret it as
like, holy cow,
that's some cool shit happening.
Or like, I lose a dream
and then I just sort of like
bonk it on the head and it goes away.
My nightmares are usually
when I'm completely alone
in a completely empty town
and no one's there
and I just wander alone
and something's there.
I never see it. It's some sort of unknown force.
And it's
the patriarch
lurking behind every shadow.
It scares the living crap out of me
in those dreams.
Yeah, sounds scary.
It's always there.
Being alone is one of the scariest things
for me for sure.
The worst times is
if it's evening
and the lamps are on
the street lamps are on
and it's evening
and the lamps are a source of light
but everything else is getting darker
and growing darker and it's like
that sort of emptiness.
That's the only thing that sort of scares me
in my dreams nowadays.
Everything else is just like, oh, well, that was cool.
So...
That's cool.
Like I said before, I don't dream often
but I had a particularly vibrant dream
last night that stuck with me.
Good timing.
Yeah, it was good timing.
Yeah, quickly.
So, I don't know how I got here.
No, don't.
Well, I don't know what the situation was
but something was going on
with Michelle
where she was doing a fashion show
or something
and she had weird dreads
like Kerrigan from Starcraft 1
and
she was wearing this purple dress
and I was in the crowd watching this on stage
and she was going out with a bunch of other people
doing stuff
and I don't know, it was like
some celebration of her
and she had done something like
maybe it was her quinceanera
I don't know.
Yeah, that's the one.
I don't know what it was
but it was something going on celebrating her
and I was watching from the crowd
and feeling slightly uncomfortable
about the whole affair.
The only reason it sounds like that
if you're someone who doesn't generally have dreams
is it's all about Michelle.
It's obviously because you now have a new element
in your life that you have to
now reconcile in your brain.
Well, newer.
Well, I don't want to get personal
but we've been talking about
just some real shit recently
so my thoughts are that it's probably relevant to that.
I had a long period
of not really having any dreams
when me and May first started dating
it kind of had quelled
my nightmares for a while
and after things that happened last month
I have non-stop had nightmares
about people trying to take her away
from me and me having to save her
all the time.
People just kidnapping her in a literal
burlap sack and me having to
beat the shit out of them.
Did you pull off the mask of the kidnappers
next time and see that it is in fact May
under that. She is the kidnapper of herself.
Whoa.
And think about what that means.
Deep.
I have a silly dream.
In my dream
Digi was doing something
outrageously
silly and
he just one stop.
Nate was doing his padded
Registeel impersonation.
Not normal Registeel, but the Registeel that was removed.
It looked too much like a Nazi salute.
I want to see that.
Over and over and over again.
Yeah, Google search Registeel.
I named my Registeel that I caught
in a Pokemon Go Auschwitz.
I used to have dreams about
being out of my relationship
and that was great and then when I was out of it
I had nightmares that I was
not out of it and that leaving it
was in fact a dream
and that was terrifying and I would wake up
to great relief.
That's my dream story.
I just want to point out that the
thing that makes Registeel seem
so horrible is just that he is
holding up his left hand
kind of forward.
Sort of like a salute.
It does look like a Nazi salute.
It wasn't intentional.
I'm pretty sure.
No, I'm sure it wasn't.
I'm sure it was just the only dynamic pose
they could come up with
with such a fucking
horrible close design.
Alright, let's get the fuck out of here.
Hey Digi, last episode
I was talking about my trip to Italy
and I had a conversation
and I posted in the real friend initiative chat
which is in the PCP discord
about
city planning.
What you like to talk about city planning is I alluded to this last episode as well
because I have some big
ideas and big thoughts
and I have a PowerPoint presentation for you
about something in Italy.
Go ahead dude, I'm curious.
I love city planning.
I don't know if we can talk about this on PCP at all
but you and me
Didn't we have a whole city planning
discussion on one of these episodes?
Wasn't that like the first formless cast?
You might have, but I might have been gone.
I'm pretty sure on the first formless cast
it was like a massive city planning discussion.
Sure, okay.
And I thought you were a part of it.
If that is the case, then that is the case.
I was not.
I don't remember.
Well, whatever. In any case,
me and you have been thinking about sea planning a lot.
And going to Boston
was the first time that I ever thought about this
in Boston so much and it's just a well-designed city
that I started to come up with ideas.
I started to come up with, I started to concoct
buzzwords in my head.
What makes a good city?
And so I came up with some several buzzwords here.
Dense, easily navigatable
and then another one that I forgot.
You can cut out a syllable.
That's even one word. That's true.
Ooh, very nice.
Those are some buzzwords.
I know what makes a good city now.
I know.
It's navigatable.
And so you go to Italy and Rome.
Rome specifically.
And you think, okay, on paper,
it's very, very dense
and you can navigate it.
But here's the thing.
Rome is Rome
and it's been rebuilt on top of itself
a thousand times over a thousand years.
They did it once a year.
You get some crazy shit.
Yeah, once a year.
It's all demolished.
The exact same city but slightly different.
Well, yeah.
It's something like 2000 or something.
I don't know.
The Roman Empire was well-established
2000 years ago when Jesus was around.
But whatever.
Anyway, so here's the thing about Rome.
It's super dense.
You can walk down a Roman road
and walk down a block
or so. They don't really have blocks.
They don't have arcans.
A street.
Hundreds upon hundreds of stores.
It's just so packed.
But the thing about Rome is
is that the streets.
The streets in particular.
Imagine a back alleyway in America.
Imagine, you know, you see a space
in between two stores
where they keep like a dumpster or something.
The size of that back alleyway
are the size of the main streets
in Rome.
So there are no big open streets
the way we as Americans would think of them.
There are only
exclusively
back alleyways that go
in between buildings.
Very narrow, narrow streets
where you literally have to like dodge
people or if you're a person
dodge multiple cars.
When they built these alleys
they would not have been cars.
Well, sure.
That's the case
for Boston as well.
They've adjusted
and they've planned for wagons and stuff.
But the streets are so fucking dense in Rome
that you can barely
it's feel like you're driving.
It's like you're claustrophobic because you're just surrounded by
on either side of you
towering buildings. Like no matter how
many stores are actually in each building
it's always three stories.
It's really bizarre, I've noticed this.
They're all three stories. So you're gonna have a shop
on the first level and then just literally
nothing on the top like, you know, two
and three levels. And they're just there
because I don't know, they used to be residential
back in the medieval times.
So you have these towering buildings on either side of you
for just miles. And there's no
like, especially in Rome
where there's so much history and architecture
and you know, oh, you can just walk and see the Charlie Fountain.
The Charlie Fountain is this view
like, you know, huge majestic fountain
that's like a staple of Italy culture
you know, it's on your postcards.
It just is in some
bum-fuck alley. You could just walk
accidentally, like stumble upon this
huge tourist destination
without even trying to. There's no
like, space for it. It just is
in the, like, a one by one
block where a normal
building would be. It's like, oh, it's just this
giant, beautiful fountain.
It's so dense and it's
over-expense. Like, it's so hard to get around it.
Let me pause at something. I think that the problem
with cities like Rome is that
you build the perfect city
and it's beautiful and everyone loves it
so everyone moves there
and then immediately it is no longer
the perfect city because
I agree, Digi, build the wall. Keep them out.
That's what we gotta do. You just need to build
more cities. We just need
there to be, like, every time we hit
the cap where, like, the city doesn't make
sense anymore, do another one. And I understand
why that wouldn't have been possible
at a time where you had to build your city
somewhere that made, like, strategic sense
for, like, combat as well as
for, like, you know, having enough water
and resources and everything. But, like, we've
spent the last 200 years making
that not an issue anymore. We
nobody lives next to a farm
now. Like, we don't have
to worry about the food being
nearby anymore. It comes by car. We
have aqueducts for the water. Even
the Romans invented that. You know, like,
there's ways and because
we don't have to worry about land fighting
anymore, like, there's not a thing.
So, like, whether or not it's a tactical
advantage to build your city here
totally irrelevant now. So, like,
there's probably shitloads of places
that just hadn't been considered places
where cities could be built before.
But, like, because
the big cities are self-perpetuating
hype machines, like, New York
City is constantly
hyping itself as
the place to go. And so, people are
going to go there, even though
it's a city that is
under constant construction
because there's so many people
that the needs of the city are constantly changing
and they're never met.
They're never realized, you know?
Did you know they recently, like,
like, stop granting
new Uber license? And they're going to, like,
have new laws limiting Uber
consumption because they are
running, like, taxis and they're
stuffing up the streets. That's, uh, that's
makes sense. I mean, like,
it's kind of like the, um,
the girl in the gun, like, person
limit thing, right? Where
he's like, there has to only be so many people
on earth or else it
becomes a problem. And the
argument from the
opposition is not so much, hey,
like, it's like, well
can we just find a way to make it
so we can keep expanding the population
and keep it under control and have it make
sense? And it's like, I feel like we haven't
we haven't found that answer
just yet. But, like, that's what we need
to be looking for. And until you have that, you ain't got nothing. Right.
You gotta find that first if you want to build more people
or whatever. Exactly. And, like, we need to
find the paradigm that makes sense. And I
think the problem is that no, not enough
people understand why
they want to go to the big city.
Like, yeah.
Oh, this goes back exactly
to, like, St. Helene
because you're supposed to go to St. Helene,
why do you want to go to New York?
It's New York. And you also
if you're from a small town,
like, uh, for instance
Virginia Beach is not necessarily a small city,
but it has no culture. It has no
nowhere to go if you're an artist. There's not, like,
like Victor, who's been, my brother Victor,
former guest in the PCP,
we all know who Victor is. We all know who Victor is.
He's been on the PCP. So Victor,
you know, he works in
film in Virginia Beach, which is a very small
industry. There's no, like, expansion
there. And so when he looks at the rest
of the world, it's like, where can I go
that I can make money doing film?
He thinks, like, okay, we got
Georgia because Atlanta
is a big film town. You got LA
and you got New York. And it's kind of like
from the perspective of someone living in Virginia Beach,
that's all there is.
Because that's all you hear about. But, like,
there are other places
and if not, you could even
build a place. Like,
my mentality was always like, hey,
let's just move all the people who we want
to work with here, and then we
have a place. Like, that's, you know,
the theory behind PCPHQ
and based on
the Red Letter Media guys who literally did that.
They've been fucking Milwaukee. Like, it's not a film city,
but they have a film career
there, you know. Granted,
they're not working in, you know, in the
big leagues, but, like,
they are able to produce full-blown indie
films on the basis of
their, like, 10 or 12-man
crew and whoever they can hire on board,
you know, to work with them in Milwaukee.
Yeah. Quick aside, quick
aside, but before we move on, I can see
the comments now. I just want to make
sure everyone on the same page is me.
I'm not saying that New York City is
Lean Tower of Pisa Tier, a.k.a. absolute shit.
Lean, uh, uh, New York City
is cool. It just is the same
sort of general idea where it's, like, people
would have the, they don't have a reason to go to New York City.
New York City, there are reasons to go there.
I would like to live in New York City.
I mean, I like Boston. I would like, I think I'd like
New York a lot as well. Yeah, and this, this whole
theory that I'm positing is why I ended
up in Boston, because when I was
in Virginia Beach, I was looking at all these cities that,
like, people recommended. I'm like, well, I don't know
what is supposed to be good
about these cities until I go there.
Like, I know Atlanta is supposed to have, like, a big
film scene, and it is, and a big rap scene,
and it's a big city, but then you go
there, and you realize that Atlanta is super
spread out, and it's really difficult to
get around, and it's, it's
dirty, and yeah, it's just like,
it's not a place that I looked
at, and went like, wow, this seems
like the dream, you know?
It was more like, and so,
and I went to Atlanta. Where was that? Atlanta.
Atlanta. Atlanta. Atlanta. Atlanta.
Uh, I like Atlanta, right?
It's, I mean, it's fine, but it's not
nearly like, when I came to,
like, when I came to Boston, this was a city
I had no concept of, like, I did not
know anything about Boston
at all until I came here,
but then when I looked at it, I was just like, oh,
this is exactly
what I was looking for,
because even though Boston's not known
for, like, a film scene, or this or
that, or like, for YouTubers being here, like,
I looked at it, and I went, well, this would
be a great place to do this job.
It's just a matter of
setting up perception. Yeah, setting up
something here, and like, there are already
other YouTubers who live here, you know,
right at the gate got to hang out with
Zenn Huckstable, who's super cool, and I'd love to work with
them, you know, and like, Tom and Ben were already
here, and it's just like,
this can make sense.
It's just a matter of actually
going to the city, looking at the resources
that are available here, and saying, what can we
build here, as opposed to like, what is there
already infrastructure for, because if
you go to L.A. or New York, where
everyone else is going to have a film career,
guess what is going to be the most competitive
market there, is
going to be the film career, which is why, you know,
everyone goes to L.A. and fucking works in cafes
for 15 years while they try to play the screenplay.
We can be big fish in the small pond. Right, exactly.
But the thing
is, there should not be, like, regardless
of, regardless
of like, the big fish small pond dichotomy kind
of thing, it's more like, what everyone should do is
think about
what kind of fish you want to be, and what kind
of pond you want to live in,
you know, like, it's not just about being
a big fish in a small pond, it's like, this
is a pond that suits my
needs, and so regardless of how big I am
as a fish, like, I would like to
live in this pond, and like, let's
find an ecosystem where it makes sense
for you to live in, you know.
There's no reason to stick with this metaphor.
I can make it work.
It's fine.
There's no, it does not impact.
It's not the same. Anyway, yeah, I just think
I think we need
I think the only answer to, like, fixing cities
is to build new cities, like
it's not to try to keep building over
the ones we already have, it's like
we need to just go out and find a place
where we can build, like, an ideal city
for a certain type of person
and then get that type of person
to come there, and then, like,
just, you know, be like, hey, here, here's
a spot for you if you think like me,
you know, and for those
of us
on the autistic spectrum, we need
to build an autism city.
It's basically what I'm saying, and that's my
dream right now, is to build
the autism city.
Beautiful, beautiful.
You should definitely learn,
we talked about this a little bit in chat, did you, but you should definitely
look into the actual specifics of
the plan for Epcot, because it is
the most autistic thing I've ever
heard, like, everything is, like, perfect circles
and, like, it's shaped to be, like,
it looks like a cell. It's very
interesting. Have you guys
ever played table?
I'm planning, me and Tom,
let me just, let me just launch
this right now, me and Tom got a new channel
called I Am Games,
which we also have a t-shirt, we've already sold
five t-shirts on the basis of one
tweet, so this is
already happening, and our
first videos and our first live streams
are going to be about fable, so
there you go, what a coincidence.
Yeah, that's a good one, okay, like, the reason.
I've never played a fable game.
Well, you're going to learn all about them
on I Am Games!
Go to
imgames.fun right now,
and it links to our YouTube channel.
Are you kidding me? No, I own
imgames.fun, links to the
YouTube channel I Am Games.
Wait, why did you
get a custom URL?
I am very serious about this t-shirts
thing.
I'm very fucking serious, I was just
looking up trademarks for a second ago,
and I found out that as long as you just put
a TM next to your shit, you basically
have a common law trademark, and if you can
prove that, like, you were the first one to do
that, then you can
back yourself up in a court of law, so
I'm officially announcing
that I own the trademark to the phrase
I Am Games, so there you go.
This is the statement.
What is the relevance of I Am Games?
You own the trademark,
you own the copyright, right?
No, I just, because I just said that, I now
have the common law trademark by saying that
just now on this podcast.
That's why I said it like that.
I just looked up the
laws just now while we were doing the show.
Like, I thought that, like, you have to apply for a
trademark. If you apply for it, if you
apply for the trademark, then
it is, like, in the system, and people can
look it up, but again,
the law of trademarking is just if you
say you own it enough times, then
like, you do.
Okay, okay, the reason I brought
up Fable, though,
is because, like, when I was
younger, I really wanted to build
like, a little town, like, I was like
when I grew up, I want to build a town, and
like, and the reason I brought up Fable is
because I was really, I really, really
loved Fable. At that time, it was
like, the first game I played on the
original Xbox, on my very first
console that I officially owned,
and I really liked
Bowerstone, and I was like, when I
grew up, I want to have a town just
like Bowerstone, and just, like,
a little bit cleaner, and
that was, that was my dream town
slash city sort of thing. I'm good
to be looking, when I play this game, I'm
going to be studying the city now that you've said that.
It's not good, it was
like, a nine-year-old
mage. I don't know, because Peter
Malinu is the kind of guy who probably would
like, involve pretty high-level city
planning into his games.
It's a very tiny town. Those were
Peter Malinu games, I forgot.
And there's this book
that I want to read called The Timeless Art
of Building, which is a, it's
fascinatingly structured, because it's like a full-size
book, but it's written in such a way that
if you were to just read all the
headlines, then you will get, like,
he wrote it so like, every paragraph has
a headline, and he's like, if you only have
an hour, just read all the headlines.
And all the other stuff is just, like, fill in
information. Basically, like, my compress, decompress
video is kind of structured the same way
as this book, which I didn't even fucking
realize until just now, but that's hilarious.
Yeah, but
he talks a lot about, like, the ways that
cities should be planned, such as, like,
taking a area, and instead
of building roads first,
just observing how
people traverse the area naturally,
and then building the roads in those
paths, and things like that.
Makes sense. Yeah. And just, you know,
there's lots of stuff about just the structure of stuff,
and then they built a campus
on the basis of his book, like,
his ideas to, like, test it out.
But the person who I look up to the most
for their stance on city planning is
Hayao Miyazaki, who
built the Ghibli Museum out of,
like,
his ideas about, like, what a perfect
environment should be, that, like,
for instance,
he has a whole poem he wrote about,
like, the principles that the museum was built
on, and, like, if you read this poem, it's just
like, oh, this is just how the whole world
should be structured. I mean, okay, that's cool
and all, but rather than look up to, like, an actual
city planner, you're looking up to a guy who built one
building. Well, it's because
think about how
a building is a microcosm.
You can look at his building as a
scale model of a city. It's
basically the way I'm looking at it. Okay.
No one has been able
to build the ultimate city, because
no one guy who imagines it is
going to then be able to go and fucking
build it, except for Disney's attempt
with the Epcot Center. But, like,
um, and Disney was
unfeasibly rich, you know, and, like,
had this kind of power, and had already
built Disney World, you know? If there's one
guy that could do it, it was going to be Walt Disney.
Right, exactly. And, like, I think the problem
is that these guys
don't do enough to inspire
other people to work with them.
Like, guys like Hayao Miyazaki,
who, I think that
a big part of what he has realized
in his old age, if you watch, like,
The Wind Rises, I think a lot of that movie
is about his guilt
over the fact that he tried to do everything
himself, that, like, he was so draconian
and so, like, oh, everything has
to be according to the letter of, like, my vision.
And, like, I think
that you're never going to get
enough people to build a city that way.
Like, you need to have people on board
with you, but also to, like, embrace
their ideas and to, like, evolve
the thing, you know? Like, so
I don't want to build a city based on, like, my
plan for a city. I want
to, like, communicate with
people and all of us come to an understanding
of what environment we want
and then set about figuring out how to build that
together, you know? So it's not so much that, like,
you know. Digi, let's just start
like a creative Minecraft. We should definitely
I mean, I think that's
basically what that exists for.
Like, I think a lot of these
a lot of
modern art is trying
to help people
to develop the mindsets that the people
who create the art have.
Like, I think that when Notch made a game
like Minecraft, there was
when he put in those tools, like, for instance
the red, um, the red, uh,
what's it fucking called? The redstone, whatever?
Yeah, the redstone. Like, it's just
teaching kids how to program.
Like, that's what it's there for, is to teach
you how to code, essentially, because it
is just, it's just literally built in
circuit boards. So, like, the reason
he puts this in the game is he's like, hey,
let's see what you can create if I gave you
a three-dimensional coding environment,
you know? Like, which is
even more, like, you can create things that you couldn't
just easily code in real life,
um, because
I mean, you could code it into a computer and then it could
be simulated there, but like, he gives you the means
to, like, literally just
lay down some redstone bricks and a thing
like, physically happens
in the reality of this game. And, like, you can
instantly see what would be the
results of if you duplicated this
in reality, but you would need all those materials.
Yeah, coding it in a computer would be too artificial.
But in Minecraft, you can do it, you can do it
for real. Again, it's... It really happens.
Yeah, pretty much. I mean, like...
No, I know it's... Because you'd have to build
the code of Minecraft first to even
have the visuals to simulate
the thing you're coding. Like, and for
kids, I think the abstraction
of just looking at a bunch of numbers is
why coding is hard. Like, you look
at a code and you're like, what the fuck does that
say? But, like, when you just lay down
redstone bricks and shit, and you look at
it, then it makes perfect sense, you know? Especially
when you can see what it activates.
So, I do think it's all just teaching...
I agree. My nephew has
like, a similar, like, sort of play kid
specifically for young children. And it has
like, stuff like, um,
with little electronics and stuff. So he can
build, like, a thing that he can sort of
make fly, or have, like, a little
light bulb light up. And it's, like, a very
sort of safe kid-friendly environment. And
like, he was like, fine when he
managed to build those things. He was very interested
and that's really neat.
Maybe like that Nintendo Labo is the same
sort of thing. I was about to talk about that.
Like, and a lot of the stuff... Like,
there's a reason Minecraft is so big in schools
that, like, it was adapted as, like,
this major teaching tool. Because, like,
I think that right now
most of, like, the
thought leaders in society are of the
mindset that, like, what we need the most is,
like, more engineers and more coders
and more people who can, like,
bring visions to life.
Because, like, right now we don't need
soldiers. We don't need, like,
we don't need people working factories, because
we can replace them with robots eventually.
Like, we actually kind of need soldiers, because
they're all, all people are too fat and we're
running low. That's true fact. That's true
fact. Well, we need to also make people
less fucking fat. That's part of the mission here.
But...
Like, Otaku Gonzo Journalism
Bro Thought Leader
In my book, I call myself
a prospective millennial
thought leader, I think. And D-List
D-List?
No, I think it was D-List Millennial
Thought Leader. Something like that. In any
case, like,
I do think that,
like, for instance, when
people talk about, like, the problem of robots
taking our jobs, right?
Like, robots taking people's jobs is only
a problem, because people don't know how to do
other jobs. Like, if
everyone knew... Imagine if we lived
in a world where everyone knew how to code.
Well, we have infinite coding jobs.
Like, if you just keep coming up with
new shit to code, that's fine.
Like, so if everyone who we had working
the factories was replaced with robots, and
then all those people just learned to code,
they would all have jobs. Like, we don't need
these factory jobs to exist, you know?
The thing about the robot jobs,
right? Like,
it makes me so mad. In a perfect world,
we would replace, like,
replacing jobs with robots should not
be a bad thing. No, never.
That should be what we want, but it's not
because people want their jobs, because people
want to work to make money.
But it's totally, but it's totally ridiculous,
because, like, that's not producing
any... Wanting to live.
The problem is that people aren't thinking... That's not producing any additional
value, it's just, like,
it's just the systems we have in place
demand labor, even though that labor
is not necessary. And it's a problem of people not
thinking generationally. Like, there's lots of jobs that just don't need to be done.
Like, these people are worried about the job,
like, I understand if you were,
like, a, you know, a 40-year-old
man, and you're getting your job taken away by a robot,
I understand why that would bother you, but it's, like,
the reason this job has to be taken by a robot
is so your kid doesn't have to
do this job when you're dead.
You know, like, your kid... Nobody ever
has to do it again. Right.
That's just a hefty toll to pay, which I...
I mean, that's the real problem. Like, we...
We're asking people to basically be sacrificed
on the altar of progress in, uh, in a fact.
Which we should be asking...
Because we don't have a system to support that, you know.
I would ask of those people who are, like,
working the factory job, like, why do you value
your life so much? You're just a fucking factory worker.
Like, get over yourself.
Just die and let the next generation
take over. You're...
No, you don't have to die.
The problem is they'll say the same for all of us in time.
No, and I agree. I think that my...
Like, my purpose is here to just
inspire the next generation, and then
when my ideas are so outdated
that I can't help anymore, just let me die.
Like... I think there's some wisdom to that.
I honestly do. You know, and that's why
I think... I think that's why there's so many
old people who just, like, fuck off to Florida.
Like, Florida is where you go
when you realize that you can't really
add anything to society anymore.
Like, just go to Florida and go, like,
just sit by the beach and look at the water
until you're out, you know?
I think that's... I think that's... I think I'm
glad I respect the old people
who have the dignity to just get out
of the way and fuck off to some
ass-backwards place like Florida
where it's, like, beautiful, but also
everyone's insane.
You know? God, I'm so
fucking immature. There are still...
I read them out most of the time,
but there are still times where I fear death.
I need... I need to...
I think it's... I think it's
fair to fear death, but it's just, like,
it's going to
come unless we can... unless
we have techno-singularity within
our lifetime, which I used to... that was the
only thing that kept me away from fearing death
before, was, like, oh, man,
I don't have to be afraid because
maybe, like, according to certain
projections, I might upload my consciousness
to a computer, but then, like, all the stuff
about that also informs you, like, hey, just so you
know, if you upload your consciousness collectively,
like, you cease to exist.
You just become... Right, you know,
you're just gonna melt into
the sea of information, and you, as a personal identity,
is no longer real, so it's...
I've pretty much given up hope.
Like, if I happen, my consciousness gets saved
in my lifetime, that's great, but I'm not gonna
back yet. I'm expecting to die.
I mean, how would you bank on that?
I'm not. I'm not.
Well, that's a good idea.
Well, like, what would you do differently?
What would you do differently at all
if you thought that one day your consciousness
was going to get in trouble?
If one could live one's life differently,
if you were banking on the expectation that you
would live forever, as opposed to expecting
to die and have to pass on, like,
your information memetic legacy,
as opposed to your physical presence
in the world, you know? You know what's made me comfortable
with death is that, like, I used to always say,
like, I want to upload my consciousness to a computer
and live forever, and people always ask, like, well,
what would you do if you live forever? Wouldn't you get bored?
And I'd be like, no, there's endless new information,
there's endless new art, but now that I've
recognized that basically all art is exactly
the same, and that it's, like, all basically sending
the same message, it's like, oh, well, I don't care
about consuming all of it anymore, like, you know?
Yeah, I mean, there's a lot of overlap for sure.
Yeah, so, not to mention the fact that...
You start to see the patterns. I imagine
as you get older and you see more and more art,
you start to see the patterns, it starts to look like,
it starts to be, like, cipher, looking at the code
of the matrix, you know? You see
the code behind it, and it just gets less
and less engaging, and then
you die. So, it's all good.
I think a lot of what keeps us going is
the wonderment of discovery of the world.
Like, I'm currently going through
the phase in my life right now, where I am
in wonderment at discovering the pleasures of
adulthood, which are the pleasures of childhood
are, like, a freedom
to do whatever you want with little to no
consequences, and have other people worry about
the details. The pleasures of adulthood are
taking ownership of your life and
taking control of your own destiny, and, like,
steering your ship where it wants to go.
But, like, once you've done that, there's
really, like, you, that's pretty much everything
there is. Like, you could become, like, an
adventurer or whatever. You could travel
to far distant places. But it takes constant effort to make it
happen, and that's the excitement of it. Is that, like...
I mean, yeah, that's right.
It is the journey. It is about the journey.
Our brains, you know, stop
growing pretty much by word 25
or 27 or whatever. Like, I really
think that our ideas really are going
to calcify in our brains.
And, like, things like, like,
all the crazy stuff going on with, like, gender
these days, and pushing, like, norms
from, from olden times and all that stuff.
Like, that all could be 100%
exactly, like, in 100 years, we'll
look back and be, like, this is exactly
what we needed. It was 100% moral. But, like,
everyone alive today, you know, most people,
the youngest generation is coming up,
they're just, like, those people are, like, yeah,
this is what we need to do. We're going to push towards this.
And the older people, through no fault of their own,
are just scared and confused.
And, like, really, I don't think
those people, many of them, will actually
change. So, if everyone became immortal,
these ideas just might calcify
and we'd stop here. I think that's why
death and the next generation is a
valuable cycle to keep, to keep happening.
I write about this towards the start
of my book that I was saying how, like,
I don't like it, but I agree.
I was saying, like, I know there's lots of people
who want to live alone and who might be pursuing
immortality so that they themselves
can have more impact. And I'm, like, you know,
I think that's fine if you really are
a brilliant mind, maybe we could use you
around for a little longer. But, like, as soon
as your ideas become dogmatized,
they need to go. Because, ultimately...
In 200 years. Like, ultimately,
until the moment that we can say
we escaped entropy,
there is no reason to stop
evolving. Like, there's no reason to ever
say we have all the answers, we know
what's going on, we know what to do.
Like, if we're still in the
universe, if we're still here not
escaping the inevitable heat
death of it, then, like, we will
die out unless we have found that way.
There's a final boss to be defeated, for sure, still.
And even if it might not even be the
final boss, like, it's the last one we know
about, you know, maybe when we get out.
Right. We don't know how it
could be turtles all the way down, but, like,
until we have escaped entropy,
we have no reason to stop
because otherwise, like, we will die.
Like, eventually.
Agreed. I love that expression
trilogy all the way down. It's like, I don't
remember who told me, like,
recently, I've been recently hearing that
there was a story written by
Terry Pratchett.
Yeah.
Terry Pratchett was who I was written by.
Gib says to Terry Pratchett
Discworld.
But the story was specifically that
he was doing a talk explaining the origin
of the world and how it functioned
stuff, and then afterward, a woman comes
up to him, at least, this is the story
of the story.
I don't remember if it was with you guys
or with Biter.
Or afterward, a woman comes up to him.
At least, this is the story that I've heard.
And says, like, excuse me, I appreciate the talk,
but I want to let you know you've been wrong
about everything. The entire world is, in fact,
on the back of a turtle.
No, no, but that doesn't make any sense.
Why would he be giving a talk about...
I'm reading it. I don't know.
No, I'm reading it right now on Wikipedia.
Turtles all the way down is an expression
of the problem of infinite regress.
The saying eludes the mythological idea of a world turtle
that supports the earth on its back.
It's an even larger turtle, which itself
is part of a column of increasingly large
turtles that continues indefinitely.
It's literally what I'm talking about.
It says the origin of the phrases on
Sir. The world turtle also referred to
as the cosmic turtle. The word bearing turtle
is a mythime, myth theme,
that seems to be the word myth and meme
combined, similar
to that of the world elephants,
encouraged in Hindu mythology,
Chinese mythology, and mythologies of indigenous
people of the Americas.
So I guess it's just come up
in a lot of different cultures.
Many 20th century
attribution claim William James is the source
of the phrase. James referred to the fable
of the elephant and tortoise several times,
but told the infinite regress story with rocks
all the way down in his 1882
essay, Rationality, Activity, and Faith.
I didn't even realize that this phrase
actually was about the thing I was
actually talking about.
I had no idea it was so specifically about it.
What did you think it meant?
I just thought... It sounds pretty abstract.
Yeah, I didn't realize
it was literally about the idea
that the world is resting on top
of a bigger world and all that.
Yes? Stephen Hawking
Stephen Hawking wrote
the story about the old woman
in his 1988 book, A Brief History of Time,
so that might
have popularized. That's probably the story I was trying to...
Okay, and this is weird.
In his telling of
the parable of the old woman
saying turtles all the way down,
he says that some say
that it was Bertrand Russell who the old
woman said it to, but that's
very wishy-washy.
Why would he say that?
Maybe he thought this was a real story,
and maybe it is a real story?
Okay, wait, we're splitting hairs.
It's all bullshit.
It's turtles all the way down, dude.
I really love that expression, though.
The mental image I get
is adorable, honestly.
It's a lot of turtles.
I've always just pictured the Ninja Turtles
on each other's backs.
What is scary
phrase all the way down?
But to where?
I just mentioned that.
I'll stack up like these adventure
time-esque-style turtles
with these really simple faces.
It's just adorable little turtles.
I've heard the phrase, I think
in philosophy class, there was the phrase
bugs all the way down, which is not
really about the
what the Earth is resting on.
It's about matter.
It's the idea that matter is infinitely
reducible, that you've got cells,
and then cells are made of molecules, and atoms.
And then it's like, oh, Adam's quarks,
quarks, gluons, and then
smaller and smaller things they're
divisible into.
Is it fair to think of the Procrastinators
as a science fiction podcast?
Sometimes, sure.
We get into futurism talk every episode,
like, that's science facts.
That's true.
Hey, Ben, I'm re-watching No Game, No Life,
and it's awesome.
Yeah, explain to me.
The part about the sun.
Yeah, tell me.
Or the part about the strong.
No, the electromagnetic force, the strong force.
Okay, so I've got the columns force
is what we're talking about.
In No Game, the color force.
Columns force, columns force.
Oh, Coulombs, the Coulombs force.
Yeah, Coulombs law, yeah.
Okay, what is this? Please explain.
So, okay, in No Game, No Life,
episode 6.
There's this part, or maybe 5.
No, it's episode 6. There's a part with the main character
and this...
I guess I'll describe her as like an angel.
She's like an all-over.
A very powerful being.
She creates this simulated world
where they're playing a game of sherry-tory
where every time
one person says a word,
that thing will come into existence
and then the next person says a word
and whatever they say disappears from existence.
And so they go back and forth
creating and destroying
either physical objects or concepts.
And the idea is that
the main character,
because he knows words from...
because it's an Isekai show and he knows
words from our world that the person
he's talking to doesn't know what they mean
and she just kind of ignores the words
that she doesn't know what they mean.
Like he summons an atom bomb.
The first thing he does is summon an atomic bomb
and that's what causes her to
put them inside of a force field kind of situation
where basically anything can happen.
They can die in this game
but it'll all be fine.
So what he does is
he removes the crust of the earth
and the mantle
and everything but the core
before eventually removing the lithosphere
and when he does that they start free-falling
towards the center of the earth.
But as they're falling it's like
who will fall faster
and die first and they keep removing concepts
and eventually he removes
Coulomb's force from the universe.
Coulomb's force.
It's the electromagnetic force.
And I guess essentially
what Coulomb's force is is that
well I mean if you look it up on Wikipedia
it's called Coulomb's force.
Or Coulomb's law.
Guys what the hell is this?
Explain it.
It's a force that is holding things
in place I guess
like without it
everything just collapses in on itself
and becomes a supernova I guess.
Yeah it's electromagnetic.
So does he immediately die when he does this?
That's what holds atoms together.
What happens is he does that and then everything
starts getting like more rapidly sucked
into the sun and because
the person he's fighting is falling
is closer to it than he is
she dies first.
What exactly happens when he removes Coulomb's law?
I forget.
It just all super collapses.
The whole universe folds in on itself basically.
Does the sun collapse into a black hole or something?
Yeah well okay and that's true
that's cool and that would happen.
The thing that bothers me though is that their bodies
would have just ceased to exist.
I thought when I was watching the scene
as soon as the Earth's lithosphere
disappeared I thought well
wouldn't they just die right here
instantly?
Yeah they'd be in the vacuum of space.
The way the scene progresses is awesome
but you have to make certain exceptions.
It is awesome but there's no
getting around the fact that if the
electromagnetic force were just gone
then all the atoms in your body would just fly
apart. Maybe they're protected because
they're in this force field? Maybe it didn't affect them?
I don't know.
That's the reason I brought it up because
I had heard Ben talk about how
simultaneously this scene is why
he loved the show but also that
he had a bunch of problems with it.
That's why I wanted to run it by him again.
I really like the show but I also hate the show.
What do you hate about it?
I love everything about the show.
I really like the idea behind the
concepts and the whole game shtick
but the thing is with the games
they sort of like
in a way I do like that they make up the rules
as they go but at the same time there's no
bases.
They just pull stuff out of their ass
that was the best game.
That was my favorite.
The thing about the games in the show
is that
all of them have
rules that can just be exploited
in ways that
make them more complicated than
a simple game would be.
For instance in the first arc they're playing a game of chess
but the idea is that
the pieces have a will of their own
so as long as you communicate with the pieces
and you can inspire them
they basically just do anything.
They don't have to move on the board
the way that you instruct them to.
I like the whole idea and the concepts
and stuff like that. It's been a while since I watched it
so this is just an impression that's lasting
so I could be wrong.
I like that.
I like those sort of things
but
it's kind of like
the you you heart of the card sort of
bullshit sometimes.
With the heart of the cards
it's like
he literally just gets the luck of the draw
he just believes in himself a lot
and gets the right card.
It's a little hard to put it into words
because I like the sort of
randomness at the same time
it could be
a bit smarter
and work within the rules it established.
I don't think it ever breaks its own rules.
I don't agree.
I don't think there is any
that the chess solution breaks any of the rules.
I'm not talking about the chess
specifically. It started well
and I think it just sort of
I don't remember. I think it escalated a bit.
I don't know.
Please make it your anime suck.
No game. I need to re-watch it.
It was a long time ago.
I'm in the process of watching it
so I know exactly
what happens and how I can defend it all
because a major
a big part of the theme of the show
how they win all their games
is just by understanding that
in a deterministic universe
everything has a logic behind it.
You can always analyze
there is no such thing as luck.
There's no such thing as pure chance
because there's always reasons
that things would happen the way they do.
Just like how you can count cards
to cheat the odds in Blackjack.
Used as an example
of a basic way that
as long as you can predict probabilities
the idea of
the metaphor of the
No Game No Life universe is that
it's just the exact same as real life
except that people are beholden to
these certain rules
that basically
the rules that already
apply in the real world
except that people have to follow them
there's just certain things
you cannot kill people in this world
because God himself has written a rule
that you can't kill people
forced to not do the thing
Right. So like whereas in the real world
people can act against their
best interest and even if
everyone plays the game correctly
someone can just kill you
in this world you can't
so like if you can play
the game the best you will win
like is the way the world works
and so that's why the main characters
are taken there because they are the best at games
and whereas in the real world
that does not help them because they are
just two relatively powerless
average Japanese teens
by going to a world where being the best
at games means you are God
they can be God
is essentially what the show is about
One more thing I have an issue with it
and this one I know
you won't be able to change my mind no matter what
but this is a matter
of taste so I'm
willing to accept it but I really dislike how
I don't mind
fan service a lot of the time
but in this show
I hate how they sort of
stop the flow
of the story just to have the scenes
with those fan services and it's very
very obnoxious
the fan services
is part of the message to me
I think it's a big... I'm writing a video
I'm writing a huge video about No Game No Life
so I'll talk about all of this
but I think
the fan service is important to
what the message of the show is
I won't get into it
I'll save it for my video
let's save all of this for another time when I'm not here
let's do all of that
that sounds great
let's go to questions for Christ's sake please
no
I want to talk about that I got really drunk last night
in my discord
in Ben St's Hellfire hand
I had a fucking bone to dig deep in
and we got really drunk
and I vommed
and I puked for the first time and forever
I don't remember going to bed
but I just remember being over my toilet
forcing myself to puke
which is something that I never ever do
and it was great
and I feel wonderful this morning
well that's good
and you know what the best part is
a little bird told me
wait no it's not
it is there's no carbs in it
that's horseshit there's like
because alcohol itself
the chemical alcohol
it has calories
but it doesn't have it's not carbs
oh really?
Ben
I understand that you have a
homestuck book club going on
in your server would you like to explain
to the class
oh yeah
I do not have a homestuck book club
but there is a homestuck book club
I'm just endorsing it
monetarily and spiritually
you'll be hearing from our lawyer Ben
you'll be hearing quite
an earful
look
I just think anything
my ownership of
reading homestuck will not be
besmirched
that ever was written or ever will be written
and that is homestuck and I think that that can only be
a good thing and I support it wholeheartedly
whenever you go to homestuck.com
there's a prompt to PayPal me
for the pleasure of reading homestuck
and you will
kowtow to my demands
immediately
yeah
what's much for you
yeah shout out to
shout out to the homestuck book club
shout out to my lawyer
god Mclaugh
hellfire boys
let's go to the questions
yeah I can't wait
before the questions
about the contest thing maybe mentioned to people
oh right thanks for reminding me
alright guys so you know
you'll be hearing this a week since the last episode
which was the final deadline closing
for the PCP theme contest
so just to review
it's closed, it's done, you're finished everyone
it's over for you
we are planning to have
the announcement as to the winner next episode
so one week from today
you should be hearing who the new
PCP theme will be
and it'll be glorious, it'll be grand
and we'll probably announce
I think we do like a top 3 announcement
and then we'll just be like
one is but a bang
and that'll be that, yeah it'll be fine
we'll make it fine, we'll make it real fine
don't worry guys it won't suck like everything else
right off the top I got a question I can just answer
real quick because this person
Vale asked with the formless format
seemingly being here to stay is there a PCP topic
that you would have wanted to do a PCP-centric episode on
guys the topics are not
gone
the goal conceit here is that
we were making up topics
just for the sake of having a topic
because we almost never have
a natural topic for the show
so if we ever had a topic
we had an idea for we would just do that
topic immediately
that's gonna be it
so no need to fear whenever there's something real important
we wanna talk about we will
I have a pity question here
it's from Alex Siebel
on Twitter who was one of the contest
one of the submitted us
one of our two songs I think for the contest
he asks
how was pokemon go community day for y'all
I personally was sad about playing alone
but got 15 shinies so that's cool
also to randoms going through the hashtag
for some reason my trainer code is
652622648067
I know you won't read it on the show
fuck you Alex
there you go
anyway I wanted to read it
and it was lame it was suck
it was suck
you got like 15 eebies didn't you
and then I just saw Eevee over and over again
there's no special move
for the eeveelutions
yeah there was
yeah there is last resort
well ok but Gib is reporting that he met real
locals families
it was sick he got a register
I got a register as well
just the word community
I don't have one
he would endorse that Nazi
I don't care about any of the shinies
I don't care about Eevee
I don't care about the shinies either
I still need an umbrella and an espion
I was glad to do it because when they release
gen 4 there's going to be two new eeveelutions
and it's going to be hard to get them
so now I've got enough candies that I can get that leafeon
and glaceon
I missed it because I don't understand how event days work
and how they're
I missed it because I understand everything
I didn't know it was like a 3 hour window
bullshit
it's going on right now
is it too late? can I go?
no it's going on to 5pm today
I'm probably going to do it right after
I must away
actually I had
so I was walking around
and it was like 5 minutes before the end
and I was catching
there was a cluster of eevees
oh I got a magmar and a ray
I got my first magmar
that's cool
I'm standing on the corner
I'm on the campus of Tufts University
and this guy
he sees me playing
and he's a very
autistic looking gentleman
and he sees me
and we just kind of nodded each other
and it's raining and he kind of comes over
and he's like can I borrow your umbrella
and so I was like yeah sure
so it was like alright here you go
so we stayed dry for a minute caught the last eevees
and we were just shooting the shit for a second
and he was like oh there's a machamp
there's a machamp raid over there
but it's only 4 minutes left
and I was like oh shit we can make it
so we ran over to this machamp
we fought this machamp raid, got him a champ
it had a terrible moveset, whatever
and then we just bummed around
and tried trading
we traded eridactyls with each other
we got lucky eridactyls
oh is that a thing?
yeah yeah
it's cheaper to boost
it's not a thing necessarily of higher eevees
because we did a bunch of couple
well maybe it does I don't know
okay fine
shut up
and then we
yep so I got a lucky eridactyl
and that was my community day
one fun thing that actually didn't happen
is I was walking down
down bubble
and then
being the cleanly man that I do
the saint of
prestige
there was a homeless woman
there was a frankly disgusting
dirty pig pin
garbage pail kid of a woman
with her husband
her groveling husband
and her pukestane children
and she came up to me
and she held on tightly to my shirt
and she begged me she got on all fours
she got on all eights
fine little legs
she's a succubus she's a spider
and she asked me she begged me
please please can we please trade
rare pokemon
she begged me for rare pokemon
and I had to capitulate
and so I gave this family
this wife I gave this wife
a Mr. Mime
named Mr. Meme
she gave me an unknown
and after that she was satiated
and she went off to pawn off
to steal another person's rare pokemon
I think you got the short end
of the stick in that trade
but I mean
also by the way in case you couldn't tell
a woman asking if she wanted to trade
the other day and that's what happened
so here's a light hearted
question that everyone is sure to have
straightforward opinion on
Pato today asked what do you think of abortion
good
oh it's great
pretty all four
in any context
it's acceptable
cool
prove to me that that baby's life matters
because I don't think it does
that's where I objectively truly stick
I mean I don't think that it's sentient
and is worthy of moral consideration
and so I'm fine with it being destroyed
that's how I feel
next question
if you died and had a charity foundation
created in your name
wait what did mage say? I'm curious about her opinion
I said I didn't even get the answer
but my opinion is
I guess yeah
with uncertain circumstances
that's fine
all circumstances
a certain point it becomes
more of a sentient being
and that's no
I've heard stories
horror stories of women getting pregnant
just so they can do abortions
what?
I think
there were like
some like
nutcase ratfemme sort of people
yeah
that's fucking
I'm surprised I had never conceived of that
but I'm not I guess I shouldn't be
surprised anyway
if you died and had a charity foundation
created in your name what would you have them do
terrorism
oh
plain and simple terrorism
a charity foundation
I would create
they would be a nonprofit
museum and they would only
show art made on the internet
from people ages like
8 to 17
okay listen that's fine
that's good but mine is the most important one
and it will save society
my charity foundation would be
help nerds get laid
and what it would be
and it would do everything in its power
to see that young men were quick
to seduce sexy young women
women are fine they don't have to worry about it
it's fine they can fuck anyone
don't worry about it
so they would be dating education
that's exactly what it would be
my charity would probably be for like
animal shelters
that's a good one
yeah because
I don't like that
all I gotta say about animals is
when we leave the universe
when we escape entropy
why are we not taking animals
they didn't earn it
because there aren't
they aren't a sin to you
do you think they would take us
I don't care about what they
would take us
I want to see elephants
I'm gonna take the elephants
we can fit them in
we can create new elements
we can just invent better
elephants later
we can just test to create
cooler elephants
I don't want to go there
let's move on
you're typing a lot of things
if you want to join in just start recording
that's fine dude you ain't getting paid
but you can contribute
alright
I had a question I liked this one a lot
it was just at Gergerad
what was your first experience
with being a depraved individual
um
I love that I like that one a lot
define depraved individual
I think it's kind of a personal question
yeah when I turned on that fabled game
Undertale I knew
does he mean like when did you realize
you were a depraved person
I mean he said what was your experience
with being a depraved
the first like the start
of your slide into depravity
was the first time I ever fucked an inanimate object
I knew
I mean honestly that's also my example
that's also my example
it's that weird time that I weirdly figured out
how to masturbate in the back of
the minivan
at the end of a soccer game
it was extremely freakish
it was just when I learned what masturbating was
that's what it was
yeah it was really gross
what's weird about that
I don't fuck my club
I mean like we're
I was in public technically
if that is not depraved
like do any of us actually do anything
that is depraved
like obviously none of us are depraved by our own standards
like if we're all like
comfortable with ourselves and what we do
like I stole like a candy bar
probably at one point in my life from somewhere
like I probably did that I stole a donut from
stop and shop once years ago
I guess that's depraved
I got pregnant just to have an abortion
okay that's depraved
that's what I would think of as depraved
and I haven't done anything like that
so yeah I don't think I have either
sorry sorry
oh you know what no
I have a much better example
it's the time that I made Victor put his face in the toilet
oh no
what the fuck
that is depraved
because growing up I just tortured Victor
by making him do things
because he's very easy to emotionally
and so like
I probably just like
I probably told him something
we used to fight all the time about who would do the dishes
because like my dad would always get mad
that the dishes weren't done when he got home
and but neither of us ever wanted to do it
and we would try to like cycle between us
and like have a chore chart and everything
but neither of us would do it so we would just fight
for like an entire hour and not end up doing it
before he got home usually what would happen
is he would get home and one of us would feel guilty
and start doing it right then
and usually it was him because he was more guilty than me
so what I would do is I would just manipulate him
by constantly being like oh you're gonna let dad down
like oh dad's gonna be so upset
he'd be like well why don't you care
I'm like I don't care you care
so you do it
and then I think at one time we struck some kind of deal
where I was just like yeah I'll do the dishes
if you fucking put your face in the toilet
and like you know gotta do that
yeah probably not
oh
we had these fights like every night for years
like over who would do
like ex chore
because we were just both
so lazy and like
we would get into physical altercations
over it you know
yeah this is not a hard thing but I understand the sentiment well
I felt it as well
the very very
sorry go ahead
the most depraved thing that I can think of
is a spotty memory I have
when I was like 12 I think
where I
was in my airplane I was flying towards the
world trade centers to blow them up
are you in an airplane right now
someone made you talk
so my auto can be deleted
and then I'll go after you
you sound like an airplane
okay okay yeah okay so like
I think the question was like what's the first
or something like that depravity
first experience with being a depraved
the first thing I remember
that I would like
considered being wrong but I just didn't give a damn
was like I was like 7
or maybe 6 or something
like that in that ballpark so like
me and this girl
we were like playing
and she had like a lot of cool toys and one
of the cool toys was like a miniature little
zebra toy and it was like
sort of accurate realistic it wasn't like you know
cutesy stylish or whatever it was
realistic and I was all about I'm still
all about those miniature little animal
toys that are look realistic
it's just I was my thing
and I loved it so much and
okay and
then like few days later
I was walking back
home and I saw on the ground
that little zebra toy
and it was just laying on the ground I picked it up
I was like oh it belongs to her I should return
it and then I sort of like
paused and I thought
you know if she didn't care enough to take care
of you she doesn't deserve you
so I kept it
good logic I would have done the same thing
I might actually
still have it though probably not
actually you know what
I would have done the same thing for the same reason
there was that time that I
kicked Ben in the stomach for literally no reason
because I wanted to see him suffer that's what I wanted
you like drop kicked me
we were lying weirdly I know I've told this before
we're like we're just lying like
heads on opposite sides of the couch
and I just lifted my foot and just dropped it
directly into Ben's stomach for no
reason because I felt
like watching a man ride in agony
that's what I felt like doing in that moment
I felt the moment
I regret it intensely
the time I felt the most depraved
is Ben you witnessed this
I was thinking of this on the show before
when I abstained
from drinking soda for like several months
and then when I was in Georgia
at a wing stop
this was like the most
impulse thing I didn't have no control
over my body in this scenario
I was just putting like I was putting my cup
in the trash and like within
the span of like two seconds I had
like jerked my hand from
the trash can I had stuffed my
because the trash can was right next to like the soft
you know soft drink like pour your thing
I had stuffed it in like a Fanta
orange soda I had
poured one sip I had swigged that one sip
and then I had slammed the cup into the trash
as hard as I possibly could
and then I walked out thinking like what did I just do
was that a dream and like am I awake right now
like was I in control like did I actually just do that
it was like
it was like my burger dream
and I walked out
and you were like hey what were you doing
I was just like I've done something terrible
I've sinned
I remember you broke your ass
I'm back on that by the way right now
I've been going for like a month
you threw it all away
Kaze told us that you guys were trying to like
be health boys
that's a way to do it man
no I'll never do that
hey by the way post foods going strong
it's going well
I'm drinking it right now
what is post food again
well I'm drinking this this lovely concoction
called huel
it's like uh it's like uh soylent
the show is turning into a fucking huel ad
week by week I just love huel
what does it taste like
tell me because it mostly just tastes like oats
it tastes like like an oats puree
it's not it's not bad
strawberry oats
paradox crocs asks
what is the thing that's changed about you most
in the last two or three years
post food baby
I'm on that huel train everyday
I would say
my answer is uh
caring less and less about myself
and more about other people
like just just gradually losing
interest in myself and in like
and like
I feel like I spent I had so much focus
on the idea that like no one had understood
the true me and like
now not only do I feel like
people are close enough that I don't that it's
fine but also just that like the true
me is not that interesting and that
like you know it's like
it's like it only needed to be like it needed to be
glimpsed as long as
somebody saw it and understood it that was all that
mattered it wasn't like I had to perform it all the
time it's not like the things I was doing
were so genius that like I had to
like my unique art had
to be out there in the world it's just like as long as
someone got it that it was all
down that Asian obliteration
the self for like the past year
I know it's been
great it's kind of my whole identity
now it's the east
I mean I've been I've
considered myself like a Taoist ever since
I was like 14 so like
I've been on this path
you know I've been on the Alan Watts
mind train for like
the last decade but
basically I am
lo-fi hip-hop is what I'm trying to say
I'd say for me
the biggest change
started with my resolution
to like do me a math of a stuff
it's a redoubling of
my efforts to actually succeed
in a business and like
economic and like actual life sustaining way
at like
YouTube stuff that's been that was a pretty
big change like decided to me a math
which was inspired by a lot of people
but yeah I mean like that and the whole
we Agua stuff and the way I'm
constantly I'm really focusing on trying
to recajigger my life so I can actually
make it
I don't know if you can accurately
tell what has changed about
you or maybe I'm just not self aware
to do so but
yeah it's hard
to say what what what have I
much I'll tell you what I think has changed
about you because like I mean
when when I at
the second or third brony con we were at
like you were so out
of control that I
felt the need to keep more distance
from you because of the
fact that I thought like if I have him around
all the time it will be very exhausting
and about a year later you had changed
enough and like matured enough
that I no longer felt that way and that's why
I wanted you in the PCP
so I would say that you've just become somebody
who's figured out that
if you scare people away
then they will
you know like if you try to just be
constantly freak flag flying
like oppressing people with your presence
then they will not want you around
and you have decided to care about that
the way I would feel like this is
you can scare someone in an instant
you can scare someone in about
like 0.8 seconds
it takes no effort at all to scare people
but to terrify someone you have to sink
your claws then that's the long
game if I want to terrify you guys
it's going to be a two or three years
at least
I was glad
I'm glad that's the
and I'm Keto now
that's all that's changed
for me it's like
if I want to shine in a positive light
I guess I could say like
I'm more about defining
the boundaries between me and people
but if I wanted to be either honest
or in a more negative light I think I've become
paranoid not too much
but like a few years ago
back in the pony days I would be like
oh everyone's my friend hello everyone
I shall call you friend but then
I realized the sort of
like the amount of
sort of pressure and weight the word
friend really has
and I sort of stopped
calling every single person I've talked
to once or twice a friend
because like
when you call someone a friend so
easily
I still have a bad habit of sort of like
people like really clicked
and I talk to them like once or twice
but we really click I sort of end up calling
them a friend that's
you gotta get into the word buddy
I do a lot of like
if you listen to my videos you hear a lot of me like dodging
like I'll say things like friend of the show
or my buddy or our pal
or things like that like I really want
to be protective of like the word friend
because people do put a lot of power on it
and when you start calling someone your friend publicly
then they are going to like latch on to that
and be like oh I am this person's friend
and like I suppose
pragmatically other people may then
hitch your wagon to theirs if let's say
this person does some things that you don't
approve of I mean yeah I usually
call people acquaintances or
friendos like friendos is
my catch all for like everyone
sort of like interact with
friendlet they're all friendlets to me
you're all
you're all mere friendlets before me
I don't know if this is the biggest change in my life
per se but this is definitely a change that I've noticed
where I've shifted away
I don't know if like I don't think these are like
mutually exclusive but I've definitely
moved away from
wanting to be friends with funny people
to be friends with smart people
I definitely value being
you know smart more than I value being funny
at this point I think
it reminds me of that highly intellectual
comedy thing that Bobby
Hill was learning in that one episode
of King of the Hill
Tartuffe
the spry wonder dog
I think I want to be friends
with funny people and smart people
but I would be friends with someone who was smart
but not funny but if someone was
funny but fucking stupid
I don't think I'd want to be their friend
I think wit takes a certain kind of
funny if they like to like
give people wedgies for example
and laugh at that
if they open fire
in public places
then I think that would be pretty funny
it would take a certain amount of emotional intelligence
I think that humor is
subjective and I think like
I value
a sense of humor
what's the word
a sense of humor that we share
I don't remember the proper word for it
but like if we can share a similar
something like that
if we share the sense of humor
I really value that because if you can have
a good time and a good laugh with a person
it's a lot easier to get along with them
and understand them and that's very
important in any sort of relationship
to be able to share the sense of humor
because when you talk to someone
someone cracks a joke and you don't understand it
it's very easy to take offense
and start seeing the person in a very
different sort of negative light
you might find them obnoxious, annoying
and that can build up to negative emotions
that's fair
this reminds me of a classic line
from one Sam Hyde
it's from some very popular
YouTube video called like
Sam Hyde gives great life advice
and Sam Hyde says
I'm friends with stupid people
with smart people, with assholes
with really nice people
because you can be friends with all of them
in different ways but it's when those people
become vacuums in your life
in whatever way
when they start to like drain life from you
in whatever way they happen to do so
that's when you know it's like
this person is not going to work out long
and you don't make a big stink about it
you don't write them a big letter
like dude, I think we're really fucked up
what you did, I'm not going to hang out with you anymore
you simply slowly let these relationships
fade in time
especially younger people think of a friend
as like someone who you want to spend all of your time with
and like for me
I think that you can have categories of friends
who are like this is my friend
for when I'm doing this
that's what, when you look at like
for instance, you might have
someone like a hiking buddy
this is a guy who I don't really have anything in common with
other than we both like hiking
but when I want to go hiking
with someone, this is my guy
because like the two of us
it's not simply a matter of you both like it
but that you engage with it the same way
like maybe you have other friends
who would love to go hiking with you
but they're not going to take it seriously
or they're not going to have the
they're not going to try to reach the top
or they're not going to be as efficient
and so you want to go hiking with this guy who hikes
like you hike
and so even if you have nothing else in common
it's like you can still think of him as
your hiking buddy
it's funny, I'm watching May play Persona 3
is about
the different categories of relationships
that you have and how they, you know
because you have different personas
no person is just one identity
you have different things you care about
that you can have people
different folks for different strokes
exactly, that's a perfect phrase
there you go
well, it's a little reversed but fair enough
what she said made sense
in this context
different, yeah
whatever, it doesn't matter
are we done? I think we're done guys
May, did you want to comment?
no, no, no, this is fine
I'm good, I'm fucking great
I got nothing else to say to any of you freaks
yeah, that's right, I gotta go hang out with my
good friends
the procrastinators
that's us people, five dollars bonus episodes
listen to Monsters 2 everybody
I'm gonna want to get it on that
go buy an I Am Games t-shirt
we have a spray shirt already
um
yeah, yeah
do all those things follow us
hey guys, I'm sorry
I'm late, where's my paycheck
where's my paycheck
can I have my money
yeah, you get all the money
you get a double share this time
hippo
oh yes
alright, thanks for listening everybody
we'll see you next episode
bye bye
see you next time
I am a stupid
I got a deadline
don't want to do it