Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. Thank you for
cheering for me because I am the best guy ever and I deserve your applause and love. Joining
us today, we have The Davoo. Mmm, these cookies! I gotta get the recipe from Liz. We have Tom
Oliver. I'm hungry for a good episode. Damn. Meet up y'all. You're starving, you're starving
friend. I've been waiting since, I've been waiting a hundred and nine episodes and we
still haven't gotten one yet. But I believe, but I believe we can deliver. Hippocrit is
here. That's what sounds like when I'm hooking up some stuff. Ben Saint is here. Oh no, my blood
sugar. Get it, get it out. Get it out of me. Get the sugar out of my blood. No blood sugar
please. And we've got Munchy. Yo, I just cooked some eggs right before this podcast and I've
got one singular yolk here. All pristine and shit. I'm about to shove it into my fat,
gapy mouth. Let's go. I have one too. I'm gonna eat it. Oh, that's good. I just cooked up a monster
absolutely zero energy in a chemical bath. I'm currently drinking a coffee. It tastes like a
fresh diaper. I've got a juice monster energy drink. Pipeline punch right now. I'm gonna fucking
drown this and hopefully my tongue seared off and I can't speak anymore. Let's all hope that
happens. While we introduce our final special guest, longtime LGBTQ ally of the PCP, his name,
Icon Clasm, aka Double Shot. Icon Colts. I remember because I did fan art and never
showed anyone. Oh, wow. Not even Victor. That's the man. And that's the man, Victor. Victor Collins.
Here he is, everybody. Oh man. I just ate a big hot dog from 7-Eleven and washed it down with
Mountain Dew and now I feel like I'm gonna vomit. You're in the 7-Eleven food. You unerotically
eat 7-Eleven food. That's a thing in your life. Yeah, I mean, that's true. Victor. Almost every
day. And it's horrible. Your last name was Collins? I thought your last name was Brough.
Oh, because of... You gotta go to 7-Eleven and you gotta get a fucking buffalo chicken log.
Oh, those are good. I like those. Oh, no. Buffalo chicken roller log, dude.
Yeah, I like those. It's a very fun name. I do those for a little while and then...
I mean, yeah, they all make me sick. Topic, ladies and gentlemen, get the fuck out of my
kitchen. You're undercooking the chicken. It's cooking. You're just like your father.
We're talking about cooking, talking about po-boy and rich boy eats alike. They all have a place
in our lexicon of food. And speaking of lexicons that has nothing to do with what I'm saying,
also let's look at Urban Dictionary and see what the fuck is going on with cooking. Here we go.
Hang on. Silly me. I searched cocking by mistake, which is texting while urinating.
Okay, cooking. Here we go.
Cooking is a dance trend invented by Lil B in that it's only waste up designed to be
done in front of a webcam. Wait, incorrect, incorrect. I don't know anything about this
topic. I'm out. Cooking. Okay, cooking. This is a good one.
Cooking, what you better be doing right now, woman.
Damn. Oh, that one was funny. Okay, cooking. In reference to wannabe comedian, Dane Cook. No, okay.
It's when you put the food in the pan and it sizzles. That's what cooking is, when you eat food.
You know, what if you're not using a pan, though? I mean, that's true.
Then that's cold. It's not real cooking, obviously.
I suspect we are going to spend easily 45 minutes talking about what is or is not
nobody's cooking. Let's not. It's making a sandwich cooking, please.
No, cooking literally is the act of heating something like raw ingredients to make it meal.
But so temperature being involved. But here's a question, and I said this to Vic beforehand.
If I make ice cream, if I make ice cream, when I'm using temperature to create it in the negative,
the opposite direction is that cooking? No. Why? A cooker is a heating implement.
No, no, no, no. It's possible that for one podcast, we can like not open it with like
an excessive. No, no, actually, let's open the scanner worms. No, no, no. Here's why it opened.
Famously, I am responsible in Ben's legendary sandwich debates. I am legendary quoted as saying
that the American flag is a sandwich, which I stand by. Why? Because like the lines?
Okay, no, no, because there are layers on the American flag, which are the 13 stripes.
By that definition. Okay, on the bottom there's a red strip, on the top of the red strip, and
the middle there are white stripes. Here's Munchy. Munchy. Munchy, famously,
onions are known to have layers. Does that make an onion a sandwich as well?
No, no, because there's not, okay, there's not similar layers on the top or the bottom.
Look, look, look. My final word on the sandwich debate is that artist intent, artist intent
matters when it comes to a sandwich debate. I am definitely an author. I'm definitely an author.
No! A sandwich has to be deliberately assembled for the purpose of being eaten. That is why
the American flag certainly was. If the author died, you'd go hungry. Betsy Ross, Betsy Ross,
just put those stripes on there. Famous sandwich, it could tear. Yeah, yeah, yeah, James Ross was
like, hey hey, babe, can you give me a beer. I want to watch the game, and she came back
here with the American flag, and she's like, wow this is really good. You need to watch the game
before games were even invented. Okay, so one American revolution. Let's not have, let's not
have Nate make us a one-hour debate about the definition of food. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I almost said that. Okay, here's here's what I think, I think that cooking, okay, I think that
making ice cream is cooking. I think that cooking is cooking is the act of, of creating food.
But there has to be like chemical chemical processes need to be involved like what if I make what about what about like making
Sushi, you know. Yeah sushi like sushi is pretty interrelated pretty elaborate. I like not anyone
I've got a button here. I think it might just be a British thing English thing
But like ovens like the other word for an oven is a cooker that which is where the word cooking
From the right that's not where the word comes from I would argue
Fucking comes from no, no, I'll kill everyone
Well, this is not important. She has rice and the rice has to be yeah, the rice
I have the best definition of cooking cooking is
Preparing food to an extent that if you don't like it, you'll procrastinate on it or try to get someone else to do it
That's not bad. Like so sushi inquires requires cooked rice
What about a salad making like a complicated salad with lots of stuff, okay?
No, no, no funny joke to like pretend that we're doing it again and be like
I'm interested in this the sandwich debate is
Go on like a salad becomes cooking if you are like like if you cook grilled chicken and put that in the salad
Well, of course, of course, then it's cooking
But otherwise it's not cooking
I feel like I could look I could work really long and hard on a complicated decadent salad
But that doesn't involve any heat being used. I feel like heat is the main
Because if you say if you say like oh, I'm gonna go cook
You know, I'm gonna go cook like this chicken or whatever
But you say I'm going to go make a salad because a salad does not
That's generally true. Hey, I see give a poster the definition of cook
I assume it's from like the actual dictionary.com the actual dictionary.com
The definition is just a prepare by mixing combining and heating the ingredients
But you can heat negatively by making
Utilitarianism
Totally count is a negative number a number
I haven't say
Probably about 300 episodes will probably be able to become like our own like court system because we'll have like legal
Fucking everything by the way, I have Nate's other thing. He's gonna say I'll just like undercut him here
Hey guys wouldn't be much better in Star Trek where you just push a button and food gets made for you
Didn't we have to spend any time cooking
And food is full there's literally no fuel to talk about this because just food is fuel and just get like energy bars
Yeah, exactly. I mean well sort of just get so I'll be the soy boy. You want to see in the world. That's my motto
But anyway, all right, I think we're past all that bullshit. Finally, we're never gonna be pasta
Yeah speaking of dead fish I think if if you say cook in a context and it sounds retarded then that's not cooking like you don't say
I'm gonna go cook a salad or I'm gonna go cook ice
Victor the voice of reason
We can't define it, but we know what when we see it
Everything I prefer I prefer to turn my strow in the kitchen
I like refer to it
Let's bust open this legendary debate that was I was first introduced to in a full episode of full metal alchemist when Winery and that stupid
Book girl were arguing is cooking a science or an art. It is an art. It's an art. It's a fucking art
Dude, what do you wait? It's a cold calculated meticulous sociopathic
When you're ripping up shit that no one thought of
Fucking literally painting is also a science. You know how to mix the code. I mean, that's true
I know I remember extra credits their old episodes
They would say that video gaming is a game design is an alchemy because it's a mixture between science and art
So you know
What the fuck is they just made that shit up
I just want to get
You know, you know like Leonardo da Vinci known alchemist because they did both science and art Wow
Yeah, all right. All right, you know, I always I hate this argument because you can kind of apply it to anything
That's true. If you decide to proceed. It's really like it's kind of like artistic intent, right?
Mm-hmm. It's like are you intending to make a dish that is new and is your art and you're assembling it and it's beautiful
Do you work at yeah, Arby's and you're just assembling a sandwich? Yeah, someone that it's not
And science is more of a mindset in its creation rather than the end result, but you can usually yeah
Yeah, so for example, if it's like, hmm, what do I like on my spaghetti the most and so like today
I try you know tomato sauce next day
I try Alfredo next day I try putting hamburger in next day
I try putting chicken in and I take notes about exactly how much I liked each thing and then I collect the data and make my best
Decisions from there that science. Well, that's I mean, all right
I want to severely destroy this
Result is if the if the only data you know acting is how much do I like it like that's not science
This episode being a real name guys, what is your favorite food that you can cook?
Sausage and eggs bird's nest which is an a which is a bread that you pull the center out of and you cook an egg
Inside the bread and then you eat it that way cheese. You scrambled eggs
Make would be like a big old slab of chicken with like on a bagel with like cheese wait wait something like that with
Maybe an egg or something
That's good. I also want to change my answer though
ice cream
You make ice cream hot damn. I have I have
This is not the food podcast, this is the cooking podcast so all the question left it and cooking good
My I like making omelettes. I make a mean omelette. I enjoy yeah the alchemy of of combining ingredients with the egg to make
The omelette alchemist
Anything is a sandwich because it's sandwiched when you eat it between the top and the bottom halves of your mouth
No, no
Okay, I want to know here. Okay. Here's my question
I want to go around and I want to hear from everybody because again, this is not the food podcast food doesn't matter
It's the cooking PCP. I want to hear about everyone's day-to-day
Relationship with cooking. How much do you do? How much do you fear it and are you good at it?
Like what do you eat? I want to I want to know I want to know everybody's thing
I don't like cooking just because I'm not good at it and I'm not interested and I
Preferably I would like to ascend to a higher plane where food no longer matters to me and it is just fuel
So I'm constantly moving toward a state where you're all fucking
No, no, there's I enjoy I enjoy the results of good cooking, but I am not good
Enough in the skill to cultivate it in myself
I like when other people cook delectable meals for me that I can enjoy
Yeah, but I do not want to invest my time into doing it myself because there are other things
I would prefer doing with that time. I don't even appreciate
I mean, it's not okay. Okay, if someone makes a great dish like I'll appreciate that it's good and I'll enjoy it for what it is
But I'll beat the shit out of them
But the sad fact like the sad fact that I have come to realize is that I'd be almost as happy just eating like a boiled egg
Like I would be almost as happy
Those traits that I dream about and like romanticize about every single day of my fucking life
They're not a day that goes by when I don't think about the timeline where I literally am Gordon Ramsey
The warped and twisted streets of bombed out France living pay to check paycheck fucking every bitch
I can and I even care about the eggs. I'm slamming together
Learning from the best and getting the shit beat out of me and the fucking twisted streets
I will say if you had like if you were all about food like there was no fucking like anime or cartoons or home sec within you
I was all food and you became the fuck the like the protege for Ramsey
You probably would be qualified for him to pass the torch to would be just like the next Jojo where there's like slightly different attributes
But it's ultimately the same screamy shouty man and a man Homestuck has ruined your dreams. I know right saying
Yeah, it's sapped away. I I
If left to my own devices, I will like I will make bagels
I will make not make but like I will eat bagels to eat ramen toast
I occasionally I will like do a fry up of bacon and eggs and stuff
But I will really go to the lengths that you know
My dad would go to have like a Sunday roast or anything mostly because I'm never never cooking for more than one person
Right, it's just me and just me I can get I can get by with like I can just buy a loaf of bread and eat that you know
But I what I do love because like cooking itself is like you know, I only cook when I'm hungry and by that point
I'm too. Oh, I'm too agitated
Yeah, dude, but what I love doing instead of cooking is baking. I love baking desserts cakes
I hate baking. I love it so much. It's something I would do even if I didn't want to eat it afterwards. I love waking and bacon
I
Don't know what you mean, but I don't want you to explain baking is too complicated and there is too much science in it
No, but like it's like it's like how much fucking egg
Science and art
Here's the thing with baking in with cooking usually it's like heating stuff up
And you have to time things to be cooked at the right time
Yeah, and then put them all on the plate and make sure you eat it before it gets cold
And you can't let things get cold because then they're gross with baking time is basically completely gone
It just you can do it at any time you can cook it and then you can bake it and you can prepare it
maybe bake it and then
You can just leave it in the fridge and it's just like as you know, a chocolate brownie
Or a thing basically and it's like there's no time investment at all. There's no time pressure
It's just like really relaxing like even baking a loaf of bread
That's true. I guess that's true. I don't know
But I don't really have much to say on the subject of specifically baking
But what I did want to say was just I don't cook a lot
I cook rarely which is bad because I should
Cook more to get the more specific nutrient requirements
I need instead. I'll you know kind of slap it together from stuff that's around so I want to improve that but I do
Generally love the feeling of once I have committed and I've cooked something great
And I have shared it with people and I see them and excuse me enjoying it and appreciating it that in that
That's kind of what I wanted to say. That's the communal aspect of cooking is the real shit. It's oh
Hey, it is on this podcast
I'm fine. I'm finally an episode right with Nate the rare Munchie Nate alliance in a PCP episode
It's been forged today so rare, but so powerful
A certain type of cooking cooking for other people is one of the most enjoyable things in this life in this life
I've I've met some chefs actually
Yeah, where it seems like people who become chefs are becoming chefs because they enjoy cooking for other people
It's usually like they had a grandma that taught them how to cook and that the grandma would cook for the whole family
And then they got inspired by that and they want to cook because they want to give other people food and not
Which is pretty interesting, you know, that that's what would drive someone to want to do that
That's kind of the way I feel about baking like I would I would bake a bunch of brownies and I would like
Like really enjoy giving it to the rest of the family
What do you think about these these chocolate things you like
I'm listening hippo. Don't worry. I'm listening. I'm sorry. Yes, that is great. I'm too high
Was there a joke I'm sorry I didn't I food episode
I hope like my favorite way to bond with friends or just like go out and experience the world is through restaurants
My favorite thing to do is just to get together by offline friends and go to restaurant and just eat together
something about like like the feeling of like eating like with you know, you're your relatives or people you're
It's just really it's better than talking alone. It just feels super like base and like and like
Primitive and it feels like you're a real that's true
I was gonna say I like I share Tom's like rage at the fact that I'm trapped in this weak fleshy
Prison of a body and that I have to like, you know, eat regularly to fuel it and stuff like oh, it's so annoying
But considering that that's the reality that I'm in like just using food as a tool to like make people like you
I mean, it doesn't have to be like, you know
maniacal or anything but just like like like
Eating a meal is like when everybody has to be together. Like you can't escape it. So it's a great time to like
Talk to people and like get to know people better and and bond just over sharing the meal with other people
I should have realized that me you're coming out of these different angles
I want I want to cook and like be around people just as a nice thing and it's like how can I like force people to be around me?
I'm just thinking I'm just more woke munch. I'm just more woke. I thought black pills
I put a few more black pills in my muffins if you know what I'm saying
So there's something so like a luring about the about like the chef lifestyle where whenever I watch like a high-level
Chef it's like they're a cowboy. It's like they're a cowboy in the old rest and they don't give a shit about anything
Yeah, put some salt in there just like slamming around
You know like like like when you when you're cooking like steak or something just picking up with your bare fucking hands
I don't even care. Here's anything in my hands. Just slam it on the table. I don't give a shit
I'm self-determined and cooking does not faze me where I don't even like food. I hate eating Gordon Ramsay doesn't eat
He literally just like tastes up of what he's eating. He's not having meals. That's the thing about him. That is true
Really? Yeah, here's here's a here's an unpopular opinion. Here's a okay. Okay. I think that food
I'll hit you for it. So food is food is sort of art in the in the way that porn is sort of art
I think food is basically all and I think that it's
Hear me out here me out because I kind of I kind of know where you're going with this
Yeah, okay food like sex is just a thing. It's just a you know
It's like a primal instinct. It's like a primal instinct that we're all forced that we're all forced to enjoy
Like like we can't help that about ourselves that we like food and you just like porn, you know
There's there's there's there's some pretty simple formulas
I mean you could get artistic with it if you wanted
But it's also easy to make some very satisfying and delicious food
Slash porn with like some easy to find ingredients. Let me just throw a shit ton of butter in there and you know
Whatever
From the perspective of a literal record
Though like because like butter isn't something that just naturally happens like butter is science
Ben I have a similar attitude towards it as you but I come to it from a very different angle
I see it as
You go back to if you just think of humans as just as an entity under themselves forget the actual
Context or culture there in they could be born today or 10,000 years ago, right?
You know food eating having sex having a shelter. It's all equally important
You know, maybe you'll have entertainment if you need it. So the thing is because eating and
Eating is a higher priority, right?
Humans have spent a lot longer amount of time put way more man hours into perfecting the craft of food
To the point that by the 20th century pretty much everyone who's you know, at least decently privileged has access to basically most food
Right and we've basically got it down
I think that over the course of thousands of years
There was a lot of experimentation a lot of studying a lot of stuff that feels like real art and discovery
but we sort of like figured it out and
Similarly with porn it's had a lot less time to advance but because people care about porn so hard
It like figured out its formula and it what it needs to be a lot quicker
Well, meanwhile, so we mean we figured out food because we don't know shit about nutrition people
Nutrition is an all-new front, but when it comes to okay, okay food that tastes good and feels satisfying sure
It's like hitting it's like hitting a fucking equilibrium goddamn
Singularity with like every single month KFC and Taco Bell is inventing a new thing
That's like basically another delicious
Look at the KFC double down and not call it aren't okay
I think the double down is like that's it's a meme. I really hate because all it is it's just chicken where the bread would
I think I think the KFC famous bowl is pretty much the pinnacle of yeah
Yeah, I think the whole double down me is like fucking retarded because all it is is just you're just swapping out bread with chicken
It's such a simple but powerful change look
Minimalist double down right there before us the whole time we simply need to open our eyes and realize people describing the double down is disgusting
I think those people are all fucking retarded, but there are other things
I don't see what's so bad about it's me. There's definitely fried chicken. Yeah, there's definitely
There's technically less carbohydrates if you get yeah double down. Yeah, well, it's a breading. Yeah, well, it's not fucking
It's breaded chicken, but but anyway, so meanwhile stuff like comics or fucking
Literature right there's like
They would just reach over like in the Garden of Eden Adam would reach over to the bush and pluck
Think about how much we figured out food like we basically know what most people like there's a restaurant for almost every sensible taste that in the book
Meanwhile tastes in movies or comics or books is
Even though we've made so much progress
There's still much more
Formulation for them to make and at this point we're probably heading towards some sort of perfection there within a hundred years or so with algorithms like
Data-collecting every opinion possible. I don't know. Maybe maybe maybe maybe it's possible
Maybe it's possible
I don't think that was enough that with enough like if we live in a post-singularity society
And we have like every fucking like everyone's making art there might be like a home stuck for every single opinion
You could have coming out every couple of months
Because the principle of diminishing returns even if a perfect story were crafted that everyone
Eventually become boring and we would need something else because
My this was I picked my words carefully a home stuck for every type of opinion coming out every two months
Okay, okay. What was what was Vic saying now? I want to hear I want to hear Vic twine
I'm gonna say I don't agree with the idea that cooking has become like this singular
No, it's not like actually perfect. Yeah, it's so much closer. It's so much like further up on that hill that it feels
I mean it might just be because like satisfying the taste buds a much simpler thing than satisfying ones like
We've spent media like 10,000 years
Advancing agriculture
Agree with that, but I mean is it is it crazy to think that like it is true satisfying the palette is just an objectively less
Someone I consider myself someone with a very unrefined palette, so maybe I don't have
to like comment on
Maybe someone with a very developed
For example, like oh, I don't need much at all. Oh, hey, I'll put some salt on it
Salt was an incredibly difficult thing to get throughout most of history
It's not like mentally strenuous from the from the perspective of a cook but from the broader cultural from the broader like all of society working together
Like the fact that you have a spice rack dude spices used to control like the commerce of the entire fucking planet, right?
But now it's just casual, so like they were the bitcoins of that kind of what I was getting at in the fact that there's
Like I still think that is going to continue to evolve because there's still resources that are more scarce
And like there are food trends that come out where it's like now
There's a million pomegranate drinks because now pomegranate is easier to farm right we're making GMO fruits that can actually fucking
Reproduce
Preservation techniques that will allow the pawpaw fruit to come back into wide circulation
Exactly, right exactly. I need I need pawpaw flavored
Fruit native to America we need it's a symbol of America
We have to make America great again with the pawpaw
Are you not referring to the pawpaw fruit from one piece that Bartholomew kuma canonically ate? No
It's from the pawpaw fruit. It's like they still grow in Virginia and West Virginia. It's like a it's like a virginia native
Because that it's not people say it's really good. It's super overpowered in one piece. It's really strong in one piece
GMO discussion in this episode because I feel like that might be important to cook in yeah, we could we could go off on some fucking
I could fucking when you like that match you can't stop
Do with cooking it's really more about agriculture, but I'm happy to talk about GMO to death goddamn it your pro GMO to death, huh?
Yeah, there's a good documentary on Hulu that you could watch that'll make it fucking red pilled for GMO's
Okay, basically, it's all bullshit like GMOs are fine. There's absolutely nothing wrong with it
It's just fucking you're you're just splicing DNA and that's completely bad
Like people people chemicals or pesticides. I don't know much about it, but like all it is like you just change in their genes
That doesn't make them like radioactive. Yeah poisonous or anything
Yeah, people act like it's fucking poison faster. We've been doing literally all of our species existence
Did you guys know the carrots used to be purple? No, no, did you guys know? Okay? Okay, you know dogs used to be wolves
We have dogs that can literally sneeze their own eyeballs
Here's something that legitimately blew my mind. Okay, like spinach broccoli
Broccoli cabbage Brussels sprouts called they're all the same plant. They all are they all are descendants of wild mustard
They were like they're the same plant that we're just selectively bred for different trades
Also like Brussels sprouts like a tiny tiny tiny little cabbage. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I know I found that out and I was like holy shit
That's adorable. Yeah, it is still don't like to eat like a like with bananas like they they they basically
It's still selective breeding is just forced into the DNA where they're just taking traits from other plants and putting them in so that
They won't die from like mass viruses
Yeah, and like without that then the economies of the places that are fucking growing the bananas would tank because all the bananas would die
And then we wouldn't have bananas. Yeah, yeah without GMOs. So it's like it's praise GMOs
And the the people that spread the fear of it like this this is a good documentary
Yeah, the the funding for those fucking documentaries are all coming from places like Whole Foods and shit
Yeah, because it's their agenda to sell all this non-GMO stuff because it's a trendy now to be fair is
Not positive some of the fear that like in the future
There will be consequences as opposed to right now of using GMOs. Is that
I don't
Would be that the the only consequence would be that like the viruses would change to
Sorry to interrupt. Yeah, how do I say my mic still working? You said fine. Yep
Like yeah, well, you know, this is all very interesting at all, but there's I think the audience really there's just one thing that came for
Victor I want to know about the philosophy of the po-boy eats. I just want to know everything
That goes on in that world
Tell me about it. I mean this is that the series was inspired by the fact that I cook these super simple dishes for me and hope every day
Almost it not every day at all, but but basically enough, but it's all I fucking know how to do
But like I know other fucking broke-ass dudes who are like like I have a friend who
Gets on me all the time for like the way I eat and stuff and he literally just eats peanut butter and granola sandwiches
So that he can save his money so that one day he could fucking buy a boat
And I'm like you are you are killing yourself. I can't eat just a peanut butter and granola sandwich
My dad will eat rice mixed with corn and pea. Yeah, and that that's a satisfying dinner to him
Like I can't do that right
Like you can you could be kind of broke and also make yourself food that
Makes you not want to kill yourself, you know, well, so everybody knows I mean in case you missed it
We have to link this in the show notes or wherever about the red the rad con three po-boy eat
That was an absolute fucking
Art piece that was that was definitely alchemy going on in that video for sure, right?
That was I got to say I tried noodles on bread
Like just the other day because I just thought I was cooking noodles. I was like, you know
I don't remember the the the you know the Victor burger being that bad. I
Want to try it again. I want to try noodles on bread and it was probably is quite good. Yeah
I'm glad that was on it. Well, the Japanese do that. They'll have like the fucking the noodles on like the hot dog buns and stuff
Right. Yeah, that's true though. There's like a bunch of other shit
Soba hot dog bun shit, right? That's right. There's people experimenting far beyond what I've been doing
I mean, it's just not in America. We're just we're we're
Yeah, hey while we're on the subject of while we're on the subject of simplistic food
Like I didn't end up talking about like my lifestyle with cooking. So here's the thing with me in cooking
The the tensions I have with it are like weird. So I love cooking. I find it therapeutic
I find doing the dishes to be therapeutic
The problem is I just never take the time to like do it because I want to like work on videos more
So I have the same problem as hippo where by the time I finally set about to cook
I'm too fucking hungry and so then it's just almond butter sandwich
So what I need to do what I do when I really like kind of have my shit together
It's just make a whole bunch of food put it in the fridge right now
Wait, was that it was that an almond butter sandwich or is that a was that a all the butter no almond butter sandwich?
Like one stick of butter
Okay, we're like even cashew butter sandwich, which is even better. That's good. Yeah. So like here's right now
I don't have a microwave though. So I can't I've just been eating like cold leftovers that I make but here's the other thing
It's about simplistic food, right? I only got one recently like as I was getting older as I was like, you know becoming 15 16 17
Some of my friends were like, oh wow you cook food. That's like so helpful, right? I'm like, oh, I'm a helpful person who cooks
I don't know and so then leading up to moving in to the bro house with digi and Victor and
Tom been and whatnot. I'm like, okay, so I guess I cook maybe I'll be useful for cooking
But then when it turns out is oh the reason why people don't cook is that they want to have like actual food and not just like
Something that you make with like three ingredients, which is what I always eat like I'm just like, okay
What the ingredients do I have? Oh boy? I have some chicken. Oh, I have a spinach. Oh, I have a
Mushrooms or I have some onions of carrots. All right. I'll saute this and I'm like that's for me is like as good of a meal as I can have
Like I'm not quite as crazy about like weirdly simplistic meals. Okay with that. That sounds pretty good to me. I mean, I don't know
I don't know like that like
Because like I'll eat like rice broccoli and a chicken breast. Yeah, that's like decade because did you was saying like yeah?
You know, I just don't like cooking. I can't I can't I don't know how to cook
I'm like, oh, well, dude, if you want to know how to cook all you gotta do is just make spaghetti, right?
Then the next day or whenever you feel like making spaghetti again make it with like hamburger meat or chicken meat, right?
Then next time put in some like mushrooms and green peppers in there, right?
So just keep making spaghetti and amp up the fucking ingredients one at a time, right?
Yeah, but then like digi then like a month later in another episode of digi, bro
He's like, huh divus telling me how to make spaghetti. I know how to make spaghetti
Like he basically what he was saying is the reason why he doesn't want to cook does see though
The reason why he can't cook by his own definition is that he wants cooked food to be like more complex
And not like the way that his dad would eat food
So what I found out is that even though I like making food
I don't like making food for other people because people don't ever want to eat what I'm gonna make for the most part
The food that I've seen you cook is pretty weird
It's pretty well, you'll have like it's just like I don't rice
You'll have like brown rice like a piece of chicken and then like a pile of like
steamed shredded carrot or something
Ever care about like the I don't maybe I just hate carrots
I mostly don't care about like the the precise execution like the difference between like exactly how long you might want to
Royal something or like breading something correctly or like having the like ratio of ingredients be correct
I became cognizant of this when like when did you was saying like oh?
You know the reason you go to Kevin's doghouse is because it's got the perfect ratio of bun to wiener to chili and I'm like
Oh, yeah ratios. I kind of don't care. I just sort of think what are some ingredients?
I like do those ingredients go well together put them together like it's just very caveman like for me and that
That's why it's so fucking cowboy like these it's because you don't have to give a shit to cook
You do not have to care and that's what makes cook so cool
Is that they're just constantly like cynical and pessimistic and they have no passion or life left on your body?
My approach to cooking
Fucking bowls together and outcomes when when I pause pause pause. What was Gibbs say?
Well, I was gonna say my dad. Yeah, he's like been cooking his whole life
And he's like the cook of the family and he's like really really good in it
I love any cooks, but when I was trying to learn from him like I was like, okay
I got a I got a I got a step up to the plate. I got to try and cook things and
He doesn't have like he doesn't know timings for anything
He just like over the course of being a cook for so long. Yeah, he just
Instinctively knows how long you're supposed to cook a piece of thing and at what temperature
I have to keep asking him what temperature do I reheat this thing at what about this?
How long do I go and just go just go until it's brown and then put the thing and yeah
I'm like that like I know like in my heart of heart when the chicken is probably done
Yeah, but you know, it's like jazz man. Yeah
Yeah, when I when I cook I will like I'll start cooking with a thing in mind
I won't check to see if we have the ingredients
I will just kind of start going and then I'll just I'll just make whatever
Substitutions, I feel like right you want to talk to it. I do a cowboy. So hi
Yeah, yeah
Oh, yeah
So like the the reason why I wanted Ben to be on this episode is that me and Ben?
Well, I played witness to Ben trying to make his infamous like rhubarb pie shit
Back it was it was the it was the devoo bar pie. It was a strawberry rhubarb pie with blueberries
That's good, but the thing is I'm gonna make this rhubarb pie, right?
And you're like, okay
Well, let me look at the ingredients and one by one by one by one by one
You had like maybe two out of the ten ingredients and just
Substituted and substituted over and over and over again. Whoa. Some of the substitutions were legit. Yeah
And it was just the most Ben experience I've ever had
Turned out like what were you left with okay? It turned out okay?
It would have been a fine pie
The only thing was that there was not enough filling so the filling kind of baked down into just kind of like a film
So it kind of just became like really thin bars of like pie crust with kind of a thin gooey like layer of
You know of devoo bar
Okay, the top of it. It was right. I mean it wasn't gross or anything, but it was not a pie
Yeah, we were looking for rhubarb and like we literally went like all around Virginia fucking beach even to like the Asian food
Sort to find rhubarb. There was just no fucking rhubarb anywhere. We grow that shit in our fucking garden up. Yeah
Yeah, I think it's I think it's more of a northern thing. Yeah, I guess so
Bites into that and he thinks you know, I could have eaten the hard-boiled egg. That's the problem Ben
It's not the food. It's that you're making a weird filmy disgusting like fish tank food
by
um
You guys remember who was who was there for it when I made the um the the Swedish fish flavored fried Oreos
that no
During a round like I was there at Radcon
You and me made Dorito a breaded fried chicken. I remember I remember. Yeah, they didn't really really taste like Doritos
They needed to be dusted with Dorito dust after frying like right not before
Remember the fucking crock pot
Chernobyl crock pot the crock pot. Okay. Do you remember? Okay. Do you remember the final days of the crock pot?
Well, I remember the time when it well when there was that one crock pot that dragged out for a couple of days
Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay. Okay, like we had like chicken and vegetables in the crock pot
This was like this was right before we retired it for good. Yeah
So there were chicken and vegetables in there and it had been cooking for it had been in there hot for like two days
It was very dried out. It was not well
So what I did was we went we went to the supermarket and I picked up some cans of soup
I got like cheese and beer flavored soup
And I just
Cheese and beer flavored soup
And mix them with
To moisten it up so I could eat it again
Right, right
Ben like set a crock pot and like the mid-afternoon
And I thought it was Digi's crock pot for some reason and like I had heard that the crock pot was done
It was supposed to be done at 10 p.m. 10 p.m
10 p.m. Comes and I'm the only one still awake and I thought well, it's Digi's crock pot Digi's relatively responsible
He'll remember but it was actually Ben's crock pot. I assume he was asleep. So the next morning comes up
I wake up and I'm like, I'm hearing a sizzling. What's the sizzling?
And I look and I see the crock pot has been on full blast all fucking night. It's all dried up and
Like and Digi comes down. I was like, oh shit Ben's gonna have to throw this away
Then Ben wakes up and he's like hmm. I don't think I had to throw this away
So like you just like neither of us like take a single stab at it
We don't even want to like be in the same zip code, but you're like nibble nibble
I mean, I mean, you know nibble nibble and yeah
You eventually get like fucking like cheese and beer soup like so like basically just make it worse
Just to make it fucking worse. That's and to me. There's a certain logic
That's the perfect summary of the experience of living in that house at that time
It was that there was always some sort of disturbing black mess crock pot
That crock pot on he left the crock pot on on warm right he didn't even like put it in the fridge
He just left it on warm for like a couple more fucking days
Continuing to nibble at it before he finally gave up and it was like all crusted and dried at the bottom
The whole kitchen smelled like ass it was just like
The beer and cheese soup gave it a very strange smell
Two separate soups a beer soup and a cheese
One can soup it was okay and cheese flavor soup. Yeah, okay
It was a real thing more than anyone in this group needs to have his needs to star in a sitcom
Just this man who's just everything about life and existence for him as a total failure
But he's so complacent with it and so chill about it that it seems like he's doing it on purpose
And it's actually really cool
I resent that a lot. I'll fucking end you good tonight
That's the creamer of real life in some ways
Here's the rub. Yeah, is don't be don't be like this. Don't do this. Why not it's good. It worked out
I got I got no down to that crock
Don't give a shit Donald's don't go to der Wiener schnitzel. Don't go to fucking Burger King
Don't just learn just learn the real shit. That's fucking easy
Put some butter in a pan get the pan hot and put it in the egg you will be satisfied by just
So this is this is my secret to being a cooking boy and
And keeping it going and cooking every day and do it and cooking real meals that aren't just bullshit and it's having a
Girlfriend who is way more responsible than I am
It's a good it's an ultimate secret my uh, yeah, that's a pretty good she goes and makes lists of shit and
Gets ingredients and goes and bides them and then all I have to do is assemble them and cook them
And it's easy because it's all planned for me. Yeah, and I don't have to do shit
That is the best way to keep cooking in your life. It's it's so difficult and because I live with my parents still
Yeah, and like my dad is is the cook boy. He cooks
Like he has meals planned like way ahead of time like I'm gonna cook a fucking a curry today
And then we're gonna have a lot of roast lamb
You know whatever and he's like he has all these ingredients in the fridge
And I don't know what I can use and what I can so I did I never get the chance to use
Let to learn cooking myself. I really should like
Like I feel like I would be able to keep track of it if I had with the fridge to of my own
But it's kind of how I felt that's a fridge with a yeah with my
With my family like my mom was the one who does the cooking primarily, but like she wouldn't do it all the time
It would be like hmm point it'd be like
two out of every third day, right and
The thing is is that most of the time we would just make meals for ourselves
I think my dad was like the only one who would like he would basically just rely upon them food that my mom made
He did as leftovers or he'd get work all the time
So he would have lunches out
But everyone else in the family just basically makes their own shit like I make my own shit
And I think my younger brother and sister took after me as a result because even though we generally like almost all the food that our mom makes
We just want to eat when we want to fucking eat, right like yeah me and my brother both like
When we like hit puberty we both became like massive needs we'd be up at totally random times
So it's like I want to have fresh food and I want it to be exactly the amount of fucking proteins
I need right now. So that's how I got into the habit of just like cooking some stupid thing for myself
The result of this is that the dishes in our kitchen were completely out of control 24-7 and they remain so to this day
I'm glad I moved out. I probably we should probably do a whole isolated episode about dish washing
I can definitely get an episode worth of that
Damn, I think dish washing is just part of cooking. You should consider that part of cooking fucking wash your shit immediately
Afterwards, I mean, I will never be a problem. Okay. I'm gonna spoil the upcoming the eventual dish washing episodes
Just right now, right? Here's the thing about that
It depends on your cooking habits
My mom would have a number of times where she would kind of snap and be like, okay from now on
You're always washing the dishes right after we're done cooking, right and inevitably invariably
Every time she has that snap in like the like early afternoon come late evening
She'll have a moment where she cooked something and she's fucking tired
Like there was one time where she was really adamant about it
She was really adamant about it and then that night she makes fucking muffins
And then there's just five fucking crusty muffin tins on the countertop, but I'm like hey mom
What's up with that whole cleaning thing, right? She's like I know I know because here's the thing about it
Is that by the time you're done cooking?
You're a completely different fucking person like
Fucking hungry now you eat the food by the time you're done eating the food
You've like the time of your life that you spent dirtying those dishes
That's like a long past memory you're you've moved on you need to move on with your life
The only way to do it is just have dedicated time where it's like there's a pile of dishes
I'm gonna fucking shred
The way to do it the way to do it is not to do it right after you've finished eating is to wait like a couple hours
Or at least before you go to bed
What me and Hope will do is that we will have washed most of the dishes by the time we're even finished cooking like as soon as
You can do that I think that's ideal
The problem is it depends on what you're cooking because it's like for example
Oh, you know what actually kills it for me almost everything I cook is fucking fried or like sauteed right you can't cook a hot-ass thing
Right after it's done you you have to let it cool a bit and some of that shit's gonna congeal
You can't just touch it right now. So like you have no choice but to put it off for a while
You know okay, okay?
Sometimes sometimes you get a dish that is like really crusty and sticky and then you know you soak it and you let it sit for a while
Personally, I think it probably is the most efficient to clean immediately
I kind of like to do like a big like to clean a load of dishes at once
I know it means passionately dishes are in the sink and it's and it's lame
But I like to just do it all I mean I end up doing that Ben
But the thing is I end up getting to a place of great anger at the world at those dishes that are piled up
And it makes my life worse like I've never do it because I'm like yay time to wash the dishes
It's always fuck. I cannot put this off any longer
Now I have to fucking wait into this hellscape and do the dishes for me what made my what makes me but my whole by the way
Once I'm actually doing the dishes. It's not so bad. It's it's the preparation to be like fine
I love washing dishes because I think it's really satisfying and therapeutic
It's just I I want to get back to work and that's the problem with me and my whole family is that we're always my whole family are like
What am I doing next type of people right like my dad's someone who it's like if he has 15 minutes to wait to go to work
He's gonna like come up with something to do that'll make him just like 15 seconds late, right?
So we're all like that so none of us want you to continue
Harboring over the fucking like food that we just made and continue to like keep cleaning dishes, right?
We wanted like move on to the next thing because now we have all this new renewed after meal energy
So like the the thing with that is
Fuck I don't know where I was going with that. So yeah
I
Want to just gotta do it man. Just gotta do it. Yeah, but
There's other stuff I gotta do because like when you have a well one of the problem
When you have a stay-at-home job, then you have a choice, but to like yeah when you got a stay-at-home job
It's really challenging and it really means that you know
You got a budget your time because you don't have the kind of free time with someone who works 9 to 5 in an office or anything
I know you're being sarcastic then but it's like
It's fucking when you have a 9 to 5 there's these clear borders of when you are or are not working, right?
But when there's always a video project left to be made just in the other room
It's always nagging at me. So what I want to do is I want to have no I know what you mean
I do I want to have a dedicated time each day where I'm cooking and cleaning at the same time
Simultaneously and then everything is clean and then like all the leftovers I'll need for tomorrow or in the fridge
That's what I need to do
I just need to manage that as a giant chunk and just wipe it all out in one go. I
Structure to that point. I
Have a certain level of fear that when I go full-time doing YouTube stuff that my my lack of an
inherently rigid rigid cold schedule
It's the toughest thing. It'll be an issue. Like they say when you become your own boss, you have to hate yourself like a boss.
You just be able to make your own schedule. You're just gonna be able to like like
Regally like like make his own hours
Well, you know that that's the thing that to do like that is the way to go and like to try to stick to that
But like if my my personal like internet creation career thing has kind of been an exercise in
Finding ways to not have to rely on my own willpower and instead putting on it like like by making like we Agua like I have to get
One done every week. There's no choice like you can't procrastinate or I mean I am right now
But you know what I've been doing for the last several months
I've been experimenting with this over the last year
But I've been doing it hardcore for the last couple months is don't don't schedule myself
But just keep track of what I'm doing which is interesting cuz CGP Grey just like did a Q&A where he mentions that that's what he does
too so like I just track how many how how many minutes in the day I spent working and then doing chores and then
Fapping and then doing nothing and then like watching stuff, right and then sleeping
So then I just look at the numbers and the numbers that just sort of constantly reminding me
It's like a pat on the fucking shoulder like bro. Hey, hey, wake up
You know, it always makes me think about it like okay, and that keeps me awake
I'm now. Maybe I don't know shit about shit, but I feel the need to ask has that actually work because I
Mean like to my view it seems kind of like you've fallen completely off the map
Well, yes, there have been other things that have made me like not well as I've been
Checking the numbers. Yes, there've been like huge stretches of time where I'm barely like putting in like even part time hours, right?
And I'm trying my best and I'm trying to crawl out of it. I think I am I've been saying that a bunch of times though
You know, it's fucking you know in a relationship having basically doubled my family amount
You know what I mean? So like just all sorts of stuff flies in
Well, he doesn't need to defend himself
Although I probably fall off the map because I'm trying to be less of an internet personality
But I guess I'm on podcasts more now. So I guess I'm failing at that. Yeah
Getting back to cooking. I
Remembered something that is like the perfect like the most fun cooking that I actually do love a lot
And I hope a lot of you agree
Being a barbecue chieftain
What is it with sitting sitting at the barbecue by the way, it's like universal
I the idea is that moms are the cookers, right?
But barbecuing on the on the thing outside is always a hundred percent dad. I
Well, here's the thing with that my dad has sort of like relegated that to me and I have like leapt it up like that
That's my favorite thing to do. I am yeah
I'm now the dad when it comes to barbecuing and it's like that Tim and Eric skit when when Eric is like
Children, I'm just gonna be one of you now
That's our new dad. I'm just one of the kids now. That's what your dad's done to you. You've been promoted. He's demoted because like
It's it's I took a great side when I moved out of the house and moved in to my own place when we we bought a grill
And I was like, all right, I am the new grill master. Yeah, I'm my dad did this and I'm gonna do this now
And this is my thing and it's it's fun
With grilling and cooking anything you are not beheld into any when you restaurant or to any cook
Yeah, your mom or to your dad you were making your own shit. Yeah for your own path
I just do literally so great
And you can just do whatever the fuck you want these fucking munchies
Let's give go. He was he was coming. Yeah. Yeah. What's so good reason? It's so it's so good is because
Um
When you are like the main guy doing the cooking everybody comes to you as like the leader of what's happening currently
And so like you put the meat on and then somebody else. So can I get you anything kind of do you need like a
Shall I bring the the next set of like kebabs or whatever bring you the next version for you to impregnate?
Yeah, and then people are like willing to that because standing in front of a barbecue on a hot day
It's like a big whoosh of hot air and it's like ow. It hurts. It hurts my eyes, but I love being there
It's like being a blacksmith. It's but it's like it's like sweating and like and like smoke all over my face
And I'm like I'm smashing these sausages onto the grill and I'm looking at them crisp up
And and I got my apron and my tools and I'm like, I'm the coolest guy and the best thing about it
It's during a party this happened once
It may happen again where there was a barbecues a summer like last year
I was barbecuing and there's a bunch of people around and they are like people my parents know and I don't really know them
They're all drinking and talking and having a good time
And I'm the barbecue boy which means that nobody has to come and talk to me about anything because the barbecues tucked away
And I'm just providing food
I'm just saying I'm like my brother would come here talk to me because he doesn't like talking to anyone either
And he would be the one bringing the fruit from me to the kitchen
So like I got to not I get to not participate in the party, but still be
Like a non-anti-social person and cartoons don't work out hippo
You could do the job of being the like four armed
Heat guy from spirit of the way who like gets the fire going for the boilers and shit
That's he basically looks like he already like when you have that like half mustache beard thing going on, right?
Yeah, it's true
Coming off of what hippo said I think one of the reasons that like
Barbecuing appeals to dads and it's kind of like that male thing my wife
That I think it's like it's something you like you want to be outside doing something a little bit
Barbecuing is something to do and then it's also a great excuse to have a bunch of beers
Yeah, like sit there and grill like my dad always did it when he always be drinking beers
And then when I barbecued I like basically got drunk while as barbecuing and had a blast right because you're outside
Yeah, and I'm outside alone
So I'm like I the only way to pass the time is really to like fucking drink a bunch of beers
Well, you're sitting there barbecuing. Yeah, and you're having a blast
And you can't you can't like get roped into any stupid conversation because you're like, oh, sorry
I gotta I gotta pay attention to this, you know the stuff
This is important, you know late in my career as a son
When I when I live with my parents still the thing is grilling became sort of a vital component of like everyday meals
So like we we would grill out on like the deck where the where the thing was like all the time and the problem is I don't share
Exactly the same, you know manly trope of how great barbecuing is because it became just like a family cooking thing
They're like I would do a lot. I'm you know bend it sometimes
I remember having to do it a lot and it was just like a thing that I was expected to do and it was like it was like
My dad was the real boss. I was just the fire monkey who had to go out and you know prepare
Yeah, you know and it was it hurt my feelings. I didn't get to be a big boy
They sucked all the fun. I like it was it was fine. It was fine. It was just a chore though
Yeah, yeah, I was not master of my domain, which I think was the difference here
My dad would only ever barbecue like once a year. Yeah, it was always a big deal
Like it was this rare phenomenon that we were grilling and it's like oh man
This is the coolest thing basically instead of being a cook. I was just a cook
About like that that being on a hot day and having that hot grill blow smoke into your face
There's something so satisfying about like being in pain, you know
About doing something hard that like physically harm you not like emotionally like work really like like hurts you and burns like like
Like I'm sure like you know mining at night getting your hands all chapped and like
I do not like that before in my life. So thank you. Yeah, that's what I'm I
Defaulted that cuz I'm a fucking idiot
hard labor hard labor feels great just to do like gardening gardening digging up weeds destroying like like
Stumps, it's great
Labor to like accomplish something that you know is good and that you want to do and it's just like of your own accord
You're like, you know, I'm gonna be a fucking man. I'm gonna get down in the dirt. I'm gonna grovel. I'm gonna flop around like a fucking pig
I'm the poor mud over my fucking spread-ass eagle
Shit, I'm gonna fucking be a man
Or even just like going on like a long hike through like the woods like that's like physical and it's like
Ah, I've accomplished this, you know. Yeah, I don't mean I don't do I don't do physical labor or physical exercise
Oh, the only muscle that I ever work out is my brain is your brain. Yeah, there we go. Also my my my my ethics
I mean, yeah, the three form a whole eternity
He said like in one episode
Maybe conscience would be a better word, I think your brain is a huge fucking muscle, bro
That's why I like yeah one time Rush Limbaugh was like people always say rush. Why don't you ever work out?
Why don't I ever see you like even like lift anything or like do anything physical?
It's because you all don't see the cylinders firing at full strength in my
You said Rush Limbaugh, yeah, yeah, okay, okay. Well, what a fucking idiot
If I if I did any physical activity, it would take okay
It would divert power away from my brain cylinders
But Rush Limbaugh is a big fatty and L is canonically like a tennis warrior gladiator champion. So yeah, I'm just saying
There's something so sad
It's fine not being able to like give another human and like like a share in the thing
You're giving another human of like giving them like the primal desire of eating food
But not having to be like a weird like like societal commitment like sexes
And a friendly ordeal where you just share and being a human and bleeding and weeping together
And you have your bread or your cheese and you can talk and you can catch up
It's just a warm homely ever that doesn't have any societal pressures on it. It's this like a cursed forced
heterosexual
Relationships I'm forced to engage in you know
Just just the the the feeling of joy
Yeah, through a chaotic, you know, just just
Just happen to happen J. Oh crystal charging sesh with the boys. No, that's that's pure
That's what life is really about. Hey, are we gonna start a PCD club?
What's the D for Pete the D club? You don't know about the D club. Oh the D club, of course, of course, I mean yes
Radcon D
The fourth one will be next so D would work. Yeah, damn. That's a good idea
I've got like one last story about like primal cooking. Yeah, cuz I've been camping a couple times
No, it's like we get like a log fire going and you know the the obvious like marshmallows is like nobody fucking does that
What we used to do was we got like um
We got like a potato and we wrapped it in tinfoil and we just threw it in the fire
And and and sweet corn as well
Mm-hmm. I remember making egg bread out in the woods and I don't know how we did that eggie that was strange
Oh, yeah, eggie bread is like when you when you get an egg and you whisk it up and then you dip the bread in the egg
Because they're mortal enemies
No, nothing
You call them french fries chips they come chips. Oh, right. Well, no, I know that we have
We have for it. We have fries, which are like this thin like McDonald's things. Yeah, but then chips are like chunkier
So chips are the good fries
So you go so when you go to McDonald's when you go to McDonald's you order fries not chips
Yeah, well, they they ask that that's they've always been like an Americanized restaurant chain. They don't change
With cheese winners the metric system that's what fucking pulp fiction talked about so I think well
That's just the name but but I mean this I mean in Japan. They have whole different sandwiches and shit at McDonald's
Yeah, fucking bizarre we got spaghetti. Are we done are we done talking about cooking now should we
Away like nothing
Yeah, I mean not I don't know anything I was gonna ask if like okay
If each of you guys had to recommend to our fair audience something for them to cook. Oh, what would you recommend? Oh, right?
I recommend. Oh, is that hard to make though, Ben? How do you make that?
You just fucking get some you know, I mean you coated in some egg and some flour and so whatever the hard you could coat it in
Like anything you want you just cut anything you got a fire
You just fucking deep you get a deep fryer. Can't you just make it in a pan?
I'd like 20 bucks. You can put oil in a saucepan and deep fryer thing. Yeah
Here's my recommendation if the way that I described the way I cook and the things I eat sounded interesting to you dear viewer
Like what I like to call it is the water saute
Which is like to do the kind of meals I mentioned with the chicken and the you know the carrot and the mushroom and the spinach and just
Instead of using oil just use like water and just like keep that's steaming
I know I know it's steaming but instead of like having a thing like where like you know
There's water beneath it and you know the steam comes up like you're cooking chicken like you put the chicken in there when this chicken is like
50% cooked that's when you can add the carrots when everything is like 98% done
That's when you could put on the the spinach because that's just shrivels up really quickly
But yeah, like it is basically a saute in my opinion because it's all like in a thing
It's not it's not just steam you're using water
Just keep adding water and then you can just like basically eat stuff that I think tastes pretty good with basically like no
Like you know shitty things for you, you know, there's not even any butter or oil, right? It's just like the fat of the chicken
So that's my recommendation
My recommendation would be just think of something you've always wanted to know how to cook
Google it get the ingredients and just cook it with your phone
Where you can keep track of every single thing you have in your fridge and it'll like algorithmically like pick out like recipes
Oh, no fuck that true
I hate regimenting things like that
I'd rather just like be like on a whim like I want to learn how to cook a Spanish omelette
I Google Spanish omelette recipe and then I just make it and I just look at my phone. It's great
You got a guy have that adversity like oh, you gotta look in your fridge and be like, oh, what's here?
It's not a whole lot here. I guess I guess there's no but like it's I can do make this
I mean, it's it's intimidating the idea that you're supposed to just become like a person who
Inherently knows what you need to put into a thing
I think if you want to get into cooking start by learning recipes and eventually you'll figure out that you yeah
Like what you can you know, how do you know what you can change about a risk?
Yeah, sure watch chopped all the time
How do you like how do you learn how to play guitar like if you want to be like an excellent like jazz guitarist?
Like the first thing you do is you like learn to play like a song and then you like look up
Exactly what to do and then as you go. Yeah, just kind of learn like okay
So I've learned I've learned you see repeating patterns of how songs are and cooking is similar to that in the sense of the the way
You can like you know extrapolate and apply things in different ways and all that kind of stuff. So yeah
Let me say you could you could go and learn how to like make a sauce, you know
And like go to the roots of like don't just buy prego try to make sauce and then you'll see like how things go together
You know and how things are actually made in
In the cooking world indeed Tom, can you speak for like three minutes straight so you earn your $30?
Is gay
I've had nothing to contribute to this topic at all
Well fair enough
Okay
Just make a fucking steak. Here's what you do. Here's what you do
You just put on a fucking steak and you move it with your hand you move it with your hand
Oh, no, no, you scrape a steak and you just fucking pick it up
Wait, wait, you don't even you don't even like pick it up like like from the top
You scoop it up with the burning oil in the pan and you slather it all over your fucking face
I'm
Literal cooking tip when you put when you're cooking a steak and you put it down in the pan
Never move it well not never but like don't move it around to cook it because you need to let the the skin like
Crisp up and harden and when it slides around on its own then you can flip it
Oh, if you move it around it likes it'll like break apart and it'll be gross
Moisture in there. I always want to move my food around when I'm watching it cook. It's a bad. It's not stakes
It's a bad idea. Okay. You're supposed to like you're supposed to like make steaks in the pan and the frying pan
And then I put it in the oven, right?
Real estate
Has everyone laid out their food recommendation? Well, no, we're in the middle of it got to I know I know like once this is done
That's basically it. I
Don't know maybe it anyway
All right, just just checking
Why were you talking about wait?
Here's here's my cooking recommendation don't do it. Here's this is this is what I'm saying
Money and you won't have to do it anymore. I mean that's just get better at your job and make more money
I mean, that's a good recommendation too, but here's what I'm actually saying. Here's my real recommendation
I cooking is nice and I like the communal aspects and all that stuff, but better than that is
Like saving any time that currently is used cooking so my recommendation is to those
asshole soy boys out in you know fucking the West Coast that makes soil and whatnot make a real version
that's not some gay soy shit and
So that I can be a man and made a pure animal product puree
Invent a new thing that
Wait, I'm shattering the fucking paradigm right now
Break out of the box. There's a soil and competitor called a hue fuel with an H and it has
No, so you say thank God
I mean, I don't I don't the soy is not actually a problem, but like I don't know what like the new I have not looked at
Like the nutritional facts here. Here's what I want. It's not the size of the problem. It's the boys the boys in that soil
That's a problem. Listen. It's the
I want a slurry. I can just chug at any moment of the day and I just want to be able to
I don't give a shit is it is like an IV drip of vitamins in
Literally what I want. That is exactly what I want. I fuck eating. I'll literally give it up. I don't care
I just want enough to worry about it
Have you tried pissy baby food?
Suckling I would not be perhaps I fucking I fucking would not be surprised if there's like an adult baby food
Pedialyte pedialyte that like yeah, yeah, have you seen recently on Twitter?
They're rebranding it that it's not just for babies because they want
That's literally their their their slogan is not just for babies. Oh my god. This ain't your daddy's baby food
By the way, I don't believe there's any ABDL food yet because the ABDL like
Yeah, well because like the companies that supply like products and like merchandise for that
I don't think they have quite the supply chain yet to like have like refrigerateable and like
Just eat baby food. Yeah, I didn't I didn't particularly mean it as like like an RP thing
I mean it was like as a thing as a Nate thing like I want just a slurry of like protein enough for an adult
I'm the real ABDL
That's so that's my record
Yeah
Have the brain the size of a fucking mountain in this baby's body
Wide and
Cooking right the reason why I was trying to like figure out like how much more we have to say is because yeah
Okay, it seems like we're basically wrapped up with food, but I kind of talk about kitchens specifically
I don't know if we should save that for a later episode
We're right right right up down time I think here's the main issue for me wait
We we've only been going for an hour, but we've got we've got segments to get to we've got
I mean if we go for 50 more minutes, that's perfectly fine with me. I got no problem with that
The people want the kitchen rent give us the kitchen rent in all caps. Yeah 10 minute video and it has monetization on
Oh, true. So, you know, here's the thing about kitchens, right?
I have had a lot of different kinds of kitchens in my life like for you know
And what I found what surprised me is that this little rink eating kitchen
I have in my new apartment is by far the best kitchen experience. I've ever had which surprised me so a
Kitchen my family's kitchen in the in the house
We live in the nice big old house that we bought specifically because we're an older family, right?
The kitchen there is too fucking big. It's like a whole section of room
That is like a kitchen and I totally took for granted the fact that doing anything is a pain in the fucking ass
It's like oh shit forgot the milk
Yeah
Renting
Football field like honestly if I were to sprint the amount of breaths
I took would be accurate to the amount of fucking space. Oh shit. I forgot this spice
Spice, you know, it was just pain in the fucking ass and then like oh, what's up hippo?
Well, I was my kitchen has like um
And it currently is it's got like the the two sides, but then there's like an island in the middle of the room
Yeah, so like you don't need to go very far. You can just make a 180 to get anything
I don't like the islands at all
Like constricted and if there's something that you want that's on the opposite side of the island
It's basically like a fucking like Odyssey to get there and back, you know, it's a it's a small enough island for that
But like I mean it works well, right?
So my mentality towards kitchens is obviously like crafted under the
Situation of basically just making food for me and my fiancee so like I don't have a family yet
So a small kitchen is perfectly fine, right?
And like yeah, yeah, my family's kitchen not only was it big
But like it was laid out in a way where it was like almost like two or three different like sections and so yeah
The kitchen I'm at right now
It's like all in one spot and almost nothing is more than two steps away from anything else, right?
It's like there's the sink and then the stove is right behind it
So I barely even have to move anywhere
It's like it's like I am the fucking guy from a spirit of the way with all the arms like controlling the furnace
It's just like I don't even have to like move that much. It's super cool, right?
So I would say one of the better kitchens I'd had that I've experienced is the kitchen at the how at the bro house
You know their last name mr. Bro
It was a cool kitchen, you know, and it was laid out like in a circle
So like everything you didn't have to walk too far
The only problem with that kitchen is that everything about it was fucking dying the light. Yeah, I had a good light
I would have ranked it as probably the second best kitchen I've had
Except it goes down a couple ranks because it wasn't maintained well
So like it has a nice like a fluorescent light because I think fluorescent lighting is like nice and relaxing
Which I guess is the opposite of how it should be. I don't know what's wrong with me
But the light went out like a couple of times
So most of the time it was like we were using this shitty little like study lamp for the fucking kitchen at night
Which made it kind of like disable and depressing which was kind of cool
Especially when you're cooking with Ben, it's like yeah having like depressing cooking time. You know what I'm saying
But then also like the electricity around the whole house was like kind of fucked
So like I had bought like an electric kettle so I can make myself tea
So I can make myself like coffee and those little instant coffee pots, but it fucking zapped my goddamn electric kettle
Probably because it was a cheap $20 one
But the point is I spent the rest of my well those things also draw a lot of power and you're not supposed to plug them in with
Other shit that may have happened. It's supposed to be like it has to be on like its own circuit
Oh, I didn't know that I will keep that in mind because yeah
So basically I spent the remainder of my eight months there like just cooking it on the pot
And then like forgetting about it and overflows and like shade would come in be like oh you've got your
For your water and I'm like I remembered when I had my own water
My electric kettle would turn off automatically and then let's see what else like oh
Well then there was the dishwasher, but the dishwasher died
Literally the same day I moved in and it wasn't repaired everything was fucking right it died the same day
I moved in so I never used it and it was only repaired like a week before I moved out
And so the thing is is that there was water in there and the water just stayed there the whole time
I lived there and every couple of months. I'd be like I have to do it
Okay, mold it all right
You know I would do that like every couple months and then the coup d'et gras of this of this kitchen is that the sink clogged up
The the garbage disposal wait there was never a garbage disposal there
Oh, there was a garbage disposal there it stopped working and the stink the sink clogged up
And if only I had known what was coming like the stink is right right right?
So it just sort of built up and then like food just food ish water
Like just stayed there and it took like two days to drain and it just felt like total ass like Ben's crock pot
Malfunction was nothing compared to this like the last entire month of being in that kitchen
It wasn't a misfunction so much as malpractice right now practice. Yeah, yeah, I'll practice and nobody doing anything
Yeah, why are you standing as a bummer?
Because it was basically like how do you have a kitchen without a fucking sink?
That was the question that we all had to figure out so like I had so much processed food that month
Like I had lost like fucking like probably 30 to 40 pounds while I was there because I was eating
Water sautees and also like not eating a whole lot because I had a broken ankle twisted ankle
I just didn't get up much so like I just lost a lot of weight
But I gained a lot of that weight back right before coming back because I was eating so much processed food and just like avoiding
the sink the whole time so it was sort of like a
The whole situation in the kitchen was just sort of falling apart in us in a death spiral the same way as like everything
Was then so it's pretty cool. Definitely like top-keck memories. I would say
But I'm glad to have a normal kitchen that just does shit now, you know
that whole arc was like it was it was like a
Sort of a waking nightmare, but also like a perfectly aesthetic experience to have in like your early to mid
With all these dudes
Guys yeah, I want you all to know that while diva was telling that story
There was plenty of time for me to master the blade which I have now done which I have now
Accomplished were you in the dojo? I was I would well and well no
I've long since mastered the blade in in a variety focus cop killers terms
But this there's a little kitchen knife that was in my kitchen that I've got it's got a little sheath
It's got a little sheath here, and I want you all to know that I've been practicing E. Ido during this entire podcast
The eye the art of the quick draw you see and I have now become a full-fledged level 99 master
That's what I want. Yeah, now you know now, you know
My my kitchen is pretty good. It's kind of it's pretty like compact
I can easily get anything the only problem is that it's so compact and I live with so many people yeah
Whenever I'm cooking something they're always trying to get something out of the fridge
I hate that and they're all sweating and heaving and fucking vomiting all over me
And they've all got their bodies pressed up against me
It's the worst when I come downstairs during the week days and my 4-chain uncle is there because I know okay
Got a timer 4-chain uncle five minutes before he starts talking to me
So I have to run downstairs
I have to like get the the butter in the in the pan as fast as possible turn that shit all the way up
Get some fucking eggs in there, and then like always like as I'm about to put the eggs in the plate
He's like so I was reading this book about Ramo the other day
Yeah, yeah, I didn't mention that that was one of the things that drove my neatism and wanting to like like sleep
It weird times and like making food on my own terms to not be in the kitchen with anyone else
Especially when I'm a fucking angsty teenager. I'm like oh, oh
What's that you needed to get like a thing out of a shell that's near my torso area
Okay, yeah, go ahead just be
For you be within three feet of proximity to me. Yeah, sure. I'm not like trying to like what's hold yelling here
Go ahead do it. It's so awful. Oh, oh, it's like trying to draw when people around. Oh, yeah
Yeah, yeah, and I think I think I've mentioned this on the previous episode also like looking for something and if your mom is there
She's just like what are you looking for? I don't think we can find it together. No, no, I don't know
I'm looking for something. I can't find it. What I would do is pretend to be finding stuff constantly
So that I don't look like I'm having an issue so she won't ask who I'll be like
Open shelf. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, open up drawer. Okay. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Yeah
I think what I actually did was I just was so weird that she was just too scared to approach me
But you know, I got the results I needed right she didn't fucking ask me what I'm looking for right
That's practicality
The same thing when I was living at home or like half the time like I want to cook
But I so didn't want to be around anywhere where anyone would look at me or talk to me
Yeah, I just wouldn't do exactly
Wait till everyone else is gone. Yeah, you will you avoid your parents? Oh, yeah
Yeah, I don't want my parents to be like, oh what inspired you to cook today. Are you not or you're not gonna cook ever again?
Yeah
Even more the kind of oh what you doing like did you just told me that you would go around into the backyard to go
Into the garage to then come out the garage door when you come home
So that it looks like instead of coming home you just came from the garage so that your dad wouldn't ask where you go when you were out
Which is I would right. Yeah, that's me even though. It's not like I was out doing anything
I just have I just I would have the intense anxiety that anyone would talk to me and because I get so like
The I used to be very frustrated when I was trapped at home. Right. It just like when I'm angry
I know if I if anyone tries to ask me something
I'm just gonna like give a every action that they're not like
So I just like want to avoid all back in this like one like period of
Teenagernessness where before I had to work, but when I had to clean the dishes
I would just be like, oh, I'm not doing them in right after breakfast. No, not doing them after dinner. No, I do them at 3
Fucking a.m. So like it was in the house where the kitchen was far away enough, right?
So I would just like ah, it's 3 a.m. Fucking perfect, right?
And I would just like put on podcasts or whatever and it's like, ah
Everyone's asleep. I'm completely alone. I could watch all the dishes. It was beautiful
I think that was probably why I like washing dishes to this day is because that was a good experience
Just being completely alone. No one's gonna talk to me the whole the whole like thing with not being like wanting to start a
Conversation with somebody but so you avoid like the places where people would
Likely be is probably the reason I to my brothers always just start like if we see each other
We say nothing we say like a weird
Acknowledge like each other's presence without having to say so
How you do it like we avoid that by being fucking strange
That's what me and shade do every time we see each other me and shade just go like
Me and my brother know exactly the kind of things that makes us uncomfortable
So like if something awkward happens one basically the way we do it is we go, huh?
I can't believe you just did that like well like like if something wrong happens
You'll imagine like what is the worst possible thing someone could say to judge you and we'll just like say that judging thing like jokingly
And it like relieves the tension right and then like I can't stop doing it with other people
So people think I'm being super fucking rude right or like if something awkward is happening instead of trying to like be like
Oh, man, are you okay? Because it's like that pisses me off when someone says that so my brother's always just like ha suffer, right?
I just sort of like do that to other people and other people are like what the fuck you like you make it fun to me
I'm like no, I'm just I'm just I'm just telling you to suffer
It's always awful when you're like downstairs and you're doing something and then and then your parents begin with so
And you know are all right. What's the lie? I have to say this time
What do I have to fit what I have to stretch the shoes to make sure that they do not ask any more questions?
This is what concentration camp. I have to make sure that they don't ask any more questions after this
Yeah, what concentration camp can I be shipped off to to avoid this kind?
Yeah, I would do anything to avoid
The way I sort of dealt with that yeah, is that I try to like have answers to questions
They're likely to say and say them before they can so that it so that it feels like I'm being yeah
And then they don't feel the need to ask that much
I think we're kind of cannibalizing the future PCP episode about like dealing with talking to your parents
But yeah, I do want to say like since we've already just cannibalized most of it
Like it was a weird like I think the most coming-of-age thing about me was deciding to stop watching TV with my family
Because they wouldn't stop watching fucking cop drama shows and it's been fucking 14 years since and then they still haven't stopped
So I was just like I'm done. I don't want to keep watching movies with you
I don't want to keep watching TV and my dad was legit offended because like for like the modern 21st century man
There's no more wars to fight no more fucking boars to stab no more fucking minorities to fucking
Like kill right there's no more manly things to do well
We just don't have the excuse anymore
Except to fucking watch TV
It's the only thing dads have left that and grilling but like it's true
And so when you stop watching TV because your parents have shit taste in shit
And you just want to be on the internet where everything is much better
My dad was just like why why aren't you watching this movie?
And he finally like two movies in a row that I refuse to watch he was just like fine. Don't watch the movie
I mean, he
Once he got the message he he never bugged me about it again like my parents they they fucking understood that
I'm an anti-social recluse and they got it eventually, but like it was really funny and I didn't you know being 14 at the time
I didn't have the emotional depth to understand what I was doing the way I do now
It's probably like like write him a fucking apology actually
Even though
What say is a real millennial thing
I don't know if any of you will get this and and if someone were to say this to me
I would make fun of them as well
But I know it is true and I have noticed it in my life
Whenever I'm like in the car or something and I have my headphones in and my family tries to talk to me
I just cannot like I cannot express the deep like I don't describe it
Like guttural like primal feeling of rage that I get I have headphones in I don't want to talk to you
Leave me alone. I'm looking out the window and blasting music. I obviously don't want to talk to you about my day
Please stop mom, please. Yes
Yes
Well, that's one of the joys of moving out and getting away from your parents
Yeah, you get to mellow out and not be pissed off at them like 100 yeah
For absolutely no yeah, yeah, there's like no
No, yeah, I can't wait
I can't wait to like come go back home to my family and visit them and be like cook with them
You're like, oh you want to like get a thing in front of my shelf three feet around right like around my general area
I'll be totally fine with it and I'm just gonna be like oh
I can be around human beings and I don't feel like a wound up stress ball ready to pop brilliant
Indeed exactly. All right. It is really fun the end
Yeah, and a munchie. No cooking is not fun. It's over is what cooking. Oh, yeah
Well, what do you say this slams head into grill and sizzled to perfect
Now that's what I call alchemy. Oh
Only a one in a billion. He's very rare
Hey, well team. I will you so that's the end of our of our main show I mean course
Damn, yeah, it's let's let's let's prepare this one. Well a base
Good. All right. Here's what we're doing team. Here's what we're doing. We're not going straight into questions
We're doing a couple of things where we're trying out some new shit, but here's the first of all so this PCP theme
Contest thing is still happening and you've all been a colossal failure
Because we have proof that that's not true because we do still have that one submission that I mentioned last episode
So we're gonna play it right fucking now on the show. We're all gonna listen to it
I wait from it's from our boy AJ Shoup and if you if you think you can do better
Yeah, invite you to try you fucking coward indeed hashtag
PCP theme send it to us on Twitter or if in the discord if you're the patreon, that's fine, too
But send us this shit cuz we're this is not a failure. This is real
This is for real. I swear dad. I'm I'm actually able to pay my bills with my internet career. It's not a joke
It's not fake. I don't have to live off food stamps. I actually will make something on my life. I'm not desperate
I'm not a failure. Munchie play the song
Play the song
You are a robot Nazi techno state Jesus Christ. Okay. All right. Here we go
I'm just gonna be work to death day-in day-out without an extra pay to be the robot slave holder here. That's right. Here we go
Yeah
Oh
What happened in rad con 17 like montage, you know what I mean?
AJ that was excellent. Yes, pretty much like that a lot. Yeah, and it's kind of
I don't think it has the right tone to be an OP though
We could we could shorten it to make it like a very
Tone of it doesn't like make me doesn't feel opening to me
Let me let me can I can I share an anecdote with you guys about the creator of that of that jingle?
Yeah, please so the other day so the other I was making a new discord and I got carried away
Invited pretty much everyone. Yeah, everyone on my friends list into this new discord, right?
And it became you know it wrap it spiraled out of control and I had no idea or you continue your anecdote
I have an anecdote about your anecdote
Okay, Ben is a recluse
Ben is not someone who goes out of his way to like talk to people at least from my perspective
He does not like initiate conversations about anything that aren't awful
When I get like a
Discord link like a link from him out of the blue like like just just you know one damn on my phone
And there it is a discord link and then he sends the same link again two times in a row not saying anything
Yeah, I was too soon. He's like hacked or like so he's like like like some sort of sleeper agent for the Russian government
My mind and and now he seems sort of like Islam bomber or this is like some sort of like suicide stunt
Where he just needs to be doing this and he's in a giant like group call and sick. All right guys
This is it. I'm going to kill myself live on air
I get blood to my kick started to kill myself
Shock of anxiety that runs up my spine when Ben sends me a link to something without saying anything that that's how I feel
When I talk to you, I mean it was funny that both you and mage were like really concerned and I was just like well
Of course Ben would do this. Like of course, you just like randomly make a chat and then like not explain it at all
Okay, so so go on. Okay, so I said so I invited everyone on my friend
I just like spammed invites to basically everyone. Yeah
Um, it everyone jumped in it it spiraled out of control. I had no idea what was going on
And I was like, you know what nevermind so I didn't delete it
But I just left it for a while a couple hours later. I
Well like later that day at my discord account got deleted or got deactivated because of spamming because I had
Done this it got reinstated today. So it's all fine
But for a while I was dead and I and I couldn't keep up with what was going on in there a couple hours after I made it
I just happened to see AJ Schoop say mod me. So I did then my then my account gets gets deactivated
Two days later, it gets back. I come back in I look and now I see that what I think I created the there's like a
Space station like aliens like roleplay like bot thing going on like there's like there's like commands and stuff
It's like a mini endless war, but like set in space or something
Well, you are you are the the god in the religion of deism like you just created it then left and then like came
Yeah, yeah, that's right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, so I don't know what's going on there anymore. So is AJ responsible for this?
I mean, I can only assume so I don't know
Probably well sounds like there's two bends in the chat
Huh?
Is this why there's two bends currently in this chair
Well, I'm the other one I made be when the other one my real account was was temporarily deactivated
He will be dealt with that that road. Yeah, he will be sent to the school. I lost all of your slime
How fucked up would that be?
Well, I would have just had crack transferred or something. Yeah, it would have been fine
It would have been fine. That's like as far as rowdy fuckers
That's when you die in a Minecraft server and then you say your friend
Like TPed me and your friends like no you have to walk back here. Those are the rules. I can't I can't cheat. It's like
No moving on
Okay, well, I mean that's our one submission right now was pretty fucking tight AJ nice job
But we want more people we want fucking more. I demand more send more to us
We want to play each one of these as the theme one after the other before the show
It kind of like my way
Like a whole album a whole album of PCP themes before the show every single
Yeah, that'd be funny. I mean, yeah, just send more people you've heard it now. They're real
We'll play them on the fucking show. So send them to us send them immediately
Saying things on the show
I think we're gonna start like reading comments or at least responding to general sentiments of comments on the show as well
So if you want to be read or have the general sentiment of what you're implying or saying be
Acknowledged by us
I just imagine this the starry-eyed fans with their poster of us on their wall
We like I can't wait. I dream for one day the general sentiment of what I think of their content to be
But I mean but on that front other other new thing
That'd be I don't know if this is what you were building to but we're talking to we want voicemails people
Yes, we want voicemail. So okay, here you go
Hashtag PCP voicemail. You got a couple options. Send us
YouTube videos or links to SoundCloud. We tried fucking Vokeroo. It doesn't work. So we can't do it that easily
So it's got one of those don't make don't make a visual for YouTube video
We're not gonna watch that. It's not what it's about. It's not what it's about
And and to anyone to anyone who's listened to those podcasts
Please do not simply import the biggest problem versus style of humor into the voicemails that you do come up with your own thing
Yeah, it's funny. I don't care. Well, there's this very specific style
I feel like some people might think it's just the default for voicemails. It is not it's just that universe
We have our own sense of humor. We were original around here. We don't want to get copyrighted
I
Happen to fancy myself quite derivative
I fancy myself quite the sketch charm if you will but I don't think I've said a funny thing in my life
So hashtag PCB voicemail begin immediately and and we will we're gonna review them
So you don't think you're gonna slip a fast one past us, but yeah, send them on Twitter
That's like the easiest way
Hashtag PCB voicemail use it the next voicemail is hey guys. It's me
I'm really glad you guys have endorsed me bombing the United States government
I guess we did I guess we did by playing this on our show. I guess reliable. Well
Okay, so that's happening keep more themes PCB theme hashtag PCB theme Twitter send us that shit
We're looking for it. Hashtag PCB voicemail. We're gonna be looking for that shit, too
That aside it's time for the fan art
Section of our program here fan art corner over the fan art corner hashtag PCP fan art PCP has such a visceral and
Voluptuous ass it is back heavy and it is like super bloated now. That's what this entire show is gonna be
Yeah, yeah, it's good. It's gonna be two hours of topic. It's gonna be eight hours, right?
Maybe at some point if it gets bloated enough
We'll just have like a like a bi monthly like fan response video. You know what I mean? Wait a minute wait a minute
PCP mail time
Guys, I there actually is another entrance in the PCP theme thing already
No, I mean this is from May 29th. I'd like I just searched for hashtag PCB fan art and this came up
Yeah, three days. Okay, let me let me get the fucking link. All right, hang on. Hang on. I will play it in the thing
How the fuck does this got no work? Please fucking? Okay? Okay. Here it goes. Let me fucking
Do the thing. I'm doing the thing. I gotta push the button
Play this go punk bitch motherfucker
I have AIDS
I
It's the PCP bitch
You know what I think that was maybe a little better as like an ending song I mean, yeah, the slower
Yeah, yeah, okay, I think I think the the do-do-do-do-do-do by the way be like while we're talking like and welcome to the procrastinators while
It's playing. I think that's so sorry. I forgot to say that is from at Peter John death pay PJD. There you go
So I can speak only for myself of the cheat sheet to getting a thumbs up on
OP
Entrance for me at least is what's in an OP Davoo. Tell us what's in an OP?
To bring Jeff back to help us judge
Join Jeff join that that server that got me fucking booted from this
OP reference I was thinking oh, how would I impersonate Jeff? I guess yell and have a lisp. Oh shit
That's already me. Anyway, so the way to get a thumbs up from me on your entry is focus on like really, you know
pour yourself over tone and
Catchy melody and like especially tone like what's the tone of an OP?
What's gonna like make you feel like yeah listening to an episode right now because honestly
I think there's very few podcast openings that make me that that feel right to me and don't put an emphasis possibly avoid
Like showing off how many random things what the PCP you know in your audio clips
Like I don't care how actually like dedicated level of a fan
You are of the group for as far as I'm concerned someone who just like has the right musical sensibility
But like has listened to like five episodes could very well be the one to decide to make the perfect theme
Sure, sure. I mean, yeah, I like the the little clips of stuff in there
But I guess I would say for a theme song
I mean, it's possible that one of us could fucking die or whatever
If that person was in the theme, I'm just saying I'm just saying right it's complicated
I'd go without it if I would I would almost never
Give the green light on a theme that has any audio clips like of us at all because I just I don't know
But I just agree. I think it's cool. I would never like I like the audio
Definitely almost certainly never hit the upvote on a theme that has like very clean
Not even altered audio clips because then it's like what am I already listening to the podcast?
It's just kind of like weird and dissonant for me
I mean that opening I think is like starting with Digi like come on Digi's fucking dead. We all know this. He's out
He's gone. This is just it's just weird to get
Voice in a podcast thing. I'm not into it
If you could get the voice of the PCP guy if you could interview PCP guy and get him to do the intro somehow
You know enter the anime land and we'll actually know
Does this back come on have an anime
Let's spend the the next eight minutes coming up with funny voices for the PCP guy
Hi guys, it's me the PCP guy
Oh, that's it. No, we can't do it. We got one and done baby. There we go
All right settled settled well true voice actor
So, I mean that was it so okay, so those two are the contenders right now
I gotta say between these two I'm leaning towards AJ because I just like the upbeat
Yeah, I really like both. I think for an opening. I think AJ's is more of an opening
I mean fuck why don't we we can fucking use the first one to open and the second one for closet?
We can use it all we can have it all
Yeah, rid of the original fucking son. We can get rid of the original. It doesn't have to be gone forever
I mean we could see I mean it's all it's like a million years old now
I mean, I would yeah that that first one that we listened to I would use that as the ED sometimes
That's as far as I would go
Well, there you go. There you go. Well, hey, we keep sending people where this this whole thing we're figuring out
We're role-playing sexually. We're gonna keep at it. Hey Victor. I bet you're glad that you stayed for this
I'm sure you have a lot to say and I'm glad I think you're bet that you're glad you're here. I
I am playing Fire Emblem Warriors
And listening to the PCP, which I would do anyway
Did you fucking hear the rumblings?
Did you hear the ground fucking shake with this drop cuz I'm about to tell you and the audience all about the greatest game of the
Fucking century is out right now. Jurassic World alive
Are you fucking serious? I'm coming in my pants. I know I'm the next all summer long
I'm gonna be running up and down the street pots and pans banging on my neighbors doors
Screaming for their first board and getting them to come out and play Jurassic World alive with me. I'm gonna be catching dinos
I'm gonna be running from the cops
And I'm gonna get that sweet ass
Sores up on my sore ass and it's gonna be sick as hell
Nice. I like the idea that playing a dinosaur catching game
Mean like like in the game. You also have to avoid the police
Oh, like oh, yeah, like a need for speed a cops and dinosaurs are dying
I'm actually more dangerous than a t-rex. This is the police commission
This is all real viewers click the show notes for it for some hot screen caps
Oh Jurassic World alive. It is fucking out and you better believe after the pockets. I'm gonna be running
Sprinting down the street cash in those fucking dino
It doesn't even look not it doesn't even look bad. I want to play. Oh, it's it's like a Pokemon go sword thing
It's a ripoff of Jurassic World alive
You know, this is this is very different
I see this is the real shit. This is like Victor you like you like look how Florida smells
You're like chlorine
It's chlorine and come the game
Yo, all right
Fan art corner. Here we go. There's there's slim pickings. There's slim pickings once again
I searched PCB fan art on the fucking
In Twitter and there's like nothing. We're still building up here
You know what there's infinite fan art of
Endless war every day is a fucking torrent
Day in day out. We're in the family because we care about them. It's a it's a vicious cycle
It's a vicious cycle. We have the lore people draw the lore people expand the lore through their art and then that becomes new lore
I am so fucking grateful for every single fan artist for the right. Okay, I'm going through
I'm going through the archives right now saving every fucking piece that has not been archa. I'm going to I'm gonna be fucking putting them up in the
Excellent
It's all precious. It's all precious and part of the culture
Like in like 10 years a fan who's like 11 years old right now is doing a lecture on a variety of cop killers to like his friends
You know I'm saying we're gonna do one ourselves or even fucking even fucking yeah
We got to beat that fucking kid to the punch. Well, okay. Here's the good news
But all right much finish your point finish your point
I'm not saying like like it's like nice to see fair just for the masturbatory like oh like here's my things
Remember people are doing an aren't I hot shit, but it's just like it's so nice to be like aware of the fact
You've made something that people like so much that they're willing to like waste their lives making stuff for it
Yeah, of course kind of like kind of like we wasted our lives making it in the first place. Yeah
Yeah, I mean ways exactly shout to no be retro pk and
Oh god
All right enough of this rowdy fuckers terrible bullshit. Here's the real deal
There is one submission and it is glorious by Simsie. This is a 100% accurate depiction of me
There is there he is
That it's basically a chibi baka it's pretty close. What is this pencil get out of here pencil we've
Digital only
It's not it's a really good drawing that is
He's got a picture here he should trace over this and computerize it and fucking digital art if I
Digital or otherwise
It's very solid to be in ASCII. They should be in ASCII
And when you put it into a coder it will actually play a video game the ASCII is actually code
You know you need it needs to have a fucking scan code so that you can scan and get best guy ever in Skylanders
Right, that's what this is
Fucking PCP amiibo
Oh my god, that's cut like in two days check the red bubble. Hey. Hey some some guys linked like like old fan art of
Like the the draw cast stuff
I don't know if now here's like the right place to show them cuz like we get a lot of still fan
I get a lot of dumps of draw cast stuff whenever a new draw cast comes out though
So like to show all of them in a PCP is
I'll tell you this yeah, we will show them on the draw cast themselves about that you fuck that's a good idea
That's a good idea silly disheveled popper. Yeah, good. Good. Thank you. All right. Well, that's literally it for today
There was one sketch
Guys hashtag PCP fan art on the Twitter. I know you're drawing it. I know you're drawing it
You're being a little shy you're being a little timid you don't want to show it because you want to get bullied by me
It's almost like as soon as we asked for it. It dried up. I mean to a degree to a degree
Yeah, cuz then they knew that we would actually be talking about it
Cuz then they knew you would actually be commenting on it and like and they know that like Ben might comment on it
And like Ben is like I mean I am also like most of us are pretty fucking like straightforward
Maybe like this sucks or like here's why you suck or here's what sucks about you. Are you saying that they're intimidated of me?
Yeah
I mean we started doing that we started doing the segment because we were getting like a lot
We're literally on D platforming them by giving them a platform by showing their shit
So you got you got nothing to lose people you got nothing to lose and everything to gain so
Like fucking fucking nexus just made like a bunch of like best guy ever art like well
He was doing is like me a math of a style challenge and it's fucking incredible
It's just like the animation he did like holy shit. It's because people aren't connecting with the podcast to connect
Yeah, individual hosts. I think that's it. I think that's it streams or I remain Ben from our right frickers cop killer series
It's interesting care about the PCP anymore. That's all yeah. Yeah. I mean, that's what I'm getting as well
But do it anyway, you know cuz we yeah cuz like rad cons don't happen enough like a rad con generated fan art
That's true. That's for sure
Um, right for when?
Soon radcon for ASAP. Yeah
All right, well, I guess that's it for that
But but it's time for everybody's favorite part of the fucking podcast. It's time for the Q&A
Like past like 40 bits have just been what's this? Oh, there's nothing. Oh, well enough of that. Here's this next section
What's in here? All right? Well, there are some things. There are some goddamn things. All right, you just shred
Shit. All right. Here we go. We're gonna we're good time to take a couple of questions. Let's see what the fuck we got lightning
This is a good one. This one for Vic that I've been wondering a lot at know you mate
Asks, why does Vic hate wearing shirts so much? I've been wondering that
Is it because you were all naked children when you were born?
Vic oh
He gone dead. Oh, I keep like sometimes I can't hear you guys for like 20 seconds
Maybe I guess just connection. I think you just died as well. Yeah
Okay, can you hear us Vic? Can you hear us? I don't ever know
We'll never fucking know why it's wearing shirts so much
I think just the Collins family are just naked children and they never stopped
No, no, actually I holly did you stomach while he was naked one time?
Okay, let's my pants were on guys my pants were on let's let's find another one here um
Okay, I guess here's one
Steel Viper 77 asks
Except steel viper among fan favorites
I by the way, I told everybody that vixx was here and that the subject was cooking just to see how we'd go and the question was
Uh, you you mean the I said that you mean that I fucking said no, I'm on the Twitter
I'm on the Twitter doing it not the fucking this is this from the this is the pity question
Among fan favorites from steel viper such as the Ben saint and the Chastity Fortress
What are some other iconic PCP recipes first of all?
What's the what's the Chastity Fortress the Chastity Fortress is the impregnable a hamburger recipe that I made the hamburger is this it is
It is a bun. It is a buffalo meat is a buffalo burger
That was the munchie. No, this is Chastity Fortress
It's a much better name. It's a money. It's a monument to my virginity
I treasure dearly
And all the buffalo burger there is pepper jack bacon and then you get witch's your sauce and a one-sauce and you drown it in it
Right last I heard this was the munchie, but what all right? I guess things change. Okay, there you go. There you go
um, I
Other is there any other iconic me? I mean the poor boy
I mean
No, the the Ben saint is
whole milk ice
juice from a from a bottle of
Maraschino cherries a couple of the cherries themselves and ice do you blend that you just mix it okay?
Okay, I mean you leave the cherries whole the chair. Yeah, okay
And the well, there's also the Ben my real name, which I don't even know why I'm not bothering to say because it's not even a secret
Whatever, it's a lame name anyway, but yeah, there's the real Ben or the fake Ben whatever you choose to believe
Who is the real Ben?
Hot coffee and chocolate protein powder
I had that decadent to even like like acknowledge as true because it will just kill you
Sometimes whatever I want to make a bin saying instead of having milk. I'll have orange juice. What?
But dude, but dude you been yeah, I actually
Why is that you they're both?
How is that right?
No, that's like the city. Yeah, I think it's with the cherry shit is it just sounds gross
I mean, there's no milk. So it's not gonna orange in it. Do you put the orange in in addition to the cherry or instead of the cherry?
No, right? No, no, no, no, no, yeah, both but there is no milk
There's no milk, but I gotta say I don't know if I've ever heard well, then that's just juicy fucking
Ever heard you describe the bin sainte before but I actually recently just like a couple weeks ago
Just like thought to put some chocolate protein powder in my coffee. So that's that's kind of
Dude one time I was elevated through the ceiling and I had to repair my roof because of this energy drink
I drank one time I
It was okay
I got a scoop of chocolate ice cream then I put in milk and like chocolate syrup
I mixed that around then I put in two like Starbucks a double shot energy drinks into it
I swirled it all around Jesus and I drank it and I could not stop I could not stop my wife asked me to stop
I
Um, I guess I guess that a fried Oreo with a with a Swedish fish flavored Oreo is is might be a Ben a Ben recipe
Uh
So yeah, I guess so I guess that would be called the red the red
Let me well that red stain
Do you remember my suit my Swedish fish addiction at anime expo? I do I do there was pictures of that and what not
Well, here's here's another recipe that Ben cooked up
I want to find what's another name for a recipe that would be Ben named
What can we give one real quick like the the Ben Jaman sandwich the this isn't well, okay
It's the I'm gonna call it a I'm gonna call it a
Because I'm gonna call it a so ugly this is a so ugly and what it is. It is it is you take you know your your plastic case of
Gummy vitamins and you melt it down into one solid puck. Yes, that's so
Congealed gummy vitamins. Yeah, it's not even bad. It tastes a little metallic tastes a little like blood
But it's quite delicious. Yeah, that's just your own mouth bleeding, but go on munchie
I have a recipe called Ben's soul and you get nacho cheese and beer you put in a crock pot and wait
And
You know, you know, you know it's soul eater how like everyone's soul looks like a certain thing and you can like see it like
That's what Ben's soul looks like looks like that goopy film that crusted dry acidic death Valley
You know cheese and beer melted crock pot
Victor can you hear us? I'm trying to connect I can't can you still hear me? Yeah, now I can hear you now
Yeah, okay. Well, did you have an answer the question from our boy about why you never wear a shirt or why you hate shirt so much
I didn't I didn't okay, so it was no you may ask why does Vic hate wearing shirts so much
That was a full question because shirts are hot and they fucking suck
Clothes are stupid, and I wouldn't wear any clothes if I didn't have to I
We're in a shirt right now
I'm so against this. I feel the exact opposite way where whenever I'm forced to be naked to take a shower
It's most uncomfortable like unpleasant experience of my entire life. I hate hat like I feel just defenseless
I feel like if some animal were to come up and fight me I would lose if I don't have my
I feel similarly it gives me like plus one defense. Why would I give that up? You know? Yeah? Yeah?
Being naked is not like fun. It's overrated. I don't yeah
I don't love being shirtless around other people sure sure fucking looking at like I hate attention
It's the same fucking thing ever and I hate all the comments about about me and and the fact that I'm sure yeah
Yeah, I also hate wearing a shirt because it makes me itchy and hot, and I'm always itchy and hot
Understandable throw them on but I'm more used to wearing no shirt than I am wearing a shirt
Actually, yeah, Victor you being around you with your shirt off is actually what motivated me to like stop fucking gay
So that I can become like as unbellied as possible so that I can one day like just not wear
Unbellied to say Finn right well
I didn't quite work because I wasn't losing weight the correct way
So I'm just like I want to fucking lose weight and like be somewhat fit just so that I can
Not have a shirt around a higher percentage of society
It would be fantastic, but even Victor here who's who's
Significantly fit still doesn't generally not wear a shirt unless he's like at home
I'm not nervous around people
I'm just
In here when I said I just make people uncomfortable and don't give a shit
Like I don't mind not wearing a shirt around people
But it obviously depends on who it is when it's a hot day
I'll usually just like wear like a Hawaiian shirt open and that and no shoes and that that that feels good
I like it. I like no shoes. No socks or shoes. Oh, yeah
I'm coming right from California and wearing shirt is just like what to do. Yes sandals
I'm wearing flip-flops every day when I come home. It's a ritual. I take off my shoes
Take off my socks. That is ultimate pleasure that put on my sandals, and it feels great
I also take off my pants, but I'm yeah, and the reason I feel up there
The reason I feel like wearing no shoes is okay
But like being naked is kind of you feel defenseless is because like when
When you walk on your feet a lot
They get tough they get the skin gets feels tough and you stop like yeah, you know if you walk on rocks a
lot then you
Will not get hurt get hurt so much with with don't wear a shirt a lot
Then you toughen up like your skin and you become like you become like the thing
You're like made of cement around your whole body, you know
I'm not saying that that's what's happened what will happen
But if you have like toned muscles, and you feel like your skin is tough
It will feel you will feel like you already have like padded armor on yeah, okay rather rather than be like a weak like easily
Pissable
I feel like also it like even though the feet your feet and like legs are probably the limbs you're like maybe
Least in control they feel the most powerful, and they feel like the things that you could most easily attack someone with
So you put your legs. They're weird. Yeah, your legs are your most powerful weapon
That's true except for your cock of course can't beat the cock, you know
Well, that has that's why it's physical and psychological
She was single combo. It's that's true. Look out everyone duck down here comes a question from line slimes
What would you change about your upbringing literally get castrated and that is not a joke
But your testosterone levels though, they'll fucking plug
Okay, if I just be a barra and have no dick that would be my ultimate dream, okay, okay here
You know what I would have had more money
Okay, what if but why what if you could you could get your dick chopped off and keep your balls having more money well
Everything easier and you don't have to do. Yeah, I disagree money
Everything is easy. I fundamentally disagree. No libido and just like it have enough you in phase me
That would have made my life so much better. I would have
Yes, having no libido. I think is what he's going for I would have want to have been poorer and
Live in a more packed environment, so I could have interacted with more people so that I could
Become like a like like like fucking like Steve Jobs his dad was like a Syrian immigrant and
Like I don't think they were very well off at the time, you know, I haven't fucking looked at the point
The what I'm just reading here is a tale of like when you're poor and it makes you scrappy and resourceful
And you become a man faster
It's not a fucking rule it just it is the thing about that is like when it when it works out
It is such an unexpected thing that it becomes an event that people talk exactly exactly hippo
Yeah, that's what I was gonna say like like it doesn't actually do that like sometimes
Someone can become scrappy and escape from poverty, but that's the exception and like it's notable because it doesn't happen
Right poor and being underprivileged is not like yeah a thing that like separates the week from the yeah
It is a thing that makes people weak and disenfranchises them
This is yet another like future podcast
I'm just gonna like gut right now, which is the whole mentality of things going wrong can then be good
It's like no things being good is good now. I know challenges. No fuck you guys
You don't know what you're talking about
You're right
It's when people try to rationalize pain and suffering by saying what makes me stronger
Here's the thing though if you don't have to actually shit if you don't have if you don't have to have pain
We're at least not as much right you can still choose to get strong through your own will now
I know there's plenty of people who will end up in why are you rich people so much more depressed
It's because they have too much shit. I don't work hard. I don't trust any statistics that say as much and I do
I'm pre-emptively saying I don't know stats on that and like so here's the thing right
I got some stats. Let's say there are like there is a scenario where people probably get diagnosed with depression more often because
I have more free time to put this way
There's four scenarios right there's people who suffer and as a result they keep suffering and they become shitty people because they've
Never had time to grow then there's people who suffer and then make something of themselves become excellent individuals. They they emerge from that
That disparity from that difficulty and they become great then there's people who don't have to suffer and then don't become particularly
Remarkable people at all. That's the third scenario the last one is people who don't have to suffer and become great
Which do exist not every billionaire walking the earth today in their mega yachts was actually poor like you know like Bill Gates was not poor
Right he wasn't like a billionaire
But he had like access to a fucking computer way before most people did and he made even more out of it
That is the ideal scenario that you can actually become good because you want to become good because like what I see for most people most of my
peers the the classic stereotypical millennials who don't know what to do with themselves generally in
Proportion to how fucking like stunted they've been or hurt. They've been by shit not by how much stuff they have
All right, this does completely irrelevant because it doesn't matter. No one's asking you why you would be less privileged
It's a question for each of us individually. I answered my fucking question here by saying that like
Well, you don't know this is totally not irrelevant. You don't know my fucking life the point is I
Grew up with you. Yeah, I'm talking to DeVue
The point is when I got to be a certain age
I figured out that I needed to work hard to get stuff
I just didn't fucking figure that out until I was like 23 and if I had figured that out sooner
I think my life would have been better. That's my whole point. So
Yeah, that's true like you need like a you need like a push you see because I don't think my family's as well off as yours
Is is I had that I had basically the exact same thing and it was a push when I was like 18
So, yeah, that was very advantageous to me. You're right. Well, that's what I'm saying
Maybe that's my only point. Maybe you're fucking right
Maybe I have the same kind of mentality as you I had to just get pushed
It was just a little bit of a nudge and then I was fine from then on out
I think everybody needs to get well a lot of people the pushing doesn't work the pushing becomes shoving and then it becomes
struggling well
It's it depends on the type like if you always have a good like if you if your parents say you should get a job
We're gonna get you out
I think if you're the type that's gonna work hard and realize that you need to work hard to achieve your goals
I think yeah, but that will that's gonna happen pretty much. Yeah
You're saying that it's all having more money is just gonna make you better poise to accomplish
Well, but you're just saying that it's all nature and no nurture and I don't agree with that
I don't think it's all nature. Okay. All right. All right. So I think what would probably because it's hard for me to say like
How would it change by upbringing without it being a change to like individual people or like I'm trying to think of like
Living situations and not people situations because there's a million ways I could think about people and interactions
But like life style wise. Yeah, I would say if I were to like go use a time machine to turn me into more of a fucking art
Monster I would say that my family somehow becomes extremely dead broke around the time
I'm like 12 so the point that I have to like get a part-time job when I'm 14
And therefore I would get the same push I got but like four years earlier
Yeah, and that would give me a little bit of an advantage
Otherwise, I can't really say because I'm really scared of like well obviously I want to be in an environment where I had lots of friends
I'm like, but if I had friends growing up
I might have never become anywhere near the person I am now and therefore would never like have any of the same thoughts
I mean, it's in theoretically possible. You might have just become a way better person
I wouldn't become a better person. You would definitely not be you though
So it's basically saying that DeVoo would not exist. Right. Is that a plus?
I would have changed that like my father would smash
Destroy my shins with a 2x4 every day to strengthen them so that I could
Like you mean like break them or something or like yeah smash
Yeah, that guy that guy got it all figured out. I wish I was retarded. I wish I was autistic and retarded
You know that means that you need to be mentally retarded as well so you can run really fast
Oh, so that's what worked well for Forrest Gump. That's what worked out for him. He wasn't retarded
He was just a little slow learned differently
What I like about removing my libidos that they probably would not change who I become in the sense that like I would probably still be in the PCP
I just would have experienced less pain in my life. That's probably true
Yeah, I mean having a little sex drive is kind of hell
In general just in general
Well, that's that there was another question. There was another pity question that I thought was
Yeah, that was pretty good. Who was that again? Who is that question from again? That is from Lines Lines
Not bad killer not bad slayms. Yeah. Yeah confirm killer a
Confirm killer. Oh, that's good. Here's a here's a question from Never Paint. All right
This is listen to the whole question before you respond, please
It is uh, do you eat dried nasal mucus? What are your thoughts about it? Listen? Listen delicious disgusting
It seems to be a very divisive topic
Where I feel like this question is some kind of statement, but I don't know what the statement is this man is telling me
Never paint here is saying that like there's a there's a hotly debated
It's a contested issue whether or not it's good to eat and dried nasal. I guess he means boogers
Yeah, it's when it's dry it's disgusting and you got to get rid of it. It's like eating a
Ironic joke well
I know I know that some people eat their own like they they they eat snot because it's in their throat
Well, that's fine. I mean, what can you do? I mean if it doesn't come out of your mouth then swallowing it is not eating it
If in the in the past make any sense in the past
I have no idea what anyone would do that. I don't understand us at all or relate to us at all
What I don't know right that nothing to say however now my fiancee does in fact do this
She has all sorts of tics like she knows she's like, you know like she's like
She eats her like nails too, right? I'm like, you have to
I mean, I mean, do you eat them? I mean, no, I don't I clip my nails
So I don't get biting them that sounds like hell and then she also eats them. I'm like what the what and then like
I don't eat the nails. I
Like I like bite my nails
Yeah
I'm too. I'm like what the fuck and then she gets whenever she's whenever she eats her boogers
I'm like why she's like a it's actually a lot of nutrients. It's actually like good for your immune
Oh
You got the fucking excuse
This is rich proteins
I mean, I recycle my semen, you know
The reason why I don't think about it much is that it's not even like in the top tier of like like tics nervous
She hasn't like
She pops pimples, but she also wants to pop my pimples it's therapeutic for her to pop my pimples now
Someone who pops my pimples unless it's in the state
Hold on. I mean if you have a pimple, what are you gonna do but pop it?
Yeah, I just leave it like that goes away and then wash my face fucking better and have a better diet, right?
Well, why would you not pop it?
Well, I only pop it when it's in like an annoying spot like on like ear or like it's right next to my nose
Why would you not pop it because it hurts fucking hurts you?
All right, and then like it hurts. I guess I have a low pain threshold
I think I think I have like sensitive skin and shit, right guys. Do we have to talk about this?
Can we get away from this?
I'll be like laying in bed.
Wait, this is a pimple popping contest now!
All right, all right, and I'll be like laying in bed and she's like oh hold on you got an acne right here
And I'm just like fucking screaming because sometimes they like really really really fucking hurt and like her
This is a nightmare.
She's got very...
Yeah, this is... this is dark.
She's got very different skin for me like her skin is very tough
Like just to be able to scratch an itch, she does a level of scratching that would like leave my skin red afterwards, right?
So that was one of the things we had to get used to was our very different like she'll just like
Hey, when we're gonna like dry off your back with a towel and she'll like do it so hard to like fucking give me rug burns
Like no, no, no my skin is like way thinner than yours. So like for her acne doesn't really hurt that much to pop
I've taken my headphones off.
But it's super fucking like hurts to have I guess like it's just annoying for her to have it so she constantly has to pop it
So like yeah, like there'll be times where I'm like
Just like hey, let me pop this pimple and I just fucking scream. She's like why are you using a baby?
I'm like it hurts.
I missed it. I missed a DeVoo.
When I'm walking down the street playing Jurassic World Alive to him
I'm walking out with my cane and all these fucking whores and Jezebel's throwing themselves at me
Oh, can I pop your pimples? Oh, can I eat your boogers? It's just so fucking taxing. So you have to walk down the street
I have to worry about that. No, no, you fucking succulent bitches. No, those boogers are from my own
Those pimple puzzles are from my own steaks and garnishes
You're not good to have my delicacies. I lost my appetite
Cooking has been
This day, it's it's well, it was a fucking question askers fault. No, I mean this true
I guess it was my fault for choosing but whatever doesn't matter. Anyway, let's go back with a fucking lounge pick some real questions
I have one. Okay. All right. I think this could be the last one, which I quite like I think you guys might think it's retarded
But I like my chipmice win. What's your food?
Sona if you were an item, what would oh avocado rice?
all right, I
Would be something they would be a cheap Jim Ben would be a slim. I think I'd be now
I think I'd be a paw paw what the fuck is up. I got a look this is a PAW like PAW. I think
Is it PAW? Okay, I see it. I would just be an avocado. That'd be my my thing. Yeah
You're very you're very millennial
Yeah, no, I would be something cheap
Yeah, I would be I would be like
You're something cheap mysterious and you don't know why you're eating it, but you are and this is your life now
All right, I got mine. I would be
Delicious mashed potato with onion gravy. That's pretty good. That's not bad
I was thinking I'm soft and deli
That works like
I hate fucking white gravy white gravy sucks brown gravy is awesome. I
Hmm, what I'd be I feel like it'd be some sort of meat product
Protein shake, I mean a protein shake. Yeah
There's people who are way more protein shake people protein shake with raw meat in it. You know what I'd be
I know what I would be my classic drink. Oh, I'm calling this. This is the Nate best man
It is water
Chocolate protein powder and fruit punch creatine. I'm drinking. I'm drinking Nate best man's every day
They're the worst tasting thing in the world
But they have nutrients that I want in my body so I consume them
Send me a picture on my Twitter at bestest guy ever of you drinking a Nate best man, please go buy your creatine
Nobody's
There's gonna be some lifters out there who already have it around fruit punch creatine chocolate protein powder and water
There you go. That's what I am
That the ultimate the utilitarian snack. That's what it is
It's hard to think what kind of food I would be cuz I don't know like it's not like what food you like
It's like what food like like in
I mean you do resemble a stacked hamburger quite a bit in most ways
Like you would be a fruit hamburger. Are they what are they quirky?
Yeah, you you would be a like a burger, but with like candy
I was I know what munchie would be munchie would be what appears to be a burger
But when you bite into it you find out that each layer is assembled from different pieces of doughnuts to deceive you
You know think
Children one sex dreams. Wait, wait. What did we munchie if he was a food
He would be that like doughnut burger that we once had
Made of it honey do that's right. They made it is like a joke and we ate it for real
There's a restaurant boss boss burger company that I like and they have a bunch of weird like retarded like novelty burgers
One of them is like a burger with like a ton of like honey on it. I would probably be that okay, dude
Yeah, I guess to like add in a random like cooking comment
I have an idea for a breakfast burger. I've done which is bagel for the bun
You still have a hamburger right right and you have cheese and egg and then maybe like mustard or something like that
Just breakfast burger, you know, it's great shit
I don't know I've not been to restaurants that have that necessarily
Well team I remember when you made breakfast
Oh, yeah, Tom's here. Yeah, I get to be a food. Oh, I forgot
I guess my food would be I don't know. I think you'd be like a bag of fun
I
Yeah, I can't remember the last time I've had it fun
All right. Wow. Just like I know I can remember you Tom because you're not
Yeah, I was meant to say Tullaby a garnish forget that he's there and they
Only because he's not speaking up enough
You've been banished Victor, what's your favorite question?
I'm a I am a general sauce chicken because I'm sweet and spicy
And completely inconsistent
This is the first time of the original spicy bro as are all back together again
You're original spicy
We made it. Well, we were all there at Radcon three. Oh, we were we were technically all the guy
Have you seen the spiced a bro pat? Have you seen that video?
Which which one is like the one with me you and Ben? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, of course. Yeah. Yeah
Legendary beautiful
Please for all time sakes on the counter you can get a spicy bros all three of us. What about us?
We're also spicy bros. We were at Radcon original. These are original. Yeah, you're right. I guess I just don't fucking matter that
Second one didn't count spicy
Bro, I'm a spicy
You're
That's true. Yeah. Yeah, I'm a fucking it. Oh, yeah
Back to you coming at soon looking forward to it. All right, that's where we're concluded the end of questions the end of everything
Thanks, all over the questions everybody
All right, so that's our that's it. We're done with all our bullshit now
We must simply say patreon.com slash the procrastinators. It simply must be done
So that you will give us the money so that $1 you're in our fucking patron chat. That's fine on discord
$5 you get all
15 bonus episodes that are currently out. There's a new one out right now
It is sitcoms motherfucker by the time you hear this the sitcoms PCP will assuredly be out
We haven't even heard it yet, but I'm sure it's going to be the best one by far. I have no doubt
That's a bold claim, but it's sticking with it
But the fortune other episode so fuck you you got plenty of shit there
What do we got at TP Crasneers on Twitter?
Announcements and all that shit
Hashtag ask PCP we announce on Saturdays we record to get the questions in there
I'm sure they know where but where can they find you? Yes, please you got it
Yeah, I'm on Vic and hope on YouTube is Vic and hope forever with the let's play show
But it's really a podcast and everyone should go watch Vic and hope because nobody watches it
All true and every day a new Vic and hope comes out the good digi bros gets
Pushed out further and further into the past one day one day we'll unearth it and it'll be redeemed
Yeah, please soon everybody
All right, well that's it anything else. Oh, and of course everybody don't not forget, please hashtag PCP theme
Make us theme songs play them on the show. We're at a contest. It is a real contest. I swear. Believe me
We you know you're two more two entries now, so it's real. It is really it is actually officially real
There is a competition going on now
hashtag PCP fan art to fucking get out in the fan art part and
That's literally it. Thank you for being here everybody good fucking and again. Thanks to Victor for being here
It's been a pleasure, dude ever since radcon three now. We didn't even say at the beginning
I should have said fucking Victor is a cameraman to the stars
He was the one who recorded all the important shit that was filmed at radcon. It was incredible
It was stupendous all the radcons every rad that that's true. Everyone. He's been fucking there. He's he's definitely a
Brony con not
Inaccurate damn right damn. That's old school. He's in the fucking horseshoe crew basically to the sky. This guy is the real
He's real. He is real. He is not fake quote quote from Brony con era munchie. I did not touch the kids as
by Victor
And
Wait, was that Victor? Oh, yeah, there will be links in the description to Vic stuff as well
So check them out. By the way, did you brother? Did we mention that? Did we mention that?
Oh, that doesn't matter. Who cares that doesn't matter. One of the digi bros. That's not that I don't care about
Divorce my purse my my content from his so that my audience will actually have more than like 300 people in it
Understandable
All right, everybody. Thanks for being here. We'll see you soon. It's been a wonderful fucking time
I
Don't wanna do