A boy was wandering far from home with his loyal growlith, Growly.
They were both freezing and they hadn't eaten in days.
Growly, I'm not going to make it.
Leave me alone and save yourself.
Oh.
The angels have come for me.
Farewell, I leave this cruel world for a better place.
Remember me, Grow...
Ugh.
Growl...
Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Yay!
Yeah, we're back.
We're back.
Even better than it was the last time, baby.
Mm-mm-mm.
I'm good and we're back.
And it is me, the best guy ever, joined by a whole cast of deplorables.
First up, we got...
A whole nation of them.
A whole nation of...
A whole nation of basket.
A basket, that's right.
That's the one.
So hey, there's Digibro over there.
Hey, what's up buddy?
Over there is Ben Saint.
Yeah, that's me. That's me.
We got Lethal Aurora Mage.
I'm back.
With a much improved mic to my delight.
Oh, that's right.
That's right.
Here's Hippocrite.
Gotta catch a mole.
Yeah.
And, uh...
Throw me off there.
And, uh, uh, Monkey Jones.
Well, if it isn't that motherfucker Ben Saint.
You son of a bitch.
Now, but before things get too crazy here.
My mortal enemy.
Fucking hate this bastard.
Now, hang on guys.
We have to establish this.
This is an official...
I'm sputtering with rage.
Sputtering, I tell you.
This is an official government sanctioned safe space.
This is a safe space between the nations of Ben Saint and Monkey Jones.
Have you provided Legos and Play-Doh for constructive, non-critical play?
I need a coloring book, dude.
That's right.
There are looping videos of cute puppies and cats.
So don't fret.
I'm allergic to cats.
You're free to excuse yourself.
Monkey hates dogs.
This is triggering.
You're triggering.
Whee!
I hate being relaxed.
I hate not being triggered.
It triggers me.
Oh, no.
What do we do?
All right.
Well, okay.
Now that's out of the way.
So, so this is, uh, uh, quite a fortuitous time to be alive.
Cause as you know, folks, uh, if you're not already following the glorious battle
between Ben Saint and Monkey Jones.
Actually, we haven't seen your battle yet, have we?
It hasn't gotten to that point yet.
It has not aired yet.
It'll be out on December 1st, I think.
Yeah, it's really December 1st.
Okay, so that's it.
It's coming.
Um, yes.
Well, that'll, that'll be hype as fuck anyway.
So we're here to celebrate not only their great battle, uh, but, but the,
the field upon which that battle is taking place, the release of Pokemon Sun and Moon.
The new, new, that's the, that's the hot topic.
Yeah.
I mean, it's hot for me.
It's hot.
But it's called for monkey because he's using these moon instead of sun.
Yeah.
Yes.
So let's, uh, we're going to talk about, about Sun and Moon and our thoughts on it
and stuff, um, and also Pokemon in general.
And then I think we'll probably spend more time on that because a lot of the things
that I personally have to say about Sun and Moon are specifically in the context
of the whole series and how kind of just ways that they could be improved
or my personal vision for what it could be.
And I'll be interested to hear what you guys all have to say.
So who's got a hot opinion about Sun and Moon?
I got a hot opinion.
I got to say that I've thought a lot about it and I see the pros.
I see the good points of Pokemon Ride.
I really do.
There's some things about it that I like, but overall I hate it.
About Pokemon?
Pokemon Ride.
Oh, Ride.
Like, like I get the advantage.
Oh, come on, you fucking baby.
No, you're the baby.
You're not even a human.
Get out of here.
It's OK.
It is kind of cool, but all right.
Just OK.
Everyone's like, oh, now now there's no more HMS.
Thank God.
Now we can just ride them.
I mean, I've complained about HMS before and I didn't like them.
But but the chains that they have made, they didn't fix them in the way I wanted
them to, I wanted them to fix them in a way that made Pokemon feel more like real
things that like I have.
Wanted it to be like your Pokemon can just surf if they're a water Pokemon.
You don't have to.
Right.
They made it even less like that.
Now no Pokemon can surf.
No Pokemon that you catch.
Can you ride on now?
Only this one lapras.
Yeah, but can you imagine that actually going to the process of having every
water Pokemon have its own sprite?
How are you going to ride on your tent to cruel?
What's that going to look like?
I don't.
It doesn't matter.
Yeah, it would be easy.
Here's where you're fucked up, Ben.
Go ahead, Hippo.
Well, I can imagine it being easy if they just if they just swap out a model of
like the idle animation for like for swimming.
I mean, you know what that look like?
You know what that look like?
You know when I was just using my two cannon who's using his his Z attack of
which is another topic that we can talk about.
But like when he does his Z attack, it's it's sort of a generic
like he's just doing an idle animation.
He's put through this big.
He's put through this big sort of attack thing.
But the thing is he flies up and he dives down to do this attack.
He is a perfectly stationary bird with his wings folded at his sides.
While he is doing this attack, it looks ridiculous.
It looks.
It doesn't have you seen that one of way Lord doing the like the spin attack?
No, I think did you didn't you retweet it?
Is it the steel one or something?
I have no idea.
There's I don't know.
Yeah, because it was some weird music.
The point is this way.
He just does this incredible like fucking disco spin.
It's like it's a whale.
Well, that sounds awesome.
OK, but my point is just that I think that practically if they did some sort of
generic like use a ride animation thing, it would it would be similarly.
Well, for water, I think it could work.
I don't think it could work for ground type because they wouldn't be moving.
Yeah. And here's where Ben fucked up.
I think the reason why he doesn't like this is because you picked the male
character, the female character when you ride a Pokemon.
She like puts on different outfits.
And when you're surfing in particular, you get to see her mid rift.
It's really fucking cute.
I mean, I mean, I do think that the Taurus riding uniform is pretty dumb looking.
I don't like it.
But they're all you surf as a girl, dude.
All right.
You haven't even gotten to you haven't even gotten to when you get Machamp
and you get to be you get to be cradled.
Oh, my God, I was going to say Machamp.
It's like the creative.
It literally princess carries you.
Someone should go to jail for including that.
I was going to that part.
Yeah, what the fuck did he?
Well, I think differently from you.
I don't think of the ride Pokemon as a replacement for HM.
But that's what they are.
That's what they are.
They are, but rather than that,
what's cool about them is that they're a replacement for like the fucking bicycle.
You know, like you can play in Pokemon for all this time and you've been riding
a bike as opposed to a Pokemon like it just like I see the Taurus as hey,
instead of a bike for getting around quickly, now you get to ride a Taurus and
like charge through shit and is way cooler, you know, ride on a Taurus.
But I just don't see why it had to be only a Taurus.
I don't understand why because they would have had to build models for every
thing.
There is there is a third option.
It's not the models, it's the animations.
There is a third option here.
They could do some sort of like for all this time.
You're the one crying.
The Pokemon company can't afford to fucking do it.
You know, I don't know.
They make this game so cheaply and they cut so many fucking corners.
Like, I mean, with this game and this is maybe Nate will comment on this as well.
This vision for what the Pokemon games should be.
And I sort of addressed this in my own video that like I think the funniest
thing about Pokemon is that even though there's like this,
there's very complex systems in place, like I think probably most of the time
they spend making the game goes into just balancing it.
But like if you look at any other RPG, there's so much more complex with what
like NPCs are doing, dude, you know, where you've got games like fucking
Xenoblade where like every NPC has an entire life and like they're only around
at certain times a day.
You know, the number one representation of that,
the number one thing that tells me that is just the facial animation of your
character, which is to say there is none.
There is exactly one expression and it never, ever changes.
It honestly is the worst thing about the entire game.
It pissed me off so many times.
Stop smiling. Stop fucking smiling.
Actually, I kind of disagree because of the fact that I was my character was
wearing sunglasses and I really liked the idea that my character was just so
disaffected that nothing mattered.
I got the impression that my character was like, I'm so powerful and like none
of this matters to me.
Like when they attack me, I'm just going to beat them.
I'll give you that.
Getting those sunglasses was a massive upgrade to my enjoyment of this game
because those vacant, soulless eyes staring at me every fucking second of every cutscene,
no matter what was happening, not a fan.
I just enjoy it.
I hear people praising the ride system and like, yeah, I do think it is.
I think that what it lets you do is cool.
But the fact that it has moved away from like a relationship you form with your
Pokemon, it's it's the opposite of what I wanted.
And overall, I really hate it.
And I really think that people are being or just fucking letting Nintendo off the hook
for this one. I think they have the fucking resources.
They could animate.
They could animate every, they could animate all 700 Pokemon in a riding
animation if they wanted to.
They could do it.
Why don't they do it?
But everyone is just like, everyone's happy with this.
I don't disagree, Ben.
We should not be happy with it.
This is not good enough.
When it comes to Pokemon, like if I got everything I wanted out of it,
it would be a totally different game.
It would like every, I mean, every generation, like when Pokemon X and Y came out,
it had tons of problems with the fact that like it was 3D graphics.
The level design didn't make sense with the 3D graphics.
There was chugging and slow down.
It was not optimized well for the console.
This game was not optimized.
It's a nightmare.
It is like every valley just doubles battles.
It's a shiny new 3DS XL just very recently.
And it lacks for me on double battles.
That's weird.
There you go.
Yeah, yeah, it's even on the new one.
So double battles are still laggy.
In X and Y, it was even worse, though.
Even normal battles could lag if you had too many big Pokemon.
I'm not quite done with the ride thing.
I'm not quite done ranting about ride.
I just have one ride cake, which is simply that I have one more point to make.
In X and Y, they upgraded to 3D and it was like there was a whole ton of problems.
And the way that people talked about it, anytime you brought up the 3D,
like how these, you know, there's all these graphical failings,
people would always say, well, it's the first Pokemon game in 3D.
So there's bound to be some stumbling blocks.
But it's not the first 3D game ever.
1995, it's not.
Yeah, it's not like they had to invent 3D and like, you know,
they should have just held off if they didn't understand the principles of how
the graphics work, then they should have held off until they did before they released the game.
And I do think like Sun and Moon shows a lot of lessons learned from X and Y
about how to 3D, but then like, still, it feels like Pokemon makes progress
so incredibly slowly and the fans are just kind of used to it because I mean,
people have complained about HMS for fucking 20 years now and it just now finally got changed.
So not enough.
I'm honestly surprised that they changed it because I felt like no one was really
mad about it the way I was mad about it.
I've heard people complain about it all the time.
Were you?
Yeah.
Well, I'm not the vocal about my anger, I guess.
OK, OK.
The thing about Riot, here is a compromise that I would be willing to live with.
And everyone's going to hate this, but this is a compromise that I would accept.
If it were exactly the way it is now in Sun and Moon only,
you had to catch a Taurus and have it in your party to do the thing.
If you had to catch a Sharpedo, if you if you just if it's like
hey, you can't you can't ride around with our Taurus, here's how this compromise
will work for me, because I think the problem with that is that I would hate
it would only be the one, but but even if it were only the one, I would still
think it would that is that it would force you to have it in your team.
And that's why I know it would be obnoxious.
I know it would be obnoxious in the pain and then I'm going to give you a solution to that.
I want that.
I'm going to give you a solution to it, though.
I don't maybe I don't want solutions.
Maybe I just want to think about what if it's actually what if you can catch
a Taurus, hold on, I want to do my solution.
What if you can catch a Taurus and assign it as the ride Pokemon and then you
don't have to have it in your party, you just use it for rides.
Yes, OK. Yeah.
Yeah. As long as it's the one you caught.
Yeah. Ben, we do Nuzlocke.
So you if you didn't have a water Pokemon, you could literally just not be able
to progress in the game at some point.
Yeah. Yeah. So why would you like that?
That's fucking stupid.
What is that already? You just have to make sure you just have to make sure you
catch a water Pokemon.
It is already true.
I mean, I've always thought that probably provides you an area where to catch
the Pokemon you need anyway. So.
Well, yeah, but with Nuzlocke, nothing is nothing's guaranteed.
But like that, you just have to be careful and just make sure I'm going to need
a water Pokemon.
This is kind of a tangential point.
But I always thought it'd be reasonable in something like a Nuzlocke to to catch
a Pokemon specifically just to advance beyond a certain point.
And then you don't let it go or whatever.
Why would that be cheating? Why is that if the game is like if.
I don't know if the game have to have a water Pokemon to let you progress,
then maybe, I don't know.
I mean, I think that if you if you're all your surfers die,
then I think it's fun to be like, well, I can't win now because I let all my
surfers die. I think that's cool.
But by the way, let me just say about the ride thing.
I basically agree with you guys, which almost happened to me in white, too.
But anyway, yeah, I did.
I have one left.
I definitely am leaning on your side here, Ben.
I think I consider it a massive loss to lose the kind of personal connection
you have by using a Pokemon that you personally have captured and trained in
whatever degree that you have.
I consider a huge loss to not have that kind of connection with the thing.
Instead of some sort of like corporatized, like mass bred Pokemon like who gives a shit?
I feel I just I like that they're trying a new thing.
But I feel like it went in the exact opposite way that I wanted it to.
I wanted I want the games to demand
that like I I harness the power of my Pokemon.
Yeah, and that's the and that's not at all what's going on here.
Even though I think it's cool, it's cool to ride around on the Lappers.
It's cool to ride around a Sharpedo and and be and be cradled in the strong
manly bosom of a champ.
Yeah, there's a Sharpedo later, but my favorite guy.
It's radical. It's riding the Sharpedo was fucking dope.
It's my favorite thing.
Can we move on from ride Pokemon?
I want to say one more thing.
OK, I from for my part, I'm satisfied.
OK, I generally agree with you about the whole thing.
And I would and I think it would be cool if you could, you know, catch your own
rideable Pokemon and stuff, but this ride function, as it is now,
it kind of endeared me to a few Pokemon I didn't particularly like or didn't
usually use on my team, like Stealthon.
I don't particularly like Stealthon, but then I got one and I started riding it
and it's just kind of so cute when it sniffs the ground and I was so happy
when it finds the item. It's I kind of like it now.
Yeah, I can see that.
I consider that a small game, though.
And I think I don't think there's any negatives to the ride system.
And I think you're all fucking insane.
Stop talking about it, because it's been 15 fucking minutes to talk about the ride system.
If there were maybe if there were maybe a dozen different Pokemon.
This is what my fear was about this podcast.
Yeah, let's do a Pokemon podcast with six people.
That was like any one tiny thing you could say about Pokemon, we could do a whole
podcast. Yeah, they could like they could animate a dozen different Pokemon.
All right, Ben. All right, we get it.
I want to say I want to say that the Pokemon rights is not about writing,
but it is about animation.
I got a grubbin and I evolved him into a fucking battery bus little guy.
He's a cuboid. I love him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, but he for some reason, he can learn.
He can learn acrobatics, which is a flying move.
Yeah. And I and I kept that with him.
So now he is is basically a little bus
that flies through the air and beats the shit out of him.
That is awesome.
Oh, speaking of animations, did you know that some Pokemon can high five you?
Huh? What? How?
Yeah, like friendship all the way up or just no one.
No, no, no, all you have to do is like
was I think starters have this except for Rala because he doesn't really he can't
really high five you. But basically, like if you hold your
mouse, I said, I'm sure mouse and whatever cursor, yeah, near them,
they kind of start pawing at it.
And you hold them close enough near them, not on them.
And they start pawing at it.
Only some Pokemon can do that.
And if you're close enough, they kind of high five you because they can reach
your cursor, you're talking about when you're doing like the combing thing.
No, yeah, yeah, yeah, in general.
Yeah, yeah, in the Pokemon refresh thing.
Yeah, yeah, that's cool.
That's pretty neat.
Oh, and like let's talk about I give give tip
me out to a bunch of the little touches, like if you spin your character a bunch,
they just do a twirl.
Yeah, let's talk about the main improvement that Sun and Moon offers,
which is the twirl. The twirl is I love the twirl.
Honestly, my opinion of this game was as if you were following my Twitter was
extremely low going in and then it got steadily better because the game,
like it front loads all the bad bullshit and then it gets much better because it
just lets you play.
I think I caught my first Pokemon, like half an hour in.
It was two hours.
It was at least another half an hour before I caught another one.
The opening. I don't know why people think it's too long.
It's really fucking long.
It's really bad.
Well, you know why? OK, you know why.
There's a very simple reason for why it was so long.
It's because the every cutscene and there are a billion of them in the beginning.
I haven't even deployed content that it's and by that,
I mean that like the lead in to like the thing, like they have to fade in and like
set the scene and then like all the transitions.
But there's so much about that because it makes me care about the world and
characters. I don't even I don't even think it was bad.
They were about an actual RPG almost.
But the first island took me eight fucking hours.
Yeah, that means you play slow.
If it's the full island.
Well, yeah, I'm just saying that it takes it takes you.
All right. I mean, OK, so not everybody has to agree.
But I think that this game continued a trend.
I don't like of taking things like loading up too much bullshit.
You have to sort through until you can actually just play the game.
And this was the worst defender of the actually just to jump back to what
monkey said. I mean, you said the first island took you eight hours.
But that's a fourth of the game.
That's not a four.
The first island does not have the same.
The first island is only one of the seven challenges.
It's seven. Yeah.
But well, yeah.
But the other challenges don't have three hours of cutscenes before them.
So like you've played like you've played a fourth of the runtime of the game
at this point, like if you're off the first island, you know, it's the game.
40 hours, you know, it was bullshit that you guys, I think, liked, you know,
that ceremony, that piece of shit, retarded ceremony where your Pokemon that you
chose chooses you back.
Oh, yeah, I really feel, I really feel special being chosen by this Pokemon
that has no option by this cutscene.
Feels right. Yeah, I've been chosen by this cutscene.
Yeah, I was a little dumb.
OK, I like the game.
I'm babing you guys, you guys.
It's a fucking Pokemon game.
I don't know if you've noticed the plots of these games and really are going to
help us at some point.
My argument is that it was cute and I like I like the little clown boy.
And he's my favorite guy and I love him in my arms.
I don't mind cute.
I love the Pokemon refresh mechanic.
I love petting my Pokemon.
And in fact, honestly, I think my favorite thing about this game,
a new change is the the way that after a battle, you can treat your Pokemon status
ailments and Pokemon refresh.
I love that so much.
It makes so much sense to me.
And you can bond with them and pet them and stuff.
That's great.
And I can rub my Machoke's dick and he's like, yes, yes, this is what I saw that.
Yeah, it's the greatest.
It's the greatest.
That is a great mechanic that makes all the sense in the world.
And it should have been there all along.
If it was the Machoke dick rubbing, you mean?
Yes, curing status ailments is great.
I think Nate that Pokemon has always been incredibly patronizing.
That's every all this is like 80 percent of all dialogue in every Pokemon game.
Wow, you and your Pokemon get along so well.
You're such a good trainer.
You treat Pokemon better than everyone else.
But here's the difference. Everyone loves you.
You're great. You're amazing.
All right, no trainers ever been so connected to their Pokemon.
You've defeated me, the ultimate trainer, Lance, the dragon master,
that's fucking shatter of universes.
It must be because you and your Pokemon are just have such a strong bond.
That's so much about the six guys you kept in a box for half the game.
That's perfectly reasonable that you beat Lance because you trained with your Pokemon.
OK, look, the difference is that this game and this was this was the worst.
This was the worst it's ever been by far.
And this is the biggest problem with the game.
This continues the trend of babying you so fucking hard.
And that is the biggest difficulty with the game, Nate.
Yes, that's that's correct.
It is a tone problem.
It is a massive tone problem.
You're a tone problem.
I'll tell you what I'll tell you if you let me fuck Pokemon is a baby game.
It is a baby game.
OK, you guys are bringing up all these things about how
Pokemon's a baby game and how we shouldn't have standards of quality.
And we're very bad because always just Pokemon.
But no, I refused to to lower my standards
because other games didn't fuck up in the way that this game did.
You're such an idiot, Nate.
It didn't fuck up anything.
You're just being when it added one extra second of cutscene.
No, I'm not talking about that.
You're not letting me get to my point.
Well, Nate, I know what you're saying, but you're implying that this is
inherently a bad thing that like no one wants a game like this.
When the reality is that for a lot of people, this is fine.
And you chose to play a Pokemon.
Dude, all right.
Tell me, tell me, tell me that you enjoyed how just eating your fucking
dick after you beat him every time.
Like how rewarding was it for you to defeat how?
And he's like, well, that was a great fucking battle.
I sure love getting my shit kicked in.
Let's do it again.
That wasn't the point that I'm making.
Everyone hates how everyone doesn't like how.
Why do we have to have a city rival?
Major, I'm glad somebody like that.
You have like five rivals and half of them hate and all of them are terrible.
All of them are bad.
None of them are good.
You don't like the blonde kid?
That guy was awesome.
He's all edgy and shit.
Yeah, I did like him.
I didn't he legitimately hates you.
He's like, especially hates how he hates how so much that I was like high
fiving him when you know, it was good.
You know, it was good about that character.
He had an actual motivation.
He was protecting this this null Pokemon.
It was this whole big fucking thing that was cool.
That made him an interesting.
How it doesn't have a motivation when he wants to become the he wants to surpass
his father and become a kahuna because he sees his self as an inferiority complex
because his father's been a great trainer his whole life.
He did nothing to make me care.
I knew all those facts, though.
You don't have to care about if he has some motivations.
Look, it's not about his action.
Your motivation at all.
So fucking vague is pissing me right the fuck off.
All right, I think I don't even know what I mean.
I don't think you even know what you mean.
Let hippo talk.
All right.
What? Oh, well,
I was going to say,
I think Nate is like it's just just a simple point that is sort of blending into
other points that he doesn't like how he doesn't like how how how's is is so happy.
He prefers Gary, who's like, eh, fuck you for beating me.
Or like the redhead from Crystal.
Like an actual rival.
And when you fight Gary,
one game doesn't really have a rival as far as I know.
When you defeat blue, blue is fucking pissed and it makes you feel good that you
overcame someone who wanted to win.
I actually gave a shit.
But literally every other rival in this game is like that.
And how what are these other rivals?
There's there's him and there's the blonde kid.
There's the blonde kid.
There's the girl who's part of Team Skull.
They both hate you.
She's not a fucking rival.
She's an enemy executive.
Nate, Hugh, what?
Hugh in black and white, too.
Every single time you beat him,
he tells you you're a cool guy and congratulates you on being so strong.
Same thing in black and white one.
Your rivals are just these like real nice,
chummy guys who just tell you right.
And I don't like to fight in all the newer games than your rivals are your
friends and like the yeah, it's always been bad journey.
It's been bad the whole time ever since Diamond and Pearl.
It's been a mistake.
They need to fix that.
I don't I don't like.
OK, think about just what does it imply?
They've got that.
They've got that in these other characters that are dicks to you.
And they've got this other guy.
Who's nice to you?
Just think about having both.
Think of think about this for one second.
What do we make of the fact?
What do we make of the fact that our rival now used to choose the Pokemon
that was strong against us now picks the Pokemon that we are super strong
and we can wipe the floor with all that is done.
What are we to make of the night?
I don't know. It's made me feel like I'm now Gary Oak.
That's a good boy.
Yeah, yeah, we're the villains.
And I'm the cool one and I'm getting all the girls even though I am a girl.
You know, hypocrite, you just changed my mind on this.
Now that I'm the villain, I think I love this a lot more.
You guys are being mean to me.
Like again, you have other rivals who hate you and do have Pokemon you're weak to
and how later does get an EV Lucian that is whatever your your starter is weak to?
So he doesn't get on page.
And what are you talking about? No, he doesn't.
Yeah, he does.
When you fight him, when you get into the Third Island,
when he like just fucking springs a battle on you right off the boat,
then he picks whatever EV Lucian your guys weak to.
So I had, you know, my grass starter.
He had a Flareon and his fucking Raichu and his in his pop or yeah,
probably a third ever and all of them were super fucking strong.
And it was like out of nowhere.
He was suddenly a hard battle and he fucking wiped me.
Oh, there's a real point.
There's a point I want to make.
Everyone shut up.
Yeah, Mage, what do you want to find about the rivals and that?
Yeah, well, not an hour, but yeah, about the rivals saying like in the past games,
maybe I didn't pay attention much or whatever, but like all the nice guys,
they didn't really have much to their character and they were just nice to be
nice with how, though, I haven't really gone farm the game, but already can pick up
that, you know, he has a bit more to him rather just being nice.
You've been tricked.
It's a fake.
After the first battle of the blonde edgelord,
he kind of says like, oh, he's strong, but I can tell that, you know,
he's not trying or whatever.
So he kind of gives the vibe that how's just kind of putting up putting up a
happy face or whatever.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, he has a bit of dialogue up to that way, where you can like you can put
how down or something and then how scowls at you.
I kind of like that.
Well, he, he like how constantly never stop smiling for me once the entire game.
He never stopped.
I told him attention and he's always like he's always trying to get you to react
to his jokes and stuff and he gets real pouty when you won't react to his jokes.
And like it's kind of implied that he has some fragility to his ego.
And then later in the game, like some stuff happens and he feels all bad that
he was like not strong enough.
And he's like, man, maybe I've been fucking goofing around too much.
And I'm not like taking things seriously enough.
He really is the catch him to to to my to my gary oak.
OK, all right, guys, you know what?
That's that's fine.
And I don't actually I don't hate the character of how my problem is simply
thus, I don't care for the increasingly infantile tone of the game is you leave
how alone, you big bully, I am living alone.
I just don't feel enough.
Oh, I don't know.
Like like the game is really trying to challenge me with anything.
Even when I was a little kid, I thought Pokemon was like condescending to me.
Like I always thought it was a baby game.
Like in terms of the way it talks to you, you know, like it constantly reassures
you and like tells you everything to do.
You've got I mean, from the second game, you have your fucking mom calling you
everywhere you go, making sure you've got enough money and just giving you money.
You know, like well, that happens in Earthbound as well.
And, you know, that's not.
That is a real game.
Earthbound is a baby game, kind of like the tone of Pokemon has changed
in any particular way.
It has or out of your fucking mind.
You guys are out of your fucking mind.
If you don't think that has definitely changed.
But I think that it's just that they have more features.
They've added more features.
They I think they've just made the Pokemon games more what they were always meant
to be in that they're a friendly, fun time that you have a nice leisurely
stroll through tells you you're doing by the way, this is like the hardest
Pokemon game ever.
So absolutely not.
It was a complete joke.
I never died once, not once.
I had 10 full party wives and I ended almost every major battle with all my
Pokemon dead, but one way I just I never overleveled.
I was always the same levels as what I fought and we're fucked.
I do.
I didn't overlevel.
I just might be a little game.
And yet I walked through every time.
I never did you only have like one team, the whole game or something like me.
Me and Mumpi are listening to this.
Like, well, why would I switch?
Everyone shut the fuck up.
Me and Mumpi's lives are hanging in the balance as we listen to this.
We're sweating bullets hearing all of it.
Yeah.
Well, I've got plenty of plenty of hints on how to deal with it.
We've got donators.
We have to please.
But we haven't even really touched about the the spiderweb of what I would
call casualization of this game.
How about the railroading, which I know has always been a thing,
but really was worse than ever.
You mean the railroading?
Every fucking Pokemon game is completely linear.
Every single one.
I'm aware of that.
But I think that not only do that, it wastes your time with cut scenes now.
Actually, I disagree with you.
Because when you put this up with who, with whom age, who do you disagree with?
Nate. OK.
Yeah, OK, so every game has been on a railroad.
But for the first time, I feel like, you know, this game,
this Pokemon game is kind of like an actual sort of close to an actual RPG in a way.
Well, yeah, you don't really have choices and it's a railroad,
but it's telling a story and I feel a bit more invested in it than with other games.
I mean, I hear I hear a lot of praise for the story in this game.
So good. The story is not actually good.
Like, yeah, you're completely reasonable for what it is.
Complaining about the amount of cut scenes.
And yeah, I feel like there are more, but a lot of people seem to think
that they're good cut scenes in the story.
Those people are wrong.
And they've been.
They've been. Skull.
What? By their own brain.
They think they're enjoying it.
By far the best team that's ever been in one of these games.
Yes, teams are miles greater than any of the previous teams.
That's not true. You're not thinking clearly.
I really want to get to know Team Rocket.
Team Rocket did nothing. Team Rocket is bull.
Team Rocket is the coolest.
Every Team Rocket guy.
Oh, I sure like hurting Pokemon.
I'm they were just they were just.
You know, when you say it like that, Digi, they actually do sound pretty cool.
Well, all right, I don't I like Team Skull, too.
I think Team Skull is great.
And by the way, punk girl, when she's not wearing her Team Skull outfit,
is probably the hottest Pokemon girl there's ever been.
So I'm big into Team Skull.
They're perfectly great.
Team Skull has so much pathos behind them.
And when you fucking I'm not going to I don't want to spoil it.
This really isn't, by the way, this is not a counter to my point.
This is just something else entirely.
Team Skull is fine.
I have no gripes with them there.
That doesn't have anything to do with the casualization.
Cut scenes.
Like, yeah, but that just is such a.
I mean, I cannot think of a single time in a Pokemon game
until this one where I ever gave a single fuck about anything.
I never cared about any of the characters.
Well, that's your problem.
I thought they all retarded, you know, like when I was growing up,
I was just like fucking mash a through Lance talking about whatever bullshit
he wants you to do at the stupid power plant.
I don't care.
But in this game, I was like, oh, my God, this character, Lily,
she has a fucking arc.
She develops, she changes, and I could see the hints
from the very beginning of how she was going to change.
And I was like, huh, this is an interesting little character.
And then there's like this huge moment of growth.
And I'm like, whoa, this is literally the plot of Killluck.
You don't fucking think Silver develops over the course of Pokemon Gold and Silver.
You're out of your fucking mind.
You don't remember the very end.
At the very end, he's like, wow, you beat me so many fucking times
that maybe I'm doing something wrong and Lily changes exactly once
at like three quarters through the game.
No, no, she changes gradually when she realizes
a whole bunch of different things at the beginning.
She's like, I never had to.
She's like telling you, oh, I've never dressed myself before.
You know, my mom's always picked up my clothes for me.
And then every time you go to like a clothes shop, she's like, you know,
maybe I'm going to try on something different.
Maybe I'll try something new.
And then at one point we buy her an outfit that's already established.
That doesn't happen over the course of the game.
That's just from the start.
No, she likes shopping, but she's never bought her own clothes before.
With the first time she buys something, she's like, oh, I bought this outfit
even though I'm sure I don't have the courage to wear it.
Yeah. And she won't put it on until after like a big character moment.
And then she gets it. And then we're done.
And then she's the same character the rest of the game.
All of my only point, she's fine.
I like it. She's not bad.
You guys are just making it out like this is so much better than the other games.
And that's I don't even have an opinion because I haven't played that far.
Nate, I hate I hate listening to you about this.
You're dumb. You're dumb.
You're about to fucking cut scenes.
You've been you've been through a million cut scenes.
And I think the solution that will make everybody happy
is just make the cut scenes fucking skippable.
So if we're retired like this stupid shit, you can watch it.
And if you just want to kill some Pokemon like me and Ben,
you can just go fucking kill Pokemon.
Yes, I mean, this is not being able to skip cut scenes
is one of the biggest problems I hate.
I hate this is a huge problem with every Nintendo game.
Lack of options.
They for some reason, they just can't get it through there.
Like even if it was just busy, honestly, I wouldn't accept your opinion yourself.
Yeah, I know. Well, OK, well, I would even accept that it was just on the second round.
Like, even if it was just the second time to the game,
if you could skip the cut scenes, like, I mean, I hate that you can't skip them ever.
But like, at least make it so when I go through again,
because the thought of trying to play this game again
and watch 30 minutes of cut scenes at the start and end of the game
is just like, I don't want to do that again.
The other games don't have that.
The other games don't have all that shit.
That's because I have no ties or anything.
But there is there is no way to you.
Oh, God, there's no there's no new game.
Plus and may I remind you all that at the beginning of gold and silver,
you have to walk all the way to the next town to pick up an egg
and then walk all the way back to the previous town
before you can get your running shoes
and before you can really catch any Pokemon.
Yeah, but you still get to play how it takes like 20 fucking minutes.
There's no cut scenes in that whole.
There's well, there's a couple like talk.
Yeah, but it's the worst thing ever.
It's the by far that was made.
That's worse than half an hour of waiting for the game to start.
No, dude, there were so many times as I went back to gold and silver
and I literally just like played through that little segment
and then just gave I was like, I don't you just said that you don't want to play
this one again. So at the worst, it's the same level of bad
from that one game in the game. Yeah, I'm not talking about the same level.
All right. Well, what about I just want to say, OK,
though, Nate, you said we're making out this game is like so much better
than all the other ones. I was actually arguing.
I was actually arguing that all the things you're complaining about
were in the previous games, so it's not like things got worse.
OK, they're just one example of something that is unquestionably better.
I think that stuff is just more of it. Yeah.
But OK, just just this one thing that I think is
and this is when I was going to say like my ideal Pokemon game.
This is what I'm talking about in Pokemon Red and Blue,
everything to do with the story of Mewtwo, which is which is the story of that game.
There's there's, you know, Team Rocket is doing their shit
and and Mewtwo was made and caused problems on Cinnabar Island.
That's pretty much it.
And is all that in the actual narrative of red and blue?
Well, that's the great thing about it.
That's the great thing about you find out that information by going into the
like that the smash up laboratory on Cinnabar Island.
Yeah. And you read the logs and you learn by playing the game voluntarily.
You're not forced into a cut scene where you find out what Mewtwo's
backstory is all the back story elements you can learn that way in X and Y.
You never have nobody tells you about Type Null,
but you can read up all these data files about great if only every part of the story
was like that. It'd be a thousand times.
But there's nothing wrong with a cut scene.
But there's something wrong with a bunch of cut scenes to take a half a run time.
Does every fucking part of every game have to be delivered environmentally?
Does every game have to be some dark souls?
The end thing where you told me you think there's too many cut scenes.
I'm giving you a solution.
I don't even think there's too many cut scenes.
I think no, I think it's pretty long.
I didn't dislike it.
Yeah, I mean, I like the cut scene.
I think I think they're too long, but I had no problem with them.
And like the way the way I played it, like, I mean,
I sat down with the game and played for six straight hours.
And those first 30 minutes very quickly no longer were a factor
because I just, you know, I just kept playing.
And I just thought I was I was glad to be invested in the in the world
and characters because if I'm going to play a game with a lot of story,
I'd like to care about the things that are going on, you know, as I played the game.
It absolutely got much, much better as I played more.
And what I didn't think was a very good start became less and less important.
But that does not. I'm really just I'm emphasizing things
that bothered me a lot at the start that don't really.
I don't think they matter that much over the course of the game.
Like you get less scenes as the game goes on.
I'm just being strongly emphasizing what those points are.
OK, Nate hates cutscenes.
That's it. That's all that's all there is to it.
And that was only part of the game.
Well, whatever. All right, let's move on to something else.
I just think it's really funny to hear this argument
from a fucking Kingdom Hearts fan where you get to start off the first game
spinning you can skip those cutscenes.
You can skip those fucking cutscenes.
Yeah, but you can't skip that stupid race.
Also, they're great.
Hey, guys, do you know what's the story that is delivered through cutscenes?
Like the the NPCs you fight,
sometimes they throw out pokemons in different types of pokeballs.
It's a neat little. Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I haven't heard that before.
Oh, that's been other versions.
The Kahuna's Crabrawler, I think, was in an old.
Or I think all the Kahuna's Pokemon were in.
But it just rounded NPCs like some guy used, I think, a premier ball.
I don't remember for the collector guys.
The collector guys use premiere balls for their body.
I have said before, I love I love getting all my Pokemon
in different colored balls and just they all have like a look at my one guy.
My starter here is in his little red ball.
Oh, this one, I found this diglet in a cave.
He's in a little black, green, deep ball or whatever.
Oh, and this fish is in a dive ball.
It's great. Yeah, your your Pokemon should all be in blue balls, Ben.
That's for sure.
Hey.
Got him.
Yeah, I really, yeah, I really like surfing.
Really like all those water Pokemon.
Can we talk about the elimination of gyms?
Yes, we can really in elimination.
It was just. Oh, no. Oh, no, it absolutely was.
This was a big deal.
Well, I don't know.
It's exactly the same.
Oh, how far are you in the game?
I mean, how many trials have you done?
I've done two and I'm back to the third one.
I mean, I know they're very different.
I'm pretty much completely spoiled on where it goes with it.
I don't think Mumki is.
I am not. Yeah.
So, I mean, I'm not.
It seems to be the instead of trainers in the places,
you just fired a bunch of the Pokemon of the type that the crystal is.
The just like it would be in a gym
and then you fight the big main one and then you beat him
and then you get the same.
The the Cajunas are basically gym leader battles.
The the trial leaders, I guess, are the trial captains are to kind of,
I guess, I know it didn't it didn't feel like it with them as much.
Yeah, well, you don't really like like, I mean, the trials of them,
the new versions of gyms, but the actual gym leaders are more like the Cajunas.
It's such they basically made two different strands of
I've always thought the Cajunas would like the elite four
and there's one elite four on each island.
Well, yeah, but I mean, the elite four ordinarily would not be fought on each island.
It seems like you fight the trial captain, then do the trial,
then trial captain and then sometimes you don't find a lot of trial captains.
Yeah, I didn't I didn't fight the water one.
Fight Elima. That's like the only one.
Well, you fight a couple of them.
I think I don't know.
The point is, I think Elima is the only one they train the totem Pokemon
and they that's their place that to show how good they are at making the Pokemon really fast.
And the totem fights are cool because they're like you have to fight.
You usually have to fight two Pokemon at once and it makes it a much more strategic.
Oh, God, the two at one.
We have to talk about that.
You always have to fight two at once.
But yeah, it makes it man.
The most hilarious fight I ever had is against the electric one.
And like, yeah, I had like only one Pokemon that had enough resistance
to deal with it, which is my sandy gas and like he couldn't do it.
Like it was like he couldn't damage it because it was a flying electric
and it couldn't damage me very much because it was you know, I was a ground type.
So like all I had was to trap it in a fucking sand tomb
and like just wait, wait out turn after turn until it fucking died.
And it took forever, but it was so funny because he couldn't hurt me.
And it was just like this battle of attrition where he just kept increasing
his speed or whatever it was totally pointless.
Well, you know, I love I liked one aspect of those of the trials.
And that was the totem fights were cool.
There's the buffed up Pokemon that's stronger than normal.
And he summons guys to fight him.
That felt like kind of like a proper boss fight.
I didn't enjoy that aspect, but there was a huge problem.
I do like I do.
I do like the idea that a Pokemon can be a boss battle.
Yeah, I don't know if I'm that impressed really with the totem Pokemon.
I don't I don't think they're that interesting, honestly.
I mean, the most interesting thing about them is that they summon,
which is not even a thing that's unique to them.
Well, see, see, and that's that's the thing.
OK, so when I when I did the first trial
and there was a summoning thing for the totem in that, you know,
in that area in the trial area, I was like, oh, that's cool.
This is a challenging place.
So I like the concept, but I think they could do it better.
The problem for me is that that happens outside of trial areas
and was probably the most frustrating thing just about doing normal battles.
When I'm trying to not even when I'm just trying to catch something.
Yeah, I'm trying to catch something to keep so many guys
and you can't throw a Pokeball.
It's a nightmare. It's a nightmare.
It is a kind of a nightmare.
I haven't had a really terrible experience with it, except for one time
where none of my Pokemon were particularly effective against this rock guy.
Yeah, well, I think they were.
But I was just fighting it with one Pokemon.
I was just trying to get it low enough so I could catch it.
And then you summon another one.
And the worst thing about it is that they can summon ones
as soon as you kill the second.
Yeah, they don't even have to like use a turn or anything.
I mean, I think it's a cool like idea to have that happen,
but it just happens way too often.
It's like every wild Pokemon battle.
If you get them to low health because you're trying to catch them,
they're going to summon something.
I was keeping track.
Turn into this fucking I had a record of five times.
I had a Pokemon at one HP.
I was used false white.
It was like stunned five turns in a fucking row.
I want to kill the enemy.
It's summoned another one.
Five turns that that's the thing about it is that it's also meant
to be a method for catching better Pokemon because the more they summon,
the higher the IVs will be of those Pokemon.
And we can get like if you want to have a really solid team,
you just keep sidechaining those things until you finally get like
and they'll also summon like their own evolved form sometimes or like Pokemon.
There's a lot of Pokemon that can only be caught that way.
Well, all right, that's cool.
But it's an issue of balancing.
And I don't think the balance is correct for that.
No, there's too much of it.
But like wouldn't it be great if that only happened in like trial areas
or just some designated place?
Yeah, that would be cool if it only happened for cool Pokemon.
All right.
I think, you know, I actually think it's kind of cool
that you can catch Pokemon with their hidden abilities that way.
But I don't like that some Pokemon can only be encountered at all that way.
I think that means that a lot of people, myself included,
would go through the game just without seeing a lot of Pokemon.
Like I think that is a huge issue.
I think Toxopex can only be encountered
if you have like all these long ass chain battles
where they summon a series of Pokemon.
And like I think there's a high probability
that that just might never happen and I might never see a Toxopex.
I'd beat the game if that were a Sabeline.
Hippini.
Yeah, Hippini.
On the first island, you can only get it by when it calls
like when baby Pokemon call for help like Bonsley or Pichu.
Yeah, or AigliBuff.
I mean, I guess it was the case before that you could go through an area
and never encounter certain Pokemon.
I mean, I don't know.
It's just a little extreme.
I think there's too many of them.
Something is hiding something esoteric, like a hidden ability.
I like that.
I think hiding the Pokemon period is too much.
I mean, it's always been one of the cool things about trying to catch
all the Pokemon in a game is that they usually have whatever new mechanic.
There's some Pokemon that you can only catch through that mechanic.
But this is like way extreme.
Like there's a lot of Pokemon you can only catch that way.
There should not have been.
I think it's yeah, they overdid it.
It's funny to me.
I actually I kind of disagree with you guys.
I'm actually inclined to be more charitable about this
because I'm a man who loves the grind as as you all know.
And I don't really mind like if you go through the through the game
just playing normally, which I just finished this morning.
And I never find Pokemon.
That's fine because I'll really enjoy if I'm inclined to go back
and try to fill my Pokedex, taking the pains to go and find them out
through whatever method it makes me.
It makes me appreciate it more when I have to work hard to get a Pokemon.
You know, I mean, that's yeah.
That's the part I do like is that like sometimes you're trying to catch a
Pokemon and it becomes like, all right, now I really got to like,
you know, put a lot more effort into strategizing how I'm going to do this.
But it's just too fucking much.
There's 300 Pokemon in this game.
You know, I don't want to do this in every fucking battle.
So just recently, I was I was having a bit of an issue with the fee bass
in that one, the only one place that it can spawn in that in the water trial area.
And you get the fishing rod and it seems like the first time you see it,
it's like a high probability.
But if you miss your chance like I did, it drops drastically.
And then I was just sitting there for two hours fishing
because I hated the idea that I let it get away.
I didn't realize how rare it was.
But don't you feel great when you finally catch it?
I don't know, because well, there's a thing with that,
because when I get fucked by a random number generator enough,
yeah, finally winning after, you know, finally getting the thing.
There's a threshold beyond which I don't feel as good.
I just feel Pokemon I sigh.
And I'm like, finally.
And I was like, when you fought, Pokemon on every level
is just all about that RNG.
Yeah. And I don't love RNG.
Like like something like in King of Hearts,
I haven't been getting better at the fights lately.
I lately I have been playing lots and lots of Pokemon showdown.
And you just you just have to learn to love the RNG.
It's the only you have to you have to accept and embrace the RNG.
That's like a Dark Souls meme.
Hey, guys, something random.
Did you all get your event much like Stingy?
Yes, Rolex has been a staple of my team.
I did. I did not get it because it seemed cheap.
I thought I thought I'm never going to use it.
It's perfect to I caught one.
Metronome is lots of fun.
It's just it's hilarious.
No, it's cheap.
Guys, his attack would definitely be cheating for Ben's Nuzlocke.
He can't over as you pancake is the coolest attack in all.
Oh, hey, you know what?
Let's talk about that real quick.
Z moves. I think I think I just completely love them.
And they're they're basically final smashes for Pokemon.
And I just don't like that they have long cut scenes.
That's the only thing I don't know.
You can only use them so much.
I do love you don't love final smashes.
Yeah, you know, okay.
Yeah, I think I think they're balanced enough
using one per battle, you know, seems reasonable.
I don't think you could use them all the time.
Then you would feel like you need to use them all the time.
And then you'd be terrible that they were really long.
But if you're like, you know, you're fighting a Cajun and you're like,
all right, they got half the health.
I can't do it.
Well, explosion.
Z moves are Z moves are good.
Like they're always good to use.
So like strategically, you probably should use them every single battle you're in,
which is well, I'm not going to spoil.
You can usually kill them in one hit if you're good.
Mom, can you say I'm not going to spoil anything?
But the battle between me and Ben, the Z moves are some of the
I mean, it's the best fucking parts of the video.
The Z moves did the Z moves did become.
Yeah, I think they're a lot of fun.
That's cool. That's what's cool about like.
Yeah, acts like in the city in that case, in that case,
the the cutscene definitely added something.
Yeah, that was fun.
It makes it more anime.
Yeah, it's like it's like me and Ben were actually fighting in an anime.
It was awesome. Yeah.
Yeah, we like we called out our attacks and then we charged them up and released them.
Did you do the pose as well?
Yeah, you better have done that dance.
Oh, in real life, we do in real life.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, we had face cam on and everything.
Wait, OK, Generation 8, Generation 8,
keep the Z moves, but have a motion controller built into the DS.
You have to actually perform the dance.
If you do it wrong, then the attack doesn't work.
I would be so down.
You know what? Quick, quick, caviar.
One of my biggest problems with this game was that there's a couple times
you get a a Z stone or a Z crystal or whatever,
and then you can just use it without learning the dance.
How the fuck did I learn that dance game?
How the fuck did I do it?
I don't know. That's so shit.
That actually really pisses me off.
Like, they make a big deal about, oh, you have to do the dance to do the thing.
And then sometimes they just ignore that rule.
That sucks.
I would say as often they ignore the rule because there's 20 fucking crystals
and there's only like eight people who teach you dances.
Did you? The first thing I did when I got to end game was go down.
Make up your own dance.
There you go.
Maybe I don't even think the dance is about here.
If you can make up your own dance, then why does why does Ilma have to teach you the dance?
Tradition.
Wait, if there's 18 crystals, surely some of them are the same type,
like same move type, like water.
No, there's actually way more than.
There's 18 types, but then there's like unique.
There's there's Pokemon specific crystals, too.
Oh, fuck.
Forgot about that.
I'll say this much.
I kind of like the Zmos.
Actually, I like them a lot more than I do mega evolution.
Yeah, dog. Yeah.
No, I like I like mega mega evolution.
Yeah, but make a little you grow up and accept it.
Make up a whole thing.
What do you mean they take up a whole thing?
They do they take up a whole move slot?
What? No, no, they take up a turn.
No. OK, forget it.
Then I've never really used them.
I just heard about a man.
Let me tell you, maybe evolution.
Mega evolutions do not take up a turn, you dingus.
They don't. Oh, OK.
Well, I still like it.
But I got through this whole game like Z moves a lot.
And let me tell you, I'm in the end game now.
Well, I went to do a thing in a certain place.
And what do I find?
But the guy's like, hey, congratulations on becoming champion.
How would you like to learn about megas?
And I was like, no, please, we were so close.
Megas are cool.
No, I'm that's it.
I'm a mega I'm a mega fag.
I'm totally on board with megas.
Then you are a mega fag.
I am a mega evolution.
I mean, I know I literally just said that about myself.
Um, I I played the whole game and I never used a single Z move.
What? Oh, yeah, I died all the time.
I can't wipe in this game.
I wonder why the idea of having to like give things to my Pokemon
never been a fan.
Say you don't even give them items.
You've got to micromanage at least a little bit.
Jen, too.
Managing, too.
I hate because I constantly switch Pokemon in and out of my party.
So I've always felt like I have to, like, remove all the items from each guy
and then put them on the next guy in Spanish by the part of the game
where you're on the second island and you've just got to the Royal Rumble.
How many times have you completely wiped?
I'm just curious.
He said ten minutes.
Rumble.
Yeah, I don't know if at all.
Maybe once.
Digi, I got a question for you.
Me and Ben are having a little debate about this.
Do you think when you get thrown into that first Royal Rumble,
if your Pokemon dies in a Nuzlocke, is that is it dead
or does the Royal Rumble not count because it's fucking horses?
I would say it doesn't count because it's so fucking weird.
Yeah, I'd say it doesn't count either.
Ben's trying to kill my Pokemon.
Do you remember the four-way battles?
If the story puts you in a battle, I think it's part of you.
But it's not a real battle because it's three on one pretty much.
And it's the only Pokemon in your party.
So when it dies, it counts as a full party wipe and that's game over.
But someone...
The biggest problem with it is they don't even warn you it's going to happen
and it automatically selects your first Pokemon.
There's all kinds of things that happen without warning.
Yeah, but you don't have your whole team.
It just picks the first guy you've got and then just throws you in.
And it's like you just...
It counts as a full party wipe and that's game over.
I don't know, it sounds like it should maybe
kill the death of that Pokemon but not necessarily.
I mean, I just played...
It does look like community Nuzlocke.
Rumble and it was full.
We are the Nuzlocke community.
It wasn't really three on one.
Like, most of them didn't attack me at all.
They guys, they fucked each other up.
I almost wanted it, but then the thing is that there's one guy
who was constantly using Reflect and he was the only one who was weak type-wise
to my guy.
So I just kept attacking him, but it wasn't working, you know,
and he kept reflecting.
And then eventually I was the first to die in the end.
Like, eventually they all killed me and I was like,
there was no way I could have known this was coming and had the right...
Like, there's no way to know what Pokemon they're gonna have
or what would be the best, you know, front-runner for your party.
So, yeah, it was just kind of...
So I think Ben, for the sake of our Nuzlocke,
I think we should have a vote.
We have six Pokemon experts.
We've all played the game out, but we put it to a vote.
And then the other side, my Pokemon is dead.
But I'm just saying, I'm just saying,
if the vote comes out that it doesn't count,
I'm still gonna do it.
And if I manage to win, I'm gonna pretend that it's legit
and I'm gonna pretend that I'm superior for that reason.
You're probably gonna be superior regardless.
In a Nuzlocke, I don't think it counts as a full party wipe if you die,
but that Pokemon should die.
I kind of agree with that.
God damn it.
Fuck you all.
Let's vote on it.
Let's vote on it right now.
I think it should count for that, yeah.
So, okay, all in favor of it counting for a full game over wipe,
if you lose, say aye.
No votes, okay.
All who think that it should count as the death of that Pokemon,
but not necessarily a full game over, say aye.
Aye.
That's what, four?
And okay, and everyone who thinks it shouldn't count whatsoever, say aye.
Fuck you.
Well, the majority says that Pokemon must die.
Ugh.
I should probably have voted the other way,
because I don't know what you were thinking.
It's fun.
It's fun to die.
It is fun to die.
That's what makes the, that's what makes the game fun.
It's almost like it's fun when a Pokemon game challenges you
and gives you shit and you don't do everything perfectly,
instead of sucking your dick the whole time.
Wow, what a concept.
What is that?
Throwing my level 15 Pokemon that I'm training
into a fucking four way.
That's so fun and challenging, Nate.
Well, you could try not to throw it into a four way.
I didn't know they were gonna throw me
into a fucking battle, hippo.
It's completely out of nowhere.
Wait, is it already happening for you?
Yeah, it fucking happens.
I changed my vote.
You're too late, bitch.
Three to three.
It's time.
What the hell?
And Dizzy counts us too,
because he has more subs than us.
That's bullshit.
Fucking cowards.
You are cowards.
Well, I do make your own decisions.
You guys, since it's a tie,
you two will have to decide amongst yourselves.
You're the ones doing it.
But we both just agreed.
So, hey, what do you know?
Okay, well, there you go.
All right, get out of jail free.
Yeah.
Congratulations, everyone.
Ben's gonna fully make up his mind once he plays it
and whether or not he's gonna play it.
Yeah, that's right.
No, yeah, I have to, let's confer on this after.
Once he sees how bullshit it is,
I think he's gonna agree with me.
Let's wait for me to win,
and then so I can say it definitely should count as a death.
Yeah, that sounds good.
Maybe if your Pokemon died, Momki,
you should just constantly let it have paralysis.
So it's like it's a cripple now.
That's still alive.
Hey, let's talk about something else now.
And I think this was an X and Y.
I can't fucking remember, but I know it was in this game
and it was pretty cool.
Let's talk about dressing up your Pokemon, man.
Maybe all pretty, looking fly is fun.
I loved it.
I mean, I haven't seen that much of it,
but what I've seen, I like,
I want there to be lots more options.
Me too, I'm not dressing up your character, right?
The way you raised that was odd.
You're talking about the Pokemon or the character?
The character.
Oh, that's good.
Well, yeah, I'm on a quest
to find a really nice big summer hat
to go with a white dress.
That's weird.
There's only one big summer hat in the game
and it is $145,000.
I'm getting it.
See, I could buy it now.
That's the one thing I hadn't bought yet that I wanted,
but you can only get it in that mall in the first island.
So you're already past it.
There's nothing more fun than giving yourself a quest
and then going on it and completing it.
Well, the items changed day to day in the shop.
And I'm asking, do they?
Do they do what?
I didn't see the big summer hat when I was first there,
so I guess it gets a lot.
No, there's no changes.
The one in the mall is the super fancy store
where everything's crazy expensive
because there's two stores in the first town.
There's the one that's like the basic bitch store
and then there's the crazy high quality store.
Where the hell is the crazy store?
Are you talking about at the mall?
It's in the mall.
You have to go on the mall.
No, I'm talking about Sun.
There's a mall that me and Ben both completely missed
our first time through the first town.
I'm guessing I missed it as well.
And then we went back and it's, yeah,
it's like a huge, they've got, yeah, it's a big ass mall
and they've got like a clothes store
and then a couple of other little shops.
And then there's like an event area
where like depending on time of day and what day it is,
there's different events going on there.
There's a guy who makes you literally pick up
a bunch of shit and feed it to a grimer.
It's hilarious.
You literally pick up shit.
It's Pokemon shit is everywhere.
And you have to feed it to a grimer.
It's the best.
Shall we?
I like the Alolan grimer
because he's like he ate a cheeseburger
and he's got cheese around his lips.
Maybe that's why, maybe that's why Alolan grimer is-
Actually I like Alolan muck.
That's why who I like.
Maybe that's why Alolan grimer and muck are all gross looking
because they eat poop unlike regular grimmers.
Well, yeah, that's, it's established in this game.
Well, grimmers in the previous generations ate like sludge
and like industrial waste.
And now they just eat human trash
because there's not enough waste.
There's not enough industrialization in Alola
for them to eat.
I feel that's why he has the yellow
because I just assumed it was cheese from a cheeseburger.
Yeah, they also eat poop.
That's pretty fucking disgusting.
But doesn't muck have like diamonds in its mouth?
Maybe.
He's got like, he's got like these like
crystalline looking stones for teeth or something.
Could be glass shards or something.
Yeah, it could be glass.
You never know, you never know.
But anyway, let's talk about forms and how cool they are.
Grimer, when you rub them, your hands goes all sticky
and it's like, it's real funny.
I've got to try it.
Who would ever pet that disgusting sack of garbage?
I'd never touch it.
He's gross, but I love the fact that they added that.
I've got to take my, I've got to take my little comb
and just gently, just gently clean off
my little pile of, of my little pile of garbage.
My little piece of living feces.
So let me, yeah, let me just ask guys,
does anyone have a problem at all with the Pokemon forms?
Cause I think I pretty much just love them across the board.
What do you mean forms?
I mean, Alolan form versus Kanto and you know, the other.
Some of them suck.
Well, they can like, okay, Persian is a nightmare.
Persian is a nightmare.
There's no doubt about it.
I don't really like Alolan Dugtrio,
even though I think he's funny.
Yeah, I don't get the, I don't get it.
As stupid as Persian looks,
I think it's a thousand times better
than the original Persian.
What?
I mean, Cat's Persian was boring and stupid
and I never cared about it.
This is not an upgrade.
This is a downgrade.
This is hilarious.
This is a great downgrade.
Do you not think that it looks like a one piece character?
I think it looks like a one piece character.
Okay, but that's not always good.
Oh guys, we lost Mage.
Where'd Mage go?
She was triggered by my hatred of Persian.
I'm sorry, Mage.
Forgive me.
Oh yeah.
I think the original Persian looks like a normal cat.
Kept her recording.
I hope she, yeah.
She's a big girl.
She can take care of herself.
Well, anyway.
We'll see how that plays out.
Yeah, I think forms are cool.
And I mean, I've recently found,
I guess I won't say it because I want to spoil you guys.
Oh, I like fat face, Rattacate.
Oh, I love fat Rattacate.
No, I don't.
Cool.
Well, you know, I kind of like Alolan Rattacate.
I do not like Alolan Rattata.
He is stupid enough.
Rattata is always in every universe,
every timeline.
Rattata is a piece of shit.
No, well, I mean, I don't mind the,
they just gave him a mustache.
It's so stupid.
Like there's no substantive change.
My biggest problem with the Alolan forms
is that there's not nearly enough of them
and there are still old fucking Pokemon,
like Caterpie in this game.
Yeah, there's no business being there.
Yeah, there needed to be way more.
It should have been,
it should have been every old Pokemon is different here.
I mean, do you guys feel,
it's going to be from Gen one.
It should have been different.
Cause like it kind of implies the game.
Hi, sorry, internet.
Just did your, did your, did your recording survive?
Yeah, my recording was just the internet.
Yeah, it's kind of implied throughout the game
that Alola is like closer to Kanto
and that there's like a lot of immigration
between the two and Kanto is like kind of important.
So I feel like it made sense
whether there'd be lots of Kanto Pokemon,
but they should all have different forms.
I should not in any Pokemon game ever
have to catch into the fucking Caterpie
and then, and have a butterfree.
That's not even any different.
Like, I mean, even in X and Y,
they made their own bug Pokemon
and it evolved into a butterfly
that had four different forms.
It was like different depending on where you were.
That's cool.
Why was that not the case here with butterfree?
Well, I mean, I, I feel you on that.
That, that's a, that's a fair point,
but let me ask you guys something else.
Do you feel it all?
I feel a bit of this.
Like these are kind of a cop out
to avoid having to put in the work to make new Pokemon.
This is sort of a, the easy way.
I think they are kind of an effort saving measure,
but they're one that I'm okay with.
Yeah.
I don't, I don't like it.
I mean, I'm sorry for them.
I wouldn't say Alola forms are bit just like
Digglet is basically just the same with hair.
Yeah.
Digglet is lazy as fuck.
Digglet's obviously meant to be a joke.
He doesn't even have a metal nose.
Even when you get,
when you get into battles with him,
have you noticed that when you fight
Doug Trio sometimes, then it like,
it has like this dramatic camera shot on it.
Like, like all these like action lines show up
and it's like, would you like fight one?
And well, I mean, I do see that when you're in battle,
like the camera does pan around and do shots like that.
No, no, no.
I mean, when you first get into the battle
and like it reveals Doug Trio,
then like sometimes it did like a weird dramatic,
like look at this fucking thing.
Like.
I don't know, man.
Are you sure that it's just a normal battle?
Well, whatever.
I'm not sure that's unique.
What do you guys think of the Alolan form?
Maybe that could be like a,
maybe that's like an evolved form special look at this.
I have no idea.
Monkey, what were you saying?
Yeah, but what do you guys think of the Alolan form
of Ben Saint where like they have a new militarized skin
and he thinks he's like a general and stuff?
Not a fan.
I think it's pretty fucking stupid.
I've really not.
It's a form change before I was a petty terrorist
and now I'm a petty dictator.
Yeah, like Fidel Castro.
That's like a tight change.
The pettiness is a constant.
Oh, rest in peace, Fidel Castro, my comrade.
Did he die?
He died fucking today.
Whoa, why are we doing a PCP about that?
Holy shit.
Wow, I had no fucking idea.
What happens when you guys sleep until 3 p.m.?
Yeah, I didn't know that Fidel Castro was alive
until today when I found out he was no longer alive.
I didn't know who Fidel Castro was.
He let Raul run things for a while, but he was still alive.
But he's like 90 years old.
Yeah, he's an old ass bitch.
Well, rest in peace, my friend.
My comrade.
You'll be partying with Che soon up there.
My friends, here.
My friend, who up there?
Che, come on.
Okay, okay, I won't spoil anything,
but what I've heard mostly from you, Digi,
about like, how do I say it?
The sort of Alolan analogy,
like the Alolan version of the Pokemon League is awesome.
Oh yeah, it's the coolest thing ever.
Everything I have heard about that is great.
The Pokemon League is a thousand times better
than ever before.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay, I really, maybe this isn't the right place
to talk about it, but I really want to hear these reasons,
because I don't know why you think that.
First of all, there's the context of like, why it exists.
Right, I got you on that.
I got you on that.
And then there's just how it plays out.
You know about what you get to do
after you beat the Pokemon League, if you fight it again?
Yes, it's amazing.
No, okay, I only beat it once, so I'll go do that.
I don't know if this is considered a spoiler, so.
Yeah, it would be a total spoiler.
Do you think so?
I'm gonna go do it immediately.
Yes, I do.
Don't tell me.
You say it's cool, I'll go do it.
Guys, Nuzlocke's end after you beat the Pokemon League,
in my mind, so you can spoil what happens post-game.
I don't give a fuck.
I don't really think of it as a spoiler.
It's just, I'm telling you, I don't want to know.
You say it's cool, but guys, I won't go do it.
Maybe it won't be as cool as you think it will
until I fuck, like.
No, no.
You're gonna go through all the trouble
of being in the Pokemon League,
and be like, that's all it was?
Fuck you, Digi.
No, I already know, and I know that if you tell me.
You get to date me, too, okay?
You're like, yeah, I wish I did, you know that.
You're gonna date me, too?
Spoiling.
Do I spy Dan Green?
Do I spy?
Oh my God, he loves this one.
Well, fuck.
Whatever, it's cool.
That's exciting, and I'll go do that,
and I'm looking forward to whatever it is
without my expectations to I.
So, cool.
Awesome, I'll do that.
I guess we need to talk about Ultra Beasts.
You know, we don't have to talk about anything,
because it's supposed to be a general Pokemon podcast,
and not a sudden note.
I don't actually have anything to say
about Ultra Beasts, because I haven't encountered any.
What's Ultra Beasts?
I mean, it's weird.
I have been in the game now,
and Ultra Beasts were only relevant at one time,
and I'm doing a thing now that has something
to do with them.
I don't know what's going on.
I don't know where the mission is catching Ultra Beasts.
Are they mostly a post-game thing?
Yeah, they're mostly post-game.
Like, I mean, they're relevant.
I'm glad.
The story is kind of based around them,
but you only really interact with them post-game.
I mean, that's weird.
Okay, because I don't really want
to interact with them very much.
Okay, yeah, let's just talk about them design-wise.
I mean, it's kind of important.
If they are going to be captured like regular Pokemon,
and we just have them in balls,
that seems very strange to me,
because they are not like normal Pokemon,
but if we just like maybe.
You mean Legendaries?
Yeah.
They don't look like, like, look at that muscle dude.
You know, he does not look like a normal Pokemon.
Ultra Beasts are pretty fucking different,
but they're also like from another dimension, so.
Right, it makes sense.
I don't know what this is.
Well, you'll find out when you get later into the game,
and we're going to stop talking.
I can't wait.
Yeah, okay, okay.
I guess I feel okay about them.
I don't know whatever.
You know who I like?
I wish I could say more,
but I guess I shouldn't for Star Wise,
but Kukui is cool.
I like the professor.
Yes.
I like him a lot.
He is the coolest professor.
He is probably the coolest professor.
He's the sexiest professor.
And I really like, I don't know if you guys have gotten this,
but it's implied later that he trains his body really hard
because he's a move guy.
He's into moves.
That's his thing as a professor.
We also know everything about moves.
So he has trained himself
so that he can endure being hit by moves
so he can learn about them.
How badass is that?
That's fucking legit.
I caught my fucking Dragonite,
and I told him to outrage on me,
and he wouldn't stop.
He spent three entire turns just tearing me to fucking shred.
Luckily, I had my Alomomola nearby
to cast Wish on me to repair my shattered body.
Yes, Wish that you wouldn't be crushed.
Wish that I wasn't dead, and it worked.
So here I am.
When you said your Dragonite was using outrage on you,
I thought you were gonna say it started a Tumblr account.
Oh, good.
Is that like a fat dragon joke?
Sure.
No, it's because he was outraged by Trump being elected.
Make my joke funnier for me.
I'm envisioning that, you know,
that butter dragon thing that was in Undertale?
Oh, God.
Yeah.
So everybody.
He's got some outrage.
I know half of you haven't gotten very far in this game,
but what would you say is your favorite new Pokemon?
I've seen all the Pokemon.
Definitely Grubbin.
Grubbin is really good.
Grubbin so much.
He's fucking adorable.
Yeah, he's kind of cute,
but Raul is way cuter.
His evolved form is really cool.
Little bird.
Owl bird started.
I like male Primarina.
I bet you do.
Primarina is cool.
Primarina is the coolest design of the three.
I don't know what that is.
No, no, no.
The grass final is by far the coolest.
Have you guys tried Petty?
If you actually play with the grass final,
like he is, like his moves and everything,
he looks, first of all, he looks cooler from behind.
So like when you've got him on your team,
you're like, yeah, yeah.
And then you fucking use the arrow move
and you're like, yeah.
Yeah, that's the best.
He swings anointing, though.
Guys, when he pulls the two little dangly leaves
on the dangle down from his neck,
his mask thing closes because it's a fucking hoodie.
He's wearing a grass hoodie.
How sick is that?
It's pretty sick.
It's the best.
I'll give you that much.
All right.
I also like Mimikyu,
but I don't think everyone likes Mimikyu.
Yeah, Mimikyu's great.
I mean, Mimikyu's the best way
to do another fucking Pikachu for sure.
But he didn't already.
Another Pikachu was.
Yeah, there's another new one this game, too.
Wait, like aside from Mimikyu?
Yeah, there's like this little fat mouse thing.
It's like a Hedgehog.
It was a Pikachu original.
A Hedgehog.
I don't know.
He has a long mask thing.
Super Sonic.
And it's like a steel electric type.
Wait, Tota Gamaru?
Yeah.
Wait, is he new this game?
Oh, he's...
I mean, I don't understand the point
because we already had a steel electric,
but I guess he's a fast steel electric.
The point is they need a new Pikachu
because it's a new Pokemon game.
God, why do they do that?
It's so stupid.
I don't know.
They always got a bird and they've always got a grub.
One thing they're not always annoyed about
is like the insistence that Pikachu is the best one
and he's got better voice acting in this game.
And it's always about Pikachu and I don't care.
Pikachu's voice acting in this game is a trainer, too.
I actually...
Oh, really?
Wait, is it a trainer?
There's a trainer you can fight in the graveyard
named Ikue and she only has a Pikachu.
And when you beat her, she's like,
Pika, pika!
I remember that.
Oh, well, she is the voice actress of Pikachu.
That's a cute reference, way to go.
And she's standing over a grave of a Pikachu also,
which I, oh my God, what does this mean?
The symbolism was haunting me.
Dude, what if she had just been fired from the role,
standing over the grave of Pikachu?
That would have been a half of the play.
She says like, I'm speaking in the language
of this dead Pikachu that I'm here to visit or something.
Yeah, she's channeling it.
She's definitely the most recognized voice actress
in the world, because it's the same voice
for Pikachu in every country.
They never change it, you know?
So we all know Ikue Atani as a voice Pikachu.
I heard a story from a friend of mine
who knew someone who met her.
This was in like 2001
and apparently she like has a tick
of just like inserting pikas into her speech.
Oh my God.
She's broken.
She's been fully broken.
That was only four, that was only like four or five years
into Pokemon being out.
Imagine it must be like now.
Her mind would be absolutely shattered.
She's yellow.
She's even yellower than she was before.
Sorry.
I want her to get surgical alterations,
become that which you love.
Guys, I didn't say what new Pokemon I like.
Oh, please, monkey, please.
The one that gave me the best reaction was Crab Roller.
Yeah, I love that guy.
Hey, what do you mean, buddy?
You're fucking great.
Can we also say what our least favorite new Pokemon is too?
Yeah, yeah.
I haven't said my favorite yet,
but I don't really know.
I'm trying to decide if I should base this on design
or on like usage.
You can specify, you know.
I mean, there's a lot of good designs,
like Ribbon Bee is fucking adorable.
Ribbon Bee has been a staple of my team
and I love him so much.
I really like, God, what's he called?
Meteor.
Oh, the Meteor guy.
Yeah, he's awesome.
Meteor is really cool.
That asshole never saw one in the whole game.
I was trying to catch that guy.
He kept self-destructing.
It was a big problem, so I gave up.
Never saw him.
No trainers had him.
Turton Nader's pretty all right.
Oh, I hate that guy.
I like Trampa's dumbass face.
Oh, I really like Trampa.
The one that I expected to totally hate
and then absolutely loved.
And I think the second form has the terrible design,
but fucking Mudbray and Mudsdale are just so good
as like teammates.
Like, he was the only one who's like an absolute mainstay.
I mean, like the donkey?
Yeah, the donkey's adorable.
And then it evolves into this hideous fucking horse.
Very underwhelmed, very underwhelmed by their designs.
Yeah.
Not excited about them.
I'm okay with the first form,
but the second form is just hideous,
but like, he's so fucking good.
I really came to like him
because just because we met like a trainer,
you know, that girl, whatever her name was,
who would know her or something.
I was like, that guy was like her, her rock, you know?
He was cool.
And you get to like those guys.
I like, I respect for that Pokemon.
He's a hardworking dude.
I also, have any of you seen Pu-Ku-Mu?
Pu-Ku-Mu?
Which one's that?
I have.
I don't know the name.
Pu-Ku-Mu-Ku.
Oh my God, that thing is disgusting and I love it.
It's this little black ball with like red spikes on it
that's got like an anus for a face,
but like, it's basically like,
I think it's meant to be kind of the Wabafet of this game
where it does like weird fucked up things
and has weird attacks and like it's...
It gets cursed.
Dude, it literally spews out its organs to attack every turn.
It's revolting.
Oh, there's an actual animal like that in real life.
Yeah.
There's a little mini game you can play
when you get to this resort hotel where you can like,
you have to, they basically pay you
to chuck Pu-Ku-Mu's back into the sea.
Yeah.
You just walk around the beach picking up Pu-Ku-Mu's
and throwing them back into the ocean.
Sadly, there's no animation for it.
Excuse me, trainer.
There are Pu-Ku-Mu's horrifying our beach goers.
We would appreciate it if you could get them
the fuck out of here.
It said that people trip over them, so.
Oh, God.
Just imagine like tripping and like falling
on a sack of organs and it bursting in your face.
Oh, God!
Ah!
Hey, was it Barakamon that has the episode at the beach
where they like grab sea cucumbers
and they like squirt their gross white in it all over?
Yeah.
I believe that's the one.
What kind of a defense mechanism is that?
Who does that?
Oh, whatever.
Oh, yeah, it was Barakamon.
I mean, don't ask me.
Barakamon?
Yeah.
One of the only animes I've ever seen.
I don't think I have any particularly Pokemon I disliked.
I will say that I did like that Meteor Pokemon a lot.
I wish that had a chance to use them in my team,
but I just got so frustrated by his self-destruction.
But I like that guy a lot.
His design is cool.
He's a Meteor boy.
Awesome.
I was like Bruxish.
Wait, which one's Bruxish?
Bruxish is the idiot's fucking fish.
That ugly ass fucking di-dive monstrosity.
It's uglier than wishy-washy?
It is uglier than wishy-washy, by the way.
Hey, you know what?
I'm trying.
Did you see it's like...
I have absolutely no idea what any of you
have been saying about these Pokemon.
Because most of them are like,
most of them you won't even fucking see.
Like so many of the new Pokemon never even show up.
Guys, look at the shiny of Bruxish.
Hey, he looks cool.
No, he's fucking ugly.
Another pick for my favorite is a cutie fly in Rybon.
Those guys are really great.
Yeah, cutie fly is great.
You know what this Bruxish reminds me of the game
Amazing Island, where you make your own monsters
to do mini games with?
It looks like something a child would make.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
It looks like something that my fucking brother,
when he was eight, would have made an Amazing Island.
By the way, guys, here's a substantive point
about something that I love about this game.
And it is by making the transition of Pokemon to 3D
and adding something like the Pokemon interaction thing,
refresh or whatever, and the petting stuff,
what that's done is it's forced Game Freak
to add more personality to their Pokemon
than would have been visible before.
Like what I said before about how the Drake,
Drake, the Grass Starter Final Evolution,
how it pulls its little things.
City-wise.
Yeah, yeah, just city-wise, that's right.
How it pulls the leaves to shrink its hoodie self.
Like having something like the Pokemon refresh thing
that lets you interact with them personally
and having a 3D model that can do these extra animations
way easier than a sprite would be animated to do,
it lets you learn things about the Pokemon
and the way they act and more details about them.
And I think that is great.
I do like that.
In White 2, I was really,
I really liked when I encountered a Jolteon
and it's animation, it has like a really fast animation.
Like it's just sitting there,
but it's like jittering back and forth really fast.
Yeah, it's personality.
In the old games that they never could have done that,
but the fact that like it had better graphics
and this one, it gives it this weird movement
that like really gives it more.
Yeah, I do really like that stuff.
One thing I've noticed about the models in particular,
the first gen one is that they're exactly the same
as the ones you can see in Pokemon Go,
which is pretty cool.
Are they the exact same models?
Yeah, I've checked a lot of them, they're all the same.
Oh, that's, I have no problem with that.
They definitely have a standard 3D model
that they're using henceforth.
Cool.
Part of the reason I really like Pokemon Go
is just being able to look at a Pokemon in 3D
and tap them and make them do a funny thing.
And it's like you can do that in this game
and it's just good.
I like that.
I'm good.
Oh.
So anyone have any other topics regarding the sun and moon?
They want to talk.
I have one.
I have some way of do ranting I could do.
Monkey, you go ahead.
Okay, okay, listen boys.
I don't want to stay on this too long.
It boys ain't girl.
But here's the thing.
Mage, I just met you, nothing against you.
But otherwise, the only person here who I like is Hippocrite.
I don't give the fuck about the rest of it.
Right, sure.
So Hippocrite, I need to know.
This is your Spider-Man in the Civil War moment.
Are you team Ben Saint or team Monkey?
I need a definitive answer.
Right fucking now.
Yeah, me too.
You know what?
Uh-oh.
I don't know.
I'm rooting for both of you
because I haven't seen your first battle.
I don't know.
The world hasn't seen it.
Hippo, Hippo, by trying to please both of us,
you've pleased neither of us.
That's true.
You're now under your worst.
Hippo, you're shunned from being untimely.
I'm throwing you under the bus.
Let me make an educated decision.
No, no, I won't allow that.
Let's see who wins the first battle so we can play it.
Oh, okay, this is the stronger party.
You've got to go with the stronger side.
You've got to choose now for your decision to mean everything.
Based on your videos,
I think
it's going to be Momke.
Yeah!
Oh, no!
Fuck you, Ben.
Oh, my God.
I just enjoy the chipper attitude.
Yeah.
Oh, wow, Ben.
I can be chipper.
Wait.
I feel the opposite.
I felt like Ben was way more chipper,
whereas Momke, at least in the first three,
was like, oh, this game is not friendly to Nuzlocs.
I can't get enough Pokemon.
Yeah, you know what?
I don't know.
I actually can't remember anything
that I've seen in my review videos.
I guess you have to have a chipper off
so that the most chipper will gain my affection.
We'll put you both into a wood chipper
and whoever crawls out is the winner.
Yeah, let's go fargo up in here.
No, I'm on Team Momke.
Well, Ben, we know that your goal is to enslave,
you know, dominate all the Pokemon.
Momke, do you have any goal of this nature?
Are you just trying to be the best boy you can be?
Yeah, my goal was to dominate all the Pokemon, too.
OK, so it's a real clash of the superpowers here.
But Momke's doing it sexually.
Yeah, baby.
I'm tempted to.
I had like a little weeaboo revelation
in the course of this conversation,
but I don't think anybody will know.
Nobody will know what I'm talking about.
So I will only do it if you guys give a proof.
Throw it out there. I want to hear it.
I just want. OK, I go for it.
All right, well, there's this.
Actually, Ben, you'll know what I'm talking about
because you've seen this show.
The anime series Katana Gattari.
Katana Gattari is a show about like there's 12 different
like guys who all are like they have a special sword
and they're all like crazy weird designs.
And each one is like you there's like some kind of weird way
that the main character has to fight them in order to,
you know, to get their sword.
And they're all these like really different,
interesting types of fights.
And the guy who did the character designs
for Katana Gattari like I think did like the designs
for this game because I was saying, man,
the characters in this really look like Katana Gattari.
They're all like weird hairstyles
and really out there stuff.
And then someone told me, yeah, that the character designer,
his name shows up twice in the credits.
And I was like, oh, shit, he actually worked on it.
Then I thought about it.
And the way that the trials are in this game
where each one is like a really unique,
different kind of way to get your stone
is kind of like Katana Gattari.
And then the entire Aether Foundation plot
is just literally the story of Kill, Lock, Kill,
like exactly the same story.
So this game is basically Katana Gattari
and Kill, Lock, Kill combined.
You know, okay.
Sure, that's reasonable.
But you know what?
Katana Gattari was very disappointing.
It was.
I disagree.
Though it was like more talky than I would have liked to be.
Well, of course it's talky.
Dude, the ending was the fucking best thing that ever happened.
The last episode was pure orgasm.
That last episode made me want to kill myself.
I hated it more than anything in the world.
Just tell me why.
Real quick, why?
Dude, I have a 4,000 word post on my blog about that,
if you want to read.
Sum it up in five words, did you?
Just tell me why.
Gay, gay, gay, nigger dick.
The final fight up the tower was fine.
It was the girls.
That was terrible too.
I don't know, whatever.
It was the girls.
Guys, guys, guys, let's keep on topic.
No, I don't want to say that it was the girls.
Get away from the anime.
Shut up.
It was the girl being like, yes, I was only,
I only, I tricked myself into loving you
as a part of my scheme to use you.
I didn't care about that at all.
I didn't care about that.
But okay, I did have something Pokemon related about that.
Wait, I just want to make a note
that the Ben St. Army and the Ben St. Fascist regime
coming to a store near you takes a hard line stance
against human Pokemon sexual relations.
I take the exact opposite stance.
I knew, I thought so.
You know, Ben, I was about to say that I am
I'm very against that and I won't allow it.
I'm going to have my own, I need a Magi-Chan to monitor
How do you all feel about the whole of being
a Pokedex occurring?
How do you feel about there now being
a dominatrix Pokemon?
Is there?
Who's that?
There's a Pokemon called Serena.
It's the final.
Oh yeah.
Of whatever.
It literally is just like a dominatrix.
I was hoping you were going to say it was
the Alolan form of Mr. Mime.
Ben, I was going to say, Ben,
that I'm going to put my flag down
and say that I am firmly on Team Ben St.
But this sexual relations clause has blown out.
Oh no, I'm driving away my core constituency.
The fact that no one still exists, Ben,
means that I can never adopt this philosophy.
So you're done.
You're done for all time.
Are you on Team Humpty then, Nate?
I have no choice.
It's the only option.
I'm firmly on Team Humpty.
You're all sinners.
I got you're own fucking brother, dude.
Sinners!
You did this to yourself, Ben.
You made your bed.
Okay, by the way, substantive point,
by the way, I was going to say,
I hated every single trial.
I think gyms being sacrificed for trials
was a huge mistake.
Why did you hate the trials?
The trials?
See, well, okay, let me respond to that.
Okay, the trials already,
or the gyms before, they were the battles,
but they also had like a puzzle,
some of which were really dumb.
So it seems like the trials are kind of just like the puzzle
that used to just be incorporated into the gym.
Yeah, only with random battles, so.
The trials I've seen so far.
I did the thing where you have to find the Zangus,
or not the Zangus, the young Goose.
It was pretty minimal.
It didn't bother me that much.
It was kind of dumb, but whatever.
I know that there's one, or the one in the demo,
and I feel like there's probably one coming up
that involves the Pokefinder,
and I hate the Pokefinder.
Nope, never have to use it.
Oh, thank God.
The young Goose one is like the most.
In the demo you had to use.
I think the young Goose one took the longest
out of like any of the trials.
Well, that are like the grass one.
They're all like the grass one.
You can think that the trials,
you just have to chase it down the normal ones.
You have to go to the holes and find them in their holes,
and then you gotta get those.
For me, that's a Redditor one.
Oh, really?
Yeah, yeah, it's different between Sun and Moon.
Ah, interesting.
Well, okay, you can find them inoffensive.
I didn't really hate them.
Yeah, I agree with Ben.
They kind of felt like the puzzles from gyms
that I also didn't give a shit about,
and could do without, frankly.
But that still leaves you with what I consider a big loss,
and that is,
the lead up of fighting all the elementally,
or the type-themed trainers in one condensed space,
and then lead up to a big gym fight,
because one of the most valuable things about that,
in my opinion, is that it does what Digi said,
or what Digi was talking about before,
and it encourages you to switch up
the Pokemon they're using,
because you know that you'll want a certain Pokemon
with a certain type to be used for that gym currently,
with the way you work with trials.
I don't think that, I don't think that's the case.
I don't think that, I didn't feel that pressure at all.
The different trials have different types of Pokemon anyway,
so you change the moves anyway.
Dude, just tell me,
did you really feel a sense of satisfaction
clearing a trial versus beating a gym?
Because I felt it was way less.
Yeah, I felt it was exactly the same.
I don't care about gyms.
I had more fun, honestly.
This isn't about fun, Mage.
It's about extracting as much percentage of gratification
as you can.
I mean, it's satisfying to beat a book.
It's fun.
Yeah, I thought the trials were,
I thought all of them were cool.
I like how they were so unique from one another.
And the trial Pokemon are harder than gym leaders,
because with gym leaders,
you only have to fight one Pokemon at a time,
and in this, you have to fight two.
Well, like I said, I don't dislike the totem battles.
I think the totem battles are fine,
but you have to admit, there is something lost here.
Like, the way that gyms work is the only thing
I thought was, sorry, Hippo.
Well, for me, the thing that is lost is the trainers,
but I don't care really about the trainers.
I guess I missed that a little bit, but it's not.
I think there was a simultaneous gain and loss
in the trial areas versus the gyms,
because on the one hand, I thought the gyms,
there's a lot more memorable ones.
In X and Y, there's one where you fucking swing
across these vines and you're climbing this tower
to go fight a grass guy.
There's one where you're navigating a spider's web
to go fight the bug guy.
There's nothing in this game that's like that.
There's something that's so different and out there
that it really sticks out.
But on the other hand,
going to fight the first kahuna is just like,
I just went into his hut and fought him.
But on the other hand, with the trial areas,
they are places you can go back to
and they're actually integrated into the world
and they feel more like a part of the world
whereas the gyms are just these totally isolated things
that have nothing to do with the rest of the game.
Well, yeah, but they're sitting that way.
It's not like that's out of place, they're done.
But both the gyms and the elite four
are kind of like that in the other games
where it's just like you just kind of show up at a place
where it's like, okay, now it's time
to just have this radically different experience.
Whereas in this game, all of the captains
are like introduced way beforehand.
You already know who they are.
Well, I'll just say that experience was, in my opinion,
the best part of Pokemon games.
So obviously for me, I'm not going to like that.
In Gen five, at least,
like I know in white two, like the champion
and like previous champions and the elite four
and the gym leaders, they will,
I think it's mostly in the post-game,
but like they show up and like you encounter them,
like if you go to fight in the Pokemon World Tournament,
the gym leaders and the elite four
will be your opponent sometime.
And there's like a place, I think they like,
I think some of them like rents-
I think that's why I did that with the battle shateau.
Like they rent summer homes in Undellatown, I think,
or at least one of them like has a summer home
in Undellatown and like they kind of do things
around the world.
This isn't the first game to have the gym leaders
sort of be more integrated into like the workings
of the world, but it is definitely feels,
I feel like they pushed it a lot more,
kind of like I feel the way that they pushed like Pokemon
as a part of daily life.
Yeah, sure.
Ride Pokemon.
Let me just tell you, like, I mean,
when you first meet Elima,
I wouldn't have even known he was a gym leader.
It was just like a guy you kind of knew.
I wouldn't have even known it was a he.
Yeah.
I could tell it still, yeah.
I could, yeah, same.
I was lying.
Well, I mean, I was just gonna say,
my favorite part of any Pokemon game ever
is in Heart, Gold, and Soul, Silver
at the end of the game in the post game
where you can track down each gym leader
that you fought, of which there are 16.
You can break into the house and kill them.
That's right.
You can follow, it's incredibly complex to get them all,
but there is one house where you can gather
every single Pokemon trainer, every single gym leader,
and then you can fight them, not as they were before,
because if the first gym leader you fight
is the flying guy who has two pieces of shit flying types,
they do nothing, they're level five or whatever,
but here, he's got a team of six guys,
they're all maxed out.
The best team you could possibly have
for a flying type gym leader,
fighting each of those guys and beating them
is the best experience of any Pokemon ever
because it's fun.
Nothing is cooler than theming a Pokemon team
around one elements and then strategizing how to fight it
and like, oh, what am I gonna do?
He's gonna counter me with this.
It's the best, it's the best.
And I definitely feel like with the de-emphasis of gyms
in general and the fact you don't even fight
some gym leaders, that's de-emphasized.
So my only point is that, yeah, this thing,
I really like it and it wasn't as big a part of this game.
So, all right, we can move on from that anyway.
Hey guys, I think I have a question
we should have probably asked at the very beginning.
Which version of the game you have
and which starter did you start with?
Just curious.
Oh, well, I, Ben Sainz, got sun
and I got a Goose the Rowlet.
So, real quick, before we move on from that topic though,
I'm looking into it and you can indeed fight
most of the trial captains again.
Like, if you go back to where they were,
you can fight them for real.
Well, that's great.
That's exactly what I was hoping would happen.
So that's good on it, good on the sun and moon.
Though I would really wonder why it isn't all.
I know in white too, you could,
there was like secondary fights for all the gym leaders
and stuff after you became champion.
Fantastic, couldn't be happier.
That's exactly the sort of thing I want Pokemon to do
every single time, never deviate from that.
Because the thing, Pokemon rewards you,
the thing that feels the best about playing Pokemon,
at least to me, is big climactic battles
where you're pushed to stress and strategize
and it's even more fun when they're themed
around a certain type and then winning.
You feel great, you get like a badge
that's designated for that thing.
It's the best.
It's the best thing Pokemon has to offer.
Let's go back to the mage question.
Yeah, please.
Well, I got Pokemon moon and I got the Snoopy Clown boy.
Snoopy Clown.
Are you talking about?
Ah, Paulio.
Oh, right.
He's not.
He's not Clio.
Hey, he's not Clio.
I'm same as Gibbon.
I also got moon and I got Poplio.
I'm exactly the same as you guys.
Oh, that's crazy.
I got sun and I picked Rowlet
because he's objectively the best.
Yeah, we're sun, Rowlet boys.
Yeah, we are, all right.
And we're moon.
All three of us.
Nobody likes cats.
No one picked Litten, yeah.
Yeah.
You know, Litten's first form is indeed dope.
I like Litten.
I was on team Litten until I saw his third evolution
and then I just abandoned him immediately.
Some people like it.
I like it because he's a wrestler,
but he doesn't, it's stupid.
He's still ugly.
Tony the Tiger sort of bullshit.
Yeah, like I've said this so many times
to so many people, I like the theme.
I think it's cool that he's a wrestler,
but I just hate that how he looks.
I gotta say, I kind of regretted getting sun.
Not that, I mean, I would have got it anyways
because I always picked like the red one.
It's like a nostalgia thing.
But I found out only after having played
through the whole game that they're on different clocks
that in moon, it's like everything's time
of adjusted 12 hours from where you currently are.
So like it's always night at day and day at night.
And I was like, this would have been a huge help for me
because I only played in the fucking, you know,
in the AMs, like just staying up all night.
And so I actually had to change my in-game clock in sun
so that I could catch daytime Pokemon.
Well, wouldn't you have had to do it
the opposite way to catch nighttime Pokemon?
I don't know that there are a lot of nighttime Pokemon,
maybe.
Yeah, wherever.
Radita, it's very important.
There would have been more nighttime Pokemon in Pokemon.
The most important Pokemon.
Alola Ratata.
What a wonderful mon.
Someone fill in for me.
Eight, no.
My Android dog.
Queens, no worries for the rest of your days.
Kahoola Matata.
All right, Kahoola Matata.
So are we going to go ahead and say
that this is just a Pokemon Sun and Moon podcast?
Yeah, I think we've abandoned.
Well, I mean, if we do a general Pokemon podcast,
it would be also hours long.
That would take 50 hours.
So we can do that either as a separate thing.
It was funny because I didn't think,
I thought we wouldn't end up talking about Sun and Moon
that much because almost no one's played much.
I mean, we beat it, but.
I mean, all right, what is there to talk about?
Sun and Moon has rendered all the other Pokemon games obsolete.
They don't matter anymore.
No, no.
It's as though they never were.
We have to go back.
We have to remember.
We've got to make Pokemon great again.
Yeah, we just have to keep the good, improve the bad.
Who said that Kukui was the sexiest professor?
The sexiest professor is Professor Willow from Pokemon Go.
Hey, Pokemon Go, that doesn't fucking count.
No, I'm just kidding.
Can you talk about how much I hate Pokemon Go
before we end this thing?
Yeah, please, yeah, tell me about how much you hate Pokemon Go.
Pokemon Go is the greatest.
Pokemon Go fucking sucks because I live in Iowa.
Oh, yeah.
It's fucking, the farmhouse doesn't count as a stop.
I have tried so hard to enjoy Pokemon Go
and at many times I have succeeded,
but they just keep making it worse with every update.
They keep making their own game worse on purpose
over and over again.
Ben was having such a great time.
He was telling us all these stories
and it's only, it's only good.
For the first week, for the first,
well, I mean, when I play it,
now how I play it is when I go somewhere,
I get in the car, I boot it up,
and then when I get out of the car,
I look around and see if there's anything to catch.
If there is, I catch it,
and that's how I play Pokemon Go.
In the first week that it was out,
there was the beautiful thing,
there was a tracking system
that would let you actually track down a Pokemon.
Like you could see where it was
and it would give you a good idea
of like where to go to find it.
And I was like walking around neighborhoods.
I was walking into like parking lots and stuff.
I was going like-
Children's playgrounds.
Yeah, I was going like-
Hearing in their windows at night.
I was sneaking onto private property
and trying to fucking find these Pokemon.
It was the most fun I ever had.
It was fucking amazing.
Me and my friends went to Tufts University
and we ran, we would spread out.
We'd be like, oh shit, a hitmoanly.
And we would spread out and when someone saw the radar
like go down from three steps to two,
they'd be like, it's this way.
And we'd all run that direction.
Like we would all go converge on them.
It was like the greatest thing.
And then a week after it came out,
they took that feature out and they never put it back
because they just don't want it.
Because they're like, oh no,
that's not how you're supposed to play our game.
You're not supposed to be able to find the Pokemon.
You're only supposed to catch the ones
that you randomly happened to stumble across.
Wasn't the excuse that it was too much
of like a maintenance server issue thing?
They never said that.
That is what fucking assholes on the Reddit said.
They were trying to think of excuses for the company.
No, there's no way-
I think maybe it's because they didn't want people
sneaking onto private property all the time.
Yeah, well, fuck them.
Or flooding those heads.
That's not the game I want.
The game I want is not one that discourages me
from doing such things.
It was the most important one ever.
The only good thing to come from Pokemon Go
was the great Hippocrite video you can find in the description.
Go click on the link right now.
Give it a big ol' like, subscribe.
And playing the season.
I'm going to remember to put that in the description.
Maybe someone will say in the comments.
I'll put it in the comments.
Hippo, that was a really good video.
And I didn't even know the reference and I still liked it.
I'm curious, Gib.
How have you managed to enjoy Pokemon Go
despite all these deficits?
Well, the first thing was I wasn't around
at the very beginning when everyone was-
When it was good.
So you don't know what you've lost, yeah.
Well, I mean, there was the tracker,
but I didn't have a group of friends to play with.
And I never felt like going to track Pokemon.
I was just so like, well, there's a Pidgey.
I haven't got a Pidgey yet.
I'll go get that.
Tracking things, I didn't really,
I mean, I live in a suburban area and there's not a,
there weren't a lot of spawns around.
Recently, they've upped spawns in general
in lower spawn areas.
So it's more tolerable now,
but I didn't use the track to its fullest extent.
So I don't know, I don't really know what I've lost.
We had a good time playing Pokemon Go all day.
Oh yeah, we went to London.
We got a bunch of Gengar, it was great.
Where was mine?
We also got the Charmander nest, remember?
Oh yeah.
Yeah, I went there with my brother.
Right next to Buckingham Palace is a fucking Charmander.
It's probably changed now,
but there's fucking Charmander everywhere.
But the reason that I am still having fun with it
is because I don't have that too many things to catch,
but I do have a lot of walking to do.
I have a lot of eggs to hatch
and I have a lot of candy to get.
Hippo, part of your involvement with that game,
wasn't it because you don't generally like the Pokemon games?
And this was like one that's not a Pokemon game?
I liked it because I generally,
I mean, I'd been playing the Nuzlocke
because Ben played the Nuzlocke
because Monkey played the Nuzlocke.
I wanted to give it a go.
And I decided, I realized I don't actually like
the battling in Pokemon.
Oh yeah, I forgot your deep hatred
of all the Pokemon.
Why haven't we touched on that?
Let's get that debate going.
The battling in this Pokemon moon's been great, so.
Talk about a hypocrite.
Wait, were you just complaining about moon
and how it was the worst game ever, like an hour ago?
No, that was because I was trying to catch a Phoebus,
but I caught it.
Oh, hey, I just remembered about how in battles,
they show you what your moves are gonna do
and that's bullshit.
That's casualization.
No, it's awesome.
No, it's the best thing that's ever happened.
It's great.
The fact that you like it is what makes it casualization.
Yeah, that's right.
I don't know how to put them straight.
It doesn't feel like attaching items to his Pokemon.
It's definitely casualization,
but I don't think that's a bad thing.
Okay, but think about it.
I don't like it, but I can live with it.
Dude, just think about it.
So many times this has happened to me.
I've been playing through this game and like,
okay, all these Pokemon, yeah,
like I don't even think about what they are.
Just look at my moves.
It's gonna be strong.
I use this one.
What that's done is that when I then find a Pokemon
that I haven't seen before,
even if I know what type it is in my head,
I have not trained myself to remember
what is good against it
and then I just suffer because I, you know,
I'm not ready to prepare for the demo.
It's not, well, yeah, but it's the game
not leading me to learn.
I can't remember that perfectly fine.
You can't remember shit.
What's strong against dark?
Tell us what's good against dark.
It was a bug.
Fighting.
Because it was like that classic Game Grumps movement.
The goth kids don't like having bugs on them.
That's why.
That's one, but there's not something else
that's good against them.
I learned typing finally because of this mechanic,
but there were so many fights I got into
where like an enemy would show up and I'd be like,
what the fuck is that?
Because if you fight it for the first time,
it doesn't give you the information.
And usually that was the cause
of why I would have a team fight.
Wait, when you fight them the first time,
it doesn't tell you what's super effective.
No, it only tells you that if Pokemon
that are already in your Pokemon decks.
Well, I like that.
Then you have C.
You don't have to catch.
And if you're in a Nuzlocke,
then that means you can get totally fucked.
If there's some Pokemon you don't know what it is.
It's called just knowing what they are, dude.
You just got to know these things.
Some Pokemon designs just don't make sense.
Like, look at Crab Brawler, the Crab Brawler.
Yeah, I just, I mean, I would expect it to be
at least a little bit of water,
but no, it's just pure fighting.
Yeah, it's just totally fucked me up.
That's totally thought it would be water.
Totally meant to mess with you.
And it knows water attacks too.
So it totally fucked me.
Oh, like Laurentus, it's pink.
And it's like, it's based on a bug
that pretends to be a flower,
but it's pure grass type.
It's not even bug grass.
It's not bug fairy.
It's just pure grass.
It makes no sense.
These are problems to me.
There's lots of Pokemon that are weird like that.
Yeah.
When we talking about Pokemon Go,
I was trying to say something about,
all right, I don't like battling.
Pokemon Go was fun because I could just catch the Pokemon
and not have to battle.
That was that point.
Let me try and defend.
The main point I was getting to the whole time ago
was I like Pokemon Go because it gets me out of the house
and I like walking around the park every day.
That's it.
I think that's the main draw of Pokemon Go.
See the irony of how Ben plays Pokemon Go
is that Ben never leaves the house.
He only opens up Pokemon Go when we're already going somewhere
and then becomes entirely consumed by Pokemon Go.
As though it was a game that he's been playing obsessively
for the whole time,
but then actually he doesn't even think about it
until you leave the house
and then suddenly it's like the only thing
that matters in the world.
It's not with Game Freak every single day.
Ben got out of it.
We were stopped at a stoplight
and the light had just turned green
and Ben was like, wait, I see a Gengar.
He got out of the car.
Dude, that's a Gengar.
You got to get out of the car.
Yeah, man.
You fucking jump out into traffic for a Gengar.
That's why he's a Gengar.
He lures people to their death.
That's canon.
Yeah, yeah, speaking of Gengar,
I was reading the Sun and Moon Pokedex descriptions of him
and they're fucking horrible.
The Sun Pokedex says if you feel a sudden chill,
it means a Gengar is coming for you.
Don't give up.
You can't run.
You know what?
You don't have a sudden chill.
What if it's just a light breeze?
No, it's just like if you feel a sudden chill,
it means a Gengar is coming for you.
You can't escape.
There's no such thing as a light breeze.
Is this true, guys,
that what the Pokedex entries are
are kind of just the opinions of Rotom?
He's just like telling you what he thinks
is going on about these Pokemon.
He's like making shit up.
The Pokedex has always been ridiculous.
Yeah, this game's gone, like, I mean,
they've always had lots of dark, weird shit,
but this game's like kind of ramped it up even more.
When it's in canon described to you
at the Aether Foundation,
that there are these Pokemon that just destroy Corsulas
and therefore the sea is lined with bits of Corsula.
They tell you that.
And if you get into,
I found out that if you have that Pokemon,
I don't remember which one it is.
I think it's that new poison thing, but I'm not sure.
But apparently if you get into a doubles battle,
where like, you know, where Corsula is at low health
and then it calls for help,
that Pokemon will come down and it will kill Corsula.
What? Oh my God!
I read something similar, like with Carbink and Sableye,
because now Sableye apparently preys on Carbink,
so yeah, Carbink.
That's why he killed him.
That's why I couldn't catch that fucking asshole.
Wait, wait.
I mean, I read that Carbink will summon Sableye.
Wait, Sableye kills Carbink?
Apparently.
Yeah, holy shit.
They show up because it's low on health
and then just eat him.
Oh my fucking God.
That's insane. That's the coolest thing.
I thought it was just like a weird recoil thing.
I didn't pay attention to it, but now that I know,
Sableye ate him and then I caused a lot of pain.
It's completely redeemed.
It's completely redeemed, the summoning health pun.
It's still annoying.
I like it so cool.
I already liked the fact that sometimes they call for help
and nothing comes.
It's sort of like, oh God, they're crying like,
please don't kill me.
And it's like no help came.
All right, that's cool.
But like, I beat this whole fucking game
and nothing like this happened.
I didn't, they only summoned more of exactly
what was already there and they never fucking killed each other.
So fucking game.
You have to, like, other stuff only starts showing up
usually if you fought multiple.
The more you kill, the more the weird shit will come up.
It just sounds like you kind of need to be delivered.
You kind of need to seek the stuff out.
The first time carving called for help,
Sableye showed up, but I managed to catch the Sableye.
Maze, didn't you say that a Gyarados showed up
when you were fighting a Magikarp?
Yeah, my first Magikarp.
It's called for help.
Yeah, the very first time I cast the whole...
The old rod.
The rod or whatever.
Yeah, the rod.
Whatever.
So, and I caught a Magikarp.
I was like, oh, hey, a Magikarp.
I'm gonna catch it, but then it called for help
and then the Gyarados came to help it.
That's badass.
Let me try and defend the fact that it shows you
the moveset.
Because like, if it didn't show you the moveset,
I mean, you would just look it up, right?
So isn't it just like...
Well, you should know.
You should learn.
You should cut it out of her life.
Because it's already in your Pokedex.
Like your character has that information, right?
Your character has registered this Pokemon
in their Pokedex and knows what type it is.
So logically, you should be able to just pop open
your Pokedex and like quickly reference like,
oh, this will be super effective against it.
Well, okay, you know what sense in character.
It's just cutting out the incredible middleman
of having to fucking constantly look up
every single thing if you're not...
Okay, well, here's the thing though.
That's a pretty reasonable point and makes sense to me,
but like the fact remains,
it is definitely, you know,
simplifying the game for you and that that's okay.
I guess that's not a big problem.
It does make logical sense.
But then there's lots of other things like that too.
Like, and this has been in, I think,
the last game or two, like X and Y before that, I think,
where like now when you catch a Pokemon,
your Pokemon still gain it.
They gain experience from that battle.
And that also makes sense, but the trend here overall
does feel like they're just trying to make it as easy
as possible.
Shut up.
I worry about that.
That's stupid.
Well, it's already a problem.
Wait, wait, wait, what you just said was, yeah,
I was like, here's the thing, here's why it's not bad.
And you were like, hmm, I agree.
That's not that bad.
But let me demonstrate how the overall trend is bad
by giving you another example of something that isn't bad.
But that's true.
Okay, guys, guys.
Let Mage go, let Mage go.
Listen, like there's over 700 Pokemon
and you're probably gonna wanna switch out
between them every now and then.
So alternate ways of getting more experience
or knowing which type,
like because there's so many crazy type things as well,
the game kinda helping you
because there's so many Pokemon
and just so many weird ones.
There's no daycare,
so you can't leave Pokemon in this.
Yeah.
Actually, actually, there is a sort of daycare
and that's actually, I almost forgot about this.
This is a great picture.
I don't get an experience from it though.
Well, that's right.
There is one and you get it way later.
It's called the Poke Island or the Poke, whatever.
It's the-
Poke Pelago.
It's the coolest fucking thing in this whole game.
But when do you get it?
When do you get it?
Once you get the fly thing,
I think on the second island sometime.
Oh, okay.
I need to tell you guys what this is
because it's just the best thing ever
and Digi was absolutely right.
I wasn't sold on it before,
but now I am convinced
that it's one of the greatest things
that's been introduced in the game.
So what it is,
it's just an archipelago out at sea
where there are these islands that you kind of construct
and what happens is all the Pokemon
that you have in your box,
they just, they go and they populate those islands
and they do things there.
So like for example,
they help you,
they kind of just hang out on this one island
and then it just attracts new Pokemon.
That just instantly like join your party.
If they, you know, it doesn't happen too often,
but they'll just be attracted,
they'll do it and they'll come get them.
That kind of reminds me of the Digimon games a little bit.
Yeah, it's very similar to that.
And it's just-
I'm not sure how to handle that for Nuzlocke rules.
Yeah, I'd probably, yeah, I have no idea to do it.
You'll have to think about it.
You could just throw them away,
ignore them or something.
Actually, you know what?
You only get them to join your team
if you like tap on them twice, I think.
So if you just ignore them,
then they'll never join your team.
So that's, you know, that's something.
But there's a bunch of islands
that each do different things.
And the fact that your Pokemon in your box
are actually given like a life.
Like they don't just sit motionless in stasis
in a Pokeball somewhere.
They're just out, living life on these archipelagos.
I have not actually experienced it,
but yeah, it sounds amazing and wonderful.
It is wonderful.
I don't know what you guys all talked about.
I was just telling them how great the Poke-Pelago was.
Going on, yeah, it's really awesome.
I wanted to say about the gaining experience
from catching Pokemon thing that like,
I mean, if you're playing this game in such a way
that you're mainly keeping a main team
and like you're not catching a whole lot of Pokemon,
then that will not help you at all.
I mean, you're not catching enough Pokemon
for it to be a big deal.
Well, I catch all the Pokemon I find all the time.
Well, if you're playing such a style
that you're trying to catch all the Pokemon,
then more often than not,
you're catching them not fleeing from them,
which is a much harder thing to do
than actually killing Pokemon
because you have to strategically not kill them.
And so I think gaining experience from that
is like just, it feels way better.
Like I'd rather, it feels like I put more effort
into doing that than I did into just winning a battle.
And I'm glad I gained experience.
Could you imagine how annoying it would be
if you had to kill like 17 Pokemon in a row
that a Pokemon had called for help
and then not getting experience for that after you catch it?
Well, I mean, if a Pokemon faints,
obviously you should get experience.
Actually, yeah, you gain the experience immediately
after killing the fainted ones.
So it's not like you have to wait
for the end of the battle to gain more experience.
Oh wait, so you can level up during one of those things?
Yeah, yeah, it's just like any other battle.
You gain experience every time you knock something out.
Yeah, I mean, I was actually arguing with my friend, John,
that that was actually a good thing to have in the game.
So I'm kind of playing devil's advocate here
because I do like the inclusion
of getting experience when you level up.
It's just in the context of me worrying
about the games being too easy.
Like they didn't have to do it.
And so, you know, I'm kind of defending a point
I don't totally agree with here
just because of the larger context of, you know,
that's why we need to make what's your Tizm.
Even if that's true.
Yeah, Pokemon don't level up as quick as a bullet from a gun.
Man, that experience made leveling too easy.
Did they put in a learning curve in this game, right?
Am I the only one who thinks this
that there was like a learning curve
that you can't over level?
Because I found that trying to grind so I could beat Ben,
it took way longer than in other games.
I didn't grind, so I'm not sure.
Well, it took plenty longer.
The higher level you are compared to the Pokemon,
you're fighting the lower amount of experience you get,
which I think was the same.
There is EXP scaling and that was,
I don't think that was always the case.
Well, maybe not always.
Yeah, that's gotta be a new thing
because I've never seen that before.
It was definitely like that in Gen Five.
I do remember that vaguely, I think, as well.
Really?
Yeah, I was sort of like a little upset,
I think, when I found out about it,
that was years ago, though.
So, yeah, I think it was since Gen Five, at least.
Well, I have never once leveled up a Pokemon to level 100,
and I always wondered where people get
the fucking endurance to do it.
I've done two, but they were in Gen Five.
It's not hard, actually.
In original blue, I did.
How the fuck do you do it?
You just fucking blasted the elite four.
You have to do it so many times, though.
I've beat the elite four over 150 times on Gen Three.
Hell yeah.
To get to level.
That's too many.
That's too many times.
I know it is too many.
Once you get your Pokemon like 10 or so levels
above the elite four, then, I mean,
you can sweep it with one Pokemon.
So it's just gaining all the experience.
I did it in X and Y with Garchomp
just because I was just EXP sharing
for everything else in my party
because I was trying to catch every Pokemon.
So I just go in there with five low-level guys,
sweep the entire thing with Garchomp.
He gains a little bit more than everybody else,
and they all level up fucking all the way
into the stratosphere.
And I just, in just the course of trying
to get all the Pokemon evolved,
I ended up with the level 100 Garchomp.
And Nate, if you're concerned about the time,
you can just play it on an emulator
and fucking throttle through that shit in three hours.
Yeah.
Monkey.
I played White Two on an emulator,
which had a speed-up function,
but I didn't realize it until I was seven gyms in.
Oh my God.
So I played it normally up until the eighth gym,
and then I finally realized I could hold out.
I just did the normal way.
Oh my God, I'm so sorry.
Like a fucking sucker.
Was this in White Two?
Every recording for one of an episode of Ben's Nuzlocke
is like, you know, like six to 12 hours long.
It's no wonder why his series went on for half a year.
It was like three.
That's just because Ben's release schedule.
One of my favorite things to do is to get like a level,
like if there's an old Pokemon in an earlier area
that I hadn't caught yet, and I need to evolve it,
and it's like level two,
I bring it to the Elite Four and I give it the XP share,
and I can see it level up like 50 in a row.
Yeah, that's great to see.
How about the XP share?
The XP share made it so that
I didn't even think about playing this game.
I just used whatever Pokemon I always used
and just fucking didn't worry about switching.
Just killed everything in one hit,
leveled up.
I do like the XP share that keeps your party
the same sort of level because, I mean,
it's like you have your Pokemon that have the good moves
for fighting specific other types,
but sometimes you're in a place where, you know,
your flying Pokemon is useless against everything there,
but you need it for the next area,
and you don't want to have to grind just with the flying
Pokemon in another area because it's useless here.
You can use your useful Pokemon in the right place,
and then switch out when you need a different type,
and they're all generally the same level
if you use the XP share, and I like that.
It's good.
My team is all the same cool level guy.
I guess.
I don't really like the idea of my Pokemon being strong
despite never actually seeing a real battle.
Something about that rubs me the wrong way.
Well, Ben, I've got a question for you, Ben.
You do love the grind, though,
and I don't like it quite as much.
Yeah, Ben, have you been getting a shit ton of comments
on the Nuzlocke of people calling you a pussy
for using the XP share?
Because I certainly have, these fucking babies.
I got one guy, he was like, customarily,
it's customary to not use a key share or a me.
I think he was referring to Pokemon Refresh.
I was like, first of all, customary according to who?
Second of all, shut up.
These fucking entitled babies in the comments
think they can run my game.
The idea that there are Pokemon customs.
Monkey, you said it in your fucking video.
That doesn't make the game more challenging,
it just makes it grindier.
It makes it tedious, that's not fun to watch.
It's just more shit on the cutting room floor for me.
And speaking of having authority over your channels,
Ben, you released your Nuzlocke far too irregularly.
Once a week is not good enough, but they're fucking hour long.
Didn't make them half an hour long.
You need to release twice a week at least.
Why?
Because I said so, because I do edit.
Ben, here's why.
Because you and me are trying to upload our battles
on the same day, and it makes it very weird to schedule
when you only do it once a fucking week.
Yes, there you go.
No, but it's fine.
It worked out this first time,
but we got like 18 more of these battles to go.
I mean, you could easily break those episodes in half.
They are longest shit.
How would that make it any better?
Because I don't want to watch a movie
every time you have a new episode.
I want to watch it day by day.
Why?
I'm looking for more content per week.
There's pros and cons to the different lengths.
I get more views, which is more money.
When it comes to having to...
I don't monetize any of my videos.
Oh, when it comes to why?
Because I would get like a dollar for each one.
It's a fucking dollar.
I don't want a dollar.
Talking about fucking money, it's when you've got two people
doing like a Nuzlocke side by side,
it's kind of weird to have like Ben's come out a week
and then for Monkey to have a regular interval.
So you're more Monkey's playthrough is more in your mind.
And then suddenly there's another Ben one.
Yeah.
And you sort of forget what happened in the Ben one
while you're watching the Monkey ones.
Yeah, Monkey's in their mind.
It's gonna be weird.
That's all I'm...
Well, you got to win the battle of hearts and minds here, Ben.
I don't think...
No, guys, guys, I like events video length
because personally, like when I watch videos,
I usually do other stuff like let's say draws.
So I like lengthy videos
because that means more time for me to draw
rather than click on the next video.
That's really been annoying.
I agree with you, Mage.
To long and short videos.
I'm just saying with the two different players,
they should be the same length.
Hey, it's not about the size of the video,
it's how you use it.
Well, to say that, I think what Mage is saying
is how I feel as well,
but I also think that that's kind of a bad thing for Ben
because you're saying that you like his videos being longer
because it means you don't have to watch the video.
No, I'm watching it.
It's on the side and my drawing is on the other side,
so I'm watching it while drawing.
I've mentioned this to Ben before that with Mumkis,
I actually just watch each episode
and it's because typically what I do is I'll come home
with a sandwich and then I will sit and eat the sandwich
and watch Mumkis' video.
It's just the right length for me to finish my sandwich
before the video's over.
Whereas with Ben's videos,
I almost always just listen to them and I'll glance up,
like with the latest one,
it was helpful because I was actually playing Pokemon,
so it was a good way to have an hour and a half long thing
to have in the background while I was playing,
but I probably would never just sit and watch
an hour and a half long Let's Play video
the way I would with Mumkis' 20 minute ones
and I'm just like, yeah, all right,
it's exactly long enough to finish a sandwich.
Did you, it's funny that you say that, did you?
Because every time you upload a new decompression chamber,
I always jerk off to it.
Yeah, that's a fucking long goddamn jack-off.
The long, slow pumps, dude, that's the way to do it.
Yeah, that's cool that we do our everyday tasks
while watching each other's shitty videos.
I'll be honest, I don't...
Mumkis sitting there, to take so long,
I feel like you're here so fast, I can jack my whole...
Do you want to say something?
Something about lengths of videos.
I actually didn't mean to bring up any of that.
I just need to get more content out.
I like long videos, which is why I made mine the way they are,
because that's the kind of video that I prefer.
This is what I was going to say.
I'll be honest, I don't watch either of them.
I listen to both of them, regardless of the length.
I glance at them every so often.
Yeah, I mostly just keep mumkis tabbed
unless I hear something of particular interest happening,
and then I tab over.
If you don't see every single growl at the scene,
you're missing something.
I mean, I always tab over, I always flip over for them.
Yeah, you have to watch the growl at the scene
every time to get the full mumky experience.
By the way...
That will absolutely have been the intro for this video, by the way.
Yeah!
But finally, one something.
The thing is, I mean, I like my upload schedule.
It's easier for me, because...
You only have to edit once a week, yeah, that makes sense.
Yeah, all you gotta do is edit once a week
and then split it into two files.
But then you have to process it and upload it,
and didgy's internet fucking sucks, it's a hassle.
Well, first of all, my internet's great,
and second of all, I render all this fucking video, so...
My concern, by the way,
was only about you two getting it out at the same time.
But it sounds like you've already got that figured out,
so never mind what I was saying.
Dude, I don't think that's a problem
with getting it out at the same time,
because we are like...
The plan was that three of his episodes would be one of mine.
That's true.
We planned it out ahead of time.
I was like...
Yeah, we decided that it would be two episodes for me
and six for him.
So...
I like that Ben's are long, though,
because I don't have to make a decision
about which one I'm gonna eat my sandwich through.
Like, Ben's can come out once a week,
and I can just focus on that,
whereas on the day-to-day grind of me eating sandwiches,
which is pretty common, you know?
Like, as I wouldn't be able to eat the sandwich
through both of your episodes, you know?
The reason I would like your videos to be the same length
is so that I can watch both of them exactly at the same time.
Yeah.
Unlike me.
I'm like, double screen.
Yeah, double screen,
and not know what I'm looking at.
Have one person's audio come through one headphone
and the other guy through the other?
Yeah.
And then eat two sandwiches.
Yes.
Yes, yes, double fisting.
One meatball and one turkey,
the double meat on a nine-grain wheat,
double meat, turkey, lettuce, tomato.
What was the rest of it, monkey?
I don't remember.
It was never revealed,
and then Manim will quit the channel,
but I think, I mean, if you guys want me to spoil
what was on his Subway sandwich, I'll do it here live.
Oh, I'll do it, too.
By all means.
Oh, my God.
A PCP exclusive.
If you want all your viewers to watch this episode,
if you're like trying to convince them,
just tell them you finally revealed it.
No, we've got to pay all this one.
Pay all this one section.
All right, dude.
Slap that on the tape.
If you want to hear the next crucial minute of this PCP.
You have to go to patreon.com slash mumkey.
Donate $20 per month, and you'll get this.
No, no, no, it's the other one.
No Ben St. Patreon, so I'm not completely sure,
but as far as I know, the other two ingredients
are onions and banana peppers.
Oh, my God.
Holy shit.
So wait, Skain, you go through all of it?
Yeah.
Pay me a picture.
So you get the nine-grain wheat.
Right, yes.
Not toasted, because then the bread gets all crumbly
and shit.
Right.
I don't even remember what fucking cheese.
What was it?
That's cruel.
Oh, I don't remember.
American, it's American cheese.
No, it wasn't American, no.
Not American?
Provolone?
Pepperjack, I don't know.
It wasn't pepperjack.
I think it might have been provolone cheese,
which this is why I was confused why I didn't toast it,
because if you don't toast the cheese,
it's just a fucking, it's a cold piece of cheese, disgusting.
He gets double turkey, double turkey.
He gets lettuce, and now we all know he gets onions
and banana peppers.
That's how you eat Subway sandwich,
and specifically, no tomato.
No tomato.
We both hate tomato very much.
Was there any sauce on it?
Yeah, he said Subway vinaigrette, I think.
That's crucial.
Okay, yeah, all right, so that's it.
Now I can finally go order it,
like ever since he first brought it up,
I was like, as soon as they finished describing the Sub,
I'm gonna go buy one and watch the show,
and it's been fucking three months.
Digi, I want one too, I'm coming with you,
I'm gonna get one too.
We should do that right after the show.
I haven't watched episode four.
No, let's do it after we lift,
because I'm still full.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I've gotta warn you, if you eat the animal way,
you're gonna get big and bloated like him.
Well, you know, Ben, we should buy them,
and we should buy them before we lift,
put them in the fridge,
and then run the constant risk of monkey
eating the other half of our Sub.
That's the full experience.
Yeah.
If you walk in and DeVoo has just devoured it all,
at my street, the curse.
That's why it's called DeVoo, he devours it.
He devours it, yeah.
Hey, that's pretty good.
Does anybody have any more comments about this game?
This is two hours.
I think we've hit rock bottom.
What's that supposed to mean?
I like Pokemon, they're cute.
Usually.
Why am I white and my mom is brown?
That's a good question.
Your dad must be super white.
My game didn't have that problem.
Oh, I thought you were talking about yourself, Ben.
I was like, what the fuck?
It has been a struggle of identity our entire lives.
Did you make your girl brown?
Yeah.
I've seen my video, haven't you?
Where I showed off my fucking girl and how cool she is.
I guess.
I had no brightness reference.
It's the best fucking video I've ever made.
What channel is that uploaded on?
I didn't see that.
Did you, bro, after dark?
It's called Pokemon Trainer Sheik.
The Winter Look.
Yeah, the Winter Look, Winter 2016 Look.
Is there any way of me analyzing
how fucking cute my outfit is?
Is there any way for me to get a winter knit cap
and those sunglasses?
Possibly.
I mean, you start with a winter knit cap.
No, you don't.
You start with a fucking baseball.
Well, Ben's a girl.
As a girl, you start with a cap.
Ben, I don't know.
I've only seen baseball hats, though.
But I'm going to look into this.
I mean, there is no winter clothes.
It's the whole game is all fucking island clothes.
Even though you go to a fucking place,
you mount it a couple times.
Yeah.
But what the fuck?
But yeah, I made that and also an hour and a half
long analysis of Pokemon Sun.
So if anyone listening to this wants to hear a more
structured analysis of the game, I can't believe I had to talk
for another two hours.
Much more structured.
It was, I mean, it was like bullet pointed.
I had fucking full notes for it.
Did you?
Yeah.
The whole thing is like point by point.
Highly doubtful.
I was doing it in the GRPJ style.
I was like trying to.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah, go to go to Hippocrite.com.
I, you know, I deliver a point in watching that.
I avoid watching that because I hadn't beaten the game.
But now that I have, I'll probably go check it out.
Did you do the green screen?
Tell me you did the green screen.
No, I was too lazy for that.
I, I use green sunglasses.
I use the fact that I didn't screen as a way to advertise Hippo more
by assuring the audience that if they watched him,
they'd get this, but better, like with, you know,
like more effort put in.
So have you guys seen that Hippocrite video where he's like
no, I didn't watch the review and he had like this guy who's playing
a guard and he has a big cane and he's taken the key off of him.
And it's really funny.
And I laughed at it.
Yeah, I've seen that video.
And you guys see the Hippocrite video when his guitar comes
in character and it starts crying and it was really funny.
Yeah, we get that picture.
He gives videos are great.
So we've seen that mage video.
All right.
Mage wants us to wrap this up.
Let's finish this off.
OK, well, that that's pretty much it.
We've run the full gamut.
Everything there is to say about this shit.
We talked about it.
Yeah, I think we can say a solid zero out of ten on Pokemon.
So I think we can all agree that this can, should, must
and will be the last Pokemon game.
No, yeah.
No, every three years, I want a new generation.
Everybody say goodbye.
Bye.
Hashtag Team Monkey, baby.
Yeah.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
But I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
My dick, I'm jerking.
Myself, I'm sucking.
I am an asshole.
I am a stupid.
I've got a deadline.
Don't want to do it.
What the hell is wrong with me?
I'm supposed to be making money.
I'm supposed to be creating funny things that the people
gladly will pay for.
Artist and genius, that's what they came for.
Instead, I'm tweeting.
Hashtag repeating.
That's why there's no heat and holes in the ceiling.
Yeah, it's quite the burden.
It's a hard knock life.
Being a genius.