Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I am the best
anal hernia ever. Today we're joined by Ben Saint.
No you're not.
You're right. Ben has that title for sure.
And name only or name only. His spirit is left.
Munchy, defend your existence.
Kid power, kid power, kid pride worldwide, kid pride worldwide.
Rise up against your oppressors.
Oh, you guys remember VHS?
No.
The Davoo is here.
I've been in so many podcasts lately that I feel a little bit of bad about being in a giant, empty,
furniture-less room with such a strong echo. So right now I'm in the closet. I don't...
I admire your minimalist lifestyle.
Davoo's never been out of the closet.
Oh, shit. Mage of the lethal variety.
Hello, Mage here, and I'm speaking from my childhood home right now.
Oh, excellent.
Boo to childhood.
You're such a fucking grump today. What's going on, Scrooge?
Shut the hell up, Digibro's here.
I love you.
Gross.
Oh, there's Mage for a second.
This is deeply uncomfortable.
Is that what it used to sound like? Holy shit.
That's what we all used to sound like.
That's awful.
This was the worst entry.
Everyone, look upon your screen, gaze your eyeballs for one split-half of a fucking second,
and look at the number of this episode. This is episode...
One. One. One.
Of the procrastinator's podcast.
Smash one. Smash one in the comments.
Smash that one.
I mean, you know, if you could spare a few, it would really help me out.
If you could find it in yourself to give this old partner a few ones, then you know.
I mean, I would like...
I know where I'll feel, you know, the economy's down and inflation is up, but it's worth it.
To walk down your local vans, you gotta have a bushel or a barrel full of ones,
but you know what, you get to buy your fucking loaf of bread and your apple,
but if you could just spare a one or two, I wouldn't be able to have...
There would be a lot of Patreon percentages and numbers right now.
Do we need to talk about that right now as well?
What?
What about them? What about them?
Isn't, like, aren't we, like, at a very specific number on Patreon?
Is that true?
No, I'm thinking of Twitter.
We've made one, one, one, one, one, one, one.
Oh, yeah, right.
On Twitter.
Guys, it would really do me a big favor if you would all please pledge to our Patreon
so we could get one, one, one, one on there.
That would be great.
But we are at 111 tweets on the PCP, and we're also following 11 people, which is nice.
Excellent. Excellent. Well, there it is.
I haven't gotten past the fact that it's been 11 weeks since Radcon.
If 3,568 people could unfollow us, please, so we could have 11 followers, that would be pretty nice, too.
What'd you say, Digi? It's been so long since Radcon.
I can't believe it's been 11 weeks since Radcon 3, and we've only edited like half the shit.
Episode 100 was there. If we're on 11, then it's been 11 weeks.
It's been 11 episodes.
Oh, right. It's been 11. Is that another?
It's okay. All right.
It's all down to the ones. The ones are the DNA.
If you look down like a microscope down at your DNA, then you'll realize it's actually not a bunch of dots as it's represented in Jurassic Park.
It's actually a bunch of ones.
You know, they say that the world, they say that everything in the world can be represented by ones and zeros,
but no, ones will do just fine. Thank you very much.
Slightly elongated ones will be the zeroes.
I wanted to be with the one that the one could not stare back at me like I stared at it, drove me to madness.
They call me the weird one hermit now.
That weird one hermit.
One weird old hermit.
Contrary to your belief, this is not actually the make ones joke episode. This is the kids episode.
This is childhood kids boyhood took 11 years to make.
Specifically boyhood. Not childhood.
If you can only respond if you're a boy.
If only boyhood took 11 years to make, this joke would work way better.
There you go. Red line is that.
All right. So here we go, everyone. Childhood, being a child, being small and weak and cowardly.
What do you know? What do you say, Ben? What do you say?
It's wrong and it's a sin.
Are there any redeeming qualities to children?
No.
Any.
They're just humans but words.
Jesus Christ.
I'm coming in.
I'm coming in with a fucking wrecking ball.
That's who I'm talking about.
I'm here to beat the shit out of the establishment.
I'm here to shake the ground like a fucking earthquake.
I'm coming in. Hashtag kid power.
I want to see all these tweets tweeting the procrastination with some sort of funny image or relatable quote from a teenager.
Hashtag kid power.
Why don't you grow a fucking brain already?
Why don't you just fucking get your neurons all set up and get set in your ways like the rest of us?
When I was growing up, I mean, we can get into this later.
But when I was growing up, I was always trying to become like a cool ass adult and be mature and like pay taxes and shit.
And now I realize that's stupid.
But not for the usual like, oh, I don't have any, you know, you don't have any responsibilities as a kid.
You don't have to wake up and be like, oh no.
But because adults are fucking lame and they're always pissy baby fucker fappers who shit their fucking diapers.
And as lame and nihilistic as hell, the optimism of the youth is the only valid outlook in the entire world.
Yeah.
That's a strong argument.
It's like basically the kids next door argument, right?
You know what? You're right.
Talk about them all at the moment.
You've changed my mind.
I feel as though this is like, I mean, I know as many, like isn't the stereotype that nihilistic teenagers are the thing.
And then when you grow up, you get past that.
I don't care what the world is outside of my vision.
Teenagers are known adult sympathizers.
That's for sure.
The reputation of adults being boring and cynical comes from the fact that most adults, i.e. most people, are failures.
It's the failure that makes them uninteresting.
Childhood is where childhood is before you've had an opportunity to fail or succeed.
Most people fail, so therefore you can only fail or succeed in adulthood.
Davoo, you're right.
But that's why I don't like children, because like while adults have risen or have failed or succeeded life,
children haven't even put their cards on the table yet.
They're in the waiting room waiting to even give life a try.
The thing about kids generally is that I see him as like not quite cooked chicken.
Like you put them in the oven and you're like, okay, that could do with a few more years.
I'm not going to talk to him.
He's just being a kid. I don't mind.
He's just doing his kid thing and he's not very interesting.
But I'll let him just sit in the oven for a little longer before I go up and try to treat him as a human being.
That's what an oven neighbor did.
All Hitler tried to do was put that childish race in the oven for a little longer,
but he can't catch no breaks for that activity.
That's sort of like, oh, just a kid, I'll let him run around and smear shut on the walls.
That's the reason why kids are bad is because adults won't just treat kids like adults,
which you just said.
Enough of this bullshit. Children are literally worthless.
They rely on adults for everything.
Everything a child is doing has been done by the effort of an adult.
I feel both the way that Munchie and Davoo feel here because on the one hand,
I feel like I take Davoo's stance because I believe what Munchie says,
that you should be really hands-on with a kid because you really need to educate children
in order to make them understand the world around them.
Don't let them just run around and be a dumbass kid.
Try to make them not a kid anymore.
The goal of every kid is to eventually beat the kid out of them and make them a functional human.
But when you see a kid who's not really your business,
and when I see some dumb, bratty kid out and about,
I think of that Boondocks moment where granddad just beats that kid in the grocery store for the lady
and everyone treats him like a hero.
I wouldn't have probably used the same technique,
but I do feel that sense when I see a dumbass kid where I'm like,
man, someone should do something about that,
but I know that if I tried to, it would just get me in trouble.
So I'm just going to be like, you know what, this kid's just not worth worrying about.
They're like fucking dogs.
They're like fucking dogs in the sense that everyone wants a dog,
and then when you have a dog, you're not trained enough to be able to know what to do with it.
You don't want to be like, oh, I don't want to have to spray it with a bottle of water.
That's so fucking cruel.
You only should buy a dog.
You should have to teach it.
You have to be a parent.
You have to teach them what the world is like.
You have to be a parent and be there.
Sorry, but before you get a dog or you get a child,
you should have to sign a contract saying you're willing to put it down if it goes against you.
If it goes against you.
You should have to play a game of ski ball
or sign a couple of waivers backwards to be able to legally own it.
Sign waivers backwards?
It's the Ned Stark rule.
This is simultaneously a breathalyzer test and a literacy test at the same time, basically.
Also, it's ski ball.
Listen, when I was a child, I didn't do anything good.
The only things I did that were good.
It's on you, dude. It's on you and your parents.
This is a celebration of Munchie's last gasp of childhood because very soon,
he will be taking that thing they do in Kids Next Door where they brain blast you so you're not a child anymore.
That's literally true.
That's what happens. You forget all the secrets and joy of youth.
That happens when they turn 13, but never mind that.
Is that true?
Yeah, because teens are their own faction.
It's not just Jimmy Neutron.
Jimmy Neutron has a brain blast.
Is it from Johnny Quasar, his lesser-known cousin?
Everyone look up Johnny Quasar.
Do you remember in that one episode, though, here's my counterargument where Santa was proved to just be a super genius
just like Jimmy Neutron and also got brain blasts? Do you remember that?
What? That's so fucking lit, dude. Holy shit.
It's like the next evolution of humanity is those people of the brain blast.
Digi, I know the next podcast we should do.
Jimmy Neutron.
Let's fucking podcast every Jimmy Neutron episode and all the movies.
That's going to be my upcoming podcast. Is it Fleek or is it Gay?
And Santa Claus is definitely going to be Fleek.
Fleek or Gay?
Oh, that's excellent.
Like in Jimmy Newtype.
Jimmy Newtype?
Dude, that's like, is anime now. Incredible, incredible.
You're going to see like transformation from like men to beasts over the course of Chibbaka.
You're going to see us like turn into cavemen.
Dude, you guys should definitely do a Gundam Chibbaka so that I can learn anything about Gundam.
That would be really helpful for me.
I don't want to watch mecha shows. I don't care.
But they're, why?
I don't like robots.
That is inconsequential and ignorant. It has nothing to do with the genre of mecha.
Guren Logan being a mecha.
The name that the robots do is what it says.
Okay.
There's a huge movement going on on any Twitter right now of mecha fans being like,
it's always been about the characters. It's not about the robots.
People are stupid. Nobody understands mecha.
It's a big deal.
Gigi, could you please forgive me because the genre is named mecha?
It's like in the room when Lisa's mom says like marriage has nothing to do with love.
But like put a Naruto headband on her and she said mecha has nothing to do with robots.
Here's the thing about genre labels, right?
Let's say that with metal music, you might like one, like there might be one really great metal band who everyone appreciates.
But then there's like a thousand shitty metal bands and some people will just, because they are categorically a metal fan, listen to all of it.
Mecha's the same way.
There are great mecha anime like Gundam that are not really about Gundam, about robots.
Every good story is about human characters.
Exactly.
There was going to be no good mecha.
Speaking about mecha and the human heart conflict with itself.
Give, save us, save us, give.
Speaking about childhood now, because that's the thing, and mecha, I had robot toys.
Which toys did we have and what did we do?
I was post-toy. I'm so young that I was post-toy.
Feeling that too, that's interesting.
Toys are not really, nobody gives a fuck, because you had more advanced things.
Speaking of mechas, Ben and I did have all the megazords that we got for all the years that we cared, and I had a ton of transformers.
I never had that many transformers.
I had the exact same toys as you guys. I also was Power Rangers and then Beast Wars.
I guess the only transforming toy I had was a Digimon toy that evolved quote-unquote.
Which Digimon was that?
In Lithuania, they only had go-bots.
Who was? I want to know.
I think it's called Hawkmon and it evolved into the Armored Digivolution of it.
Oh, I think I had that.
You flipped up a skull and then you turned it upside down and it became like a metal skull.
You put a thing on it and then you expanded its wings and into the wings you put in legs.
It also opened up and you had a little mini world inside of it with a little mini Digimon.
That was really cool.
Speaking of Digimon and childhood, is Digimon still good?
Some people have told me that it got good again or something.
Digimon Tri was good.
A couple of them have their defenders.
Nate, here's what you have to do. You have to Google search Digimon, look at the monster designs.
Do you like them? Digimon is good.
I couldn't tell if he was asking, is the new show good?
And the question is, look at any screenshot of it and you'll be like, I'm not watching that.
That's how I felt about it.
Is it the one with the mobile one?
It looks really bad.
It's one of the mobiles.
No, not that one.
That was an actual child Digimon show.
This is a different thing.
Whatever, we don't need to get a good Digimon thing.
Digimon sucks.
Let me tell you an anecdote from my childhood.
I remember one time, I don't remember why this happened but I got sent to the school guidance counselor
because I was in distress about something.
And who cares?
And I remember going to the guidance and she sat me down and was talking to me
and I remember in hindsight that I ended up just sitting down and talking to my guidance counselor
for a long time about how hard it was for me to decide whether I liked Pokemon or Digimon better.
I remember I did a school write whatever kind of essay that you want.
Not an essay, but a short story in 6th grade or whatever.
And I wrote mine in the style of Homestuck and I had to explain to my teacher what Homestuck was.
I can't believe Homestuck was Munchies childhood.
You know what?
That is weird.
It makes sense though, doesn't it?
Think about Homestuck and look at me.
There is definitely one thing about being a child that is a huge advantage over being an adult
is that adults will never get it.
Children, they get it.
That's literally true, that's literally what I believe that is true.
I feel very much so that occasionally a new thing will come up and people are saying like a word
and I'm like well now I guess I'm an adult because I don't get it.
When Munchies said fleek before, I had a fucking crisis.
I know, I don't say fleek, I said it because it's retarded.
The funny thing about that Ben is that fleek is an old ass slang too.
It's not even in anymore, it's like already out.
I said in the context of a podcast being called is it fleek or is it gay?
I don't actually use the term fleek to describe things.
That was what made it so funny to me is that it's like an already dead slang
but it's funny that Ben had never even heard of it.
My girlfriend is five years younger than me.
But I don't get it because I'm an adult and adults will never get it.
My girlfriend is five years younger than me and she continually refers to hitting the whip
and I have no fucking idea what she's talking about.
What does this mean?
A car is a whip so she probably means go to the car.
Does it mean go for a drive?
No, it's like a dance move or something that I don't understand or comprehend.
Well I don't know anything about dance moves.
This is a bunch of white dudes trying to talk about what is probably an urban dance culture.
An urban dance culture is an urban one.
Come right out and say it, coward.
Alright guys, let's get down to brass tacks here.
I want to hear retarded stories of how you fucked up as children.
That's what I want to hear about.
I've never done it before.
The only time I've ever fucked up is never.
I was trying to think about it but I couldn't do it.
I remember when you fucked up when you didn't carry the monsters podcast.
That's true.
I didn't carry it.
I have a better question for everybody.
I want to know, when you were kids, did you want to grow up?
No.
I have a big story about that.
It's a good question.
I want to hear Monty's big story but me and Nate you go first and then I'll go.
I was just going to say yes.
I reached that at a certain point because of the deep frustration.
Teenagers just want to be able to drive.
They want to be able to do stuff.
That's not true.
It took me years before I fucking got the motivation.
Even Millennial Childs are post-cards.
Millennial Childs are post-cards.
I wanted to be an adult because I wanted to be able to do stuff and seize control of the destiny of my life.
The reason I wanted to be a kid is that I wanted to relinquish control and not have to think about anything.
I just wanted to not be responsible.
Who wants to be responsible for stuff?
I do so I can run my life and win at life.
A lot of my relationship with seeing myself as not wanting to grow up was that I really hated this idea that everyone supposedly was going to grow up.
People would always tell me you're not going to care about toys when you're an adult.
You're going to care about girls once you're an adult.
All those things would piss me off because I was like you can't tell me.
Literally all of them happened.
I remember the day when I could not bring myself to care about toys anymore.
They said you won't care about toys but then I look up from my computer and I see more anime figurines.
I'm already over anime figurines.
I don't even like them.
I keep them somewhere else in the house where I don't have to look at them.
I had a similar attitude of whenever people told me when you're this age you're going to be like this.
Maybe you're not going to fucking decide.
I will decide what I would like.
I will make those decisions.
Thank you very much.
I had similar experiences.
When I was younger I had people tell me when you grow up you're going to grow out of those Pokemon.
You're going to get a job and not draw anymore.
You're going to start caring about things, other things.
And I'm like no.
And there I am liking Pokemon and drawing pretty equal split.
It's always a pretty equal split of things that you have grown out of and also things that you've retained interest in.
Like a lot of the shit that like I wasn't really told that I would grind a lot of things other than the fact that I would probably mellow out.
Which I think a lot of it.
For what it's worth you have mellowed out considerably.
It's true.
It's just that Munchy has mellowed out from like Christ consciousness levels way above like human comprehension to something we can see on the visible spectrum.
Oh you're making me sad dude.
No, no Munchy.
Don't be sad.
It's like Munchy is like a prism that light of the universe is shining through.
But you've refined yourself to be a more focused beam.
Yeah I would say that.
I would give my take on you to say something around the same time I did I think.
MLP reviewer give and take?
Please tell us.
I had to hurry and be called that in full.
Oh sorry.
It's in my head I was supposed to give.
No one told you that name.
I haven't been called.
I haven't heard that name in years.
I'm sorry.
I've been trying to think of my childhood and it's strange that I can't really remember what people were talking about like to me.
Like you know I don't remember things that I was told as a kid necessarily.
I just remember like general feelings of stuff that it was good.
It was good when stuff happened and I want to have that again.
But then you know I guess I just have a bad memory.
I'm not coming up with it.
I'm coming up with like brands like Bionicle and Beyblade and fucking Bugslide.
I define myself exclusively with brands.
I just want to slam back my total quality.
I don't remember what like I was like as a kid and whether I wanted to grow up or not.
I distinctly remember as a teenager looking around at people like getting driving licenses and cars and being still teenagers you know at school but like acting adults and they had suits.
I mean they had school uniforms but they would like you know like I'm cool because I wear this suit thing.
It's kind of like a suit.
It's like I being a creative person.
Yes I don't know what that means.
I distinctly remember feeling an aversion to being an adult in the way that they were doing it.
Like I believe you could be an adult and still be a kid because it's more fun that way.
Like just to be into stupid shit because even if it doesn't mean you're popular it's still cool because you like it.
That's all I can really remember about like childhood yearnings of adulthood.
I remember a lot of cartoons at the time for female specifically were all about fashion and makeup and stuff.
And I had like a very sort of distinctive version to them because I never got into makeup and fashion.
I still haven't and it's always bothered me.
I sort of tolerated the ones that had something else to do like as ashamed as I admit it.
I did like Winx because it had magic not just like fashion and stuff.
Winx was lit yo.
I didn't like the pressure.
Like one of the reasons I didn't want to grow up as well.
I didn't like the pressure of having to dress nice and put on makeup and think about all those things.
I just got damn patriarch.
He's trying to keep you down.
Fuck that.
But before I get into, I should get into my big old story about how it became the boy that you see before you.
The big baby boy.
Himself, right.
I would like to say to Mage, is it true that being a woman is awful?
Not in the sense like it's bad, but in the sense like you do so much shit just like on the reg.
That does seem to be true.
That would seem awful.
I don't.
I don't do it.
I'm purple.
I'm not a female.
Well that's tough.
Mage has taken the Ben approach of just shirking all societal expectations.
You live in the alternative lifestyle.
Yeah, if you just live an alternative lifestyle and become a weird hermit, no one expects anything of you and you don't have to do anything.
I want to see fan art of Ben living his alternative lifestyle.
Just in whatever way you imagine that, please.
That could mean any number of things.
It could mean anything.
There's no definition for what that means.
It could be literally anything.
You have a question though guys.
How are you different from your child self?
I was pretty similar as a child.
I was a little more of a spaz and I cared about things more and I'm embarrassed of that in hindsight.
You care about things very, very slightly.
I cared about what was going on around me and that was a mistake.
Oh yeah.
You've turned into a fucking adult, dude.
You've turned into an adult and you're no longer hashtag relatable to me, a child.
We walk around and things happen around me and I'm going to turn around.
Oh, look at that.
Who cares?
Now the bombs drop around Ben everywhere and he doesn't even deign to look at it.
When Donald goes drunk, Ben's not even going to realize.
He's going to be living in a Trump-style society, not realizing it's gone full drunk on him.
Being straight, white, cis, male, I won't even notice the difference, no.
When the bombs fucking drop, his pristine, pasty, white condition will make him immune to all radiation.
So regarding the question of difference between childhood and desire to grow up,
for me, I can answer both with one line.
I am 100% goal focused since my conception.
I can remember what you...
Please continue.
I've never heard that exact sentence before.
I'm sorry.
I don't.
I don't, but what do you mean?
Many of my earliest memories is me thinking what will be my...
All I would do as a kid is just think of overarching lifetime plans for something, right?
I imagine if I had grown up in an engineer family or had an inventor dad and mom,
I probably would have gotten into engineering.
Like if I had an actual social life, you know?
If I had been the fucking child of some sort of internet content creator or some shit,
I would have just gotten onto YouTube way earlier, right?
So I didn't really care about growing up or not growing up.
I just wanted to have a purpose.
And so the difference between myself then and now is that I do have a purpose and plenty of goals.
Before that, I was just totally aimless not knowing what to do with myself.
I also had no purpose or goal in life as a kid.
That's pretty much what I was going to say too, for mine.
I'm way more disciplined now when I do what I want to do.
I guess in college I had a vague idea that I was going to go to grad school and become a physicist.
So I guess I had a goal at some point.
Like personality-wise, were you similar or different from how you are now?
I think right now the me that exists now is more like my self as a child
than the me that existed as a teenager in my early 20s.
Completely dependent on others around you.
You're very much like yourself as a teenager in certain specific ways.
You're an absolutist is what you are and you always have.
I am now, that's for sure.
Well, fair enough.
You've expressed it in different ways before.
The biggest difference between me as a kid and now is that
really the biggest difference for me, I don't think I was very different from childhood through adulthood.
It's more like after becoming a brony celebrity I changed
because I became able to talk to people and be social.
I think that I act very differently now from how I did in 2012.
But 2012 me was almost exactly the same person as 2-year-old.
I remember videos of you in 2012 saying,
Man, I was never knowing how to talk to people until the last couple of years.
I'm just expecting another update to this in 3 years saying,
I wasn't able to talk to people until 2017.
I would say that my perception of what I meant by a sentence like that changed a lot.
When I said able to talk to people then I probably meant at all.
Whereas now I mean I can socially go out and start conversations with strangers.
Becoming a very mildly successful internet art person.
Achieving a little bit of success in that arena has changed me.
Went straight to Ben's head. He's a broken man.
Yeah, well basically. It has changed me in ways that are probably net negatives.
Because I have found ways to survive and to buy without interacting with anyone.
And I have leaned into that.
And I think I need to choose. Am I going to get my life on track and find a balance?
Or am I just going to get my life on track and find a balance?
Or am I just going to lean into it and completely become a hermit, a hermit, nothing master?
As we all know, as much as I already was going to do my thing right after him.
I still want to answer the question myself.
I just think it's funny that Ben would accuse himself of not interacting with people.
Because the way that you do your career involves extensive social networking.
Twitter doesn't count.
What about Discord? You run several of them.
It's all baby shit. It's literal baby shit compared to talking to people in person.
We all know that internet friends aren't real friends, am I right?
Of course.
Growing up, this is also, again, I'm post toys and I'm also post friends.
Because growing up, I basically only had internet friends.
So there's no real distinction to me.
There's no difference really between me going down the street and talking to someone online,
like emotional wise.
I don't feel any differently.
I feel the same as how you described.
The lines of the meat and the wired, bro.
I have to back up.
I do interact with people.
What? No.
She said her audacity crashed.
What? Oh, oh.
Oh no, technical difficulties.
Mage fucked up.
But it's okay. We came back.
Okay, Ben was saying something. Feel free to pick it up.
Was I?
Alright, if you can't remember, who cares?
The thing we were on, the thing we were on currently was how do you feel different
between being a child and being an adult?
And I haven't gone yet and Mage hasn't gone yet.
Okay, well if you guys just want to grab it, I mean, go for it.
Yeah, I wanted to say that the difference between me as a child and me now is mostly,
like my sense of humor is basically exactly the same.
And all of the things I like are like, you know, I still love all the things I liked as a kid.
YouTube poops.
Yeah, fuck it. I love YouTube poops.
Pooping while watching YouTube, you know.
They're very, very good.
But like the difference is like, I've become more confident, which is obviously good.
And like being able to get over depression is another thing that I've just, through like the amount of times it's happened.
The amount of times he's died in Dark Souls is really hard to give to getting over depression.
But like, in terms of like not having like a focus as a kid, like I never knew what I wanted to do.
I always had multiple passions and multiple skills that were good and people would praise me at multiple skills.
What a humble brain.
Which one?
Yes. No, no, no, this is a good thing, but it's like it causes a problem because when you are good as a kid at multiple things
and you're praised equally, you don't know what you should do.
And I had like no focus and I would never actually got like very good at any one thing.
Hippo was like Ebony Darkness Dimension Raven Way. He was too talented and everyone hated him.
I was too talented to succeed. But the thing I've learned, the thing that changed like a few years ago
is that I just realized you don't fucking need a focus. You don't need to know what you're doing.
You just need to do stuff and then you'll die and then people will pre-sit together for you.
You just have to start doing stuff.
I didn't die.
Is that what you're getting at?
Yeah.
No, just kill yourself.
I didn't mean it like that.
You'll die.
I think what you're saying is that like you don't, even if you don't know what your end goal is,
you can't like wait until you know what it is.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
The best thing is just to not...
You are dying right now.
Yeah.
If you don't know what you're doing, like I didn't know what I was doing and I was agonizing over what I should get into,
what I should forge ahead with.
I just realized that it's just a big waste of time and anxiety, right?
Just to even think about it.
It's like people that are like, I'm going to start writing my book.
I'm going to start drawing my comic or whatever, but I'm going to like flesh out the world.
I'm going to spend like weeks and months and years just like writing notes,
fleshing out the world and it has to be complete before I actually start.
This is even worse.
This is the tip that you hear when I talk about...
I was just going to say my webcomic site, apsadventures.site,
is like exactly this whole like, it doesn't matter how good it is.
I'm just happy that I'm making it and it's cool.
That's what Beast Capades was.
I just started it with no real plan.
That's great.
And the plan developed.
Giv, could you please explain to me the origin of Pumpk?
Is it just like your avatar was the pumpkin?
In fucking Inktober 2016, I think, I was just like, I'll just draw because I wanted to get...
I always want to get better at drawing.
Inktober is an excuse.
I drew like one thing on the first day and then on the second day I drew a pumpkin girl
and I was like, dude, fucking sick.
And I really like...
More like Plumpk.
Got him.
Good.
Please draw Plumpk, everyone.
We need Plumpk to fan art.
No, we do.
I'm really happy, by the way, that I invented the pun Gordjus, because she's a Gordjus.
Yeah, she's gorgeous.
Anyway, yeah, that was the origin.
I just drew it and then I took it into a comic.
You don't need to start off with a grand plan for your whole life.
And that's actually one of the good things about adulthood, if you can get yourself functional,
is that you either have to get a job or you're allowed to be in need, which is depressing in itself.
So let that be the motivation for your first initial goal.
Make yourself, at least relatively independent,
you know, by funding your life through some form of art, any form of art.
I would not have gotten onto YouTube, by the way,
if I could have made just as much money doing anything else within the same timeframe.
But I got onto YouTube because it was the thing I liked the most
that I felt most plausible in being able to make money from.
I feel like there's something there. I feel like there's something there into that,
because I, too, I felt like my approach to, like, YouTube content specifically...
I still want to go ahead and answer the question, by the way.
You certainly will get one, mate. Just let me...
I just want to respond to this point directly.
It was just, like, there's something there of, like, when you're a child,
it's like you live in sort of a fantasy world of possibilities.
And, like, for me, that was, like, making big, like, best anime ever and, like, nothing else
and just taking as long as it took to get those done.
But adulthood is more of, like, you selectively cut off avenues
that are not practical and, like, you intentionally limit yourself
or you give yourself a more pragmatic way to survive,
which is what I've done with, like, Miyamafa and Wiago and stuff.
It's just an excuse to make content as kind of an acceptance that, like,
okay, it's true, like, I can't actually survive
just making crazy, big old projects every six months.
It won't work.
So, Michelle...
I just had the same reaction.
I assume people who just heard about Pearl Harbor being bombed had.
So you're saying that Wiago is going to be, like, your only content now?
Like, that's what's gonna happen?
Absolutely not.
Okay.
Wiago has always been.
Wiago is a means to an end.
It is a support structure, a scaffolding,
upon which I can build my more complex projects.
That's what it is.
Do not fear, people. Do not fear.
Go to Michelle eventually.
Okay.
2030.
Okay, okay, wait.
As for me, I feel like in some ways I'm sort of the same person,
but there's definitely a big difference of how I used to be as a kid
and how I am now.
I'm specifically talking about my preteen years,
so, like, legit a kid, like, 11, 12, 11, and younger.
So we're illegitimately a kid in faith.
No, no, like, you know, when you say a kid,
sometimes people, you know, think 14, 16 and stuff.
I mean, I'm talking about, like, a childhood deer, you know, like a kid, like an animal.
Everyone under 30 is a kid to me.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, you're just 29, but I'm wicked and nihilistic and cool and under.
I turn 30 in April, you cuck.
That's right, I forgot.
Ben is gay.
Ben says cuck now, guys.
Let Mage go so I can make fun of Ben more after she's done,
and I won't feel bad about cucking off Mage.
Indeed.
Yes, okay.
So, yeah, when I was a kid, I was very extroverted, I'd say.
I, my mom had to lay, for years, she had to teach me not to greet strangers,
because in my mind, I was like,
oh, hey, a person, I should greet them,
because that's the polite thing to do.
So I would greet people, even random strangers on the street,
and she had to teach it out of me for several years,
because I refused, because that was rude.
How can you not greet someone when you see them,
when you make eye contact?
You must greet them.
Break that curiosity and friendliness out of your child right now,
beat that shit out of them,
make sure they're scared to communicate with other humans.
That's the way to go.
Yeah.
I wasn't scared of people like at all.
I, like I said, I'd greet them,
and I would fight other kids as well.
Like Dragon Ball Z was a big thing,
but even before Dragon Ball Z, I would like fight people,
either for fun or just...
Majors fighting people before Dragon Ball Z made it cool, you guys.
The thing is, I'm gonna, I'm getting to it,
but yeah, like Dragon Ball Z did, did make fighting cool.
We had like the sort of like, I'd say like,
it's almost like a roleplay.
We all assigned names of the characters,
and I was, was it K-18, I think?
The girl, the cyborg, the girl one, the blonde one.
Android 18.
Yeah.
She was called K-18, I think.
But yeah.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, so I was assigned that name,
and we would like sort of play fight,
but the fighting was, I mean...
But the fighting was real,
and the bruises were all too real.
Yes, yes, and we would legit fight.
I would, I would take on the guys,
the guys stronger than me, like bigger than me.
Oh, yeah.
I once almost won against like a teenager,
when I was like, I think 10,
but he cheated, he had to cheat to win against me,
to win against a little girl.
I'm sorry about that, but I'll wait till you're done.
Bring it back to team fighting,
because this is a big thing.
Yeah, it was snowing, he used snow against me,
and that's how he was.
That's not true.
Pocket sand is real sanction.
I want to like, acknowledge the like,
weird like cultural prejudice I have,
because we're just like, what do you call it?
The privilege goggles.
Whenever you talk about being a childhood
in your home country,
I just imagine Lithuania is like,
this like bombed out third world nation
with like maybe like two streets,
and it's all color coded,
just like mage's avatar, it's all purple.
I just imagine that every time.
And everyone's fighting on this town.
Think of cop kill town, look at that.
Yeah, exactly like it.
Cathedral's everywhere.
I mean, you're not completely wrong.
It's very popular.
No, it's terrible.
I mean, I grew up.
A lot of dead cops in Lithuania, a lot of dead cops.
I grew up in post USSR.
Lithuania, there were like a lot of Russians
around a lot of chaos, I'd say.
Oh, God.
I grew up with like, sometimes no electricity
and brown running water and stuff.
Oh, God.
I thought you were going to be like,
no, it wasn't that bad.
Yeah, me too.
Mage is a feral child.
I know.
I was.
I would run around barefoot.
And your anime wasn't even dubbed right.
Yeah.
When I was a kid, I ran around barefooted
and wielding knives.
It's like cop kill town.
It's like Neo Milwaukee.
Just kids running around with like weapons.
You would feel right at home in Slime City.
You would feel right at home.
I have to say, for years, up until this very moment,
anytime we talked about Lithuania,
that was the picture I was getting,
but I thought that's clearly me projecting like,
oh, God.
It's a lot better now.
Okay.
Only adults run around the streets naked with knives.
That's the only way.
My neighborhood was terrible as well.
I heard rumors.
Okay, I did see drunk people stumbling about,
but I did hear rumors about people using drugs
and stuff and selling drugs around.
I was disgusted.
I saw some weird nasty people,
but I never really saw them and thank goodness I didn't.
I did see discarded needles here and there,
but that's beside the point.
Anywho.
Nice.
Yeah, back to happy childhood times when I was a good kid.
Yeah, so, yeah, like I would fight.
Silence.
Yeah, I would fight people.
I wasn't scared to pick fights with people.
I think my record is like two bloody noses.
Wow.
What about now, mate?
You looking to start some shit?
I feel like you got shortchanged in the Royal Rumble.
Yeah, I was going to say, yeah.
I would like to put a call out to the fan artists.
I want somebody to draw feral little mage
with dual-wielding knives in the purple streets.
Yeah, wait.
Bomb down to the streets.
How would you become the funny,
like girl-like,
girl-like,
the funny,
girl-timid,
draw-fan-art girl.
That's the power of fucking artistic expression.
We're all speaking the same language of
fluffy tumblr shit,
but then we have
totally different people from totally different fucking worlds.
It kind of blows my mind every time I hear shit like that.
You were always kicking people's asses,
but you were still like this?
No.
I was still generally good natured.
Like,
the very first job that I wanted to have
that I remember was a veterinarian,
but then I learned what a veterinarian had to do
and then I was like,
my stomach's weak. I almost fainted the first time
we took our cat to the veterinarian.
So that dream died quick.
And
whenever me and my friends were bored,
I would get these schemes on how to help
the environment and nature and stuff.
It wasn't because the TV told me so.
Hey, you know what would be fun?
If we would take these brooms and take these rakes
and clean up the neighborhood.
That'd be a fun project for the day.
You know, Mage, that reminds me.
There's a story my mom tells me about
me as a child.
She was taking me to
summer camp and I was like,
oh, I don't want to go.
I'm going to be sad and I don't know anybody there.
And so she drops me off
and then this is from her perspective.
She comes by to pick me up.
And at the end of the day,
she's like, Nate, come here.
I crawl out of the woods
and I have my belt stuffed with pine cones.
And I'm like,
I've got four sticks strapped to my back
and I'm dual wielding these big ol' limbs.
And I'm like, Mom,
I'm in the middle of something.
I need to come back later. We're dueling right now.
The shit is real.
Go away.
That's what happens.
Stick duels in the woods.
Stick duels are the best.
Stick duels were a major part of my whole childhood,
where me and my friends
would go out into the woods
and just try to find
sticks that are about the size of
swords and
come back to the house and fight with them.
We would have a pretty sizable collection
because if they were good, you'd hold on to them until they break.
So we'd keep a pile
of all our really good sticks by the side of the house.
And then my friend
Marcus, who is like a
like a fucking built
action guy, he just loved to play around
with stuff like this anyways.
He would just film videos of himself
doing kung fu and shit in high school.
And so
we would just go into the backyard when he came over
and because he was really quiet and literally
just wouldn't talk or say anything, we'd be like
I guess we're just gonna fight with sticks.
That's what we'll do when he comes over.
So every time he came over, we'd just fight with
sticks until one of us got hurt
and didn't want to do it anymore.
My friend that I had in high school
told this story.
He would tell the story like it was true
and no one believed it, so it was really funny.
He said that some
like
dojo master
stick fighter had like
come to his house one day and knocked on his door
looking for him specifically
and challenged
Who was this? Which one was this been?
Started with a J.
Okay, okay, I got you.
And then he had challenged him just specifically
and he had dueled him in his backyard at stick fighting
and he had won.
So, you know.
Damn J.
This is unrelatable to me.
This stick wielding experience, not only because
I don't live next to a forge, but also
like again, I'm post going outside.
Going outside was not an option when I was growing up.
Like you couldn't do it anymore.
Was it dangerous or something?
Well, it was a combination.
It was really hot in California.
It was a combination of it being drilled into.
It was like don't go outside, there are strangers there
and also there are video games now.
I mean, Munchy, that was a thing when I was a kid
right before I was a kid as well.
It's like what, the late 80s at least?
I just got to very briefly mention
my brother got big into stick fighting.
What he would specifically do is go to the hardware store
get a big old plank and then sand it down
to where it becomes like an actual weapon
and I think like if you
honored him in battle in combat with a regular stick,
he would eventually like get one for you
and help you make your own.
So I ended up getting one, but yeah.
I think I need to take a step back to point out
that the ages that I would have stick fought
would have been ages like
12 to 17, which is the period
of time I have known Munchy.
So I know what Munchy's been doing
as opposed to stick fighting.
He's been in the PCP and drawing fan art
and sending me pickup lines on Tumblr.
Those are the fucking days, dude.
Those are the fucking days.
I still like reminisce and think about
how that's how we met.
That's how all of this happened
was I sent you, hey are you an archaeologist
because I've got a bone for you to pick.
Bone to pick for you to examine.
I love it.
We have a whole section of this podcast
talking about the death of toys,
the death of going outside and the rise of video games.
That needs to be something we talk about in depth.
Instead of doing stick fighting
all that I do with my friends
was just play Smash Bros.
Which is the same amount of pain
and shit talking.
I did that at the same time, too, though.
I could play Smash Bros. since I was 8
because I had the N64.
It's just whismical.
Stick fighting was a younger man's game for me.
Video games are an old man's game
in my mind.
When I was 9
and younger at summer camp,
maybe between 9 and 12 or something,
those were peak stick fighting years
as I recall them.
But hey, I've got a story
which is relevant to this question
of what we like as a child versus an adult
only this is how I was exactly the same.
I know I've told similar stories
but I don't believe I've ever told this one
and I think everyone will appreciate it greatly.
I don't remember exactly
what was going through my mind at the time
but I was around
between 12 and 15 at this time.
Something in that range.
It was nighttime and it was summertime.
I don't know what was going on
but my parents went up to bed
and they were like, Nate, walk our dog
which was Buddy at the time, I think.
Yeah, Buddy was my muse.
And he...
Three quarters peak and he's one quarter poodle
for those wondering.
I'm sure the audience was just dying to know.
I'm adding richness to the scene.
So imagine me with this little dog emperor
on the leash taking a shit
and here I stand.
So the way that my parents
are back yard was set up
my parents' room is kind of up
really high on the house
and there's three layers down
is where the grass is behind the house.
Jesus Christ, what kind of house did you live in?
I mean, there's the basement
then the first floor, then the second floor
and there's an attic
but they're in the second floor, not the attic.
There's a hill in the front of the house
that doesn't go to the back so it gets lower.
The basement was exposed in the back.
Yeah, that's right.
But whatever.
Incidentally, my parents are selling that soon but whatever.
So the point was...
This is the point.
I'm walking buddy and I don't know
I don't know what was going through my mind.
I think it had been a late night of watching anime.
That's how all terrible ideas started.
That's right, that's right.
Was it Adult Swim?
It was definitely Adult Swim.
Or maybe Toonami or something.
One of my stories was on
and I don't know what was going through my mind
but I was thinking about the future
and I was thinking about what I was going to do with myself
as life went on and I wasn't talking to buddy
or anything, I was talking to myself
and I'm just like...
I'm not.
I'm not going to be a cog in the machine.
I'm not
going to be a cog in the machine.
I'm going to achieve my destiny.
I'm going to do whatever it takes.
I'm going to make it in this world and be important.
So I was just talking to myself loudly
just repeating these mantras
to myself based on, like, I don't know,
a tri-gun episode I just watched
or a couple of bebop or something.
Like you do.
That's what was going on.
Were you wearing your entire HD hat while you did this?
You know, I should have been.
If I thought to gather it, I would have.
Not much happened in that story.
Okay, well this is the important part.
It's that afterward, so the next day
I'm just at breakfast,
whatever, and I'm sitting there,
I'm eating breakfast, and then mom,
my mom just leans down over the countertop,
looks at me with her big eyes
the way they look at an oncoming train
and says, uh, so,
not going to be a cog in the machine, huh?
No!
Get the fuck in there.
They had heard everything.
That's so terrible.
My words.
How could you do that to someone?
How could you do that to your son?
I would have died right on the spot.
I would have died right there.
Speaking of embarrassing Nate's stories,
will you tell us about
the story of the, um...
The talent show?
Is that the one? Okay, yes.
I don't know if I've ever told this,
so I'll tell this one quicker than that one.
So it was just, in high school,
I thought I was the shit, and this was like, um...
Which you were, evidently.
Which I was. It was either freshman or sophomore year.
Whatever, it doesn't matter. The point was,
oh god, I'm still hurting.
I'm still hurting from the climax.
It was absolutely devastating.
And I'm sure dad had heard it too,
and they just colored their...
Imagine them up there.
Imagine they're up in their room.
They heard you, and then they talked about it,
like, when they were in bed again.
They were up there.
I'm upset with them.
It was cruel.
I mean, there's nothing they could have said,
like, Nate, we can hear you.
Shut the hell up.
They could have just not said anything.
Well, they didn't have to.
That story reminded me of a very short one
from when I was like 12 or 13,
maybe a little older.
Somewhere in the early teens,
and I had woken up,
jacked off,
and I was like,
I was about to leave my bedroom.
He started off the day,
groggy, like, I don't want to leave the bedroom,
but I was younger.
I had to look out to make sure that nobody was around
before I left my bedroom.
I didn't want to be bothered until I had time
to wake up and be able to talk to people.
So I was listening in
to the downstairs to see what was going on,
and I could hear my grandma talking to my mom,
and she's like,
well, why don't you go wake him up?
Because that's how she sounds.
And my mom's like, well, he sleeps naked,
and I don't want to sleep naked.
She goes, he just does that so he can touch himself.
And I was like, oh my god.
And literally,
I was just like, well, I mean,
yeah.
I think that says more about your grandma
than about you.
It does.
Well, that's interesting nonetheless.
It says the same about both of us, actually,
because she was right.
There's things to be learned.
Obviously, that's true,
but I think it speaks something
that she felt the need to point it out.
Your grandma's logic doesn't make sense.
Well, don't mind the fact that he's naked.
He does that for purposes of masturbation.
That means there's no reason to not go to the room.
That's really refute.
Yeah, it doesn't.
Guys, quick question.
When you were a kid,
did you ever worry about secret cameras
in your house?
No.
Well, I didn't grow up in a former Soviet Union country.
Well, as a matter of fact,
our dad did set up a camera
in the basement at one point,
which was most likely to keep it.
Oh, I forgot. I thought it was on the outside,
but no, there was one on the inside for a while.
Wait, are you sure? I remember being outside,
but he could look in with it.
That's what I remember.
I remember him saying knowingly,
when you had some friends over,
I'll just be keeping an eye on the outside,
but maybe I'll take a look on the inside.
I'll just be watching through my surveillance camera.
Yeah, don't worry. Our dad's a fucking creep.
Oh, he didn't think
of the consequences of how we'd feel.
The consequences.
He's a silly man.
The consequences that I was unsettled by him
generally.
Help me ruminate on this.
Because this is a real thing of thought that I have.
I think that hiding stuff from your parents
is literally like a good healthy thing to do.
Yes.
It will help breed individualism
and make you more independent as a person.
An adult does not need to know
when you start whacking off.
It's just like what?
I don't necessarily agree with you, Munchy,
but I think that the problem,
the reason I don't agree with you,
is that ideally you wouldn't have
to hide things from your parents,
because your parents would have a better understanding of you.
The only reason I did this is because
I think it's a fundamental question
of human nature as opposed to a good
relationship with your children.
I straight up don't think a child
ever should pass along the information
as to whether or not they jack off.
Okay, you don't have to tell me.
I will know that.
Yeah.
The reason you have to hide from your...
Sorry.
I have to say this.
The reason you have to hide from your parents
is that they refuse
to be in the reality
you are actually in.
I don't want to be in the reality
when my son is jacking off.
Your son is going to jack off.
That happens. They all do it.
If your son is like
13, 14,
you should just know.
He's probably jacking off.
You should know better.
A lot of parents just try to
live in the universe in their own mind
where you don't do the things
that they don't want you to do.
A lot of the time it's not a matter of
not wanting to accept it.
It's just not wanting to believe
in the sense that you don't have
the attention to it.
Why would they not want that?
Because
it makes
for a society that
can change.
Nobody wants a kid that is just obedient.
Because
they need to rebel in some way.
It's not about the parents knowing.
No, because leadership.
It's about the kid taking the initiative
to not tell them certain things.
I think that
the way that we often...
the systems in which discipline is instilled
in the military
is that you have
an extreme authoritarian figure
grinding you into the ground
and they are also
they have total control over you.
That can make you
experience ego death
in a similar kind of way where
you can gain maturity
by looking past yourself.
I do think there's also
good reasons, good things you can learn
by learning to deceive
people who are wrong.
The reason you should lie to your parents
is that they're probably wrong.
But if your parents are
communicating with you
and you have a good relationship
what are you going to hide from them?
You can't just make up shit to hide from your parents
just to learn that lesson.
Your parents can just teach you
that lesson.
There will be differences.
I'm going to teach my kids to hide a lot of things from school.
I'm going to teach them to hide a lot of things from...
How much you are going to have in common with your kids?
You are way overestimating.
I am not saying that I am going to do
a perfect job raising my kids
and go through all... I'm just saying that in an ideal...
I'm saying philosophically why your point is incorrect
because no parent alive
should ever know everything their children do.
I can't imagine any of us having children.
Why do you need to know?
There's a huge difference between knowing everything
they do and hiding
things from your parents.
If someone goes and takes a dump
and you don't tell me that you went to take a dump
you're not hiding it from me.
That's a good example
because taking a shit
is an embarrassing thing to do
just as a human being.
It just is. People don't really want to talk about it.
If you're stupid...
But what if it's a really impressive shit?
That's one of the base...
literally everyone does it
and yet we're kind of embarrassed about it.
It's just...
I'm embarrassed about it because
I think there are legitimate reasons
to be embarrassed about shit
and those are the reasons that I am.
I don't want you to smell my shit because it smells bad.
And I don't want to look at it
because it looks gross.
But the fact that someone takes a shit
there are people out there
there are women out there for instance
who will not acknowledge the fact that they shit.
I know them.
Or they won't acknowledge that they fart
and I'm like I don't give a fuck
that you shit or fart because I do the same things
and I'm not going to hold that against you
but some people feel like they are expected
to think those things are embarrassing
and so they find them embarrassing.
They're not using logic, they're using expectations.
So I'm saying that
in my idea of a perfect society
it's one where
we don't have to tell everyone
everything that's going on
because we should all have a level of understanding
and trust in one another
that we trust you to be doing something good.
The reason that people come into contact with their parents
is that those trust relationships break down
because your parents do not
set reasonable expectations for you.
They want you to be perfect instead of being human
even though they made you
while being imperfect
and being human and they don't understand
how to be perfect.
If you want to truly be
on the level with your kids
you have to be employing as much of an open mind
and critical thinking as the child themselves
is growing up.
When I think of kids I'm thinking
what is the most
difficult and hard to relate to?
Imagine if I, Ben St,
were capable of the titanic feet
of employing the level
of critical thinking as a child.
Imagine if you had the capability
of listening
instead of jutting in and interrupting
to do in the middle of a statement.
So the thing is
the thing is
I think my dad in particular
never saw coming how little
of a shit me and my siblings would care
about Christianity because
my dad came from a broken fucking house
broken fucking family, broken fucking world
so he needs this
theological backbone
but then he made the mistake of raising his children
to be happy with life
so it's like why the hell do I need
a diadol narrative to back up
conscious
ability to make up a warning?
I used to love Christianity up until
someone told me that people actually believe
the stories
whoa!
that's pretty bad
that's post-soviet
we're not just like
we're not just role playing
what I liked
about it is just like
it sounded to me like fairy tales
and like oh it's just
stories to teach a moral
that's what I thought about it
yeah it's a story time
I used to take
a class that he would teach
Christianity
I think wrote Roman Catholicism
specifically
basically in that class
they just would tell the stories and I'd get to draw
so it was like the perfect class
once a month
we have grape juice and crackers
it's pretty good
Catholicism is like the jock Christianity
branch
whereas the more Protestant
particular education oriented
actually like really seriously
following the Bible to the letter is definitely
the nerd group of Christianity
it's like what Ted Cruz is all like
I put it more in terms of
the virgin Protestant
versus the Chad Catholic
someone make that shit
it really is though
actually fucking hilarious
the Catholics are all about image
and looking good and being popular
whereas the
Protestants and especially Baptists
following the rules and being faithful
correctly
someone should draw
the virgin Martin Luther
the Chad Chad
because someone making like the
imagine if someone made the Chad Protestant
it would come off as totally
unironic and they really believe
that they're cool
the Chad
the Catholic needs to
have like eight names at least
he needs to have like the name of
every Baptist in his
Virgil, Sanctius, Augustine
the 14th
do we?
as people? yeah
don't you get like the middle names from
being like baptizer or whatever
oh some no
maybe Catholics do, I mean we were
Protestant so like
or someone like chooses like a given name
like they choose like a biblical name
when they get confirmed or something
when I was young and getting confirmed
I was mad at Catholics
and I expressed this very autistically
that I didn't get to choose like my own new name
I really wanted the name Gabriel
I thought it'd be cool but
I was asking my dad what percentage of devoted Catholics
do you think are going to go to heaven
he said 25%
wait but doesn't your dad believe in heaven
and stuff though? yeah well my dad's just like
basically one time
me and my dad were talking about the idea of cult
like people who take Christianity and then like
have their own stupid idea of what it means
and they take it too far and he's like oh well
the whole Catholic Church is basically a cult
and I said what percentage of them
in spite of following Catholicism correctly
are still like believing in God
correctly he's like probably 25%
those are the ones you're going to get to heaven
why wouldn't it be zero?
there's a lot of looseness
because you're a Protestant you've already
deviated majorly like from the codified
original Catholic shit
so like it's loosey goosey out here
Catholicism also deviates from Judaism
so you know
well I mean because Jesus
well I imagine the number for Jews
is 0%
oh I probably
whatever what the fuck was I even talking about
talking about my dad, talking about relating to your kids
so I'm thinking okay I need to be prepared
because my parents also like
projected the fact that when they wanted to
homeschool their kids onto the fact that
they would have done really good that they suddenly had to do homeschool
because going to public schools
is a much bigger pain in the ass
the thing about homeschool is if you're fucking disciplined
you can just get all your work done immediately
and like the light world is your oyster
the problem is it's so easy
it's such a much more efficient way of doing it
that it's really fucking boring and hard to like pay attention
right? so like we just barely
squeaked our way through it but my parents didn't
get why it would be hard
for that reason they couldn't relate
so I need to be prepared I need to like basically
hope that my kids are as
unrelatable to me as possible so I'm imagining them like
not being into video games at all
or art just being fucking chads
they want to do sports I need to prepare for that
also political views
like how the world is
because we think oh old people are so stupid
for not understanding
every color is the same level of human
no like fucking racism is bad
but in a
generation or two who knows where it could
evolve into a degree that we now are
fuddy duddy so I'm just basically going to
assume that being a fucking
anti-SJW racist is gonna be
popular in like 2020
or like 2030 or so
it's already getting pretty hot
and also like respecting
things are heating up
having a respect
will be seen as wrong
there'll be all these like woke like fucking
parables about how
having a listening to the other side is wrong
trying to be respectful to someone over
disagreement is like all like it's lies
right? I need to be prepared
for my kids to have that ideology
that I think is just completely wrong
so that I could be prepared
and act cool about it be like uh huh
that's your belief?
oh really? you believe that?
you don't understand
just like any parent
what if you act all like
befuddled about it?
I've never heard of a person who actually blows up
and says what you're doing something
new get out of here
I've never heard of a person has a parent like that
oh I know
I have friends who have parents
who are just like
I mean it's like
if you're a parent and like for whatever reason
if your world view comes
majorly in conflict with like what your child
chooses to do with their life
like it has to be in a serious major way
that's really the only way I can see it
I'll just give you some perspective
I have a friend who's mom
this was when Pokemon Go was first coming out
possibly one of the only
old people in existence who was still
writing the Pokemon's demonic line
even when Pokemon Go made a popular movie
whoa that's retro
I know right?
she found a fake article
in which there was a fake interview
with the guy who created Pokemon
who in this fake interview says
that he made Pokemon specifically to convert
Western children to Satanism
and she thought it was real
and sent it to my friend
her daughter saying this is why you shouldn't play Pokemon
she thought it was real
does her dad work at Nintendo?
is that how she knew?
we interviewed a Japanese entrepreneur
Ken Pokemon
we asked him why
my friend told her
that's a fake article and she's like
it might be but what it's saying
is ultimately true
dare we take that chance?
it's enlightening that her answer
does not hinge at all
on whether it is fake
she's the kind of parent
who will be like that
she will actually do a gasp
my friend said it was really hard
drop her monocle
what's the rule we established
one person says one thing
and another person says the same thing
it must be true
my friend said it was really hard
for her to learn how to drive
and her mom
if anything might be dangerous
happening in the car
I would gasp and freak my friend
be like
there are definitely parents
you will go
juggling knives in the car
that's slightly dangerous
I would gasp if I was in danger of automobile
more like
it's time for you to slow down at the stop sign
and you are in no way
you're not taking too long
to slow down but I'm worried you might not
so I'm going to gasp
I kind of know what that's like
to drive these days is pretty terrifying
when you're not in control
indeed
what would you guys do at school like
would you guys be happy in school
insert the entire school
podcast here please
is there really anyone
on earth that was unironically happy
in school
when I was a kid I loved school
when I was a teenager I hated school
I mean
it could have been good at school
I was happy at school
if you look at me now
you would probably think
we didn't really have bullies
in my school
that didn't really go on
nobody got beat up or anything
I felt
everyone was way too high to worry about that
I felt ostracized
and I felt like a nerd
and a social pariah
but looking back I had a clicker too
that I was pretty tight with
jokes in class and people would laugh
and stuff
I remember a cracked article
and any time I said a cracked article
I always want to say it because I don't trust cracked
that much but they said
there was an article that mentioned
that the kids who shot up Columbine
they were not bullied
they just have a huge victim complex
yeah
I mean
same goes for Elliott
Roger
he actually got turned down by any women
he just
never got offered
he got turned down
at least once
not enough
the fault lies
most of it was just him from afar
looking at women and being like they would never accept me
what was Gib saying though
he was chiming in
do you love
Elliott Roger as much as we
the conversation changed
and I forgot what I was going to say
the topic is childhood
my whole experience
of school was the first day of school
I got on the bus and I distinctly
remember that like
I cried because I had to let go of my mom
I had never been like outside
of like eyesight of my mom basically
by this point
when I get on the bus and I go like right to the back
and I'm looking out her through the back window
and she's waving and I'm crying
and it was misery for
like 12 years
I want to quickly say
it's weird like did she say like that's the
the first time he you know
he wasn't with an eye shut of his mom
like remember my wild days
when I was a kid like around five years or so
like my parents would just let me go
into the neighborhood and I was not
supervised five years old
yeah well mage it's different when you're raised
by wolves it's a different sort of
dynamic you know there
yeah it's interesting like
right now it's dangerous and probably
no one would let their kids go off
it's actually safer than it's ever been
statistically it's just
it had nothing to do with it being dangerous
where my parents are not allowing me
I had no interest in being outside
the eyesight of my mom so
yeah and I'm just saying in general
like nowadays like no
no self-respecting
the perception the what are they called
hover parents or whatever the hovercraft
whatever
all parents are beta orbiters of their children
beta orbiters
that's a problem
all parents have been
totally friends
totally fucking talking about this now
let's talk about the death of going outside
let's not talk about that right now
because I was walking around my old childhood
ruins for devious reasons
that will not disclose
I was walking around like like old schoolyards
and stuff like that and I've noticed that I still
have the feeling two this day like years after
I moved out of like my elementary middle school and stuff
where when I'm in the car
and like we turn in
to go to school and we turn in the same
turn that I've been like I went to
when I was in school I still get the
pit of anxiety and like
oh god it's really happening like I'm going
to school today like it's like
I'm ready I'm ready to go into homeroom
oh god like years like
even I was going to my kindergarten elementary
school and I turned
into the complex and I felt a pit
of despair growing my stomach
and I felt I was going to go
to school that day
you know it's interesting like
having not gone to school
there's an interesting perception
I get from people right
whenever a new school a new fresh shooting
happens right and we count up the
bodies one two
twelve bodies
and so then you know the people
have their opinions
and what's funny is that there's something
like both sides always agree on
but they never like talk about this part
so basically one
side always goes so
okay you know how we keep some
a bunch of kids keep getting shot up and some
kids decide to like grab guns and shoot kids
in these giant prisons that we locked them
up in for nine hours a day that they're all miserable
and depressed in I think it's probably
because of the video games they
relaxed with when they come home that's
what caused it right and then other people
are like hey you know those giant buildings
were like kids locked up for nine hours
a day and feel miserable and depressed and anxious
like their entire youths I think
it's actually the fact that they have a weapon
to shoot kids within the first place we should
get rid of the weapon and I'm like hold on
why are we addressing the fact that we're locking everyone
up in these nine hour prisons for their entire
youths that they're all terrified and depressed in
like why not address that part of the issue
excuse me I mean I
yeah I mean you collect all the all the
delicate exploding hundred point bonus
you know bullet sponges in one place
that I'm gonna want to get the high score
we're not saying that you all deserve to lose
your kids for help making us participate
in this system just that maybe I don't feel as bad
my favorite is the hot diggity demon
tweet which was um
new school gets shot up people
ban guns me ban schools
I think I retweeted that that was a great one
when I went to college in the UK
this is a slow down topic but I just want to
quickly say Munchie let mage finish she's been
tramming in die die
when I went to college in the UK
we had like first of
all we had like lanyards so we wouldn't
be able to access the
the buildings unless we were allowed
to and we also had metal detectors
so we couldn't bring anything
metal in them and UK doesn't even
have guns so I think that's
an interesting practice that made should
be considered maybe
it's an interesting
thing I completely agree that schools need
to be banned get rid of them now
yeah I had a
point and I forgot so continue and I'll think about it
alright I have the thing about
school I don't
remember being on the school podcast I remember
I think I missed it
I wanted to be on it I don't want to go on to
like a huge spiel but my basic
thoughts on school is that
I used to hate it
obviously because that's what you're supposed to do
um but like
after checking my privilege after
going through and remembering that
I'm I'm actually
like I'm a white boy
and it was a pretty good school and it was pretty
good and there were lots of nice people there
I didn't actually have a terrible time I had
a lot of like good like
like um like the art department
at my school was quite nice
and the teachers were chill and they
would let me stay behind like after
school to just work on the teachers were
chill the school was lit the cafeteria
was on the
like like the average
places to chill at
so the obvious things about school were like
uh yeah that some people it's
social structures are shit
a lot of teenagers are terrible and
cliques are gay um
and I was shy so like
says member of the pcp hypocrite
got him
it was a good it was a good time
if it wasn't the greatest but like
I I appreciate school
like when it's done right it's pretty
good
well school gave me the chance
to rise the highest I have in my life
and fall to my lowest point
and that is the story that I was
telling before and allow me to share
it briefly now it was
it was just um so when I was
I think I was um everyone knows that
I was a god as a young child
I was the ultimate dodgeball champion
I was I could do 50 pull-ups in high school
I uh I just I
I had hair down to my waist I was just
a god just in every possible way
um I wore those
in Kingdom Hearts wristbands every day
um
that's how you know that's how you know
that's how you know I wore weighted
leg braces because I wanted to fucking be Goku
okay but anyway the point is um
I actually developed a bit of a fan
club in uh
in high school there was like three girls
who would call themselves this
and I I occasionally get creepy
Facebook messages from them up until
last year um really
yeah it's true I just
had to check uh I got back into Facebook
and I yeah yeah last year I got another one
but anyway the point is
because I like
one time okay one time
I mean there's that one time
a friend of mine walked up to me
and said hey Nate that's my friend
Jessica she wants to date you I looked up
I saw her and I said that's nice and went
back to reading like one piece or
or two or something that's
that's why did
why did you say that sense why was that your response
was like nervous or like you know
did you not like or were you just not
interested in the entire endeavor
at this point in my life I just had like
no interest in girls really
I mean I did have a crush on a girl but
I don't know it was like it was more like platonic
I guess like I wasn't thinking about fucking or anything
I don't know Jesus how I get
it I didn't want to fucking go back
I didn't want to go back to school either
well I did a little bit but I would have
been nervous about like when I was young I was
like legit scared of alcohol and I think I was
the same way kind of scared of sex because
like I didn't understand it was like a foreign world
I was like ah what does this mean
I thought that sex was like bad and something
that only like the bad kids did because
people weren't supposed to and I was like
I'm better than them because I'm not
doing that bad thing and I mean I was
a kissless virgin up until like my fucking
twenties so you know that was
weird um anyway
anyway so the story goes that
I believe it was sophomore year and
the talent show is coming up and I thought
I'm gonna fucking ace this like I ace everything
um and maybe
whatever I like
and just to paint the picture I took
all AP classes I could
take even when I wasn't good enough
to handle like I never got lower than like I don't know like a C
or you know the B's
and C's I was a student but I took all
AP classes because I
would not it would hurt me too deeply
in my pride to not take
the hardest possible classes that were available
even though the valedictorian herself like
just did not do that because there was no point
the point is
I'm characterizing myself as an asshole
egomaniac okay but the point is
uh there's a talent show
the talent show comes up
and I've decided I'm going
to choreograph my own dancing thing
and I'm gonna dance to another one bites the dust
and sing with Freddie Mercury and so I do that
I choreograph it and I get up there
and I sing and dance uh
and I they they count down
the who are the winners and I just think to myself
oh of course I'm gonna win this
but then I don't and it was humiliating
and I didn't make any sense to me and it was the worst
time of my life that's it
that's it that's it terrible
I thought it would give you like everyone booed you or like you made a fool of yourself
you didn't you know everyone well you don't understand
I don't care what other people think of me
it's only what I think other people think of me
that matters to me wait that doesn't make any fucking
sense um anyway
that's hard that's hard
it was 80% build up and and like
2% like oh here's
as all my stories are
like half to nothing
have I told the story about
have I told the story about thinking that I got
the role that I wanted to in the school play
but then it was actually his wife
that's right
I won't repeat it then
uh
if I could go back to talking like at the very beginning
oh wait mage hasn't heard it
okay let me say but the audience has
let me say it real quick real quick
I
I auditioned for a play
even mage doesn't want to hear it
no no no I do want to hear it
I just don't want to take up everyone's time
no you're not my friend anymore
every small audience member was probably like
oh you forgot about this to say
there are like a thousand like loose threads
in this podcast
the reason I rushed through that one because I thought
I had totally dropped off
whatever
I want to go back to one of the very first questions was
did you want to know how I became
the mature and by mature
I mean insane person you say
for you
this is where I reveal the fact that I am actually
the main girl from Karakana
but instead of being beautiful and elegant
I'm actually inconceivable and a maniac
so
when I was like a little kid
all I cared about was having like the approval
of like adults I didn't care about the other kids
that liked me I didn't care about any of that
all I wanted was like the praise
oh wow like Anthony
like thank you for helping me take out the trash
you're so responsible
you're so nice
you're such a mature kid and I'm like
fuck man I spent a couple of years
all the time I've known you you've never docked your name to me
now I can't be undone
I've said this before on the podcast
did you not know his name
no
I guess we know what level of friendship we're at
DeVu
anyway
I was so hopped up on compliments
I was straight up sniffing those
that praise day in day out
and so I wanted to like modify
my behavior so I could maximize
the compliments that I got
so I talked about this a little bit on the sitcoms episode
but it goes farther than this
I basically like there was an age at like 10 or something
I was like alright cartoons are kids shit
like I can't do cartoons anymore
it's all about sitcoms and like daytime television
that's where all the mature adults are doing
that's what that's what that's the new show
that I was hooked up on
I was watching Golden Girls
I feel like this is good because you went through this so young
that you got to like figure out that
adults were dumb before you even were one
yeah exactly
yeah how do you get out of that arc
that's what I want to know
well a funny thing
I found this little thing called the horseshoe crew
that were just like talking like
in like my little pony and shit
so I was in that like whole scene
and eventually I was realizing you know I quite like
when things were like drawn
and it's that sort of like
metamorphicized into me being okay
with the fact that I am a child
and I was like completely like reversed
where like a long time of my life
where like I was like from like 8 until like
I don't know like 12 or 13
where I was really dedicated to trying to become
like not necessarily a mature person
in the sense that like I'm like
you know like like a serious all tax person
in the sense that like I'm you know
I'm the cream of the crop of kids like wow
is that part of why you were so
into homestuck because it was like
all cartoony and kitty but also like
really cerebral and literary
a little bit yeah
anyway it went full circle to the point where now
I'm like full like
kid power and I reject
all sense of the adult world
I just want to go back
not like I just want to go back to like being
like nice and like looking
with optimism to the world and not being
nihilistic and not being like oh like
life shit now question mark
I don't want to be reflecting like oh how good
things used to be I want to have things be good
now I don't want to be thinking about how
like oh YouTube so bad oh I'm just
here to make a quick buck oh
like like online creation is
such a fucking drag oh they're all
fucking hacks and ours is not a single good
YouTuber wow wow look at me
aren't I cool for not liking things oh
wow I'm so fucking
I'm so mature oh I
I realized that I'm just around by
day and day out oh I'm
such a fucking adult I'm such an adult
everyone praise me praise me I hate
things praise me no I'm not
about that shit I'm here I'm
full of energy and passion I'm here
I'm here with the youthful eyes of a baby
boy and I'm here to make my mark
on the fucking world I'm not going to have any fucking
naysayers and debbie downers make fun of the
internet the internet is my playground the internet
is real youtubers are great everything is
fucking great all you adults are fucking
lame you're all lame and you don't get anymore
you don't fucking get it we've grown past you
we have evolved past you we have did you
evolve you have mega evolved and you are
fucking old shit you are old hat you don't
get it anymore leave literally
leave yeah dude yeah
like yeah talking about
being rebellious against what
people want you to be when you're older
oh you'll get over this you'll get over that
the number one thing that I wanted to be
rebellious against was thinking that my
childhood was better right like
there was a time when I was like 17
and an older person said oh yeah I remember
when I was your age that was the best years of
my life and I'm thinking gross
one I'm I was thinking one
I've just been sitting around doing nothing with
my life being completely miserable two
how old were you how old were you 17 or 16
Jesus fucking Christ two
uh this guy
in like his late 50s is
fucking handing me the free sample at a
grocery store obviously
this guy yeah well
when when when when you peak
at 17 when you're the kind of person who
peaked at 17 and it never got any better past
that that's not a good sign what do you think
he was handing me the fucking free sample
at price chopper so
I was thinking yeah it's like clearly
people who just were not fit for this
earth like they should have died they should have died young
that was been the only way right
yeah yeah that was the only way
and they missed they missed their chance that's the two
things I still want to talk about is like life
getting better or worse when you become old and
also the death of going outside which I guess
actually need that much elaboration but those
are the two subtopics I'm still particularly
interested in
I just like to say
that I'm deeply sorry about how much I
fucked up my story because I told it like
shit yeah I
thought I had not I thought I told
it on episode so I rushed to the ending I just
want everyone to know it was really good when
I told it in private
for you maybe as you said yeah
in the call and you did say and it was
like a really like fun story that like wow
yeah you know I'm glad that you're my friend
like I'm really glad that I but not anymore
yeah you really
now I see how you handle it under
pressure I'm not confident
it's actual quality
I'm told it on the episode before
right
yeah yeah there was a little hype
as to the reveal of that
I had lost that that was what made it good
if you had actually been performed
the same thing you played the song
you sang it we had to sit there be like yep you
definitely lost it
if I did it on the episode yeah that
we should do that I mean it was a dance thing
we would just hear a foot shuffle
yeah I did moonwalk did moonwalk
you haven't seen Fuli Kuli yet have you
no I would like to request you watch that
and we could maybe do like a whole fucking
because everybody else has seen it we could do a whole thing
it's good for me that's true
me on Chibi Bakas Fuli Kuli
the arc of the main character of Fuli Kuli
is that he basically
like is trying to grow up
like he wants to be an adult
and he wants to he sees the adults around
him as like failing because they're all
like kind of immature and he's like
oh you're supposed to act like this like this is what
it means to be an adult and then it's kind of about him
realizing that you don't need to do
that and that adults generally
being an adult does not mean you're like a radically different
person it just means that you have like a lot
more responsibilities basically he tries to be
cool but instead he's a fool
that's the title
exactly my life where I was super
like it was super inspired by all the
like adults around me and not like in the sense that
like I really like liked what they were doing
but just in the sense that they were authority figures
and so by default I looked up
and I felt that that's what they were doing
was the correct thing to do
like I didn't have any role models
like my dad is a very good
mature person and he's like
cool in his own way but like he's not the kind of cool that
I look up to in a way if you know what I mean
so like I remember specifically
as a child thinking I remember
specifically out loud thinking this
like you thinking it out loud like not subconsciously
like this was something that actually went through my head
sitting there thinking I have
I look up to no one there's no one
who I respect until I found the internet
then only on the internet did I start
finding things I respect and then learning
things about people who aren't on the internet
like a reverse MC mat
I never sort of looked up to any adult either
like people my friends had
idols and stuff like Britney Spears was super popular
back then I remember specifically
thinking to myself like
why would I want to be like someone else
when I can just be me you know
it's just that you never made sense to me
to try and be like someone else
that seemed like hard and what's the point
if there's nothing missing in my life
I only admired fictional characters
I want to
I want to express deeply that this is
this is a very shameful praise
this is a very shameful inspiration
because I don't like actually
like feel like I want to follow
the footsteps or like believe in
the qualities of the adults around me
like like no the adults around me
I'm really like you know what like I want to take up that mental
I want to do what you're doing I'm not like inspired
in the same way that I'm inspired like people online
it's just because they were like the adults
around me and because they're adults
they know what they're doing
it's instilled in me
I'm really curious about this
because you are a big lad
and I'm wondering like
how being like maybe
as tall as the adults
around you affected the way
you look up to them metaphorically
because I have
as a small boy
like knowing that people like obviously
you're a kid people who are bigger than you
are in charge and that's how you
understand it and
but like I've noticed like a couple
times even though there's like a kid who's like
clearly he's like a young teenager
but he's taller than me I feel like
this inherent like
oh he's in charge
not that I actually act on that in any way
but I'm like it's like for a brief moment
I'm like oh
wait no he's a kid he's a kid
I'm cooler than him
I don't really get that
I kind of feel like once you are tall
like that power dynamic of tall
versus small kind of disappears
because I really like even when I'm talking to
someone who's significantly shorter than me
I don't like think about it or like even
realize it most of the time
that's your tall privilege
that's your tall privilege talking
that's tall privilege you have the privilege
of not noticing
us manlets have to notice
where it's forced upon us
being tall is not what it's all cracked up to be
what I hated about being
taller than everyone else
it's just practical and I like
I mean there's some good points but what I really hated
when I was a kid I was usually
the tallest kid in any friend group
or even among like boys
and stuff
so whenever we hung out and whenever people
got in trouble I usually got the brunt
of the blame because people assumed I'm the oldest
and the most responsible because I was the tallest
even though that wasn't the case
I was once hanging out with
like two other boys
and they were throwing rocks
at a sign and they were
throwing rocks at a sign and
this old dude he went up
to us like he sneaked up on us and he
grabbed my arm and like
the two guys scattered
that's grounds for salt
and the two boys just completely
ran for their lives
and I got a big lecture and I was like
oh you're the oldest you should be more responsible
to set example and stuff like that
and I was the youngest of the group
and I was so pissed
he still is cognizant of this
sort of like bestial, fucking
primal power dynamic just from height
and physical stature but like you can be aware
of it and then like not let it affect you
much but especially over the course of your development
it can put you into a feedback
loop and I
based on how people treat me
and talk to me I think most people think
I'm usually three to five years
younger than I am and it was only in the
last couple of years I've started like
getting people treating me like I'm definitely
an adult like after
I spent like a solid year driving and
having a full-time job and like being
completely independent only then
did I seem to have enough swagger
where like people think okay this is like an actual
fucking person like at a store
not like they're with their parents you know what I mean
it's catch-de-vous swaggering
the fuck out of the grocery store
yeah yeah
even up until like my like early
20s even when I was like 21
people would still talk to me like I was in high school
or even say like oh
like think I was in high school right
and when people treat you like that it affects
yourself image so Munchie
meanwhile who's passed for an adult for a long
fucking time and creates this fucking feedback loop
and I think it's a good one
if people think you're an adult unless you're just
nothing but slapped with blame for throwing rocks at you
Munchie's a trans he's a trans adult
he passes
here's the best thing in life and here's
like the thing that like I'm gonna be turning 18 soon
and this is gonna that's gonna be like
the death of my actual life like everything
after that will be nothing because I define
my life as the following
as long as
I can walk up to a cashier
or you know where or my mom
my mom can introduce me to someone
and she can say how old
do you think he is and she can gesture to him
words at me and they can be like
um 22 some guy said
like 28 like everyone has
like like the
gap between my actual age
and uh my
like what people think my age is as long as
that is at least 10 years plus
I'm in the prime of my life as long as
people think that I'm
older than I actually am that's when I know
that I'm like wherever I can walk up to a fucking cashier
or just the other fucking day
when I was getting my passport done
uh the uh the receptionist
the receptionist was like oh
what are you like 22 I'm like
some people get upset some people get upset
because they get older and people stop
carding them at liquor stores
Munchie never got carded
I'll get offered alcohol
all the time and I'll have that
fucking moment I praise this I live
for this I wake up specifically for
this they'll come by and like
would you like a drink and I'm like
I want to know
I'm underage I'm not
allowed to drink alcohol
the sadistic glee that
he says that
he's been waiting to
say this I was surprised Munchie that you're still
against sex that'd be the ultimate the ultimate
prank like after she gets up it's like
I have to let you know something
criminal
I'm underage
that's terrible
that's a great party trick
Munchie's story reminded me
like a little bit what my parents
like to do like whenever they have
used to whenever they used
to have like friends over
the ones they haven't seen in years
so I have a sister older sister by the
way so like
when these
friends would be had been over
I used to be like a little baby and stuff like
that so like my parents
would go like this like let me introduce you to
my littlest one and I was
the tallest person in the room
it was pretty fun
nice
it's fucking beautiful
before we wrap up here
I feel like that's what could happen
I just want to like clarify my
transition here so you can
understand my growing pains
when I say
that I was trying to be mature as like a kid
you may think but Munchie you're so fucking
inconceivable you're just
unfathomable the way that you are
in the sense that you're fucking autistic and retarded
and I hate you like all you do is scream
and thank you viewer like good job
and like thumbs up and thank you
but what I mean is I don't mean like particularly like I was trying to be like
really like serious in the sense
that like real world like
adults would recognize me as an adult
I would like play you know
I would play along and I wouldn't be like a weird
autistic person in real life but I just
mean that I wanted to have the praise of adults
in any scenario so when I was around
people online I would you know
I would act mature in the sense that I would
make funny jokes that's really what it
translate to was I would make funny jokes
and it would be as Steve puts it
on point
so I wouldn't
be fucking like I wouldn't be like a fucking
spur lord but I would be autistic
is what I'm trying to say
and he is to this very day
you guys get it am I explaining myself well
I'm not I'm not I'm not being a
weird like uh like faggot
who only like like dresses in suits
I'm just being I'm just being the kind of guy
that people would unironically praise
for being cool that's what I was
that's what I was like chasing after my life
and I felt the way to do that was to try and be like
mature in the context of whatever
scenario that I was in be it like an actual
like real adult or a funny
person online I can only imagine
munchy in that hamburger onesie
that's that's that's all he
whatever that was still
me trying to be cool whatever my teeth is like
I go to the store I just imagine munchy
with that hamburger onesie in a store
yes I am an adult
I wear the out of the house not in conceivable
amount of time like I wear that like pretty regularly
outside the house like like downtown
incidentally it's a it's a pizza onesie
with the burger like jacket
thing but by the way I'm so
upset with you did you like I'm
so distraught every time I remember
that like okay
here's what my intention was I don't think everybody
can use you but I want this to be the case
when I left like on accident
the burger burger was
right there and I gave it to you like
I didn't want you to ship it I wanted to be
that to be like little Cal from Homestuck
like I passed it to you then you used it
and then like you threw it away but you just
have that you threw it away into a trash can
that was that was going directly to a landfill in
Chicago and then Nate while surfing
on the web aka the trash can
to find some sick pumps
he would find it and would just like transfer
from PCP member to PCP member
appearing the background of videos until the end
of time and have its own narrative arc until
finally you returned to me at the end of like
a conclusion of an art but tragically the
only thing that gets transferred around here is
YouTube wait so who does
have the burger thing right now you
I thought I gave it back to you or something
no you have it's gone it's
lost it's it's oh god damn
it yep it's
it's iconic
you should never have trusted digit hold on
to that this is your mistake I mean it's
possible to say in my house somewhere
I don't please you had it
when you were going around the country
oh god in that
period I had returned it to you
no like at anime
visit me yeah I did
at anime expo I had oh no
you did not give it to me well
I'll have to either find it or find
out who has it
wear it you have to wear it maybe it's currently
going on its own like little cow
it's very let's hope so
let's hope so if it somehow
found its way into the giant
goodwill throw away all the clothes
I think that
happened like a year ago then that would
be where it is but okay great
I'm really happy about that
well hey this is life
anyway let's move on okay guys
we're done with this childhood is gay we've
settled that moving on it's time
to feed begin our
before we we actually get to the thing
there's an announcement about a big change
happening with PCP right now
and it's relevant to this coming up section
here's the deal everybody we are flipping
our recording and releasing episode
days from now on we're releasing
a pcb episodes on
Friday wait the same time
yep listen and we are recording
on Sunday it's because bed
we want to do a thing where we can respond
to the latest episode that just came out
and actually be talking about
what people are still talking about
and flipping that one little thing will allow
us to do that so that we can be
on top of our shit
responding to the new episode that came out
and we can be fucking timely with this stuff
that's the reason that's that this
is a small change for us and
just make releasing on Friday
really all you need to give a shit about
and so now we'll be doing the ask questions on Sunday
this change is great everyone will love it
this change is being carried away by security
no way
it doesn't really matter at all it's just
you know people expect them on Friday
possibly including this one I don't know
I'd be speaking of
shit from last episode on fitness
that came out
there was a huge response
to hashtag PCP fit life
and we got a ton of fucking people
working out and going to the gym and taking a walk
there was one guy that was just like in the woods
just hanging out just hanging out in the fucking woods
yeah
simply beautiful
we're gonna have to make some like merch
like a PCP tank top
so we can get people in there
dude I would love to go to the gym with a PCP
fit life tank top or something
that'd be fucking sick
we'll fucking do something like that
we should definitely do that
I don't know if they have tank tops on redbubble
but we could definitely figure something out
PCP fit life is the way the truth and the light though
we need to make this real
and revisit it
by the way I mean I guess on the subject of the PCP fit life
I've been working out
things have been going good
I've been lowering my sugar intake
I'm still avoiding all sugar
and life is good
I'm doing uh... I'm going keto
I'm going keto
really, really
I gotta lose like 20 pounds
I gained like 20 pounds
I'm mad about it
go load it up
this is a diet right Ben?
yeah, yeah
is that real?
you just go
really low carb for a while
that's pretty much all this
do your raccoon tendencies
I give this a week
no
no, I think this is pretty easy
I think this will actually be pretty easy
it's not difficult to do keto
especially for someone like Ben who can live off of like
peanuts for 10 days
just only eat meat
digi, yesterday
the only thing I ate was a bag of peanuts
no way, no fucking way
do you not still have any carbs do they?
they have a bit
but Ben, what about your, I mean they do have protein
but what of your
omega-3's? what of your vitamins?
oh wait, I have a jar
I have a jar of fish oil pills somewhere
ah, perfect
I'll eat the entire jar
as one puck, what was it?
it melts them together
didn't we name that something last episode?
it was like the
Ben C or something
no, wait, it was the so ugly
it was the so ugly
the log of
it was worth it, I don't even regret doing that
I recommend, in fact I recommend it
excellent
I mean, that's really it
we just wanted to talk about how awesome it was
that people were actually sticking with this fit life
we got a bunch of, so many pictures
and shit, people were tweeting me
people were tweeting the pcp itself
we retweeted a lot of them, so keep tweeting
at tpcrasnators with their hashtag
pcpfitlife and we'll
fucking retweet them, we'll start a
sensation and save the world from
obesity and being gross
oh my god, all the questions are
actually relevant to the topic
in this episode, the questions are good
they're not bad, and they're pretty decent
but before we get to that, we got other shit to do
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa
okay, fine, whatever, I'll talk about it
when we get through it
so the next up is, it's the pcp
theme contest everybody, that's
still going, it's real
and last episode, there were two entries
now that we got like fucking six this time
we got a whole bunch of fucking pcp themes
I want to see what the retention weight for the
pcp is, because I guarantee you
and now on to like
90% viewers click off
well that's fine, we can totally gauge that
and if we know
then so be it, but
we won't change anything
we won't change a thing, why do you think that
because I've always listened
I've never thought the question section was any worse than
the show itself
I always love the question section
I agree, I don't see why anyone, I mean maybe
at the very end when we say like
I mean the show is just random
discussion, like it's never like
a completely on topic or a
complete view of the topic
most of the time the questions are just like
these questions suck, oh here's
what's your favorite anime and then all of us grow
and be like oh yeah we usually just don't
answer any of the bad questions
and just find the good ones
isn't that what we usually do
I don't think it's ever had like a real
problem
other than not having enough good questions
well in any
case that is dead and irrelevant
because it's time to talk about pcp themes
now, we're all going to fucking listen
so get your asses into the pcp themes chat
we're going to listen to all of them
thank you for sending us a link
to twitter, we can't fucking play this
with our music box, we literally said
to make it soundcloud and youtube
you have fucked up, I don't know
how you did it this bad, what made you think
that we could, like that we were going to watch
a video on twitter, who
post videos on twitter
for the first one I guess we'll all just have to hit play
at the same time, jeez Christ
is this the one from
Gavin Watkins?
that's right, that's right
alright, here we go
remember everybody tweet us
hashtag pcp
you need to read the part where he says
this is an indirect recording
of the theme
if you like, I can give you a direct
file so the sound quality is much better
what? oh fucking
wait a minute, if I remember correctly
I listened to this earlier and it sounds like
it was like a cell phone
recording out of the speakers playing
that's so stupid
let's not even listen to this one
what a terrible
dude, you gotta put that on
soundcloud or youtube or something
wait, stop
let's think about this for a second
he has a music file
a computer file
which he then decides to
record digitally
with a microphone
and then upload that file
I actually have a development
on this developing story
because I actually did communicate with this guy
and get him to send me a file
but here's the thing
the file that he sent
I gotta pull up this
email that he sent because it was fucking fascinating
listen to this
ok, so he said hey guys
you retweet my song, that's cool
ok, sorry, so he attached a file
to this, it says sorry if I accidentally
sent you the wrong file
I'm in a setup stage for my computer
and I haven't set up the sound yet
but I'm pretty sure this is the right file
I also, listen to this
actually accidentally
deleted the one from twitter
so I spent a while trying to recreate it
as best I could
while changing some things
how many things went wrong
in this process
he made the song in whatever
program, saved it
uploaded it to twitter, deleted the
master file and all other files
and the only form that existed
was the one on twitter
and then it was deleted from twitter
it's like that time that digi deleted every piece
of his video, so he couldn't recreate it
before the fucking
you know, before the video was upload
are we gonna listen to it?
I am downloading an AIF file
that was attached to it right now
upload it to soundcloud or youtube
we have to be strict, we're gonna get people
sending it on fucking crazy shit
we're gonna get people on mega upload
okay, I can hear sound from this
but no one else can hear it put me
so you gotta fix this buddy
you gotta put this on twitter
or fucking whatever, I apologize
cause I told him just to send it to us
no, you gotta put it on youtube or soundcloud
or something, the end
alright, now we're gonna play fucking one
by Eric Seabass
it's called Crazy
alright, shit this is alright
oh my god
I know
okay, that was pretty dope
that was really cool
it's pretty dope, but it's not
this is the aesthetic of the pc
this could be a jingle for
literally anything
it was a little long
I think it was a little redundant at the end
for a theme song
this is entirely
misguided section
I don't understand
okay, no one is going
all the ones that we've had so far
are not like
PCP matching tonally
stylistically or anything
we should have just made our own
fucking theme song
who's gonna fucking do that
we already have one
I don't understand why we're even
like why not just use the one
we already have
because you fucking cowards were saying how you
didn't kick it match the tone
I said that the
using it as an opening
was a bad idea, it was perfectly fine
as the ending, it just doesn't make sense
as an opening song
that's the point, we're looking for an opening
we decided we didn't want to do the intros
so I took it upon myself to put a clip
of the theme song at the beginning
and did you found it offensive that it would play the song
at the beginning of the podcast
at no point
was my encouragement that we create
a new intro song
I don't like the idea of an intro song on a podcast
it works out like the dick show
if it's super iconic
just like the worst podcast in the world, the dick show
thank god they don't have an opening song
but their opening song is like
not only is it extremely unique
but the fact that he yells yeah over it
whoa, so you're telling me there's like a good way
to do an opening song
no way, no way
if only we could
have some sort of competition to like do that
I should get residuals every time you use that
oh there he is
oh my god
your residuals were getting paid for being on episode
Jesse you're residuals
I'm owed money for my song
Jesse if you don't want us to edit
you're gonna have to sync with us at the end
anyway to get off the lofty
philosophical abstraction
remember the last time Davoo tried to kick Jesse
from the PCP episode
to make it funny I'm leaving
wait please get us your audio we need it
yeah that'd be good
that'd be helpful
listen
next song
what do people want
like what kind of
what do we want out of this
yeah I am actually
I've been trying to
shut up I would like some funny
like a couple of funny
joke lyric lines
that are about the PCP
no that's exactly the opposite of what I would want
thanks man
I like having a unique opening
on every video
why are we not doing that anymore
that was voted down
the reason why we stopped doing it
is because the intros were
shit like for the past like 30 episodes
of intros it was just like
google search the word of what the episode is
ok well then let's not do
a shitty low effort version
and just do the good ones we used to do then
no one will do that
the editors don't want to do that
you guys make a shit load of money editing this thing
I don't care what you want to do
make the show good
when the intros were forced
when they were obligatory
they were uninspired and bad
that's what happened
luckily we found a solution
to make a good theme song
like here we are
doing the solution
let's just keep going shall we
here's the fucking next one
I'm not done talking about this one guys
I just don't think this is a good solution to the problem
god I have to pee so much
I want to talk about the one we already listened to
the one we already listened to
not into generic rock
guitar shredding even if it's good
shredding playing whatever the fuck word I'm supposed to use
even if it's well mixed
I know most podcasts
they think that's the standard
basically have basic instrumentation
and it's well mixed
I want something more particular and original
I already have zero punctuation in my life
I watch lots of the other escapist shows
and I also listen to the biggest problem
I'm completely full
of
competent guitar playing
but listen to this though
this is an important fact you should know
no one here has veto power
it likes to accept one person
it could definitely be used
this is a group decision
it's a democratic process
if everyone wants to have bad taste and pick a bad song
me and digi are both
against generic guitar pieces
that last one was absolute no
for me because it literally sounds like
every other podcast intro
and it was not distinctive
there's no melody that's going to stick in your head
I definitely want something more distinct
it has some sort of strong
melodic
easily chordable thing that you could burst in the song
almost like if you had a cool outro
like I'm supposed to
it is a great outro
this is not about
an outro
this is about an intro
we shouldn't have an opening
the show should not have an opening
it should either just start
I've literally been
against this
against the beginning of this idea
that is fucking bullshit
you never said shit
at the very beginning of this being an idea
I said I will not be a part of this
I will go along with the group
but I have not been on board
that may be true
but I don't believe it
I'm somewhere in the middle on this
I'm willing
I'm more cooperative with the synth idea
I'm optimistic to see what they can come up with
but
even at the beginning if they're all bad
that's what I'm saying
I am prepared to say no to all of them
because I know making a good song is damn near impossible
even for highly talented individuals
no offense
do we want to see if one of these guys
is somehow not going to part
it's my dank lord
here we go
hahahaha
whoa
I actually like this one a lot
okay
I don't want this
for the intro
but I do want it
wait
if you leave a comment before the video
and please kill yourself
yeah
there is no such thing
as objective criticism
yeah
I know why
anime is a Japanese colloquialism
what will we see
dude
dictionary
if you want to make your cries
consciousness high
then you should try
pcb pcb
yeah
okay
pcb pcb
now they're here to fight for me and you
the best guy ever met some other people
too
hahahaha
oh man
she has weaponized thickness
so much
that was lame
it's nothing but trash
whoa those tits
I love those tits so much
use that homestuck fuck with that homestuck suck
page and death is the piece
welcome
free pcb
pcb pcb
this is long enough
this is an actual pcb
theme song
it's not so incredible
I loved it though
dude
I have some thoughts
well it's great and it's funny
that was the best one by far
so far
I kinda think
we could shrink it
we could shrink it for our opening
it's always possible
I don't know if I'll love
the pcb
I don't know if that's gonna be fresh forever
I think that the problem is the song
does not have the best production quality
and it is really funny
as a joke song that we play on the
podcast
I don't know if it has staying
I meant just now
I'm already exhausted the full breadth of that
joke
I can't
give it an emphatic
I wanna hear that to intro every episode thumbs up
as I said in the last time we did the contest
I don't know if this
I'm not terribly into
the song where the lyrics are all a bunch of
references to the shit
I don't know
so do you want it to be pcb themed
or do you want it not
pcb themed
like generic or something
when I say, when we talk about having a theme
that fits the tone of the show
I don't mean one that makes references to the show
it doesn't have to do that
it's really funny having this conversation
because me and munchy just recently
constructed a perfect intro
for our
show
why don't we just do the same thing we did there
what show is that
the one for
stealing your dad's opening
it's like 20 seconds
a fun rap song with some goofy lyrics
that explain the point in brief
and like
it's basically the same thing as the isma one
to me that's like
if you were gonna do an intro it should just be
20 seconds and explains the
point of the podcast in a funny way
the intro for stealing your dad's
beautiful and it will be out in the next episode
that will be live so get hyped for that shit
everyone
that seems like reasonable advice
it should be like relatively short and punchy
short and punchy
and then it has a strong melody
and B about the PCP but also still
I literally get the list
this guy's got a heart though
I love how smile
you could tell he was smiling during the whole recording
like a big giant autism smile
you know what I mean
I do want to say
I will always
I will always be more likely to give the thumbs up
to a song that doesn't have lyrics
verse one that does just because
again podcast intro I do think
20 seconds is about right
alright this is
this is by mostly midi
this is a video on youtube and
he did the thing that we said not to and like
had like a video in the background
it just has a bunch of like images
I just want to say about the song
too late
really
you can see in your voice
okay
this is just literally
the final fantasy intro
it's similar
it's pretty chill
it's not as though
it's a little too chill
it does sound like he was made on
like chiptune
again
these people have put in hours to like
do this like futile song
now when they get on all we do is just shit on them
like oh no we don't want to do it
that was nice but again
it was generic
think of it this way none of these people
could have even spent more than like
a week or two on this right
like we only announced the contest so long
ago so it's not like we're burning down their
fucking masterpiece
alright they're entering a contest
and here they are facing the fucking fire
I release songs better than this every day
alright so I'm going to be a harsh on these people
if I could make the intro for the
show myself there's no reason we need
a contest
cause the reason we didn't like the outro song
for the intro was that it wasn't hype
it was just kind of like a silly
possible
but I'm sure that there's some people out there
who were working on a song anyway
who were just like I don't know let's fucking enter this
you know that's what the first one and this one
feel like
I can't prove it and maybe I'm wrong but it could
have been the case they just made a song
that's pretty good
I would say this intro is closer
than the ones I've heard so far but not in a good
way if that makes any sense
it at least
feels like sitting down to hear people talk
but we do want
one that's more energetic so I guess that is another thing
it's like we're sort of using these as the
initial wave of pawns to churn
through to then analyze like
here's what you did wrong
and as we analyze and destroy these
people's lives and dreams we're like understanding
slowly what we actually want
we're getting more and more specific each time
that's how you become like a content creator
you just make shit that sucks and then you just figure out
what you did wrong and then you fix it as you go so whatever
alright let's go to the next one what's the next one
this is by Alex C. Biel
oh
I know that guy
oh I don't want to do
anything
to
do
that's fucking called sleep in a good way
what pcp
episode
will I
have
replay
go
to the school
of college
cause it's
I
am
so
all the time in the world
to listen to
my favorite
pop
what a guy
we should play this in one of our
funerals
yeah my face
wow
that's it that's it
that's the one guy
yeah that wins
there should be a good like the rotation of ending
like you can always have the same one
if you want to like
have right now
yes
listen to the song
fuck off
a bit like good
this is okay this is like a good song
not a good show
shut up mate I'm trying to listen to the god damn song
alright keep passing the book
okay reference to the page
yeah
hey that was great
it's a terrible theme
it's terrible
that's like
it's not hype and it's also very long
that's like when you're watching the anime
when you're watching a season of an anime
and then like one of the episodes has like a really sad
like part of the narrative ending
the different ending theme song
for that episode
that's what that one is that's good
okay let's clarify real quick
do we want to be hype or just upbeat
I don't know
I just want it to sound like it would be
what you want to hear before a pcp podcast
I won't know it until I hear it
that's what's important
we could just have like a happy version
of the normal song
I think we could clearly say that that song
did not suit the tone
right
think about the way that we open our show
for any dickheads who think about how dick always opens
the show and how his theme plays
into that real well right that's good
so think about how we start our show
which is usually with Nate like busting and saying the shit
or munchy you know and then we introduce
each and every one of us
and like what's the right mood you want to be in
I mean traditionally with the intros
I would just have them fade whatever song
is playing underneath
yeah I mean that's the right thing to do
and I mean like I don't know like if we're struck
with like some great song
and we just like think that like oh if we just do
something slightly different as an opening
we can like work that like hey man
it's all I'm hoping to experiment and do all kinds
of crazy shit here
next one is
by
Groundless Slash
Garbage Burner
this is PCP punk rock anarchy
okay okay
I like this part
good song
look at that song
wow
reference
this
this is like an AMV song
cause these people screaming over it
yeah
oh I do I do
IT'S AMV
this episode
that's what it is
PROCESSED
oh it's soft already I was gonna sing it
I really liked it so much
not for the PCP necessarily
but I like it a lot
I can't
I find it hard
okay I think tonally it was about right
but I find I can't I don't know if I can sign off
on a theme song that is like
that could be the opening to
any podcast
I generally agree
since we're doing a contest I'm shooting for the stars
you know
and that's it
wait wasn't there
we already played it last episode
oh we did
I'll have to listen later
I didn't even know this contest was happening
until I came into this episode
and that's why you know
that's why we voted you out of the PCP
digi
we were waiting to tell you
well that was good alright just take that feedback
listen to that whole section and for what you can from it
I wanted everybody
I mean should we have people in the comments
like comment on like
what you think about the submissions
feel free but I don't care what they think
yeah okay alright
that's fair
none of us know what we want
and some of us don't even want to
I know exactly what I want
I want no theme song
I want individual intros on every episode
well we can't very well do that
but after we've done this contest
at first and I was voted down
so frankly shut the fuck up
and get on board with the program
because that's what's happening now
we don't even want to do it anymore
I'm in this now
we're contractually obligated to carry this contest
I'm interested I'm invested now
I like this and I want to keep doing it
I mean I think it's
getting all these submissions is great
there you go
our criteria are all massively contradictory
we should just let the fans vote
that's the worst thing I ever wanted
no absolutely not
we should just let the fans vote
I am at least curious of their input
like they're
oh yeah I want to hear their input
I want them to vote on whether or not
they think we should have a theme song
whether or not they think
because personally
when we started putting the opening
on the show
I didn't know at first because I wasn't listening back to the shows
I had missed a bunch of episodes
but May listens to all of them
and she was like yeah I skip it every time
it's a huge pain in the ass
so I was like well obviously everyone's doing that
because nobody wants to hear this song for the thousandth time
for 30 whole seconds at the start of the episode
so like unless it's
insanely short
that happened like one time
that happened one time
it was the one time I saw it
and I was like this is horrifying
it was too long one time
Jesus
this is what's happening it's over
we're doing a PCB theme
there's no debate now we're in it
there's no challenging this
this is great
get excited
this is trumps America
it's sad to have to debate this because I like
I really like these songs
I really like that they're being made
so I like the contest for that reason
but now it's so fraught
it's so fraught
okay so the thing is we keep saying all these criteria
but speaking only for myself
if you just make a great song
it makes me hype just because it's great
you might be able to give a thumbs up for me
just being like you know what
maybe this doesn't fit my preconceived notions
of what the shows tone should be
but the song is great
on it's own
you gotta get the Beyblade
animated TV
you gotta change the thing that they say
at the end they say let's Beyblade
you gotta change that to PCP
and that's what you gotta do
that's what I'll get my vote in the general election
vote for that
I wanted to be
acapella
of Ocarina of Time songs
that's the PCP intro
alright
let's go home
alright let's go to questions
oh god no
let it end
let the show be over
no we have to
what are all these weird
why are we obligating ourselves to random things
we've said we're going to do all the time
can we not make decisions that
change and evolve based on the situation
that is obviously in front of us
when things are bad don't let them keep being bad
we told people
that we were going to read questions
and people have asked questions
do they even really care
look look we can bust through the questions
in like three minutes
this is a simple
issue
when the episode goes long we do less questions
so let's just do less questions
here it is
here's the pity question
this is a question that is answered
by another question in this thing
this is from at biscuit meep
are there any episodes of the PCP
that you wish were never made
from iclone that says
can you do another show similar to the monster episode
it was everyone's favorite
there's the joke everybody
monsters 2 literally went
that's what I want
immediately great question
there it is that's the pity questions done
onto the bonus lounge
what do they got
someone just says driving is gay
no question mark
alright let's talk about that
that is not the question
I mean
is there anything that you did in your childhood
that really makes you cringe now
a cringe scene is stupid
and childhoods are great
and if you did something stupid as a kid
it's not like oh my god I'm fucking so stupid
it's just like wow you did something wrong
well everyone's done something wrong
I remember Jimmy Newtide
he said one cares not to acknowledge the mistakes of one's youth
Johnny
Neutron also said God of Blast
do we listen to him do we blast
do we have a holocaust every day of our life
do we do G-Hodges because Johnny Neutron wants us to
no we live our own lives
we're autonomous we're not
ISIS bombers like you
and Johnny Neutron
feeling the emotion of cringe
and thinking that it's a bad thing
that's the first mistake
that's the first clue that you're not mature
that's what they mean
cringe is bad and it's not true
yeah
cringe goes to like chibi bakas
literally we are
bringing chibi back
mean hippo are in the process of
reviving chibi
this is the point of chibi bakas
okay next question
drawing like yaoi is not cool
you should be proud of what you've done
actually I haven't answered that question
next question
how much rape bro
question mark
next question
all of these are just
terrible
the problem with this is that
when you tell people the topic
sometimes they're all like the same question and suck
what was your favorite anime as a child
there you go
that's the same question but the child
exactly that's what I'm saying
excellent
wait was that a real question
that was a real question
wait who asked that
someone says what were your dreams and ambitions
do you have anything
it was R U guy
when you were kid what was your favorite anime
my dream and ambition as a kid
was to make a fucking
manga
because I liked dragon ball
I had one volume of dragon ball
just dragon ball
in the library and I would read it and reread it over and over again
I'd be like I want to do this
right
I'm a veterinarian as I already said in the episode
my dream as a little kid
was to trick a digi bro into talking to me
dude same
what a mistake
when I was young I wanted to be really ripped
that was my as a result of watching
dragon ball z and later one piece
I just wanted to be an anime character
didn't really care which one
my dream was just to be some sort of artist
professionally so yeah
my dream was to be 2 million dollars
and it's still my dream right now
we have fan art too
we have a fan art section
god no
the fan art it'll just be on screen
here's all of it right now
here's all of the fan art on the screen right now
time for the time for the fan art which we were supposed to do before
question but who gives a shit
look at this first one
hey thanks parron unit 01
the cool drawing of me
Adam desu
wait no no this one's good
I feel like
the spite
that we're like spitting right now
at just like people's like hard work
trying to make us feel like
it's not even funny
people that worked really hard
to express their sincere admiration of us
fuck you
yo this one in Nate was good
except my eyes are bright
the one that was pointing at the city with his fucking
all of his hair bulging out and everything
let's get to that
back start for this is Ethan
said in chat
actually
complex backstory here
usually for every questions
we announce we're doing questions and then at the end
Nate will say oh we're done
we're done doing questions now
but last time he didn't say
we're done doing questions and so for the past week
I've been occasionally going to chat and saying guys
we're still going we need more questions
so we've been doing that for like the past week
and then eventually I was in a call with Ethan
and he said like he asked a question
and he said hey Munchie how do I throw my best for that at him knowing
and then I said this
by stuffing a bar of soap in your mouth
and walking your football field away
also I'll be kicking you double that son
and then someone will be better
wait wait wait going back
going back to the urban dictionary one
look at the way that it's shaded
look at the way that shadows are
it's baffling
like the shading technique employed here is baffling
I don't think this person is an expert
well it's weird because like he did it right
in certain places but then he like
like look at the folds on your robe like that makes sense
like down at the bottom
but then over it there's just these big thick
fucking bars
those are anime blush lines
yeah we were all grilled
I think the point of that is that the light is at his back
so he was trying to make it like he was darker in the front
oh no I get what he was going for
he just put his technique as bizarre
is all I'm saying
there's a face on the bottom left there
who cares about this fan art of a lot of us
how about this fan art of only me
how about that
Lane Slimes
that one down there
I like that me and Nate are directly
in front of each other
like we're Nemesis
that's true
I'm the only one not making a comment
I'm just giving a death stare
it's the angel and the demon
you know Nate and Mage
I have a huge dick in this
a huge dick
lots of cubes
what was the BD for though
I have no clue
I'm assuming big dick
I assumed big dick as well
this was like in the chat
because I saw where this was
it was for a specific reason that BD was there
but I can't fucking remember
back to daddy
then we have another one just of me
because I'm just like a photogenic person
this is my lines line
this is me eating my ice cream soup
ice cream soup
I love ice cream soup
that's my favorite soup
you fucking animals
except that I'm on keto now
wow
what the actual fuck
why
here's my chip
it's just like a digi
my ice cream soup is different from
munchies ice cream soup
probably just
Mage what is your ice cream soup
it's just literally melted ice cream
I like melting ice cream
unpopular opinion
I really like the expression on this drawing
by the way
it's cute
let me make a radical proposal
let me make a modest proposal
if I may
maybe
art of one of us doesn't count
I know what you mean
art of you a lot
and you like it a lot and you want to talk about it
what
I hear what you're saying
and there's definitely some logic to that
like this is not like this is
this first one is Nate fan art
and this second to last one is Munchie fan art
this is not PCP fan art
and same with digi
maybe we just need to use the smell test
if it seems PCP related or not
I mean
I haven't been given the chance
to use the smell test most of these
would not have
let me say
the Munchies one
aren't they related to what he said
related to the PCP
they're not just Munchie
like the digi one
I would argue I guess it's just
digi fan art but the rest is
PCP related
okay alright
we should smell test these before
alright here we go
Karabelle I have not seen this
can we play a game until it just hit play at the same time
oh god okay yeah
but you have to click and pause so it would load for you
I will click and pause
alright I'll do that
let's all press play
one, two, three
go
hello everyone and welcome to another
episode of the pro crastonators
podcast
I am the best guy ever
and today we're joined by an illustrious cast
two scoundrels
first up Ben St
excuse me
I'm so sick because my body
has been neglected
it's wasted away
there it is
that's why I'm on keto
did I mention I'm on keto?
you guys do this podcast quick
I'm about to be a puddle on the floor
10 minutes
I love Olaf from frozen
dude I love the wizard of Oz
dude I love
nuclear thrones
dude I love water
I think our crit is here
our art is so funny
that we deserve animations
like are we just like such like a
unique cast of characters
that we're going to play like in an audio clip
of like a part of our show that we've already had
they're just like on the show wholesale
again
we could probably edit that in
yeah we'll edit it in
yeah that's easy
oh I liked that
I wasn't sure why he chose
of all segments to choose one like that
the intro seemed to be popular
I don't know
I think he picked him, wait wait
that was a recent episode
maybe he just picked the most
recent episode
please explain to us, please with a gun to your head
tell us why you chose
he wanted to do the Olaf joke
and the melting part
oh
nah hey thanks Karabella
we have to leave, good bye
alright listen everybody, hey thanks for being here
we were actually done now
thank you so much for all of your art and music and stuff
everyone we appreciate everybody who made anything for us
including with the themes, forgive us
I already did
I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm no longer a child
alright there you go
patreon.com slash theprocrastinator
there's a new one out now
go to patreon.com slash theprocrastinator
to cancel your pledge because we trashed your song
yeah exactly
$1 in the bonus lounge
more questions, more visibility
more questions
more questions forever
send us more
now remember hashtag PCP theme
if you want to do the music for the themes
listen back to that section
figure that shit out for yourself
and hashtag pcbfitlife
if you tweet your shit
is that going to be a lot of retrain segment now
well I don't know maybe
just be fit and do that
and then hashtag pcbfanart
or possibly hashtag pcbart
but fanart works better
send us your pictures and we'll fucking talk about it
we're so sick
we're purring hard the machine
good bye
hey
I
supposed to be working
right now
I'm supposed to
be working
right now
but I'm not working
I'm doing nothing
my dick I'm jerking
myself
I'm sucking