Hello everybody, PCP, hi it's me Gibb. This is The Pro Crastinators Podcast, we're here with Ben and no one else.
PCP, if indeed such a thing exists, hey, fuck, I just heard a beep in my headphones. I'm gonna fill a buster for like 30 seconds while I plug my headphones in
and try and kill some time where I'm talking before I can hear you again. Okay, I'm back, I'm back, good. Podcast works.
So yeah, this is the PCP, The Pro Crastinators Podcast, assuming such a thing exists as of right now.
Oh yeah, the channel's been destroyed, it's gone. Yet again, and nobody knows why, no reason given.
No reason given, I mean that's part of the course, if you're given a reason it's probably like a bad thing.
Yeah. They're actually paying attention like they're trying to kill you for real, but because they're doing their general thing of like, you're just gone.
Yeah. Submit like a thing like fine, I guess we'll be back in some amount of weeks.
Until then I guess this will be on my own, my own Ben's channel I guess.
Or maybe not. Maybe we won't be back in a matter of weeks. We just don't know.
God, I'm like nervous about uploading it. I'm like nervous that if we upload this they'll like take punitive action against wherever it's uploaded.
Why would they do that? I mean, I just don't know.
I mean, that's what they did like when Monkey got deleted, right? They just like deleted all the new channels he started to make.
Right, they also stopped doing that. I think that was because Monkey was being investigated for a specific reason, like oh he's making school shooters real again.
Like oh, he's the cause of it all. It's like that was like a strange thread they were following.
I don't think anything like that has got anything to do with us. I think it's just one of the generic
something or others happened and YouTube did not actually check to see if it was valid or not and they just said oh yeah, go on.
It's a bit weird though because it's like it wasn't a strike. It was just like termination immediately.
There was no strike. Just the channel is gone at about 4.30 in the morning
and then when you look it says it's the terms of service violation
and there's a little like form email saying should I read what the form email says?
Yeah, just if it's got no info that's important.
No, no, no, no. Let's see. It said something about like illegal activity.
Like encouraging illegal activity or
where was the other thing? Here, YouTube account notification. We'd like to inform you we've received a complaint regarding your YouTube account to the Procrastinators.
Upon review, we've determined that your activity, the activity in your account violates our terms of service linked to the terms of service.
As a result, we've terminated your account. We don't allow content that encourages illegal activities or incites users to violate YouTube's guidelines.
The only depictions of such activities that we may allow need to be educational or documentary in nature and it shouldn't be designed to help or encourage others to imitate them.
Um, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Yeah, so I read that and I was like...
Wait, wait, wait. You are prohibited. You are prohibited from accessing, possessing or creating any other YouTube accounts.
I missed this part before, but it says that at the bottom. What the fuck?
That's, that's insane.
Uh, yikes.
I mean, when they say you, they don't know that this is a shared channel. Like, do they just mean
Nate or what?
What, what, what, I don't know that action. How could they take action on that?
Like if I posted this into one of my channels, well, but like I'm not the procrastinators. Well, but here's
Okay, I guess what makes me nervous is like they say here you are not allowed to
make new YouTube channels or own other YouTube channels. If we upload
some content that is clearly meant for this channel,
then that, I don't know. I don't think it's likely that anyone would like notice,
but I think there's,
I think that would be considered like we're getting around YouTube guidelines and they might take punitive action. I just, it seems plausible.
That seems plausible to me that they would take, they would punish us for the same no reason that they've given here.
Uh, uh, it encourages illegal, I mean, I'm not sure,
I'm not sure if this is specific to like our complaint. This encourages illegal activities or uses, incites users to violate YouTube guidelines.
That sounds like it was chosen specifically or auto-generated specifically based on what our, our crime was.
Um, I don't know that, but it seems specific.
It said, it said we received a report, right?
Uh, oh, well, reports. You're right. It said
we've received a complaint regarding your YouTube account.
Upon review, we determined
blah blah blah and we don't allow current, yeah.
Like had issue with something that was said on one of the many videos on this channel. I'm gonna guess it's more recent.
It could just be like you were puzzling. It could be like a holdover from when Brad had the channel.
But that was like content ID strikes, so that would be something different.
Um, but also there were a few people who were like flagging the videos in an attempt to get Brad off our channel.
Yeah.
So that could also still be it. It's like we don't have any information. We're just gonna
figure it out.
We don't know if like, yeah, we don't know when the complaint was filed. Could have been could have been two months ago, three months ago.
Don't know. We don't know what it was filed, what video was filed in response to
how many of them there were.
I mean,
apparently
they quote unquote followed up like apparently they quote unquote checked
and
agreed with whatever the complaint was, but I don't actually believe that any any human being like looked and checked at all.
No, absolutely not. No.
Uh, it's fucked. It's very fucked. Um,
I all right if if you're worried about like re-uploading we can just put this out as an mp3
We we have like an iTunes feed. We have we have a procrastinators website if like like
It before until we know exactly what the fuck is going on. We can release this in non-youtube areas
Yeah, sure. Yeah, true. Yeah, sure. Yeah, true. Yeah, sure. Yeah, true. Yeah, yeah, I know it's yeah true and sure
Yeah
Shut up. Okay, I'm sorry. Um, but yeah the the channel I mean
My my first thought was it was the um
The stream we did. Yes, where we talked a lot about killing cops in now
Uh, yeah, none of us advocate literal murder obviously
But it could be taken like that if you don't have any understanding of of like context
To be honest, it was my first thought too is is this about the charity BLM support stream? Which
Wouldn't that just be fucking amazing?
If that were if that were what did it? I mean, wouldn't that be
I mean, it would be a goal. It would be a great
Marketing ploy to get us back is saying. Oh, you think black lives don't matter. Huh, youtube?
Yeah
Huh, is that what you think we don't
But they won't they're they won't they we don't know we don't know if that's we don't know
I mean, so like if it's not that there's no reason to go down that
Path of like accusing youtube of something. They're not doing that's just gonna make us look stupid
inciting um
What what what was the description inciting something or um encouraging illegal activities or inciting users to violate youtube guidelines?
I mean, that's
That seems like maybe that would count maybe someone
thought it was terrorism
Thinks that like it's like an antifa terrorist stream or something
I mean, it wouldn't be that surprising to see antifa and they think oh, it's bad
Yeah, well, I didn't mean the stream didn't say antifa
I mean, I might have like joked about it in the stream or something. It wasn't like tifa blm
I mean some people think blm is a terrorism. Yeah
I don't know man. I I guess if I had to bet
I would say that yeah, it was probably that stream which is fucking amazing. Um
And like obviously should not have been flagged or such a thing
But
We just don't know
Nate has supposedly appealed the suspension, uh, which they gave you the option here to do
Um, he he didn't I kind of wish I could have seen what he submitted
Uh, oh
Well, what are you what are you just the same sort of stuff he posted the last time but the bread thing
It's like just as much information as you can. Please could you get back to us as soon as possible?
You know email shit. I don't know if they're
You know, I don't trust I don't really trust Nate to like be on top of this
I mean, maybe you don't
Well, I trust him to be on top of like administrative email shit
I
Well, I mean this is important for him as well. This channel is obviously it is but like he he was pretty
I guess it worked out in the end last time, but he was pretty like
he was pretty like lackadaisical about like
how many like
Like he he didn't want to make tweets about like the the the channel getting hacked for like a week
Last time. I don't know. Yeah, I still don't really understand why
Like something about like keeping his like his feed for the audience like clean, but it's like
I don't know. I mean of what?
Uh, of I don't know. Okay, I don't I don't know either. Um, so that's that's all I mean
That's all I mean when I say that we should um
I mean, we can do the tweeting ourselves. We can't we can do the tweeting we can do the tweeting ourselves, but like that's
uh
Lol
Pcp's dead
Nobody even shows up. This is just us. I was I was so hype
Like like not hype as in like a good just sort of like getting like adrenaline
Thinking like oh, it's just gonna be me. It was gonna be me until two minutes before
Like the the cutoff point
I'm I was thinking. Oh, okay. I'm gonna be I'm gonna be doing the thing myself. Okay. I'll
I'm sorry. I was gonna I was gonna have a whole spiel about like the pcp is just me now
Yeah, every like everyone like I don't expect
Like you were the only one I would have expected to show up tom isn't on that much munchies never on
Digi is very rarely on jesse is very rarely on yeah, and that's it
Uh, it's just me. It's it's you
I would say I would say I'm more on more often than you are right. Would you agree with that?
Uh
I guess I don't really pay you too much close attention to that. You're like usually on
um
I'm usually on I'm almost always on at least on the normal episodes
Is it Nate is never not here like that's so that's wild to me. That's wild to me that he's not here
When's the last time he's missed an episode?
It was a while ago. What's he fucking doing?
What I think I think it was it was a similar thing to this where I was here and then you were here and then
I think they came in late and so well, maybe jesse came in I can't remember
I feel like there was one time when I was in your position
And poised to be the only one
On an episode and I was like, oh, what am I gonna do?
What is this episode gonna be about? Yeah, one of these days it's gonna happen. Yeah, and it's gonna be a historic moment
And it's gonna be really funny. That'll be the straw that broke the camel's back. Um
Nobody. Yeah, nobody shows up
If the uh, we've we've been we've been dwindling and I don't know why I genuinely do not understand why why uh, uh
More people don't feel like
They ought to be here
regularly, I mean I can I I I can see why they don't it's like digi only comes on when she has something
she wants to talk about
and
You know, she doesn't like just
Casual chat. I mean she did but now she does that with me and that was like that was like when may appeared
Did you just stop talking to us a lot?
Uh, you think so? I don't know. It's been so long. I don't know if I even remember what that was like before
Well, I mean back in the old days when we were all cool
We would talk in the pcp chat so much that every single day would be like a like a fucking wave like a
10 hours of like discussion that I would I would wake up to and I'd scroll through it
Yeah, my thoughts at the bottom now. I do that in other discos the pcp chat is sort of
Completely dead and it's not a bad thing really. It's just that
um
There's there's not a lot of discussion going on between us. Um, I mean
Yeah, there's there's less. It's not that we like we
It's not that we never do that
Uh, it's it's it's gotten more rare though. I mean, it's definitely more rare than it used to be
I don't know if I would call like
May showing up the reason why it went from like more talking to less talking. I don't know if there was like a hard
Not not not like entirely just did you specifically? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Uh, I guess so
I guess that's probably true
Man, you know munchie wants to focus on school. Jesse just wants to be away from the internet entirely
It's like people have reasons
I mean, you don't I don't understand the wanting to be away from the internet thing
You don't have to like look at the comments or anything
You can just show up and record an episode and then leave and like that's fine
That it takes like two hours out of your week. I don't know. I just don't know
What everyone's thinking what went wrong. It makes sense to me to me. It's obvious. I should be here and so I do
I can't empathize with other people's perspectives
That's a symptom of autism they say
Yes, so there you go
So to to save this podcast being about itself. I have a topic. Okay
Um, I am fucking
terribly
Fucking exhausted arguing politics in
The social media areas that I frequent. Yeah
It is it is a dreadful slog
And I I see now why people are so angry. It's not because they think other people are the devil
It's just that the small minutiae of like getting someone to
You know getting to the same page like getting to level one with someone
Is so fucking taxing because everybody is distrusting and antagonistic towards everyone else
Yeah, everyone assumes so much of your position based on what the talking points are
They they consolidate your you know, if you're saying a leftist thing and a moderate is like
I don't believe that leftists are good because of these various instances of leftism being bad
Therefore I am going to ascribe all of that bad stuff to you and I'm not going to trust anything you say
And I'm going to assume that you are going to be the worst kind of person
Yes, and they just don't read the thing I'm talking about. They don't read the words that come out of my mouth
And it makes it so fucking difficult to just
Converse people always talk about let's just have a discussion, but they don't want to
Even consider the idea that the person they're talking to is not the worst
type
It could be quite a nuanced person
It could be like a you know one of the good ones you could be talking to right now
But if you just go into it expecting to hate them
Then you will and I will hate you back
And I'm so fucking tired of trying to be the mediator the moderate man that gets people to talk to each other
I can't do it anymore. I quit
I got really mad at my roommate yesterday and I yelled at him and I was a big jerk
Because I was kind of doing that. I don't know. He said he we were having like a
Discussion about cops and he said one thing that was a little more that was a little like
It wasn't it wasn't even he wasn't even being pro cop that would be wrong to say
He he said like one thing about it that I didn't agree with and I like
Really lost my cool and made an idiot of myself
Uh lamal very funny very very epic. No, it's not funny or epic ben. You're a bad man. It's true
You gotta ran it in you gotta be like
Well, that's that's the problem is that if you it's so much less taxing
To go crazy and ballistic and just let whatever reaction comes to you immediately be the one that you go with rather than
Holding yourself back thinking about it and then approaching, you know with more neutral terminology
Because it just it just wears down on you if you talk to everyone like that everything becomes a long drawn out fucking
Everyone says
Ben instead of getting mad and being insulting. Why don't you just why don't you just like
Engage with them. Why don't you just like be nice and like show them they're wrong?
Why don't you show them they're like politely demonstrate how incorrect they are?
Like that's not really hard and and like taxing to do
Like really like annoying and difficult and doesn't work most of the time even no matter how well you do it
Uh
Anytime I don't do that. It's because I'm like, I'm just not willing
I'm just not willing to do that to put that work in for someone. I don't think deserves it
Uh, yeah
Yeah
It's hard. I just I I don't know really what
Like direction to take either. I just stay silent on issues and just let people do whatever
So that I don't wear myself out or I
Let myself get mad
And respond to people like no, you're so fucking stupid. I'm not even gonna talk to you like I don't want to say that
I don't want to be the guy that does that. No, I sometimes it feels like everyone hates me
Yeah, so it's like
I don't want to know what it wants to be. I've been sane. No, nobody does take my take my
Uh, uh heed my warning ebonyzer
These chains these chains were forged in life
Uh, yeah
Be nice kids
um
That goes for both sides. I like sure sure
Like a person on the right
Who who assumes that because I'm not on the right or I'm on the left or whatever
I mean such broad terms, but like yeah, generally speaking. They will like assume that I am like
a social justice warrior out to get a gotcha moment
and but
um
For me to assume that they assume that before they've shown their hand would also be wrong
I need to like and engage with people
normally
Uh and see if they they do things that are like, okay
He's not he's bad faith
argumenting right now
And sometimes I try to push through because a lot of the time you can't tell the difference between
you know someone who's
Legitimately only thought about it a little bit and they're just asking legitimate honest like uh sincere questions
about stuff
Like they've heard a thing and they're like i'm i'm not quite sure about this thing
and if you attack them
They're gonna have a bad experience with you and it's like it's just
You gotta you gotta handle everything you gotta walk around so many fucking eggshells
And then some of these eggs, they're not eggshells. They're just rotten eggs
Sometimes you step on rotten eggs and eggshells
You know and it's like you can't you can't win sometimes it sucks
You know it's a little related. Have you followed any of the shit that has gone down around jk rowling this week?
Uh, I followed it vaguely. I know that she is uh what you would describe as a turf lamal and um
I
But I can't like off the top of my head. Remember what she'd said about things
I've seen you responding to tweets. I hate that guy that guy that guy. Uh, what a guy
Uh, the the the reminds me
What what you were just saying reminds me of is that all right, so
I mean, I guess we can go over what happens if you think it's interesting to to mention but like
uh, Rowling
Rowling says like turfy stuff Rowling says like trans people are you know in so many words
Uh trans people trans women are just like perverted men with a vagina fetish who want to jerk off in bathrooms
Like let's cut to the fucking chase. That's what she's saying. Uh, uh, that's that's that's the effect of all her words combined
um, so she says this and then
everyone in
Oh, did I just do it? I don't I really don't think that's a straw man. I really I understand like maybe it might seem like
I'm complaining about oh people like making assumptions about what I actually mean and strawmenning me
I don't think that's what I'm doing genuinely. I think that's what she's what she's getting at
um
So she she says all this stuff that amounts to that basically and then
You show up and you you you criticize that or you criticize someone who agrees with it, right? Like this fucking loser
Uh, uh, uh, Graham Linnum Graham Linnum
Uh, uh, Linnum Graham. I I think it's pronounced Linnum, but I don't know. Um
Um
You glinner you show you criticize him or something you ask you innocently ask him
Why did your wife divorce you Graham?
Why tell us why your wife divorced you because in your heart because in your heart, you know that it's because he's like a weird obsessed
Uh twitter turf troll and like is just like a weird
Jerk and like of course you would divorce him if you had like a fucking brain
Yeah, I mean you say innocently us, but you know
That you're you're you're poking a protodam to see how he'll react. It's sort of like a yes a joke stir innocent innocent question
That anyone would want to know the answer to could have happened could come up in any in any casual conversation
totally reasonable
And everyone
Everyone is just like it's amazing. It's amazing how instantly it's like oh another loser
Oh another loser incel guy who hates women
They like cannot it's these like it's these like
it's these like
Dweebie guys
And and even more so it's like these like it's these it's these cairns
It's these white cairns who will who will descend and will respond like oh this guy. Oh, ha ha look how he hates women
It's like because you're criticizing jk or someone as a point like that's it. That's all it takes
They don't just they don't need to justify it at all. They can't conceive
They can't conceive that anyone would be would be here
Voicing any descending opinion unless you just thought that women were bad
And they and they shouldn't be allowed to talk if you think jk rallying is wrong about anything
The only possible reason would be that you are a misogynist
And I don't know whether it's literally that I think it's more that jk rolling
is framing whatever she's talking about as
you know
As like a women saying what I'm saying is a feminist women thing
And if you're against that position, then you're you know, you hate women if you believe
direct quote from jk rallying quote
If you think that trans women are women you are saying that
that that
quote that
natal women
natal women quote unquote
You want them to be molested in bathrooms
Jerked off over in locking rooms by creepy men who are just who are just pretending
Who are just like who just like went through all the trouble of getting like hrt and like an id change and a legal name change
And all that shit. They're in there
Just jerk to jerk it, right? That's the only reason they would be
Uh
And and and direct quote direct. Yeah, this is what she said. She said I am jk rallying and you
This is how I type are a rapist by proxy
comma
sjw's comma ben saint you that's what she said
um
And that's it and that's it. Um, I hate I hate jk rallying. She is bad. She's always been bad
Everyone knows that she
fucking
Poops her pants on twitter like every other month by saying some dumb shit that everyone hates
Uh about harry potter or about fucking genders shit
So, you know just another in a long in a long and very epic line
Of that kind of thing
Just and then this fucking guy graham linem is just like oh my god
Someone more famous than me is also a fucking piece of shit
Just like me that makes me look better in comparison on on this on this. Oh my god
People disagree with it. Look how many fucking bigots there are the hate women. I'm gonna fucking come
And and he's you know, he's got he's just he's just he has he's hiv positive is what i'm saying
What is that true? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
That's probably why that's probably that's probably why his wife is laughing
That's probably why his wife divorced him honestly is probably because he was hiv positive
um
Because from the brain damage she gave himself from like jerking off
Oh, that's that's kind of mean of her to do from like jerking off and eating and eating poop
He gave himself brain damage and got aids. That's I know it's sad
It's sad, but true
And I won't turn away from reality
You'd think uh a writer would be able to write good tweets
You might
You might think so
Graham is very funny. Graham is very funny and cringe. Yeah, this is like supposedly a comedian
What did he write? I think I recognize one of the things he wrote the one everyone knows was the it crowd, which I've never seen
Oh, yeah, that's funny. Uh
He didn't he co-wrote it didn't he
He he co-created it
He didn't co-write it at least that's not what I mean. Maybe he did that too. I don't know
Um wikipedia says he co-created it
Whatever that means
So he's an ideas guy. I don't know
could be
I guess I
I guess did you did
Did you see that um all three of the uh main cast of harry potter rupert grint emma watson daniel redcliffe?
They said trans lives uh trans trans rights
Trans lives matter. Fuck off joe. Fuck off joe. Get fucked
Um, so he said um jk Rowling died. He said the the which is pretty cool the the the
Uniformity with which those people step in line and claim to sincerely believe that someone saying jk Rowling can suck my dick
Is a threat of oral rape. They all say it. They all love it
They think it's totally reasonable
To say something like oh jk Rowling is getting rate oral rape threats
Be just just because she said that sex is real and and women are real
That's why that's why people people threatened her quote unquote threatened her with oral rape by saying jk Rowling can suck my dick
inexcusable
Unfathomable, I mean it's it's it's it's the reductionist argument. It's like
The the consolidation of everything into one point that you can easily tweet twitters that is hell
It's the thing that is destroying our society destroy twitter. I would invite anyone
I would invite anyone if you're bored and you want to see if i'm right just just respond
With something really mean to gram linen
Just just say like something just say the like the worst thing you can
Like just try and try and make him cry because if you win if you you win an argument if you make somebody cry
Just just say anything to him that you think would hurt his feelings
Right and just like wait how long until someone says that you are a that you hate women
or
Something like that right any of the things i've just described right that you're like an abusive woman hating like toxic
man
But also an sjw snowflake
Or something
I mean, it's it's funny in this context and i'm talking about doing this only in minecraft obviously
Yeah, this is true. Obviously, obviously
Guys, ben sain. I think I think I think i'm worried about you ben. Yeah
I'm worried about you. I'm worried about you. Where are you headed? Where are you where your heads?
I'm headed might be a dangerous danger to yourselves and the people around me. I'm headed to the fucking i'm headed to
Fucking the end to fight the ender dragon in minecraft
I'm i'm where i've got my i got my ender pearls. You don't understand and uh, you haven't been playing minecraft
You've been in a coma. No, I think that's not you're actually nate wake up mate
No, they added they added the dragon and the end and the withers and and these are new these are these are all things
They didn't exist before but now they've been here for years
And i'm playing minecraft. Okay. All right
Um boy, oh fucking boy. Oh, yeah, anyway, I did see that all the kids all the the kids
What are they like 40 now? Oh, wow
No, they're like all right. They're like 100 now. God. They're so old. God. They're like 30. They're like 28
Can you believe that like luna lovegood the actress is like a grandma now?
feel old yet um
She I saw I saw that um
I saw daniel radcliffe's response and I have seen pictures of emma watson saying trans rights stuff before I didn't see um
Um rippet grin. I didn't see rippet grin's response, but that's really funny that all three do dude. Everybody fucking hates her
Everybody fucking hates her except for like weird except for like weirdos like glinner and
and carons
like a couple of like
It's like the same it's like the same like older white women that you might see like on twitter
Like responding to you know blue wave democrats who respond
Who respond to trump tweets tweets by saying like by spelling his name lowercase t uppercase r
lowercase urmp
Or whatever or urmp
There's just like a there's just like a certain
Subset there's just a certain subset of a human female
It's it's just like the older you get the the the progression points the progressiveness points
The the progressiveness points you they have a half life and the older you get the less powerful and the less of them you have
You can only put them into so many things these people
They've gotten to the point where like feminism is good and like maybe gay marriage is good and things like that
Trans excuse me. That's a little too far. They don't have any more. I don't have any profession points
They don't have any more points to allocate, you know, they're their supply is dwindling as we speak
Pretty soon. They're gonna have to choose between like gay rights and feminism like they're gonna have to lose one or the other
They just don't don't have the stamina juice to sustain both
You know it's like flexing a muscle
Believing in rights is like flexing a muscle
You can't do it indefinitely
Yeah, it's like
To some extent it's understandable
But thank god grandma does not have a twitter account
Well, they do now, you know, that's who these people are
They're going to they're like getting to the age where they will be grandmas like like
You know the the the whole thing with like, oh
Grandparents they occasionally say the n-word and something like a little
A little bit of a oh, that's a that's a little bit of a racism there
Grandma grandma a little bit of a you know of the times remark
Um, but they say it in at like Christmas and Thanksgiving and like family gatherings
They say it in their own home. You never see him
Um, unless you do and even then you only see him a really big only see him at Christmas and Thanksgiving
And everyone agrees we don't talk about it when grandma says the n-word
We're just gonna keep going. We're just gonna keep barreling on through to the other side
And it's just imagine if all the grandmas and grandpas had
Twitter accounts and were engaging in all of these conversations along with everyone else
They do and the grandpas all have pictures of their dogs or themselves wearing sunglasses glasses or the american flag
I guess they do it's just not as many grandmas all have themselves
Wearing masks or I think I think the thing to do is to do a facebook and change twitter into like the young version of twitter
Which is better and let the old people take twitter and ruin it like they did with facebook
I mean facebook is fine. I guess it's just sort of we can't just we can't just keep losing ground
We can't just keep surrendering more and more territory. We have to take a stand
Now we got we got to innovate like the the whole idea of innovation is to make sure old people don't know
What the fuck is going on so we can sneakily just like plot their like uh mass genocide
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, it's tossing around the g word are we now that's the kind of thing that gets your channel banned from youtube
Oh, no youtube. I'm so sorry. I won't kill you. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry
Please let us let us have our channel back. Mr. YouTube man. Mr.
Susan Wojcicki. Mr. Mr. Man. Wojcicki
Oh, sorry. I don't believe that I don't believe that that autogynophilic men
Masculating as women should be invading women natal women spaces
Um lamal
That's what that's what you sound like twitter
Die, it's like it's like I don't want old people to die. I just know that I don't like anything they have to say
That's right. That's right. It's it's just an unfortunate like you're too old to pay attention to what is happening
And even if you did you would have really stupid old-fashioned takes because you're setting your ways because you're old
And that's just how it is. That's what human life is if you didn't want to die
You shouldn't have let yourself get old enough to start being wrong. I'm sorry. That's just the way these things work
It's it's the way of the world the the the master of the universe
Uh laws of the universe. Hey, yeah, if you
Uh, don't if you if you feel like speculating
I'm I'm thinking because we don't know if it was the black lives matter charity stream
That got us flag seems plausible, but we we can't we can't know for sure
Did we say
Did we do you think?
honestly
There was anything we said on there that was like
a a what what were the
the terms again
Encouraging illegal activities or inciting users to violate youtube's guidelines
I mean encouraging illegal illegal activities as in like encouraging rioting. I guess
We like looting we saying looting is based if it's against war not like things like that
I just feel like that's not that spicy a take and I've and I know that other I've seen other youtubers
put out videos
Who are in support of blm and who think that the rioting is who are who support that?
Right because they think it all like it's all you know riot is the voice of the unheard or whatever, right?
Like is the is is that it do you have to be just like like no riot is ever legitimate?
Is that the is that the implication here if if that's what it is?
I mean, I mean, I guess it would probably either be that we were not 100 critical of the rioting or
Like joking about killing cops
Now I now I I looked at the terms of service. Okay. This is this says encouraging illegal activities
or inciting users to violate the youtube's guidelines, so
It doesn't so it doesn't imply I
Mean it's sort of
I mean it does say that we we violated the terms of service
But the way that we did that was by encouraging an illegal activity or inciting users to violate guidelines and like
So that's really weird. That's like very weird phrasing and
Uh, uh, I looked at the guidelines and the guidelines do include like you're not allowed
You're like you you're not allowed to like say certain things about groups of people
You're not allowed to like compare a group of people to like animals. You're not allowed to call them subhuman
which
I guess you could maybe argue that we did like if we if we called if we called cops pigs
Or whatever or something or said like cops or bastards
Maybe but like the groups that you are not allowed to say that it it doesn't say a job
It does say that like based on a certain cast whatever that means arc is being a cop being a member of the cop cast
Um, I don't know
So if you construed it that way, maybe you could say that but like the wording of those of those words in there are clearly
Designed that it's it's like meant to like what it's meant to prevent is like racist speech
Like you know saying some saying nasty shit about like black people right not about fucking cops, right?
So if that were what did it it would obviously have been like taken out of the spirit of what the rule was meant to do
um
I I
I guess I mean, I think the most likely thing if it was a report on that stream is that
somebody said that we said um
Something that there was maybe a joke
Yeah, um, but it you know and then the youtube bought what skimmed through it
Found the words and said oh, they did say that and obviously doesn't realize that jokes exist
and so
maybe report plus like
Uh, just grabbing the the the transcript led to that
but
I mean
I don't know. I don't really want to assume that that's exactly what's happening. I I'm trying not to I'm trying not to jump to any conclusions
Um, I just you know, we both we both
Independently were like is that why is that what did it?
if I
I mean, I've seen people saying what do I see I've seen people saying
Uh, maybe it was a naughty edgy things. We've said that got flagged
Maybe it was you know, because like you're maybe it was like the fact that like mumki is banned and he's on certain
Uh, uh videos on our channel. I don't buy that. I don't I think that's his own channel back up
He's doing things. Yeah, that's that can't be it. I mean, I would say
I wouldn't say can't like obviously that shouldn't happen, but like
It I think it seems like a stretch, but it doesn't seem like 100 impossible that youtube would just be that stupid about it
Um, but it's probably not it. I think that one's a long shot. Um
I mean, we didn't get we didn't get banned
Or it didn't get banned when we up when we did the blm stream the charity stream
By the way, we fucking did a fucking charity fundraiser and we get fucking kicked off youtube
um
It wasn't that or it wasn't right when we uploaded it. It was after um, we the latest episode
Which I guess
Makes me think that it was something on the episode that went up and I don't remember what we talked about in that episode
Yeah, I can't remember exactly either. I mean, we have the mp3. We could go through it
I get a couple hours. Yeah, I mean I guess I don't want to even if we even if we like fight figure out exactly what it was
It doesn't mean the channel is going to come back any quicker
Yeah, even even if we even if we thought we could identify like oh that must be what it was. Oh clearly clearly
I don't think there will be a moment where it's like. Oh, I see. I see. This is exactly what we said
That was an unambiguous terms of service violation. There you go. Bam
Problem mystery solved
Uh, I don't yeah. No, it's not
What do we gain nothing?
Uh, right
so
Boy, I'm frustrated
I'm fucking frustrated about all
This all things. Yeah
Yeah, but you know what's good
Is that it looks like tom has made a lot of progress getting ready to start shipping out backer rewards
That's that is good. I like seeing those piles of merch. That's that's pretty cool. Um
You know, um
How's your how's things on your end? How's the many list of ben saint things that has to come out?
um
You know, I was um
Well, I think I mentioned last week that nexus did complete his vaporette and I have it. Oh, and I was gonna like
I was gonna like tweet about him. So I was gonna make a tweet and like hey guys
Here's another like like artist highlight for a guest artist. Yeah, you should do that
I should do that, but now everything's fucking falling apart. Oh, I can't I can't
Possibly now. It's just not the time
It's just one tweet. No, no, no, no, I have to keep my eyes on the prize. Um, no, but I will do that at some point
Um, kazzie says hers is almost done
Actually, she messaged me just like right before the the stream started or this podcast started to say like it's almost done
Lamal, which is cool
Um
Jade said she was gonna she was gonna maybe get it done this week
But I think she's like at camp or god she's I forget she told me she was going somewhere for a little while
So I guess she's must be up. It's fine. It's fine. It's fine. It's fine
And then I'm just curious about like why to go somewhere during the pandemic
She I I don't remember
Um, I probably shouldn't like I probably shouldn't like read out what she said
She said she was going somewhere
And was gonna try and have it done before she left which was the end of last week
But the week has ended and it didn't work
But whatever so kazzie said she's almost done
So if she ends finish this soon, that'll be four out of six and then munchie says he is working on it
He says he's working on it every day
Which okay, uh, I don't know how close he is
Uh, how many pages are all these guys doing how many I don't remember how many yours was like what like six pages five
Something like that. Um, I mean nexus says is longer than that
Um
Munchies is shorter. Well, no, maybe it's similar. I don't know
Uh, I don't I don't I don't actually know how many pages it. Um, I think that
jades was was maybe a little longer than yours and kazzie's was also
longer, they're a little longer than
They're a little longer than like the two page ones from uh last time
So, I mean they're a little more substantial. It's good. The book is gonna be like half vaporette content
I think or pretty close to it
Um, so, you know, I mean they're doing they're doing work
Um, uh, how about the rfck pins? So, oh, oh, oh, you know, I have um
God
Really frustrating
So the pins I have um, I I actually have samples of
Six of them. I think I have the potrin. I have the map. I have
Endless not endless war. I have the slime corp. I have the slime heart. I have the lord of ghosts
And I'm missing one. I don't know. Uh, I have samples of those here right now and they are producing
I just told them to produce samples of the last like 18
Uh model so they are making samples of of a bunch more right now. They're gonna send them to me
It's gonna be pretty good. I will make like last minute color adjustments when I see how they look in person
Um, so the pins coming along really good
The patches the the the other company I found that makes patches
The woman I'm talking to is so fucking frustrating. She's so useless. I hate her
Like she made the sample pin the patches and like they looked pretty good
I had a couple of like things and I was like, hey, could you change this could you change this?
But they look really good. I was really happy with them
And she's so difficult like I make like really simple requests. I'm like, hey
What colors did you use?
And like she will take like two days to get back to me or until answer with like something unrelated and I'll be like
I just want to know what color please tell me what colors you use and I'll I'll I'll I'll have to ask multiple times
Or like, okay, can I see a picture of what the threads look like so I can compare colors and like
Again, like it's like a 50 50 chance whether she will actually like answer the question
I'm asking or like do the thing that I want her to do to help me make this fucking order
She's so dumb or like doesn't understand English or
Just like lazy and doesn't want to like it's I don't know what the problem is like I cannot tell
but she's so
awful and yet I have to fucking deal with her because
The pet that I've already paid for the patches to be made. They've already designed them. I like we're doing this
It's just like I literally just have to pick out
The only thing I have to do before they make another round of the of the things is like I just ask show me the colors
Please very I'm very polite. I'm very polite when to deal with her
Just said just please show me what the colors look like so I can pick which ones and she's like, okay
That was like three days ago
I hate her I fucking hate her Jesus christ
um
So that's what's going on with that
I went on fiverr and I paid somebody
to
Make a vector out of the slime coin
coin design
um
It looks pretty good
I spent a while like fucking around with it after I don't know
It's like
Little parts of it are like a little bit off-center and I feel like it's small enough that it wouldn't matter if I if I had it made
Right now. I don't think anyone would notice but I can notice that like the border is like not entirely uniform and thickness
But it's like really it'd be really hard. I'd have to like take move everything around in relation to each other
To get it and it's like, why?
Why couldn't you have just
Why couldn't you have just done it 100 percent?
Why couldn't you have just done it perfectly? Probably because she was some girl from pakistan and I paid her like $20
um
but still
Yeah, I guess you get what you pay for
And now I'm probably gonna have to like if I'm if I'm to be satisfied with the final product
I'm going to have to spend any turn of you fucking around with infinite tiny little
Little little like nodes and points in fucking inkscape get that friggin vector exactly how I want it
Um, what else am I fucking doing? What am I talking about after?
Talking about stuff. Oh the um your other lecture
Oh
Oh, that was right
the other thing
Actually, god, I really wish the thing with a channel didn't happen
Because I had just look it's fine. I'll I'll continue. I'll continue as as I was I had just
Finally kicked myself in the ass enough to get back to like
Doing the slime and punishment finale. I had finished the story. I had finished laying out the story board
All right
Like to to
Which was a necessary step in doing it which I hadn't completed yet. I had just kind of done little bits and pieces here
I have the story board laid out now
And I and I have started making assets for it again. I haven't started putting shots together again. I need assets. I'm making assets
and
so
I'm doing that partially because I am not going to release the chris chan 102
until
Slime and punishment finale is out. So oh, yeah
So me getting that done is like a prerequisite to me getting the slime and punishment or the the the
The the thing out the the lecture itself is like mostly edited. There's some stuff I need to add to it, but it's like
More mostly it's cut together
Not a hundred percent and like
There were some things I there were some things I wanted to do with it a little bit above and beyond
um just like
You know the pretty the pretty bare bones editing that I did with the um
With the other one, uh, so, you know, it's it's
That's gonna happen after the pen the finale which I was which I would have been working on
A lot more in the past day if I hadn't if this fucking news about the channel had not come to light and and
Divided my attention pretty heavily, but it's okay
It's fine
I'll get back to it. Damn. So you go um like a whole bunch of irons in that fire
Dude, I have huge amount. I keep thinking about I keep thinking about how many fucking irons I got and how they all
distract me from one another and I'm
Just so fucking bad
I'm just so fucking it's so fucking dumb. I'm I'm I've I've I've destroyed my my life by by not not having everything
Done the fact that there are things that I haven't finished the
I won't go through the list. I've gone through the list a bunch of times in various places. I just I just
I hate it. I hate that there are things that I started that aren't done
It's so fucking like draining it cause it saps my energy constantly
um
The the the the
I will I will receive a passive buff
I'll receive a passive buff to my life as soon as the slime and punishment finale is done because it'll be one more thing
That I can remove from my thought process that room that drains my mental stamina constantly
Knowing that it's that it's that the the promise was made that it would be done and I haven't delivered yet
Um, I will do my IQ will just raise by 10 points spontaneously
Promise if you think I'm stupid. I'm not that's why I I have
That's the reason don't it's not my fault
It's it definitely sucks to have a bunch of things hanging over your head. I mean
That's why I've made a
I guess not a habit, but I've like made um
who?
I me. Oh, I me. I have made a habit of of like cutting projects off
Like it's difficult to just do one thing like you're always gonna have
Other ideas distracting you while you're working on one thing. Yeah, um, which is why for the past well this year is like
uh, just like figuring out how to
Make myself do one thing so that it's done
Lord of ghosts was that um pretty pretty successful. Um, but
uh
it's
It's oh, I've just realized I'm about to talk about art problems. Gary hack it. Fuck you. I don't like you
You piece of shit you little choke for anyone wondering Gary hack it commented
You may I
commented on like why
Like can't wait. It was what was it like can't wait till gibb starts talking about he can't focus on his art or whatever
And I was like, why is this about him? Why why is this not about me? This is like describes me
This would be more appropriate to be said about me. I don't get it. Um, but it was funny
Yeah
Well, so I was thinking oh, I shouldn't talk about that next time but uh, you forced my handband now. I'm talking about that's fine
That's good
but yeah, I was
I was having because like with a lot of ghosts I had um
Done the sketching and dialogue well before I was drawing it and inking it finishing the pages and releasing them
So what the work was was entirely just sort of like workhorse work. I didn't need to think I just needed to do it
Yeah, so solving solving that problem was quite easy really
It's just a matter of focusing your uh, your your arm your your energy
But you don't need to I have something to say about and so you see
Yeah, did you find did you find it easier to work on like after the sketch was done?
And you just had to go in and do the mindless work of like inking it basically shading it. Yes
I
Okay, when yeah when I did the when I did the vapors or vapors one and two I sketched
And then I inked right
And and I did it like like I sketched it all out first and then I went back and inked it
and I
hated that
Because the inking was like so mindless. It was really boring
And I got like no satisfaction. I got very little satisfaction from it like every time every time I finished inking a page
It was like I hadn't really made anything. I had just done like some mindless busy work
Just some shit that's like required of me to you know to make this thing technically done
Even though like in my mind it had already been done before
um
But I say that I say that but then with like vapors three and champion chapter one
I
I didn't do that. I didn't pre-sketch it. I sketched and then inked each page eventually
Which like broke up the like more satisfying creative work of like laying out the page and like sketching the page and like and doing all that
But like it also it also it was harder. It was less
It was more satisfying work to do that, but it's also way harder. So
You know the end result is that both went very slowly and I suck
Lamal
lol
It's it's just sort of lol. I mean for me that the sketches were very basic very bare bones
And to to ink them makes them appear real and I'm like wow. I'm actually good at drawing. I guess, you know
um, so it was like more of
Appealing to look at once it was inked and I was like the after that shading it was just sort of like
I don't know fill tool gray here and here. I don't know if I can
um, you know
Yeah, my my my sketches for like those when I've done sketches like that sketch the page out first
Mine are pretty basic, too
But I I feel I still feel like that's when I try like I've already when I've done the sketch
Unless it's like
Unless I've left a lot of shit out like I've already translated
The the idea has already come out of my brain and onto the page like there it is
Like to my eye like it's there already
And I know that like it's not done, but like I feel like
I don't know that's the like yeah, yeah, I get that that feeling when I'm
Uh putting dialogue in like I've already written it in like a in a screenplay way and now I've
Putting deciding where to put the switch bubble in the panel
And I'm like and then you know, I sketch it like
When I'm when I'm sketching I just sort of scribble the words in so that I can see like roughly how much space it would need
To write all of those words. I I forget if we've talked about this before do you do you like write out a script before you start sketching?
Um for a lot of ghosts, which is really the only one I've done
Any sort of planning on?
Yes, I wrote an entire screenplay of the dialogue when it came down to doing this the page layout
I based it off of those like the the things that the conversation requires happen
Yeah, uh, but when it came to actually typing it up
I would tweak a few things if I felt like the delivery was sort of weird and not cool enough or just sort of
Wording could have been improved, but the the the focus of each speech bubble stayed the same
I
I have I have never done I have never done like a like a script treatment before
I will have like um
Well, I mean, I guess I like I wrote out the scripts for the vaporettes that the guest artists then you and the other guest artists
Then like I guess followed or whatever for the actual
drawing
Mine my comics. I've never done a script treatment before before drawing. I will have like
I might have the most I might have is like
notes
Even then I don't really do notes because like I know what the story is like if it's a if it like
If it's a short story and I've never really drawn like a
A protracted comic with like a really like long well for champion
I did have notes about like like what like but like whatever
um
For the other things I don't usually have notes or anything about what it is. I'll just know what the story is
I know like what the what the basic beats are and I'll have like scenes in my head
And I'll just and I'll just like I'll just draw it out
And like I'll have an idea like if there's going to be dialogue in a moment
And then like I won't know what it's going to be, but I'll draw it
I'll just think of like, okay
I guess they'll have to do this and I guess he or she will say something
And I'll know like the idea that they want to say but not exactly what they're saying
I'll draw it out
I'll like include their mouth being open leave space for a bubble and then I'll like it'll be done and I'll go back in and be like
Okay, I know the idea. She's expressing. How exactly do I word it? Like how exactly would she say it?
Let me figure out the exact words. Um, I guess it's like that. No, that's stupid. No, that's stupid
That okay done cringe move on don't think about it anymore
I mean the way I was thinking when I did this screenplay it was like
um
Screenplay as in like it includes like direction like character moves here grabs thing throws thing
Yeah, um, we see a shot of this we pan over like like as if it was a film
um
So I can like base the panel layout off of that
Like I know what needs to be shown as well as who needs to be saying what
Um, but when I write a dialogue scene
If it like ends in a punchline, I'm thinking in my head
like I have a some sort of a vision of
What the panel layout needs to look like in order to deliver this punchline or if it's a really cool thing like it zooms up
Like a close up of their mouth and they say fuck you like
Yeah, some sort of some sort of thing like that like silhouetted against an explosion
Um, and they say a one-liner like I I in like in my head. I imagine
Visually what that speech that that thing they say would be said against but I don't need to sketch it
When it comes to sketching I sometimes find that I'm not good enough at drawing to sketch the cool thing
So I have to like come up with something else
I yeah, sure. Yeah, sure. Sure. I've been there
Um, do you ever when you're when you're like writing out a script when you're coming up with the story?
Do you like see it?
Does it appear how to how does it how does it appear to you in your mind when you're like conceiving it when it's
The form it takes for me is generally a
an image or like a sequence of images
and then
I'll be like, okay
That'll happen that image happens that image happens
that image happens
and then the actual process of making the comic is like
just kind of
Making it up as I go along of like
thinking like
All right, so to get so to get to get the characters into the situation where that first image happens
Like what would they have to do? Okay?
I guess they do this and this and this and this and this and this and this and okay there and then then it happens done
Okay, and then to get to the next one. It's like, okay
Well, I guess they got to do this and this and say that and this and do this and this and this and then okay there
There it is there. It happens again, right? Yeah, it's it's like thinking in keyframes or key scenes
Like you know the the big moments that you want to explain and they need to be set up. So
Yeah, or like going from point a to point b
Uh, they need to like if they're in one location
You can just cut to another location
But sometimes you want to have a few panels to buffer it if if it needs like
You know, you'll you'll get a feel for how it needs to to look while you're sketching
Yeah, um, but a lot of the time if I have two cool moments and in between them
I'm not exactly sure how they get to the other cool moment
Um, I just know that they need to expose it something before the next action scene
I sometimes leave the sketch a little too loose and I find that that is sure
That's that's um, that's caught me in a few places, right? I've ended up having to like
um
Come up with something while I'm lining it rather than sketching it which is difficult like a background
Not not really just a background
I mean sometimes a background because I'm just like it's buildings. I don't fucking know. Yeah, but um
the
like
A transitional phase from one
Area to another. I'm not sure
exactly some type like
Yeah
Like it's just it's difficult. It's difficult trying to like because you don't imagine in your mind
The the mundane panels that don't really
Leave much of an impact. You always think of the coolest moments. Yeah
I I think that sometimes
sometimes
Making a story like that is just a matter of finding any
excuse just to move the story to towards where you want to go something like and sometimes
Sometimes it's okay
I know I've done it to just be like
Whatever just have someone say something just justify it in any way. It doesn't matter. It doesn't matter if it's bullshit
We just got to get we just got to get this
Wherever we're going as fast as possible make it as can make it as uh as efficient as possible
Even and just just get it there
Just stop drawing you don't like draw make it so you have to draw as few panels as possible
That is
I mean it didn't it didn't end up being
Uh a low amount of panels. No, but like chapter two of lord of ghosts where he's like traveling from
You know being in the ocean to getting to the you know endless mud and all that. Yeah, um
I knew that cuz rck is like the grand canyon of slime
It means he would need to go through that slime sea and then end up somewhere else on the other side of the grand canyon and from there
Uh, he needs to travel across the ocean because in my mind it was just like it's just like the earth
It's just real life. It's just is exactly the same as the earth, but like with weird shit in it
so, um, I knew that he needed to go from
Somewhere in the grand canyon to the
Uh east coast of america and then cross the ocean. Yes
Which is why I had the the the cow town
And then the the sea train, but like in those locations. I didn't really have anything for lord of ghosts to do
I just so uh, let's put a cowboy in here. They they say something like we don't like
Monsters around here and they the fucking shoot him. It's like, oh my god. I'm betting shut out and he runs like and it's just a
It's an excuse for a little comedy, but I also need to explain
In my head
It needs to be explained how he gets from one side of the slime sea to another side of the planet
I I really think that a lot of
I think it's underrated how much of like successful
storytelling or making any kind of narrative
content
is about
Like how little can I get away with showing without losing it without losing anything as I like progress the action from a to b
Uh, I think that's just good. It's just good storytelling to cut out craft and it makes it easier too
And it makes you able to to like tell more of the story you're trying to tell
The more efficiently you can do you can you can move the action along
The best thing to do is to have like the world
Because people love building worlds you build the world as
Completely as you possibly can you think of the absolute history of every location if you really feel like going in that that in depth
So such that when you come to deciding what to show from that world
You don't need to think of you don't need to make shit up. Everything's already there. You just need to show it
Yeah, you know you've built a world now just film what's happening in it and the the thing you're showing
is like
You know, um
It can be very brief. You don't need to explain what's going on in the world
You can leave it to people's imaginations to fill in but if you know
Then it's easier for you to structure everything. Mm-hmm. Yeah
if um
I'm uh, uh, if you've
Yeah, I get if you've got if you've got a really fleshed out idea of the world then like that can kind of
I don't know. I guess that can answer questions like if you're thinking like hmm. What happens between here and there? Well
I know this exists
Maybe that that's what happens. Yeah
maybe that's it
Because it's you you can tell sometimes where things are just
Made up out of nothing. They come out of the of the author's ass. They're just like, uh, then this happens
Yeah, and the reason the reason you can tell is that because is there was no
There's nothing possible that could have indicated that this was the case
You know, like it's it's a it's a common thing in one piece where like
um, it's it's not so much that odour
Deliberately puts things in one piece knowing that he will use them later
But he knows so much about the world he's created that he can pick and choose lots of things that he's already shown
Like as mundane objects in the background to become things that are relevant later and then people look back and they're like, oh my god
I think it's a rich tapestry. You know, I think that you know, there's like there's the architect and the gardener, right?
You know what I mean?
Oh, yeah, that's the I feel like king georgia or a martin conversation
Uh, yeah, I
I guess so there was a that's where I heard it on youtube. I I haven't yeah, maybe
I think I might have heard the two of them compared like that some at some point
I feel like odour does the gardener thing where like he will come up with some like weird device
To just like enable whatever he wants to have happen happen
Like the dials or whatever in in in a cloud
zone
My favorite sonic the hedgehog level skypea and and then
Oh, yeah, if he want if he like he'll just come up with that because it enables like, you know
Like usop to do all these weird combat things and like uh, uh, you know
Is it excuse for like long distance communication in a place without
No, no, they have to end in mushy. That's not right. Whatever it enables all these weird things to happen
He'll have to just have this idea for like what if these things did have these weird properties like that would be cool
Um, and then he'll just kind of go with it
Uh, like and that'll be and and if he wants he can he'll bring them back later
Like cuz dial cuz dials are like a pretty a pretty like, um
Versatile concept and like I guess because of that he'll just he can just bring them back and like make them
Show up later like maybe later usop puts them in his fucking slingshot or whatever they do they do a thing
Uh, I feel I feel like he's doing the gardening thing there where he's just he's just he is just kind of making shit up as he goes along
But then he'll like he's he's he's he's grown
He's grown so many fruits and veggies in his garden
That he can then like has a big stockpile of them too
Like he can take any of those seeds you see to continue the metaphor that he's already cultivated and replant them for next year's harvest
I'm getting hungry
Yeah, it's it's it's beneficial for him as well because it's like one piece is just
Anything you could think of there's an island about it. Yeah, there's a there's everything can exist
That's kind of what I want to do is just to have like
Everything that I could think of that's really cool is all in the same universe. There's all
They can all interact punk will meet everyone. It's all in c197, dude
It's all it's all in c197 the dimensional marriage is coming. Yeah
Fuck yeah, um
Anyway, what I was yeah, what I was talking about
um with regards to working
uh was
That
With the sketches a lot of ghosts. Uh, it was easy to figure out how to get myself out a little bit
And I haven't really heard like half of what you've been saying. Could you start over my robot?
For me. Sorry viewers. My I don't know if it was your connection or my headphones, but yeah, I missed a lot of that
sorry
The way to solve the problem of working on things without needing to think is just minimize distraction
Lower your expected dopamine level so that you're not constantly craving a certain amount of entertainment every day and
And you know, you can what you can barrel through and it's quite easy
But when I'm doing this tezuka manga thing. Yeah, um, it is it is a different
Feeling of work. You can't sit down at a nine to five and come up with ideas
It doesn't really exactly work the same way. You can get yourself in a good situation
but coming up with creative ideas like
So that it's it's difficult and it's a different process and I need to figure out how to
best
Make a situation where I can
Like thrive creatively
Have you so that I can have that as my creative way to do things and then my other way that I've already figured out as the
The production way you've you've seen you've seen that John Cleese lecture right about creativity. I have yeah, yeah
I need to rewatch it because I keep forgetting
I know that there's like the open and closed state the playful mind and the and the analytical mind or whatever he says
But I forget how to best get into the playful mind
Thing because I've tried like, uh, maybe if I just drink some alcohol that'll
No, no
Loosen my inhibitions just a little bit because and then once once my inhibitions are loosened
I'm not going to worry so much about the things I do. So I would just create right
Stuff and even if it's shit, I'll do it in any way and then I can look at it later and decide what is good and bad
Like that's not the stupid idea. Very stupid. It didn't really work very stupid. It doesn't it doesn't work. I think I think not for me
I think as a as a concept like
Loose lowering your inhibitions is a good way to get into a playful mindset where you just do things
It doesn't even matter. Just do them. Yeah
However, you can get to that you talked in the money spenders podcast about how like you you get into that when you're like really tired
And I made it and I commented like hey me too. Yeah when I get really tired my inhibitions are lowered and sometimes I'll just like
Draw a thing or write a thing because I'm too stupid not to do it lamel
Yeah, it's like you've got to lobotomize yourself. You've got to become the stupidest motherfucker so that everything you do
um
It is well you you do everything rather you just do anything that comes to mind and then
After that you have a whole list a whole big
Like spread of things that you've come up with
90% of them are gonna suck
But at least you will be able to like see okay, that doesn't work. That doesn't work. That doesn't work
That doesn't work. That's has potential
Keep that and then you just do that over and over again until you have like a like a pile of like
You know, it's like a panning for gold
Get a whole lot of dirt and eventually you'll find a tiny little nugget. Yeah
Yeah, but you got it. You've got to move a whole lot of dirt before you can find those
That's exactly right. I like that analogy
So, yo, not sorry sorry not to distract and we don't have to harp on this
But did you see John Cleese's stupid ass shit on twitter?
It's speaking of John Cleese
John Cleese, I mean he did it in that stupid like centrist way
But he was basically like what he was basically anti tearing down statues
um
He was he's been saying like uh the romans practice slavery the greeks practice slavery
Why don't we tear down statues of greeks and romans?
Like that's not fucking smooth as shit
um
Yeah, that's that's uh, that's a take that is
Uninformed that sucks ass dude very disappointing coming from a cool dude
A pretty overall I thought I think a pretty cool dude
Like like johnny boy honestly
I I yeah, it's I mean it's not a major
Infraction, it's not it's not a major infraction, but it's very cringe and I just I expected better of him, you know
Yeah, he does have old man brain now. He does but you know, he mean he's pretty fucking old in that lecture
Isn't like in that lecture that that that thing he says like I'm very old and I'll soon be dead
And that's like fucking 15 years old or maybe maybe not that old, but I think it's pretty old
like yeah, jeez
Funny funny stuff
Oh, no mortality help. Oh god, I'm afraid
Um gotta immortalize yourself in your creations real quick. Uh, I guess I guess in the absence of any better options
I better get on that
Uh
I have gotten to a point where um the oh am I a robot again for you for like a
Second you were but you're fine now. Yeah, like I saw the thing go red. Um
I have gotten to a point where I have a full outline of the comic
um, and I want to
to go over it
And maybe I don't know ask people what they think I might ask you what you think
um, it's it's fine. It's just sort of like
A lot of the a lot of what's cool about it is coming through my head and I'm aware of the
An outline doesn't really explain enough for a for a person to really get
What's going on you need to expand on each of the points and explain it in depth and at some point
You may you might end up writing a book
So like that's the point where you you don't do that and you instead start sketching because that's not what you're doing
But yeah, I've gotten to a point where I think I have something that is you know, it's doable
Oh for for tezuka you're talking about tezuka
The yeah, the okay, right. Yeah
Clarissa gunsmoke
I don't know whether gunsmoke is a good last name, but that's the the first name I came up with and I can't think of anything
Isn't gunsmoke
And this is not to say that no it's not a good name, but gunsmoke is the name of a show right like an old tv show
Maybe uh, yeah, I actually think it is. Yeah
Uh, I'm not familiar, but I've heard the name but like that's fine
I think clister gunsmoke is perfectly perfectly good name. It's very evocative
I I didn't uh
I don't know. I you probably don't want to give any spoilers
Otherwise, I would ask like give us some tidbits. What's the story about does she fuck?
No, no does she fuck though. No, she doesn't fuck just because she's a woman doesn't know she's a sex object
Does just does clarissa would you describe clarissa gunsmoke as having a big old mommy milkers?
No, no damn. All right. Well, I will be
I mean, she may be a cowgirl, but that's not that's not what it means consider yourself to have lost a fan today
Um, no, don't worry pumps doing that now. Oh, yeah, that's true. That's true
Oh, here's here's here's like some funny fucking
Uh inside of scoop. Let me find let me go to my only fans page
Oh, right
Uh, what was it?
Oh, yeah, pumps bra size. You want you want to learn pumps bra size cannon? I do I do
Uh 24 g 24 g
That sounds it's we that sounds that's a really small number in a really big letter
Lamal, yeah
The the the letter is like the
The the uh the amount difference between like around the the torso. Yeah, and then the bust. Yeah
And it's 24 because she's very small. She's like a tiny I based it basic
Like a little bit off of the the life size punk plushie that I have
Like this is almost like a cannon punk
I sized her up a bit and I figured it out
I spent a few days because it's really confusing
Looking at bra sizes because that's just what I'd like to do. Okay. There's nothing wrong with that. That's right. That's right
I'm I googled it. I googled a 24 g
And I know it does not exist. It does not exist
Unfortunately, everything starts at 30 or 32
Hmm
Let's see. Let's see. Let's see a 32 g
Um
No, that doesn't look right
Okay, I don't I don't think it exists. I don't think that I'm not sure that exists either lamal disappointing
Um, well, maybe oh boy. Oh boy. All right. Hey viewer. Hey, whoa. Hey shut up. Hey shut up a minute
Okay, cool
sick
Yeah, check out her only fans
Check out punk solo fans. There's uh, there's how much how much does it cost to be a to be an only fan of punk?
Um, if you go to the only fans it is five bucks a month
Or you can go to my patreon at patreon.com slash give and take to get it for also five
Dollars, right? That's why I've seen it five dollars per month. That's why I've
Wait, no, wait. No, that's not why I've seen it because I don't patient you for five patient you for one dollar
Yeah, you gotta up you gotta up for five
Five also gets you access to like sketches. I'm thinking of also doing like
The screenplay I have yo I'll patron you for five dollars and you patron me for five dollars
And then we'll both then we'll have added ten dollars a month the global economy
True
That's just true. Yeah, it is it is true. That's how money works
um
Facts, what were you saying?
Uh, I forget I think so. Oh, yeah closer. You are asking me about Clarissa. Um, right the gist is
The she has a gun
And she's a cowgirl and she rides into town
And something happens with the gun and Clarissa in the town
That's as much as I'm willing to give at the moment. There's obviously more to it
But I want to spoil
Until I feel like it's it's more robust and I can give like a cooler synopsis that is less
Like it has more to it, but also it doesn't reveal anything
Dude, that's pretty based
That's pretty based. All right. I'm excited
You think you think I'll have it done on time
Um
Yeah, I mean I've given myself till the end of june to get sketching done
Uh, which means I got like two weeks and a yeah, uh, and then uh
Depending on how many pages it's gonna be like pretty
Like the maximum I can do is 55. I probably won't go that far, but I might it depends
So I really need to to figure out at first
I need to
Do like extremely rough sketch like panel layout like stick figures
No information at all just so I can see how many pages it's gonna take up if I do it. Um, you know, just ballpark it
Um, if it's extremely low
Then I have room to expand things that maybe I rush
Like if I if I'm being conservative when I start sketching and I realize that it's only like 20 pages
I can be I can go over it again be more liberal be
Like have more space. Maybe one of the pages can be like a big one panel person shot
um
Something like that or like a double page berserk spread sort of thing
But if it's like like 60 70 80 pages, I need to cut it down and that's that's the the next step for me
Yeah, to figure out how much uh, I can work with
Yeah, I was I was gonna ask you so you don't know how long it's gonna be you don't have like a
Do you have like a ballpark?
Goal I I don't really I mean I don't have enough experience yet
With how this the amount of words or the amount of story translates into screenplay and then sketch will it be in color?
so
Be in color. Yeah, will it be in color?
The the the contest says it has to be in black and white. Oh, but I could easily make a color version later
Um, I kind of want it to be in color because her hair is is red. Yeah, that's the cool thing
She's got she has red fiery red hair like like
Completely red not even a little bit of orange
uh
dude
Let me complain about those pin the pins. Um
They I gave them the the pixelated uh, uh red man design
And they kept the pixelation, but they smoothed out the outer like corner or the outer edge of it
So it's like a a like round, you know over at like egg shape
Uh smooth on the outside and crunchy on the inside has the pixelated jagged edges and I was like, no, no
You must fix this. This is unacceptable
It needs it needs to be it needs to be painful to the touch
And uh, she said we're on it. We're on it, sir
Um, or at least they said that uh, yeah, I think they'll they'll fuck they'll fucking do it
They'll fucking do it. I'm paying money. I had to pay I had to pay $900
I had to pay $900 to get them the last like 18. Um, um
Uh, the last 18 pins like the molds created and a sample produced and then them shipped
It was like 950 or 60 bucks to get all that so fuck. Yeah, so that's fine
That's fine. But then the actual production of the thing will be like as one penny. Uh, it'll be
The the the place I found that I ended up going with is like, I think it's like five cents per
One made and we're gonna end up making like several thousand of them. So
You know, you know, whatever
Uh, it's not it's not that bad. Well, because we went with the chinese
A producer worse will will will end up turning a profit, which we did not expect to when we were when we originally planned it out and
Planned to go with the uk-based, uh, manufacturer
Um epic it's it is it's it's pretty epic. Um, fuck. Oh, no, I was gonna say
What was I gonna say? What was I gonna say? I had I just something popped into my head. Oh
Oh about the um
So about the the black lives matter charity stream, which may be destroyed our the the procrastinators channel
I don't know. Who knows who knows? Um, I did I guess I'm gonna have to wait until like
Channel ad revenue pays out for that assuming we even get it at all now
But like because I didn't want to wait. I already like paid out
Like people donated including like munchy
I've donated 50 and I said that I would pledge 50 and all and everyone else's pledges combined were like 702 dollars
So I went and just like pledged I went and like donated 752 dollars just out of my own money
Uh, uh, just like to before like, you know waiting to like hopefully get that paid out from the channel and get Nate to send it to me
I sure hope we're still getting it. Um, I mean I said I think we should I think we should because
We should because the the google account is not destroyed
Like the google account that's linked to the adsense account still exists
So I don't see why that money would not come through
Um, if it doesn't I guess I'm just personally out
750 but don't worry everyone your donations went through they might have and they I don't know
Hopefully they don't just come out of my pocket lemal. That would suck really hard
Um, but we'll see they've been they've been donated already lemal
Uh
That's a that's a nightmare potential. Um
Yeah a little uh, it's fine. Uh, it's okay. It's it's okay. I'm okay with whatever happens
Um
Well, well, um, shall we go to voicemail? I guess we could go to voicemails. I I feel was there one last thing
Is there any last thing that I wanted?
That I wanted to bring up before we go. You know what if I think of anything. I'll just fucking interrupts. Yeah, let's go to voicemails
Okay
So I've got one two three four five
There's there's five there's six, but one was for digi and digi's not here. Oh, so bummer, uh
Let the meat play
Let the meat cake
Uh, this is I think chad thunder cock. Nice. I remember what he was what he said, but he
Remakes are based and the original demon souls looked terrible. Um
That was that it was about the the the the demon souls remake
I mean, it was mostly directed to nate who apparently didn't like the
The the look of of the demon souls remake. I thought it looked pretty cool
Um, I haven't looked too much. I saw I saw matthew matosis saying
That he thought that like
He didn't seem to be a fan of the look of the new one
I don't know. I haven't seen it. I haven't looked into it. I
Super do not care. I I just think that this voicemail is a little dumb idiot because
Okay
For saying that the original demon souls looks like shit or looks bad
No
No, that's all I gotta say. No. No. No. No, it looks it looks great matthew matosis was saying everything everything old looks not
You you know matthew matosis was saying something about like
Okay, I know there's like the jail part
And there's a part that's a jail with the mind flayers
And he was saying that like the remake seems to be a lot of like
Have a lot of like extra detail in it
And he said that like it was like they added all this extra like detail
But in a way that makes it look sort of like ornamented and like fancy
But like it's not supposed to be a fancy place. It's supposed to be a very like
Drab and like utilitarian place
And uh, he I he didn't like that
Which sounds like a reasonable complaint to me, but I didn't actually see anything
And I've never played the game. So yeah, I've only I've only seen the trail. I haven't played the game
It's good. I have not played I've only played dark souls and part of dark souls
Two and a little bit of blood born and that's all the souls born. I've done
Yeah demon souls the the thing that is weird like about demon souls
is that
um, you know graphically whatever
It's an early ps3 game. They didn't have like a massive hit yet. So it's like certain things look a little cheap
You know, but the atmosphere they created with demon souls is like the best of the entire series
Yeah
Like the the feeling of the locations is just so
Perfectly crafted. That's why it's kind of almost my favorite. Yeah
So this guy's saying it looks like shit. You can go away. That's what people do. Cool
Uh, all right fair enough. Oh wait
I should say, um, we
I mean, who knows if it'll ever exist again
But uh, because we did we did free three people
We did pay the voice bail for three people in voice jail
So, uh, three of them are out on on bail right now. This is lore and it was um, it was uh, oops
Was it was it? Oh god. Oh no, I'm blanking. I'm blanking on who it was
I know it was the japanese man yuta who I guess was the first person we ever put in voice jail
It was um, yeah, nobody could remember. It was um
Oh, no
Who else who else got free? I don't remember. I don't even remember who's in who's in voice
Yeah, we can't even go and back and check. We can't I can't go back and check
I'm blanking. Hey reply in the comments if you were there remind us of remind me
Remind me of who got freed from who got their their bail looks like we're just gonna have to lock them back up again
Oh, no, no, we can't now. How how will we get them? How will we make sure they come back for their their court?
They're they're a trial
We've lost our records
Hey, help us help us enforce help us enforce our our unjust, uh, racist, uh,
Legal legal codes and penalties in the comments remind me of who got fucking freed
I know it was japanese man yuta and two other people
And I genuinely forget who the other two were
Wait, didn't didn't you make an image? What what didn't you save an image of like when you say you freed them?
Like you you had like a scratched off their name. It says free. Do you have that image still?
Oh, you know what I fucking do I fucking do it it
I'm so dumb. It was oh, it was mozilla fennekin and a well-researched thesis
Yes, mozilla. There we go. So the those have bail they're out bail has been posted still in there is um
lull pussies put here eating with spoons who apparently is teen cp
Under an alias. There's all die corporation. Oopsie bobo and fuck die buster
Oh and lost tape lost tape archive are all still
Rightly in there. We're still profiting off of their off of their slave labor
Uh, uh, just as just as planned. This is why we made voice jail to begin with
Um
Based okay cool. Just wanted to just wanted to clear any questions about that up
Um, all right sick, uh next voicemail. Yeah. Yeah next voicemail. Uh, this is from donald duck. Nice
Uh, so donald duck. What do you gotta say?
What
He said I don't I fucking hate the procrastinators podcast
And then he said something unintelligible and then he quacked. It's just it's just like
A bracket's unintelligible
Um, cool. Hey. Hey donald. I'm really sorry you feel that way. You know, why don't you
Listen join the team join the become a patron
Uh join the the exclusive uh of the procrastinators patreon discord
Uh get in there
Uh start a conversation. Uh help us help us grow the channel. Help us help us know
Help help help us grow the channel the way you want to see it. What do you want to see?
Let us know, you know join join the team join the movement
um
Um, what's that's that's how you can that's how you can be constructive in this thank you for your input and we love you
Okay, this this next one is uh called from lecture hacks. Yeah, it's a short one. Okay go
I have a relatively serious inquiry that I want you all to discuss
Uh, I am looking for some lecture tips and tricks. You know what I'm saying
No, one aspect that I want to ask you guys about is
Titling the lecture. Uh, you all seem to have a different way of doing it
So I was hoping uh, you guys could maybe discuss your thoughts on that
Thanks. Um, just title it whatever you think is funny
But also explains what it is. That's it
I everyone told me
Everyone told me not to title the jennifer dayan writes lecture. Uh, um
Oh, what did I end up titling it? It's like jennifer dayan writes and the birth of a multiverse or something
Yeah, something something like that. I want I just I just thought it was funny to give it a title that sounds like a like
Like a freshman seminar course at like a liberal arts college like the like the class name is like this long like sentence
I just thought that was goofy
um
And uh, so I did it and that's
That's it. Was that seo optimized? No, not really. Um, but I didn't care
Yeah, I mean really the the subject matter is the most important thing
If you wanted to if you wanted to like succeed and be found by the most people then give it like a very utilitarian just just like have it
Have just just make sure the title says what it's about says that it's a lecture and if you can fit like a funny
I don't know
If put a lot of exclamation points in there, I don't know
Yeah, obviously I was I was hoping there would be at least one other person who's done a lecture in here to answer this question
my the the risk a lecture I think I called like
Risk a circuit 101 so like a an introductory course to what risk a circuit is
Which is seems all right
Like like what like the best character in how to appreciate the best character in Homestuck is like
You know that'll that'll get him if somebody doesn't believe that they'll be like what how could they how could they do this?
And then they click I mean, but like I don't know to me a title like that is interesting and like what is this
Like why would anybody make a video call this?
Uh, I guess like we got to check it out
um, so
Yeah, just like
Make it clear what it's about
Call it 101. I get I don't I to me just like calling it something 101 is just funny
It's just funny that there is a thing called like
Sonichu 101
And it's a lecture. So I don't know I could just lean into that I guess
um
Or just come up with something else funny
If you think you have the fucking chops for it you dumb piece of shit
um
That's it. Yeah, it's about it. That's it. Um
This next one this is the one I was talking about ben
Uh, the whereabout it's about Nate. Okay
I don't know should I play yeah fucking play it. Yeah fucking play it. Whatever
Okay, now that you said it that I am
Absoluble crimes they can respond they can respond next week if you feel so inclined
Yeah, so this is from a dramatic tweet reading. Yeah, uh go
In response to one Nate best man
I'm disappointed that I can't find a tweet post anything about blm from you
You've said the n word in videos
Claiming it's okay because you love boondocks rap music content from black creators, etc
And you don't get why people say you shouldn't say it
Because if you really loved black culture as much as you say you do
Now in times where black people need public allies you are a ghost
Being not racist yourself isn't enough you need to be
actively
anti-racist
You can reach so many
I just haven't seen you a creator. I love use their platform to support what he says he loves so much
Which makes me think you're scared to lose subs or you support how things currently are
Because being neutral allows this to continue which is supporting racism
Hmm
Yeah, um, so yeah
thoughts I
I I generally agree with the assertion
Yeah, but I think I I I feel like
It's it's definitely more of like I don't don't want to lose subs
By rocking the boat sort of thing if I don't if I don't say anything political then
Um, I can't lose anything
Um, or can you?
Um, uh, I mean
Like I I I I understand I mean the the
Approach because lots of people do it, but it's like yeah, I don't know you've got a lot of subscribers
You've got a lot of twitter followers. It would be nice does just to say a little thing. I mean
Does Nate I don't okay the one the one I agree with basically everything the one thing
I'm not sure I agree with is like
Is it is it?
I don't remember Nate saying like oh, I love black culture
He doesn't seem like a
Champion of that or anything. I don't know if that's quite fair
To characterize him as like oh you claim to love black culture so much. I mean, I know he does like the boondocks and maybe those other things
I don't know
But yeah, I do think it's I think he just likes things that he likes. Yeah, which are good. Yeah, um
I do think not
I do think not speaking out in support of blm is super cringe
uh
Very dumb and and lame
uh, and I um, so
I don't know I
There's not really much to say like I know that well, I don't I would encourage everybody just to say speak out about it
I think it's good to do that
I think
Like fuck anyone who would like unfollow you
For that like fucking get out of here. I don't know
Fuck youtube who will delete your fucking youtube channel
If you do it, I don't know
I just feel like it's a little hypothetically. It's a little unfortunate that Nate is not here to
I agree say what he would say so like
Nate, I'm sorry
Well, you know, I felt like this like I agreed with this enough to post to to play it
Yeah, I'd like to hear what you have to say. I would like I would I would like to hear
If Nate would like to respond to this next week. I'm sure that would be fine
If not, we'll all be judging
Okay, cool. Yeah, how many more we got one more
Classic Luke send yourself on a high note riddle my ass batman. Yeah, um, he's in parentheses. I recorded this drunk
Oh, no
So, uh, get ready here. Here we go
Oh
Just watch my friends, baby for one minute while I go get his bottle. Okay, Jerry
You know delaying. I hear breast milk does wonder for the developing mind
Nice try, Jerry. Bye. Oh, hi grammar meet jr
By lane
Jerry, how you gonna need your help with a shower?
See granny bet perfect. You have a tiny ball, baby
Why do you need a tiny ball mind you baby for your plan? Never mind that I take the baby you take the phone now
On the count of three play my epic shower playlist music
But the first song we're about to make history. Jerry. We're about to make history, Jerry
Is it kramer? Elaine's gonna be back soon. No time Jerry one two three
Kramer stop giving the baby a shower in my sink. Jerry focus. We're losing valuable seconds. Oh, damn
The baby's pissing on me. It's pissing on me. Jerry. Jerry. Sorry to margin here
I need to get a speed running record right now so I can get laid
Is it George take off your clothes and pissing the and babing the baby's piss. Well, I give me a speed running record. No, yes
I should blow over sex
Hey, I'm back. What the hell is going on here?
Done time one minute. That's record Martha. We can have sex. We can have sex
Why did George just run down the hall naked dredged and pissed for sex Elaine for sex
So
So for what I understand that is a new episode of Seinfeld
About the the shower
George the showering thing that happened last week the showering thing. Wait, what the the shower speedrun
I think that's what it was. It's like there's a shower speedrun. There was a baby
And the baby was pissing and then I don't know I forget who it was
But he he did the shower speedrun so that he could get laid so that people would think he was cool
um
It was a little avant-garde a little
I don't remember the shower speedrun thing at all to be to be honest
For from last week the whole Nate was like going like the beginning of the other thing. He was like talking about speed running
Getting in the shower. Oh, yes. Lathering. Yeah. Okay. No. Yeah, I do remember. No. Yep. Yep. Got it. All right
I see. There's like what if try baby piss
Yeah, what what if that was uh seinfeld and also said by real my ass batman. That's that's that's the the voicemail
I think it was pretty good. That's the voicemail
All right. We we did it. We got we got a little bit of everything in today
And with just the two of us
Uh, uh, uh, we can we can now reap the spoils
We can now reap all that sweet ad revenue from our channel that doesn't fucking exist anymore
I'll be a little I'll be a little embarrassed
I'd be a little embarrassed if like the channel came back and this goat does go up on the channel
But like that's fine. But like it's worth it. We don't know at the moment
It's worth the risk. We don't know at the moment people understand that like if it comes back then
You know, we'll have egg on our face. But at least it'll be a tasty egg. We could we could yeah, we can have an egg
I'm willing to risk it. I'll if if that's what it takes like I'll be fine
I'll be I can accept some embarrassment. Just please just you two just don't be fucking shit
Just fucking undo this injustice
You have done unto us. Just fix it. Please please solve the problem that you created for no reason
Thanks
um
I hate you
lol
Kill all cops
Done. All right. Yeah, so now the the the ending preamble that I have not tried myself
And I don't know how it goes
Make sure to go to the patreon.com slash the procrastinators
Uh pledge for is it five dollars gets you access to the bonus episodes
I think it's five dollars for the bonus episodes five dollars for the bonus episodes
There's like a whole bunch of them
And I think it's one dollar to get it and you get into the patreon discord
right
Yeah
um
So that's that's a cool thing. You got the there's uh, there's merch links as well
I don't know if I can what the fuck that is about. Oh, yeah, we have merch. We have shirts
Forgot about that, you know, they've always been there, but I don't know that do they do they show up under the videos?
I think they still do. Yeah, they're part of the description needs
Good go to the twitter at tpcrastinators to hear about
Uh updates on where the fuck the channel is I think we'll be posting on there and our personal channels
That's probably the best place to follow it. Yeah
um
Send go send your thoughts and prayers, please
Uh, oh, yes, uh speak. Yeah. Yeah speak pipe.com
What was it?
Speak pipe. Oh, how uh the procrastinators
I don't know the the the links there link in the description. I guess links in the description to these things and
I think that is
the main things
Uh, go see my webcomics on gibbentake.site go to my patreon gibbentake
patreon.com slash gibbentake yes go to gibbentake.site and go fuck yourself to listener
Hmm, don't do that. I didn't say that. Hey, disavow that. Hey get out
Here. Hey, what are you doing watching this show? Don't you know this show is not allowed on youtube this show?
Um, I don't know. It's it's it's it's a hard. It's a hard
It took a hard left turn if you know what i'm saying. It's a hard our life if you know what i'm saying
it's uh, it's we're
We've we've taken over the we seized the means of pod podcast production. Yeah, and now it's it's a communist podcast and it's so far left
um
That it will it's really far. So it's so we're such we're such radical lefties now that we're voting for joe biden
Um, we're gonna we're gonna we're gonna we gotta we gotta heal
We gotta restore the soul of america and you can't say that and you can't say such shit like that without youtube cracking down
on you
um without without the uh, the liberal elites the global elites cracking down and saying
But we
Hey god, oh god
I'm sad. Give him sad. I'm I'm upset. I'm upset about the channel situation
I'm just upset. Don't worry ben. I'm just upset about the channel situation and i'm taking it out on you and on all
All these fine. Don't worry ben. Cry on my shoulder. You can do it. I will probably probably yeah, look at this fag
Geez, aw Jesus sad though. It's a bad day having a rough day having a rough week so far
And it's only sunday lamal when we record we record these on sundays by the way. That's the joke
That's the joke. Hey, wait one last thing. I made more gummy worms. Do you have something to say?
Oh, I made oh, yeah, I got weird shit. I got kappa carrageenan. I made some out of carrageenan. They're very strange
They have a very strange texture the experimentation continues. I got guar gum. I got agar agar
I have big bags of it in my freaking pantry the carrageenan very odd very odd goo texture
Might might be might be an interesting to to cut with some regular gelatin
Um
Think about it. Okay. That's all I have to say
Uh, I just wanted to keep you updated. Yeah, it's my gummy worm corner play the jingle about ben's fucking gummy worm laboratory
Or whatever that's a segment now
Getting in before we go. Sorry. I've derailed. I've derailed the end of this thing
I've derailed the end of the thing. They're not gonna they're gonna forget about going to our patreon. Sorry
Hey, you there. Bye. Yeah, okay. Okay. Bye. Fuck you
You