Hello, and welcome to this week's episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
We are back to talk about your favorite things one more time.
I'm the best guy ever, Guy, and I'm here with my internet dudes.
First up, Ben Saint.
SaintComics.com
Baby
Endless Jess
Yabba
Dabba too
Uh, Lethal Aurora Mage
I'm here, hi
And The Davoo
Hi
And uh, you'll probably notice if you've been watching that we've got a slightly different composition today of people
And we specifically requested Mage be here and Ben too
Uh, because our topic for the day is fan art
I have been derelict
He has
I've been derelict in my Pro Crastinators duties
Not as much as Mage though
Though that was because I gave Mage some shit
But regardless
You sure did
But regardless, all is well in PCP land
And we're gonna talk about this shit
Well, so right, fan art
So what we want to talk about, or what I was planning on bringing up
Was um, not really instructions on how to do it
But things that you should never ever do without my permission
Um
Well, okay, okay, that's one thing
The impetus for this was simply that
If you go, the links in our description will bring it to the PCP Reddit
In the bottom of the video
If you go there
A nice fellow did a couple of PCP art pieces
A couple of fan art pieces
That just got us thinking about fan art in general
And so we thought we'd take some time
Just break down what we like about, what we don't
And uh, you know, that kind of stuff
Alright, alright, guy, guy
So there's many aspects of fan art that we can talk about here
There's the aspect that a bunch of us do
Which is actually doing it
And then there's the aspect of getting it
Which is a whole different
Which is my exclusive side of that equation
So, right
And first of all, the first thing I have to say
Is that it is downright disgraceful people
That best guy ever has gotten exactly one piece of fan art
From Hippocrite
From Give and Take
And nobody else
So anyone watching this, stop right now
You're not allowed to watch any further
Unless you go draw me something
Send to me on Twitter
Do whatever you gotta do
And that's the end of it
Someone, someone did make a meme out of you though
That, that's true
That was um, a hyper bit hero actually
That's arguably fan art
Of a, of a kind
You know, actually two people have done that sort of thing
I guess that counts
But I want the drawly people
The drawly people
And, and uh, of course Cotton Candy did my banner
But that was a commission
So that doesn't count
But it's true
In any case
We drawly, we drawly people are just more valuable than the rest of you
Well, no, whatever
It's a sad truth of life
What about the draw I did for your video
For free
You mean um, oh for, for TBAP
Yeah
Well of course that was wonderful
But I just wouldn't count that as fan art
Because I asked you for it
That's true
Mage is a coin
Let's start with you Mage
You're asking people, you're asking people right now for fan art
So
No, I'm demanding
I'm putting a, putting a ultimatum
Do it or I'll, or I'll never do another video again
Uh, a guy
Yeah
I believe that your icon and banner and, and well
Like, you know, the face that you use
I mean, I did that for you
Unprompted I think
So I think that could just be fan art
Hmm, I, I suppose that would count
You could call that ascended fan art
It was just fan art to begin with
But then it, although, you know, I guess I kind of had the idea
That you might use it for an icon when I made it so
But it doesn't really count if you're related
So it's fan art
I can't remember
You probably did, you probably did actually
I'm, I'm, I'm a fan of guy kind of
True
Very critical and, and, and
That's true, you're probably my most critical fan
I think you're the most critical fan I have
Yeah
If you do in fact count
Which is, which is a good thing to have
Um, but, but regardless of that
I, I want to ask you and Mage, I guess
Or specifically Mage
I, I brought, I made sure Mage was here
Because she is by far the most prolific producer of fan art
That
Among our entire view
I would say she's the most prolific producer of art period
You think so?
Uh, close to it
Well, I mean, you're probably right
And so she's got the expertise that we need
To really crack this nut, you know
So, uh
No pressure or anything
Yeah, yeah
To crack this nut we call
The real America
Yeah, so, so Mage
You, you're into, you're doing a lot of undertale art
Are you still, still doing that?
Is that, are you still doing that?
Yeah, I haven't heard, I haven't heard from you in a while, so
I, I, I've been busy playing a game
But yeah, I am gonna do some more
Uh, there, uh, a secret project that's coming up
That's might be in a video
Ooh, a secret project
That sounds, that sounds sexy
So
Would that be on your channel?
Yep
Lethal Romage, cool
So, so what drives you, Mage
What's that core fire that burns in you
That compels you to produce?
Uh, specifically undertale or
Or, you know, whatever you're currently into
Well, I am currently into undertale stuff
I, I mean that in the grander sense
The thing at the time that you draw
That you are currently interested in
Uh, gosh, inspiration
I mean, I know that's such a go-to answer
But like, there are some moments in the day
When I just sit down and I was like
I feel like drawing today
And I don't stop until that feeling goes away
But I have to exploit that feeling
Because it's sometimes very rare
And it's just like
When you feel it, you have to do it
Because it'll, it'll, it's very fleeting
What everybody thinks
Sure, I know what you mean
Um, but your art is, is very good
So I imagine it takes you a very long time
To produce
Uh, I mean, does that like
Go away? Do you lose drive
As you're going along?
Um, most art
Just kinda like, it takes a few hours
Uh, I rarely like
Uh, put a piece of art down
And then come back to it the next day
Rarely
Oh, really?
Sometimes it does happen
Yeah, but usually I just kinda get in the zone
So it's good and good
You gotta do it
You gotta do it in one shot
Or else you might never come back to it
Yeah, yeah, exactly
Um, my favorite thing that you've done
I was just gonna say
My favorite thing that you've done recently
Is, is your Muffet picture
That's totally awesome
That's not that recent
That was like three months ago
Well, it's, it feels recent
I don't know
It was like her first Undertale art that I saw
Uh, I was just wondering how long that took you to do
Uh, probably a few hours
Uh, no, wait, actually
If, if, um, now I lost my place
How long Muffet took you
Yeah, yeah, okay
If you're counting the sketch that didn't happen
Then it probably took me a few days
Because the original sketch was like
A bit too complicated
And then it had like a perspective
That was really hard to do
And I tried to change it
But then I just scrapped the sketch altogether
And then I made a new one
And there we go
Okay, cool
I can weigh in on this subject
Yes, please
Ben is definitely our second highest fan art guy
I'm a very slow, I'm a very slow artist
And very often it takes me, like
Okay, a big piece that's complicated
I spend, I sometimes have to spend days on it
Because I'm just not fast enough
Or just not motivated enough in general
To do it all in one go
But, but, if the thing is coming out well
Then that gives you more motivation to it
Like if you do something and it looks good
You're like, yes, that's great
And that like restores some of your energy
And you can like, you can keep going a little longer
You know what's cool
Like your little successes build each other
But if it starts to look bad
Then it's like, oh god, forget it
Like if something goes wrong
I don't want to do it anymore
Sure, that's understandable
I was just going to say
It's interesting that you guys work in sort of
Like, I mean like
A piece of art is like one image
That you're just working on
And like crafting to make as good as it can be
And just the way that you were saying that
Like when I'm making a video
I don't know, like Digi I don't think really does this
His impetus is to get the video done as fast as possible
But when I get to like a complex moment
In a video, I'm sure Davoo can relate to this
And Jesse too actually
It's like, I try to frame
To make that as good as it can be
And like do all the little things I need to
Like a good moment for this is my
In the Gurren login video
When I did the like, what was it?
Like the alternate version
Or like an interpretive version of the spiral nemesis
Where I did like guts with all the waifus
Like I made that part really good
And just like you, I felt a strong desire to keep going
But then I finished it
And then it was on to the next one
And I didn't care anymore
And it was like, well, now that fire is gone
Just my jealousy of the 2D media
That's completely unrelated to this
Anyway
Oh shit, there's Wolf's Rain
Stray, stray
Wolf's Rain fucking rules
It does
It's got wolves, dude
I don't know
You guys want to talk anymore about that
Or should we shift into what we think about
I want to say
That when I make fan art
I don't do that much of it
But sometimes when something really fucking gets me
On a deep level
And when I really love a piece of work
And I want to like
I want to participate in its splendor
In some way
And I want to like feel close to it
So you fuck it is what you're saying
Yeah, I want to fuck it
Yeah, I make videos
That's how I do that
Honestly, it's not that different
From like, oh you like someone
You want to fuck them
Oh, I like this thing
I want to draw it
Sure
It's intimate
It gets me intimately knowledgeable
With the inner workings of a thing
And once I've done it
I feel much closer to it
Of their bodies
Sure, I feel ya
Like I loved Lisa so much
I was like, oh my god
This story is so
You know
Good
Touching or whatever
The story is so emotionally resonant
I was like, I have to create
I have to depict the final epic scene
Or you know, in Undertale
The fight against Toriel
I was like, oh my god
That moment is so beautiful
I have to capture it
I have to participate in it
In some way
I have to depict it in my own way
Ah yes, good
Yeah, that's cool
It's almost like
Right, okay
Now tell me
Alright, if you really like something
I can't be the only one
That if I really like something
I can get caught up
Just like thinking about it
Over and over again
That's how fandoms start I think
Just like mentally dwelling
On this thing and how much I like it
Oh yeah, all the time
That's when I make a video
So I can tell people what I think
And then I can
Gradually go to other things
Same, same
Well, I mean when you draw something
You gotta think really hard about it
Right?
So to draw a thing
To draw a fan of a thing
It's both an excuse to
Just sit there and dwell
On how much you love something
And just think it really hard
Like this thing, this thing, this thing
But it's also an amplifier for it
Because it gives you
You have to focus on like
Oh my god, this face
She's making this face
The tears are running down Toriel's face
As the hot fire burns around
But it doesn't hurt the fallen child
Because she's merciful
That's pretty heavy stuff dude
And that's what it's like
That's what fan art is like
And that's why I do it
What a good description
With fan material in general
I'm much more drawn to works
That expand on the context
Of the original or create new scenarios
Within the thing that are plausible
But aren't shown or don't happen
When seeing Undertale stuff
Where someone makes a comic strip
Out of a scene that happens in the game
I'm like, uh, okay, fine
You're like, okay, I already saw this in the game
Oh man, fuck you
Okay, I see what you're saying
But I personally am a much bigger fan
Of what Ben was saying
As a viewer of people dramatically
I fucking love all these
Incredibly dramatic depictions
Of fights in Undertale from the non
Because Undertale's fights are so abstract
To see them rendered in any other form
That's even slightly realistic
It's so cool
Like how epic was the fighting frisk
In Sans actually
All the fan art I've seen of it
Makes me love that fight more
Because I'm like, holy shit
This is so fucking rad
See, good
Who are you agreeing with?
In this case, she's agreeing with me
All the scenes in Undertale
Were obviously written around the fact
That they were going to be very minimalist
The more tools you have
The more detail you have
The different you're gonna write it
And when it gets all drawn up
It's not as funny or as interesting to me
When it gets all detailed and stuff
I know it's not as good as the fight
Of course, but it's a cool thing
It's a cool supplement
Like, again, it's kind of fanarty
Because these things did not happen
They just floated around in a heart box
For a while and died
Cool supplements are not interesting to me
Well, fuck you
I mean, as an artist
It's that feeling that I just described
Is what I get when I'm depicting something
That's in the game, actually
As a viewer, I'd probably be more interested
In something that isn't in the game
Like D'Vu was saying
Some kind of expansion of the lore
But that really comes with the risk
Like Sans' dating Toriel
It's gonna happen, guys
Shut up, man
But that really comes with the risk
Of someone overextending themselves
And interpreting it in some...
Going overboard in how far it's being interpreted
On this earth
Which can be really annoying sometimes
There is nothing on this earth
I hate more than unrealistic
Fan interpretations of situations
It makes me want to wipe out the entire human race
But did you guys play Undertale Red?
No, but I saw it on YouTube
Why is this?
I have not heard of this
Oh, you should play
It's kind of cool
It's really cool
And it's exactly what you were talking about, D'Vu
What it is is a single fight
It's like a single theoretical fight
From Undertale that takes place
Some time around
Like the time you're in Waterfall
It's a game, you play it
It's a game that you...
Yeah, yeah, but it...
Yeah, it's a game
But it's just one Undertale fight
But it's got alternate paths
For if you're a good guy or a bad guy
Or a genocide or whatever
And the fight can play out in different ways
I mean, it's a little like...
Yeah, it's cool
And it's a little dumb that the character in it
Ends up having a kind of a relationship
With one of the main characters
Who talks about her a little bit
Like she knew her
That's a little cheesy
It's so really great
I have no problem with it
But then again though
In Undertale, all characters
A lot of characters seem to know each other a lot
Like they seem to have a close-knit community
That's true
It's a balancing act
It's a small community
You just have to balance how plausible it is
With how cheesy it is
With how cool it is
And if those things are right
And it's acceptable
Then it's great
Then there's no problem
If she was the chosen one
And she's like
I'm the actual true God of Undertale
You have to beat me for the real deal
Because I was hiding in the shadows the whole time
And if it was that, that'd be more annoying
What I'm into is ambiguity
And subtlety in fan material
Stuff that isn't
This is where everything feels bad
In this fan art that I'm making
Because Undertale itself isn't always
Things feel bad right now
Things feel happy right now
Well I always look for
The first thing that I look for in fan art
Is an interpretation of the work that is
Porn
Oh yeah
Yeah
That's entirely true
That's what I'm saying
I'm way into pornography
Speaking of those sorts of things
You know what I think
Is a pretty good sort of fan art
The show Teen Titans Go
I love that porn
It's not porn
It really is a kind of fan art
For the original Teen Titans
And I think like fan art
It can be polarizing sometimes
Like what fan art can do which is cool
Is expand like DeVue was saying
I think expand on little things
That the fans are all aware of
That maybe the community is aware of
But the show itself doesn't really address
Like for example
My favorite episode
Hang on, hang on
My favorite thing
You know I don't think it's fan art's place
To really expand on the original work
Like the episode of Teen Titans Go
Where it's just an episode
About how awesome Raven's legs are
That's the entire thesis of the entire episode
And like people who hate Teen Titans Go
Which there are amazingly
Those people exist
I don't get it
And they see themselves as the vast majority by the way
I know they're
I hate them all
I wish they were all dead
They are scum
To make like a big
To big lampshade hang that thing
And make a big episode
That's a big funny take on it
Is cool
I really like that sort of thing
That is not an expansion upon
The original Teen Titans
That is a parody of the original Teen Titans
Right there
It blurs the line
I mean it is a show
That's a sequel
But it's not really
I don't like read fan art
And stuff
And then go back to the original
And go
Oh well all those pictures I saw
Are now a part of this
It doesn't
But they are
They are in your mind
My mind
Almost none of that
Really changes my perspective
Of the original thing
Look look
I'm not asking
I'm not saying that it's good
To change your perspective
I'm saying it's cool when fan art
Can just make you think
At the time of viewing
That fan art
That's an interesting thing
Yeah definitely
And that's kind of what I'm saying
The Teen Titans Go
Though fan art has like
The ability to make you
Like make certain characters
More endearing
For instance like an undertale
Grilby like
He's just a bartender
And he's like a flying man
Like I have seen like
A lot of Grilby fan art
And just like
The fan depictions of him
Has just made me
Like a huge fan
Of the character
Even though like
He literally says nothing
I agree
And especially when the fan art
Doesn't do anything to like
Depict him in a different way
It just kind of
Puts a spotlight on him
And it's like
Look at this guy
He's a fire guy
He hangs out at the bar all day
He listens to everybody's problems
He's probably a chill dude
And we're depicting him as such
So then when you play the game
Again you'll see him
And you'll be like
This guy
This guy's pretty cool
And like you know that flames
That flames school girl
Who's like the glue fire girl
She's probably
Grilby's best friend
Or wife or daughter
You know
I'm just making up things
But I like him
You think all
Hey you think all flame heads
Are related?
Yes because I'm racist
You know I can
I can see that
And I can understand
How like that kind of
Fan interpretation
If you like it
And choose to embrace it
Oh listen to Ben
Condescend on everybody
Shut up
You can give
It can give someone more
Like depth in your mind
If you want it to
Personally I feel much more
Comfortable keeping fan
Like interpretation
Like that separate
And I don't like to
I don't know
I don't like to think about them
I don't think it's
I don't think it's really fair
To like combine them
With the original work
I really think they
I don't know
Should be kept separate
Well but I mean
How do you do that
You can't stop people from
Making art
And I think as soon as you
Look at them
I just don't think about it
Like I never thought about
Vinyl and Octavia dating
When I watched
My little pony
And
I think what's important is
To like draw a line
Between your head canon
And what's canon
So like you can like
Head canon has about a lot
Of stuff and have fun with it
But when you're watching
The show or playing the game
Sure
You realize that
Like what you like
Is probably not true
But you can still
You know
Sure but these
You know more dramatic
Depictions of Grillby
Or like the sans fight
None of those are like
Deviating from canon really
They're just
People who are
Who are dumb
Who see fan art
And they go
Well this is canon now
Yes
Actually believe it
Oh yeah
That's a whole other angle
True
Don't understand
Those people at all
You know this
Maybe this can transition
Into what I consider
To be the big problem
Of fan art is
The self perpetuating cultures
Where people
Continue to go
To make the fan art
Not necessarily
Because of their
Original enjoyment
Of the work
But by the
Amount of attention
And friendship
They can get
From continuing to create
Fan works
Causing people
To continue to dwell
Too much
And get a little bit
Tired of it
Well I mean
That's an issue
And I think that
Definitely sort of happened
With Undertale to the point
Where I got sick of it
I was on board with most of
That point
But then I got confused
At the end
Yeah
I'm 100% on board
With that point
Davo
But isn't that just
Like what if
What if people made
No fan art
But just talked about it
Too much
Just posted
You know pictures
It's like the same thing
It's not like a fan art
Problem
And a thing
Explodes in fan works
And the whole community
Comes around it
The fan art perpetuates itself
Like Davo said
In a way where
It turns into memes
And the memes turn into
Dreams
Like people
Hopes and dreams
Yes that's right
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da
Okay sorry
It's the best song
In Undertale by the way
Hopes and dreams
I disagree but whatever
But anyways
What I'm saying is that
There's memes that spring up in the fan art
And that turns into
People's interpretation of canon
So you have stuff like
There's like 50,000 different comics
Of Sans crying
Like a fucking baby
Yeah
And he's such a nihilist
And he's so depressed about it
And people live
At some point
That kind of waned on
On our Undertale
At least back when I was
Still looking at it
Eventually people realized
I think as soon as people
Realized that crying
Sans was like a common thread
People got a little embarrassed
About it
That's good
Because it's self-awareness
Yeah
It's the whole
You know
It's like
That's like a huge
That would be a huge moment
Well let's just say
Hypothetically there is
A part in Undertale
Where Toby decided
To actually make that happen
For some reason
There was a lot of build up to it
That would be like
A huge payoff
And that'd be like
The equivalent of a character death
And in fan art
You could go all the way
You could make the ultimate thing
Happen
But then everyone would do it
And everyone gets sick of it
Yeah
On the subject of fan art
Perpetuating itself
By its popularity
I'm with you on that
And like for me
I even the things that I love
Like Undertale's like
My favorite game of 2015
And one of my favorite games ever
I did like one fan art of it
And then I wanted to do
A second one
But it turned out
It was turning out bad
So I was like well I give up
What was the one you were doing?
I was gonna do undying
The undying
I was like I did exactly
One Undertale fan art
That was pretty okay
And then I made another one
That was deliberately bad looking
And that was
I don't know about you
I make everything I do
Deliberately bad looking
So I can hide behind that
Like a coward
Exactly
That's my life
I actually do pretty pride
In my shitty art
But anyway go on Ben
Anyway
I guess all I'm saying
Is I don't feel the
I don't usually feel the
Needs to do any more than that
But if someone was like
I mean I did get a bunch of views
I got
I've gotten more comments
On my Toriel picture
Than I have on anything else
In my DeviantArt
Of course
I've gotten more likes
On my Alisa fan art
Than I have on anything else
On Twitter
Fan art's a good way
To get popular
Just to do
If those things were
Like super motivating to me
I would be tempted
To do more of them
But I don't know how many
More I could do
Before I started
To be like
Yeah
What you gotta do
Is hop from fandom
To fandom
To do your fan art
Get that sweet subscriber money
I mean
Yeah I mean that
That's my natural inclination
Is to find something
I like
Do like one cool picture
Of it and then move on
Well good
That should work out then
Let me explain why
The whole fan perpetuation
Thing is
Is something that I find
To be
Not something
Something that I have to go out
Of my way to avoid
In regards to Undertale
Whereas
With my little pony
It's not as much of an issue
At least not for nearly as
It takes a lot longer
To become an issue
Is that Undertale is one game
In a hypothetical world
Where Undertale didn't get popular
But I still played it
I would have had a great time
I would have spent
You know a day
Looking at fan art
Then
I would have forgotten about it
Come back to it a year or later
And had an amazing time
But if
You let yourself get stuck
Sucked into the big community
You think about it day in day out
Every day every week
And so then you can't have that cool
Come back to it in a year
Experience
You never have to get about it
You know
I don't know
I rewatch pony episodes sometimes
And I found them
I like living in Undertale hell
Yeah
Well that's good
I can
I understand what you mean
Under hell
And I
I
You know I guess I would
Hypothetically have like to like
Forget about Undertale
And then play it
In a year
There's still time
It's gonna happen
But I never actually do that
I never actually go back and re-read
Or re-play things
Even if I really like them
Which is too bad
And I should probably do that sometimes
That's a healthy part of the experience
You know
It's like stuff like My Little Pony
Is you know half
It's mostly a situational TV show
Where things happen
There's new episodes coming out
There's a continuity
So it's something that can remain
In your subconscious all the time
Or it's something that you can always have
On the mind
Like ooh what's the character
Is doing this week right
That kind of sitcom
Yeah
Romcom
You know
Soap opera type stuff
Undertale is a single
One
It's a somewhat linear start
Begin
End
Story
So you have a problem with the fact
That people keep bringing it up
Even though it's done
It's not something that should be
I mean
I'm not following
I think ideally
Yeah
In terms of your ability to enjoy the game
It's not something that you think about
Consciously
Often
For like a whole year
Yeah
Now me avoiding
Me taking it
Well it hasn't been a year
Coming down
Well I'm
Well I'm just saying it's still
Probably going to be
Pretty around
A year from now
Because of the
Fan popularity
Perpetuation thing
Maybe
Anyway
I'm not really agreeing with that
Personally though
I like seeing a lot of fan art
Of Undertale
Like for me
Me too
What I like about Undertale
Is like the characters
And I like seeing people's interpretations
Of like possible dialogues
And in between characters
Possible
Outcomes
Like what's going to happen
After the end
Or what happened before this
Or like
Yeah
Just sort of like all these
Things that are around the characters
I think
I love seeing that
I love that scene
I think that happened
After the end of the game
I think is the perfect place
To make fan art of
Because
Like all that is speculation
It's all
What makes the game interesting
Is like oh man
What's going to
They have a happy ending
But like what does that mean
It's fun to think about those things
That are really supposed to get answers
Within the work
But you know
Everyone's got their own interpretation
Of what that could be
And there is no answer
Well I
So it seems logical to
You know to pick whatever you want
I can totally say
That Undertale
Like that wrestling match
Like that wrestling video
Is the exact thing
That I would like to happen
After Undertale ends
You know
I forget what it's called
Metaton
Entertainment
Or whatever
You know
That's good stuff right
That's good fan work
I really like
I do really like seeing
Different interpretations
Of characters
Sometimes
Everything
Everyone has like a different
Idea
Of what she actually looks like
Because it's really vague
Yeah
Because it's in black and white
And like
I don't know
Like the hearts
Are the hearts red
Or are they white
Is like
You know
What color is the weird spear beam
Shooting out of her eye
You know
Like what color is
And like
You know
What's she doing
I don't know
Everyone's drawing of her
Looks really different
And some of them
I think are amazing
I think are really stupid
I have this policy
For myself
Is
I absolutely know
That Undertale is good enough
To be a thing
That you can
Dwell on
All the time
Indefinitely
I just think
There are other things
To get to
Nothing's good enough
To draw on indefinitely
That all
Well until further notice
I guess
But I'm just saying
There are so many other things
That also deserve your time
For the first couple of months
I would have said
That Undertale was not
Overrated
It was
Correctly rated
And just there's
A million other things
That are underrated
Is my opinion
Um
I don't know
Maybe
Yeah probably
I'm not bothered by that
People can make art
Of whatever they want
Uh
You know
I am annoyed
But when communities
Obsess about things
That I'm no longer interested in
But I would never begrudge
Someone for the art
That they're making
I am off
Sensation and burnout
Are problems
Yeah
I am often
Perterrived by the thought
That there's probably
Lots of really great
Emotionally affecting media
Out there
That I'll never find
Sure
That I haven't found yet
And I never will
And that's very troubling to me
Um
That brings me to another
Thing about fan art
Which is
Um
That it kind of brings
Attention to a thing
Yeah
Like the way
That I found out about
Homestuck
Was through
You know art of the trolls
Or not
Actually it was mostly
Screenshots of the trolls
That I would see
As people's avatars
And stuff
But whatever
And like
Rainbow Dash presents
The
The biker gorilla
Named episode
Rainbow Dash presents
Her pussy
To be cummed inside
Am I right?
Anyway
Yeah
And I
A friend of mine
Made me watch that
The one with the
Rainbow Factory
Made you watch
Rainbow Dash get cummed inside
Okay
Before
Making me watch an episode
Gave you the opportunity
He said it
Instead of
Making me watch an episode
My friend
Made me watch
The Rainbow Dash presents
The rainbow factory thing
And that
Made me
More interested
In the show
Is the rainbow factory
What she calls her pussy?
Then the consecutive episodes
That I watched
Of my little pony afterwards
Because of the fact
That it was this
20 minute
Production
Or is it her bottle?
This 20 minutes
Why don't I fucking kill you?
Holy fucking shit
Slide show story
About all this meta stuff
I wasn't able to follow
And I was like
Man
If it's able to inspire
In people
This much effort
For something they're not
Gonna make any money off of
It must be good
So it wasn't just advertising
It really sold me
On the passion
That people had
You know what's interesting though
Yeah
That's Sam's
Stronger than you parody
Last time I checked
Over 5 million views
And that's like
Only one of the variations
I think that's like
The animated one
I mean
There's no way
5 million people have played
Undertale right
There's an entire subgenre
Of stronger than you
Mashup parodies
With Undertale specifically
Yeah
But like
The fan work
Has eclipsed the game
At this point
Clearly
There's no way 5 million people
Bought that game and played it
You are probably right
Yeah
A lot of them could be
Just rewatches as well
Okay true
True
But I doubt even
1 million people played
Wouldn't that be like
Crazy successful
I mean
Guy
Yeah
I will agree with you
That there is probably
A contingent
I don't know how large
I'm not complaining
By the way
I'm just pointing it out
That do
Or at least
And or enjoy
Undertale fan shit
And haven't actually
Played Undertale
Yeah
There's probably
Quite a few
Just like there were people
That did homestuck
Fan shit
And they never read
Homestuck
True
I know
Those people have a
Slightly better excuse
Though
No
They should be
In hell
Well okay
You can say they're
Equally bad
Sure
On days like that
Guy
Kids like them
Should be burning
I think I've ever heard
So well done
Well done
Everyone else never
Say it again
It's really annoying
So I mean
We could now
Shift into
We've talked about that
For a while
How about we now complain
About the other side
Receiving fan art
And how everyone's
Doing it wrong
Or not doing it enough
Let me tell you
Assholes
Yeah
And I think
Mage can relate to this
A story
I like
Doing fan art
And giving it to people
I have given a couple
Of favorite artists of mine
On Twitter
Some fan art
Oh yes
And I have gotten
Like retweeted from them
And like
You know they've said
They liked it and stuff
Which was very nice
Did the Lisa guy retweet
Your thing
Yes
The guy who made
Lisa retweeted
My picture
Who by the way
Is a Nordic god
He's the most beautiful
Man in the world
And a karate master
That's right
But
Yeah he retweeted it
And as well he should
Because that piece was
Fucking awesome
And it got like
Very good
Because I did one of her
Characters
And I did one from
Katie Rice
I drew her characters
Camp we don't want you
Yeah
From Katie
And
It's
Nice
Because being an artist
Myself
I know
That fan art
Of my own characters
Is the most precious thing
Yeah
It's the most valuable commodity
Other than money
And it's even pretty close
To that
Because like
That's how you know
A thing is popular
That's the fan art of it
It inspires people
Yeah
So if fan art of your stuff
Exists
And is being made
You need to fucking
Foster that
You need to like
You know try and kindle that
Because that's
That's how
That's one of the ways
By which you
Propagate
So
Yes
I made some
And gave it to people
Because I knew they would
Like it
Because I would
And it was true
Remember the time
Way back in the day
Ben
The first ever piece
Of fan art
That I put into that
Big intro
Celebrating it
That's
That was a great
A more innocent time
That was a great day
It was a great day
And then given of course
Put us into a video
I think shortly after that
Which was
That was probably a while later
Man
Man it feels good
To be a
YouTube gangster
Anyway David
What were you saying
Oh
I think that
If the apocalypse happens
What if fan artists
Are
Fan arts like the
Like the most valued
Commodity
You can draw
Like a bottle caps and fallout
Or something
DeVoo
Yeah
DeVoo have you played Lisa
Is that what happens in Lisa
That happens in Lisa
What
There's
Because it's the post
Apocalypse
And all the women are dead
So porn
Becomes the most
Precious commodity
Like porn
Is money
In Lisa
Whoa it's awesome
Yeah your money
Your money is mags
As in nudie magazines
And you have to trade for them
Yeah
But like
One of your party members
Is this
He's an artist
And just like
He like
Draws porn
And that's
Oh man
He's drawing money
Making it good living
Yeah he prints money
Awesome
But he's actually a really shitty party member
And his design is really shitty
And Mary Sue
Well
Because he was a fan
He was like a kickstarter reward
Oh really
Okay
Well that's
Oh that's a whole other subject
We should probably get into
But anyway
Yeah
We could do that
But what's that DeVoo
Kickstarter rewards
But the artist
Putting a fan made thing
Into the real thing
Okay man
I was watching this one
Undertale video
Wait
Muffet
Muffet's great
Wait are you saying Muffet
Was introduced outside
By a
Well she's the objectively best character
In this series
So obviously that redeems
The whole thing
Right guys shut up
Everyone
Explain what you mean
What do you mean about Muffet
Well she was a
Kickstarter
Thing
Right it was like
There'll be one
Kickstarter character
Made by a fan
Who can design her
Or it
What no
What a great
That was so sorry
There was so sorry
What's his face in the
Flying thing
Oh yeah
And Muffet
Muffet was the best
The flying thing
Are you talking about
Sunderplane
No no no
What flying thing
The other one
I forgot its name
Is he a boss
Like he's kinda hard to find
Sort of like
Is he a whale
Yeah he's kinda like
A flying whale thing
And he's like
I see
What
He's pretending to be
Cool or whatever
I don't remember
Like Glide
I think
Geez I never found this guy
Yeah he's
I've seen pictures of him
He's encountered
Before Papyrus's battle
In that
Area where
It was a locked door
Yeah
If you run around
For a million years
You'll fight him
Which is what happened to me
Because I was trying to
Open that door
Yeah and he's
Really hard as well
Holy shit
I've never seen this guy
Just looked him up
What the fuck
So Glide so sorry
And Muffet
Are rewards
I know for sure
That she was definitely a reward
Because she was
Designed by the artist
Who is making a comic
Called Avis Demon
I'm a fan of that comic as well
She's a brilliant artist
Like her art
Is just wow
And how
Toby utilized
What a mind blow
The Muffet's design
Was pretty great
Because he
Yeah with the whole
Spiders thing
He created this whole
Subculture
Within the world
Which made it feel
Realistic man
That really makes me wonder
Whether she was
Designed before the demo
Because even in the demo
There were the
Spiders in the bake sale
I see
So maybe she was
Trying to extrapolate
Off of that
She was like
Ooh I'll make a spider
And then Toby realized
Ooh I could have a payoff
To this whole spider situation
Maybe they work together
That's a genius
Like I always thought
It was kind of funny
That I mean
Muffet really kind of
Comes out of nowhere
She's in the middle of
Hotland
Like right in between
Like the mediton sections
Not only there for like
A brief time
And that's like
One of my favorite parts
In the whole game
But man
Like all the work
He put into that
Jesus Christ
Did this person pay
For like a boss fight
And a character
Like and
Ties to the story
Jesus that's
That's a lot of shit
And anyway
It doesn't matter
Well I mean so sorry
Has a boss fight
Right
And his own little
Area
And his own little like
I don't know
Coated into the game
But he's like
Hidden away
Yeah
So
Okay so of those
Glyde looks cool
Muffet is the best character
And so sorry
Is the worst thing
That's ever happened
Oh each shit
Each shit guy
So sorry he's fine
He's fine
I mean look at
He's like the butter dragon
You ever go look at this guy's art
Yeah so fucking what
So he's ugly
And whatever
He's a nightmare
He looks like
Like a rejected Barney character
He's a fucking comedy
Character you piece of shit
Well
I'm laughing
Guys
Design aside
I actually found his battle
Sort of annoying
Like his personality
Or attitude
Or whatever you call it
I mean yeah
It's a little annoying
Yeah I mean he's a dick
Whatever
I like him
Like a fucking chud
I'm not even
I agree with you Ben
Like I think he's a good addition
To the game
I thought he was funny
And I enjoy you know
Treating him like the garbage
That he is
And I absolutely love
That you can murder him
And Sam says
You didn't kill anyone important
That's not true
And you can still get true pacimist
What?
Yes it is
No you didn't
I don't believe you
How do you know
Okay well I've just
I just
You've heard it?
I was reading on Reddit
Someone tested it and said it wasn't true
I'm gonna go look this up
That would be really stupid
If that was true
No it would be hilarious
And I would love it
It would really
There's more homework for you
For Undertale
Find Glide
And then test this thing
I will
General Toby's done a good job
Handling fan stuff
By like sanctioning official albums
Like Live at Grillby's
And the other metal one
You know
Yeah that's cool
If you can like review and be like
That's what I would do
If I had created a thing
That had like a huge fandom around it
A lot of like
You know fan theories
And fan cannons
I would just go around
With my cannon stamp
And I would find the things I like
And go yeah
That's cannon
That sucks
If that happened to you Jesse
If you had
If you were in that position
Well no one's in a position
To do that to Jesse's shit
Okay okay listen
That is the game space funeral
By the catamites
That guy actually kind of did that
But it's hard to take seriously
Because someone made a space funeral too
And it wasn't that great
But I mean it was a thing
And just in an interview
Someone asked him like
Do you know about space funeral too
And he was like
Oh yeah sure
It was alright
It's cannon
Ah Jesus
What a hero
And so now it's technically cannon
Because he said so one time
Yeah it's like what
With the DBZ guy
A curatorium
It's like what he's doing with DBZ now
Like for a while he was just like
Yeah all these things are cannon
And like what he's doing now
With Dragon Ball Super whatever
He made like
He made like the strongest person
In the universe
Like this weird little dude
With like these giant nipples
He is like canonically
The strongest man
In I think every universe
That exists
And it's like
How seriously are we going to take
What a curatorium has said at this point
It's been like 30 years
Another cannon
See still
Yeah
Another cannon that's very big
Very pervasive
Pockabell's cannon
Indeed
That's in all these different songs
That's true
And that guy
I gotta say the fandom around that
Is really out of control
And it's time for a change
Yeah
We've just been rehashing
And rehashing it
Since like 1640 whatever
Should we get back to the topic
Of receiving fan art?
Yes please
Sure whatever
Way off for a minute there
That's fine
Maze you've gotten fan art right?
11 pages on DeviantArt
Yes
Of your characters
Yeah
In my
Favorites folder
What do you think make
I was going to say
What makes good fan art
To you
To receive versus bad
I appreciate all fan art honestly
Like
Whatever the quality
You might think it is
It's okay
You can tell them their shit
No
People take time
Out of their day
To draw something
Specifically for me
So I'm going to take time
Out of my day
To favorite and leave a comment
Whenever I can
Maze you're a big person
They're little people
They don't matter
Oh that's not nice
Okay
Well I will say
One thing
Yeah I mean I agree
That I appreciate all fan art
Because it is a person
Taking time
To show appreciation
For what you do
And that's great
But
I don't care
For the ones
That are just trying
To look like the original
Dude
The t-bap fan art
That tried to copy your style
A lot of the t-bap fan art
Looked as though
It was traced
Like right off the screen
And it's like
Yeah okay
Thanks for the fan art
But you haven't really
Added anything
Or given like
Your own interpretation
Of it
Even if you can't draw
At all
I would still rather see
You just like
Try to draw
Fucking my characters
Or whatever
Just however you would draw
Like
Why did it take
Why did it take like
Three years
For someone to like
Draw
Like someone made a keg
Standard
Like normal
Like he looked like
He was in the show
And I still haven't seen
A phantom horn one
Anywhere
Like if it was me
I'd think that'd be
Like the first thing
That I'd want to do
Like he's a pony man
He's in the
Whatever
Just draw him that way
You know
It's like
Why is everybody
Drawn
They always draw us
In groups
Like with our
I agree
Yeah
If you're going to draw ponies
With big sparkly pony eyes
Just give them all
Fucking big sparkly pony eyes
If you want to draw them
With tiny little
Gross beady teabap eyes
Give everyone like that
You know who I blame for this problem
Just draw all eyes
The way you draw eyes
I blame Dr. Wolfe for this problem
Because he's got his
Bizarre weird OC
That doesn't even make sense
And everyone's like
Oh we have to
We have to just use
The style of the art
And put it in there
Dr. Wolfe can go to hell
And don't ever mention his name
I don't ever
Fucking say that name
Or any name
Don't ever say any name
In my presence again
Okay
Coming back to what Ben
Originally said
Yes
About you know
Tracing art and trying to
Make it look like original
Yeah I agree with you
I have seen people just
Sort of like
Or take my original images
And just sort of like
Doodle on them
Or add some text or whatever
Make them into like
A collage or something
Yeah
It's not
I mean
Okay you wanted to do
Something and you're
Very good at art
And okay I appreciate the effort
But at the same time
I prefer whatever you can do
To love to you
Right
Copy pasting my work
Yeah
It's kind of like
The illustration equivalent
Of like
Like a knock off YouTuber
Like the angry video game
Nerd knock offs
Being like the waging
I don't know
Whatever
Because I've seen guys
On YouTube
A couple guys actually
Who you know
Are like
Openly proudly inspired
By me
And I watch their videos
But it's like
At the point where
They're just like
Stealing my jokes verbatim
Yeah
And it's like
I saw that one guy
You showed me
That was just
Your video
It's cool that you're
Inspired by me
But this is literally
A worse version of my video
Yeah
I'll kill you
The inspiration and
Stealing work
Is two different things
Hey
I mean
If it's for fan art
Then I would never call
It stealing
No matter how boldly
They've
You know
You mentioned
James Rawl
You mentioned the angry nerd
And
He blinded me back
When I was first
Getting into the nerd
Way back then
And I looked at the fan art
What bothered me
Is that almost
None of the fan art
Looks like his face
Almost none of the
The eyes
Or the noses
Or the mouths
Really looks like
An abstraction
Of what James Rawl
Had
There was a guy
Who did
You know
As we mentioned
Fan art of all of us
And you know
It was cool looking
But almost none of it
Really like
Captured our facial features
All that much
I don't understand
Picture perfect
Or even
Almost unrealistic
I think when it's
A real life person
And you're going for
A somewhat
Depending on how
Realistic you are
Just look at your icon
Right now
I'm looking at it
It doesn't look
Anything like you
And I appreciate it
I agree
I'm not saying
This is like
A required thing
I just wish
It would happen
Sometimes
Or
Let me put it this way
If you're going to make
Like
A more abstract
All of those little
Squiggly details he has
Will be some sort of representation
Of our facial features
You know
I guess
Look at Maze
Maze doesn't look like her thing
She's got like an established
Character now
That like is her face
And it's you know
Yes it's me
That's draw me
As a purple anime girl
Nothing else
Yeah
And you know
This reminds me real quick
Speaking of fan art
And the angry video game nerd
Did you guys ever see
That
I forget what anime it was
But like in a real anime
Some background extras
Were with the video game nerd
And the nostalgia critic were
In an anime
Like in some big show
Yeah
They were actually
Acting in the background
Drawn in some show
And in James Rolton
John Walker
Made a fan
Recreation of that
They did a fan recreation
Of that by
Re-staging it
Which is just like what we did
When or most
Some of us here
When someone did that fan art
Of give and take
Never give up
And we recreated that
At BronyCon last year
Which was
Never give up
That's right
Good times
The best
Um
I
Okay
Those
No those fan arts
Someone did of the procrastinators
Yeah
Mine looked like absolute ass
And I hated it
Sure
My face was the most
Like it was totally
Like warped and disgusting
Get it together
Whoever you are
Yeah
Let's talk about
Crappy fan art
Of us
And how much it
Anchors you
No I was wearing glasses
And I had a little heart
Tattoo on my neck
Yeah
Which was cool
That was cool
But you can find it
On the procrastinators
Yeah
The reddit
The subreddit
We'll show you
You can go there
God damn it
Click in the link in the description
Shut up guy
Fuck's sake
Alright
Yeah Jesse
Let's talk about
Shit fan art
I love getting fan art
Of all kinds
I think it's the best thing
It's the thing from the fans
That I respect the most
I respect it infinitely
More than some
Shitty, worthless
Pissant
YouTube comment
That took you half a second
To fucking crap out of
Your shitty brain
Yeah
If someone actually takes a time
To draw something
Or make something
That makes me feel good
And a lot of it's really good
But what I don't like
Is the ones
The guys who like
Make it crappy on purpose
Just be like
Hey you crappy fan art
That's not fun for anyone
Jesse
Get out of here
You're one to fucking talk
Look at your fucking
YouTube thumbnails
What are you talking about
Look at your fucking
Horse cast
YouTube thumbnails
That's the very definition
Of crappy on purpose
Whoa whoa whoa
Whoa
My
MS Paint
Masterpieces
Thumbnail drawings
Are goddamn masterpieces
They're 10 out of 10s
How dare you
Insinuate that they're anything
Less than perfect
That they're flawed in any way
They capture our spirit
They capture our essence
Yeah
I don't know man
I think they're just trying to go for
I think they're
Maybe they're just trying to go
For that same sort of appeal
You know
I can guarantee you
That I am legitimately
Putting my all
And giving the maximum amount
Of effort when I draw those
Well if it's all the same
To the person seeing it
On the other end
Whether you put your all
Or not right
Yeah
It's great
10 out of 10
And you guy
Let's not even talk about
Your art
I'm proud to be the worst
Artist that I know
I wear it on my sleeve
As armor
So that it can never be used
To hurt me
Yeah that's right
You piece of shit
It depends on the context
As you go
And I have no interest
In getting any better ever
Now that I've discovered
That I can pay people
To draw things for me
I have no incentive
To get better
It's the best possible timeline
Oh yeah
Well there's a commission
In my armor
Because Ben has hurt me
Let's talk about commissions
Yes
Podcast successful
If I get into being
A person with a lot of money
I would just be commissioning people
To make fan stuff
That I want to see
All the time
No dude
Listen
I could never pay someone
To do art for me
Because it wouldn't look
The way it did in my head
Sure
I have to do it
My way
I know what you mean
Yeah well I can't
I can't do drawing
So I can compromise on this
Wait mate you do agree with me
Or you don't
I agree with you
Like I cannot
Like pay people to do
Like commissions for
Like I cannot
Commission people
To do art for me
Because like for me
I have this horrible thing
About like
If it can be drawn
I might as well draw it myself
Well of course you guys
Can draw
You guys have that ability
No shut up Davoo
I'm gonna kill you for saying that
And here's why
Because all of my drawings
Look like shit when I start them
And I just fucking
Keep changing them
Until they look good
So all anyone
In the whole world
Has to do
Is just draw a shitty drawing
And then just keep redoing them
Until
Okay that's all I do
I'm sick and tired
Anyone can do it themselves
Of this professional illustrator
Elitism
Fucking looking down
On people this pompous attitude of
Oh shut up
You can learn to draw
Anyone can learn to
Fuck you
I've tried motherfucker
I can't
It's impossible
Ben is absolutely right
Quit kind of sending to me
Anyone can learn to draw
Anyone can do it
The thing is
I don't want to
I don't want to take five years
To learn how to draw
Because I need a picture
For my video next week
Here's the thing
Yeah Ben I totally agree
I totally agree
I don't have time for that shit
I could just pay someone
You just redo it
Over and over again
And eventually it becomes good
I do not have the technical know how
Listen
I can't do that
But it will take me
Ten times as long
As it will take you
And you'll be glad
For the experience
No I'd be glad to
Pay money to save myself the time
So I can be working on my video
And editing it
Guys
Do the things
That you are better at
And pay for
Davoose
Alright Davoose
Enough
Okay
Paying for commissions is fine
Like guys
I am going to open commissions soon
So yes please do pay me for commissions
Everybody pay me
Oh shit
She's got skin in the game
It's an important thing
I'm going to do that too
So forget everything I just said
But the thing is
Like you can learn how to draw
Like there's a certain amount of hours
You have to
Have been drawing
In your life
I think there's
There's some sort of rule
Somewhere this is
Like oh
If you had drawn
This many thousand hours in your life
And you should be okay at art
Guess what
We only have so many hours
Into something new
In our life
Before we potentially die
We have to choose
What's true
To go for
I don't understand
So like
You know
It's never too late
To learn to draw
But you have to
It's too late to care
If you're a high school kid
And you just
You're not doing anything
Particularly important with your life
And you want to learn to draw
Then you should absolutely do it
But
You know
Our video creators first and foremost
And that's what we focus our time on
And that's what we have interest in
Perfectly
Like I was a terrible video editor
What three years ago when I started
But I've just done it
For millions of hours now
And I'm decent
I'm okay
So I assume it's the same with art
The whole point of society
Is that you pay
And how all you genius illustrators
Are with your art
How you said
That you
Are saying it was such a scorn
You genius illustrators
How you said that
Like you can't commission
Someone to draw something
That's how I am with editing
I can't commission someone to edit
For me
That's exactly right
My videos could never be made
I'll commission a guy to draw for me any day
Because
Fucking make it look pretty
Make me look pretty
The whole point of paying people money
For anything ever
Is that they can do it better than you can
You could grow and cultivate
All your own food
But it's a lot easier
To just pay for it
To be off a shelf
Right
Specialization is the nature of capitalism
I can respect that
But whatever
Like if you were making like
If you were the angry video game nerd
And you had like a million subscribers
And you're like
Okay, time to make a new video
I'm gonna do every single piece of it
It's not feasible
It's not smart
You gotta break that shit up
I feel like I had something else to say
On the subject of
I don't know
Drawing
Or
Commissioning
Fan art
Or whatever it is we're talking about here
On the Procast Nudist podcast
Every weekend or so
Yeah, I don't know
But really honestly
The worst sin
A fan artist
At all
Can commit
Is not
Drawing
Best guy ever
Fan art
Get out there people
Get out there on your tablets
And your gay little notebooks
Do whatever you gotta do
To draw fan art of me
And my cool waifus
I'll have it a great time
Because if you don't make it real
It will never be real
So live your dreams
And live my dreams
Okay, while I can respect the attitude
Of like
Oh, it's easier to just pay someone to draw it
I can understand that
And that attitude is what keeps me
Alive
And in business
Kind of
So that's fine
But
On the other hand
I kind of hate that attitude
Because
I really like it
When people that don't know how to draw
And are bad at drawing
Nevertheless
Like put forth a sincere effort
And produce an image
That just to get across
Their idea
Like
I think
Like I was reading this comic
The other day
Called Skuzzy
And it was about like
Some kids that wake up as zombies
And it sounds stupid, right?
But it's
Drawn
In this really like
Child-like way
Everything's all like
Real simple
Like blocky shapes
And like
Everything's all colored
Flat colors
Like the characters are just purple
And their teachers are yellow
Yeah?
Have you all seen
The original One Punch Man
Webcom?
Yes
Ah, that's a good example
I guess of what you're saying
Yes, I have
Yeah, it's got really
Really basic shitty art
Yeah, so
It's really rough
Look at the brick into that
And even
Attack on Titan
At the beginning
Kind of is shitty
It's still a shitty
It's too shitty
To be published
As it was
I don't know how it got through
Their approval process
But it did somehow
And it was popular
Okay, okay
Forget about
The actual
Attack on Titan manga
Yeah
If you ever saw
Like
The manga
That he did before
Attack on Titan
That he submitted to some
Like shitty little
Rinky Dink contest
It is so bad
Every bit
Of that like
Proto
Attack on Titan manga
Yeah
Is worse
Than the worst panel
Of the original
One Punch manga
And there's some pretty bad ones
It is like
Fucking a child's scribbling
How the fuck did he win?
I don't know if he won
I'd like that he just lost
Or maybe it was just
A really bad contest
I don't know
Well, that's fascinating
Maybe they lack the idea
Of the story
And not just the art
Okay, but you're making
A comic for Christ's sake
You're not making
A book
Although the story
Was way more basic
Than Attack on Titan
It's just like
A guy comes to town
And there's like
A monster
It was a genetically
Engineered monster
Luckily I too
Am a genetically
Engineered monster
And he gets big
And fights it
And that's it
That's the whole story
Yeah
That's the end
Of really shitty comics
Becoming popular
One Punch Man is
Legitimately great
And deserves it
They're not shitty
Just because they have
Rough art
They're really like
Scuzzy
I really like
The original
One Punch Man
I really like
Just fucking
Garbage made by
Assholes
But when you compare that
To like
The new version of
One Punch Man
It's pretty much
Better in every way
I don't care
I like
The original
Remakes should all
Burn
I mean
I agree
I've been watching the show
And I keep thinking
The whole
Part of the integral
To the joke
To the reason it's funny
And amusing
Is that it looks amazing
But it's
Silly what's happening
But it looks amazing
Similarly to
That is true
That is a unique joke
How weird Al
His entire comedy
Requires
His incredible production
Value
That's true
Because
It becomes
As valid
As the original
Song that was made
If not even
Better produced
As it is sometimes
That is integral
To why it's funny
You know
My favorite image
That proves that point
I think
Is when you see
King
Like there's a couple
Panels
That are these
Massive close-ups
Of King's face
And King's whole deal
Is that he has just
Intimidated people
With his scary face
And everyone thinks
That he's super strong
And you know
As it turns out
That's not the case
And like
The super good
Detailed like
Intimidating glare
Is what like
The people in the story
Are experiencing
And with shitty art
That would not be conveyed
Anywhere nearly as well
And makes the joke so much funnier
When you find out
Oh
It's fucking
It's fucking not true
It's fucking baloney
Yeah
So that's a unique thing
To the
Enhanced version
I want
I just really want
To reiterate
That I think that
People
That can't draw at all
Honestly
Sometimes I think
That makes their art
More interesting
Like if you put forth
Like a sincere effort
Like the guy who
Poo-pooed on my
M.S. paint drawings
No
I was just about to say
Now I see
Your true
Hypocritical colors
Where's my
Hypocritical colors?
I was just about to say
That if someone like
I mean
I would say like
Davoo
You have like
You're not a great artist
Or anything
But you do have like
A very like
Kind of
Unique aesthetic
And everything
That you do draw
And the same is kind
Of true of Digi
Digi has this weird
Like scratchy
I would really like
To see more art
By people like that
Yeah
Like my art
I do make sure
Whatever I
Because I always draw
Something for the purpose
Of something else
That needs to like
Convey something visually
Or I'm making it
For a thumbnail
So I always have a clear idea
And I'm usually
Able to square it in on
At least accomplishing
The goal that
It was intended for
Even if it otherwise
Sucks
But what about
Like you drew that little face
That little face
With just like this
Gross little thumbs up
Just kind of sticking
Out of the side
Like
I almost made that
My thumbnail
And I love how
Polarizing it was
Like people either thought
That was amazing
Or horrifying
And they never wanted to see it
I know you were torn up
About whether
To use it or not
Yeah
Until eventually someone
Came around with one
That I thought was basically
Perfect which is what
I'm using now
So Ben are you saying
That guys like me and Jesse
On further down
On the artistically competent
Spectrum if you will
On the artistism spectrum
Yeah that's right
Our shitty art has value
Because it's shitty
It's an artistic representation
Of ourselves
Someone just drawing
Like what's in their mind
Even if they have
Without any technique at all
Can sometimes convey something
That you wouldn't get
From like a very practiced
And like skilled artists
Like on this very podcast
On the Steven Universe episode
Episode three I think
My Mexican cherry opal
I think was his name
Yeah Mexican cherry opal
That's true
He was a masterpiece
That's no doubt
And you know
Talking about Digi
Because way back in his
Some of his earliest pony videos
He drew this character
This really weird looking
Terribly drawn character
The gray thing with the white hair
Yeah and then recently
In one of his asterisk videos
He makes a reference
I saw you put it in there
When he said who am I
To complain about characters
Design
Yeah what would I know
About character design
And I decided to draw
A fan art of that character
That would be making
A specific pose
That would fit
And so in the process
Of drawing that
I realized
Whoa this is actually
An interesting design
It's just terribly drawn
But it's a kind of
Interesting character
That I've never seen before
Especially the color palette
So yeah
Yeah that's true
When he does draw things
They end up looking really weird
But in a way that I kind of like
Yeah like when we did
The comic jam
I remember thinking
The art was very interesting
It was one of the most interesting
Along with like
Yeah like there's
One of like
Just like a close up
Picture of a pony
Like screaming
Yeah that's right
And it's really
Spooky looking
I think Digi in general
Is a guy who is
Who is able to
Really really really
Think about
What he likes aesthetically
Like he has very specific
And detailed ideas
Of what looks good
Yeah
But not a whole lot
Of skill in explaining it
All the time
And obviously almost
No skill in recreating it
See that's my problem
I'm not
I'm a shitty artist
Because I can't visualize
What I want something to be
And then convey it
In my pen
And a lot of the times
I'll have ideas
Of what I want to do
And it just
It won't come out
It will not come out
Anywhere close to
How I'm envisioning it
What
What can you do about that
What can be done
Because when I was drawing
That fan art of that character
Of his
I was really looking at it
More closely
And I was imitating
Some of the
Crappy drawing
Like
Like inking methods
That he was using
Where he would
Draw some of the hair
And then use the erase tool
To make different threads
Of the hair
I was like whoa
So
His lack of skill
Created like a unique
Look
That's kind of how I did the hair
On my latest picture
On my Twitter
It's also ugly
Everyone go follow me
Well I mean
He would use a pretty
Thick erase tool
But
Yeah
Um
So yeah
The lack of skill
Can create a unique aesthetic
So what you're advocating here
Ben
Is to not assume
That even if you are
The shittiest artist in the world
Don't assume
That you don't have
Any ability to produce
Your own work
You gotta
You gotta take it
Sometimes you just gotta
Do it
And see how it comes out
Because even your shittiness
Can give it its own personality
Well clearly
With one punch man
That was great
I was able to make it
To prove that it was
Worth existing
And then was able to
Get it drawn well
I'll give you that
However I gotta say
That guys in the position
For example of me and Davoo
Who are focused on other things
And are just trying to
Manage their time to get shitt done
For example right now
Right now in this very moment
I'm commissioning a guy
To make this pixel art thing for me
And I don't know
Fucking shit about making pixel art
What am I gonna do
Gonna learn how to do pixel art
He's talking about all these
Mathematical equations
That he's applying to like
Animate pixels moving and stuff
To replicate like
Different effects in the sky and stuff
Like am I gonna learn
All that shit
No of course not
That's why I'm commissioning a guy
And it's the same thing with
Whatever
Yeah it just works smart
Like I made an RPG once
And I'm not a very good pixel artist
But I did most of it myself
Because I had to
You know
And that I had to
So that I could make a game
And even Toby Fox
Is not a very good artist
You know
That's true
Look at the beginning
The frisk who looks like shit
And then the whole beginning area
The ruins looks like garbage
Compared to the rest of the game
Which looks much better
Right
The guy who made Lisa
Is not a great artist
Yeah
But he
In his figures look really weird
But in that kind of like
Strangely comedic game
It works really well
They give personality
And he's not a great artist
It's true
You know
You made a fair point there Ben
It works smart
Because
Like Trey Park and Matt Stone
They made the South Park characters
Even though they can't do good art
And those designs
They're iconic now
Yeah they're iconic
They're fucking fully cool
That makes them cool
And
Yahtzee
Making his air punctuation art style
You know he hasn't ever had
To update that
And he can't really do art
Otherwise
And again it's working smart
It's knowing your limitations
Down to the wire
Yes working around
Your own limitations
Yes
That's where art comes from
And it's related to fan art
To bring it home
That's true
Anyone can do fan art
Doesn't matter about your level of skill
But get creative
Do what you
You know have an idea
Have a vision
Get creative and put forth a sincere effort
And your vision
Will shine through your lack of skill
I absolutely love
Our shitty first ever T-Bap fan art
It felt like there was heart
It was all fucked up
And I loved it
Yes it was drawn in their own style
It wasn't just like
Traced from our thumbnail
It was its own thing
And I'd like everyone to do likewise
Yes
Alright anybody got any last words to say
I'm gonna throw in another
You know one of those
Jesse
I should have killed myself years ago
Yeah
Because of your lack of art skills
Yes
Yeah
That would have been better
I think we got a lot done today everyone
I think we've really made progress
I think we've all come to understand things a little bit better
Our
Well good
Okay
Everybody draw fan art
Mostly me
And also these guys too
Everybody should do it more
Go to the subreddit
There's a link in the description
Give us PCP fan art
At the very least of the five of us
Who are here today
I demand it of you
I want fan art
I want fan fiction
I want fan games
I want everything you can possibly do
Whatever you gotta do
And by the way if you make a fan game
Make it something other than an 8-bit platformer
That's a rule
But I like those so you can do it
Don't listen to different
I like 8-bit platformers
Any game starring me is a fucking 10 out of 10 game
Which Jesse has had two games made about him
At this point by the way
Two
Yeah
Two?
Other than quest for donut?
Yeah somebody made a game where I'm beating up
The cinemasins guys
Yeah
Me
I made that
Oh that's right
Oh yeah I still haven't seen that one
I sort of like a really stupid Atari 2600 game
In terms of depth
I like it
I wanted you to make like
Like more of those
Yeah
Of me beating up different YouTubers
With different settings
And I wanted to like compile them
Into like a Mega Man
Where you pick the stage and stuff
Oh that's a cool idea
I'd commission that from DeVoo
That's worth it
Because you wanted me to do a Final Fantasy 7 edition
Where you can beat up everyone who thinks
Final Fantasy 7 is overrated
What a great idea
Dude commission that for when the remake comes out
And have that at like the beginning of the video or something
That'd be great
Okay good thoughts
Alright let's end it right here everybody
Thanks for watching folks
We'll be back next week talking about something else
Leave whatever you've got suggestions
Leave in the description
We've actually done like many of the suggestions
People have left
They've been better than stuff we could fucking think of
So shoot that shit in that box
Give us a like
And shoot it right into my rainbow factory
Yes
Alright everybody
Say goodbye
Bye
Yeah
We did it
We did it we're all done
Woo