Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemail for the Minecraft stream. I really want to have Redcon funded by you. We can be Pro Crastinators.
Hello everybody and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. We're just starting. We're just gonna fucking go.
The only podcast you ever need. This is the only one you need to listen to. All the rest, they're just suggestions. This is the one you listen to on repeat from now until the end of time. It's great.
The only mandatory podcast.
Whoa, who's that? Is that Ben Saint?
It's me. It's Ben Saint. I'm alive. I survived another week.
The only podcast that has lamp oil, rope, bombs, if you want them, you have to listen to the entire thing.
True.
And who's that? Who's that piping in from the back?
It's me, Morshu.
What?
Whomps?
Morshu from The Legend of Zelda CD-i, the guy who says lamp oil, rope, bombs, you want it?
I didn't know we had a guest on today's episode.
Yeah, but put Eleazar, put the Morshu in the corner. He's the new PCP guy with his old-
Oh fuck.
After all that work to make a legally distinct PCP guy.
There is no PCP guy. We changed the form out. It's Tombstones now. We're Tombstones. Put them on a Tombstone.
Where's the PCP guy Tombstone? Is he dead? Is he at large?
When you come into the graveyard, there's an archway and it's like a wrought iron arch.
It says procrastinator's graveyard over and in the middle there's a little engraving.
There's an engraving and it's his face. That's him. That's where he's at. He's overseeing the afterlife.
There's all this description. Sounds like how you would play a text-based game. I only do graphics, graphics only. I don't read, so...
I play Noida. That has pixels.
It does. Moving up in the world.
I've become addicted to the feeling of getting a really fast wand online, of getting castaway down to zero and just getting a chainsaw.
And just piss bullets everywhere. I need it. I need that thrill.
And if I start a run and I don't find chainsaws, I'm like, oh god, I'm so weak.
I feel weak right now because I'm not blasting damage at beasts.
I want to blast both of you. I just want to tear you apart.
Is that why Twitter's been a war zone for the last 10 days? You've just been blasting everybody?
I've just put my chainsaw on my spark bolt and my spitter bolt and I just...
No, it's not my fault. I didn't do anything. I've done nothing wrong. I apologize for nothing. Everyone else is wrong.
And I'm not even kidding. I'm serious.
I just sit here. I just respond to life as it comes at me in the only reasonable way.
Ben just sits there, buys keyboard with his couple of gallons of gasoline
and every time he sees an opportunity, just pours a little bit on something.
I disagree with this characterization. No, I'm innocent. I'm innocent of everything.
Okay, good.
Okay.
No, everyone...
I've been looking at all that stuff and I'm like, whatever.
Personally, I'm too physically deteriorated to care about whatever is happening.
God, I wish I were that physically deteriorated.
I've been this last week ravaged in a non-sexual way, which is the worst kind of way.
Ravaged in a digital way, with a bout of disease of some kind.
It's not a disease, really. It's just like I'm stupid.
Tell me more. Tell me about your disease.
It's called not eating or drinking properly and it's destroyed me.
Well, I mean, ultimately, I think that was what it was, because I don't know.
I'm living in a new place, right?
I said I was living in a new place and I'm like, okay, I'm cooking food for myself.
I can cook food, that's fine.
I think it's just something about the dryness in the room or something that I'm not used to.
And I got really dehydrated and I didn't notice, because I don't notice things.
So I got so dehydrated and it wasn't even warm, so I was not even thinking about that being a thing.
And then I started vomiting and it was the worst.
Every morning was agony, getting through the day.
It was all I could do to survive.
I was just like, and all of this time, stuff was happening on Twitter.
I'm like, you know, I could think.
Nothing.
But I don't have the energy to do that.
I just need to live right now.
I just want to try. Nothing actually happens on Twitter.
Things happen off of Twitter and then people go to Twitter to bitch at me about things that happened elsewhere.
And then I spend the rest of the day replying to idiots who don't see that I'm the only rational actor.
That's what's going on.
Don't get it twisted, but okay.
Excuse me.
Sure, whatever.
Yeah, whatever.
It's just a bunch of something.
This is an opinion I could have on it.
I don't really know what it would be.
I just want to live.
I just want to stop feeling pain.
I feel a little better today.
God, it sucks.
I don't understand.
When a physical ailment gets here, there's nothing else matters.
You're saying you were simply dehydrated.
Dude, dehydration will fuck with you.
No, no, no.
It's dehydrated.
Well, it got to a point where, you know, that like...
Does dehydration make you throw up?
It makes...
Well, I don't know.
All right.
Here's what I assume was the series of events.
It was dehydration which caused constipation,
which made it difficult to eat things
and to drink things without like,
like eventually throwing up.
I'm like, okay, I can't keep things down,
but I need to ingest and I can't.
And I had to go to the hospital to get like water pumped into my veins.
Did they intubate you?
They intubated you.
They put a IV or whatever into my vein
and I almost fainted because I'm scared of the blood
and the blood came out of me and I was like,
oh, no, no, no, I need to lie down.
No, no, no, I need that.
Put it back in, please.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, it was the scariest thing of all time,
getting treated at a hospital.
I couldn't, you know,
dissuade people from going to hospital more
than the scariest of it all.
Definitely don't go to the hospital.
This is a PCP official advice.
Don't go to the shoplift and don't go to the doctor.
Just, just die.
And don't go to college.
Disavow.
But the rest I disavow.
It's funny.
Yeah, it was fine.
I mean, it wasn't fine, but it's finer than it was.
I now know that I'm stupid and I should drink more
and that I've got to eat proper meals
even when I feel sick because if you don't eat,
you don't have fuel, you can't fight anything
when you don't have fuel, it just makes everything worse.
It gets you to a point where you can't recover naturally.
You know?
I don't, I still don't quite, but you didn't,
you didn't need to eat.
You didn't need fuel.
It was confusing.
You didn't need fuel to fight off a disease.
You just needed to drink fucking water.
That's all you needed.
No, it's confusing because like,
I feel like I also have a cold and it's not corona
because we have COVID tests and I took one just in case.
I don't have COVID, but like,
I feel like I've had a cold
and this, it's always multiple things.
It's never just, oh, you have this one symptom.
This means you have this one ailment
and this is this one solution.
It's always like, I do the one solution
and it turns out I have another thing
that's also like, that's not the solution.
So I should like do two solutions to these things,
but they might contradict.
I don't know.
I hate medicals.
I hate science.
Fucking doctors.
They're so smart.
You should have tried to,
you should have prayed the dehydration away instead.
I should have.
Yeah.
Good job.
Thanks.
You wouldn't have to go to the hospital then, huh?
You didn't even think about that one?
Maybe if I just like sliced open all of my limbs
and drank the blood,
that would cure my dehydration because it would be liquid.
Because then you'd have less blood that needs water,
but also your blood would be the water.
I just recycle.
It's recycling.
It's like green energy basically.
You should drink your pee too.
Disappear.
The drinking pee is like something I do on the rig anyway.
Don't shoplift.
It's like a normal day to day.
Don't go to the doctor.
Don't go to the hospital.
Don't go to college and drink your pee.
Why would you drink your pee
if you could just shoplift a drink by your own code?
Why would you...
I mean, well...
Fuck.
Disappear.
No, no.
Eleazar, cut this whole thing.
Cut the entire episode out.
We're starting over.
Start over, please.
Cut my life.
Do pieces.
No, no, no.
That's not the right song.
The song for this situation is clearly
get down with the sickness.
That's the entire summary of what happened.
There's this small moments of early morning
where I'm feeling weak
and I need to make myself breakfast or whatever
so that I have energy.
But I'm like, there's no way out of this.
This is the end.
I'm hollowing in real time and I'm like,
you know what would be nice right now?
It's like a bottom of a muddy ditch
and I could just throw myself into it
and fade away.
Nobody would ever find me.
I could just like, that's just what I need right now.
You ever feel like that?
You ever feel like just crawling into a space and dying?
I don't know what not feeling like that is like anymore.
It's been too long.
Oh, my man.
You know, when you play Dark Souls
and you go and the Skeleton Men,
like right outside Firelitron.
I feel like a Skeleton Man.
It's like when you're playing Noida
and you don't have any chainsaws
and your wand is just doing a little pew-pew-pew
and you're like, this fucking sucks.
I just want to kill everything.
You know, it's more like when you're playing Minesweeper
and you lapse in judgment for one second,
you click on mine,
because you just didn't count.
Three, you counted two and you were an idiot.
You were right at the end of an evil-sized Minesweeper thing.
You don't have to explain Minesweeper to me.
I'm an expert now.
Have you been playing it?
I don't know anything about it.
I'm an idiot.
Simple, you click on the squares
and then you get frustrated.
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
That's it.
You missed the bonus episode where I became a Minesweeper
and Picross Master.
I was tutored.
I was tutored in the ways, in the mystic arts.
Patreon.com
slash The Procrastinators.
$5 gets your access to all our bonus episodes,
including that one.
What a time to be alive.
What a time for the PCP.
I said it before the episode.
I'll say it again.
We have entered the funniest era of the show,
in my opinion,
and I cannot be dissuaded from this opinion.
It's all coming up roses.
Great, it's looking up from here.
I don't know.
What's the argument here?
Where's the evidence to this claim?
The jokes.
I don't see it.
Come on, Ben.
Where's the funny?
Come with the funny.
It's not like ha ha funny.
It's funny like a...
Is it sad funny, like pathetic funny?
It's funny like when you're at a funeral
and you can't help laughing for some reason.
It's funny like it's like rain on my wedding day.
It's ironic.
It's a free ride that you just couldn't pay.
That's exactly what I'm saying.
I'm on your wavelength.
That's the new wave.
That's what it's going to be like from now on.
Trixie quit.
Trixie quit is what I'm saying.
And I think it's really funny.
I don't know if I'd say it's funny.
I think it's funny.
Well, I think it's unfortunate.
I am glad.
I'll just say it.
I'm glad.
Good.
It's good.
No, no, no apologies.
I didn't do anything wrong.
That's...
I don't care if she's mad at me.
She should be.
No way.
That's not what I meant to say.
I mean, she...
I should be mad, but I'm not.
Fucker.
Fucker is what I'm saying.
She's weird.
She's weird and I don't want to work with her.
And it's good.
She...
She can't fucking...
She can't hang.
She can't hang, so she's gone.
And that's what's up.
Ben, this is when I was talking about the gas
and the pouring the gas.
This is what I was talking about.
No, no.
This is...
I said...
People ask like,
are you gonna talk about this on the podcast?
What am I gonna not mention it?
I must.
I must acknowledge.
We must acknowledge the facts of the universe
that we now inhabit.
Of the dark timeline that we find ourselves in.
I don't know.
I mean, I don't feel like celebrating it necessarily.
I wouldn't mind if Trixie felt like coming back.
Like, I would be okay with her being on the show again.
I'd rather she didn't, but whatever.
Oh, you...
Everyone's entitled to their opinions, I suppose.
I don't know what caused this schism all of a sudden.
I don't know how everyone became enemies.
I'm very confused.
Well, you...
Well, you saw...
I mean, Alex, you saw the conversation we were having.
I saw...
And you saw...
And you saw the tweet she made immediately afterwards.
So, you've got all the pieces.
I guess.
I just don't understand how, like,
eight years of knowing someone can explode in a fireball
of, like, Radcon reward fallout.
It's very strange.
You know, it's not...
I don't know if that's entirely it.
Her tweet made it sound like it was all about that,
but it really wasn't.
Maybe I don't know what tweet you're talking about then,
because I'm not sure...
The one where she said...
The one where she said,
Ben is an incorrigible asshole,
and I won't be on the PCP anymore.
That one.
Oh, that one.
Well...
Yeah.
I mean, it's just a podcast.
So, like, whatever.
It's a problem with Ben's saying as far as it seems to be the case.
As long as Ben's saying is here,
Trixie will not want to be here.
And it's like,
well, yeah, I can see not wanting to, like,
clash heads if you don't need to.
But she hasn't been on the podcast in a while anyway.
Yeah.
So, I feel like this is more like,
oh, no, she's leaving the PCP.
Like, it feels like it's...
In the minds of many people witnessing it
is more of a big deal than it actually is.
It's just Ben and Trixie have fallen out.
Like, things have happened like this before.
I don't know whether it will come back to how it was before.
Like, I don't think this is like,
oh, the irreparable bridge-burning, the end.
Like, years from now, for 40 years,
they'll be still, like, throwing spears through each other's windows.
Like, it is not...
I don't know.
It doesn't feel like that big of a deal.
It just sort of, like, Ben annoys Trixie so much
he doesn't want to be on a podcast.
It's not really that big of a deal.
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't think I agree.
I think she's gone forever
off to be weird with her creepy, shady roommates.
And those are her new friends.
And that's the direction she's taken.
I don't know, they're totally creepy, shady.
Riley is a bit of a...
They're creepy, they're creepy, they're creepy, shady.
Riley is, like, eccentric.
I don't know whether creepy is the word I would use.
And I don't really know much about men salad and bird.
They seem like more chill than Riley.
Riley's, like, the big, crazy boy.
This was the thing.
The tweet made it sound like it was, like,
we were arguing about the...
the lecture, which we weren't.
She got mad and left because I was angry
that Riley was talking about planning his own Radcon
for us.
And I was angry and I insulted him to her
and denounced him in the strongest possible terms.
And that was what was too much for her.
And made her say, no, I'm leaving.
Ben's a mean asshole and won't be on a podcast.
Because he said mean things about my
quote-unquote producer, Lamal.
And I just think that's weird.
I'll just say this.
I've been to BronyCon and I enjoyed the experience.
I don't think me meeting Riley would be that bad.
I don't find that to be, like, terror.
I don't find him creepier or anything.
He seems like a wacky, crazy guy.
Creepy is not the right word.
I don't think he seems like an asshole.
Well, maybe.
But, like, he also seems like a nice person
to the people he cares about.
That's the impression I've been given.
I don't agree with that.
Yeah, well, whatever.
He seems tribal.
They all seem tribal.
Like, they're the in-group and everyone else is the enemy.
So in that way, yeah.
I guess I would say nice to his friends.
Against everyone else is the sense I get from them.
But I would not stay in a positive way.
But I see what you're saying.
I see where you're coming from.
I feel like...
They're not like the devil.
And I could see myself...
I'm not saying they're like the devil.
Reaching out to them personally.
That was bad of me.
But, like, you clearly have no...
Like, you have no intentions of ever, like, making peace with them.
I don't like them.
That was fine.
It's fine that I don't like them.
It's not a problem.
It only became a problem when one of them
tried to stick their fucking nose into my business
with the rad con stuff.
And Trixie, and I said, Trixie, this is...
I hate this.
And she was like...
Why don't you respect my friends?
Well, because they're fucking annoying
and they are...
They don't understand boundaries.
And keep them away from me.
That's it.
That's how I feel.
And Ben St. did nothing wrong.
Hashtag free Ben St.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's like, from my perspective,
I can see both sides of it.
Like, yeah, they...
Kind of...
It is kind of weird and annoying that they're like...
Rad con.
Wait!
We should just throw our own rad con.
We can have it at, like, our concert.
Like, okay, we'll just do that.
Like, no.
Like, fuck you.
What the fuck gives you...
What right do you think you have?
What do you think you have a say in any of this?
Of course you don't.
Shut the fuck up.
But I also see
their perspective a little bit.
I don't know.
I'm more willing...
I don't think that you're in the wrong.
I hate you for agreeing with them at all.
Cool.
I don't want to, like,
side with them or anything.
But I just... I feel like this is...
There's gonna be a lot of, like,
bitterness built up
based on the idea that this is so
massive an event.
And I'm like...
We're all just people.
It's not really that, like,
devastating.
Nothing's really been done...
I mean, at the end of the day,
it is just a podcast
and nothing...
And nothing else is affected by it.
I mean, sure.
I understand that.
Sure, yes.
You know, in a cosmic sense, I mean,
we're all just tiny specks
on a little blue ball
orbiting a star, one of just
billions in the Milky Way galaxy.
What does anything really matter
in the grand scheme of it all?
I know, I know.
I know.
I just feel like
an urge to...
I don't know.
Like, calm everyone down, because it's like,
people are getting really upset.
So, like, all over the place.
I'm like...
I don't know what can...
Like, this isn't...
I'm not that concerned,
honestly.
I'm also not concerned.
People get the impression
that you are raging at them.
Like, you are absolutely like...
Like, I want them dead.
Well, sometimes I do get mad at people.
I got mad
at those Radcon comments,
made me very mad.
Some of the people on Twitter
responding to me about it made me very mad.
Uh...
What of it?
I think the thing with you, Ben,
is that, like, in text or on Twitter,
madness comes across as more,
like, devastating and
diabolical than you do when you are
a human being, and I can hear you,
and you're just Ben.
You're just Ben.
You couldn't hurt a fly, even if you had,
like, a two-handed sword.
I could. I think I could.
You gotta find two fucking
chainsaws and get your casting
delayed down.
If I had a big wand, with a lot of capacity
and a high and a low
refresh rate, I could
kill many flies
with bullets.
Uh, I know what you mean.
This whole thing has been very
weird for me as someone who is not
prone to conflict
and tries to just, like, smooth things over.
Watching this all explode, like,
back to back, and I'm just like,
okay, um, I don't even...
I'd even had the time
to formulate an opinion
on Riley and Co.
I knew nothing about them, and then
all of a sudden, there was a fight,
and I was like, ah, interesting.
Okay, I have no
greater context for this.
And it was weird.
I mean, I mean, what more
context?
What more context do we need?
I don't know. My context was a couple tweets
and a cringe drama
video, and that was all the context I had,
and I feel like...
Wait, what cringe drama video?
The big fight thing.
The Ethan Ralph thing.
That was not really related,
but it was like, direct information.
No, I'm just saying, like,
it's like, how did I realize who half these people were?
It was through that video, so I'm like,
I'm not gonna judge anybody from that video.
That's like, the worst
the worst moment of all of their lives
in the last couple months, probably.
Yeah, which they
decided
it would be a great idea to upload.
It's pretty cringe. I will give you that.
Right? Okay.
I agree.
So, I mean, I think we can draw
some conclusions.
I mean, Trixie's known for posting cringe
before. This is different.
This is different cringe.
I guess it is a little different. It's very personal.
I was very surprised when I saw it.
Yeah.
I mean, I have... It is the thing,
like, traditionally, you would be like, oh,
God, let's not talk about this.
I hope it doesn't blow up. I'm surprised.
But then to be the first, like,
journalist on the scene.
The first journalist. I'm surprised
you guys are on a different wavelength
about this. You guys are all
you guys are pretty well
just like, eh, that's
whatever. Who knows
what means anything.
I have many opinions
about what's going on and I hate
all of it. I hate everything
that's happening over there.
I
hate that video.
I hate Yig Studios.
I hate everyone.
Hmm.
That's it.
I think my thing is more
the way I respond to things
is like, well, what
is the purpose? What
ends am I hoping to achieve
with the way I respond to anything?
Like, I don't know. If I tell
them that I hate them,
even if it's true. I didn't tell anyone.
I didn't actually tell anyone. That's new.
This is a new revelation.
Okay. I didn't tell, but okay.
Yeah, I know what you mean. Alright, go on.
I have, like, opinions
on the way that was handled and what it was.
I found it generally to be kind of funny,
but like cringe and like
why.
But, like,
I feel like if I wanted
to change something, I wouldn't, like,
I don't know.
But my opinion on it is
like saying it on Twitter
or saying that, like,
in a podcast, it makes
no difference, really.
If I really wanted to change something, I would try and talk to them directly.
Well, that's what I did. That's what I did.
I talked, I talked.
I'm not criticizing you. I'm just talking about how I handled this stuff.
I started by talking to Trixie in the PCP chat
and it led to the fight
and then she quit because she was mad.
That's what I did.
So I don't, what are you saying?
I guess
what I'm saying is, like,
I wouldn't have wanted Trixie to quit.
I would have wanted her to, like,
whatever problems I have,
I would have wanted them to go away
rather than for her to leave with them.
You know what I mean? Well, they weren't going to go away.
This isn't like a criticism of how you did anything.
I just want everyone to be friends.
We just want to go back.
We got to go back.
They weren't going to go away
because the Yig people
were completely overstepping
boundaries of good taste
and
society
and propriety
and it wasn't okay
but Trixie cares more about them
than she does about us
so she was not willing to
hear it
and so she left because she
can't deal with it
and that's a problem
and it wasn't going to go away
and I'm glad I brought it up
and if she needs to leave
over that then so be it
that's what she should do.
I got a PBRB.
Oh, god damn it.
Oh, no.
Now it's just me and Ben
and that awkward statement
and I don't know how to follow it up with anything
relevant or meaningful.
You guys are making it awkward
by not just agreeing with me.
If we were agreeing with you
this would be much more entertaining, I agree.
If we had like a 20 minute dunk session
that would have been much more entertaining.
I don't need a 20 minute dunk session.
I just need everyone to agree.
You two
you're so like, oh conciliatory.
Oh, can we all be friends?
That's true.
To my detriment I am conciliatory.
I will admit that outright.
I understand that but to my eye
there are irreconcilable differences here
that do not permit such a solution.
That being the case
I don't see
what has
I don't see this as like a bad
way, is like a bad
resolution. It seems to me like this is the only
thing that could have happened.
Well, I would agree. I think this probably was the only
way considering all the pieces that were on the board
this was going to go.
I think it's like
my general reaction to these things
is to like set back, assess, try to figure out
everything that's going on and I don't know enough about
these other people, the you guys
to make a
informed decision and so
my general stance is to
just do nothing. I was like, well I don't know what's going on.
Well I was totally willing, I was totally willing
to ignore them until they started
stepping on our fucking feet
and talking about going
over our heads and doing some shit that
they don't have any fucking business doing.
That's what did it for me.
It
I wouldn't, I was not going to
say anything
until then. I don't know.
I feel like
I've said all I can really say
about it.
I think
from my perspective
with regards to like RADCOM
organizing, it's always been sort of
out of my hands anyway because I live
so far away and it's sort of like
I don't know, I don't feel
as connected to like organizations
of those things
so like if it just happened to be like hey
if Riley said
hey we're doing like a
RADCOM like brony lecture redo
and we're going to pay for your flight, I'll be like yeah okay
like I wouldn't have too much of a problem
with them organizing that
I'd just fly over and just
exist for a while like I do
whenever I come over and
make some content
or content, I guess content's destroyed now
lol
Oh yeah, that also happens
but like
I feel like
you don't understand
I don't have as much of a problem
it's more than that
because it wasn't just like hey I'll fly
everyone out
first of all, I don't believe he was actually
going to pay, I think he was lying
but whatever
setting that aside
it wasn't like oh I'll fly everyone out
so they can re-record this lecture
okay, we'll have RADCOM
we'll have it
at my concert
like me and Trixie will put on a concert
and we'll just make RADCOM like a sideshow act
to that, we'll just subsume it into our thing
and host it there
yeah, I mean obviously from
and I just find it despicable
from the perspective of fans of RADCOM
that would not be what they want
the absolute gall of it all
the energy would definitely be different
I was just thinking
myself, I'd be okay with whatever
happens, but like
if people want a RADCOM 5
or 4.5
whatever it was going to be
a Trixie and Riley
music concert obviously
is not what people know or care about
in the audience that we have
so it would be like
of course not
absolutely not
never, never, never, never
I don't know
I guess I'm just too open minded
I'm just like yeah, why not
I would be willing to do that
I would be willing to go there
this is horrible
it's despicable
I'm just over here with my
wooden planks and rope
and I'm building bridges every day
look at what has happened
look at the state
of the YIG Studio channel
which is being run
by these people
I don't want them in charge of anything that I do
no thank you
I agree, I'm not really down with
their aesthetic or what they're doing
their content doesn't interest me
and I don't say that maliciously just as
merely a matter of taste
I guess
I don't know, the thing is
we're talking about this whole
what Riley wanted to do
but like
none of us ever had a conversation
passively
we're saying like Ben
Riley never approached you despite the fact that
publicly had been stated a few times that you had been approached
I don't think it really happened
that's what you were saying
it was never
I guess
the only thing that I'm confused about
is it just
it sounds like we're extrapolating some things
from this hearsay
I don't know what's true and what's not
people saw Riley saying stuff
and then they showed it to me in my discord
and I
said in the pcp chat
that I didn't like it
and Trixie communicated that
I didn't like what I was seeing
to Riley
and Riley took that as a
oh, Ben has refused my offer
of hosting a radcon
Ben
Ben just doesn't want there to be another radcon
I guess
that's the really
you know what, it's not the really
galling thing because there are many
truly galling aspects of the whole thing
but one particularly galling aspect
was the way that it was cast
the fact that I don't like
that these people
are planning radcon
for us without asking us about it
without even consulting us
as though they have any right to do that
is that like oh, well
I guess if Ben says he doesn't like the plan
then Ben is just anti-radcon
he is the one that is like holding it up
and preventing it
as though it's this or nothing
as though it's either like these strangers
these fucking strangers because that's what they are
these complete strangers can't plan
this thing then I guess
Ben just never wants it to happen, he must be against it
oh, he must just hate it
I mean, I don't think
anybody would deny that like
it feels like a lot of the moves
and things that are said seem to be
I don't know
I don't want to say manipulative
I will say manipulative
to gain sympathy
because as soon as this
happened you were kind of reframed as the enemy
which I don't think was the point
I guess I'm just
I don't know
it's strange because we never had a conversation about this
I feel like a conversation probably would have cleared a lot of this up
if it was going to be like
hey
we want to redo the Brony lecture
and we're going to be touring and doing concerts or whatever
and if we can all meet up here
and I'll pay for you
we're just doing this anyway but you can just
go do the thing by yourselves
and we just happen to be in the area
that would have been one thing
but if it was like oh, I'm going to produce
an entire new Radcon event
and now I'm in charge of it
that's where I'd be like
eh, I'm not too keen on that
because I don't want to like
tightly integrate these people that I don't know
into the production
my only thing is
I don't know which idea
was actually the one being proposed because like we said
none of us ever actually had
a conversation about this
because it was the former
I read the comments
I read what was said and it was the second one
that's why I was mad
okay, alright
I have no way
of knowing for sure
I posted the
screenshots, someone showed me the screenshots
and I reposted them and you can read them
and that's what they say
okay
I just don't
like it
I just don't like it
I'm not a fan of the situation myself
I think
I think it's all a bit like
it's all pretty cringe
it's not much, I don't know
oh I guess I should go to
Trixie about what I think but I don't know what I think
should I just say
well
I don't know
what am I supposed to DM her about
like
it just sort of feels like
there's nothing
I can do about it
I don't like being wrapped up in this
but whatever
nothing can be done
let's just
blow it all up
okay, let's do it
alright, kaboom
it's all dead, it's all gone
are we voicemails?
we could have Wreck on
but we can't call it Wreck
well I guess we can
it's like
it's a bastardization of Trixie's dead name
so it's kind of weird
there's nothing we can do
we gotta go into the graveyard
and we gotta get
our lightning rod
and we gotta dig up Brad Garlinghouse's corpse
we gotta revive him
we have to have BradCon too
it's the only option
honestly, BradCon
I'm ready, I'm ready for BradCon
look, we all gave Brad
a ton of shit for XRP
but now we're all into crypto
a lot, he's the leader we need
let's see how Ripple's doing
I was kind of annoyed
I was kind of like
annoyed that my
brother
he had gotten into crypto
through other means
not through anything I had heard about
and he had gotten some Ripple
and he made some money off of it and he told me
and I was like, oh cool I guess
because he didn't know about the whole XRP
Brad Garlinghouse stuff
that ruined the PCP
he doesn't know the context
so I was like, I felt mad about it
but obviously he didn't know
it was just sort of like
you were mad
because he was into XRP
and he didn't know that
I wasn't mad at him
it was just a little reaction I had
like, oh fuck no
you've betrayed me
well I guess you couldn't have known
that's funny, that's pretty funny actually
I just saw this live stream
on this random YouTube channel
and I got into it
Ripple is
it's up from
where it was like last year
but it's like
not that high
so it's neutral I guess
that's how Ripple's doing in case
in 2020 we destroyed XRP
in 2022 we need to max revive it
here's its entire
here's its entire life story
in graph form
it went up and down and down and up and down
it went down and then it went up again
yep
looks like stockmarket.png
to me
doing great Brad
it's trading at 6 cents
a bit
oh my god it's almost worth the same as Dogecoin
dude bits
you remember my little pony
do you remember when they had
bits
I thought you meant on Twitch
no no no no
Twitch copied my little pony back when it was called
JustinTV
and that's where all the new episodes were live streamed
I remember what you know
yeah do you remember
that was like the parent side of Twitch
and Twitch was like a subsidiary gaming branch
and then Twitch just took over because it got so big
I've never heard of JustinTV
back in the old days
there was a little pony like
oh this is a new episode coming out
and there was like 7 different streaming services
that would stream the episode from Hasbro
TV
and all these nerds would come
and watch on JustinTV
the ponies
that's what's gonna heal us
we're all gonna get into gen 5
it's gonna be good and we're all gonna be healed
isn't already out? isn't already going?
no the movie's coming out soon
I think
there's 3D
yeah we talked about this
and now it looks like
any fucking
DreamWorks movie
I don't know if the show's gonna be
animated in the same style
so it's a walloff
I bet it'll be
I bet it'll be 3D
it is 3D
oh the show yeah maybe
yeah yeah
what's the name?
well that's something to be excited about
I guess that's something
that's coming in the future
get hype
uh
we still on board to do
a pony movie review episode
I'm down
pony movie review bonus episode
hell yeah
hell fucking yeah
I'm not gonna go see it in theaters though
we're gonna be old people
we're gonna be
I can't even imagine going to a movie theater anymore
the kids these days they're like in the 3D
ponies and that's stupid
back in my day we had
back in the day we had flash puppets
flash puppets
and they made the funny meme
faces in season 4
do you remember the memes
do you remember when they gave the purple one wings
and everybody bitched for months
remember when the pink one made the funny face
you know what they're not gonna be able to have a derpy in 3D
you're not gonna be able to have an animation error like that
oh are they gonna do you think they're gonna try
to do any of that like
like recreate the brony fandom
like beat for beat
it'd be pretty cringe if they did
have like oh here's
a accidental glitch
pony and what are you
what do you fans want to call that
and then like they tweet about it and
don't even summon that kind of energy
into the physical plane
well the thing is if they do do that
it'll come like corporate
feeling and then nobody would get into it at all
yeah exactly
it has to all be organic
I mean companies don't understand that
I'm sure they're already working like alright how are we gonna
how are we gonna get the brony bucks
we gotta figure out how to plant these little seeds
and it'll suck but
I hope not
it's kind of doomed from the start
because the brony thing only came about
because nobody was expecting
a pony show to be
good in any way
it was a surprise that's what
that was the gimmick at the beginning
gen 5 is just like oh yeah
I wonder if they'll do that gimmick again
I wonder if they'll just do it again
I wonder if it'll still be good
very unlikely
I don't know if it's evolved creatively with us
it has pros and cons and it's like
there's better cartoons out there
I don't know who's involved in the studio
like making this show
because I'm obviously Lauren Faust isn't involved
I don't know if like
Megan McArthur or the fuck her name was
if she's still helming the ship with this new series
or it's somebody else
who knows
but that'll probably affect whether it's good or not
it's a different animation studio of course
yeah
whatever
who cares there's nothing to talk about
the show wasn't even that good
what?
it wasn't even that good it was just fine
no you don't understand
there was a rainbow pony in it
you don't understand
it's true
no I do understand all that
that show was like 20% cooler
than other shows
do you remember when applejack wore those
thigh high horse shoes
that was strange
galoshes
no
god no
fuck
shut up
okay
no more
pony talk at the dinner table
eat your slop
hey you hear that
about buffy the vampire slayer
what
let's go on
I've been watching
your old buffy the vampire slayer
and it's been very nice
I'm on season 5 now
because it's base
why would you do that
why wouldn't you just play noida
it's like if noida was a tv show
and it was better than noida
you could have a chainsaw
you could shoot multiple bullets
per frame
60 bullets a second
getting a new episode of
the buffy the vampire slayer is just watching
bensank die right in front of me
that's why I like it
hmm
okay
solid
anyway
I want people in the audience
to get into buffy the vampire slayer
and then you will realize that
it's the coolest thing ever but it's hard to talk about
because there's so much continuity
that you don't want to ruin anything
people have been telling me to watch
buffy the vampire slayer since I was like 13
well you're late
no I was right
I've been right all along
nope
I can't
literally my entire personality
is that I haven't seen buffy the vampire slayer
and I can't go back
on that I'd give them everything
hmm
oh no
that's the weakness
it's a vampire but instead of sunlight
it's watching buffy the vampire slayer
that's correct
if a monitor appears
with buffy the vampire slayer on it
and the light of that monitor touches you
you burn and turn to dust
yeah
it would do heavy
a holy damage to me
that's correct
if I make a steak out of
melted down buffy the vampire slayer
DVDs
I think so
to be fair that would kill probably anybody
yeah
that would probably kill most people
I'm actually just more
vulnerable
than most people
I have all the vampire weaknesses
and none of its strengths
if you stab Ben with that he turned into a poor
90's CGI skeleton
and then collapsed the dust
like vampires do in buffy the vampire slayer
yes yes
Willow has funny jokes
and Xander also has funny jokes
and buffy is buffy
and there's Giles and he's British
Giles the British man
now we know why you like it
oh yes I got the library
turn it over
find out about the vampire's buffy
and buffy's like I don't want to do any of this stuff
he's like well you have to train buffy
you have to be a vampire slayer
oh I'm British
that's the whole show
well if it's got
I guess we just watched it then
then maybe I am interested
no no no I live for racist characters
of British people
British
if more people say British then the world will be more British
I'm British
I'm gonna drink a bottle of water
a bottle of water
wear your tees
you fucks
we're drinking all of them
we don't have any left for speech
damn that was pretty good
alright I've been owned
so Kantan's dead
yep
it's on hiatus
it's not on hiatus
Trixie's been quote unquote fired
and reiterated that she let herself be fired
which I think
the word is quit
I think quit is the word
I believe that is the word
yeah that's how I would describe it
well
I mean she said that
it was Nate who didn't want to work with her
and Riley and all that
I don't understand
this is it
this is it again
what did the crew
in conjunction with
this Kantan
what did they have to do with it
it's suspicious
I don't know
it just speaks to a larger pattern that I'm seeing
here where these
individuals
are just being inserted
into places where they don't belong
it seems like it's a package deal
you know
and I hate that and if it's a package deal
I say no thanks to the whole package
so this is
more reinforcement of why I did the right thing
as I always do
yeah
I guess there's just not enough information
right now like I can understand
Trixie with
her new boyfriend
well no I can't
I can't understand that
that was unacceptable when it was May
and it's unacceptable when anyone does it at any time
sure
I guess I know but like
and now it's a business thing
Kantan is a business thing right
there's a show
you wouldn't
Trixie never brought May to
shows
well she tried her hardest to bring her to Radcon
that's true
the only reason May wasn't at the shows
is because we put our foot down about it
yeah
this is what I'm talking about
this is a pattern of behavior
just
I don't know what to think about it
exactly because I don't know anything about that situation
or who said what about it
could ask Nate but I don't know
whether he want to talk about all that
shit
I tried reaching out to Nate and he was very mama on the situation
he's just like I don't want to talk about it
and I was like alright fair enough
I mean it's obvious
I mean I guess I can only speculate
this is just my speculation but it's
seem really obvious
that it's the fact that she's moving
into an RV
and going to be roaming across the
country
that's the plan
but she frames it like oh it's Nate's fault
that Nate doesn't want to work
under those circumstances
when like
you're the one who's changing shit up
you're the one who's doing this
it's not that Nate doesn't want
to work with you anymore it's that you
made all
you have radically changed
the situation
yeah I mean
I would like to think
that there was some sort of discussion about this
before it was immediately implemented
but I have a feeling there probably wasn't
which is unfortunate
well I don't know
that's one thing I don't know
I'm talking about my ass because I don't know
anything about any of this other than the surface
image of it
I'm speculating but it seems obvious
and what Trixie said
on Twitter pretty much corroborates it
so I'm treating it as like
99% certain
it just seems like
everything
indicates that that is the issue
I'm curious about
the RV thing like the idea of getting into
an RV and traveling around like okay
whatever
being able to do cantant I can't
help but say it like that I like saying it like that
just fine being able to do
cantant
like in the RV
means like traveling back
to Virginia to do like a bunch of episodes
then going in the RV and traveling away again
I guess
like how else would it work
that seemed to be the plan
but then they were doing
like
like anime that came out
like seasonal anime
so it would need to be
prompt it would need to be like as soon as
the anime episodes are out
yeah that's right
so like how far could she reasonably go
in an RV and then come back to do things
and also watch the anime at the same time
I don't know it feels
like there's a lot of
how would that work
seems like kind of a problem
seems like it might throw a wrench
into things a little bit
I mean Victor has been on cantant
before and Victor's cool
so that might continue like that
well Trixie said
Trixie said that
like she assumed Victor
I think she just assumed Victor
I don't know I mean I'm not just going to take her word for it
Victor
and Vic and Hope have been like doing anime videos
still like Vicks on that
that stuff
I could see that
I hate anime
and like if I were Nate
I would put all this effort into
you know building up cantant into a thing
I wouldn't want to just abandon it
I would probably
want to keep it going in some capacity
even if my co-host were to leave
whether or not he feels the same way
or whether
that's a possibility I mean I don't know
maybe Vic wouldn't want to do that
that would be
I mean who knows
so I mean I guess
it just remains to be seen what the fate of that
is
I just I can't help but feel for Nate a little
because he moved to Virginia
for this show
I kind of agree
but on the other hand
I think that's what you get when you work with Trixie
this is just what she does
I mean back when it was like
PCPHQ
like way back like it didn't seem like
same shit
well maybe I don't know maybe I wasn't paying attention
so that's the same thing
I mean we all
well I think what it was
is like we
we'd all assumed
like all of us had assumed that once there was an established
location
it would become
more stable for everyone
and then we could like
that was the idea behind PCPHQ from the beginning
was like
we get
creators together close proximity
to the studio be able to record things
with each other whenever we feel like
obviously quite difficult
especially now
because we're all doing different types of things
and like getting together for content is like
not as much of a draw
as it used to be
but like
for like I'm pretty sure
like even though Trixie hasn't been known to like
change ideas for things
I would have thought
and I would have assumed that because Nate was there
it would have been more stable
more consistent more
like that's a permanent
fixture on the whole
on the map and
if Trixie wants to do something different
she can do something different but also
still appear on canteen and it'll be fine
but I guess
none of them are so
I don't know
I don't know what
I'm not sure what point you're
getting at
there's no point to anything
it's all stupid
we're all just specks of dust
we're just orbiting in the space
it's a galaxy
trillions and billions
billions
we're all little stars that blink
in a galaxy
I just find it to be
unfortunate and I don't like it
I liked
content for them
I thought that was cool
finally getting some sort of
it's not unfortunate
it's choices
people have made choices
specifically Trixie has made choices
that have caused this outcome
those are mutually exclusive though
yeah
I mean unfortunate for
Nate who did not choose
whatever
you can say that this is obviously a result
of a logical conclusion to choices made
but it can still be unfortunate that those choices
were made in the first place
well I guess you're right
I guess you're right
excuse me
I apologize
dab
very well
I don't mind being the enlightened
centrist on this one
I don't care
so cringe
but
so be it
if you want to
just one more nail in your coffin
then go right ahead
if you want to put a nail
like half into the coffin
yeah
in the middle
I don't necessarily want to put the nail
all the way into the coffin
I can kind of see why you'd want to put the nail in the coffin
but I can kind of see why you wouldn't
so maybe I'll just kind of
tap the nail
so in case something bad happens
I can quickly nail the coffin
ironically how I feel about all this
because I feel so detached from it
I can't feel rage
one side of the other
it's not even just like
I feel furious
I'll just in case
maybe it's not coming through
maybe it doesn't come through when I speak in my voice as much
okay good I want it to come through
I'm afraid it's not coming through hard enough
well yeah honestly trust my tweets
my treats reflect my feelings more than
my voice does
you have a voice of an angel Ben
oh no
god shucks no go on though
I don't know
I'm very
I'm I
I guess
I don't need to belabor the point anymore
but I am mad
I there
I said it
I'm mad
it's out there guys there's no coming back
there's none
there's this um
this cat youtube video channel
I've been watching
where this cat has these buttons
and the buttons make noises
like words
and this person has been training the cat
to associate these words
with emotions and feelings and things
so the cat has learned
that when she's upset
with something she can click the mad button
and she just goes mad
mad mad
and her tail wags affirming
that she is mad about something
and I just thought that was funny
I'm just imagining Ben saying with this button
pressing it to let the world know
that he is mad now
that's me on twitter yeah
that's what twitter is for me
it's the mad button
I'm gonna find the video because it's really cute
fucking baste
link it so someone can superimpose Ben's face
mad mad mad
what a perfect
metaphor
for being mad
at least I cut this awkward sound
no we're gonna have to piece a party
podcast we can't do that
we are
and we can
but I thought last time we talked about this
we aren't and we don't
no we do we do
we must
something has changed in the two weeks I was not on the podcast
yeah we have crossover
cheesy is like a
he's like on the pizza party
podcast now
he's our man on the inside
that's what I was gonna say he's our man on the inside
he's our spy so we're gonna take it down from the inside
that's exactly right
or is cheesy trying to take down
us from the inside
I don't even want to
think about that possibility
the consequences of which would be
disastrous
if it's all cheesy's fault
he's done a lot of damage in the last two weeks
no I disagree
Riley is just a construct made by cheesy Manfredo
I unironically think
that everything that has happened is good
and I am happy about it
and I am not
sorry for anything
there's people
I feel like you guys have this attitude
and people on Twitter have this attitude that like
oh no I hope you can resolve
your differences I hope we can fix this and I legitimately
do not want to fix this
I do not want this to be undone
you consider this fixed
yes yes I consider this to be the solution
this is good
I like it
and it's frustrating
that I think I'm in the minority
about that
but I'm right
I don't like finality
in these sorts of things
I guess that's the only reason
I mean at the end of the day
Trixie not being on the podcast anymore
changes virtually nothing
you know like nothing's really
changed
the bigger issue I guess
I have is just that like it feels like
you know
they were our friend for so long
and now she's not and it's just like
I mean
well I mean think about what that says
think about what that says that like
friendship ended over this
that's my point I think it's really stupid
how much did it how much
how much did it actually mean
then well that's that's kind of like
the whole like reflection point like oh I
guess there wasn't much there to begin with and that's
really unfortunate there you go
so I feel the same way
bummer
man I watched Godzilla vs Kong
what a cool movie
it was so stupid it was the best
it was it was
it was a monkey and a lizard punching
it was all I could have ever wanted
I've heard I've heard mixed
I've heard seen some people saying it was base
and I've heard some people saying it was cringe
it was the dumbest movie I've seen in a long time
whether they were
gunning for the monkey or the
crocodile yeah who who wins
who wins Godzilla definitively
wins
so okay so
you were right
uh yeah I guess
I mean I'm sick
you you were saying on Twitter
you were arguing on Twitter that like
you know obviously Godzilla
is gonna has to win there's no way
you couldn't
but it was really cool it was cool the way
they did the fight like they made it like
like Godzilla is like a big tanky guy
who moves slow but Kong could like swing between
buildings and was like dodging all the hits and stuff
like as soon as he took a good hit from Godzilla he went down
I'm like yeah that's
if they were gonna fight that's probably how it would go down
you know it was it was pretty fucking cool
and there's lots there's lots of polygons moving
around there's lots of shading and lighting and like
good punching and buildings blew apart
uh every time a human was on
screen it was the cringiest thing of all time
but luckily like half
the movie like the main character of
the movie was King Kong and it was really
cool he like he like
new sign language and signed to a little
girl and it was smart
it was so fucking cool like this
little girl taught him they lived on an island with
it was the dumbest movie of all time
and I loved it
watch it it's great
okay turn two
I'm gonna be honest I
probably won't watch it but I
I don't expect you to maybe
someone in the audience will
take that advice
I was just watching the one letter of media
I had a half in the bag about it and it looks
like visually look pretty funny
it's fucking sick
pretty funny
it's the worst Mechagodzilla design though
definitely the worst Mechagodzilla design of all of them
where would this
rank in Godzilla films
would you say Mr. Godzilla
hmm
um I mean all the
legendary films have been kind of like
okay
but not great like
I don't think these are better than like the classic
Japanese monster movies
just because like it's weird
it's weird
because like Godzilla's supposed to be like this
like allegory for like you know like the
dangers of like nuclear weapons and stuff
and it's hard for
American audiences to empathize that
when they are the nukers and not the nukees
so like
they change Godzilla's allegory
in these legendary films from a
nuclear thing to
to an ecological allegory
like he's like at the top of
like the ecological food chain
like Titans are like reversing the
damage done by man to the environment
and shit and that's kind of cringe
but it's more like relevant to western audiences
but it kind of like
reduces Godzilla what he was supposed to be
like thematically but like half the movies
are just like him fighting with
robots and like has nothing to do with that
message anymore anyway so I don't get too bent out of shape about it
but um
it's kind of strange but there's
the punchings really good and like this is
the only time you're ever going to see like
these classic monsters rendered
in such high detail animating really subtly
that you can't get out of rubber suits
so for the novelty of that alone I enjoy
them a lot because it's kind of how my child brain
imagined all the fights happening
on screen when I watch them when I was five like seeing
that realized in real time is kind of cool
okay
but
King Kong
flanged or unflanged he's
flanged because he's not in orangutan
no that's why he lost
yeah
he was a flanged orangutan
he's been flanged
Godzilla's not flanged
no not at all
so it was Godzilla supposed to be like a gorilla
he looks like one
I mean no Godzilla
King Kong yeah yeah
he's a gorilla man
I'm going to find some gorilla facts
one of the he's perhaps the greatest of them all
oh no
he's the king
oh god
alright let's look up some gorilla facts
here we go
I might not find anything really funny
I know that gorillas can bench press
like five thousand pounds
they're like so fucking strong it's insane
but like they're also
they have to eat like
constantly
they constantly have to be eating
because they're muscles
they're talking energy
inefficient
the movie had the funniest opening scene
of any movie ever
it was like some song was playing
and it was just Kong waking up
and going through his day like a person
like taking a shower and a waterfall
oh okay
like treating him like he's just a person getting up
like you know how they do that in movies
like the movie starts and someone like wakes up
and goes about their morning routine
but it was just a big giant monster
it was a ten out of ten way to start
hilarious
I just opened up the Wikipedia article for gorilla
and I saw a picture of a gorilla
and I thought what if I was
standing where the photographer was
looking at this gorilla
with him looking back at me
and I'm so fucking scared
I would hope that they're using a zoom lens
in a very far away
if he wanted to
and he probably does
he could just lope over to me in like seconds
and then he'd head off and rip me limb from limb
and it would just be a funny joke to him
yeah but look at his expression
he's gonna do it
he looks like he's thinking about it
it's like
you're looking like a snack right there
he's like
it would be funny if I just
if I just bifurcated
that guy right now
and he's right
it would be funny that's the fucked up part
to be effective
if I had a
if I just had a wand
if I had a wand with
all I need is one
mana
one mana reducer
and one
and a chainsaw
and a good old fashioned multicast
in the fight of gorilla versus ben
give ben a wand and prep time
he can beat anybody
I can beat any animal
prep time
easy that's my superpower
they're fucking scary
I've learned the only gorilla fact I need to know
which is that they're scary as fuck
they're so big and they can look at you
and be like
they're so big
that I poop my fucking pants
and even think about them
today's gorilla fact
gorillas will make you poop your pants
with fear
that's pretty fucked up
it's pretty fucked up how they evolved to do that
but I mean I guess nature is pissed
well it's like human reflex
if you poop your pants
then you way less
so that you can run away faster
makes sense
oh
they're poached for bush meat
like Australia
what's bush meat
bush meat is meat from wildlife
species that are hunted for human consumption
oh so meat
so meat is what you're describing
I think they mean like
non farmed animals
yeah I guess
it'd be like not allowed
meat
oh bush meat
is not
bush meat is not to be confused with bush food
which is
any food native to Australia
and used as sustenance by indigenous Australians
so
okay
alright
no bush
I guess people fucking hunt gorillas for meat
that's so fucked
a silverback gorilla is typically
more than 12 years of age
so he's basically a twink
that he's gonna kill you
if you hunt a gorilla
and kill it for meat
that sounds like a way for a human to become flanged
that's pretty alpha
taking down a gorilla
I think you have to beat him
you have to fight him gorilla style
which you can't do
you simply can't
you have to beat him with no prep time
Tarzan it's possible
true Tarzan did fucking wreck shit
and he could surf on vines
he was pretty cool
I think he could surf on vines
but I don't think he could beat a gorilla in a fist fight
no no no do you remember the movie
where he got
no I haven't actually
seen the movie
you haven't seen Tarzan the movie Disney
TM
we just mentioned the movie and got a copyright claim
from Disney
this is a classic film Ben
well
did you not see the film
no I have not seen the film wait I've got
oh my god
what are you looking at a gorilla again
are you pooping your pants
no I'm sorry I got a message on
I got a discord message that is like
disturbing me a little bit
I'm sorry is it relevant
or secret
okay wait hold on
hold on
at least I cut this stuff
a few moments later
you guys still there yep
sorry about that
boo
sorry
I had to
I got some
weird shit was going on with my discord
but I guess it's fixed now
sorry everyone
for that awkward pause at Eleazar Cut
ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
the awkward pause they wouldn't know about
if you didn't know
but I'm mentioning it
Ben answer the question
what's the question
have you seen Tarzan the film
I think I've seen
most of it
I don't honestly I'm not sure
I might not have seen it actually
do you remember it from the Kingdom Hearts level
I remember Tarzan surfing
on vines
I vaguely remember the Kingdom Hearts level
I remember Phil Collins
yeah
you basically remember
I think I've probably watched
the first half of it a couple times
the Phil Collins soundtrack
is unironically based
I've listened to it by myself
like by itself
before and it's just
that guy knows how to play a drum and sing
honestly
my dad used to listen
to Phil Collins and as a kid I like
hated it I hated all the music my dad
liked but now I hear
Genesis and I'm like
okay this is kind of epic though
this is kind of fucking epic
it means you're getting old
it means I have taste now
that's how old people defend the fact that they're getting old
but my dad also likes
smooth jazz
and easy listening and I hate that shit
so it's not
it's not total crossover
everybody just likes Genesis
what's that one
about the
easy lover
that's a good song
no singing
say something
for god's sake
are we ready already
we're giving up this fast
I guess we're an hour in you wanna go to voicemails
I was about to say it's pretty
pretty normal to go to voicemails
I guess we're an hour
this has gone by really fast
we only talked about one thing
this hour has blasted by
I haven't had much to talk about this week
because of the
previously said
trying to live
ouch
which sucks
I wanted to get back
I wanted to work on that comic idea
I think I have an idea
I need to get going
because the deadline for that thing
is the end of April
this is good
to mention it
I wanted to mention it again
the kato anthology
I believe the deadline is the end of April
if you want to submit your comics
to that
I mean
I don't know
what if I make a one page comic
and nothing happens
you could have something
you could have something happen in one page
no, no, it can't be done
it's a show about nothing
no, nothing happens Jerry
it's a four panel comic
and it's the same panel four times
I've done that before
I've made that twitter joke before
just have it be like
27 pages of the red man comic
link in the description
if you the listener are
or know a comic artist
who might be interested in having their work printed
for pay
you keep all your intellectual property rights
in the kato anthology
they're gonna be starting a kickstarter for it
I don't exactly know when but soon
soon after the deadline
which is the end of April for submissions
check it out
if you please
so what are you saying
you're a bitch
I'm gonna do it
I'm just sort of
fucking stupid
oh, I see
technically I could have been trying to work
while sick
but I feel like I don't want it
well, that's hard
yeah, it's hard
that doesn't work well
I had something happen
especially like just
today
and like last night and this morning
I got messaged by
on twitter
by one of the
people
who I constantly see
replying to Christine Weston Chandler
on twitter
calling her all kinds of terrible things
saying all kinds of nasty stuff about her
you're a pervert
you're a predator
you're a pedophile
and I
and you know
I don't like these people
it's really bizarre
they respond to everything Chris does
and I hate them and I don't like it
it's an ugly look
so this person messages me
I don't even remember why
and it doesn't really matter
but she said something
about that
and then she was like wait
you're the guy who did that lecture
you a white knight now
that doesn't make any sense
and I'm like listen
I respond to her and I'm like listen
quit stalking Chris
on twitter
it's pathetic
it's bizarre
it's not a good look and it doesn't
accomplish anything so just knock it off
and she
replied to me
well first I mean
she said
in her poorly spelled
grammatically
semi-coherent
rant back to me
she included
many a transphobic
comments which did not
sit well with me but
in a mix among there
was the sentiment that
like Chris sent me
unsolicited dick pics
and so that's why I hate them
and think they're a pervert
and continually
doing this
and I had to take a step back and be like
you know
that is a legitimate grievance that this person has
so
maybe I partly feel a little bad
for scolding them about it
but at the same time
it's still not productive
what they're doing
it's still not helping anything
you can have a legitimate grievance
while taking action that in no way
you can get rid of that problem
or settle that grievance
right
so I guess I felt a little abashed
like
I hadn't considered that
maybe Chris actually had done something
which I guess she did
but I guess it doesn't change my opinion
that much
I still think they should just stop
I don't know
so I guess I felt
weird about that
I don't know
how else to describe
I don't know what else to say about that
but that was a funny story
that happened to me
believe it
alright
voicemails
for sure
bass
let's get over to
speakpipe.com
slash
pcp voicemail
speak
there's so many
it's okay we'll blast through
we'll go so fast
speakpipe.com
you're correct
if we go to the second page
the first one here is called
five months late
are we ready
here we go
three two one go
I haven't caught up to the newest pcp episodes
but when I just watched, Tom essentially said
that people who have a problem with the gender binary
should try to get rid of gender language altogether
instead of adding more choices that people have to learn
as a probably cis male
I think that both of these are valid ways of abolishing gender
so I support both
if you get rid of gender language then boom
gender language is gone, cool
but if you keep adding more choices that essentially reaches the same result
where the way you refer to someone becomes an expression of identity
title
or even just something akin to a name
by virtue of there just being so many choices
that are based on gender
and becomes an individualistic thing
I do remember what he's talking about
and what I was saying wasn't that
that was the better choice
the point was that it would be
easier for people to understand
because I think a lot of people get confused
by
non-binary gender pronouns
and by trying to reduce choices
and make things simpler
it's easier for most people to understand and to make things more complicated
I don't know
I don't know anyone
I don't see anybody using
like neopronouns
they don't seem to be
I don't feel like they caught on
no, I kind of think
maybe that's for the best
it's just ammo for
bad actors to use
well, well
I don't like that argument
I don't like that argument because
that sort of places the blame
I don't think it's a blame thing
it's a little bit like
they were asking for it
that's harsh
that's harsh to say
but I feel like it's kind of the same
like
I think I should criticize it
because it's like
it's less efficient or whatever
I don't know
no
maybe I just didn't
I never got it
I guess I'm just personally I never got it
I'm personally glad that it hasn't caught on
so I haven't had to reckon with it
I mean
all of the sort of gender stuff
at one point for me
was confusing
but I've gotten used to what little
changes I've had to make
right
I feel like naturally
people have just accepted that it's easier
to just say
he, she and they
as the three main things
and
special words
are sort of
not really
that you can have them
and I guess
if I met a person who
tried to use them
I would use them for that person
like in wider society
it's so confusing having more than three
I don't think people are ready to
like branch out
I don't think they need to but I'm not known
non-binary so I don't know
whether there's some like yearning
for a special word that isn't they
maybe some people feel like that
I hope they
as the default becomes
more normalized
I think we should all just
default to that and use it
as more
I think it's great
I like it
everyone's a they
it's better this way
it's they
and then their literal name
it's they way
or the highway
yeah
got them
okay next voicemail is called
noita sucks lol
okay three two one go
no it is a piece of your game because
when you go on top of the mountain to get the orb that's cool
but then you have to go across the desert to get the other orb
that's bullshit you have to go way too far
and it takes too much time to get just 25 health
in any ways because you don't want to give yourself a disadvantage
but of course it didn't matter anyways
because you got shit rng that run
and the first three floors there's no fucking good ones
and you have nothing and you get to the fourth floor
and you die and you know what
that doesn't matter because you already died because you crossed the fucking lava lake
and you got killed by that
you're a freaking nerd don't go for the desert orb
you still fucking killed you because
you got stuck on a fucking rock
and it's like
in the fucking game it's terrible like the first floor
it's like you get terrible rng every time
you go for the gold
you go for the gold biome
first thing every run you freaking dweeb
no you just go down the holy mountain
you just go down the mountain
and pray for a chainsaw
if you put it on your wand you go
because you're stupid and you didn't pick electric immunity
you fucking idiot
and that doesn't matter because
the only way you can win this shitty game
is if you get good rng
like literally you're just trying to get like
winning is so easy
every fucking game
or some other garbage
there's so many more ways to do it
you just don't know
you just don't understand
that's true, mana plus is the most
you don't need it
it's just way easier if you have it
this person is a fucking dweeb
that felt like a
ye old PCP argument
right in my living room
it really did
god, imagine
is it a nightmare and do I cry
if I don't get any chainsaws
or I don't get any spark bolt with triggers
or I don't get any mana reducers
yes
but you can still win
you can still win without those things
it's winning is trivial
winning is trivial
you're a freaking...
imagine what a fucking dork you have to be
to start your run and be like
op, but I mean
you can't start the run
by going to the...
what do you go down in the mountain
and you look for levitatium so you can get over the hill
and walk over the... you're not supposed to do that
you're just supposed to go down the mountain
yeah, you can be a...
oh, I'll spend an hour walking over to the
desert and get that extra 25
you just go
and you shoot everything
and you get
the hearts and you get
the chainsaws and you go
and that's it
and you just do it really fast
and you just blast through and if you get bad rng
good, it took you 5 seconds to get here
so you just do it again
that's how you
fucking win the game
in my opinion
okay
next voicemail
doidgazers2
3, 2, 1
go
hey guys, this is me again
D
the golden bitch
and um...
that's me, as I'm known
it was funny
and this is doid
chasers again
and so
this is the segment we're going to do
after we smoke weed now
and we're going to talk about
how much of an asshole
ben saint is
ben saint, you are bad
I don't like you
and my bird
does not like you either
and neither does riley
we all don't like you
so kindly go to therapy
because you need it
and don't ever talk to me
or my son ever again
um
I want you to know that
yeah
sounds like hands more man
a little bit
was this, this was 4 days ago
when did that whole thing, was that
after that? I don't
I don't even remember
I don't even remember the time
was that just yesterday
so this was before
so this was before she literally
said all that
hahahaha
prescient, prescient
I guess something was in the air
um
bass
okay next one is called names
3, 2, 1, go
and also if you do not want to call me dietris
you can also call me d
you can call me the golden bitch
you can call me
the golden bitch d
you can call me her royal friends
you can call me dricksy
you can call me dixie
you can call me razzmatazz
you can call me birdblower
or you can call me
late for dinner
an embarrassment of riches
okay you're welcome
next voicemail is called
radcon5
3, 2, 1, go
also Ben
we're having radcon5
without you now
testing my rv park
no come on
there will be no lectures
unless they are about drugs
send me the $30,000
also the whole thing will be about
otaku, ganzo
underground, hip hop
and experimental death noise
riley will be there
not ben saint
and also won't be called radcon anymore
because conrad's dead
so it will be called
trisby
yeah
and ben you're not invited
okay
this hit is a little too close to home
a little too close to home
we gotta move on
next one is called hyben
3, 2, 1, go
hey it's me
the viz vizier of
ygq's studio
how many of these are there
oh there's more
easily done it multiple times in the future
like the other ones
I've had enough of these people in real life
and if you
think you can take me
ben on a one on one
change match
and the planes of reality
I will fuck you up
friend
trisby doesn't need
fake friends like you anymore
we're on a different plane of existence
man
I will
I have a girlfriend
you
soon
oh god the next one is called from bird
3, 2, 1, go
hey ben
it's me
bird
base
fuck you ben
is that the real bird
it's a real bird
about my beautiful
girlfriend again
okay
I just imagined a little parakeet saying that
that was a little convincing
that was a little more convincing than the other ones
this made me reconsider some things
okay next one
is called the monopoly man
3, 2, 1, go
ho ho ho
here's the monopoly man
I'm glad to say that
all of good nade fucker boys
have been entered
I especially like the one that promises
the body right
the rights to nade's body
so I will award
the dodge coin
to
monopoly man
and with that I will become president
ho ho ho
this was the monopoly man
congratulations
I can't get enough of that little forced laugh
ho ho ho
he's just
he just plays it totally
straight he's committed to the bit
and you know what is working for me
congratulations
on your
your totally non-fraud
fraudulent election
sir the next voicemail is from
Janess
3, 2, 1, go
my worst fear came to
Trixie left the
PCP
I'm still struggling to
get over it
but at the end of the day
it was her choice
and I hope she'll eventually decide to come on
even if it's like on an episode
to say goodbye
I just want you all to be true to yourselves
and maybe it's time to
start looking for recruitment again
and again
hmm
we've such an illustrious history of bringing people in
we've never looked for recruitment in the first time
no
there will be no recruitment
there will be no
you gotta be grandfathered in
that's true you gotta be grandfathered in
new members
they only poison the well
we gotta keep the bloodlines pure
we can only breed with each other
no
that's how it's gotta be
they can't fuck
anyone else
hmm
I
while I
while I do not
while I can't pretend
to understand
being
sad that Trixie has left
I nevertheless
recognize that it is a valid
response and I empathize
with the general concept
of sadness
LeMau
uh
that's my statement on the matter
said at the funeral
yeah
end with LeMau
it's always appropriate
oh god next one is called uh doid
gazers again
three two one go
hello and welcome to doid gazers
uh
I'm your host me and with me is my co-host
and new best friend uh Riley
say hello Riley
what's up golden bitch
it's me Riley
and I'm riding a surfboard
through the plains of reality man
what's up with you
oh nothing much Riley
um so today on the show
we're going to be lighting up a fun video
and we're going to talk about how much
we hate bin saint
um bin saint is not really
cool is he Riley
well I'll tell you what
golden bitch
bin saint
really boils my blood
and if I had the opportunity to defeat him
in pitch combat I would
using only my skills as a
lyricist
yes so um
then we're going to smoke some more meat
it's like I'm there
with the doid gazers
um so yeah um don't forget
to subscribe to my weird patreon
blog post thing um
I've almost made seven
dollars thank you
you're welcome
hey
my pleasure
next voicemail is called hi ben
three two one go
wow this civil war arc
has been quite a twist
I wonder what the writers
will think of next
um only
only god knows
sir
next voicemail is called ben was
right three two one
go
hey ben uh
you were right and Trixie
was wrong I agree
I'm not in the rad con discord
because I don't back stuff
yeah but like
you were definitely in the
right on the twitters
yeah I think so
wow
I think so thank you
um
I know I'm right
about the lecture and I know
even more that I'm right
about the comments
from her quote unquote producer
so the right
ness just keeps compounding
and multiplying itself soon you'll be all
away to the right you'll be far right
soon I'll be far right
yeah base
base and redpilled
uh next voicemail is called
base joker two three
two one go
you know what my problem is
batman
when you've bitten off more than
you can chew well
no one bats an eye
but when you've
shitting off more than you can
chew well
suddenly the whole world loses
their marbles
it's true
I never thought of it like that before
but you know what he's right
I've been living
that phrase for a few days
shitting off more than you can
it's too real
ugh
this is just
I'll never
I'll never shit the same
again
um oh god next
speaking of which next voicemail is called
a message from your gaping ass
oh three two one
go
hey ben I have a problem I think you can
relate to of course
know why I really fucking hate the cast
button on my phone
do you know how annoying it is
when you're playing with your whatchamado
cast button and then suddenly you
accidentally press the cast button
and then oh look at that
now all your roommates know you jack off the tranny
porn and they're like wow
look at this huge fucking faggot
he likes jacking it off to lady boys
and you know what
maybe I fucking like it okay
it's not your goddamn business you'll have to
fucking look at it stop judging me
anyway I hope
there's a later setting that's introduced
where I can turn off the cast button
anyway uh tell me what you think I should do
about this problem
uh embrace it stop getting so
worked up about people seeing the porn
you watch you should just
you should be
proud
of yourself
proud of your boy
I'll make you proud of your boy
just switch to a browser that doesn't have
a cast that you built in
just be proud to be a faggot
I guess is all I can say
I mean it's cool
look it's not it's not it's not wrong
to like a penis no matter
what your sexual orientation
because penises are funny
no they're serious no
shut up they're serious business
you gotta fucking
take them for
for a spin
don't be late
what are you saying
next voicemail
please save me
next voicemail is called panic play
date three two one go
many months ago
tom had mentioned that there is an empty
space in our hearts
and minds that the game boy used
to fill and I think I have found
something that will fulfill that niche
it is um
called the panic play date
you should check it out
google it right now looks cool
it's designed by teenage engineering
um
it's like a game boy with a little crank
on the side like a fishing reel
so I would imagine that would be
an obvious choice of game
um
and yes the development
gets free and open source if you want to
mess around with it I have looked at it
but I'm very uncreative
what is the point
let me know what you think
I think it looks cool I'm excited for it
should be coming out later this year
and I
I'm really really curious as to
what people do with the crank
um yeah I remember
seeing this a while ago
uh like announced like ah
it's a revolutionary new idea
it's a thing that looks a little bit like a game boy
so you remember it so you're just nostalgic
and it's got some sort of games on it
and you crank the crank
to charge the battery and also
it's a gameplay feature thingy
it's like a Nintendo
esque gimmick
I'm like eh cool I guess
okay
how many things do you want a crank
well that's the whole thing
I feel like the crank is probably going to do more harm than good
I feel like it was a gimmick idea that probably
should not have been included
yeah but it's
I mean without the crank
just a knockoff game boy
I think if they yeah that's why they have the crank
uh maybe
they don't have like good games I don't think
I don't think the games are what they're selling it on
it's just the game I'm assuming it's a platform
and I don't see why I would want that
it's an open platform that people can develop for
kind of like kind of like how pico a got big
hmm
yeah so
so it sounds like they should have just embraced the fact
that they're just a knockoff game boy
and just let people develop for that
I mean there's a whole market for like
knockoff game boys that like people like
so yeah
I don't I guess I don't mind the idea
of like having like a crank for like different
kind of like gameplay experiments
and like people probably do cool things with it
but I'm just thinking like
like when I think of a game boy I think of something I can
easily place in my pocket and that crank is going to
fuck that up it's going to be annoying to have to
like oh gotta move the crank and
it'll get caught in my pocket trying to take it out
yeah
yeah it looks it's going to be jutting
out I wish it could like fold it in
or something
can you can you like
I don't know maybe
up in the back when you're not
when you're not cranking it
yeah I can see on the Wikipedia
there's an image of it
but I'm also
seeing
how much is it that's important if it's over
$99 it's a failure
like that was a great thing about game boys
they were like disposable and didn't cost a lot of money
notable indie game
developers such as
Keita Takahashi which is the guy who made
Katamari so
he's making a game for it
uh cranking times
time travel adventure I like that guy
he's really cool so
I'll have a look at that
fascinating
uh
cranking time travel adventure
gameplay
it's $150
it's a little pricey
yeah
I mean
it's also yellow the worst color
I would have to see like what
I mean if it had really quality
games I feel like $150 is fair
but I mean does it
is the question
every console lives or dies by its library
sure yeah sure
oh it does
it does kind of tuck itself in
well that's good
that's much better
if it couldn't do that it would be really annoying
yeah that's true
I don't know
it's like mostly consolidated there
that's pretty solid
uh
next one
yeah
next one is called Kyoto Ninja Clan
3, 2, 1, go
ho
konnichiwa
this is ninja-sama
where could
samurai-sama
be
he disappeared
maybe Kyoto Ninja Clan
have
something to do
without this
also it's possible
beno-sinto-san
also
betre
Kyoto Ninja Clan
fuck you
return on ninja scroll
okay until
you next time
sayonara
ben
what do you have against the continent
of Asia
why is the entire island nation of Japan
out to destroy it
I have nothing against them
I just love scrolls
so much I'll do anything for them
even betre
I'll betre any clan for a scroll
if I see
if I see a quality scroll
I'm gonna join the clan
and then I'm gonna
you got your first wall scroll in high school
and ever since then it's all been downhill
I was full metal alchemist
I got it at anime boston
anyway next voice mail
innocent pork chops
mayoral masquerade
3 2 1 go
there was a little piggy
except that pig got too big
we're here to cut him down
to size
and snap him like he was a twig
this hog had had a reason
to do something he would
regret
an order from the city
mayor
to shut down machines
and there
there was a little pig
got in a giant charade
we have to let him go
run free
let him escape this
masquerade
with that in mind
could someone call an uber
for this swine
well if you call an uber
for the
uber
for the giant
if you call an uber
for the giant hog
who has been ordered by the mayor
to shut down machines
won't he just
decommission the uber
he can't ride it
he'll destroy the vehicle
perhaps a horse drawn buggy
a pig drawn buggy
perhaps
animal power
power to the people
by people I mean beasts
that's my recommendation
next voicemail is called
Mr. Suck and Fuck
3, 2, 1, go
I'm going to
fuck
me
yeah
but I'm not going to
fuck him
in his
go on
fuck him
in his
brain
no
you wouldn't dare
I'm going to
fuck my cock
thanks
cock
I wonder what it was like
to record this
that's just
rude
with my
ow
cock
and I will
come on
with
my cock
fucking over the top
dude we get it
we get it
I get it you got a fucking keyhole
god
I mean
I cannot believe these are still going on
I mean he's on message
he's on message
he has a thesis and he sticks to it
and
I respect it
I respect the hustle
the guy who does this 24-7
next voicemail is called
Joker rap needs critique
3, 2, 1, go
hi PCP
it's me out of character
I need some
feedback on this
Joker rap I'm making about the Joker
okay so here it goes
most guys eat mice
the Joker eats plaster
most guys drive slow
the Joker drives faster
most guys can't shit
the Joker is a master
most guys can't do magic
but the Joker is a caster
most guys can't do math
the Joker knows all the factors
most guys think they're safe
the Joker is bringing a disaster
rabbits love breeding
the Joker is busy defeating
most guys are betas
but the Joker is alpha leading
okay that's it
the actors
does not fit I think
I think maybe trim down
the ones that don't work as well
I keep all of the best ones
I think
the one
the Joker knows all the factors
there's too many syllables
the Joker knows factors
the one that's
syllable synchronicity
I like how the Joker is a master
of shitting
he never
shits off more than he can prove
that's what we've learned about the Joker today
um
that's what was my favorite line personally
next voicemail is called
shaggy has a thought
3, 2, 1, go
you know scoop
every poo poo
is pee pee time
but like
not every pee pee
is poo poo time man
like you ever think about that one scoop
no shaggy I don't
it's not wrong
next voicemail is called shaggy has
a second thought
3, 2, 1, go
you know what else I've been thinking about scoop
like
why do all the Jews
have so much power
it's like crazy man
shaggy no
please
I was with you
shaggy
you've been
you've been letting the youtube algorithm
recommend you videos again haven't you
I knew who it was who left the first one
and I was hoping
there wouldn't be that in the second one
do we know this person
it's jelly beaner
in the thing
they love talking about Jews and I don't like it
oh yeah
they've got like
loves Jews in their handle
on like discord
in places I've noticed
yeah
what's up with that
what's up with that jelly beaner
huh
huh big man
you gonna fight me huh
they answer me tough guy yeah you can't
you can't do it
next
voicemail is called
dm321
go
as you struggle give someone an uncharacteristically
huge amount of strength and throws
bin over the side of the fortress
bin plummets to his death
no
don't make it to make a reflex save
sounds like we're talking about mechanics
they mutter amongst themselves
unsure of whether bitcoin
bin was the only person
with bitcoins in that fortress
or whether
that lone figure up above
may have some as well
I say to them
go away
go away please
you're on your own
shit I've got rid of my only ally
and now I'm outnumbered even more than before
I dispel invisibility
I was standing here the whole time
oh tom
hey tom help
hey you yeah tom I see you there
I know where you are
no don't help her no she doesn't deserve it
you saw what she just did to me
her only friend
bitcoin
I mean
true
that's why you should kill gib
this is my ghost my ghost to speak
bitcoin you gotta kill her
and then it'll all be yours
I'll attempt to pick pocket the bitcoin
oh
why did you
because
you should have done that while you were still invisible
no no
you gotta become visible
and then you have to pretend you're an ally
then pick pocket
while they're defensive
if you're still in fight or flight
you're gonna be watching your pocket
I roll for notice
I roll for noticing that
no stop
I hate you
I try to notice something
how do you do that how do you say
I hope I notice something happening to me
I think the dm would just guide you through
yeah the dm would say
roll a perception check
roll to notice
yeah it's not an action
I just stand there being like uh oh
do I fuck it up
I grab your ass instead of your coin purse
like uh oh I hope I'm not being
pickpocketed right now
I mean when you think about it we're all passively hoping
we're not getting pickpocketed right now
well now I'm actively
instead of all that
I'm at the top of the wall
and the door bridges up
the gates closed they can't get in
I just uh
I'm just hiding behind the wall
and behind the battlements
that's what I do
they can't get me
you hide behind the battlements
what about Tom
well that's what that's Tom can do
what he wants
that's my action
Ben's in line of sight
and we're not in initiative order
I'm dead I was curled over
the fucking wall I'm done
if you were still with
in line of sight when you fell I would cast
feather fall on you and that would drop
concentration and so I'd have to lose my
visibility and then I'll try
how come you get to be a wizard
I don't know because Tom says
anything it was just
I'm playing a sorcerer
in the game I'm actually playing right now so
likely story
you're a fucking
you're trying to
ensorcel us right now with these fanciful
tales you're spinning
these yarns
I pick up my wand which has
no all the buffs
and I cast chain saw
on everything
yeah that's it
I hope to god you've stacked it
with a mana reducer I just pray
okay
sounds good
DM
let me roll
for initiative please
okay next voicemail is called
Ben's tweets to Trixie
feel free to skip if old news
no I will not skip
3, 2, 1, go
I don't know if this will be like old and dead news
by the time
you respond to this but
regarding like all of the
Trixie drama on Twitter
and Ben's say in response to it
I actually really appreciate
Ben's tweets even though they are
pretty harsh and
kind of getting like a little bit
maybe mean-spirited at a certain point
but just like
as like a PCP
fan it has been very frustrating
to see the situation with Trixie
so it's actually somewhat
cathartic to have someone just kind of like
speak out and just
nope the whole situation there
so I mean I hope
you don't keep on doing it you know
forever because that would be a little bit immature
but it just
has been it
it feels
feels nice in a weird way
but yeah I've been really liking the episodes
of the podcast recently I feel like
they kind of hit a slump when more
of the members left but recently
it's been hitting a really good stride so
I don't know here's to our episodes
sorry about this one
yeah
I wouldn't
I wasn't going to do it
I wasn't going to say anything
the only reason I did
is because
Trixie's crew
stepped on my fucking toes
stepped on our collective toes
and that's the only reason why it had to
come to this
I have been
frustrated watching Trixie do
everything for a long time
now
is it frustrating
is it embarrassing yes
but it's not my business I was just going to leave her to it
but
there's a point when it becomes my problem
and
that's what happened
so
thanks for the voicemail
next one
is called Roger Roger
three two one
go
so now that Trixie left the show to burn every bridge
she has ever made
why not try to fix some of the old ones
talking monkey and Jeff baby
hit them up see if they want to come back
for an episode I'm sure they'd be happy to hear from you guys
anyway
PCP forever
Tom will never die
call me back
I certainly hope not
Tom alone will
live to upload his consciousness
into the fucking cyber mainframe
this is the first chance I get
I mean Jeff
I don't feel like Jeff knows us at all
I think Jeff was the only
but it would be hilarious if we got Jeff
it would be funny
it's hilarious in concept
in concept only
I guess I would do it just for the gag
but I have no idea what I would
say to Jeff
and I mean kind of the same for monkey
like what do I have to say to monkey
there's just so much time that's passed
now it's just like
it's a different person
really
it's yeah
it's I mean I've thought about it
like I've tossed
around the idea of like wouldn't it be funny
if we had monkey
I asked monkey to guess but like
do I really want to
not really
my heart of hearts it's not what I desire
against a monkey return
I don't really hate monkey
or anything it's just sort of like
I just don't want to talk to him
I mean it would be fine to have like
my logic on again but I don't want to
yeah
I sort of yeah
it's kind of similar
not that they're equivalent it's just the same sort of feeling I have
nothing would come of that
I don't feel for me
yeah
I guess I agree
okay next one is called literally me
three two one go
and the podcast
go back to being an alt right
podcast now
leave
no
no alt right
it could though it could though
no Ben Ben
but I'm dying
everyone says I'm right on Twitter
and it feels good so I think
maybe I should start leaning
into it maybe I should start leaning
into it
oh god
I've always led
you know I've always led an alternative
lifestyle what if I let an
alt right
turn it right
keep joking about it I'm gonna have to start saying
things like vowsh
mmm
Bosch hasn't made a video on it so I don't have
an opinion Bosch hasn't made a video on the PCP
so I don't know what I feel about it
I don't know
it's it's it's
it's hard to say it's just
it's just so complicated
I need that man I need that man
to cut through the bullshit
I need that man to slap
his hands together
when you look at comments
on like the the lectures like
specifically I look at the anamorphs and the guiltier
lectures obviously because like they're the ones I do
and there's just tons of people being like
are they
seriously misogynist and I'm just like
can you really not tell
it's a joke like
I don't even I don't even remember
like what are they talking about
like there are some times when like in the
anamorphs one where Nate is like
saying like haha a woman wrote this lol
but like clearly as a joke
and like it happens like twice I think and it's just
like
yeah I don't know like
I don't yeah
yeah what
I guess what is there are they are they really
misogynist you really can't read the room
at all I don't fucking know
like I haven't
yeah I haven't watched in a while but like
I assume I assume
there's laughter and it's like
a yeah so
the I don't know
it's I don't fucking know it's pretty funny
it's pretty funny that a woman wrote a
book I mean yeah
what do they think of next I know it's crazy
Harry Potter
oh
see see this is why
women shouldn't be allowed to write books because then
because I mean we've seen what happened
we've seen what happened with JK Rowling
how many times are we going to let them get away with this
this has to be the last time we have to put
our foot down
we did it guys we're an alt-right podcast again
yeah
I will push back against this
damn damn
I don't feel strong enough to fight this
but I will I will just say
don't do that
get it Tom she's disease killer
while she's weak
no
she hasn't been drinking her water
you should be conscientious of others feelings
die nerd
that's what I say
when someone says
anything
we'll go full march Simpson on this ship
if you don't straighten up
we'll see
can I roll
can I roll for
charisma to
hey Ben that's not how you do it
you're supposed to be convinced by what you said
you don't say I want to roll
can I make a wisdom check
a will saving throw
to remain
true to the
my strong western values
I stab Ben in the neck with my stiletto heel
round house kick
damn
make an attack roll
shit
I don't hear dice rolling
oh I was rolling in my head
and I thought someone else would do it
I roll a 20 I went fuck
oh shit that's funny
that's it
can't argue with that
next voicemail is called
the large nose man
has finished
three two one go
I've done it
no
I've finally
thought for Nate
congratulations
but that's not all
while he was in a comatose state
I also convinced him
to fire tricksy
from canton
oh yes my true
mission has finally been
completed
you say I use
the league of Nate fuckers
to fuel my
transphobic agenda
and now my mission is
complete
this is on brand for us now
and awake
what I am most
needed
when will we need him
under what circumstances
we won't know until the time has come
when the time is
right we'll know
at the end of the time
when all of the fighters come back
to do the final battle against the big
battle
it'll be a big
battle you ever seen star wars
you ever seen super smash brothers
I've seen something
you ever read red wall
the martins journey
or whatever the fuck
there's a lot of animals
where they fight in that one
there's small mice's mouses
I like that
that was
red school okay let's move on
next voicemail is called
Ben was even more right
dad
you just keep getting righter and righter
just keep getting alter and alter
three two one go
more twitter drama
more correctness
from the king
keep it up
then
this is what it's all about
I do it all for this
for this moment
the king
voicemail that's me baby
say for those voicemails
I harvest the voicemails
that say I'm cool
I play them over and over again
I'm secretly
not playing all the voicemails
that say that I am
not right
they've all been
deleted
Ben goes through all the voicemails
the day before the podcast and clears
out all the ones he doesn't like
you all thought
that I wasn't doing that
but the joke's on you
I was
next voicemail is called
fear them three two one
go
what happened with the ninjutsu
okay
see you next time
thank you for the warning
I guess
the saga gets more complicated
ninjas vs samurai who will win
samurai sounds like
he's on the rocks so
it sounds like the ninjas have grasped the upper hand
I've always been more of a ninja guy
than a samurai guy
samurai's my friend now
we've gone so far back
I think it's like because
you've stolen
samurai scrolls so long ago
that the samurai clan has deteriorated in that time
but the ninja clan
scroll has only recently been gone
so they've still got their full strength
that's a good point
that's a good point oh shit
oh my god wheels within wheels
next voicemail is called
mario kart update
three two one go
hey pcp
it's me again
I'm the guy who's playing mario kart
I am
falling out of it I don't really like
mario kart 8 anymore
because once you get to the high ranks
it's nothing but people playing mario kart
I'm so sorry to hear that
is there anything I can do for you sir
it's all the same it's not fun anymore
they always choose the same maps
the game gets really boring
but I'm glad to say
that I've started working on those commissions
that I have been leaving people
waiting on for several months
you know life's really working out
I got caught up on the podcast
and I was surprised to see that
um a tricksy
I
I don't know
it's I'm honestly
honestly it really makes me want to cry
it's like it's so it's such
it's such a sadness
I don't even know what to say
oh
oh what happened
damn
that's some real emotion right there
I could
I could feel
the tender
the tender feelings
I could hear he was crying on the inside
he was putting on a brave face
but his true feelings
shone through
next voicemail is called
good podcast
three two one go
alright guys seriously
I don't mean to hang on it too much but
uh
oh
tricksy situation not looking good
despite everything that's around the podcast though
what do you mean
I have been getting caught up while I do those commissions that I owe
it's actually been pretty nice
I've almost banged them all out
actually caught up on the PCP now
went right through it all in just a few days
um
all the guests been gait
podcast doing great keep up the good work
Tom, Ben, Gib
been my favorite members
for a long time and now you're the only one
yeah nice
keep up the good work hope Nate comes back someday
Nate is still
technically a member
Nate is not like left like tricksy has
he just doesn't show up for the podcast ever
that's uh
yeah
but hey
thanks dog
glad you like
us
um
this is our fucking
rodeo now this is our
fucking
uh
side of side of
mashed potatoes
oh god I'm floundering
next voicemail is
someone take this man's flan
she doesn't deserve it anymore
no please
I killed an ape for that
next voice
I killed an ape for his meat
um his for his bush meat
next next voicemail is called
doid gazers civil war
oh god
three two one go
hi this is doid gazers again
with me uh your host me
uh today
we're going to be smoking some weed
and then I'm going to be um
doing some fire wax
that's what I tune in for
we're going to talk about how Nate Bestman
uprooted his entire life
and moved to Virginia to do
a stupid anime show with me
and uh because anime is stupid now
and uh I'm on a whole
another plane of reality
um Nate decided to fire me
and that's not very cool so then
uh do a diss track with my new best friend
Riley um give me money
I hope there's a diss track
I'm going to be living out of a uh
RV uh or actually
no just a van maybe
I don't know um but um
yes this is what I want in my life
and you have to respect it so
um it's true yeah it's
true Nate and Ben
two not cool dudes
thank you
give me money
we should we should bring back
t-bap but call it two not cool dudes
yes
uh um
T-N-C-D
tick and
T-T-N
tick and no
tink tink tink da
that sucks that's garbage
that's trash not throw it all in a
fucking trash no no no no no
no no no no I
I do hope there's a diss track though
pretty funny
there was one
I mean some people were
saying that the
the track that she
put out on April
Fools some people were speculating
that it was uh in response
to me
but it doesn't like it's not
specific like there are some lines in it that sound
like they could be about me but it's not like
it's kind of just a general
like haters
don't know shit
track so I don't know
I don't know if that's normal
it's fine to talk about haters
yeah pretty much
yeah it's not sure
sure well I hope
I hope they make a diss track about me I hope
I get some uh
you deserve
somebody needs to make a fucking diss track
about you it builds character
in which you are lacking
please
you need some
yeah
somebody diss track this fool
uh next voicemail
is called hi ben
it's another one called hi ben
okay three two one go
okay so
due to recent events
um
if Nate comes back on
the PCP
um
Ben can you just like
you'll be in charge
I like the culture you've cultivated here
thank you
with the whole not screening voicemails thing
I think it really adds up
to the show so
yeah I think Nate would hate it
just you and Gib just
stay in charge and Nate can be like a
special guest
I mean maybe
Nate maybe watch
um I mean
no no word
on whether Nate has
uh reconsidered
his
his status
of that so I mean
I mean I could come back
as it has always been a possibility
I see no reason to think that he will
but like it's like
like Nate left
like a wound to fester and now it's too powerful
and he can't treat it
if he tries to come back and be just
like the old times like hey everyone welcome to the
p-bro grassy podcast
we'd like to send upon him and
eat him and destroy him
too much has happened
we can never go back
to the way things were you can't go home again
once you give up your
PCP flange you can't get it back
you'd have to go through a
reflinging initiation ritual
we unflanged him
and once lost a flange
he unflanged himself and walked away
that's true that's true he gave up the flange
it's truly the most
unflanged move to leave the PCP
I did have to agree
I would there's nothing
there's no more flanged
uh
thing to be us
we have the biggest flange
it's huge
okay uh next voicemail is called
last one I swear
3, 2, 1, go
hey what's up jumpsits
me
oh my god
I was calling in with the
question actually
so I was expanding
my mind
last night
you know with
Bird and the other ones
and uh
so I checked
Yig Studios account
of which I am the vizier
and um
I've been getting a lot of
emails since last night
they all say the same thing
here let me pull it up
they all say in the subject
no
Nate no watch
do you guys have any idea
what that means
no
you're still not cool
bye
no sir
it is a mystery
I can't
I've been wondering
frankly I've been wondering the same thing
and I just can't puzzle out commenters let us know
what does it mean
what does it all mean
there were so many no Nate no watches
the episode because we pulled
the switcheroo
it was fine and all
but boy
there were a lot of them
next voicemail is called
Puppa Prince 3 2 1
go
so a second week no new idea
for a voicemail that's it bye
okay
let us know if you think of anything
I believe in you buddy
uh
that's respectable it's admirable
he's putting himself out there
one of these days
I believe in him
this is the wheels
the wheels have started to turn
next voicemail is called
Mike Literis
lol 3 2 1 go
I still remember the ambitions you had vividly
I couldn't wait to check out which funny
yet touching artistic achievements just had created
in an effort to always surpass himself
as an artist while I was gone
I couldn't wait to see how many hundreds of thousands
of subscribers my favorite friendship simulator
had gained in my absence
just what wacky antics of my favorite
unironically fact it's loving online creator
Nate had I missed
also there's ban
just thinking about the abundance of artistic masterpieces
I'm wondering
about the abundance of artistic masterpieces
I must have missed send shivers down my spine
a b p c p h q was already founded
how many ones for munchie would I
have to retroactively press
so I innocently clicked on the pcp youtube channel
not knowing what would await me
I cried and screamed so blood curdling loud
that I lost my voice permanently
my dreams were shattered and I shot my pants
and I had an orgasm
in three weeks
I am utterly defeated and will never recover
same
give his best girl
why did you come back
why did you ruin it for yourself
you should never
you should never have looked
you should have just let yourself be content
with the fantasy
not knowing
it's like the typical story when god said not to look back
and then someone did
you look back and you've become the pillar
you've become the pillar of salt
it's you
that's so sad
what was that, that was a greek myth about that
it was a fucking
no it was Sodom and Gomorrah
that was also a greek myth
where your wife died
and you can't look at her face
oh yeah
she's forever
never coming back
I can't remember the name
was it Persephone
Persephone in the underworld right
yeah something like that
that's the one that Pluto
said because she ate the pomegranate
so she has to be
she has to be in the underworld
half the time
I don't know if that's the same one
I think it might be a different one
yeah
I've heard the one you're talking about
he goes to the underworld to get his wife back
and you can't look at her
what he does
like a fool, like an idiot
which is basically the same
as the story of Lot
it's Lot
it's either Sodom or Gomorrah
and his wife
he's the only good man
in the city
and he has to flee
and he takes his family with him
and his wife
and God says don't look back
but his wife looks back and turns into a pillar of salt
so he escapes with his daughters
but it's okay because he just fucks his daughters
instead of his wife
and starts a new family with them
so it's all good
he's the only good man
well I mean what choice do they have Tom
you know
God turned everyone else to salt
what would you have done
God's kind of an asshole
I mean
he
he knew what he was doing
he knew what he was fucking doing
so I'm saying
next
voicemail is called LeMau
Trixie PooPoo
3 2 1
go
I think right now
you're
recording the PCP
if I'm not too late
I did not get what you guys are saying
on the last one
about Eaton Ralph and Digi
and whatever
holy shit
wait
wait to fucking make your audience
wanna forget about you
becoming trailer trash
and fighting over switch
I completely agree
100,000%
big dick I am
I'm in fact not mentally
yeah
oh my god
that's about the size of it
what a shame
good voicemail
shame is the word I would use
yeah
I'm so proud of it too
oh my god
next voicemail is called
I Will Fap All Day
every day for the rest of the PCP's
X
maybe it's supposed to say
existence
it must be
3 2 1
go
oh it's just fapping
oh god no stop
that's just
fapping
and yet I'm gonna listen
to the whole thing
thanks
for the voicemail buddy
well hang on
all day every day does that mean next week
there'll be 7 of these
no it's all day every day
we got this an hour ago
which means he started an hour ago
won't stop until he's dead I guess
all day every day
they're gonna have an arm the size
of a person
they're gonna have
one way to get strength at that right
that's one way to get
ripped
next voicemail
is called
Jebediah Prickinson is confused
3 2 1 go
hello
this is me Jebediah Prickinson
great to have you
buddy
wants to fuck me anymore
don't know what it is
I mean
look at him
he's so muscular
I mean I'm not gay
I just think it'll be
pretty bitch to touch sticks with him
or something you know
goodbye
goodbye thank you
what a way to end
just join the fucking league
you wanna join league
just do it okay you only live once
follow your heart
well fuck
that's it
we listened to all the voicemails
what a nightmare this
was
ah yes
joy
to the world
the lord
is come
in
Nate cause he's league of voice
league of Nate fuckers fuck
it is the lord's day today
league of voicemailers
god it's easter that's right
maybe I should call my parents
or something
I just saw him last weekend
I don't fucking wanna
I've had enough
had enough
alright
I feel like I'm gonna
plus out me too
but I'll probably play some more noida
before I go to sleep
I just I didn't get enough chainsaws
before I'm just like
I thought I was over it
I thought I was over it but I'm not
even close
um any last words
okay gentlemen
patreon.com slash the procrastinators
podcast
bonus episode
pick cross
mine sweeper
learn the secrets
I literally learned all the secrets
of mastery
of pick cross and mine sweeper
and you can too
patreon.com
slash the procrastinators
send us a voicemail
if you wanna keep abreast of all the dumb twitter drama
twitter.com
slash tpcrastinators
I'm sure you'll find it all for osmosis there
but why would you want to?
yeah why
it's pretty funny
um okay
I've frankly said
too much already
that's the end of the episode
good night and sweet dreams
good night
goodbye