Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemails for the Minecraft stream. I really want to have Redcon funded by you. We can be Pro Crastinators.
Let's get fucked. Is that what it says? Wait, is that the actual lyric? Or did I just trick myself?
I don't know, but what is it? Is it Beyblade?
Something in the backseat? Fuckin' in the front seat.
Sittin' in the backseat? Oh wait, Sittin' in the backseat? Sittin' in the front seat? Party and party and yeah, fun, fun, fun, looking forward to the weekend.
That's a major pop hit of our generation.
Hey, ho, let's go, it's, hey you, no, not hey you Pikachu, it's the Pikachu movie, short film. Hey, ho, let's go. There's a bit in the Pikachu movie.
Well, I didn't fucking see that shit.
Yeah you did, it's the one, the 2000, the fucking Pokemon 2000, or maybe you didn't.
Er, I don't know if I watched Pokemon 2000. Is that the one with Lugia? I don't know if I watched it.
Alright, I'm using all my words wrong. The one with Mewtwo in it, the first movie, has a fucking Pikachu short film that starts earlier.
Oh, it's Blitzkrieg, okay, it's a song by the Ramones, it's Blitzkrieg Bop, okay, I'm stupid, I never knew that.
I could swear there's a bit in the soundtrack, it goes, hey ho, let's go, and then it cuts through the next scene.
Maybe there is, but it's either an homage to the Ramones, or they just put a classic rock song in the movie.
Yeah, whatever, welcome to the Procrastinatus podcast where we don't know what we're doing.
We don't know about classic music institutions of our culture, and we gotta Google and go, what's that song where the guy says like,
that it's like, there's eight days in a week, what's that song called?
I have no idea.
Welcome to the Procrastinatus podcast. New bonus episode, I said the new bonus episode is going to be out for the last episode,
but it is out this week, I put it out this week. It's very funny, it's the fun facts challenge where we find the funnest fact.
We compete to see who finds the funnest fact, and boy, is there fun and facts along the way.
There sure are, they're so fun and so factual that I've forgotten all of them.
I need to go and subscribe to the Procrastinatus Patreon so I can find out.
I remember many of them, yes, and then as we say in that episode, leave your own fun facts,
not on that bonus episode where no one will see them.
Leave them here in the main comments so that other viewers will be confused and feel like they are missing something.
They'll be confused to see comments of random fun facts, even though we're saying explicitly do that.
They'll know exactly what the context is.
Yes, because those will be the people who have been checking back for a year and a half now to just see,
is Nate or Trixie or Jesse back on the podcast yet?
Oh no, they're not, okay, but I don't actually watch the podcast, so I don't know that there's literally no reason to be doing that,
and I'm wasting my time, but I'll be back again next week, again.
Those will be the people who will be stymied.
That'll be the entirety of our viewer base.
Just a bunch of people who click on the thing and say, is there, oh, we get the views anyway.
Suckers.
Suckers, thanks for the click.
Thanks for the click, suckers.
Wait, wait, no, we need the watch time.
No, please don't go, oh.
We should start doing a thing where we promised that we'll reveal Nate at the end of the show,
and we keep promising that, and then we don't do it.
The return of Nate will be the, it will basically be like the end of the world, it will be the apocalypse,
it will be like the return of Christ in the book of Revelations.
You think you want it, but it heralds the end.
By the way, I'm looking in, okay, I wasn't sure how to pronounce it, but apparently the word is pronounced stymied.
Yes.
Although, oh wait, British pronunciation is the same.
Okay, I've never seen this before.
Did they just add this thing to Google Translate?
I'm gonna put this in general.
Now, when I look up the pronunciation of the word, now there's this mouth,
and when I play the word, like the mouth moves to show, I've never seen this before.
Google something pronunciation, and you get this little, you can see the mouth move.
That's so weird.
I guess it's cool.
I'm not getting it.
You're not?
No, I'm getting a video about how to do it from YouTube.
Maybe you need to go to Google proper.
Maybe.
This is in my search results.
This is right above people also ask.
Maybe if I type in exactly stymied.
Stymied pronunciation.
It does come up.
Maybe it's only words that people often ask how to pronounce.
Yeah, it's probably certain words.
I mean, somebody had to make this little animation for it.
So, yeah.
Fascinating.
Practice and get feedback.
They want me to record my voice.
What?
Let me click on it.
Use my microphone.
Ah, no block.
No, I don't want that.
They'll give them an inch.
They'll take my splinch.
We'll take a mile.
Well, okay, a thing I got to talk about.
Yeah.
Clarissa, chapter three.
The finish of what I had already drawn for the Tezuka Award show,
the last bunch of pages,
will be out by the time you're listening to this viewer, listener,
on Gibbentake.site.
Clarissa Gunsmoke.
The Bandit King.
It's cool.
It's epic.
Have you been reading it, Ben?
I have not yet.
I know.
Listen.
It's just how I am with everything.
I just don't watch things and I don't read things.
I will, I will, I will.
You said this is the last update.
This is like the last of it you got to upload.
Yeah, for the time being.
And then I might...
Well, then I'll have no excuse.
Yeah.
I might stream more drawing of future pages soon,
if I have the time.
This is just sort of like in between
waiting for Lord of Ghost stuff to get ready,
which is closer.
I have been, I have been working on the Lord of Ghost.
I got, I got, I think I only got one page done today,
but it was another one that I spent a long time on
because it was a big like background,
two big background landscape shots.
Dang.
I hate, I hate doing them.
I hate doing background landscapes.
You're really good at them though.
You obviously have like a very clear vision in your head of like,
okay, well it has to look good.
Well, yeah.
It has to look like this and then you'd spend hours on it.
I did spend, yeah, the first desert,
the first desert shot I spent hours and hours on
and then I spent even longer on like the,
the aerial shot of Cowtown over the hill.
I just, yeah, I had a very particular vision
and I just was like, I probably could have done it faster.
I probably could have gotten away with less lines.
I sometimes fall into the trap of zooming the image in too far
and putting any detail that is probably not strictly necessary.
I think I fell into that a little bit on this one,
but the end result is good.
I mean, my backgrounds are, when it comes to like,
Kazin and Clarissa, there's a shot where you see the town from a distance.
I'm like, okay, well, it's in the distance.
So I'll just give the illusion of rectangles
and then people will assume there's a town there.
I mean, that's what you should do.
That's what you should do.
Like, yeah, like the further away something is, the less detail.
It really doesn't look like much if you zoom in
and being like, oh God, there's no drawing here.
Yeah, but that's okay.
Like as long as it suggests what it's meant to suggest, you know.
Yeah.
Yeah, my, I had originally, yeah, I asked you how you felt about me
putting like another eye tower in Cowtown
because, you know, there's one in New Los Angeles City
and this war, of course, and there's one in New Big and by the sea.
And you said, no, that's like a lower thing.
There shouldn't be one in Cowtown.
Originally, yeah, this, I don't know if you are looking at the image,
but the church, the big church on the horizon,
I mean, I guess I'll post it.
The big, the big, don't show the audience.
This is secret.
This is secret content.
Secret.
All these are.
The big church on the horizon was like huge.
It was like way bigger and it had an eye in the bell tower
instead of the bell.
But I was like, okay, no, I'll just make it a normal church.
So I made it like, I mean, it's still really big,
but it's just, it was regular big.
And it should be given a bell tower.
Yeah.
The, the, the, the, the perspective on the town,
it's a little weird.
I don't know.
I sketched it like this and I followed my sketch pretty closely.
I mean, it was a rough sketch, but like the curve of the ground
on like the left side, which is kind of flat and the right side,
which is just kind of like tilting off the, the, the side.
It's pretty weird when you think about it,
but I was just like, eh, whatever.
It's all right.
It's got, yeah, it looks, looks all right.
It works.
It's got depth.
It's got a really round hill.
Like I made the ground like a big round sort of bump.
And then I don't know if you notice, I don't know if you notice,
but if you zoom in, if you zoom in past the building
with the big tall cowboy hat veneer, just to the right of it,
you can see on the seashore, there's the cactus on the cow town sign
where Lord of Ghosts crawls out of the sea.
Ah, that's cool.
Yes.
I was, I was wondering if you would like study what I had drawn.
I did.
Like, I, cause I, cause I drew this, I drew this sign on the, on the road.
And then I went back and I looked at the thing and I was like, oh shit,
that's not what the cow town sign looks like.
But then I thought, wait a minute, but he, but, but Lord of Ghosts doesn't come by road.
Lord of Ghosts comes by sea.
So he comes in from like the other side.
So then I was like, okay, so I got to put, I got to put a little,
a bit of sea in the background, you know, because, because he crawls out of the sea
to get here.
So sea in the background.
And there was a little gaff.
I was like, okay, if I put that sign there, it's like, that's like, yeah,
the other side.
And also, yeah, the building that he comes in next to, yeah, on the right of that,
you can see there's the saloon that you drew.
And to the left of it is a little piece of the, of the blacksmith.
So, you know, continuity, continuity.
Epic.
I didn't, I didn't ask you to do any of that, but you did it.
No, that's just, you went above and beyond.
It's called being a professional gift.
You should try it sometime.
Well, I love doing that with my own stuff.
But I'm like, oh wait, I drew this here.
And then like, I have to 3D, like 3D print in my brain, a map of the area.
Yeah.
Or 2D printed with paper.
I mean, what's the point?
What's the point of a comic if you're not like, you know, with what you're drawing
is not like consistent with the story that's been told thus far, right?
Yeah.
The point is to make a narrative, a world.
So, yes, I just thought that would be fun.
I thought that would be cool.
And for all you people at home who can't see anything that we're talking about,
you have to have already pledged to the Lord of Ghost Kickstarter.
And maybe there'll be plenty of comics left for you to purchase afterwards.
Perhaps.
I don't know yet.
I guess I should open up the floor for people who want to buy a comic
before I send off for the final print.
I will do that.
Probably.
Yeah.
Because I'm like making, oh God, how many?
There was a number.
I know the number somewhere.
Speaking of printing, yeah, I have to go.
I've ordered the final, the next printing of the Roger Radcon.
I ordered 100 new copies just because 100 was not much more expensive than 50.
I feel very stupid that I didn't think about that we should just print it all in one go.
It ends up being a little more expensive because we only printed the first amount
and then I had to print again.
But it's not actually that bad in the grand scheme of things.
It's just like, ugh.
Ugh.
Like less efficient.
Probably like two or three hundred dollars more expensive doing it in two batches.
But oh well.
Yeah.
So yeah.
But yeah, I will have plenty of copies left over though.
So reminder for anyone who might be listening who wants a copy of Roger Radcon.
I'm going to have extra copies.
So contact me one way or another and I can have those.
Honestly, I will probably have them for a while.
I don't see myself selling out of them.
But if you thought I was going to run out, I will not.
So I'll have those for people.
Buy it.
Please buy Road to Radcon.
I have Dwarven Gold Madness.
Please give me money.
Also, drawing the...
I don't know what you looked at for references for drawing the buildings in Cowtown.
I looked up...
I googled pictures of Tombstone, Arizona and I drew buildings from that place.
Yeah.
I looked up a few Google images of western towns.
I didn't want it to be like a Hollywood set.
I think I saw some real shit.
Tombstone, Arizona is a real old western...
It's a real old western town, but it has sort of become a tourist trap.
There's a main drag that is very much deliberately playing into the old west vibe and they put on shows and stuff.
So it's somewhere in between like a theme park of itself and the real deal.
It's funny though because I don't know anything about the old west outside of Hollywood movies of westerns and stuff.
I've seen maybe one YouTube video walking around like an actual wild west preserved ghost town.
And it's like, oh yeah, seems about right.
But I don't know much about how these buildings and all of this stuff actually came about.
I just know how it's depicted.
A lot of bear wooden boards.
So many of them seem to have the thing on the front.
A lot of them have a sloping porch covering in the front and also a flat stand up portion over the front with a billboard space.
Looking at almost every building on the main drag in Tombstone, Arizona has the pieces of wood built up over the front entrance way into what amounts to billboard space.
I guess because it's all businesses.
Yeah, the high street would be like that.
You ride through it on your horse and you're like, where's things I need?
Exactly.
I just thought that was interesting.
Yeah, that's the thing.
It's like you watch the cowboy movies and they've got the high street where the saloon is.
They've got the motels or the hotels or whatever.
Or the Holiday Inn.
Yeah, they stay in the hotel or they go to the ranch and they get the cows.
Oh wow, cool.
But like regular people, where the hell do they live?
What do they live in?
How they're building apartment buildings?
Or is it just like individual houses and huts?
I gotta assume that they all live in little ranch houses that probably are a little bit more dispersed around the main drag.
I gotta assume that there's the main street and then around it there's a lessly densely developed area of a lot of like,
probably some farmland, probably a lot of the houses have a little bit of like ranching land or whatever.
The idea of Manifest Destiny, go west and like government handing out free land to people who can claim it,
was to encourage people to just make claims and build cities and towns and stuff.
So the western town archetype isn't really a town in like a normal European sense.
It's sort of like there's a bunch of farmers like laying claims all over the place and they need some place to like consolidate trade and business and like train and travel back to the east.
Yeah, and they just set up little shops or places of business like hotels or whatever on heavily traveled areas and other people are just like,
well I guess this is kind of the place to be and they set up shop there too and that's how a town forms.
I guess most of the people...
Well there's people living here, gotta build a church and then they do it and then...
Yes.
That's how they do it.
The people living there probably all live in the business that they run, right?
Probably for the most part, yeah.
Yeah, probably.
And then maybe there's just accommodations nearby if...
Because you never really see that.
You see like, yeah, hotels.
Mmm, mmm.
I was trying to search that like a while ago, like what the hell do they live in?
I couldn't really find much so I guess that must be it.
It's just not really one of those types of towns.
Until it was...
I mean, you know, over the hill there's like some range houses or whatever.
I mean probably the town would just be like the main drag and like, you know, the businesses and then...
I mean the surrounding area might technically be the town but like, you know, that's like just, you know, where people live.
I assume, I don't know.
I should read a book about this because I want to like...
When I think of like world building, when it comes to art and stuff, I'm like designing settlements and towns and castles and whatever.
I'd like it to be informed from reality more or so than just like icons of like, oh, a castle.
It's like a big brick and it doesn't really make sense when you think about it in a lot of like media, a lot of video games.
They build it for a video game gameplay and not so much for like actual...
Like why would they build it like this?
Reasons.
I like to figure out or at least learn about that sort of stuff.
Speaking of reading a book, I've sort of been reading a book.
The book is called Diplomacy by Henry Kissinger.
And the reason why I'm reading it is because somebody left it in my last apartment, the temporary apartment that I moved into between my old apartment and my current apartment.
In that temporary place, someone had just left this book and so I just read it in like one page excerpts when I'm taking a shit.
So I've read like maybe a dozen pages of this book that are not in any kind of order, just totally randomly.
Thanks Kissinger.
I'll just open it up to a page.
I guess I kind of am finding it entertaining. I'll open it up to a page and it'll be like, what was the one I just read?
It was about like, you know, after the Munich conference, you know.
Hitler had accomplished his goals and yet he, like those around him, said he was morose because war had been averted.
And war was like, you know, his end goal and because it was involved, all his public speeches, you know, described, you know, a war hawkish attitude for the future of Germany.
He had used up all the goodwill from, you know, Britain, you know, Churchill had agreed to a peace but had, you know, also begun a rearmament program at the same time.
All the goodwill that he had garnered from the guilt of Versailles had worn out by this point, which is, you know, I don't know.
I guess it's kind of interesting. It would probably be more interesting if I started at the beginning and read through.
It's a very big book though. It's very thick. I don't know if I want to commit to actually giving it a full read.
But I mean, I guess I could. I got a book here. I might as well read it. I don't know.
Might as well increase my brain. What if there's a fun fact hidden inside?
Shit. There's even one fun fact. It would be a crime to leave it undiscovered now, wouldn't it?
It's like you troll the library, read every book, trying to find the funnest fact so that you can impress people at parties.
You can say, hey, did you know?
My entire life is just one big fun fact challenge when you really think about it.
Why else does anyone do anything for the discovery of fun facts?
I found, I saw a woman, crazy, I know, but I saw a woman reading a library book on the bench the other day and I was like, wow, what a concept.
I felt bad. I felt guilty that I don't read books much. I felt like...
Flashback to Vapors Chapter 2.
Yeah. I felt like maybe I should be going to the library and reading books.
You know, I should be doing that as well. There's a library not too far from here.
There is a library. I didn't even know there was a library because I hadn't looked for it, but yeah, there is a library.
It's maybe like a 15 minute walk from my, maybe a 10 to 15 minute walk from my house.
I had to go there the other day because of my taxes. I had filed for a tax extension, but my extension period was up.
So I had to file it on October 15th and I did.
And I went and I looked around for places where I could print it.
I had to fucking print some physical shit and send it in the mail. I thought I could file it electronically, but they wouldn't let me.
So I had to go find a printer and send the shit in the mail.
And I went to CVS and Walgreens asking if I could print something there, but they all were like, no, we only print on photo paper.
We can't just print documents for you. It was like shit.
So I went to a cute girl at the Walgreens counter who was totally into me, by the way.
There's no doubt in my mind.
This gave me very, gave me directions to the local public life.
Listen, she was dedicated. She pulled out her phone. She was like, here, I can look it up on my phone for you.
And then we did. And then we talked about what we saw on the screen.
So that's the connection.
I'm looking at my phone. What are you looking at? I'm looking at my phone.
No, we were both looking at her phone.
Oh my God.
We were using this. Yeah.
Dude, that's second base. That's third base, basically.
That's like, that's an indirect kiss right there.
So that's indirect eye contact.
Both of our eyes are looking at the same thing.
So right, she told me about this public library and I went there and did you know that at the public library,
they let you use the printers for free? You don't even have to pay for it.
Wow.
I thought they would charge me like 10 cents a page or something.
And I would have to pay like a dollar.
But no, they were just like, no, I use it.
No, I pulled on my wallet and I'm like, should I?
And she's like, no, it's all free.
I was like, oh my God, but that's communism.
And I pulled out my gun.
And I pulled out my phone and I said, hello, victims of communism Memorial Center, please.
I have someone to report.
And then the cops showed up and they blew it away.
They burned it down.
And America was safe for another day.
So that was pretty neat.
And then I had to rush to the post office because I realized like, actually,
I made small talk with a librarian and I was like, oh yeah, kind of a life saver.
My taxes are due today.
And she's like, oh, no, are you going to mail it?
Do you need to send it to the post office?
Do you have an envelope?
And I'm like, no, I'm envelopes at home.
I got to go home and write the address.
And she's like, oh, you know, you might want to make sure you got it sent.
No, she asked me how I was going to send it.
And I said, I'm going to pop it in a mailbox.
And she was like, oh, you might want to send it from the post office because they'll,
they might want to see that it was postmarked today.
You know, and she dropped it in the mailbox.
They won't postmark till tomorrow.
And I'm like, shit.
I said it out loud to this nice lady.
I said, shit, you're right.
So then I had to fucking sprint to the nearest post office, which I did.
And it all worked out fine.
I got there like half an hour before they closed.
It was, it was very exciting.
But I did it.
I did it.
I got my taxes filed.
And then I filed for an extension to the payment.
So now I don't actually have to, I got, I got the, I got the filing deadline extended
from May all the way to October.
And then I got the payment deadline extended all the way to December.
So I don't actually have to pay it until December.
So, you know, that's a, that's a fucking W if ever there was one.
And I'm going to try, I'm going to try, I'm doing this.
I'm doing it all.
I'm trying to delay it because I want to get, I want to get a business credit card.
I want to get another credit card, a business credit card that won't put me under 524.
And I want to have a bunch of things to buy, to spend on at the moment, at that very moment
when I get it.
And I'm trying, I need to spend, I'm going to need to spend like $4,000 to get.
Have you considered giving takes Patreon?
$4,000 directly to give and take Patreon.
Yeah, but I get that sign up bonus.
And I'm going to have to spend like $4,000, maybe less because then I'll have like five,
if I use it for everything, I'll have like five months to do it.
So, you know, my regular expenses will add up.
But I need to find maybe about like $3,000 worth of extra stuff to spend it on.
So, taxes are some of that.
And, you know, I think I got to pay the artist.
Edward D. Al has been working on the Radcon dojin.
That is, he's falling a little bit behind, but he's still working on it.
So, whenever he gets done with that, I got to, I got to pay him.
And I got to do the next printing of, oh yeah, and I got to pay for the printing of Road to Radcon.
Of course, that's going to be like, you know, 300 and something, maybe 400.
And then da, da, da, da.
So, I'm trying to get all these expenses, pay them at the same time with the same new credit card to try and hit that minimum spend.
And then if I am struggling to hit the minimum spend, my last ditch option, if I'm like, oh shit, I'm like $1,000 short,
and I'm not going to get the sign up bonus.
My last ditch option is just dump anything I need to spend into like Instacart credit, Instacart gift cards for myself.
So, I'm just pre-paying for my groceries.
But, you know, if I just dump $1,000 into that, like, you know, I'll use that eventually.
It's not actually a loss.
So, that's my panic button if I need to spend something right away.
I don't know if I'll need to do that though.
Oh yeah, I'm strategizing.
I'm strategizing my churning techniques.
Yeah, it's like a whole operation.
It is like a whole operation.
You're going to have to start hiring employees at this point.
Yeah, just to manage my payment strategies.
I'll pay them in, I'll pay an accountant in like share of the cash back rewards.
Like, I won't actually pay them a salary, but I'll promise them like you can have like 25% of whatever I get from credit card sign up bonuses for managing my finances.
No, no, no, no, you should pay them in JPEGs and say, hey kid, get yourself an NFT.
Oh god, do you want to talk about NFTs and how fucking dire, how fucking dire the situation on Twitter is?
It's equal parts like gut-bustingly embarrassing like hilarious, but like also like God, why do people, why are they like this?
Why can they become like this?
I know what it is, I know what it is.
It's the same phenomenon that is the reason why people, remember we did the episode about MLMs?
Multi-layer Mario?
Multi-level marketing, the like basically pyramid schemes, but it's not technically pyramid schemes.
Yeah, kind of.
It's mostly women that get into multi-level marketing, not exclusively, but a lot.
So, you know, a lot of these women that get into multi-level marketing, it's basically a scam to trick people into, you know, signing up for the business,
and then, you know, they have to make a personal investment in the business before they can start selling product, and then they start moving product.
If they start moving product, maybe they can make a profit, but most people just sign up, make the initial investment, get the product,
don't actually move any of it, and then, you know, the company just takes their money.
But then, you know, because the real way to make money in multi-level marketing is not actually by moving product,
it's by convincing other people to sign up to be salespeople.
Yes, it's exactly the same NFTs.
Yes, that's the NFT mindset.
It's mostly like male tech bros that think they're getting in on the ground floor of some shitty new technology.
They're doing the same thing.
They're out there, you know, posting about how great it is, you know, posting about like, oh, yeah, you know, this is revolutionary.
You know, this is like, you know, this is a novel way to support artists.
You know, this is like, this is new, and it's totally not a scam, and it's, you know, it's just like multi-level marketing.
Like, it's not a pyramid scheme.
They reassure you over and over again, and then they'll post about like, oh, I work from home.
You know, I'm so, I'm so happy and grateful to have this opportunity.
You know, now I make so much money without even doing any work, and it's so easy.
And like, the point is not whether it's true or not.
The point is to convince people to get in on it, because that's how you make money is by scamming them.
So NFT people are out there just posting about how great their fucking NFTs are with the exact same, the exact same reason.
They're just trying to fucking, they're trying to sucker someone else into buying their NFTs for more money than they sold them for, or than they bought them for.
It's the same fucking scam.
I saw this one guy in the wild who was, I think it was in like a reply to a tweet about Steam saying no to NFT games, which is, you know, that's alright.
Based, I guess.
Pretty based, I guess. Probably not for a good reason, but it's not, you know, it says fuck you to NFTs, so that's good.
And then there's a bunch of NFT bros in the replies or all going like, ah, Steam, you're really lost to yourself a gamer, you know, all that sort of like stupid, stupid like seething, coping stuff.
But then there's this one guy who's like all high and mighty about it.
And he's like, oh well, you just got, I should, I would recommend you look into this because you're really missing out, you know, like just trying to be nice and civil about it.
He's not actually coming across.
Yeah, he's not, he's trying not to come across as a snarky person.
He's trying to come across as like, I know more than you do, but that's okay.
I'll tell you how.
And, you know, but like it's, it's so clear that like he has no like information.
I was waiting for him to like, like if he was replying to people like, okay, so what are the benefits?
Like what is the actual thing?
He just says, oh, no, just look into it.
Just look into it.
Just trust me.
Trust me that everything is good and that I'm smart.
I have a feeling that probably the market researchers at Steam did that.
You know, I have a feeling that they have someone who, who looks into this kind of thing.
Ah, it was just, it was just, it was so like, he said at some point like he had bought his like monkey leopard.
He bought his, he bought his D's nut.
Yeah.
He bought his one of those for like $300.
Of course.
So, so like somebody was saying, oh, what are you, you paid for that with your car?
Idiot.
And he's like, actually I just played $300 for it.
So, you know, it's relatively cheap.
It was a deal.
It's, it's only going to go up and it's like, okay, $300 for an avatar like that.
Um, you know, okay.
It, tell me, it makes, it makes me sad.
I don't know what, what, which, which is more sad.
Like the, you know, the fucking, the lazy shit, like the, the lazy lions and like the, the D's nuts and like, you know, the, the, the, the pixel punks and whatever.
Like the ones that just obviously look like shit and a bunch of like, and a bunch of like, sick of, sickos.
Like, you know, they're like posting, there's their avatar and they're posting around about how great it is and how cool it is and whatever.
I don't know if that is sadder or like, like real artists that make like a good piece and then like sell it as an NFT because that, that seems like more of a waste.
You know, like, like something like, obviously the lions are like an incredible fucking racket and just everyone involved is being scammed and it's, it's funny.
When, when someone is like a real artist and they make a piece and they sell it as an NFT, it's like, ah, there was something good here, but it's, but it's tainted now.
It's, it's weird.
I was, I think with, with a lot of the, like, you know, the, it being a scam and everything and people being stupid with their money.
That's funny. But like, the, the problem that I have that makes me sad is that the, the environmental damage that it causes that people just don't really seem to give a shit about.
Sure.
And well, you know, like, oh no, but they donated some, they donated like a few thousand bucks to like a charity or whatever.
So like, actually.
I donated an NFT to a charity.
Yeah, I donated them one of my line of a hundred thousand, you know, identical JPEGs that are all worth, you know, a, you know, 0.1 ETH a piece.
So that'll, that'll help, I think.
Like there was that one talking point that, oh, Ethereum is going to go carbon neutral.
So really it's fine if I do it right now when it isn't carbon neutral.
And I've not heard any news of it trying or succeeding to be carbon neutral as a cryptocurrency.
Probably saying that it will is enough.
Yeah, like that's just enough for them to not think like, oh, I'm not doing anything bad because eventually it'll be good.
But like, I feel like if they want to like convince people, their tactics seem to be just, I don't know, stupid, like, ugh, you fucking normies.
You're never going to make it.
You're NGMI because you're not in on it.
You're not, you don't know.
You're a fucking right-click site.
Yeah, not NGMI.
You're never going to make it.
Yeah, that's a thing they say apparently.
If you don't own fucking NFTs, you're never going to make it.
You're never going to make it if you don't own NFTs.
What does that fucking mean?
It's so straight.
It's just sort of like insult tactics, but it's like clearly people have problems with NFTs and crypto and all that.
And it's a lot of it is like the energy consumption.
Surely they should try to like solve those issues in order to make people more interested.
But they don't have like the brainpower to like think long term about how to get people interested in the scam.
They're just sort of like it's both, it's both like so ridiculously bad for everyone, including themselves.
And they have no way of like actually making a scam.
It's like a scam that doesn't even work.
It's not going to propagate much further than it already has, I don't think.
No, the way it's going, the people that are at the head of like the big fucking NFT rackets have already made their money.
And have either already fled or are going to flee soon or maybe they set it up in a way that they don't actually need to flee
because it's not technically, they didn't do anything illegal.
But you know, they won't be delivering on whatever it is these fucking rubes think they're going to get out of owning this shit.
Because why would they bother?
Tragically, fucking devastated to report looking now that you know last week I said that I was sad that I had not bought the dip in Bitcoin.
Well, I'm even sadder now because it has kept going up.
It has passed 60k again and that is, that hurts.
If I had bought when I was thinking of buying, if I had bought when I was briefly entertaining the thought of buying, I would have made 50%, I would have made a 50% return in the last like three weeks.
So please mourn for me, viewer, please fuck.
Right now you want people to not care about crypto so that the value goes down.
I mean, I do want that, I do want that.
It has not passed its previous high, which was achieved in April, but it is close.
It is fairly close and if it continues like this, it will shortly pass its old high, which will be very upsetting for me.
It will be very upsetting.
But I guess we'll see.
I guess we'll see.
I'm completely gone from that.
Please lie and go down, please lie and go down.
I mean, I care in that I really want it to fail.
I really want it to die and go away.
I'd be happy to see it fail, but I would be tempted.
I would only be tempted if it goes really low and I've said that before, but like every time it dips, I feel like it's nothing enough for me.
I'm not even talking about buying, I'm just saying, I just hate it.
On the larger scale, when I can't conceptually, it's not good.
I can't help it, but when I was into crypto for a little bit, it was neat.
I've seen the number go up.
Even though I knew it was like, this is dumb, but it's slightly more money than previous.
Slightly more money than previous, Ben.
That's true.
It's very exciting.
It's hard to completely discount that.
I understand the intoxication of when you're invested and you see number go up.
You feel a completely unearned sense of superiority.
Like you knew something.
Like you knew something when, of course, you didn't.
You just got lucky.
Roops for old roops.
I mean, for the most part.
Yeah, that's true.
Speaking of, that guy mansplaining NFTs.
I saw some amazing mansplaining on Twitter.
It was the funniest shit I've ever seen.
There was a, you know, that guy who was doing the impersonation of Robin Williams
that everyone said was really good or whatever?
No.
Did you not see that?
Some guy was doing like a tribute impression of Robin Williams.
Supposedly he does a really good Robin Williams impression.
Anyway, a bunch of people sent the clip, sent the video to Zelda Williams, his daughter.
And she posted like, hey guys, I'm only posting about this because I don't think it will stop unless I say something.
Please stop sending me the video.
The guy is very talented and all, but it's really weird to watch this ghoulish impersonation of my dead dad.
Thanks, goodbye.
And she said something about, in some part of it, he acts like,
she said something about him on his saddest day.
And I don't know exactly what day she was talking about,
but there's some part of it that is like a sad day for Robin Williams that he does an impersonation.
It is part of the impersonation.
And this guy responds to Zelda Williams and being like,
actually Robin Williams was not just a comedian.
He had a full range of emotions.
He had his sad days as well.
And it's part of the tribute, actually, that it includes that to his daughter.
To his daughter.
Man-splaining her dad to her.
Please tell me they didn't know it was...
I mean...
Oh, that's so bad.
It was the worst.
Okay, I got really upset seeing it.
And I typed an insulting comment and I replied to him.
I don't remember what it was. It was a fuck you of some kind.
And like, yes, obviously it's really bad.
It's like complete psycho behavior.
But then I stepped back and I was like,
okay, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Yes, it's terrible. It's a terrible thing this person is doing.
This person has royally fucked up.
But already, like, 500 people have told him,
shut the fuck up buddy, you're awful.
And also, this is a guy with like 50 followers
and Zelda Williams has like hundreds of thousands.
And like, I don't need to dog pile this person any further.
Yes, what he did was wrong.
But it's not necessary for me to protect Zelda Williams from this random guy.
Right?
So eventually I was like, what am I doing?
And I replied because like, it's stupid.
Why even fucking bother?
I don't know.
But what a thing to see.
I could not believe it.
That was some next level shit.
Wacky.
Yeah, wacky.
That was my week on Twitter, I guess.
Yeah, I guess my week on Twitter is a new corner.
New corner, my week on Twitter.
Just the sounds of Hellfire, because that's usually what it is.
Although it was quite good for me.
Whatever, Tober has been going well.
Yeah.
Been drawing a little drawing.
I really liked the drawing of...
Is it scraggy-aggy?
Scraggy-aggy.
Scraggy-aggy, yes.
I really liked the drawing of her and Pumpkin.
They're like, you grew over there.
I thought that was so cute.
Yes, I love that.
I was tired and I was like, oh shit, it's 1 a.m.
I haven't drawn today and I did that.
Lore.
It's great.
She's just like, cool.
That's why I grew.
That's what, yeah, true.
You know what, Pumpkin is cool.
Good job.
Pumpkin is so fucking great.
Is scraggity like her mom, sort of?
In my head, she's like a...
What's the word for like a not relative, an aunt?
A babysitter?
There's a word for it.
Oh, an Onesan.
Yes, the Onesan.
She's the scarecrow of that Pumpkin patch
and so she knows all the pumpkins that grow from there.
And Pumpk was, you know...
I guess she sees him as like an auntie or something.
Right, yeah.
Makes sense.
Kind of was like, oh wow, she grew in a patch.
Well, I guess why not?
Where else would she have come from?
If you think about it.
All the pumpkins, they grow.
Some of them, they go to the flower kingdom
where they're normal and other ones.
This is a secret lore, I'm telling you now.
Oh my God.
Secret, secret lore.
Some of them go to the flower kingdom, some of them.
The flower kingdom?
Yeah, where all the flowers from, the flower heads from there.
Oh my God, it's all connected.
I was like, that must be where flower heads from, right?
Oh, okay.
All right, sure.
And then some pumpkins, they get stabbed in the face,
they got their face cut out.
They become a jack-o'-lantern instead.
Damn.
That's what Pumpkin happened.
The two evolution routes that a pumpkin can take.
Yeah.
Very, huh, very cool.
Didn't even think about it.
Love it.
I love lore.
Yes, I've thought a long and hard about the world-building
of how to connect all of my comics together.
And it's really funny and really epic.
The kind of rules, actually.
Good job.
Pumpkin people is a very, very big part of the future.
Oh.
Oh my God.
And then, of course, Cowtown is nearby something town.
That's the same desert.
Something town?
Yeah, from Clarissa.
Oh, right, right.
Which I haven't read yet.
You didn't even know.
You didn't even know about that one.
No, I don't know.
I don't.
Okay.
It's all coming together.
And even more reason for me to finally read it then.
Hmm.
Yeah, I'm excited.
That's kind of exciting.
I like it a lot.
Yeah, I'm excited to write Belle Jape II.
It probably won't be called Belle Jape II because it has nothing to do with jail
or vaping it.
Unlike the first one.
Yes.
Bape, Bape, Jape, Belle, Bape, Jape.
Once she kept making it, saying it wrong, but I can't say it the way he said it.
What does he say?
Did he say jail, Bape?
Jail, Bape, yes.
Yeah.
Great.
Wait, now I forget what the actual, it's actually called Belle Jape, right?
Belle Jape.
Yeah, Belle Jape.
Yeah.
Because they're in jail and they should be on Belle.
Wait, but they don't.
And there's Jape-ery going on.
But there's no jail.
Oh, but they're out on, they're out on Belle, from jail.
Well, maybe there should be Belle, but there is, maybe there's no Belle and they gape their
way out of jail.
Really?
Right.
The title has no sense to it, but it's fun.
It sounds like what the story is.
It evokes the mood.
That's one way to look at it, I suppose.
Yes.
I gotta stop looking at this Bitcoin chart.
It's making me sad.
No more.
You absolute buffoon.
Yes.
True.
Oh, one more thing about NFTs that sucks.
I mean, there's lots of things that suck, but Steam said no.
But because Steam said no, Epic Games stepped in and said, hmm, we might consider it.
Of course.
We're going to counterculture stupid fucking idiots.
Nice.
So now, look forward to fucking NFTs in Fortnite.
I don't doubt that could happen.
That's the coolest thing.
That's the coolest sentence anyone's ever said.
Damn, first they put Martin Luther King Jr. in Fortnite and then they put NFTs.
Like, how much better can it get?
Now that is Epic.
Oh, no.
I liked Epic Games only because they gave me loads of free shit.
Every week, free games.
Like, oh my god, I'll simp for this company because they gave me free shit.
But now I can't because they're NFT fucks.
They're NFT scum.
They'll still get that free shit.
Yeah.
That's a...
Well, that's tragic.
Yeah.
I mean, when is a company not tragic?
True though, true though.
God.
Well, what else?
Okay.
Here's a funny thing.
Here's a funny thing that happened this week.
In my fucking disgusting rat-infested, raccoon-infested parking lot
behind my apartment that I live in,
they have fucking been backhoeing.
There's been a giant backhoe in there all week doing construction work and digging,
and they have successfully dug out a giant square pit
into what I assume will eventually be a basement for a house or building of some kind.
And there's just a giant pile of rubble and rock and dirt on the other side of the parking lot now.
I can see it through my curtain.
It's pretty hideous.
It's pretty funny.
The other thing that's been going on is that, like, okay, there was Columbus Day this past Sunday.
This past Sunday, they were all fucking day.
No, no, it was Monday, right?
Because they had the day off.
Yeah, it was the day they had off for Columbus Day or Indigenous People's Day.
And they're partying at this house.
This house is constantly throwing parties or some kind of frat house or something.
I don't know.
They're always throwing parties.
They sound huge.
And then, this past week, fucking my property manager,
my weirdo fucking gunnut freak of a man who is in charge of this property for the landlord or whatever,
I've just been hearing him screaming out the window at this fucking other house,
just like screaming at them to, like, turn the music down, turn the bass down.
The worst one I heard was he's screaming at them.
He's like, hey, turn the bass down.
Hey, you fucking, what do you think you're fucking doing?
Hey, turn the fucking bass down.
And then, like, I think they try to yell something back and he's like,
no, you can have your music.
You can have your music.
I don't give a fuck.
Just turn the fucking bass down.
It's like, okay.
And then, he immediately pivots into yelling at some child,
but in a friendly way.
He's yelling down into something.
I don't see any of this, but I can hear him yelling at, like, a child.
He's like, he's asking, like, hey, what do you, hey, what do you got there?
Hey, you're riding, you're riding your bike.
Hey, that's nice.
Hey, tell, hey, you know, take it easy on your mom or whatever.
It was like.
It was like he realized he was being, like, aggressive and then there was a child.
It's like, oh, I got to act nice in front of this child.
I got to scream pleasantries at this child from my fucking, from my balcony
with the fucking POWMIA flag or whatever.
Hey, you're walking there.
That's great.
I'm giving him, like, a New York accent because I don't know.
When I imagine someone screaming at partiers out of their apartment balcony,
it seems like a New York thing to do.
But no, it's here in my own backyard.
Yeah.
Boston.
He's a, I fucking hate that guy.
I don't know, although I hate the party house just as much.
So honestly, I don't know who I'm rooting for in this, in this, in this conflict.
Maybe they'll take each other out.
Yeah.
We mutually annihilate one another.
What else did I do?
Oh, Crack's birthday was yesterday.
Crack.
Yeah.
World-famous creator of Endless War and well as the world, as well as of,
isthereanrvyet.com and many other, and many other famous projects.
Turn 30 yesterday and I went and hung out with him for that.
And we had Indian food.
And I bought, the most, the most exciting thing for me was buying,
I bought a bunch of, I bought a bunch of weird cakes from my local Russian bazaar.
For, for, for Munchie's birthday, like a month ago, I bought some weird cake
that was called Smetanik.
I think I mentioned this.
And that was okay.
That was okay.
I bought so much of it.
I bought a more modest amount this time and I still had leftovers.
So I made the right decision.
I bought a more modest amount and I bought an assortment of various things.
I bought a cake called Rizik and I bought a different cake called Spartak
that were kind of similar, but they were, they were different too.
They had different flavors in them.
And I bought, oh, okay.
This is a deep cut.
Long, long ago on the PCP, Mage was talking about Lithuanian desserts.
And one time she mentioned something called bird's milk that I was very curious about.
Oh, yeah.
And, and, and miracle of miracles, they had bird's milk at the bazaar.
And I bought it and it was okay.
I didn't love it, but it was, it was pretty good.
How would you milk a bird?
Well, well, the, the idea is that it's like, you know, it's not something that...
Like an egg and a milk inside.
Well, it's like birds don't give milk.
So to call it bird's milk is to suggest that it is something incredibly rare and like precious.
Right?
Oh, I see.
But it was just okay.
It was okay.
I mean, I liked some of the other stuff, but yeah, it was kind of like a marshmallow-y.
It's sort of like a spongy kind of marshmallow.
It's not really a cake.
It's like a marshmallow-y thing that you cut slices of.
They had another marshmallow-y thing called a white zephyr.
And the white zephyr, you, it was like in a ball.
It was like a swirly ball.
It looked like a, like a meringue cookie, but it was spongy and you would slice off slices of it.
And it tasted kind of like, it was like fruity actually.
I thought it would be like vanilla because it was white and puffy, but no, it tasted like apples.
It was a little bit tangy and had like an apple flavor to it.
And then the other thing I got, okay, the best thing I got by far was this, it was called a, it was called dulce de leche waffle cake.
And it was like crunchy.
It was kind of crunchy.
It was sort of like one of those, those like waffle stick bars.
I don't know.
There's a kind of cookie that is like waffle sort of and it's, they come in little sticks and they're layered.
It was kind of like one of those, but it was full of some kind of wall nutty dulce de leche goo.
It was so crispy and also so gooey and had such a delicious nutty walnut flavor.
That shit was an insane.
That shit was great.
It was so, that was so good.
The other stuff was pretty good.
The rizik was okay.
It was very soft.
It was very tender, creamy.
It was better.
It was a bit better than the, than the smetanic.
The spartak was even better than the rizik because it was basically the rizik,
but it was also like chocolatey and coffee kind of flavor, which was even better.
And those were good.
Those were just kind of cake in a good way.
But this crispy gooey fucking waffle cake, dulce de leche waffle cake, I can't believe it.
It's my new favorite dessert as wild.
Did I just spell that?
I think it, I'm not sure if I'm saying it right, but it's D-U-L-C-E.
And then it's three separate words.
Dulce de leche, L-E-C-H-E.
It means, it means like sweet of the milk.
So I assume it's milk.
Yeah, I know, leche means milk.
Yeah.
Dulce de leche.
It means milk, milk sweet.
Caramelized milk or milk jam.
Milk jam.
Prepared by slowly heating sugar and milk over a period of several hours.
I usually think of it as like a Mexican thing, because the name is Spanish,
but I'm sure they probably do it in all kinds of cultures,
but I'm sure they don't call it dulce de leche in Russia,
but probably they just called it that because the concept would be more familiar to Americans
by its Spanish name.
It is from Latin America, apparently.
That's cool.
I would believe, though, that Russian cooking had a similar thing you could do with milk.
Yes, those Russians always be drinking milk.
They always.
I mean, that's where white people countries is where milk drinking happens,
because white people develop the gene for lactose tolerance.
The makes the skin white?
No, this is a thing.
White people are way less likely to be lactose intolerant.
Non-white people are much more likely to be lactose intolerant,
and it's because just geographically, where white people came from,
there were more cows and more access to dairy food.
Lactose.
And so white people just kind of evolved to be able to tolerate lactose better.
Interesting.
Yeah.
Hell, yeah.
Phrenology.
Race realism.
Fun facts.
That's a fun fact about milk.
Hey, I'm just saying fun facts, okay?
I'm just saying fun facts.
John Tron just wanted to say some fun facts.
That one time with Destiny, he just wanted to share some fun facts he thought
or might be true.
Hell fucking, yeah.
How long have we been going?
Okay, we're over an hour.
Pretty good.
I've exhausted my list of topics,
although usually I tend to think of some stuff last minute.
You got anything else going on?
The only thing is that I've been using my new tablet,
which I got from the Lord of Ghost Kickstarter stretch goal to get a tablet,
and I got one.
Right.
I think I may have mentioned it on the PCP already.
I don't know how to say it.
I think you mentioned it.
I think you might have mentioned it.
Canvas 13.
It's the first tablet I've had that plugs in with an HDMI
and is a screen as well as a pen,
and it's got buttons on the side, and it's all very nice and sleek.
It came with a funny glove.
Is it your first tablet that has hotkey buttons?
Yeah, otherwise I'd use...
I guess I did have the iPad though.
That was all the finger gesture stuff.
That's exactly what I said, but this is bigger and it's cooler,
and it works with my PC.
How big is it?
13 inches, because it's the 13, maybe?
Let me measure it.
Oh yeah, the iPad you have to draw on separately,
and then you would have to send the file to your computer, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, that sucks.
Yeah, this is 13 inch, so bigger than my iPad.
Hold on.
13 inch tablet.
I want to see how...
I can't imagine it in my head.
It's not the biggest, but it's good and better than...
Is it roughly iPad size?
I mean, my iPad was kind of a small one,
so maybe I don't know how to judge sizes.
Yeah, okay.
It's like a sheet of A4 paper, or thereabouts.
We don't...
Fuck, we don't call it A4.
Do you know...
Europeans and their fucking A4 paper...
Sick.
What the hell do you call normal paper?
Nine and a half...
We call it eight and a half by eleven, like sensible people.
Is it even the same measurements as A4?
Hold on.
Is it? Let's find out. A4...
Well, okay, regular printer paper is eight and a half by eleven.
So if A4 is regular printer paper, then yeah, it's the same size.
I assume printers are the same, so yes, that would be the same.
Okay, eight...
I'm going to paper sizes.org to find out...
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, right, because you guys don't...
Oh, is it not quite?
Okay, I'm looking it up, and A4 is...
It's 8.3 by 11.7 inches.
So yeah, it actually might be slightly different.
You're using inches we're using millimeters.
Yeah, but...
So ours is exactly 210 by 297, and yours is 215.9 millimeters by 279.4 millimeters.
This is the metric shit.
So it's almost...
I'm actually shocked.
I'm actually shocked that we don't just use the exact same size of paper.
That fucks me up.
That's a little...
Your paper is a little shorter and a little wider.
Just like us.
Just like you.
Just like our population.
Fucking LeMau.
Well, okay, so basically...
It makes sense, because I see on printing sites for a lot of ghosts or other,
and I'm like, you know, you've got all these normal ones I understand,
and then the U.S. letter.
It's like, what is...
Huh?
Why would I do that?
Because we do it in fucking Imperial.
We do it in Imperial units.
Imperials.
Those were the bad guys in Star Wars.
They were the bad guys in real life, too.
But now we're the bad guys.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
Did you know that Star Wars is based on a real shit?
It's called war.
It really happened.
Did you hear the stormtroopers were a thing in real life, too?
Oh, what the fuck, dude?
Stormtroopers were a German soldier thing, I think, actually.
I don't know if they were...
Hitler's stormtroopers, but they were in German.
I think they were...
Were they called like the Sturmwaffe or something?
I know they use the phrase Sturmendrang,
which was like...
Sturmendrang is like...
Is that like...
Wait, hold on.
Sturm und...
Okay, I know that the final bad guy in Advance Wars
is named Sturm after Sturmendrang.
Oh, Sturmendrang...
Oh, sorry.
No, this is wrong.
Sturmendrang is a literary and artistic movement in Germany
in the late 18th century,
characterized by the expression of emotional unrest
and a rejection of neoclassical literary norms.
Okay, so that's not actually what I was thinking of.
Okay, the term Sturmabteilung...
I don't know how to pronounce...
Oh, wait.
We can do the pronounced thing.
Google.
Show me what mouth shapes to make.
Oh, I think it's Sturmabteilung.
I think it's Sturmabteilung is probably how you say it.
Right, British...
Let me...
Sturmabteilung.
Okay, so the Sturmabteilung...
And then it says...
Sturmabteilung.
The first official German stormtrooper unit
was authorized so much second 1915 on the western front.
So they called it stormtroopers in Wikipedia.
Okay, well, Wikipedia says it's literally storm detachment.
Sturmtrippen.
Oh, really? They have Sturmtrippen?
Sturmtrippen were special soldiers of the German army
in the last years of World War I.
Yeah, I think I learned that years ago.
I was like, oh my God, Star Wars.
Oh my God, it was just like Star Wars in real life.
This reminds me of when I learned the translation
for the Sailor Scouts, the Sailor Senchi,
how in English they call them Scouts,
but really the term Senchi just means soldier or warrior.
Oh, yeah, but they're women, so they could possibly be proper soldiers.
They're just merely Scouts.
I'm not sure if it's like they were women,
or it's because it's a kid's show
and they didn't want to make it about soldiers, warriors, or whatever.
Maybe they thought that was too military,
or guardian I think would maybe be another way to say it.
Sailor soldier.
Yeah, most literally I think it would be a soldier in an army.
But I think in England they call them,
or in English in the West they call them,
I think they might have switched up a little bit over the translation,
but yeah, they usually called them,
in the show they were called the Sailor Scouts.
And I think they translated the title
as I think it was like Pretty Guardian Sailor Moon
instead of like Pretty Warrior Sailor Moon.
That's neat.
That's just an interesting quirk of translation
that I find very funny.
Pretty Stormtrooper Sailor Moon.
Stormtrooper Sailor Moon, yeah.
Stormtrooper Sailor Moon.
Yeah, in Germany that's how they translated it.
Sailor is kind of like an SS officer if you think about it.
Ah, geez, Rick.
Ah, shit. Ah, fuck.
But yeah, about the tablet, it's good.
Yes.
I draw, and it's got all the buttons on the side.
I can do like, I can set one of the buttons to be
Control V.
Yes, back.
No, what's the backwards one?
Control Z.
How do you not know that it's Control Z?
Because I've been using that button so long I forgot
what it is that I do.
What the fuck? Okay.
I don't even look at my keyboard when I'm actually drawing.
That's like forgetting what Control C is.
What about when you type?
What about when you type like in a word processor?
Don't you Control Z to undo?
Yeah, but I don't look at it.
I just remember it from muscle memory.
You were out of your fucking mind.
You're not even human.
What do you mean?
I don't need to look at it.
Yeah, but you just know because people talk about it.
People talk about Control Z.
I do know.
Ben, I just made a mistake just now.
No, it's not just a mistake.
It's over for you.
It's over.
That's it.
There's no more.
You're going to jail.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
The buttons.
Thank you.
I turned the buttons.
I set the buttons to be one of them.
Control Z.
I think that's why I tripped up.
I would say Control Z, but then you'd say,
how British?
And I'm like, oh, no, I've made fun of,
I've made fun of few people enough for one day.
Oh, good.
The point has been made.
Fuck yeah.
Yeah.
No more bullying.
Cool.
All right.
Fair enough.
And then there's like one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Is that eight?
Yes.
Eight buttons.
All right.
I'm going to do all these different things like eraser and fill tool and lasso makes things
quicker.
I like that.
Quick is good.
Oh, wait, not to derail, but speaking of quick is good.
Did you see that thread on Twitter of the guy saying that like,
Oh, I did.
Yes.
About the speed.
Like so many of the radical left are speed runners because like speed running is an exercise.
It's like it's like demonstrates like a lack of work ethic because it's about doing.
Yeah, it was very confusing.
I tried to read it like three or four times to understand what his point was.
I think it's just sort of the left is lazy.
It's like the left is lazy and speed running is also lazy because I know that it takes
a lot of work to get the speed run down, but it's all work done in service of just beating
the game, which is what a normal player would accomplish in less time.
You know, it's about it's about doing it.
Yeah, it's about doing it fast instead of doing it right.
And that's lazy.
I just I just really love.
I love his the way the thread continue like goes and he every so often he's like, and
obviously this means like something completely stupid that no one would ever think.
Some some weird fucking like Jordan Peterson, Carl Young like weird heroes, heroes journey
symbology shit that doesn't fucking mean anything.
But he thinks it's like he thinks he's really on to something.
He's like he says Petersonian.
It's Peterson.
Yeah.
It's genuinely I cannot tell if this guy is joking or not.
I mean, it's it's it's funnier and I like it more if he's not joking.
Yeah.
And then there was a bit where it's like, oh, let me find it.
Let me let me read it.
Type in weird.
Oh, wait, you've replied to it.
I'm looking I'm looking at it right now.
Of course, of course, he has to he has to make a reply tweet saying, oh, I sure did trigger
a lot of libs in with this comment.
He's not even he's not even well, he doesn't say lips.
He says left is because he calls himself center left.
So he's not a conservative per se, but he is like an anti woke center left, whatever
that fucking means.
Okay, this is the part like number 10 to number 11.
Yeah, where he's sort of going.
All right, I'll just read it.
In other words, there is a connection between sexuality and creativity that we see throughout
time as Peterson points out with the Tiamat and other examples.
Yes, Tiamat, the multi headed dragon, of course.
In the sexual marketplace, which archetypes are simultaneously deemed the most creative
and value the highest?
Next tweet.
The answer is obviously entrepreneurs like Elon Musk and others.
Of course.
Like obviously is Elon Musk.
Obviously that's the answer.
The most sexually creative person of all.
I know what you were thinking when I asked that question.
Obviously you were picturing Elon Musk as the most, most highly valued in the sexual
marketplace person that I can imagine.
Yes.
It's just it's it's like every stereotype of this sort of person.
It's great.
And then.
Okay, the shit about the sexual archetype is so is that I genuinely I genuinely don't
even know what he's talking about.
I have no idea.
I think he starts off with.
Yeah.
It's it's it's a Jordan Peterson line of talking.
Yes.
Jordan Peterson generally for a lot of people seems to be like letting, you know, young
men know that they're smart and they're Rick Sanchez.
And that makes them better for society if they're buying a book.
Sort of.
So like.
I think that's what that's what some people take from it.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I have not read Jordan Peterson.
So I have no idea what he's actually getting at.
There's a lot of stuff that he's sort of implying and assuming that everyone knows
his fact.
Yeah.
And he's not explaining it in the context of speed running.
So I don't know what his actual point.
I don't think he makes a point.
He says.
Okay.
For he started.
I think he does.
He starts up really strong.
His first week ends with the reason is to elevate alternate sexual archetypes in the
marketplace.
Parentheses quote fastest Mario.
So he's saying.
Okay.
I don't get this at all.
He's saying that fastest Mario is a alternative sexual archetype in the sexual marketplace.
I.
I don't even.
I don't even know what he's getting at there.
Like.
I can only assume that like it is a it is like a something.
It is something you can do to be like sexually valued by your peers is to be the fastest
Mario and like that's that's hot to some people.
I suppose that's what I can gather from like the sexual marketplace wording being like oh
well if you want women to fuck you sexual marketplace you need to like win in the sexual marketplace
like you can be an entrepreneur billionaire like Elon Musk or you can be the fastest Mario.
The left wants everyone to be the fastest Mario instead of being a creative individual
like Elon Musk a generative rich guy like Elon Musk.
This is just so wacky.
His his point at the end he says I'm not saying speedrunning is bad but rather that thinking
about the talk the topic philosophically there are dangerous elements within it elements
which he describes as leftist and doesn't I don't think he elaborates on why the leftistness
of it is a bad thing.
Okay.
This is this is the part they okay and explaining the sexual argument.
Okay he says they are aiming to make a new sexual archetype based upon speed rather than
doing things right and refuse ownership of what few innovations they can provide to their
own scene denying creativity within their very own sexual archetype.
It's like okay so I what like I get I would understand what he means if he were saying
like they value speed over doing it right like obviously that's stupid because like
if you're speedrunning the right way to speedrunning is to do it fast.
This this guy is he just values he thinks that just playing the game the way you're supposed
to play it like a casual player would is like just just a priori either as good or better
than speedrunning it and like that's just a given fact and like to do to do otherwise
is to like pervert the you know the natural order.
It would be it would be something very vague that he couldn't actually explain because
like if if if speedrunning is a meaningless pastime because you could complete the game
quicker without practicing the speedrun then he's therefore saying that time saved is like
the most important aspect of media and therefore you don't need to do any of it.
You don't need to see any musicals play any games at all.
You could simply you could simply not play the game.
You could simply I don't know breed your wife or work an extra shift or work an extra shift
at the Shake Shack and get and get some money to pay for the child you will eventually
sire with your with your with your God.
Mario DNA.
Yes.
But I don't know he calls it a sexual archetype and I don't know.
I don't know what he means.
Is he just saying like a I imagine he means a a a sort of way of of valuing other people.
I think that is based on speed where it's like in his like in his mind the way things are
is that people are valued for quote unquote doing things right doing things the right
way which is I guess what Elon Musk and his mind and the left is like no that is bad doing
it fast is better instead of being valued for doing things right.
You're valued for doing things quick and that would be bad for him because he does things
right.
There's so many assumptions like just the assumption that yeah the right way to Elon
Musk is a paragon of the right way to do things whatever whatever that is Elon Musk we know
we know for sure that Elon Musk is a paragon of it right that much there it can be no debate
on.
I just it's funny someone pointed out in the comments that like boy if you think if you
think this about speedrunning wait until you hear about the sport of real running which
is also just about going from one place to another as fast as possible and spending your
whole life training yourself to do exactly that.
Literally you could say the exact same thing about sports I don't know just a just a complete
fucking skit so I was totally deranged individual very funny very cool loved every second of
it.
Oh I guess the last thing that I have wanted to mention is the funny bit in the in the
latest void gazers you don't have to talk too long about this but the funny bit in the
latest void gazers where Trixie says that she would quote unquote forgive me if I commit
Harakiri and kill myself I didn't watch the video but I Simsie time stamped for me the
part where she says that and it was very very not as funny as it sounds because it was very
awkward and sort of uncomfortable and to watch her like fumble like literally fumble and like
fuck up and drop the mic as she's it's it's the last thing it's literally the last thing
they say in the video is Trixie telling me to kill myself check it out I guess check it
out if you want link in the description to the time step you know what yeah fuck it link
in the description to the time stamp wait hold on I'll find it from my server but the bug
scroll back a little bit they posted it they posted it now before that now before that
no here we go here we go copy link posting that right on the server time stamp for your
convenience do you like Pokemon oh yeah no there we fucking no no no no I don't like
Pokemon I don't I kind of don't in a way I was thinking about this the other day I was
thinking how sad it is that like I think I'm just I think I'm probably never going to buy
Pokemon game again because I genuinely no longer believe that the Pokemon company actually
wants to make their video games good I genuinely don't think yeah I mean I don't know
about caring I'm sure individual artists want to work and make things good but like
ultimately doesn't end up being sure something that looks like people care it looks like
thrown together thing every time which it would be okay if I couldn't tell in the final
product but like I can tell in the final product it's just insulting but we've but we've
talked about that we've talked about that over and over plenty of times before yeah I
don't know anything else before we move on to voicemails no just make sure to check out
Clarissa chapter 3 Clarissa all the chapters Clarissa gun smoke on the Gibb and take dot
site why yes I and I that goes for me to when what day do you think you're going to post
the last chapter I've posted each chapter on Tuesday so it should be out on Tuesday
but by the time you're listening to this it'll have been out I okay I will Tuesday
wait Tuesday yeah you said sorry cool I will check it out then I am a little distracted
because all right this is hard to explain but so you know you know how on a computer
you've got like windows and they like open and they move or you move them around
mm-hmm the the window the in the chrome window that I have open that has the speak pipe links
in it I oh there it finally went I've been clicking on it for several minutes and it just
has not been like moving it has just been staying behind all the it just didn't it was
like no you can't click on that okay I have issues like that sometimes it's still happening
where because I'm clicking on a different tab and it's not switching tabs it like doesn't
care that I click click click sometimes okay it okay it went okay it went sometimes for
some reason like a full-screen application will it be visually there but I can't click
on it I would click on whatever window is underneath and I have no idea why that happens
and how to fix it sometimes I just need to minimize it and maximize it and then it works
again yeah a thing a thing that happens a thing that keeps happening to me is that I
will have multiple chrome windows open and one of them will pop to the front like one
that I'm not using it will just randomly pop to the front and then I will I will try to
okay like click on the other one that I want to be using to get that to the front but it
doesn't work I can't click on it I have to click on the one that came to the front first
and then it will let me re-click on the other one that I want to be and then and then it
will come to the front and it's a small annoyance but it happens like multiple times a day and
every time I'm just I'm stuck like why like why why did you do this like what what would
cause this and will you please stop I don't know are you are you there yep okay I heard
a beep I wasn't sure if you just connected yeah so for oh my god fuck off I'm getting
mad just let me switch tabs just let me switch tabs okay thanks shit sorry right the first
voicemail of the day is called delta rune not isekai and there it is three two one go
in delta rune they come from a fantasy world it's not an isekai an isekai you need to come
from the real world a world based off of our reality in delta rune they come from a world
full of monsters and bullshit you fool I mean where does it say that whereas I mean all
what do you mean where does it say that there's a there's there's oh you you mean where does
it say that it has to come from our world not where does it say that the world of delta
rune is full of monsters and and and while while we're at it all anime looks completely
different from real world so like how based is it in reality if people's eyes are that
maybe that's a weak argument but that's pretty it's definitely the world of like sword art
online is obviously supposed to be the real world the delta rune world okay okay I don't
know I think this is kind of an interesting objection it's it's really just sort of like
the a real world right like I feel like it's that doesn't have like oh I wouldn't have
America they don't have references to real countries it's all just sort of things that
would exist in our real world like cars and houses and trash cans and stuff cafes and
but there's just happens to be monsters there but there's no countries okay to the like
no actual named similarities to low real life locations so where where is it so here's
a thought I think I actually kind of agree with this guy because if you if you what I'm
trying to say okay if the if the definition of an isekai is just that like the character
like goes somewhere or goes on a journey or goes to a different place even in a metaphorical
sense then like every story is an isekai because that's like that's literally like right in
like the hero's journey like you start in like the initial like place of safety and
childhood and then you you know something disrupts the order and then you have to go
on some kind of journey in order to like Delta Rune return with the moon or whatever
but it's not like a location that exists in like it's it's a magical not real reality
that they travel to I think I think I know what you're saying and I think okay yeah I
think the distinction for me is like yes obviously obviously the the world of Delta
Rune has these like creatures in it but the question yeah if you start in a fantasy world
but you go on a journey that is I would say that's not an isekai I'm like okay yes well
it's not just a journey I consider a journey to be like a physical like a like a you know
a trip like a car ride or whatever yes but but but there's like it's a fantasy within
a fantasy world because like the dark world when they stop playing at the end of chapter
one they're in a room with symbols and icons that represent all of the people that were
in the fantasy world yeah so that so that fantasy world doesn't isn't real in the same
way that the world they're in then is real the I would say that if I wanted to call Delta
Rune an isekai I think my argument would have to be that like yes elements elements of the
world as the real world as it's portrayed in Delta Rune are not the same as our own
you know yes there are monsters and stuff there are animal people and maybe there's
other stuff that I'm forgetting but like it's it's nevertheless meant to be it's
nevertheless meant to be you know analogous to the real world in the way that like it
still counts as the real world like it's still like you know a town like a regular town
even if it has like monster yeah there's no there's no experience points and fighting
battles and RPG mechanics in that world that's just you go to school you go to work
there's money it's physically equivalent I think I think that's a I honestly I think
this guy has a point but I feel like that would be my argument I mean I never really
calling Delta Rune an isekai in the first place if I wanted to say that Delta Rune is
not an isekai I think my argument would have to be that like the yeah the world that they
go to is not even a real world it's they're like it seems like they're just making it
up in their imagination or something yeah like magic works in the dark world and it
doesn't work but then again I guess the world I guess the world that they go to in
Sword Art Online is not a real world it's just a computer simulation so maybe that
argument doesn't hold any water okay is Sword Art Online even an isekai I think
almost everyone would call it an isekai because that's like because it's about going
from the real world to a fantasy world even if it's a video games I don't think
yeah I feel pretty confident in calling it one I mean I'm it's interesting because
like it's a but by that logic I guess an imaginary world also counts as another
world yeah an imaginary world or a dream like fucking Freddy Krueger or something or
or like Freddy Krueger an isekai is nightmare on 13 on Elm Street an isekai
and I'm gonna say no for that one yeah so I feel like one I feel like for me
the distinction needs to be the laws of physics are just different and there it's
it's it's just could not the stuff that exists in that world could not exist in
the real world which does work with Sword Art Online even though that's a video
game yeah and so it's a simulation it's not literally happening it's bits and
bytes simulating it in all of the people's brains who are hooked up to the
machine that's playing the game so like there's there's some way to distinguish
it but I don't know if I would hello hello no I don't know Jesus did you hear that
I heard a shouting person was that the shouter yes that's the shouter asking me is
that my shopping cart no it's not my fucking shopping cart leave me alone
this is the first this is the first time that he has that anyone has knocked on
my window thankfully I hope it never happens again he's outside the window
well I'm on the first floor like he's just standing in the parking lot oh okay
yeah yeah that was that was awful I hated that I was gonna say I was gonna
say Isekai Sword Art Online Sword Art Online oh I think our headset I think that
a key part of the the Isekai genre is it's not enough to merely go to another
world I think the tone has to be like it has to be like a wish fulfillment
like wouldn't it be cool to go to this world like I mean it's all it's meant to be
like heart huh I mean are there stories where you go to a world that sucks well
how about Silent Hill um I feel like Silent Hill is like basically every in
Silent Hill you are a guy living in the real world and then you are transported
to this other world where crazy shit happens which is the definition of an
Isekai but it's not an Isekai because it's not a wish fulfillment like wouldn't
this be cool it's like oh my god it's so scary this this other world is like a
reflection of my nightmares and guilt and that feels like an important part of the
genre I guess I'm trying to think of like because like there's no such thing as
an Isekai that's all good because then there's no story well it's a it's a tone
thing if wish fulfillment obviously there will be little timmy thinking like I
wish I could fucking use a sword and kill people and he goes to an Isekai he gets
Isekai and I'm like yes now I can do it this is great but there are challenges
with with swords come fighting and war and it's like oh shit true though so I
yeah okay yeah that works so it but if but if someone plays Silent Hill and they
don't think it's scary and they think it's cool like oh I wish I were fucking
wandering around in the fog that would be so sick that then it becomes an Isekai
for them yeah hmm hmm but you people get transported to a new world and for
each individual person it could be an Isekai or not depends yeah it's up to
the individual whether it's an Isekai yeah that works for me I guess another
thing is is the Sword Art Online being a video game as a viewer of the art the
you know the show we're getting we can see it as an Isekai but for them they're
just playing a video game like yeah when you play and VR game it like on stream
on twitch or whatever are you getting Isekai into that video game right then
when you're when you're watching someone stream on twitch no when you're streaming
what when you're like put on the VR headset and you're in half-life Alex are
you Isekai in that moment or is Isekai only an art form genre trope thing I
mean I think I think the the the the boring answer is yes it's just a
literary genre art trope thing but it's funnier to say that yes you can Isekai
yourself in real life if you get really grossed in a game you play Minecraft for
40 hours then you become Isekai into it absolutely 40 hours straight that is I
choose I choose to believe that that is the case yes alright next voicemail is
called fuck where did it where did I put it next voicemail is called what I say
to my parents every Friday afternoon 3 2 1 go yeah yeah true tell if they ask
what you do every Friday at 2 p.m. unless it's late just tell them I'm getting
high on PCP and they'll know they'll know what you mean they're doing I tell I tell
everyone I know that I'm doing PC I'm doing the PCP and they think doing I just
say it weird I'm doing I'm doing they think I'm just they think I'm talking
about listening to the podcast for some reason next voicemail is called better
than every YIG song 3 2 1 go nice fucking audio quality isn't this a Jesse
song yeah maybe they're adding to it I remember Jesse saying this line and making
a rap of him self saying this this is different they're doing the instrumental
I don't get it I think I haven't listened to it in a while I don't get it
really get inside my butt I don't get it I don't get it why doesn't Barney grow up with his audience
what was that thing last thing that I said why didn't why didn't Barney grow up with his audience
the funniest thing I've ever said holy shit oh it did it became Susie Delta run
oh true true true this is better than every YIG song because I liked it
it gave me a chuckle man you believe so much can you believe that YIG doesn't
even write their own beats there can't even they can't even write a beat they
can't even make their own beat literally all they have is their fucking middle
school rap rhymes literally all they have is their fucking like is their fucking
like their fucking basic ass elementary school rhymes I do feels good oh man
sometimes it feels sad but that's okay cuz I'm based I feel I feel bad and
that's good but it's okay cuz I got wood so I feel bad and that's not good I'm
not good and that's not bad Wreck-It Ralph yeah okay next voicemail is gone
shoutouts to Wreck-It Ralph next voicemail let's give him a producer credit on the album
next voicemail is called interview I saw this week three two one go
last question mr. president is there any person you just hate yes there's one
person I hate his name has been saint he hosts this podcast where he's Mr. Obama
to dozens of listeners he's contributing to the dissolution of rational discourse
particularly on platforms like tiktok in my space he's the kind of leftist we
need to fight because frankly he makes us look stupid can you tell me what show
he on it's called digi's anime podcast what show he on mr. Obama mr. Obama with
all due respect you're a fucking bitch sir mr. president mr. president what are
you gonna do drone strike me what he he will he joked about he joked about
drone strike and his daughter's boyfriend that one time so oh yeah why
why not I guess he's gone fucking mad with power so strong even now he's
insanely powerful he is he's just overflowing he built all of this
drones himself he I would say with his hive mind brain I would say that he
embodies the sexual archetype based on doing things right and on a crewing
accruing power in the conventional way is very highly valued in the sexual
marketplace is what I is the if you ask me who is Obama I would say that
next voicemail is called the legend of oblivion fall 3 2 1 go oblivion fall
what an absolute legend yes just wants to titty but he can't have it even though
it's right in front of him he won't even acknowledge it because he's a true
hero and scholar and gentlemen and that that is what true love is all about I
need to rub one out for you it's the only way I know how to how to pay my tribute
so keep up the good work man just you're a hero true true oblivion fall is a
heroic character in my in my personal telling of the the saga of the PCP
you should get all that money from the care from the indigo go he should yeah
he's yeah honestly he hero statue he deserves the top surgery in my opinion
do the swapsies otherwise it's just a waste could you do that could you just
plant tits from one person to another I don't know because the way breast
surgery works you you put like a silicon thing in there I don't think you can
transplant them it'll be wacky and probably did you know I don't know I
don't know anything about it transplant other body you can transplant other body
parts I have no idea hmm I've never really looked into it it could be possible
that'd be really funny really funny if that could happen it seems it seems like
it would be possible but I mean what the I don't fucking know anything so who
knows I just like wondering where they would connect you need to slice the
chest off in order to put the breast on I feel like there's so many things that go
wrong well I mean yeah sure but I mean that's that's that's surgery for that
surgery medicine it is fucking scary holy shit
oh okay next voicemail is called 770 is it is called it's Gines it's Gines
3 2 1 go I want to have a similar work ethic as Trixie, Alice Jess, and Davies
Jesus so I need you guys to shame me so I don't end up going on social media every
few minutes instead of being focused on the things that gonna make me happy in
the long run learning and creation way better than entertainment
right just gotta be focused on the things that will make you happy true and
of course do is doing as I do doing as I say and not as I do in that way is very
good because I am very prone to distraction and spending time on social
media so I'm glad you're not taking a lesson from my actions it is somewhat
amusing that they say Trixie, Jessie, and Davoo
three people who have made nothing for a very long time
three yeah three yeah like yeah I don't know what's up with that I almost don't
I know what they mean though like the heyday but like I don't know
Davoo didn't I mean Davoo
Davoo did a lot of editing work I guess is what they're talking about
this is stupid stupid examples but I understand the point you're trying to
make yeah focus is good distraction is bad I am guilty of it much myself get
cold turkey it's so easy yeah pay it like costs like I don't know 20 bucks and
you have a program that can block you from this distractions you don't even
need to try you just set it up so that you can't undo it and then you're like
fuck no I can't go on Twitter how about then you forget about it after an hour
how about you set yourself a challenge we're like okay I will I will voluntarily
not go on anything that is a distraction and then the punishment you set for
yourself is if I fail if I fail to not do the things I said I would not do then
I will force then I will have to buy cold turkey I will have to spend that $20
and I don't want to spend that $20 so I'm gonna make myself not do it with will
power and the punishment for not doing it you gotta buy cold turkey yeah I mean
you have to do you have to follow through though if you don't follow through
and buy cold turkey then then you'll never yeah if you tell yourself I will do
this thing and then you don't follow through it you're gonna then you're
gonna know then yourself is going to learn that you are a liar and you will
not be held held held them responsible for the thing their promises they make
and that's a fucking that's a road that way lies madness you'll you start you
start you start you start dropping responsibilities like that and you
will you will fall find yourself deep in the pit of missed opportunity so
watch out next voicemail is called did I already put it there I think I did
yeah the next one is the next one is called ideas five months late three two
one go in episode 260 you talked about self-diagnosing autism and gender dysphoria
coming to the conclusion that autism is probably too complicated but that gender
dysphoria is just being sad about your gender I've got two counter ideas first
pretty much all mental illnesses require the strange mental state to make your life
or the life of those around you worse and for a long period of time just being
sad about gender doesn't always meet that and secondly I think autism is a bad
comparison talking about self-identified mental illnesses I put gender dysphoria
in the same camps of depression and anxiety disorders having a negative
emotional state for a long period of time so should we accept people self-diagnosis
or for those conditions I don't know and have the answers discussing yourselves
and by the way this isn't a defend true scum trans rights are human rights even
without a doctor's note yeah I mean autism might not be the perfect one-to-one
comparison I forget the conversation exactly but yeah I think if gender
dysphoria can be self-diagnosed and it can because I mean once you feel it you're
like oh you know I get it and then yeah really the proof is in the the
transitioning and then feeling the gender euphoria when you when you do
something completely different and then like it feels better than you would have
expected I mean I feel like that's some sort of a proof it's like well it's like
I mean having gender dysphoria or or any I mean it's like how do you know that
you're happy how do you know that you feel happiness well you feel it and if
you feel it then you have it and I mean what what more is there to say about
something like that autism is you know it's maybe more you may not you don't
feel like oh I feel very autistic today you just you yeah yeah it's a completely
it's a different beast yeah so I guess I think I agree with his point maybe
something like depression and anxiety is more of I mean depression is like you
know there's there's being depressed there's being the mood depressed and
then there's having like depressive disorder which is like yeah I think the
when it comes to depression I don't think most people know where the line is
between the disorder and like feeling depressed yeah and I I feel like it
doesn't matter most of the time hmm I think it matters in terms of treatment
it matters in terms of like sure what what the prognosis is for your issue yeah
I mean talking about myself I've been depressed before but like I've never
been diagnosed so I don't know whether it was like a chronic depression or
whether it was depression via gender dysphoria which is lifted a little bit
um how to know so you can you can you can you can know how you feel but you
can't necessarily know something more like specific like you know you're if
you have a chemical imbalance or you have like a you know an underactive
like you know hormone receptor or something like you don't know those
things those are more those are separate from the feelings that you have
because of them right but I feel like it's a valid point okay yeah good
next one is called the monopoly man three two one go
oh here's the monopoly man yes enjoy your 20% annual inflation in
freedom land yeah increased rent by 30% okay all right fair enjoy life you
know what that's the price of freedom baby I think they changed the the lilts of
their ho ho ho it used to be going straight up but that one was ho ho ho
he's allowed to get creative with it no no no where's the good old monopoly man
I remember ho ho ho old good new bad this new the new the new patch they just
dropped for the monopoly man has completely ruined you know the integrity
of the character next voicemail is called cheese three two one go hey Ben I
need to stop talking about baby bells every episode because every time you do
I have to go and buy them and they're getting really fucking expensive is cheese
keto should I just eat cheese well I lose weight if I eat cheese yes most most
for I mean to answer your questions in reverse order yes most most cheese is
keto baby bell is pretty keto I mean if they're getting expensive do what I do
buy them in bulk from Costco get instant or get instacart and get an instacart
shopper to buy from Costco when you buy the big bags from Costco they're really
not very expensive they they they ended up they ended up being like like less
like 50 cents a piece or something like that so buy in bulk if there's something
you want a lot of if I can buy a greater bell and then chisel it down into many
small baby bells a greater damn I really wish we talked about this another I
really wish I had I think we talked about it on a shekels for heckles I really
wish they would sell me the other flavors I really want the cheddar like the
sharp cheddar baby bells in the black wax container like that sounds like you
can like find like a black market baby bell supplier for those I might I mean I
would probably be more expensive yeah something actually you know what let me
let me try it right now and go on Amazon so this caller has fucked himself
because now we are talking about baby bells he has totally fucked himself
okay I'm finding I searched for a black baby bell and all I'm finding is baby
clothes that have like bell bottoms you know babies wearing bell bottoms you
know like this shit right here fucking come on internet okay there it goes
yeah you know babe you know baby bell okay searching black baby bell okay I see
okay I see one for baby I see them but they cost oh my god 109 dollars for 8.4
ounces of mini baby bell white cheddar what are they putting in them okay this
one is this one is $50 for a pack of 30 of the of the baby bells that's a
that's a $1.65 per baby bell I don't know if I want to do I want to spend I want to
spend under a dollar at least on on my fucking baby all right yeah they do have
the other flavors here on Amazon but they're really expensive and that sucks
you gotta go on a baby bell road trip you gotta get in the RV and fill it up with baby
I gotta get in the RV it's the only way I guess look at this fucking this is this is
$64 for 4 ounces 12 for 12 mini baby bells that's $5.40 per baby bell I can't
I can't possibly justify it but I want the cheddar one so bad wait what is this
this purple one the purple one is sharp original remember they they sell
different ones in different countries yeah those might not match well according
to this one yeah the purple one is sharp original and the orange is Gouda I
would love to try them but they just at these prices I simply can't I simply
can't justify it this one is the the sharp original is $74 $74 for 12 baby
bells only three left in stock order soon no thanks no I don't think I will fuck
fuck next voice next voicemail is called let me get it the is this it 774 yes
next voicemail is called B Dan or BDAN 3 2 1 go
what is happening who was I talking about some artist wait it was I said some
artist was bad and can't think of 3d and someone's and someone's I said someone
thought that I misgendered I think but I said but I said they but who was I talking
about what is the trend recently I feel like the only one I feel like I would
have been talking about and said that would be like mint salad but like why
would I why would it be a problem that it was a rebel rebel taxi what why
people why would it why would it be a problem if I said they about rebel
taxi it has to be a trans person right if they I had to be like if I had to
defend my pronoun use I think I don't know sound quality was bad I don't know
I don't remember who I was talking about oops next oh wait before before that I
found I found um oh god what is this
would you please the media okay cool the media could not be played already open
it in my open it on Twitter oh this is a reply to the radical left speed running
thing you can't catch me I'm the fastest thing alive I was thinking about why so
many in the radical right to participate in speed running huh the reason is the
left's lack of work ethic what go fast what do it right and in a Peter Sonia
sense Peter Sonia to elevate a sexual archetypes in the marketplace fastest
hedgehog shadow what the fuck are you talking about beta male Sonic beta male
Sonic holy shit can we can we have Elias our play that on the that won't get
copyright strike right this is no this is a fan animation this is from from
turbo jet on on Twitter holy shit very funny so shadow what the fuck are you
talking about you're a beta male so true so true killed him killed him with that
one holy shit okay well yes I'm glad I'm glad to have seen that the next one is
called the next voicemail is called please don't play please don't play the
last voicemail three two one go hey fuck that last guy am I right absolutely I
get it what was he even talking about yeah what was even his fucking what was
even his fucking point he was trying to make I didn't get it I didn't fucking
get it said they the day though but who I don't remember they am they am they am
okay next one is called Riley thinks Ben listens to void gazers birdstork cameo
okay up there it is come on load okay three two one go
so quiet I could barely hear it he said he's saying he's saying something about
this part is for fans or for Ben saying and then bird says like just wait Ben
saying and Riley says there are questions about him okay I didn't yeah I
didn't watch the latest void gazers and I would never sit through an entire one
I did what I guess I did watch the bit I did watch the bit where they mentioned
me because it was time stamp for me and it was like one minute long so I guess
guilty as charged but I assume this is the part at the beginning of the because
they're doing it like a Q&A section so I think this is Riley introducing the
like the fact that they're about to do a Q&A no I'm definitely not going to listen
to the rest of although I'm I'm a bit curious because I know they got questions
about Trixie why did I pay you for a Blu-ray DVD and then you didn't give it to
me for years even though you could have made it for me where are my Blu-rays
I'm a little curious what her answer to that would be and I think she got another
question about the Brony lecture too which honestly I'm not interested in that
because I don't I know what she's going to say about that one well it's gone so
it doesn't matter anymore yeah it also that yeah it doesn't matter because she
she trashed it so oh well well okay cool thanks for the thanks for the voice clip
next one is called $600 uploading it right now yes $600 okay three two one go
wait what it's so quiet put your phone closer to the speaker voice Miller why
you fucking suck so bad at this I'm sorry again yeah me too okay I think he
she's saying she's saying getting Ben to make oh this must have been about the
the Blu-rays and something about getting Ben to make cover art for the Blu-rays is
not well I mean yeah I did say at one point in the distant distant past that
I was going to make Blu-rays but it's not like she has I don't know if she's using
this as an excuse like oh I can't make the Blu-rays anymore because I would have
to pay Ben Saint to make the cover art obviously that's not true and I don't
remember what I I don't remember $600 I think I maybe asked for like maybe 200
maybe like one for each of the two covers I feel like that's more like what I would
have asked for but whatever either way it literally has no relevance at all so I
don't know why it's even being mentioned but I guess this is part of the part of
the coping and excuse making about why did I why did I Trixie the Golden Witch
except you know hundreds and or thousands of dollars from fans for a Blu-ray
that I then deliberately never fulfilled my obligations to make and I guess it's
all that darned Ben Saint I guess I guess it's my fault that she didn't do that
for some reason make make sense to me next voicemail is called
it is called oh okay this guy just clipped a bunch of stuff from the from the
Q&A is posting it but okay the terms of forgiveness here we go 3 2 1 go
I