The Pro Crastinators Podcast
Hello, everyone!
Ah, boo.
Keep it, keep it, keep it, keep it, keep it in.
Fine. Hi, everyone. Welcome to the episode about what is the limit of free speech?
What is the show that we're on?
You have to say the name of the show.
Well, no, he doesn't. They don't know.
Yeah, freedom of speech. He doesn't have to say anything, motherfuckers.
Should it be illegal to chew Tums whilst doing a podcast?
No, you should be eating Tums at all times.
No, this is a terrible idea. I disagree with you.
Tums taste disgusting.
What?
I hate Tums. They taste like vitamins.
Tums are alright.
What about chewing on Mentos while you drink Diet Coke?
Endless Jess eats through an entire thing of Tums just because he likes them.
For fucking leisure?
You know, Michelle has had a stomach ache. I've just snacked on some Tums when there's Tums around.
I've eaten like two or three.
I don't think I've ever even had a Tums.
It's like the same with those gummy vitamins. They're delicious.
They're just giant sweet tarts that are fucking great and they make your stomach not hurt anymore.
And you can eat like ten of them a day.
Tums taste good?
Tums are bizarre and disgusting like twisted interpretation of like a butter mint.
They're like butter mints, but they taste like cough medicines.
Do you guys remember when I found that jar of gummy vitamins that had melted in the sun
and fused into a puck and I carefully extracted the puck from the bottom of the bottle
and then took a big bite out of it and briefly became the healthiest creature in the universe
and leveled the entire city block that I was living in.
You guys can introduce now.
Hey, so who's here?
Yeah, let's get over to the left over here.
We have a man who crosses professional boundaries to criticize individuals in his own medium, Digibro.
I am a monster of a man.
And I will rape.
We have the sometimes frustratingly silent hypocrite.
Nigger.
It wasn't silent just then.
Oh, no.
We have the man who deigns to criticize an entire half of Homestuck, Munch.
It's me, welcome to Manga Mondays.
Today we're going to be talking about sex.
Ah, trick you.
We have the resident nigger guy, Nate Besteman.
That's not accurate.
Also, I would say that lesbians are physically incapable of having sex with each other.
That's my free speech.
Guys, I didn't know this until I thought about it for a second like three years ago.
Scissoring isn't possible, basically.
Well, you can get close.
What do you mean it's not possible?
The Mac doesn't check out, Ben.
It just doesn't check out.
Audience weigh in. Tell us when the last time you scissored was.
Think about it. Think about the actual act of scissoring.
What do you mean?
There wouldn't be enough pressure.
You make the pressure.
Are you trying to say that two vaginas being pressed together can't cut through paper?
Is that what you mean?
Yes, that is what I mean.
They'll moisten and tear the paper.
It won't be a clean cut.
That's why lesbians don't check from construction work.
We have been female black faces saying that.
Wow, female black face is just offensive.
Regular black face is back and it's cool again.
But female black face is out.
It's still not okay.
You know, we're not there yet.
Give it time. Give it time.
That reminds me of my old catchphrase nigger bitch funeral
that I kept saying all the time and people would give me weird looks
and I was like, I don't know why I keep saying it.
And we have Tom, who I can't really think of anything you've said that's ever been offensive,
so introduce yourself.
I'm scared of this episode already.
This is going to be good.
We've got two loaded episodes back to back.
Tom, according to...
Tom, communism is the only moral economic system.
It was originally Karl Marx's birthday.
My lord and savior, apparently.
Oh, was it his birthday?
Oh, that's right. Happy birthday, Karl. You did it, buddy.
You did the episode properly.
To begin the actual topic, has this ever happened to you?
Complain about something that people are doing to which someone else goes,
well, it's my free speech to which someone else goes,
well, it's my free speech to criticize your free speech,
to where someone else goes,
to my free speech to criticize your free speech,
to criticize my free speech,
to which someone else should go.
Why do you even following this line of argument,
but no one ever does?
That's what we call a free speech cascade.
That was a words cascade that just washed over me.
Like, I was drowning in the ocean.
Well, it's been every day of my life.
The last 15 years have been on the fucking Internet, man.
Yeah, I mean, it's been forever.
You'll see a lot of the time these days.
People want to get technical victories over each other,
so someone will say something,
and maybe it's slightly overly general,
and the other person will say,
well, that doesn't apply to everyone.
All right, you know what it is?
It's the modern gun.
Yeah.
Because guns were invented so retards don't get killed.
You're like, oh, I'm physically deficient and weak,
and big people can beat me up and take everything I have,
so I'm going to invent a device.
Is that what we call a retard?
A physical retard.
Yeah, well, you know, if you are in any way,
if you are in any way retarded,
as in, like, to be lessened in some way,
like you are lessened than the regular human.
You mean, like, disabled,
do you just mean, like, people who are not able to punch some other line?
I mean, like, when you say, like, something's claimed retardant,
you mean to say that it, like, is not capable or claimed?
I don't think that's a common term.
Retarded just means slow.
Yeah, exactly.
I see it all the time.
If you're too slow, like, you're not fat,
you can't run away from the big guns
who are going to catch you and beat your ass.
Sonic is a ultimate neurotypical.
He's always fucking mansplaining.
Yeah.
So what you're saying is that nowadays
you just use technical fallacies to, like, get out of here.
On the internet, what is strength?
What is physical strength is intelligence,
because all anyone has is their words and their argument.
So if you're intelligent, that means that, theoretically,
you should destroy everybody on the internet.
However, they invented guns,
and the guns are called rhetorical argument,
where they can fuck you on the technical aspects of your argument,
and they don't have to be intelligent.
They just have to know these so-called rules.
But, like, because of the fact that if you're too intelligent
and you're actually following the rules,
but doing it in a way that, like, goes above people's heads,
then it doesn't matter, because they have the gun, you know?
Oh, and if you're too intelligent,
you could, theoretically, say everything exactly right,
but people will just latch in on one of the, you know,
areas that touches something that's simply politically
incorrect or incorrect,
and then they can just make a whole case about how, like,
it's not that your argument is wrong,
it's that you shouldn't be listened to because you've said, you know,
that's basically what happened with that Google thing, right?
Yeah, that's true.
When can I cash in my IQ points for various prizes at the store?
I want to cash in it for tickets or coins.
You do that at Chuck E. Cheese, dude.
You just got to go there.
It's a game of wits to Chuck E. Cheese, yeah.
Yeah.
So, hey, everybody.
That's why you go to school.
You go to school to build up your IQ points,
to go to Chuck E. Cheese to cash him in
for a plastic ring shaped like a spider,
and then you do all these things.
It's like when I played Ganguro Girl,
and many of the clones of Ganguro Girl,
where you got to go to the library and read
to buff your intelligence points so that you can woo
the slutty girls who like smart guys.
The titular Ganguro.
I was at Stephen Buster's,
and I was getting mad IQ points
while studying the art of monkey ball,
and I got so smart that I was able to purchase
with my raw brain power a Pinkie Pie plush.
This is your story.
Whoa, holy shit.
The Pinkie Pie would be pleased by this story.
Guys, I think no one should be able to say anything
at any time, regardless of circumstance,
or law, or whatever amendment made.
It's your freedom of speech to think that, so, you know?
We did cover how language is a problem,
but we got to just ban it.
So I've been asleep since the last PCP,
and my memory is a little hazy.
I just woke up from a stupor.
The last one we did was on language, right?
That's like the same thing.
It's like a sequel.
Yeah.
Also, it is.
You've got to put the build upon.
The fatigue department as well.
The groundwork.
You've got to build upon the groundwork that we laid.
Specifically what the prompt of this episode is,
because we're trying to sometimes have prompts
that are like full sentences rather than just single words.
Yeah.
So that the conversation isn't so amorphous and vague
and weirdly utilitarian.
The specific title, for us at least,
is what is the limit of free speech,
because that's where really interesting
and also very frustrating debates take root,
which is when there's things right on the line
between someone expressing themselves
and someone pulling off an extortion.
Hey, can I?
Can I?
Wait, I got something.
I just looked up.
I'm looking at the definition of free speech
on UrbanDictionary.com,
and I got to say it's extremely enlightening.
Here we go.
Get ready for this truth bomb, everyone.
Free speech, dictionary definition,
the right to express any opinions
without censorship or restraint.
College definition,
the right to express any opinions
without censorship or restraint,
unless you're a conservative.
Yeah.
Got him.
Smash.
Smash the glass ceiling.
Smash the conservatory.
So that is that writing prompt,
that question prompt of what are the limits?
Oh wait, definition two?
Definition two?
Yeah.
Nothing more than an illusion.
Wow.
This guy is moose.
Moose, this guy moose who wrote that one.
Moose, he's a woke boy.
Well done, champ.
Let me throw out my position,
and then I'd be interested to hear rebuttals,
because I think mine is one of the extremes.
So I think, like,
so free speech is a legal issue.
It's like, should you be put in jail
for saying things that are wrong?
I think that you should literally not
be criminally penalized
for saying literally anything,
except, oh, but okay, that's not true,
because then the shedding of fire
and a crowd at theater could actually kill people.
As long as your words.
Okay, by extension, let's say, for example,
that there's a Jewish kid,
and then everyone starts calling him a kike,
and then he kills himself.
If that happens, what's the connection here?
Is that free speech?
Should that be criminalized?
The thing about it is that
the speech is not entirely the point.
They could have just easily said,
we don't like you, you're different,
and none of those words are technically wrong,
but that is what killed them.
The words themselves don't matter.
I don't think those people are responsible for his death.
They're not murderers,
but they were deliberately abusive,
which is not cool.
I mean, I would say that they
just give people free reign to do that.
I would say that his death is partly,
they are partly to blame,
but it had nothing to do with the word choice.
Can we at least agree on this to begin with?
No individual word itself
should ever be forbidden from being spoken.
Exactly what I wanted to bring in and say,
I wanted to say that outside of context,
no individual word can possibly be seen as harmful
unless there are certain frequencies
in our fucking neuro system that can be irritated
by certain syllables.
There is no way that individual words
outside of context should be put into the realm
for niggers only if you know what I mean.
I think the fact that even in academic
or journalistic writing,
you have to say the N word,
that is so immature and ridiculous to me,
because we know what the fucking word is!
I know what it is!
Just say the word, I'm not a child!
If you say it, I'm gonna think it!
Yeah, you bitches.
Think inwardly.
Is this really helpful?
Wait, did you say think inwardly?
I know, right?
We sent this episode with the word inward
and I kept thinking it was inward
and if you listen back to that,
you'll hear me saying inward.
Oh, how interesting.
Well, we wouldn't be showing that.
No, but there you go.
But anyway, I was gonna say that like,
the reason I think people say inward
is specifically for kids, right?
That's the big thing that everybody comes back to.
But here's my position.
Well, okay, maybe not.
Maybe with a word like nigger.
You better not let your kid listen to a single rap song ever.
See, but that's my point.
I'm listening to Kanye.
We gotta ban hip-hop because we love black people.
Hip-hop that uses the N word, I guess.
But okay, here's my position.
Was that racist of me to imply
that black people make rap music?
I'm sorry.
That's about as racist as saying
that black people play more basketball,
which I think is just true, right?
Maybe I was racist.
Let me look up the urban dictionary of basketball
and we can get to the bottom of this.
Okay, here's the important thing about this.
First, I was gonna say that kids should just hear any word.
I don't care, it's fine.
But about this other topic about being racist or whatever,
I think that there's two important things to do
at the same time when you're making any of these kind of statements,
and it sort of relates to free speech.
It's that you can make statements about groups
that just are demonstrably true.
For example, black people are more propensity
to get sickle cell anemia or whatever.
That's simply a fact.
But then if you look at an individual black person
and you say, hey buddy, you're getting sickle cell anemia,
that is in fact racist because you're discriminating based on race.
Every individual just needs to be treated as an individual.
I prefer Cooley's anemia.
I have to go back a step.
It's my favorite anemia.
My mind is being torn and twain thinking about this.
I need all of you to participate in this with me
and ask me this question of yourself.
You're like Mark Twain who wrote literature
that used the word anemia.
Literally, what is the worst that can happen
from your kids learning swear words?
They will save them.
They'll make you uncomfortable by saying them.
That's literally the only reason.
That's literally it.
You even hear people who are pretty open about free speech
talking about how they still don't want kids saying bad swear words.
But really why though?
What the fuck?
Let me fucking go through this.
I think you might be in a similar boat to me on this
because we both grew up very proud to follow the rules.
Proud to do what our parents said on some level.
With my family, my brother and I had a sort of pact
that we were like we're not going to swear till we're 18.
That was just the thing we said.
I started breaking that in the eighth grade
because I would swear at school in front of school kids
but I never swore at home in front of Victor and Shay
because I didn't want to let them down.
Neither of them started swearing till they were 18.
They just kept to it the whole way
whereas I was a piece of shit and broke it early.
The thing is we knew the swear words from childhood
because my parents had showed us Beavis and Butthead
and South Park when we were little.
I knew all the swears and I used to swear when I was a kid.
But when I was going into elementary school,
my parents were just like,
yeah, this word, this word, this word,
don't say those at school.
I was like, okay, because I was a well-mannered kid.
I just didn't say those words except for it.
I wouldn't even say them at home eventually
because we decided we weren't going to swear
because we wanted to be good kids.
Once we were all 18, we just started swearing constantly
because we all know the words.
My parents swear constantly as it is.
They weren't protecting us from it.
That's how we think.
And the consequences of this have been
literally nothing because everyone swears all the time.
It doesn't fucking matter.
I was just thinking about that.
I'm curious about the whole black market of swears
in school meta is you're not allowed to say this
and then kids would be like, fuck.
And then everyone would be like, hmm.
And I'm like, if it's swear words,
would kids come up with words that are banned
or would they just secretly...
There's always things that you're not allowed to say.
If it's not swear words,
would it be something else that they would be like
to show how cool they are?
The answer is yes because me and my brothers,
in replacement of all the swear words,
we just said things that were similar,
which the funny thing is that the things that we said
in place of them could get us in trouble
in some of our friends' houses or at school.
We would say heck or frick or freak.
Dude, what the freak?
Exactly, the famous dude with the freak brother.
You said that in one of the early videos in your old channel.
Dude, what the freak?
Well, because we were under 18 when we made those videos,
so we didn't swear at any of them
because we were going to show them to our parents.
We didn't want them to see us swearing or anything.
We just wouldn't swear even in the content.
But the words we were using,
I would go to friends' houses and they'd be like,
you can't say that word.
They function like saying the N word.
They work in the exact same way.
Exactly, but it's like,
you can't avoid having a word for those situations
because that's how you learn to talk.
It's how normal people speak and how the media strikes.
You're absolutely right, but let me ask you a question real quick, everybody.
If I go up to a black person and I say,
you fucking N word,
how, like, do I win?
Do I get off scot-free for saying these things?
Like, I did not work.
I win, right?
Is this just the racial slur podcast?
No, I feel like we're focusing a little too heavily.
Literally everything that you talked about,
I want to say a thing about.
Other families, other things you can't say.
For example, white trash.
I am doing a fucking favor
for a family of a friend of mine, right?
I'm driving them to a place
for, like, a really important thing
and no one else is willing to help them.
I'm taking time out of my day to fucking do this shit.
And I tell a white trash joke, right?
And I guess it's more or less
at the expense of their family,
but, like, my family and me
we're all equal levels of white trash.
We're all, like, pseudo-voromazurians over here.
So I didn't think of it as, like, a thing,
but, like, I guess they were a little bit quiet
and then my friend was like,
that wasn't appropriate when we were alone.
And I'm like, you fucking nigger.
I'm helping you people fucking out
on the one fucking driving.
And according to other people who I've spoken to
in my life, if you're driving,
you set the fucking rules for all fucking speech.
That's the first one.
I want to respond to Ben, though.
Ben, the reason I think that
our kind of first trajectory...
Real quick, to just piggyback on what he said
just a little bit, I absolutely agree.
Anybody who talks shit about you
when you're doing them a favor can get fucked.
Well, of course. Absolutely.
Especially if you're, like, shitting on my music
when I'm driving you around.
I then confronted my friend on that
about calling that inappropriate.
I was just saying it was offensive to them.
I'm like, look, I'm fucking triggered
by the word inappropriate.
That's my fucking trigger.
Because, like, being a well-mannered child
generally, the only thing
my dad would ever get me on
would be, like, overreacting to something
or inappropriate something.
So anytime anyone uses those words,
you have a times 20 chance of pissing me off.
Just a fucking record.
Just a fucking, you know...
Now everyone on the internet is going to be like,
hey, Davoo, you feeling inappropriate today?
Hey, but
what Ben was saying about race, I think this ties into...
Yeah, Ben has a lot to say about race.
Let me tell you.
Wait, no.
But this is what I was going to say.
The reason that I think that's our
place to start with this is because
what exactly is
a swear or something that you can't say?
It's like, they're like
basically a crass way of
referring to a forbidden topic.
So, for example, like,
nigger, racial...
whatever, like WAP, grease ball, etc.
All these, they imply
racism, and really that's what's
not acceptable, and that's perfectly reasonable.
I want to let everyone know that this is
literally the most
alt-right podcast we've ever made.
That's not even true.
Dude, no.
I have an answer to this question.
In an academic way, but like...
I don't know.
Fast and loose.
Stand-up comedian David Crow postulates
that swears have a lot to do with their phonetics
more than just their semantics.
So, for example, like...
It feels like you're getting whipped
by someone else's mouth, whereas if you just say
sex, it's just a little bit more
harmless or like...
Ben's right that we don't need to focus specifically
on swear so much. I need to jump back to that
alt-right comment that Munchie made, because
I seem to remember where, like,
ten years ago, this was
literally the entire Louis C.K.
stand-up routine, and every
liberal was behind him.
Well, we know what that boy was up to in those days.
Yeah.
He went back on a lot of it.
He became a fucking Libcuck because
that's where culture went.
But, like, that, like, literally
the stuff I was saying earlier about the N-word
thing was literally a bit he did.
I mean, we stayed the same, and the Overton
window has shifted around us, but...
I was thinking a lot, Digi,
about how the internet, like,
used to be pretty liberal in a lot of ways.
Like, you think...
Like, French women was always, like,
portrayed as conservative, but they did...
They had a lot of, like, Libcuck...
They were not conservative until recently.
Yeah.
Look, I haven't been on the internet
for the longest around here, but I've been...
I think I've probably frequented politics
boards for, like, longer than most people.
Uh, like, so starting
in, like, you know, 2007-ish
I would go to the politics boards, and I'd be the
only non-liberal there every single fucking time.
Sure.
What changed was the social justice war.
That, as far as I can tell, from my own
my own anecdotal perspective,
single-handedly shifted everything.
It's because there were no millennial conservatives
until we had it, until they had an enemy.
It said we, but I'm not one of them.
Right, exactly.
So what it was was, originally, the demographics
on politics, at least on, you know,
pop-media boards where I would go,
I'm sure there was plenty of conservative, dedicated websites,
but, like, you know, like, the tig-w-tig forums
or, like, the escapist forums,
the screw-attack forums, it was always, like,
it was always, the only demographic
politically was just Democrat voting liberals.
Like, generally people who you would describe
as pretty blue-pilled, right?
I guess particularly because I was in gaming communities,
and at that time, it was all about
Jack Thompson and Fox News.
Those were the enemies, both conservatives,
both Republicans, right?
I mean, yeah.
But then gaming started attacking itself
from within, Sarkeesian style,
and all of a sudden, the demographics split wide open.
Now we have far more hardcore liberals,
and then we have the alt-right people
who are still sort of, like, center-right,
because they're not, like, Christian, they're not, like,
fucking, they're not, like, Ted Cruz conservative,
but they're more, like, Trump conservative.
And then it just seems like the whole, like,
blue-pilled, mild-mannered Democratic liberals
just don't even exist among my generation anymore.
It just sort of split those two ways.
What I think happened, because, like,
I grew up super liberal, and, you know,
my mom raised me on, like, political music and stuff,
and back in the 2000s,
the reason that everyone online was liberal
was that being conservative meant being pro-war.
Like, Bush had taken us to war,
and, like, the platform of liberals was anti-war.
We wanted peace, we wanted, and, like, pro-abortion,
pro, like, stuff like that.
But once the war was no longer the big concern,
because, like, well, both sides are equally likely
to go to war, so, like, we don't, like,
now that it's, like, an identitarian conflict,
and, like, there's a whole young generation
who's, like, well, you know, yeah,
we will back the Republicans, because they're not arguing for war.
They're just arguing for not this stuff that we don't like.
Right. No.
Fun fact, I learned from Free Domain Radio,
Barack Obama was the only president in U.S. history,
I believe, unless I misheard this fact,
the only president in U.S. history to have war going on
when he took office and war still continuing when he left office.
You could argue, though, that that's just because, again,
he is, like, a replaceable tool
who was just put in place, and, like, the machinery around him
just continued to operate.
Well, that's it. That's why nobody cares, like,
nobody cares about being liberal anymore,
because it doesn't seem like, it doesn't say,
it doesn't stop anything.
Like, when, like, people were so angry when he, like,
won both elections, like, you know,
you had Eminem making songs about it
and all this shit and all these people,
and then, like, we finally got a Democratic president
and it didn't end the war.
So it's, like, why be Democrat at this point?
Every one of the fucking Nobel Peace Prize,
like, to remind everybody of that.
If I remember correctly, one of the things people wanted
was to stop the drug war, and all Obama did was
minimize mandatory minimum sentences,
but nothing else.
The fucking war on drugs continued completely.
Utilizing drugs to pay for secret wars around the world.
Well, yeah, all that shit continues.
Well, hey, guys, let's...
Yeah, I don't know what the fuck you're talking about,
but listen, guys, let's actually, we've been danced around.
Let's get to the real topic.
The limits of free speech.
Margie, did you want to comment on this?
I just want to say on the subject of the Internet
being more liberal, just something really illuminative
was in the Parkour Dude 91 saga.
Renowned liberal.
One of the main, like, enemies of Parkour Dude 91
was this guy, Fly Away Now,
and Fly Away Now during the legendary trial
of Parkour Dude 91.
One of his main problems was,
Jace, you are racist, and that's not good.
And so he went in hard on critiquing Jace's racism,
which is a thing that I don't think could happen nowadays.
I don't think anyone would...
Would portray a racist...
No, Four Context.
Fly Away Now is a member of a trolling cult.
It's like a four-chan trolling cult.
Was this sincere criticism, or was it a joke?
He's saying that a troll would never use that
as a weapon against somebody now,
because being seen as racist would be seen as like,
that's what the trolls are now,
is that they use racism themselves.
I mean, that's sort of like that guerrilla mindset guy
will call people pedophiles, despite...
And I don't mean to imply that four-chants
never been racist or edgy or anything.
I think there's been undertones of the Scientology activism
and stuff like that, and there's always been
jokes about fucked news or whatever the hell.
So, I don't know.
I just think it's an interesting change in the world.
Yeah, thanks.
So yeah, limits on free speech.
I was talking with that with the wife,
and being all like, oh yeah,
because then there was the obvious yelling fire
in a crowded theater argument,
and she told me, I didn't research this,
I never researched anything because research is bullshit
because everyone says different things.
She said that she's heard that that argument
was concocted during the First World War
to minimize and delegitimize anyone
who protested the war in a crowded theater.
Sorry, which argument is this that was diminished?
The yelling fire in a crowded theater.
Oh, okay, okay.
That they're saying, we need to stop the war.
And then other people are like, you need to be silent.
To which they'd be like, oh, free speech bitch,
this is America.
To which other people said, no,
what you're doing isn't free speech.
It's like yelling fire in a crowded theater.
Well, I mean, okay, let's...
So that's an example of the yelling fire
in a crowded theater where there's some action
that's happening and you're compelling people
to take an action based on false information.
So if there actually was a fire
and you yell fire in a crowded theater,
that is a reasonable thing to do.
It's less about that you can't speak,
but it's more about that you take responsibility
for what happens as a result of the speech.
For example, if you tell someone,
come here for free cupcakes
and then you don't give anyone free cupcakes,
or buy a cake and get a free cupcake,
and then you don't give it.
That's false advertising.
Yeah, that's false advertising.
The difference is that it's not the fact
that you've said the word fire.
Your intention is to sow chaos.
That's true.
Your intention is to make people do bad things.
Unfortunately, when it comes to this,
if someone is just talking to their friend
and they say, yeah, so you know,
me and my friends are gonna have a bonfire tomorrow,
if you say that in a movie theater, obviously you're fine.
If someone says it but just yells the word fire
and starts running around screaming,
different intentions, obviously.
All we can do is we need a court system
to just figure out what was the intention
we had in the court system.
What if the guy was
mentally unsound
and just yelled fire
because that's what he does?
Well, then we just take it case by case.
If he couldn't help it, then we probably
shouldn't let this guy hang out in theaters.
The thing is with free speech is that
if we could take it case by case,
people would prefer that
because it is
a lot of these things,
you can't just ban a word
and have it fix all the problems.
People are gonna find ways to get around it.
There's always gonna be
people
scouting the system and stuff.
We do do it case by case.
That's what the court system is for.
If you scream fire in a theater,
you would go to trial.
People, I guess,
okay.
I don't know anything about anything, actually.
I don't know anything about justice.
I used to think
free speech was like
you can say anything you want
and if people try to silence you, that means they're wrong.
You don't have that in Britain?
That shouldn't be there anymore.
I mean, never was, I don't think.
Free speech is not codified in law.
They do have nowhere near the kind of freedoms
we have in America in Britain.
Okay, well, USA.
For what it's worth.
Wait, I'm sorry.
I think it was finishing this point.
I'm sorry.
I don't know.
I didn't think he had any more point.
I had a bit of a point.
I was trying to rescue him.
The reason that USA
has its first amendment
was because we wanted to protect
your ability to talk shit about the government.
Right, that was the whole point.
We did that.
Talking shit about the government
is how we started the revolution.
That was the whole point was that we
talked their government until everybody got pissed off
and then we fought them and became our own people.
I can do that.
Well, they changed the rules over time.
You can.
They do have freedom of speech in Europe now,
but not
necessarily to the same extent.
Here's what he was thinking about.
When YouTube rolled out its whole
we're going to just bury
videos that are hateful
and racist and misleading and shit.
I remember thinking
that they're saying it's free speech.
You just can't have speech as hateful
and racist.
I think that the whole idea
of the Enlightenment era free speech
revolution is that you can say
anything, even things that are
hateful and harmful.
You can't say things as long as they're nice.
Probably dates back to thousands of years.
The purpose of 10 years in universities
is that professors have the freedom
to pursue academic pursuits
that challenge mainstream ideas
exactly for these kinds of reasons.
Yeah, exactly. I don't get why people are
typically offended when they see something
that contradicts them.
For me, the moment I hear something
that goes against my perception,
I'm fucking excited. It's like my favorite
time of the day. It makes my fucking month.
I personally don't feel
like I have enough ego
to say that I just love
things that fundamentally challenge my world view.
I am a weak human being
who's entrenched in his own biases
like everybody else.
Except for DeVue.
DeVue is the one exception here.
I do want to say DeVue is legitimately an exception.
DeVue legitimately
and not naming. I have watched this man change
his entire mind at the drop
of a fucking pin.
I'm not saying that's necessarily a great thing to do either.
You even were able to accept your fucking
incorrect fucking metaphor
in an idiom fusion that you do.
You were able to fix yourself on that.
Congratulations.
To put a point on it, this is the question.
Is hate speech
free speech?
That's the biggest question right now.
I think definitely yes
because
hate speech is determined
by the people who are getting offended.
That's right.
Let's say, for example, if
in a liberal government
liberals
they would change
the law in some way
and it would be like, okay,
if you cause offense you're going to jail
and then somewhere down the line
the people who put that law in place
are now technically offensive
to a majority that's sprung up
and then they would go to jail
and it just feels like a stupid thing to put into place.
The idea that
some sort of vague
because it's an ever-shifting
what is offensive to who
depends on who's around and how many of them there are.
That's true.
Should the government be in the business of determining
what's hate speech and what's not?
Ben, if you want to comment, feel free.
You can't base law on opinions.
I guess you kind of can.
You know what?
I think the problem is that
people are so worried about
the type of speech
instead of where it's being used.
Let's say I have a private blog
where I am constantly
saying racist shit
and I just share it with my friends.
Let's say it's on Facebook.
If Facebook finds this thing
they're going to delete it
because it's against their policy
even though it's private and it's just among me and friends
and it's not aggressing against anyone
it's just me expressing my beliefs
that are extremely unpopular
and even if I personally think
people shouldn't have the beliefs that
this person has, why am I the moral authority?
That's against the policy
on what we built this country on
that no one has moral authority.
That's the point.
How about fucking Hulk Hogan
who just was filmed
against his will?
He said the word nigger in private
to someone.
Watch Jesse's video
for the full discussion of that.
I've been curious about this
but I couldn't really find
a definitive answer
and I was also scared of googling it
in case the Google comes to get me.
Is it
illegal to be racist
just actually?
No, not in America.
Absolutely not.
You can be as racist as you like
but if you say anything
then it becomes a problem.
I want to as an example
lay a ground rule of something I think
and I want to hear you guys' opinion on this
because to me
I've always taken free speech and everything
really in life as the rule
of I can swing my fist as much
as I want but if I hit your face
then it's a problem basically.
That was one of the founding fathers said
that I don't remember who.
That was the idea of
what the law was based on in this country
was that you can do
literally whatever you want but the second that it
hurts somebody else, that's when you're in trouble.
The problem is what constitutes violence
does need to be.
The problem also is that like
where is the line on personal responsibility
if I am writing a blog
that's like I hate black people
the blog, at what point
is it that I am aggressing you
by writing things that offend black people
and at what point it is yeah but you chose
to read it. Now if I was
let's say that I
go on someone's blog
and this is a personal blog and I think
that internet websites
that you own should be respected as
private property. Of course
private property. That you invite people on to
essentially because I mean you pay for it
you literally buy hosting, you buy a domain
it's your intellectual property
you have control over what gets posted there
let's say that you
get someone who's like
I'm a black writer and this guy
is calling me a nigger every day
in my comments so I P-ban him
this guy creates
a new account on a new computer, shows up again
and continues doing it
at that point I would consider this an act of
aggression. Like this
person has been not only are they
doing something that they know is offensive
they've been told that it's offensive
they've been kicked off the platform
and they've circumvented the system
in order to find a way to continue
fucking with me. At this point there's nothing
I can do because this person's gotten around
the tools that I have at my disposal
to defend myself so this is where
I should be able to say to the police
hey this guy is like
creating multiple accounts to
continue a harassment campaign against me
this is clearly harassment
I think I would agree
Internet harassment in general is something that
where harassment becomes not free
speech that is sort of a line under itself
which is part of the reason I wanted to start this podcast
for but also in general
people do need to understand
that internet harassment is real
harassment for the simple fact that
when you get a message from someone
that's directed at you
do you think
hmm those are some slightly
less colored pixels on this screen
forming words that mean nothing
or do you think
hmm a person
has said a thing
to me. Well that was
what I was trying to say earlier like I used to
like when I was a young boy I was all
for like free speech means you
can say whatever you want in like
no nothing should be banned
and you should be able to say whatever you like
but like as the years go on
I do recognize that
there's nuance to all things
and especially this
the context and the intent
is very important to understand in any situation
yep
let's say you have a number of friends
let's say you have like almost all of your friends
however many you have if you have none imagine you have
12 friends imagine if 10 of your friends
sent you a letter
all saying that they don't want to be your friend anymore
and they hate you and they list
very specific things that you actually
do do as to why they hate you now
will you think
hmm this is some ink arranged
in shapes that I can identify
as words or are you going to be stressed
out and upset so there you go
speech can be
like people saying things
and meaning things
and having harmful intents
can constitute the building
blocks that can create the bridge of harassment
and it can be done even without words
or physical activity
just with digital information being transferred
to your computer it still counts as
real communication that's why people go on social media
all the time
I feel like I understand
why a lot of young people
like on the internet they get up in arms
about like their ability to say
whatever they want regardless of
how it may affect others
because of the fact that they're young and they
all they know about like
incorrect language is swear words
and the fact that in school it is cool
among friends to say swear words
because the teachers don't let you
and I feel like that they take that
idea of like
not allowed to say
and then they just extend it into
like internet interactions
without knowing that it actually hurts people
that's a very good
so I mean
I think that we could go back and forth on these
details all day but I think the reason
why there's no like hard
agreement why there hasn't been an answer to this question
is because the reality is
like
the vagueness of this topic
makes it basically unsolvable
except with some vast network of specific
investigation into each
you know individual
time what happens
which it should be yeah that's what the government
should be
a body that exists to
solve individual problems
that we have but because
of the fact that this first of all country
is way too fucking big second of all everything
is industrialized that's the entire way we think
of the country is mass production and like
we just try to have everybody follow
the same broad set of rules that
just doesn't work for
300 million people living across
3000 miles of fucking
land like it doesn't make
sense to hold everybody to the same exact
standards and circumstances all the time
you guys already don't
yeah
you guys okay there's this one example of one
website that does internet interaction
very interestingly
new grounds so on new grounds
you know the interaction
is pretty limited you have forums you have
direct messages and you have
reviews right it's
for the pretty standard you know early internet
package but on reviews you can review
a movie you can review a game
and once you've done the review the review is done
I don't think you can edit reviews
I don't think they've ever added in the edit
feature and
a the artist who
uploaded the thing that you are reviewing
can respond to you by making
a creators response a single
creators response that they themselves
cannot edit and once they
have written their response
it's done and new grounds has
responded to the tons of requests
they've gotten to be able to respond
to their responses
to which new grounds has said
our philosophy is to give
the creator the last word
and I think you know
if that were a thing that were practiced
voluntarily
I think that that would solve a lot of harassment issues
sort of like someone
you want to criticize some person on the internet
you know like where does it cross the line
from criticism to harassment you know
maybe you just come in
you make your point you don't be
a huge dick about it
once you've gotten your fucking
point out and then they've made their response
maybe you give it a little bit of follow up
there and then you move the fuck
on that's sort of what I under
that's what I see as the pattern with these people
who like get so harassed they have to like go
fucking therapy and shit start taking pills
it's that they might very legitimately
fuck up on something right
as a content creator they might actually hurt
people and they get called out on it
and now they have to deal with it but then
they never stop getting
called out on it they have been forever
banished damned to the land
of weeping and gnashing of tweets
I've been planning to to launch
a series for a long time
and I think I might finally do it sometime
soon because I'm ready I've got the mental
wherewithal to do this but I want
to do a streaming series
called digi bro takes on takes
all comers and I'm just going to make
a discord server that
has an open season
like like you know
call line like anybody can join this
server anybody can jump in the call
but I will only activate one person at a
time and the idea is
if you have any problem with me
come into this call and let's
argue about it until you
sound either you we've resolved
your issue or you are
repeating yourself and sound like an idiot
and need to be kicked out because the audience
has decided that they don't want to hear you anymore
you say that you can
identify a terrible or good anime
in just one episode
but you also say there's no such thing
as an objective opinion
this is a contradiction
because reasons
what about
what about food
reviews I think those should be
illegal I don't think those should
I think those should not be comfortable
we have the only good food review
show ever created on the face of the planet
we have the real people clamor for
well
I think
it's discrimination against
against bad food
because
it's wasting food and we all know
people should be allowed
any
dissenting opinion because I'm pretty sure
all of us feel the exact same way
I think food reviews are fine
not that
I'm about to qualify it
that's not the issue here
it's just people shouldn't
be allowed to find a recipe
and then do it wrong and then give the recipe
a bad review on the internet
because they fucking it up
they decided
to put fucking olive oil
in their french onion soup
and it's not my fault it's greasy
you fuck
that's a reasonable
it's not my fault
fucking soup lover
you make a reasonable point
about how everyone's voice
seems equally valid
unfortunately online
at some point
at some point I realized
I think it was probably in the t-bap days
that a huge percentage of the people commenting
especially on YouTube
are kids and I was like wait a minute
wait a minute
these aren't full people
I don't need to think
I don't necessarily need to give
these opinions
being expressed in the comments
the weight that I would to an actual
you just caught on to that
I caught on to that back then
I had this realization at some point
in my YouTube career
my default kind of thing to do when I
read a comment is always to project
my situation onto them
they are the same age as me
they are the same intellectual level
we gotta avoid that though
I imagine that
every commenter I respond to
I just think
this is a dumb 12 year old
even if it's a good commenter who I love
I just think
or an amazing 9 year old
yeah
anyone who leaves me
constant loving comments
about how great I am
nobody can be this big of a fan of me
if you're above the age of 12
if they're someone who bashes on me
I'm like no one can care this much about
shitting on an internet creator unless they're 12
as Endless just said
in fact it is true that most of these people
are kids the problem is that some of these kids
are 35 years old
now I will say I found one of them
in person recently
I mean I assume I'm being pretty discriminatory
but someone who I'm pretty sure is an internet
commenter
I passed them on the side
he just looked like
you know he was gonna
comment
he was all geared up to go back to his house
the tips of his finger
his fingers were weathered
guys he was wearing a cod shirt
so that's a pretty good sign
so he's like probably 5 foot 6 or so
you know stout portly
like a really squished looking face
he's got that sort of like
shaved head thing but he doesn't shave it
consistently
you're just describing every 35 year old
youtube commenter that I've met
exactly
and he has like you know dinky little glasses
and he just sort of walks with like a little bit
you know just kind of like walks a little bit
goofily and most importantly
of all he's wearing a call of duty ghost
shirt which is like the least popular call of duty
so I'm just like oh yeah
this is a guy who like has some specific opinions
and I'm just like yeah
Davoo cradles
his chin and his fingers
this is a guy
this guy thinks individual thoughts
individual ideas
the mad man
if it was a modern warfare 3 shirt
I'd be like okay he could just be a normie gamer
but a ghost shirt that's too specific
so I can feel
the opinions coming from him
what if he's just a normal guy
doing his normal programming job
and he just really liked modern warfare
and he pre-ordered ghost because he was super hype
and didn't know he thought the dog was gonna be dope
but he's wearing it right now
because he spent a lot of money
like special edition that came with the shirt
and he just I gotta get my money's worth
this is just how I'm wired dad taught me
to use everything I spent my money on
I feel like that way about certain shirts
but I wear them indoors
wait so did Davoo talk to a guy or not
yeah what happened
okay I gotta tell you about my guy who's similar
at the airport
yeah you tweeted about this man
for anybody who missed my tweets this was legendary
so me and May
were at the airport going back to
Rochester
from my hometown Virginia Beach
and like just some random college dude
had sat across from us
and was asking about my shirt
because I was wearing a Gintama shirt and he thought it was a bleach shirt
and I was explaining
I was explaining to him that it was a parody of
bleach and he was just like
he just got like oh you guys into anime
and she was like yeah we're anime
YouTubers we're like it's our job
we always do is watch anime
we get into this whole anime
so we're talking to this guy for a while
we're making him a fan basically he's like
way excited to hear about anime
he's like a 20 year old college dude
but there's another guy
who's like sitting across the way
who's like a big fat guy
in a Ninja Turtles t-shirt
when we had first gotten
to the airport terminal I saw this guy
and I thought if anyone here would recognize me
it would be that guy it's like what I'm thinking
when I look at this guy
so we're just talking about anime
for like probably 15 minutes
and then everybody gets up to go in the line
and the fat guy comes over and he's like
hey I heard you guys talking about anime
you know I wasn't sure if I should jump into the conversation
or whatever right
and he's like yeah I'm like
okay so the other dude like clearly had been
watching like everything on crunchyroll
just like whatever showed up on crunchyroll
he was giving it a shot this fat guy has just seen
I fucking hate people that watch anime
this fat guy has just
exclusively seen Attack on Titan
and that is it but he comes up
and he's like yeah you know
I really like I was really into death note
you know because I think
it's like a perfect mirror reflection of like
the Lion King
because you know
what the fuck
and then he's like well because you know first
he's like each character is like parallel
so first you've got like light who wants to be
god just like Simba
and after he said that
my brain went like
like all the juice drained out
and I was just like dumbfounded like
I was trying not to look at him as hard as I could
he's like
I think Ryuk was Rafiki and like
I mean he just
basically he just compared the main characters
of one to the main characters of others
like light is or L is just like scar
because he wants to stop Simba
like
that's the
mark of a great story
is that it's exactly like another story
Simba is like L
because he's trying to stop Scar
who's the bad evil man who took over
and seized power through illegitimate
evil means like he's the one
but L doesn't want to be god
Scar doesn't want to be god
Scar
is kind of does
I'm sorry
this just reminds me of a time I was in an anime convention
where I went up to a guy wearing a samurai outfit
and I was like hey dude your gene
I love samurai shampoo and he's like actually I'm going
on from uh you know fucking
loop in the third and I pretended
I knew who that was at the time
oh you didn't know who Gaimon was
I didn't know who the fuck that was at the time
this was this was long ago but it's I've never
forgotten it I've always been ashamed
there's nothing worse that to your credit than getting
a thing wrong
especially getting like a classic wrong
for like a modern show
like he looks disgusted when I said I love gene
yeah it's so cool
at that one party
that I went to when I was at your house
we met that one guy who went to
some like anime cons right
embarrassing
I don't what did he look like I don't remember
he was a bizarre
he was a bizarre like lantern
looking motherfucker
he looked like some sort of like
portly like last lantern
like the pokemon lantern
I don't know what you're talking about
there's a lot of people that could fit that description
he was talking to us about how he went to cons
in the local area
he was a big anime guy
and then I said yeah me and Ben are like
stars of brony con we go there all the time
yeah
I wish you had
I'm just picturing lantern the pokemon
just like hey guys we're going to an anime convention
I do not recall that conversation even a little bit
so okay so first amendment right
there's one thing about that
I don't care about that anymore
it's been a thing for me right
let's just do another wild card episode
what I think is
one of the most widely held fallacies
about specifically
the first amendment of the constitution of the united states
is this fallacy that
this is going to like
ugh I'm tensed up because I could get all y'all
fucking jumping on my ass over this
this perception that
the first amendment
only applies to
units of individual solitary
people
as opposed to like corporations and what not
well here's the thing about that right
because the actual text
of the first amendment is
well hold on I'll just
probably should have looked it up before
first amendment
what it says is
I gotta keep fucking coughing to get to it
for score yeah okay
Congress shall make no law
respecting an establishment of religion
or prohibiting the free exercise
thereof
or abridging the freedom of speech
or
of the press
or the right of the people to peaceably assemble
and to petition the government for our readdressive grievances
that is a part
like a certain like
comma section and no one ever talks about when they talk about
the idea of free speech basically there's this idea that
if people band together to form a corporation
they've now voided
their ability to speak because it's no longer a person
now it's a company
well that I don't think that press clause
really covers like corporations it covers
the press well it says the press
which basically means like
people who report information in the news
group of people who say things right that's not
like what a corporation is a corporation
is a business a money making enterprise
I mean if you want to argue that a person
you know should be treated like
you know if a company should have the rights of free speech
that's probably fine I just don't think that clause
addresses that yeah well no one
ever no one ever brings it up though like
like we always like doesn't come up
when people say freedom of the press isn't that
exactly what they're talking about
yeah but people don't really think about it right
because you hear people say like oh well a corporation isn't a person
therefore they don't have free speech
it's god damn it that part is not about corporations
it's about the god damn press
I know but like
the press isn't a person
yeah it's the press it's not
okay I'm sorry what do you get
because my feeling is that like you know
if you team up with someone
like even the PCP isn't incorporated
but it's not a person it's a group of multiple people
right so I don't know it's just kind of like
for me I just think of that as sort of a fallacy that people need to
like I wish that
like the way that
publicly traded corporations work
is obviously very very
problematic and really should be looked at
but then I just feel like people sort of throw out
like the entire every single baby
with that particular bathwater you know what I mean
I think I know what you're getting at you're talking about like
people walk around as though if you don't represent
a single person then you don't
really have the right to of
expression I don't
here's a here's a here's a thought about this so for example
Chick-fil-A just fucking
loves Jesus down to their
like you know Chick-fil-A doesn't
want to give like their their female employees like birth control
and whatever there was like a thing about that
because they like
the text they say is we have a sincerely
held belief that like we are
like a religious organization this is a fundamental
principle of us and this goes against
our religious beliefs and we don't want to be forced
to do things that go against our beliefs and
like I could understand someone
being skeptical especially like an atheist who's
like well that's obviously just a trick
to like get away with you know
just not having to spend more on their
employees but the thing is I am
100% convinced that Chick-fil-A
is 100% sincere
about their love of Jesus and
even though I don't think he's you know real or whatever
I mean you know the
thing about Chick-fil-A they close on Sunday man
they cut off profits one seventh of the
week you would think
that that would be unpopular
you would think that they would get a lot of
backlash for that and they do
but the thing is there is a large population
of people who sincerely agree with them
they might be in the minority I don't know
they might be but there's enough of them
that like the goodwill generated within that
population like more than
makes up for the fact that there are lots of people
and lots of people don't want to eat their
shit because they're you know terrible
you're just you're appealed to your demographic
that's like good business
I don't think they're doing themselves any favors
really by like because they really
are putting themselves in the camp of like a small
minority I would argue like
I guess I don't know the statistics
there's like three quarters
there's a lot of religious people in American
most Christians are atheists in denial
I would argue especially in America
most atheists are Christians
why do you refuse to
love God yet you know exist
and you've chosen to just hate
the thing about refusing
birth control right I think my dad
actually agrees on me with this position
even if a little bit like begrudgingly
which is I think it's
in general bullshit that you
have to give employees like
certain things unilaterally
like what happens to just oh you want
this job here's what we'll offer you
maybe it's money maybe it's healthcare
maybe it's this handshake agreement done
I mean I think both of us
the fact is
where the fuck were all these Christians
like protesting the idea of
you have to give every employee a certain amount of healthcare
a certain amount of dental based on certain you know random
bullshit back before it became
religiously controversial right
like Christians should have been on their fucking toes
to realize oh shit if we're allowing
way back in like the FDR
and LBJ era for
the government to force you to give certain things
to your employees that could be turned
against us I don't think they did back then though
I think that the reason it's become an issue
is because like as things
move in a more progressive direction
in some aspects of American life
like the idea of how contraception
should be because it's like you know
you can make an argument it's part of women's biology
and healthcare now they've added on
yeah now they've added on birth control
and like abortion onto it
well I don't think it's wrong
I don't think you should be able to have a get out of
get out of benefit
free clause because you don't believe in abortion
I just feel like everyone shouldn't have to be
giving certain people certain things outside of
like a simple contract
between employer and employer
I mean me personally I don't think
any company should be giving contraception
because like it's not a mandatory thing
like don't fucking
yeah like abstinence is 100% effective
you know I mean that's
I don't know
I mean if it's that's like
if that's a thing that would be covered by health insurance
like birth control is
is covered by health insurance and jobs
provide health insurance so why wouldn't
I know this is an extreme example but just for the
for the intelligent
reflection of this principle
it's like so like what if I am one of
these people who what do they call them the people who are like
into getting viruses and into getting diseases
bug catchers
I don't know
I'm sorry bug chasers
if I'm a bug chaser and let's just say
that I go get AIDS because I really want
AIDS and I'm into that like is it
then the company's responsibility to pay
for that because now it's
a medical issue
and it just did the same way I would argue
that you have exactly as much agency
to not have a child and need
you know an abort you know
contraception or whatever
well I know it's
I don't know you have
agency in lots of things like
why does that mean that it shouldn't be covered by health insurance
this is the real point though I'm with
DeVoo and I'm really libertarian I just think
basically companies just shouldn't do it they shouldn't
be in the business of like giving health care
it should just be everyone's job I don't like
the way that health insurance
is set up I don't like that you have to
work for a company so that
someone will pay for you to get
like just give me the money I think it should
just be available well I think it should
I mean I think it should be universal and I think everyone should
have access to whether you fucking work for a corporation
young people working at entry level jobs
or trying to get jobs in the first place
ever notice how you're totally dependent
on your fucking job for your fucking health care
and you're definitely on your fucking insurance company
and your hospital to get the right care
and you're responsible on your government to be able to
take care of all your shit maybe there's a reason
why politicians love to talk about how you
should give people more fucking health care
because it makes you more dependent
I just want to point out that about
this probably applies to lots of health care issues
but about birth control specifically
like birth control is cheap
and children are expensive and like
really like everybody wins
like everybody wins if people have easy
access to birth control
like that's not I don't think
like I think that that I think that providing that
service pays for itself like a hundred
it's only it's just that is a real practical
concern that I am very sympathetic to
but it's just that when we do that it then
opens up the door to this like this
Chick-fil-A type situations where
things get messy because they really
religiously have a problem with doing
so who wins
right
Christian Baker
being requested to make a gay wedding cake
thing I just wait I just want to
say that I really think the problem here is with
like the fact that health insurance is like
a corporate responsibility
I think that's where the trouble comes in I mean you
can get health care outside I mean I
never have so I don't really
know I'll find out when I quit my job one of these
days but
yeah that sound like your boss
haha
someone was just making a transition it was a topic
interesting yeah it was
Baker being requested to make a gay wedding
yeah oh that's a good one
do they have to now here's my dad
okay my dad I didn't clarify this my dad's
like a super Christian guy got lots of like
degrees in Bible he's like he's about to go on
like a short missions trip actually where's it going
where's it going
well I thought it might be like you
like you got there or something
okay fine fine so
he's going to my house
like one of the fucking trolls
it's going to go down into like central
some some fan
some fan
some fan in like Zimbabwe
listening
he's like hey are you Davoo's dad
I like the difference in like
laxness
that we fucking have on this show we have
Davoo who's just like I can't dox
my dad's where he's going on like the mission
for the church and then
Digi's like Virginia Beach my hometown
you know
that's out there that's out there
I don't think a town is doxing
he muted himself
okay he's probably been trying to say stuff
for getting him muted himself well maybe anyway
so my dad did just muted himself
oh my god
you know it's just common courtesy to
accept custom from people right
so like he'll clean a gay person's
windows for example right no no problem
there right but he thinks
baking that's like
artistic expression right making a
cake make an argument yeah is like
something that comes from more from your soul
right and just exist
but yeah where like I totally
feel that way too I thought I think it's
ridiculous that like
that you have to be
forced to uphold any kind of
like right societal
moral standard that is like the whole
point of freedom of speech to me
is that like and freedom
of to be able to do whatever you want
with your corporation is like I think
everybody's just a pundit for the world
that they want right like
that we all exist
to try to promote the world that we want
to live in and like most
of us disagree with each other about the
specifics of that world like the
amount that we agree on is where we've
drawn the lines in our country like
the lines in the sand is where we've like we all agree
on at least you can't kill people
like there's some people who disagree with
that but they are such a minority and we feel so
strongly the opposite that we're going to make
sure those people are not listen to
wait wait wait what was Gibb saying
I was going to say about the gay wedding
case thing because I heard about that way
back when it was like relevant
and I remember always thinking like of course
you should be allowed to refuse
service if that's what you believe
even though I didn't think it was a good idea
I think that the
point is that you should have
the freedom
of expression to have a
like unpopular business model
that does badly for like
you would do in any other situation
like there was a situation that happened a couple
years back that was like the inverse of this
there are a bunch of like like super
hardcore Christian people like
passing out pamphlets and stuff
and like I think it was like
like a pro-life sort of thing that they were doing
and they went to this coffee shop to like take
a break and this guy
comes in and screams at them
that he's a gay guy and he disagrees with everything
he said get the fuck out of his cafe
we were talking about gay people don't even need a portion
and they did
and they had to leave and like
all the same people who would like be
you gotta make the cake were totally
on his side kicking them out so it's just like
that's a tough one
that's a double standard
would you force a Jewish baker to make a swastika cake
to which like the rebuttal to that
is usually oh but that would be ridiculous
cause those are Nazis and it's like there you go
what is actual free speech to you
is all the things that you
the thing is that we don't
need the government to do anything
about this because the free market
will do something about it
if you refuse
you just go somewhere else
if you make a statement that like you will not
make a gay cake for anybody
people who think that that's not okay of you
to do will not buy from you
and you could even lose your platform
as a store
you have to be renting a space
what if your realtors don't want to support your business anymore
because they don't believe in the same things as you
what if the people in your community
want you driven out what if they pick it like
you you know what if they stand in protest
outside your store every day and you can't get any customers
all of that's fine
now we get back to the thing I said at the very beginning
which is that people get into giant like
twisters on like who's the one that broke the free speech
you know it's like
who's the one who crossed the line
to censorship here right
and we need to always be very vigilant
of when we cross the line
into saying
the government should do something
about it and I think because people jump
to that so often we should take more
time out of our day to emphasize
that we very specifically don't want
the government to get in on
I feel like RazorFist just had a video about this
with the whole
EA gambling thing so check that out
I'll have to check that out I feel so bad
for the word censorship
it's really been abused these last few years
it's really taken a beating
and it's gotten a raw deal
censorship used to be a powerful bastion
and like this is a criticism of guys on like
the right as well
this isn't just like SJW
it's like censorship is like when
it's censorship
when someone you know like
I don't know I can't give you an example
when the government steps in and tells you
when people invoke
the government to say that
like if you're petitioning
Obama to ban
the word retarded
you are advocating censorship
that was a huge movement that happened
in the late 2000s
and you know
funnily enough
this goes back to what I was saying before
about how Louis C.K. was like the bastion
of free speech and then became a cuck
same thing with Stephen Colbert
he had this amazing segment where a guy
who was doing this campaign
to get rid of the word retarded
had come on his show
the entire thing and then at the very end
turns to the audience and says alright kids
don't say the word retarded
it's totally gay
this is the funniest shit I've ever heard in my life
that's fantastic
did you remember that?
I remember it
and now he would you know
now he'd probably be on the total opposite side of that
because it looks good for support
like it looks good to just
co-tow to whatever the gay community
wants you to say
AndyYoutuber who like
got picked up by the mainstream
and like became like a real
just streamlined everyday vloger
here I go
this is a disgrace
what he's doing right now
god it's sickening
I used to love Colbert
I loved him
Jesus Christ
all the money they threw at Colbert to take that job
censorship
that's goddamn censorship
old hard cash
it was immoral
all the fucking Obama stimulus bucks
don't trust anybody
if someone sold out enough
that they can run a late
night talk show they're not worth trusting anymore
to a degree
so the thing that retarded right
I remember one time making a chain of tweets
that was like two guys talking
and it was like oh man
dude my boss
he's totally blind to the truth
yeah man your boss sucks
oh dude
I'm in a cancerous relationship
oh man yeah man
I hope you get out of that relationship
oh dude my finances are just
crippled right now
oh man I hope you get a good break
oh dude this guy I saw yesterday
this joke I heard yesterday
was retarded
whoa hey man
it's offensive to use real life disabilities
as a negative insult
but someone responded with
I don't know with the very cogent
argument but I still
that was like my favorite tweet you ever made
with the very
not really logical but emotionally
I understand it argument which was as follows
I don't know man saying retarded
as an insult just seems kind of wrong
which is simply because
if you're retarded you're a worse person
dude I fucking hate people
who say shit like that because
they just like
literally that's complacency
it's just oh well I don't want to think about it
I'm just going to do what people tell me is like
the right thing to do
this is the hard truth that no one wants to face
if you're retarded you're a worse person
because in our society we value
who you are on the inside
and if you're retarded you are actually
worse at being a human being on the inside
and no one wants to face up to that
no you're not wrong in an intellectual
capacity way if you have a mental deficiency
then you are less
now to say you're a worse person than average
this isn't if you have great moral character
I'm not trying to disagree at all but
just for example my mom is a special education
teacher and I would say
retarded to her all the time
and it was very common for her to say to me
Nate like I wish you wouldn't say that
like that's people you know
that's a very negative thing to say
and like my kids would you know be the kind of people
I wish you wouldn't say that bitch
how do you like them apples
it's perfectly
I never like did that
occasionally I would try to avoid that particular word
for emphasis when talking to her
cause I didn't want to hurt her feelings
which I guess is self censorship but like
well it's just police
I think we all are gonna
self censorship is a good idea
in all capacities
not just of swear words
or things that are obviously offensive
censor yourself all the time for all kinds of reasons
cause your inner
your inner monologue is probably
most people around you
censorship you know even just in its usage
right now unfortunately has this
the same sort of phenomenon that the word racist
has had in that like so many different
like degrees all get mixed up in one
word and then people basically hear
the most extreme thing when you say it
um so like like if I
delete someone's tweet like I
understand that is like you are technically
accurate to say I am sort of
censoring them yes by the way which I like
literally never ever do
like that would be a fair thing to say but
beyond that I think you are going against
sort of the spirit of what real
censorship and like notable censorship
is if the if governments never
existed but Twitter did no one
would have thought of the word censorship as meaning anything
all that bad I sort of yeah I basically agree
and just incident I just really want to point out I never
delete tweets or like
posts or anything I like
I just leave it there I just want to
delete tweets I want to jump back on that
right to do so that retarded thing that
DeVu was saying about the guy saying like oh it's
just kind of like uncomfortable to say that
I think that is so fucking intellectually
dishonest and it's because
the words
that you feel uncomfortable with are changing all the time
it was totally different ten years
ago we all said retarded nobody thought it was
weird but now that people now that
someone in your social group is not okay
with you saying it it makes you uncomfortable
we used to say gay and now gay is not cool
but I still say it anyway
I think gay kind of circled
around being cool
this is how fucking simple I know people are
is that people will fucking
watch someone like that guy on the
Colbert report who will just turn up
on TV and give you a sob story
about why it offends him when you say
retarded and then you'll go around to your friends
and be like guys it's not okay to say retarded
and then you'll listen to
some other guy some
comedian who will give you the exact opposite
story with a decent amount of reasoning
and you'll go oh I guess it's okay to say retarded
again because this guy made the argument
and now I realize oh I do like saying it
and like people are exactly
that fickle that's what the Overton window does
is it just bounces back and forth
between comedian this comedian
made it okay to say gay again
this gay guy I think like you know now
we got Milo out there Milo
Milo's flaming gay he's
gonna say all these words you got YMS out there
calling people faggot all the time like
and he's like hey I do you think
I'm not allowed able to handle the word faggot
and fuck you and I'm like well okay
but did you the gay community has disowned
Milo they have disowned him
they haven't disowned YMS though
and he's you know you're right
what's more offensive to YMS calling him a faggot
or calling or questioning the fact that he needs
someone else to edit his incredibly
lazily edited quickies
YMS please fire your quickie editor
get somebody who can make them
well just like the guy is editing them
as though he's trying
to make the worst youtube video
I mean they could be a lot better
they're not great
I think that on this particular
slippery slope of like these words gay and retarded
I think retarded is a little bit easier
to justify because if you can google it
the second definition is
delay or hold back in terms
of progress development
but everyone knows what you mean when you say retarded
no one's using that definition
well hold on though because I actually
I don't know maybe I'm a little
bit more literally minded than average
possibly I kind of think of the word retarded
as like I tend to think
of like stupidity you know people whose brains
aren't sure sure but if you like if you
there's like a fan and you stop the fan with
your fingers and then you start moving the fan in the opposite direction
you are retarding
the blades of the fan
right like retarded does kind
of also mean you're absolutely
right that normal that word does in fact
have a basically socially acceptable
definition but here's the thing though
it's just if I call you
if I call you a faggot
like there's really no way around the fact
that that's simply an offensive word
now going to gay the thing about gay
is that the thing that we're really referring
to is something that like I think those
those words kind of the gay is getting
its new meaning because of a thing
that
is more commonly colloquially attributed
to gay individuals
isn't that discrimination to do that then
that is I think it like it has
a little bit more of like a discriminatory
or a little bit more like stereotypical
origin and even though
you recognize it's not all gay people
but it's like certain traits that you can
often see stereotypically
at least in gay men
most commonly
but then a lot of people
use the word gay me included
as just like bad
even though I don't feel that way about anything
homosexual I think what a lot of people forget
when it comes to like stereotypes and stuff
is that we as human beings
like to be a part of something
we like to be stereotyped
if it's something that we actually
feel connected to
there's a reason that black comedians
constantly talk about being black
because
they've taken which elements of
the stereotypical black experience
people want to identify themselves
with and like claimed it
they've been like yeah this is what black
people are because we like that
and we want to be this way
at least for a bit
yeah well my dick is big
what's the line that
Kendrick sings in black or the berry
that whole song is him rattling off all the black cliches
that black culture
has tried to embrace and be like
this is the positive image we want of ourselves
we'll invite some of the dumb shit too
watermelon and chicken whatever
everybody likes those things
that's not offensive to say that we like those things
I don't really care all that much for watermelon
although I will say just like the other day
that girl chasing a chicken around
that was kind of offensive
is there such a thing as inner blackface
because I think you've got it didgy
I definitely have inner I've got some kind of weird
concoction
I only interpret the world through black and Japanese
media like all I consume
is black and Japanese media so I don't
even know what white people are up to
because I can't listen to country
I can't do it
did you ever heard
but me hippo and Ben
I don't know if I heard correctly it's about how y'all
is a black word
y'all is just a southern word
everyone in the south says y'all
but also the people are black now
well okay
sure
you know Thomas soul doesn't just
do business in economics he also does black history
shit right he has a book called
it's a stupid title but it was
actually fucking reviewed by it better than food book reviews
black rednecks and white liberals
in which like his findings
that the southern culture and southern accent
all got sparked
by northern Britain
like those are the ones who moved to the south
in America and that's where the
accent evolved into the southern accent
and then that southern accent
and southern sensibilities were taken
where then you know that's where most of the black slaves
were and then they immigrated northwards
and then that's where sort of the modern
racism situation so what you're telling
me is that Gibb is
a slave holder that's what I'm hearing
southern UK
oh shit well
and in most countries north is where
the fucking boondock stuff
the funny thing about the east coast is that it's
like especially with black people it's all
very interconnected and there's lots of
emigration around
most of the people I knew in Virginia
in Virginia period
were from New York and like
so people constantly like transport
like between the south
like Georgia and Virginia where the cost
of living is a lot lower than New York
cause New York is like crazy overpopulated
and like the cost of living
is insanely high to have like a tiny shit hole
apartment so like people who can only afford
to live in like a one room apartment in New York
will just like get all their shit together
into a fucking car
and just like abandon as much as they
can and just hail Mary
down south when they have kids
so that they can raise their kids in a house
so like that's where literally like
half of all the black people in the south
like come from it's just like New Yorkers
who flee down to have kids
and then eventually a lot of those kids go back
up to New York cause they need jobs
you know? Is this like the fucking penguins
or certain like breeds of fish that like
go back and forth for mating seasons?
Is that what we are? Is that one of the things
of it's black people is penguins? I mean it's not just
black people but that's just like the majority
of who's in like the burrows in New York
you know like white people are doing the same shit
but it's just poor the poor are
doing this. I can't believe it we're fucking
penguins this is like the biggest revelation
Happy Feet is our future
Hey listen there's one more area I
wanted to talk about. Munchy did you wanna
chime in? Yeah I have a thing to
say about self-censorship that's alright
Yeah me too actually. No I censor
you yourself
I walk outside and every
single day when I'm interacting with
literally any of my family
all it is is like
self-censorship. That's all it is
I do not
There's this line in a Sam Hyde
like one-off
like vlog that is just meant
to be funny. It has hit home for me
and made me cry on certain occasions
Where is it? We are gonna create
a community for people just like us
brothers it's gonna be called Georgioland
and I am a white nationalist. Is that
the line you're talking about? Yeah that is it
It's sister line
is my mom would hate me if she knew what I was
really like. Yeah interesting
interesting. You know
I just wanna say
about all
self-censorship
there it is it's happening right now
I'm trying
to get the words out but I won't let me
I
like the idea
that you can say stuff
like the n-word instead of nigg
because
just because you are okay with it
and just because
people around you probably will be okay with it
doesn't mean you have to
go as hard as possible every time
I think it's okay to be
like I don't want to be called out as a bitch
if I say the n-word
I think that's just as okay to say niggas
I think it's fine if people
are uncomfortable with saying the word
because they legitimately don't
use it
like someone like Anthony Fantano
he never says it
even if it's in like an album title
like but it's because
he just he's never been someone
who says niggas so like
he knows it would be forced if he started now
like he's been avoiding it his whole life
why would he suddenly start
you know that's a reasonable
point the reason why I disagree
and I deliberately dislike when people
avoid saying the word is because
that really that is the vicious cycle
of keeping the word like
in this weird state no one can say it
I do call out I actually
just like I've said in the past
like I think he's a bitch for not saying it when it's in
an album title because I'm like to me
that's being ridiculous it's like
you're you're like you're you're so
obsessed with following the rules that
the supposed rules that you can't just like
literally call the thing by its goddamn
name that they gave it
you know like it's not disrespectful
to call it by the name that they gave
it there was there was a time I was
at karaoke in Seattle one day and
I I was I was doing some
singing and I was singing
some some fucking Kanye
song I can't remember what I was it was like the
closer for the night I go up there I'm busting
it out like the DJ guys this big old
black friendly fellow I'm saying it out
we get to this part where I bust out
some of the stuff the nigga we
we lock eyes he gives me a smile and a
firm nod and I keep going
I had that exact experience
during karaoke when I was
doing yeah because
I was I was at a karaoke bar with my
one of my black friends was there and him
and the other black guy who just happened to be
at the bar like teamed up to do a Kendrick
Lamar song because you know
hi everyone every if you
know anything black then you must
be a fan of Kendrick Lamar it's just like the
rules right now basically in culture
so yeah these guys won't get on
stage to do bitch don't kill my vibe
but I immediately detect that neither
of these guys actually knows the words
but I do so I get up there
and I'm like gonna do the actual rap
parts you know for these guys
and I'm sitting there and like I'm saying
nigga and I see the dude I can tell the
dude who doesn't know me for like one seconds
like hold up did that white dude just say
nigga but then he's like then again he knows
all the words and neither of us do
so who's the realest nigga up here for real though
right and you know what
okay look I'm just gonna like make an assumption here
maybe other people like can confirm
this if I'm a black guy
and I hear some white person say nigger
I might perk up because maybe they're racist
or maybe they're chill right and you have to
like worry about that right you know
like it's just unfortunate that we're
in a situation where the words are this
you know
intense oh yeah oh what if
what if we send the naked one
that's good that would be awesome
oh by the way the song was runaway I was
singing that's what it was
one time one time did you remember
Matthew Matosis review of fireshock
infinite where like it's supposed to be
this society where people are racist against blacks
but they never go farther than saying
niggro yeah he literally
was like shit maybe saying nigger all
the time like because that
because if you if you don't let them use
the word nigger then you're like
you're making your whitewashing it you're making
it look better shit than it was
and like yeah and honestly
if you're a person who gets upset when white
people say nigger but not black people as
much all I can imagine
is like an old-timey 1950s photograph
with a couple of fucking water faucets
there's a nice one that says
the words for white people
only you can only use prim and proper words
if you're a white person then down here at the
little dingy water fountain
that's the ones that the colored people can say
they can say words like nigger if they wish right
that's what I see it's fucking
I hear you all right hey by the way
you guys ready for a big call out
you want me to you want me to call somebody
out on the show oh jeez
yes I'm ready I'm ready
so this is also this debate
is a thing in the black community
because of the fact that
Quentin Tarantino
wrote Django Unchained
Spike Lee is not okay with this
Spike Lee who's like the blackest
director ever you know
he made he's made all kinds of
fucking great movies he made
what's the fucking one that Jesse
loves Nate you know it right
glorious bastards
do the right thing
and like he directed kings of comedy all this other shit
he has a real
problem with Quentin Tarantino
saying you know like writing nigger into his
scripts and he called out
Samuel L. Jackson for being
in the movie he was like
he's like yo I'm not okay with that
Samuel L. Jackson was like look
like this is real shit and he said
he said Samuel L. Jackson said you think
I'm gonna pass up the opportunity to play
the most hated black character in
cinema history like no I'm taking
it you know but like
it's just what are you trying to do
Spike Lee are you trying to make it seem
like the racist slave holding
American south wasn't
offensive enough to say nigger
I mean you know what Spike Lee is trying to do
at the end of the day here's what I think it comes down to
like I understand
why there are some people who are
uncomfortable with the message of
Tarantino's film and why like
they would think it's not okay for him to
write this movie but
like I don't
like I don't see how those people cannot
understand that there are other black people
who will be like no this is actually exactly
what I wanted this is totally vindicating
and I love it which is how a lot of my
black friends were about the movie like
literally my friend Marcus
was a black guy who didn't really say
nigger much until he watched
Django and then started saying nigger
all the time like and he literally
attributed it to the movie like
that was amazing that's the kind of
shit that is actually happening in the
world this is real that
was a real story I just told you and
like you have to think about that when
you talk about this shit you got to think
about the black guy who watched that movie
and felt so like
I mean I don't know what that means about him
and maybe some people be like oh I'm not okay with
that being like how the youth are feeling but
like look that's just what it is like this dude came from
Virginia Beach he was raised
weird because he had to go to speech therapy when he was
young so he talks white and like
people picked up on that and didn't really
include him and so he hung out with
me and anime nerds and learned how to do
kung fu and became jacked and joined
the army like this is the kind of people who
exist we got to think about everyone
who exists when we talk about who can say what
words and what they mean to who you know
right you know when I like I feel that in
myself I forgot my call out though
my call out is Nino
my call out is Nino who jumped on my
song white nigger to help make this
point but then he came back
later and he got famous on black
twitter and started
writing for a fucking huffington post
and I was doing this
yeah Nino writes for HuffPo
on like their black site like they're
they're like black interest
page yeah okay
point being that because
he started like hanging out with them
he's all like oh now I now I'm not
like about white people saying nigga no
more like and I was
like oh you fucking cunt
you nigger get out of here
there you go whatever you know when you
talk about like what's up with the double
standard and people like people were very
explicit about it like movie bob will say
dude slavery is why
the countries that we are living in right now
did these things that underprivileged
certain colors and overprivileged others
that's the reason there's a double standard
because when you go into it on an individual
basis it seems like the double standard comes from someone who
went to fucking college or got a job in media
like or got a fucking liberal
friends you know honestly
I don't have much to say on this point
except that I just want
to say that like like did you
like well I don't know I don't
have burn with a seething rage
at how how like lucky
black people are they get to say the
word nigga I don't burn
with that but I don't feel that way
either I just want to clarify
that the reason that I feel so strongly about
this is simply that this word
has always been in my head
and to me it's like
it's so ludicrous to be like
oh like
everything you like has always had
this in it like you've you've
the movies you grew up on the music you listen to
just like everyone else it's the same reason
black people use the word is they
hear it all the time so that's I
heard it all the time and but it's like
it's literally discrimination
to look at someone and be like oh well you might
have grown up with this word just like anybody else
but because your skin color is different you can't say it
I completely agree and that was my point
my one of my favorite shows of all
time is the boondocks and I know
100% without a doubt
it is due to my love for the boondocks
and the excessive use of the word
nigga but I started to incorporate it into
my day literally when I was 12 I
read all of the comics
this is what I would call
the good kind of cultural appropriation
like I developed an appreciation for
hip-hop as a result of watching the
boondocks and like I got introduced to
just like more black characters expanded
my interest so I would say
that like because of the fact all cultural
appropriation is good except for like really
tacky cultural appropriation I think
that because of the fact that like black
culture has so much like meta text
to it and that like that the boondocks
is specifically about exploring that
like when you watch that as someone
like me who's got like a very
categorical brain where like I
memorize all the names and connections between
things like I do with the anime industry but like
with black culture because it's
so self-referential and everybody's like playing
off of each other all the time like
when you start studying that
it's involving in the same way that like anime
is and that's why
I end up like like all my
favorite shows that aren't anime are like
the boondocks in Atlanta and like other shit
like that because like it's almost a narrative
I'm keeping up with of like what's going on
with the blacks you know like well okay
I just want to make the point that like
it just simply is part
of my human experience to like
use the word nigga for example
and I just want people to know that if you
tell me that I can't do that that's
I understand your perspective but
it's not that I'm just burning
it's just you're simply telling me to not be
who I am so if you're comfortable doing that
that's fine like you can make that
argument but that's why I
strongly disagree with that point
the only other thing I want to talk about was I wanted
just to cover for the sake of clarity
you always got to touch on the private
versus public like censorship
legality like
what did you get banned on Twitter is this
censorship is this you know
fucking is that a violin free speech
like what's the deal here
I think that like obviously
Twitter's
they're a company who can do it
whatever they want but like
I do wish that there was like a protected
version of Twitter because I think
Twitter weirdly is
like a resource the world needs
like I think it's proven that
like the amount of like
like I mean the entire fucking Arab spring
happened because of Twitter like what the fuck
like it's it's so important
to like disaster
relief efforts and stuff like there should
be like an open public
highway version of Twitter that
like yeah and
it should be and it should be for everybody like
you shouldn't be able to get banned from it you know
well that's the thing about corporations in general
is that this is something that libertarians
because there should be no money let's sorry
just there should be no
corporate interest tied into it so that people
can have unpopular opinions and it's not
going to affect anyone's business
interest is why I want it to be like yeah
you know but like okay so like that's the thing
about like corporations in general and this is something
that libertarians are they really need
to like get themselves fucking
woke on this they really need to address this that
the whole reason we came up with free
government the whole reason we came up with the idea
of rights is because we
entered an age where we were approaching
industry where governments were able
to have a level of organized power
that they could really micromanage and fuck
with people's lives no one would have come up
with the constitution in like 5000 BC
right so for the same
reason we are now entering a society
where things are so interconnected that
corporations are able to do a very similar
thing like even though it's all
technically voluntary the level
of control they can have
over society is getting
pretty fucking
thick and it's getting harder and harder
for me to justify it as simply
their private company if you know what I mean
yeah that's like the argument
where people are arguing like our twitter and facebook
are they at the point where they're becoming like public
utilities that's the issue
that's the issue
like what if someone still made the argument that
well you know the internet's run by private
companies so like it took
there was a point where we decided
that like telephones were a public utility
because like an inventor
made it and then it became popular
and then they made a utility and then I think
the same happened with the internet and
like it's just I really
think a lot about this like what's the right
balance we I have no interest
in like dictating exactly to a company
what to do to pursue
their profit motive that's that's their business
and that's totally fine but on
the other side when you're in the business
of like allowing people
to communicate it becomes
like if twitter
is actually causing society
to splinter down
the middle into like a more divided
society that is
not good and the question is
how to address that like social media
really seems to just have done
this straight up so
what's the fix I don't you mean like
politically I mean politically yes and
along like ideological lines
say like oh man fucking
social media is going to make it to where you only get
articles and headlines that you agree with
and I I get fucking ha ha
here's what Trump did this week like all over
the damn place to this day so I don't know
like if this isn't working on me but personally
in my experience I've
seen it as it's making people
more aware of what
other sides are saying than ever before
maybe that's the problem I don't know
I have the exact same experience
as you where I constantly have
friends we're both super libsuck
you know full of conservative gods
ha ha ha ha ha
all the issues Trump is bad or Trump is
good I think the problem
is is that most people do
not have
people who are they don't have
a varied taste in friends yeah they
get into the bubble of people who agree with them
yeah maybe they get into their bubble because it's
really stressful but I think ultimately
I think the internet still
like even in your bubble you're going to see things
eat through the algorithms are not perfect
and I just think that like people are more aware
than ever if you go to an extreme opposite
end 500 years ago
people with opposite political opinions
lived in a different country past a border
and maybe a sea or two and didn't even
know them you the only chance you would have
to conflict with them is up the
broad side of a sword in a battle right
but now we actually are much more aware
of other world view you know that
like yeah that we wouldn't have known about
and it stresses us out but
it moves society you know like like
forces us all to hear one another
I feel like
right now I love being alive now
because I get to listen to like
I'll listen to fucking like
Ben Shapiro then like the young Turks
and then I'll like listen to something Stefan Mullen
you says then I'll go listen to like fucking
Sam Harris, Kyle Kalinsky
fucking I'll listen to like the same
video about the same topic
from like five, six sources
I can't do that shit
I would drive me nuts
put it on in the background like while I'm working
so I just it fills the time and by doing that
I feel like I'm finally getting closer
to like I know everyone's biases
because I've listened to all these people a long time
and now I know like okay Stefan Mullen
you is like insanely dedicated
to like protecting children to like kind of a
crazy degree I'm not calling him crazy but like
so like he's got huge biases he hates
big government he you know logically
see has deducted that like government
is evil gotta get rid of it like okay that's his bias
the young Turks super left wing
but SJW you keep all that bias
brings to the table all of internet
yeah interaction
and all trying to deduce the truth
from politics yeah it's just
like an eight like a times eight
or more Venn diagram
you have to have everyone's bubble
all lined up and then that's right
everyone has in common is the truth
I think that I think Stefan
Mullen real quick like like the Stefan
Mullen you think yeah have you
heard I think he's probably probably heard him talk about
his audio book
universally preferable behavior I've never listened to it
but I've heard about it I recommend it to you because
it's basically him trying to derive
in a sense of objective morality
yeah it's through like just logic it's just
what I've been to yeah yeah I feel like
utilitarians would it would be your
I'd like never quite get through it because he
I feel like I'm finally ready to try and listen to all of it
because he's basically it's him trying to solve the problem
with no one being able to agree on morality
right so I don't know
I gotta listen to it
God you fucking I didn't expect
you to go out about that audio book it made me forget
what the fuck point I was gonna try to make
well shit about biases
something to do with oh that I
don't think the problem is that
we we get into like a bubble and only listen
to a few voices it's that those voices
are not good or are untrustworthy
okay that like there's too many voices
that like
there's a reason that I've come to where like
the only like politicized
YouTuber who I really follow is
RazorFist and it's not because
I agree with everything
he says it's because I trust
him to do
the most research
that every video he does he will
have looked at everything he knows
the names of everyone
in the government he knows
like what they're doing he knows their histories
he knows what's
happening he doesn't listen to the media
and what they're saying he waits until
there is real information that he can use
and he almost always
comes out like if he said something was
going to happen it usually happens
because he's keeping track of what's
going on better than anybody and like
the world is not that hard to understand
you just need to know all the information
the problem with like the young Turks
and Kyle Kulinski to a degree a lot of
these guys who do daily
multiple episodes of the show
they want to produce content as fast
as possible and I don't think any of them have bad intention
but it's their business model that puts
him in a position of doing that
fundamentally the reason why he has the luxury
to be fucking informed is that he's
not a political
YouTuber he talks about video games
and heavy metal and he only makes
a statement on politics
when he has a statement that he's actually pretty confident
in and can look cool making
and I mean
someone else who like their
their job every morning is to get up and like
put on their spin to make them
make their side look good it's just
I'll tell you right now that while I'm happy
this hasn't happened
if like super bunny hop ever
became a political guy
he would be one of the only people I'd listen to
because I know he'll do all the research
I know he'll come in with all the
info he'll never open his mouth about it
if he if he didn't you know I have a
yeah and like that's why I have so much
respect for both of those guys
as as like journalists
on YouTube because I think
that we're in an era now where
magazines are just straight up
irrelevant and because
of the fact that none of them know how to adapt
to YouTube because they're all fucking retarded
we have we as YouTubers
have to figure out how to make journalism
possible on the platform and like
those two guys are the only people
who I know of who I consider like
serious respectable journalists
who I can trust to have done
all the research and I know
they're going to tell me facts you know
dude dude doctor wolf watches
the episode before he
he goes deep
like integrity
doctor wolf always gets a laugh
I want to know what my self-censorship real quick
before we close out okay because when did you
talk about him and his his childhood
I really wanted to just share my piece
we went on a different course so I'll just let things
ease down now so you know
having like Christian non-swery parents
parents who I want to go put
it on the record will say
like nigger if we're talking about the word
like they'll say it out of context
they'll say racial words out of context
but they'll never say fuck or shit out of context
right I'm just like
nah that's a little bit bullshit
that's a little bit bullshit anyway you know and then also
like being homeschooled
and put into sort of like a really tight Christian
bubble of like various like kids
who also have Christian parents so there was
just unlike Digi not really
ever surrounded by
swear words right and not having
watched adult content as a child
so like it took me a while to even learn
what all the swear words were actually
and like you know it's like you know seven
or eight or so and
then by the time I'm around 13
I start getting into more like I start
watching like South Park or Family Guy
and stuff like that just completely off my own volition
because my parents like don't even barely even watch
much TV at this point
let's just watch Fox News actually
all the fucking cop drama shows
but so then like you know I'll be watching
like South Park right and then my dad
will be like oh would you watch it I'm watching
South Park you know and he's like
hmm and I know exactly
what to tell him to like
to shut him off right right which is
oh don't worry I'm not going to go around
swearing like they do in South Park
and he's like okay I guess that's fine you know
and then like maybe I'll be showing some episodes to Aaron
who my brother who at this point would be like 12
years old and like
I'd be like hmm I don't know
but hey Aaron's like don't worry neither
of us are going to swear don't worry we're not going to do it
you know and he's like okay as long as you promise
to not be like those violent cartoons
and then you can totally do it
so what happened was
as we get older by the time we're like
adults or like he's almost an adult
we no longer
like give a single shit like we
are perfectly fine to swear on one another
because we do not care anymore
except for the fact that we've
promised to not swear as a result
of watching swearing cartoons
and we're both filled with pride over it
we have so much ego on the line
to prove to our father
that we're not going to break the promise not of like
loyalty but just to prove that we're
this is exactly the line this is the exact
logic that me and Victor are on
and exactly like didgy
we came up with our own like swear genre
so for example we started using
um van
as a swear word right like what the van
is going on here yeah are you van
and kidding me right so
we came up with that as a swear
because we were think we were talking about
like old actors maybe we were even talking
about Mary Poppins we were we brought
up dick van dyke and we thought
you know dick if van
were a bad word dick van dyke's
entire name would be bad yeah I
thought you were going to go with uh Jean Claude
van dam to avoid saying the word
damn that works too but that would apply
as well but just you know but dick van dyke
so there you go so van
just started saying van as a swear we
I think we gave it like a couple years of run time
before it like really wore out as welcome and just
made us cringe and then that's just when we started
I'm curious to know on the subject
you have like made up swear words like that
did your parents ever object to like not
the word but like sort of the tone
that you say the word with like hey I know
what you're doing there buddy you're trying to get
something past me by saying a completely
literally inoffensive word but it's your tone
that's the swear being said oh yeah
yes oh what the fuck
and overreacting it's all about tone and shit
he wouldn't like it's anything he wouldn't like
punish me well sure sure no matter how young I was
but it was just sort of like it's just interesting
once again my mind is being torn apart
by the breadth of the realization
that this is just what the 90s was
like this isn't unique to our households
because this is the entire logic
that humankind
underwent up until
the 2000s and here's what I mean
do you any of you remember
I don't know if you were still watching Cartoon Network
at all at the time when regular show came out
I know Munchie
I don't really like to call myself a 90s kid
this was all 2000s
do you guys remember the first time on regular
show that they said piss
no I don't did anybody see
that was that like ground
to me it was because
okay okay on adventure
time first of all kids are
they saying suck on cartoons
they said suck on
Steven Universe the other day
exactly so they
started saying okay adventure time broke the
seal on saying sucks
and like dang it and heck
and stuff like that like they were able to say that
shit then regular show
yeah they could say kill and die
and they've used that a lot
they like really went in on the fact
there's like a whole regular show about dying
and then there's yeah
in regular show they started saying piss off
they started saying
is the idea behind the word suck
like suck dick is that like
we're suck puns because then
you have feminists on it
I guess we're gonna have to have a whole
fucking debate on that
because you couldn't say
you couldn't say suck
but you could say that something blows
even though they're literally saying
that is true
the fucking thing about it is
I literally watched them
physically move
the overton window
like a boulder like sycophus pushing it up
the hill like because you can
look at the 80s and see that
there was a period where cartoons were
a lot more violent and crazy because like
G.I. Joe was the biggest thing and transformers
and all that shit and
then you go to the 90s and they cleaned
it all up no one there's like
no guns anymore no one can say kill
no one can like you know
do this or that and then you get to the
I definitely remember Bart Simpson saying that
well Simpsons was different
and that was why Simpsons was so popular
was that it was like a counterbalance
because it aired on primetime TV
on WB it was not a kids show
that's the thing this is not
like it always gets less censorship it's an ebb
and flow you see an old cartoon the characters
can fucking drink alcohol and be drunk
and now speaking of the Simpsons
we might be entering an era where it's
too problematic to have a white person
voicing non-white character
the thing about like both America
and Japan are very particular
about time slots as being like
the definition of what can and cannot pass
so like primetime TV
like even with adventure time
and regular show the reason those shows could get away with that
is that they usually aired in the afternoon
and it was more of like an older
like the kids who were like
10 to 15 watched during
that time you know as opposed to the
really little kids who they're gonna like
just show nothing but Teen Titans go to
you all morning because that's like
Teen Titans go is
the only show they've ever made that is
not only great but also
like it's so mind numbingly
colorful that kids can just stare at it all day
so that's all they air through the morning
but like you know
as they moved to like younger and
younger shows using these words even
Teen Titans go is gonna say these words now
you know like even the stuff they're
showing to little kids because like just nobody
cares anymore like now that we have the
internet you cannot protect kids
from bad words anymore like it's just fucking
impossible unless you really are strict
parent you know but like
it's like we can't lie to
ourselves any longer and why did we
ever do it in the first place we all look like idiots
I think religious regions
I think a lot of this came from
like oh oh oh yeah yeah I have to
tell you guys the one last fucking fake
square I came up with okay well me me and my
brother did wasn't really what was more like
it was actually an all new innovation
in the whole medium of language itself
so my brother
he just started saying shitsu you know
oh shitsu oh man
or even my fiance she likes to say shetlinpony
right but yeah shitsu
oh shitsu you know and then
we were like oh shitsu and then sometimes
we delayed it oh shit
now you're pushing the edge there boy you're getting
ready for a beat oh oh you have no idea
oh yeah oh that's just the beginning
then we were like wait a second we were just like
oh shitsu oh shitsu wait a second
fuck
shitsu it still works
we're like we have this
like agreement
it's all arbitrary right yeah like
language it's all arbitrary the fact that
fuck is offensive in the first place is arbitrary
it was just made up no one's gonna be around
to challenge this we hereby declare
that you could swear as many fucking
goddamn mother shitting cunt
blocking times as you want as long as you
stay sue within any
time afterwards that's good I like it
so sometimes we just be like what the fuck
what the fuck off me shitsu head
sue
two straight years being like we're still
doing we still have our pride
that we are not swearing
just like we promised our dad I like that
that's creativity at work
so have we figured anything out here
have we answered the question of
is free speech cool or is it gay
no what we've learned is that we can
just say nigger sue and it's fine
yeah it's all arbitrary
it's a bunch of bullshit let hashtag
let children swear
that's where I'm at that's where I'm at with this
what we've learned is that we've already
heard all of these complaints
yeah yeah you're right on all of our other
shows and this has bred
no new conversation whatsoever
agreed indeed
I hope you listen to this podcast
while doing something productive
fans you know friends and family out there
that's what I do when I listen to podcasts
let me talk about my 4chan uncle
because I'm in an interesting situation
4chan uncle
as you all know I have an uncle
he goes on 4chan
a deadly combination
and he's always downstairs
in my house now because he's a dead bean
for various other reasons
and so I'm walking downstairs
and he always tries to rote me in conversations
about Hitler and the Jews
no matter how he's doing harassment
you wouldn't censor his free speech
by not listening to him now would you munchie
no I would never censor his free speech
I just have my own free speech
the entire reason that he is talking to me
in the first place
he's always been in a stupor
and he doesn't really talk to anyone
but I have
outed myself as someone who
knows what 4chan is
oh no
he always wants to talk to me
you can't underling this bell
exactly I can't explain to him
but I don't believe these same things
or you know do any of this stuff
I just know what 4chan is
but I'm not going to do that
I'm just going to censor myself
and just go along with whatever political opinion is
so mostly because I'm just a coward
that's the only reason that this is happening
sounds like a hassle
you want to save space at home
we all want to save space at home
I don't even challenge scary 4chan ideas
I'm in this bizarre
dichotomy
whenever I'm around my mom's
it's like yeah I fucking hate Trump
and then whenever I'm with my uncle
I'm like yeah I fucking want to suck Trump's dick
looking pretty dangly right there
but also
hey can you take me out to lunch real quick
I'm playing like a fiddle
I was going to say having
pretty
hardline but firmline
strict conservative Christian
type people as parents
and then also being an art person
on the internet
pretty good at spinning whatever I want to say
to be palatable to both people
like oh oh oh oh
me and my fiance were
at dinner with both my parents
and we were actually talking about
Stefan Molinou's peaceful parenting
paradigm system that he's created
which is all about don't spank kids
don't even yell at kids
don't even punish them, use reason, logic
and whatever the fuck which I'm really interested in
but I know
that if I say to my parents
the idea is to never spank kids
especially my mom is going to immediately
perk up and be like
no, right?
so I'm like trying to avoid saying that
but then like my fiance does
anyway she's like yeah the idea is to never spank kids
and my mom goes
try getting that to work on every kid you have
um
Davoo was abused
that's what we've learned here today
thank you for listening
should we move to questions
I want to say one last thing
my favorite thing to do
in Super Smash Brothers
is to throw the
ice item at
Princess Peach
hashtag
free speech
wait
there it is
classic hippo tweet
the first question
is from two weeks one spar
and I'm curious about this as well
is it too late for me to get into
rowdy fuckers cop killers lore
oh absolutely
no it is never too late
what do you have to do to get in
because I listened to the latest episode
not having heard the last few
and tried to join the discord
and it was totally incomprehensible
okay I would say that
in terms of what to listen to
probably the streams on twitch
are the best things
on twitch
on twitch slash rowdy
frickers cop killers
we tried to make it rowdy frickers cop killers
which literally would not allow us to have it
for the record cop killing is allowed on twitch
but fucking is strictly banned
did you guys see
what I told you that I deleted
last night
in the chat
please say that on the podcast
fucking embares yourself right now
this is amazing
so I've been doing
just blood borne videos
with May and so I just had the game
open and the recording software open
and she had gone to bed and I was listening to
rowdy fuckers cop killers and I wanted to make
a video explaining
why the PCPs quality
had sort of fluctuated so much over time
like what literal
physical things happened
such as that it used to be
that everyone was editing it
and like because
people were putting effort into the editing
and then that no longer became
incentivized or like
the people who were doing it weren't available to do it anymore
so now it's different and like
just things like that
you know I explained all of it
it was like 40 minutes long
and I edited it I listened to the whole thing back
I fucking created this video
started uploading it
and it was like 20% done
but like because of the fact that I'm doing
Let's Plays I'm just like trying to get all the footage on
and off my computer constantly
so I just deleted literally
everything while
it was still uploading not realizing
that it had not finished uploading
Jesus Christ did you I linked
a program that might be able to let you recover the files
it's possible it could theoretically be recovered
if you do it quickly how I
deleted everything like oh there's
it's a real thing deleted files
this is a program I link over Cuba
try it out it's possible
but yeah I
including the thumbnail and everything
like that because I had already uploaded
the thumbnail so single fucking piece
yeah I like damn spent like
15 minutes making a thumbnail
you look straight at the thumbnail for the video you were uploading
I'm like I don't need this anymore
yeah okay well let's
let's learn a lesson
and be a little more patient stop smoking weed didgy
look what it's doing to you
I was really tired at the time
but to the important question
to the important question rowdy fuckers cop
killer right you can watch the twitch
videos but mostly you got to join
the discord
pick up a weapon get in there
get in the dojo
pick up some cocktails and start doing
there's no like when you go into
the discord it doesn't give you like a pamphlet
explaining what the fuck's happening didgy
I'll explain to you right now there's basic training
there's the basic training room with a link
to the help document actually
crack is working on
crack is working on like a new website
that has like a more detailed like explanation
can you just make it I will explain it to you
right now I will explain to you right now
by which I mean he's hacking
okay
the rifle is cop killers
originally it was supposed to be a non-setting
and it was not supposed to have lore and I
specifically said this to bin that we should probably keep
just a grounded setting and unfortunately
even though I quite enjoy the lore
it's warped in this bizarre
like stealing your dad ripoff show
basically
it's still your dad painted green
but it's also canon to stealing your dad
no it's not
didn't it come into being before the lore of stealing your dad
no no
no it's not it's not at all
it's not you would make you change the lore
okay okay okay where's the lore of
stealing your dad deep in
the arizona desert where
the grand canyon exists
there's existed a town and that town had
nuclear a nuclear reactor on it
and that nuclear reactor spilled
and it flooded the entire grand canyon
with toxic waste a.k.a.
slime
and this slime was so valuable for
various obvious reasons
there's a specified obvious reasons
yeah yeah
but there was a city erected next to it
named we don't we're not entirely sure
some of the names are
slime city or neo los angeles city
or neo melwami
or neo guys i just want to let you know
every time i say the name of the city
i always say new los angeles city
a.k.a. neomilwaki
you have to say the whole thing
that is what i want to say for me
NO DO IT NO
okay the rest of the lore is this
this decay america's fastest
growing city is just a normal city
but it's green
and inside the city there exists
an obelisk with unknown
presumably extraterrestrial
properties known as endless war
who incentivizes violence
with his mere presence
me and bin in real life
have moved to slime city
to try and get rich
working the slime mines mine the valuable slime
and we've started a let's play
show for a leisure and that it
canonically exists within the world
and because me and bin presumably after playing
a heated match of super smash brothers
got really mad at each other but because we're such
pussies we didn't want to directly fight
one other so we rounded the local youth
and endangered
juveniles and forced them to do proxy
warfare because we're too close to fight each other
in real life
wait but do you guys like live and work together
in canon? yes
we live in a house to get our own apartment together
and we record let's plays on twitch
are the rowdies and the fuckers aware of this
that you like live together?
in the discord
in the streets
in the mean streets of slime city
is the discord literally a real
or is it a metaphor for a war
you're just going to have to find out
watch the streams
to find the place to do the
combat to pick a side
let me tell you this is a real thing
with real life consequence
because me and munchy released the new rowdy fuckers video
well I released whatever we did it
I released it the other day and in response to that
video coming out new people
joined the discord and the discord became more active
and this affected the slime economy
so much that slime stock
prices went through the roof
and the economy was destroyed
as certain people
as certain people became insanely wealthy
on the slime coin stock market
as a result in like a month or so
me and bin are going to have to fight
iron man style with at least
400 mucks in pokemon
at least 400 mucks
at least
hey guys it's me
no it's the lord of ghosts
no it can't be the lord of ghosts
he's so scary
it's the lord of ghosts
he's a rowdy fuckers calculus character
and he's also real he exists in the real world
I'm very scary
no it's the lord of ghosts
he's so scary don't stay dead
everyone revive explanation point of life
don't feed into his lies
the lord of ghosts is too scared
do not feed the negus slime
it's bad and I'm scared of it
believe lord of ghosts I have all these incest
I have the salt whenever I scratch my head
there's like a Kyoto blossom of skin
and salt and you can pop it in your mouth
I'm gonna feed that right to the right fucking now
oh no I gotta get out of here
holy shit
what a haunting
rowdy the rowdy fucker conquered his fear
and drove away the lord of ghosts
this time
oh did I just miss the lord of ghosts
oh yeah but don't worry
I was just peeing
I have a feeling we'll see him again real soon
tune in to slime fest 2
yes
since we're on the subject of meta questions
and behind the scenes shit
Gwee Kale asks where's the bonus radcon 3 content
for non backers
we still haven't resolved it I don't think
there's no progress on the subject
good question I think we've all just
at least I've been wrapped up and there's still
some major videos to get done for it
but we really should just release that
in some fashion the typical thing
about all these kick starters is it's like
it's hard to say exactly when
is this
appropriate yeah when is this appropriate
to address when we still have like unfinished
business in doing the actual thing
you know
which we were all hard at work on by the way
the silly our dads are being aided currently
and I went into like a Ryers meeting
with Ethan and we went through it all
and we wrote down some jokes and funny shit to edit in
and so those will be out soon and they're looking
to be quite juicy
I mean to clarify
we have given like
all the bonus content has been released for
the Kickstarter people
it's just like we're deliberating whether or not
on when if we are
to like sell it to everyone else
yeah I mean I definitely want to
it's just the only mechanism I really
think that we have is to like make it some sort
of patron reward
but I don't want to like I don't know
that's kind of a weird way to handle it other than
that like I don't know how to like actually set up
like a purchase thing where someone can send us like let's
say five bucks
and then we give them all the videos in response
I don't know how to like do that so
I don't know we got a workshop something we
should talk about this tomorrow's meeting or something probably
Dan it's Jack you probably know something
send it to us yeah if you want to tweet at us
send us some ideas so we're already
two hours and seven minutes do we want more questions
or I got one question from the
from the from a pity question
for today from the Twitter at TP
crass tears hashtag ask BCP
here's a question at zoom
zyke asks what color
best embodies you as a person
and I just want to redirect you
to the newest episode of ready fuckers
cop killers where Ben and munchy go through
a big old breakdown of all the colors
associated with the people here are the
problem children here are the problems
yeah bow and digi are the problem
when when it comes to PCP
you say you say it's
you're the problem but you could just as easily
say that mage and Nate
are the problem well I mean
the reason that okay like munchy
and Ben were saying for example that they love
my color my bright green which I agree
is great and it like fits my stuff
it's whatever it's entrenched like give
it has always had this like
green but it is a grandfathered
in from the pony days Tom has never had
like a set color he was like blue as a pony
then he had the red with rebel pixels
just has gravitated in sky blue we all kind
of know this Ben is black and white munchy
is obviously pink and mage
insists on being an extremely
specific hexadecimal value
purple and everything so
see that's the thing is that like a mage
has like both mage and I
have historically like always been
like pink purple range
like that is true that she
back in the pony days to make you like
an indigo digi but it doesn't really
back in the pony days she was like a darker
like a deeper purple and I was
more of like the pinkish purple because
I had like the sweetie bell design and
everything on my pony yeah she's my
I mean but you know people
but yeah but like I mean like I've got
like the magenta meme thing right now
which I kind of want to lean in on because
I'm gonna make it like a relevant plot point
in my I think you should yeah
like good meme so yeah I that's
what we kind of settled on you on you
kind of like in between red and purple
okay I'm completely fine did you
with you also being purple in fact I
want that I think that is a good idea
but there just are so few
like cool colors it just
honestly I feel like what we're
the approach that you guys have taken
maybe reconsider the idea that like
we're trying to represent a whole range of
colors and more just that it's like
a set of like a palette
that complements each other yeah like
you know what you're deciding a ghibli movie
or something like you're just choosing colors that
go good together you know
yeah yeah that's pretty much I don't
know that they do well it's just
it's just kind of a lopsided rainbow
really yeah the
I'm like on the one side
you've got that you've got like the reds and the pinks
on the other sides and then you've got like the greens
I'm sort of saying that you can reconsider
the color design to be more like
that that it's it's less about
like having a breadth of
colors and more about creating an aesthetic
in the way that the colors blend
you know you know I really think
thinking about we should really make me like
I think we just have to change mage to be
like a deeper like purple blue
like she was in the 20 days
you're gonna she's gonna fucking riot
this is gonna be warfare in the streets
well that would help
so much wouldn't it because there would be more blue
let's okay here's what we need we just would
but we can't just we can't we can't
fucking miss color here's what we do
here's what we do hashtag
hashtag make mage orange
we need to start
she needs to become orange to fill
out our color palette that's what we're missing
we have yellow we have red
Ben is like Ben's like the hemospectrum car
cat where he's like the orange guy the time
for God and it's just become black and white
which is fine but we need a goddamn
orange and we got like hidden behind
my black and white runs the secret
one's the secret orange patreon
exactly I
actually great I take it back
Ben is now black white and a secret orange
he is the orange secret
agent
we hippo what what are you
what
just tell us
well I like the dark turquoise
I love that color
but I if if we
really need to change it I would
not mind going into a briska blue
oh
we don't have a dark because it is briska and it's also
hypocrite is
yeah yeah my channel
is blue themed
and I like briska so I like that
blue green
are we prepared to abandon the
decades long rise
to fame of Gibb and take the world's
greatest pony reviewer
Gibb and take has been a dead character for years
now like aside from Gibb and take lives
in the pony cast every week
with every new episode of my little pony god damn
like he just said he's never been a part
of the pcp though except for maybe
the one horse cast
Gibb and take is banned for the pcp
hypocrite is allowed in
blue themed like so
that's that's always been you know what
make it hashtag make Gibb blue
I like it I would think that if we needed
orange Nate has like plenty of orange
shit in his like I could not
no okay listen listen to me
I cannot be orange because of the communist
glasses meme I cannot be
orange it's unacceptable
I would die and plus like we need
that light green like nobody's like that kind
of green
I personally believe like
like you Nate
Ben
and like
I don't know maybe me are like the strongest
like no one can budge that like no one can budge
the next I love my
my bright green for the following reasons
one it is matched like the background color
of all the art since Ben first designed it
years ago to it is like
the color of spiral power which
I always think to myself whenever I look
at it and there's a third reason I can't remember
but those two are good enough
some other third yeah we'll ever change that
I wrote it down but I think like four reasons
I just like purple because I
associate it with dementia and that's
like I've always tried
to convey that my videos are
someone who's unhinged and lost their
mind and like that's like I want
that to be a constant presence felt in my
videos that like this guy might
be insane and that's why I've
always used purple theming except
for what I'm trying to be like accessible
like in the pony videos where I had green
so I was like that's why the after dark
videos were purple and the main channel videos
were green it was like oh
wait real quick I remembered what the third
point was because I looked it up it's that
the purple and pink of my avatars look really
good with yellow because it looks like delicious
watermelon that's that's oh I remember
when I was designing Wewaga though I specifically
was trying to make it a watermelon that's
right you did yep that's absolutely right
that's absolutely right yeah like greens
purples and pinks are like my my my
by the way did you I remember
this moment I stuck that with me in my mind for like many
a year where I sent you
like this in card featuring did you bro
did you brony in in a
in the background like a little of a bar
and you said that that was your favorite
thing that you've ever like I've ever
made was was fucking did you brony
in a bar and it was fun because
like I am super into
the aesthetic of bars
and like it was just a I mean
back then I didn't have shit tons of fan
art so I hadn't been presented in this way
over and over again like
now I have like hundreds of drawings of me
like smoking weed and drinking and all this
like people exclusively draw
me like doing those things now
but at the time it was like oh my god someone
finally drew me in a bar like this is where
my pony has always belonged
you know and like now we're finally here
hey here's a here's a funny
ish question anyone else want to comment on
this color thing
no okay great
I just want to say how much how glad
I am that I snatched up the black and
white yeah you really lucked out there's not
there's nothing else people would fight over that
like in like in Pulp Fiction
when they all not sorry Reservoir Dogs when
they all thought of her who'd be Mr. Black
but anyway yeah one spar and
with another question here asks during the
process of editing a video I find
that starting the render i.e. the wait
for hours button can feel relieving
at some times and anxiety inducing
at others but this is the this is the
interesting part do you have do any of you
also feel a specific way
when you initiate that process wait I
read that question wrong I thought it was do you
have a ritual that you do when you start
that process I'm gonna answer that question
because I like it better yes I
I relaxed
I crack open
a big
glass of water skull I smash
a glass of water
to get the jagged it I fill with water I take
a long deep draft
think that's the word for drink of it
I just lie down I just lie down
drink drink there well
I'm trying to flex my words
I just I just
I'm trying to express how relieved and
great I feel when I'm finally rendering
a video it's such a wonderful feeling for
me you really
you really remind me of the youtuber
CGP gray in a lot of ways
though though if you just took gray but
removed all like if you took name
removed all memes sure
get CGP gray okay
he's super methodical
I think it would really behoove you to listen to the first episode
of hillarine if you would get super inspired
he's very Spartan and
he does not
have anything unnecessary in his house
I'm gonna write that down
yeah if you were to like create a
spectrum of like
robot internet celebrities and CGP
gray is like pretty far in one
end and then like Maddox is completely
on the opposite end as far as you can possibly
go Nate is like
super like closer to CGP gray but
more in the middle I would say
robots
it's just how to deal
you know I was thinking about this I was
is this a thing I was thinking about dry
comedy and I'm like now man I'm into that
wet comedy I'm
I was at you I came
with that when I was like 12 okay that's
part of my I didn't I just want to say
somebody said that that spectrum that
Davoo just described like I was trying to
think like what is the meaningful
like putting those two people on opposite ends
of spectrum and it's just like literally
an insanity bar and he's putting you
in the middle of the insanity bar like
everyone here is insane just in like
well all of them are like human robots
but like CGP gray has actually
like completely thought out every
element of his and is like
actually just maximum efficient where it's
yours is like a somewhat warped like
halfway there like yeah I'm working on it
you know
yeah it's like if your robots fucking
CGP gray is like running like perfectly
corrected Linux and Maddox is running
like some fucking malware
my techniques and it's just a window
like he's a window it's not
a lean machine but he keeps the desktop
clean you know what I'm saying that's true
beautiful so my technique
for how to deal with the render is have a dopey premiere
because it renders shit I think
literally 10 times faster though every
times in Virginia when like Ben was
having to borrow my computer for rendering
Ben was like hey Davoo I gotta like render
this video literally all day okay
hold on give me a second to render this other
video extremely quickly in Adobe Premiere
before you turn on Sony Vegas and take
all day on rendering or something I actually
there's actually something fucked up with my computer
because I assembled it myself and then
shipped it around the country three goddamn
times so the fan
the CPU fan isn't quite fixed right so
I had to throttle the power of the
CPU to only work at like
80% of its capacity
until I could get that fan fixed
and even still Adobe Premiere
renders videos like five times faster
than Vegas would
so use Adobe Premiere to take the edge off
yep makes sense to me
agreed never um
when I render video but maybe
it's usually just like a sigh of relief like
yeah because I I mean
I edit really fast and I just tried it
like for me it's like the second I've made
the last edit if I I mean
well if I've watched it back
enough times that I don't want to have to watch the entire thing again
because chances are I watch it like
over and over again the whole time
I'm editing it so I know it's
done you know and then you write
you don't understand it with Adobe Premiere
render so fast I can just
render it before having to
watch it back I'll watch it back in the render
and redo the render sometimes
I just don't even bother because like
they the preview window can be so shit
in Vegas that like it's not even
you know it's actually I'm just looking back
at one's actual question and he's asking
like it could feel relieving it sometimes and anxiety
inducing at other times I
would assume that the anxiety part I mean
like getting a project done is just like pure
good feelings for me but the render
itself I remember when I was rendering
my my big funnel fancy lecture recently
that was like over a 24-hour render
so like that was very anxiety
inducing because I was afraid of knocking
my fucking connections and killing it
so I had to start all over in that sense
sure it could be anxiety
inducing I think it
can be anxiety inducing
when
you're not able to like
you're not at your fullest
of brainpower and so you have looked over
it to make sure that all the things are right but maybe
but you can't convince yourself
you can't convince yourself that it's actually
correct but you you can't waste
all day looking at it so you have to
press render but you just you're just not sure
good point it hasn't happened a whole lot
cause I'm not a mainly video guy
I have press rendered it's always the same
I'll press render I like
jump up like a fucking gunshot went off
I like run down the stairs I'll get some food
and I'll like I'll like stumble outside
just take a long walk while the video
renders because I've done my dues I'm not a video
person I don't care about editing just
like I've done it I've done my dues
I believe bye and then I fucking run out the door
yeah one thing
I do like doing after I hit render
hope we just power didn't go off or something
why
I wanted to say something that was related to him
because well when you
go ahead you're first ever
one thing I do like doing when I
hit render is usually
I have like multiple projects stacked on
top of each other and going on
like in my brain at the same time
so as soon as I've hit render on one
thing I'm like okay I can't really use my
computer but I really enjoy
like figuring out
how I can make progress on the next
project immediately
right if I'm still awake if I'm tired
then I go to bed if I'm hungry I get food
but I always want to like immediately work
on the next thing while the thing is
rendering because it's like a big old
like time
it's it's like it's like a ticking clock
you can get stuff done in this time frame
that's exactly how I feel that that's why
for example I really love working out
because working out gives me just an
hour and a half generally
three days a week that I can't do anything
but like just
think and I'll generally put on
podcast to listen to or something you know
what Nate I just realized I have that
exact same like time and I really
appreciate that but for me it's taking
a shit I take extra
ordinarily long you're gonna you're gonna get
the hemorrhoids if you shit too long dude
I think it has to do with you being
you start he stands up
I talked to my doctor
alright and my doctor said if you take
a long time to shit that that I was like
wait wait wait you mean just like if
I'm on the toilet for longer taken
a shit that's going to like increase
my chance of hemorrhoids just like literally
exactly yes that's what it is
yeah if you're straining on the toilet
yeah I just say it it's the incentive
to get off the toilet fast
I think it happens a lot more if you're
in your late teens I don't know about you guys
but I used to take super long shits when
I was in my late teens I would sit in
there for like 45 minutes and then like
eventually I just I think
just because I started eating more I don't
know better or my body stopped letting me
eat as bad as I was like
yeah I shit more
if people want I used
to do that because I would like get home from work
and I have my own bathroom and I'm just
I didn't even realize it because I was trying to
immediately get back to working on videos when I
get back from cleaning windows but you know
just my body requires break time so it
snuck that in under my nose and
if someone ever asks just how much time
did you spend sitting on the toilet after
shitting I could just
tell them I got to level 207
on candy crush with no power ups
indeed so hold on
the thing about rendering and nervousness
I did the only nervousness
I really have had in my youtube career
when it comes to finishing videos
it's just that I've it's just for the
when I started working for digi and then I have to be
sending them off to someone else who could sit
it back to be after like a day
that's the thing that was like the most
difficult is that like you're done with a video
but now you have to like wait for a
random time for someone else to
then see it and then approve or deny it
or like you might have to change something
and then like I could have completely moved on
to a different project by then right
but very recently I
finally attained enough confidence that I
know exactly what digi once that
like I don't have to worry about like
something blind sighting me 95% of the time
so that's nice
well guys if we're all done I want to
read this one final question
just bear with me for a second it's a little long but I think you'll appreciate it
it's from AJ Shoup and here it is
my friend
yeah what's up AJ
that lowly cryptid
here's the question
my friend orders a big mac
I say why are you ordering a big mac
he says to me he says
I remember my mom used to get these back in college
I'm thinking a burger because of mom
hmm that's bizarre
I ask him how life's been
oh you know same old same old
what a middling response
I can get something better out of him
I ask remember that girl you liked
Hannah he says oh yee yee
she was nice but we didn't like the same kind
of movies he likes criterion stuff
you know Jim Jarmusch and whatever
what a particular man
so I ask him I ask well
what did she like to watch he says
anime oh huh
interesting we sip on our sprites in silence
I look up and ask in a quip whip
of a query
what's your favorite anime
that's it everybody thank you
for being with us on this episode
of the procrastinator's podcast
patreon.com
slash the procrastinators
give us one dollar
let's get into the patreon
was this real
like was this
was this the shit
was this the raw shit
was this the like pull back the current
you see us laid bare
was this the shit that you want
yeah that's what I
can only hope I hope
that I don't disagree
I like this episode
it was good it was actually like
substantive the whole time
yeah you ain't wrong are we still recording
of course we are of course we're still recording
oh I'm the host
wait hang on I gotta plug things
patreon.com slash the procrastinators
give us one dollar join the chat
five dollars to get every god damn bonus episode
there's like 14 Jesus
wild cards it was a hoot and a half
we got some shirts red bubble buyem
and stuff and at TP
procrastinators follow us on twitter for various
links and things and we'll get back to you
about purchasing radcon backer videos
so have fun
bye
you