I'm going to bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
That son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch.
Alright.
So you want to hear some weird, funny stuff that will make you go,
Wow!
I'm recording, I'm just starting to get some...
Okay, alright, hello everybody.
Sorry, okay.
Alright, we'll start off with some goss.
Do you hear what happened with...
Remember May, aka Digibro?
Oh, no.
You're not ready for this.
I'm probably not ready for it, but sure, go ahead.
It's about as bad.
It's as bad as you can get without incarceration.
Okay.
Without, like, people are in jail over this.
I mean, the word on that is that
Ethan has been tweeting that May,
aka Amanda Lynn Morris,
has only about one week after they got married at Ralphamania.
This is true.
Every word is true.
You know, there was a whole situation where her dad
didn't want them to get married, didn't like Ralph,
and, like, stole the championship belt
that was going to be the prize.
You don't know any of this?
Of course not.
Why would I keep tabs on something so stupid?
I thought I might have mentioned.
I thought I might have mentioned it on the show.
First of all, I hadn't heard that she got married.
You hadn't heard about Ralphamania.
No.
Okay, start with that briefly, because that sounds funny.
Is that, like, a wrestling match and a wedding combined?
Is that what I think it sounds like?
I think so. I think so.
Honestly, I don't know exactly what it entails.
You may now pile driver the bride.
I mean, given Ralph's proclivities, yeah, probably.
I mean, I don't know exactly what Ralphamania entails,
but I know that there was...
Well, they had planned to get married a couple months ago,
I think, at a bowling alley.
Like, bowling alley event.
And they were going to get married,
and then Ralph got, like, punched, or he got beat up.
And he's, like... Like he does.
Like he does, and he was, like, bruised enough
that they canceled the wedding, and they were like,
we'll do this later.
What a life.
I know.
So that happened, and then...
I don't exactly know the details,
but some shit went down, and Ethan or Amanda's family
did not like Ralph, and they were, like,
don't marry him, and she was, like,
fuck you, I'm gonna marry him.
And Ralph was, like, fuck you,
your daughters are gonna marry me.
And Amanda's dad...
I don't think... Okay, I think they left some stuff
in Amanda's dad's house,
and Amanda's dad, like, got rid of it,
or did something with it, and this included
the championship belt that was to be awarded
at Ralph Amania.
And so Amanda's dad stole this belt,
and this was a big point of contention.
He's the champion now.
He's the champion, bitch!
That's what he's gonna do about it.
So that's the backstory.
But they did get married, literally, like, a week ago.
And now, as of yesterday,
Ethan is tweeting,
they were in New York or something,
and Amanda has taken their kid
and fled, and has disappeared,
has kidnapped their child,
and has disappeared into New York City, or something.
Yeah, and is missing.
What?
I don't know.
What information is there on this?
Is it just the tweets?
Just what Ethan said is, like,
she's taken our kid, she's gone,
I have no wife, only a whore.
Stuff like that.
Insults to her family.
Suggestions that he fucked her sister,
which I would say is probably not true.
He's probably just saying stuff,
because he does that.
Yeah.
So they got married.
Amanda and Mae was all about it.
And then ran away.
Did she need the marriage for something?
What?
You think it was a preenup,
a marriage scheme?
Like, haha, now we're going to get divorced and take him?
I don't think she's smart enough for that.
That's why I'm confused.
What on earth could be the reason?
How could you go so far with Ethan Ralph,
and then run away?
You would run away immediately.
I mean,
I was thinking it's like,
the fact that this is immediately after they get married
makes it so much more of a hassle.
Like, now you have to get, if you leave,
now you have to go through the whole legal process
of getting the marriage in old.
Divorced, as they call it these days.
And I feel like that's bad,
but I don't know, maybe,
maybe she did it to get a freaking child support.
Maybe the whole thing was just a big child support scheme.
Or maybe at some point it became,
you know what?
Maybe I'm giving her too much credit,
but maybe she thought
that if she went through with the marriage,
she could get a better,
whatever you call it, alimony settlement,
if they divorce,
because they have their kid.
Which would honestly be pretty smart.
Sort of.
How do we know if she ran away?
What if she was kidnapped?
What if this is like a movie?
Ethan said they had an argument or something.
Okay.
That makes it sound like,
like,
all right, now I'm thinking
Ethan was waiting for the marriage.
And then
that's where he truly spews his bile.
Showed his true colors.
He showed his true colors.
Like, now that you're married to me,
perhaps, perhaps.
But then he's like so
bare-facedly awful.
Yeah, right.
I don't even know what they could argue about.
Maybe Ethan Ralph was going
two left wing.
It's like,
he like sees on like a magazine cover.
He sees like
Alexander Ocasio-Cortez
and he's just like,
hmm, were you looking at her again?
Keep your eyes off her
buster.
Ugh.
Oh.
Well, that's pretty funny.
It is pretty funny.
That's the
honestly first smart thing
Amanda's done
possibly ever.
Yeah, I guess.
Aside from leaving Trixie,
but I mean that kind of goes hand in hand
with getting with Ethan Ralph.
Not sure if I would say it was a net
positive. Probably not, honestly.
But
alimony though.
That's sweet alimony.
Maybe.
It's just so, like, outrageous.
It is outrageous. I know. I saw this.
It was Michelle.
Michelle DM'd me to be like,
look at these screenshots.
It's like, oh my god.
Well,
I guess I'm glad for the update.
Michelle's my man on the inside.
Whenever there's hot goss,
Michelle is like, yo, check it out.
Oh, fuck.
Ah, shit.
I guess that's all I could say about that.
I'm only seven minutes in.
Welcome everyone to the pro-crastinators podcast.
Pro-crastinators podcast.
That was the intro.
Okay.
I have a couple things to say.
One,
the
the project that we
discussed last week,
you know, other than
the cover art mockups that I
showed you, I did a little
speculative
cover design. Other than that, I have
not done anything on it.
That's okay.
I have reasons, but my reasons for that
partially include
that I spent a considerable amount of this
week trying to get the RSSS feed
updated.
It was a bitch.
Man, yeah, did you see what I
said?
I don't really understand
what it requires
or what's broken, but it sounded
like it was hell and
way more complicated than it needed to be.
It was hard for me the
first time, like when Tom explained how
it worked, it was tough for me to get to grips
with it just because there's a lot of steps involved.
I had to log into a bunch of websites
I'd never logged into before,
and I had to, you know,
do all this stuff.
But I figured it out, and that was a couple months ago.
And then
I try to get in there today, and I do
and I'm doing exactly the same thing, and it's not working
and I'm like, what's wrong, what's wrong?
So I spent like two days trying to
figure it out and talking to customer service
and what eventually comes out
the second time I talk to customer service
is it seems like there are new data limits
that were not there before.
So I have imposed a new restriction
of only, the website can only store
the hosting will only host 50
gigabytes of data.
And we're already up to 66 gigabytes
which means, and that's why
it wasn't letting me upload anymore stuff.
How, what's
making up those gigabytes? Is it like
just the MP3s?
Yeah, it's the MP3, it's the 345,
well 315 MP3s
of the podcast. Yeah, okay, that's a lot of MP3s.
Yeah.
So, and this is really bad because
I mean, one, it means I can't
I mean, I can't add anymore, I can't add
any more data
with this host.
There's no more room.
Is it not like an upgrade
to a bigger plan thing?
I didn't,
there probably is.
Honestly, I clicked around their website
and I couldn't really find
like a clear statement
of like, what are the plans?
Like what would it cost to upgrade?
I'm kind of just pissed
because like
there was room before
like we didn't change what we were doing
but they've changed what they're giving us
for the money we were paying them.
That pisses me off.
But yeah,
I couldn't really figure out exactly
how much it would cost
to increase our storage size.
Theoretically, maybe
there's a way that we could just pay them more
and get more storage.
Or we could
switching hosts with Theoretically also
work.
Although we'd have to go and update all the
previous links
if the stuff was hosted on the new server.
And yeah,
just
very discouraging.
Very discouraging.
What good is the website?
Because we had it
specifically to make the
thing link to iTunes or whatever.
Yeah, the website
posting on the website
and again,
I don't really understand how RSS works.
I just know that when I make the post on the website
it auto posts to
Spotify, iTunes,
whatever.
So it does that
which is
good.
But also
I don't know if like anybody
I don't know if anybody even uses those
apps. I mean, not that regularly.
And uh...
There's always a couple people.
There's a couple people. There is a couple.
I know. Yeah.
I think it's literally just because
if you're on your phone
you need to pay for YouTube
red
or like it's a hassle
to listen on YouTube. Yeah, it's easier
to listen on your phone
in mp3 format or whatever.
That's fine.
I guess I get it.
But you know, most people
don't do it that way.
And
other than that the website,
I mean, it's a convenient
archive like you said
and
I guess the plan was we were going to be releasing
the perfect
comic party through the website
which makes
sense.
Um...
I mean this storage limit is a
pretty fucking like we can't do that
until that's resolved.
So...
Yeah, I guess I like having the
website. It's just like
a lot of trouble associated
with it and now there's a bit of
new hurdle
that is
a new challenge
for us to rise to
and overcome.
I think we will have to either upgrade
our choices are we upgrade
or we get a new host and figure out
how to make the website work with the new host
or we just can't, we delete the website.
Yeah.
Those are the three paths forward.
Well, what was the thing
like the thing
that was like
make podcasts
easy. You just put a thing and it does everything.
What was that?
Somebody said that, Chip said that.
Chip said something called, was it called
Autumn?
It was called like Autumn.fm,
Anchor.fm
The best hassle free option for
podcast hosting. You just upload the audio
file in one place and it gets published to all the
apps. Yeah, I mean
I vaguely heard of that before.
I guess if we delete the website
then we could try that
see if it's easier.
That's what the RSS feed
does for us now.
So
I guess RSS feed
is like the
tech person
the tech
what's the word legitimate
tech literate person's
version of Anchor.
If you know what you're doing
you can avoid using
a software that's owned by somebody.
I mean I guess
if we got rid of the website
that would allow us
to continue
updating all the apps simultaneously
which could be useful.
Honestly
now that I've cooled down a little bit
if it's
not
particularly expensive
upgrading our
fucking stupid Bluehost subscription
is probably the easiest and most pain
free way to do it
depending on how much
but again I clicked around and tried to
look for
plans and like the website was very cagey
about it and I couldn't just find a clear
like
10 more dollars a month and we'll upgrade
you from 50 to 500
gigabytes or something like that
websites
websites so anyway
that's I didn't do a lot of stuff this week
I didn't stream I didn't stream again
I dropped the ball I meant
to start streaming battle network
and then I didn't do anymore that
this week because I was
what the fuck I feel like a lot
happened this week and yet I didn't get anything
done that's what it feels like
yeah same
probably for
completely different reasons
maybe I had stuff going on on Friday
yesterday
band practice
you know the band you know that band
the dad's band I was in the dad
I was gonna say is the dad the dad's band
the dad band they're gonna do another charity
thing at some point
everybody liked the last one all their
friends all the people who went it's like oh when
you gonna do more
good I'm like okay I can
I can be the second guitar
again whenever they would be
would be at the same venue
it might be that was a good venue
hmm
uh
yeah probably
yeah what things are being talked about
about like watch
like how to set it all up and
we're still just
playing that they're playing songs they
because they've been playing together for like
I don't know 20 years
um 15 years
probably so they've done
a lot of songs they know a lot of songs
and they can be like oh what about man on the moon
oh yeah if you believe
they put a man on the moon and they just play
it I'm like oh okay and I look
it up on my phone I do the causes play along
but when we get an actual set list together
I can practice properly
sick sick so that's
gonna be fun
mm-hmm
um yeah
so these are just plans you haven't
really started practicing
putting this out list together okay now
with this um jumping jack flash
and Saturday nights all right for fighting
we're probably gonna do you know those
I
I can't place
the tune of either of those
uh
uh jumping jack flash rolling stones
it goes jumping jack
flash he's a flash
flash I don't know the lyrics
he's a flash
I mean it's hard to
like I don't know if I know that one
the riff cause it's very simple
Saturday nights all right for fighting is Elton John
he said Saturday nights
all right for fighting
get a little action here
okay okay I'm sure I've heard that one before
better better better
mmm
mm-hmm
good old boomer classics
um
you should play uh
how can you can you add
uh
battle against a true hero
uh what's that
uh from on the tail
oh yeah
um I don't know
wait wait is it
is it the
oh god I can't now I can't think of a tune
um is it
is it
is that
that's that's asgore
fuck
now I'm blanking battle against a true hero is my favorite underkill
it's the undying grim dark version
what's the
the genocide root
um
I feel so dumb
now I'm like disturbed that I can't
think of it but it's but you whatever
one. I also am blanking on it. I think you had it for half a second, but then you switched
the Asgore thing and now it's blanked my memory. No! You had it. You did have it. Battle against
a true... Wait, wait. I know it starts with a little piano. Kind of like Asgore. It starts
with a little piano progression. Yeah, that's it. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, thank you.
Okay, well, that's... Okay, here's my proposed set list. Battle against a true hero. Asgore.
What do we think? What do we think? They like to, because they got a singer, they like to sing songs
that you have lyrics to. Sorry, buddy. Okay, we can work around that. They're going to do
comfortably now. We practiced that last night. It sounded amazing. Sick. I know that one. I do
know that one. Yes. Yes. I have not played any more Disco Elysium this week. I'm still on
day three, cringe. Did I play anything since last week? I think I played a little bit, but I didn't do
all that much. I think I went around. I talked to the big fat man in the container again. He gave me
a new task. Oh yeah, I went into the little doors, like break into this door and send him a message. I
didn't do that. I broke into the door. I used the key. I got from Mannyana and then I looked inside. I was
like, oh, it's a little place. I guess I want to spoil. Everard gave me the key. Even though I'm a
communist, I didn't do it because I didn't like embossing me around. I have not done it yet, but I'm
leaning towards I probably will do it. Not because Everard told me to, but because everyone else in the
Union seems good and they all like Everard and work for him. For their sake, I'll probably do it.
I think I talked to Mannyana and he's like, yeah, of course Everard's corrupt, but who wouldn't be? We put up
with a little bit of that, oh, he's got a fancy chair just because he does care about the Union and
getting the people what they need. It's hard to imagine because he's so ugly and so annoying voice
and he's busting me around, but maybe it's true.
Honestly, I admire a little bit that he's just unapologetically corrupt. He's just like, yeah, I'm a
fucking smug. Yeah, I'm an oily businessman. You know, what of it? Okay, all right, that's fair.
Doesn't it say in his dialogue somewhere that he's so oily that you can't even tell, even when he's
telling the truth, it sounds like a lie. Yeah, that's awesome. Yeah, somewhere. Rules. So, I mean, I don't
like embossed me around, but Mannyana says he's good and frickin' the little Irish man says he's good
and all the Union people seem to are with him. So like, okay, whatever. But I mean, but Measurehead
works for him and Measurehead is a real scumbag. So that's bad.
Oh, right. Measurement man.
Measurement, measurement man.
I realize who that is now because I never went to, like, they talked about this guy who's like blocking
the way and I'm like, okay, well, I'm going to bother because like, it's probably going to beat me up.
I didn't go talk to him. I didn't interact with him at all. I found the other way. I already found the other
way round. Yeah, I went back that way and I talked to everyone that way. And I had no reason, I think just to go talk
to that guy. So I just haven't yet. I am by now I realize that's who that is. I should talk to him. I can get some
XP's and get some XP's for my human brain.
I would recommend it. I think I had a very unlikely, I had a very unlikely success against him on some skill
checks that let me get through him. I think I was not really supposed to get by him with my build, but he's got lucky.
Which, you know, whatever, I'll take it.
He's pretty funny. Have you met the crypto zoologist?
Oh, I haven't. I've met his wife in the wheelchair. She says, oh, I need to find him. I don't know where he is.
And I was like, okay, I'll do that side quest. Side quest accepted.
What about the race? Have you met the racist Laurie driver? I'm sure you've met the racist Laurie driver.
Well, the guy standing in the middle of the street.
Yeah, yeah, I talked to him. I think I mentioned that last time.
Yeah, probably.
The new guy I talked to, I guess I talked, I went into the apartment complex. There was the lady sweeping.
Yeah, lady sweeping and the artist girl.
The artist girl and the guy overlooking the crime scene, who I finally realized I could go back around that way.
The boy with the open shirt and the cigarette.
Yeah, I didn't realize the area where the girl was was somewhere I could go.
Yeah, did you just talk to her from down below previously?
Yeah, but even when I talk now that I've ruined my relationship with Kuno, I talk to her from the back and she doesn't even turn around. She ignores me.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, wait, you mean the forest girl?
Oh, the forest girl, yeah.
Not the artist girl.
No, no, no. I did talk to the artist girl from below. I haven't talked to her again. But the guy with the cigarette, I couldn't get him to say anything, so I had to go and talk to the old lady, get his room number.
Yeah.
And then I have to come back at a specific time the next day and I'm like, shit, I'm going to forget. I'm going to be walking around being like, oh, shit, it's time and I'm not there.
I was, I remember, I think, what did he say, like come back at like 21 hours or something? And I was like, I remember I went to go see Everard and like I was in Everard's office and I was keeping my eye on the clock the whole time.
Because I'm like, I got to meet that guy on the balcony in like 15 minutes.
Are we going to wrap, are we done here? Are we done here, Mr. Clare? Yeah.
Okay, but you haven't gone to meet him yet.
No.
Okay.
Yeah, well, how long nothing in particular going on?
I'm just sort of, there's a lots of things that I'm failing at and I'm like, okay, well, couldn't, I couldn't, oh, I did the worst thing when I talked to the Hardy boys again after Everard said, tell the Hardy boys to cooperate with me, I go back to them.
I do some dialogue but I can't really do anything. But there's this one, try to intimidate them, try to show them who's boss and it failed and then I couldn't help but put my gun in my mouth.
Are you fucking serious?
I was like, I asked Kim for the gun because that was the only option I had. It's like, oh fuck, I fucked up, this is the path I shouldn't have gone down.
You asked Hardy for his gun.
I asked Kim for his gun because I didn't have one. It's like Kim, that's the only way and I couldn't back out of it. I was on the path.
That's really fucked up.
So Kim was like, okay. And then I had his gun and I could only, because I had failed it earlier, the only thing I could do was think about what I was doing and how stupid it was.
And then once those were done, the only thing was I could put the gun in my mouth and say, if you don't respect me, I'll kill myself.
I'll fucking do it.
And there was an option to put the finger on the trigger to increase the tension. I don't know whether that would have made it more likely it would have worked or whether I would have just died so I didn't do that.
I backed out. I was like, no, this is bad. So all I did was lose morale and the respect of everyone there, including Kim, who thinks I'm insane.
Oh no, that sucks.
It's so embarrassing.
Things went pretty well with the Hardy boys for me. Although, okay, you know, I had-
It was a 58% chance to succeed, so I thought it was fine, but no. No. I did the worst possible thing, the most embarrassing. I'm such a fuck up with everyone.
Yeah, you're a real sorry cop. You're a real sorry cop, I gotta say.
I haven't been saved scumming though. I was told not to do that and I was like, this is fun, even though I'm so embarrassing, the game doesn't end, so it's fine.
I think it's okay to let yourself fuck up a little bit.
I had a couple deaths and so this was on, I guess you could call it an alternate timeline, because this got reversed with one of my deaths.
But before I met the Hardy boys, on the first day, when I met, well, you know, I forget her name, but the lawyer girl who was pretending to be the gardener,
When I talked to her the first time, I had, I think I had like a critical failure of like a role, and my whatever personality trait of me was like,
you literally cannot think of anything other than the fact that her skin is a different color than yours.
Oh yeah, I got the same thing.
And I said, it's like, you're black. What?
Yeah, she brought that up later.
Fortunately, that got reversed with one of my losses, so I actually have to deal with that.
Yeah, well, I did that, because it was the only option, because I failed it, and it's just like, okay, and I'm like, yeah.
What kind of music do you listen to?
I'm just observing here, like there was no option that was good.
What kind of music do you listen to? Whatever's on the radio? Okay, bye.
And so when she was revealed to be a lawyer, she saw me and it's like, ah, it's the guy who like, I forget exactly how she put it.
It was like, oh, it's the cop who knows I'm black. Hello.
Like she just brings it up again. God damn it.
True. Very, very observant. Do you know your name yet?
I do. Do you know it?
Yeah.
It's Harry Dubois.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You have not found the cryptozoologist, so you have probably not been down to like the fishing village or the church, right?
Yes, I haven't really, like I feel like I've walked around there, but just haven't found.
I saw the statue, the big exploded statue, and it's like, that's cool.
But I didn't think you could go further south.
There's a, yeah, I was pretty surprised.
There's quite a lot of territory to cover down there that I kind of didn't even realize at first.
Yeah, when I went to the bookstore, there was like the maps on the wall and I bought the postcard and I looked at it and I was like, oh, there's a whole other like southern area.
Yeah, there is a whole other area.
I think it's like across the bay or something like that.
Yeah, it's like the bit where the restaurant is, it's like the end point of the harbor kind of.
Yeah.
Well, I guess where the harbor is, is where the harbor is.
You gotta cross over, I think it's called a waterlock.
It's sort of like a drawbridge, and that's how you get to sort of a whole kind of second section beside from like the city area.
There's going to be so many bottles I can pick up and put in my bag.
Hell yeah.
I kind of like ran through that area like almost without talking to anyone.
So like that, I've like walked all around there down there, but I have not really explored it.
I haven't like done most of the stuff to do down there.
I'm kind of, I gotta do that.
I gotta do that and I gotta, I gotta go back into.
Okay, you, did you do the like bookstore, like did you go into like the back rooms?
Yes, I explored all that.
You find the dice?
The dice lady, yes.
Okay, I think we talked about this.
I missed that and I have to go back and do that.
Yeah.
Did you do the thing, the like the intercom thing and you found like the spooky lady who kept repeating herself?
No, I did not find the spooky lady.
Yeah, I think it's discovered.
I thought of it, but like my character didn't think of it for a while, that it's like a recording of somebody on the phone.
She keeps repeating a bunch of stuff when you press the button and it's like from a company that no longer exists, which has been renamed and it's like the wrong number and stuff.
I don't know where that is physically in the building, so I don't know if I could find that.
Yeah, I haven't done that yet and I, you have not been down south to the church.
I know that the kids, well, you don't know, but there's some kids down there and they mentioned that there was a lady, a mysterious lady in the church.
And just because there's like a mysterious lady in the back of the bookstore and a mysterious lady in the church, I thought, are these the same mysterious lady?
Are these perhaps both of the same mysterious lady who was there at the crime scene with the Hardy Boys, who's left the lights at the footprints?
Hmm, but probably not actually, it probably just started multiple mysterious ladies.
I got the sense that the mysterious lady on the phone, she was responding to somebody, which could be a clue, but it seemed like it was a very old recording.
Because it was for a company that didn't exist anymore, but I guess, I don't know when the company stopped existing.
I think I talked to the dice girl about that. She has info about all of the failed enterprises. You can ask about all of them.
I must have missed a big path back there, because I didn't find any of that.
Did you bring the torch?
Yeah, I did. Maybe I just was in a hurry to do something else and I was like, I'll come back later.
Yeah.
I found the gun back there.
What?
I haven't found the gun yet.
Oh, not like a gun gun. There's like an old gun.
Oh, yeah, no, I found the stashed in the walls.
Yeah.
Like the rifle. Yeah, I picked that up.
Yeah, I found that and I found the polar bear freezer and, oh wait, I think I found a second freaking, did I find like a second computer cube?
Oh, I didn't find a second one of those.
I feel like I found...
Hang on, I need to go pee, sorry.
Or maybe I just found the first one.
Wait, you need, what?
I need to go pee, sorry.
Okay.
Hello?
Hello, I'm the Nostalgia Critic.
So where were we? Disco Elysium.
Yeah, although I haven't been playing it, so I don't have much new to report on my end.
Yeah, good game though.
Pretty good game.
I was listening to some Grimbeard reviews and I re-listened to his video about planescape torment and he pretty much...
He pretty much says directly that he considers Disco Elysium to be like the truest and most successful successor to planescape torment.
Seems like a pretty nice thing to say about a video game.
I've heard of planescape torment a lot, but I've never gone to play it.
I started it once and I didn't get very far before I found something that frustrated me and I put it down and I didn't pick it up again.
Although, it's kind of...
I mean, you can die in that game as many times as you want and it's fine.
The thing that frustrated me was there was like an item that I found that I used and that I felt like I should not have used.
And I was like, should I reset my save so I get the item back?
Yeah, and I was like, I'll worry about it later.
Oh, I had such a great idea for a meme for Disco Elysium.
I might still make this, but it's just a little involved.
There's a Snoopy comic.
This depends on whether I can find the Snoopy comic.
There's a Snoopy comic where Snoopy is talking about how he hid his foot or something.
And his head blames his eyes for getting hurt and the leg blames his brain.
He's talking about different aspects of his body that are arguing with each other.
And then at the end, he's like, I didn't say anything because I didn't want to get involved.
And I was like, what if you could replace those words with rhetoric and drama and a physical instrument?
Because it's just like how the little Disco Elysium facets of your brain can sometimes disagree.
What a funny meme, guys.
I mean, yeah, good meme.
Just make him Snoopy.
When I'm down, just make him Snoopy.
Give him the old make him Snoopy.
Do you do that now where you're having thoughts and you're like, oh, this is the rhetoric part of my brain.
This is the, what are the names of them?
Inland Empire.
This is the conceptualization.
No.
This is the empathy part coming through.
Like if I was in a discord call, I could talk to different aspects of myself.
That part never comes through.
No, not really.
Dang, maybe I'm fucked up.
Maybe I'm all free.
I mean, just like in real life, you know, in the game, I'm maxed out on encyclopedia,
which is the only part I ever hear from.
It is funny how you see something and encyclopedia will give you a lengthy explanation of what it is,
even though it's very simple what that is.
Sometimes.
Sometimes, yeah.
And it's just sort of like, I wonder if people's brains work like that where they see something and they can't help but think,
oh, yes, that is what this is.
I guess it's not like that.
Yeah, definitely.
But like not in a spoken word, like sentence structure sort of way.
They just sort of know what something is.
Yeah, like in real time, that encyclopedia popping up to give you a text dump would take like a nanosecond.
Yeah.
The brain's funny.
I think it's serious.
Serious business.
Don't you forget it.
Okay.
My favorite one is electrochemistry because it wants me to take drugs.
That is a pretty funny one.
I'm like, it's odd because like in real life, taking drugs is bad.
You never take drugs.
Exactly.
But in a video game.
Nobody would actually take drugs in real life.
In a video game, you're not actually getting the high of a drug.
You're thinking about the benefits to your character in game.
And a lot of the time, I mean, maybe there are literal benefits like stats and stuff.
I feel like a lot of the game is telling you that being extremely high and extremely drunk just makes you like an idiot and you do stupid things and you forget what you did.
Because that's what your character has done.
They're super alcoholics.
Like why would you indulge in that knowing how shitty everything is?
Okay.
I kind of want to do like a drug play through at some point.
I saw someone on Twitter talking about it and they said that their experience was that like they started the game thinking they shouldn't do drugs.
Because they were like, there's got to be some hidden negative to do in drugs.
And then they took drugs and they were like, oh wow, actually taking drugs is like a huge mechanical benefit and your stats like benefit immensely from taking drugs.
And then it turned out at the end, no, there actually was a hidden cost to it.
Like, oh no.
Yeah.
That's how it feels.
I don't know what that is exactly, but that's just what they said there.
Well, it's at the end.
It's like at the end of Undertale, but with the genocide route.
Like you're doing that.
You did the genocide route once and then you look at the photos of all the Disco Elysium characters and then, oh, there's Kyra there.
You fucked up.
It's the drug version of Kyra.
Maybe.
With the red eyes.
I mean, it reminds me of Lisa a little bit.
Like.
Simpson?
No, the game.
Yeah.
There's no, like, you don't get like the bad ending from using joy in Lisa, right?
I can't, I never use joy because of how obviously bad it was and it turned people into beasts.
And I didn't really want to risk having a moment where it's like you've taken too much joy over the course of your adventure.
You just turn into a blob and that's it.
Yeah.
Well, that doesn't happen.
Yeah, I don't know that it happens.
I don't think so.
It would be cool if it did.
If you take like a little bit too much, like maybe there'll be a tell in the game.
It's like you feel like this is a little too much, you know, a little moment of reflection to let you know that if you take one more, you'll turn into a blob.
I think, I don't think it really, I don't think there really is like a big like story change to the game, whether you use joy or not.
There's like one, there's like one party member you can't get if you use joy, but like, who cares?
Yeah, that's kind of annoying, I feel like.
That there's not more of a consequence?
Yeah, because it's like, I mean.
Honestly, I kind of think it's fine because like narratively.
Yeah, I mean, what that what that tells me about the world and about the character is that like it was already too late.
I suppose.
But you only know that once you've played the game and you know how it ends.
And it's like, oh, so now I can play it because I know that there's not like a potential happy ending.
Where you can live long and prosper and all that.
If you're gonna go out like you do.
You may as well drug yourself up the whole way through because you know how it ends because it's.
Yeah, it's like it's like in a in a video game, like an RPG or it's like you don't actually know how many health potions you'll need.
So you keep hold of so many of them.
And by the time you finish the game, you're like, oh, I have 700 of these.
I should have used them.
Yeah, the whole time.
Yeah, but you're right.
I mean, I think that's probably why in the painful.
It's like, it's they make it as clear as they can that like, no, you're supposed to use the joy.
You pretty much have to use the joy.
No, I resisted.
I thought it would be so good.
Did you did you actually get through it without using it?
Yeah, it's so fucking hard.
Like you can't fucking beat Lobo.
You can.
It's just that you need to do a lot of healing and make sure that every attack is as powerful as you possibly can.
It's it's you're definitely supposed to use it.
The game is balanced on the assumption that you will use it.
And yet and yet and the game tells you the game literally just writes like graffiti on the wall.
It's like use joy like use it.
But I know sinister.
It feels like you're not supposed to listen.
That's what I thought.
Yeah, I thought that they're like that.
Oh, no, you're not going to fuck me up.
I know.
I know what joy does.
You're not.
It's like it's I thought it I felt like it was saying like, um, you know, these are the voices.
This game's this game's super hard.
This game's like super fucking hard, bro.
And you're a little pansy pussy.
So you better use joy and I'm like, fuck you.
No, I'm not.
I'm the coolest.
I'm going to be the hardest motherfucker ever.
I'm going to slice everyone and I did.
God damn.
Yeah, I would recommend trying it because it's not.
As impossible as it seems.
It's not luck based.
You can.
You can do it.
Well, if I mean.
Yeah.
Impressive.
But there's no like reward for it.
No.
Yeah.
Just the reward of being able to say, haha, I did that in regular conversation and people go, what?
Yeah, I can't say that.
I beat I beat Super Mario Brothers and I've did Lisa the joyful without using joy.
Super Mario Brothers.
It's hard.
I mean, to be fair, I've never beaten Super Mario Brothers.
Like all the way.
I don't think so.
Yeah.
Hmm.
Can I really even call myself a gamer?
If I didn't beat the first game ever made.
No, you can't be the first game ever made.
I am the first game ever made.
And why is he speak like that?
Because that's how you said it about Rayman.
Oh, video.
The hardest game ever made.
I do so many likes like pointless silly voices in those videos.
Yeah.
I think it's literally just because I was reading the script and I realized I sounded like a
YouTuber.
Like, I gotta sound weird.
You gotta sound weird because I don't like.
I should just say this next line weird so it doesn't get boring.
Yeah.
It's it's it's literally just I think I sound like a real loser real tool when I'm just
doing my script reading voice.
Sure.
I'm casually talking about stuff.
I sound okay.
But like Rayman was it like I don't know how to like read a script in a non lame way.
No, I think if I was like, I mean, if you if you're someone like, if it's like a long
video, then I think you pretty much just have to accept I'm just going to sound boring to
myself because I'm going to be reading the script for like an hour.
If it's not, though, I totally am like, I get I get it.
Like, I've been talking for five minutes now and like, is the audience really want me to
like, sit here and talk for five minutes?
Like, it's boring.
It gets boring after five minutes.
I gotta do something.
I gotta put a joke or an edit or I gotta zoom in my face so it's a little bit bigger and
then zoom it back out.
Otherwise, they'll go back to playing Fortnite.
Otherwise, they'll go back.
Goodness knows that's worse than my video.
Otherwise, they'll go back to doing what the zoomers do, which I gather is watching like
place together three videos in one like one is like a leftist political speech.
The other is like someone like running in Fortnite and the other is someone like, you
know, doing like slime like squishing slime in their hands.
Yeah, most satisfying compilations.
I've seen I've seen those triple videos and I got to say they really work for me.
I like it.
That's I watched one that was like a family guy clips.
And then there was the train, the guy running on the train tracks and getting the coins
and then there was like somebody using like a knife to like cut some weird soap thing.
Yes, the blue like soap.
Yeah.
I was like, this is good.
Actually, like people are like saying, oh my God, the children are so fucked.
I'm like, no, they're not.
They're just they just like this is good.
This is a good like evolution.
I gotta be honest.
I didn't really get it.
I was just like, why am I why are there three videos in one?
If I wanted to watch one of these videos, why wouldn't I just watch one of them?
Because attention span.
I mean, I know, I know so many people.
It's such a normal thing now to like, when you listen to a podcast or a long video or
even just a video that you've seen before, you play a game at the same time, you have
two different stimulus.
I mean, definitely.
But I don't want them to put them together for me.
I want to I want to customize my experience.
I want to match the like the the podcast I want to listen to with the game I want to
play.
True.
I don't I don't want them to do it for me.
I don't mind it, though, because like this particular game they're showing is like that
guy running down.
It's an endless runner.
Yeah.
The the game that is the inputs that they put are like so simple like duck, jump, turn
to the left, turn to the right, get those coins.
It's not a very interesting game to watch, in my opinion.
But like it wouldn't be an interesting game for me to play either.
It's just sort of like, oh, look at him go while I listen to something.
And then I switch my eyes over to the soap and I go back to the little guy.
I do like the soap.
I do like the cutting soap.
Yeah.
But I would just I would just I would just watch that.
I watched someone cut soap on my own damn time.
How many times have you googled soap cutting?
Rarely.
Since you saw it.
Very rarely.
Oh, since none.
Exactly.
So that you need that curation.
You need them to do it for you.
You ain't going to look at it.
I guess.
I mean, I guess you're right.
All right.
So lesson learned.
I should be googling soap more.
That'll that'll do that'll do a lot for me.
Well, all all that is to say that I didn't do any work aside from a little bit on the
cover of the project.
Yes, the perfect comic party comic party.
I will at some point I will have to actually make that damn content.
Yeah, I've worked a little bit to make some Clarissa had a bit of a little mental moment
or breakdown because, you know, that's that's just how I roll.
Breakdown a moment minute.
Yeah.
But like I feel like I can.
Yeah, I can.
I can do it.
I can.
I can get that chapter ready.
The perfect comic party.
I think we've got a pretty good logo mockup.
I really liked your logo mockup.
Thank you.
I was thinking about like because it's I was looking at shown and jump and they've got
the letters, the blocks text.
You can write it vertical.
You can write it like horizontal, but each letter kanji, whatever fits in a square.
So it's quite easy to make it fit nicely on a rectangular sheet of paper.
Yeah.
But with PCP, you got so much wasted space underneath the P and it's hard to like put
it in a way that it reads nicely.
I think I figured it out.
Do you want to wait?
Did you I'm not looking at the discord.
Do you want to post a shot of it or something?
No, I want to draw a secret.
Okay.
I want to draw it cleaner first.
I have a I want to be nice and shiny and cool and bold and stuff.
And then yeah, once we once we have a little title, we have to have a logo we can use over
and over again.
Yeah, it looked really good.
And I mentioned, I mean, because the frickin PCP, the Radcon dojin is supposed to be done
really soon.
Like literally the only thing left for it is I think Kaiju has to draw the cover and
like that's it.
And I don't know, we could put that in there or something.
We could include that in the first issue if it's done by then.
We could include like parts of it per weekly publication.
And be like, oh, yeah, so one of the dojin because they're right.
It's in chapters because it's like chapter one.
That's one chapter per episode or per per issue.
But yeah, I need to get my head down nose to the grindstone get the Clarissa because
it's like it's 20 something pages.
And I've got like three inked, not even like finished.
I got to do a bunch of inking and then I got to put the speech bubbles in there and then
the shading is like, I want it to be nice.
So I'm not going to rush it out the door just so they can be part of this thing.
That's why I didn't put like a deadline because I don't think I need to warm up to all this
because I've been so like anti doing anything for like a month.
To get get get the momentum going again.
Yeah, sure.
Ganbatte!
Kibucha!
Thank you.
Arigato.
What else?
I guess I got I guess I don't have that much more to say about that.
It's going to be fun.
It is going to be fun.
You know, despite it being like, oh, we talked about it and it's not instantly a real thing.
It was really a, I don't mind that too much.
I think it's still like, it's a fun thing to think about getting done.
It was never going to be done in one week.
No.
Yeah.
I did think I could get more done.
Like I could get the title, the logo finished.
But sometimes a week is fucked.
And then you and then you relapse and your therapist says, you know, you got to just fucking do it.
You idiot.
They don't, they didn't say that.
But like that was that was the essential thing.
Like you're, you're, you're, you're looking inwards and you're making yourself feel worse.
And so you have to, I can't remember exactly what they said.
I can read it later.
But like, it's essentially that they're not offering consulance, condolences or like pats on the back ruffles of the hair.
They're saying, you know that you have to do this stuff.
So you'll feel better if you do it.
So do it.
And it's like, God, I wish you would just say, no, you can wallow in misery forever and it would be great.
But they won't say that.
I'll tell you that.
I say you can wallow in misery forever.
It's fine.
Do I really want to listen to Ben Saint?
I don't know.
That devil's bargain.
Yeah.
So I'll draw.
I'll draw.
And I'm going to do it.
There's also, there's also the question because I had this last year, February drawing like booby images all over February last year.
That was a daily draw thing.
I still want to do that.
I don't want it to be too serious though.
So I'd be a little, just a little doodle every day, something, something to get the blood pumping in my art hand.
Honestly, warming up is good.
Warming up every day is like a good thing to do that like real artists do that I have never done.
And that's probably why I'm a hack fraud and have to come up with stupid schemes like the perfect comic party to motivate me to do that.
It's all baked in.
Warming up is hard because you're drawing and you're like, this isn't a good drawing.
Right.
Because you're fucked in the head and you think every drawing has to be good.
That's not how professionals do it.
They draw billions of drawings.
And then they just, they get the work done.
I mean, I know, I already know that it's more important to put the hours in than it is to make progress during those hours.
Because putting the hours in makes you feel like productive, which helps you like mentally to stay on track.
If you say like, I'm going to take a break today and you don't put those hours in.
Even if those hours are spent just looking at a sheet of blank paper, the fact that you did it means that it's easier to do it later.
And I know that, yet I know that.
And yet I'm just not sticking to my schedule.
I'm going to change that.
This coming Monday, I'm going to change that.
That's a different struggle you're describing than mine.
What's your struggle?
My struggle is not like, oh, I don't want to put the hours in.
I'm afraid my drawings will be bad, et cetera.
I don't know.
My struggle is like, say it, you know, yeah, I could put the hours in.
And maybe the drawing will come out good.
So what?
Yeah, that's the more fundamental like, why do anything thing I was struggling with.
Yeah, I don't know.
Well, you got to do it for the perfect comic party, Ben.
That's exactly right. That's exactly why. That's exactly right.
So there you go.
Nothing is real.
Everything is made of fake little lies we tell ourselves.
And our lie right now is the perfect comic party.
That's good.
We should make that the tagline, perfect comic party.
It's the lie we tell ourselves.
Oh, Ben, if you could translate that to Japanese, we could put that on the side.
Put that on the cover somewhere.
I could machine translate it.
I would probably want to ask an actual speaker how they would really translate.
That's really funny, honestly.
You can make a shirt.
That would be a great shirt.
The PCP logo, perfect comic party, and then the Japanese text underneath.
It's the lie we tell ourselves.
I think we should rebrand everything.
Did I mention this last week?
I think you did, yeah.
We've been needing a rebrand for a while,
and I think this is the perfect opportunity to rebrand the Patreon,
rebrand the YouTube channel, rebrand everything.
In line with the new aesthetic of we do a comic compilation.
Submit your stuff if you want to be included in our ever so often regular comic publication
where we publish our own comics instead of publications.
Hell yeah.
It's the lie we tell ourselves, and it's the procrastinators podcast.
Yes.
You need to think of a way to squish perfect comic party into a square format for avatars and stuff.
The fact that the website has this problem now is really frustrating though,
because the plan was we were going to publish it on the website,
so now I don't know what to do with that.
I'm sure we'll think of something.
Either way, we'd want the website to look nicer than it does currently.
You know, the website does look like shit now that you mentioned it.
Does it still have that default plant pot image?
Yes.
You know, it is crap.
It's not a hip-happening joint that all the cool kids want to go to.
You know what?
You make a good point, fuck WordPress.
Fuck everything.
Do you know how to make a website?
Because I really don't.
Yeah.
I mean, I made mine.
Yeah, and it's nice and slick.
It's a bit hard.
Mine is slick.
Honestly, I mean, if I were to be tasked with making a website,
what I would probably do is just take my code for my website
and take that as my baseline and just, you know,
modify it, swap out assets, and re-theme it, basically.
Yeah.
Because, I mean, my website is very pretty, you know,
format-wise, it's pretty clean and straightforward and uncomplicated,
and it's just about, you know, presenting content front and center.
Yeah.
So, yeah.
I feel like I've heard you say that it's a kind of,
you built it in a kind of way where it's annoying to add new pages
of things to comics.
I did.
Did you, like, improve that at some point?
Some, well, somewhat, yeah, somewhat.
I did make it, I did make it a bit more modular in that,
like, I made it so that, like, more of it refers to, you know,
a cascading style sheet, and therefore,
I don't have to change every individual page.
If I want to make one little change, you know,
I made, like, one, I added an iframe that included a window
into a sort of default template menu,
so I can just change the menu file,
and that changes the menu on every page.
I did improve it somewhat with that, yeah.
I still have to, like, I still have to manually add, like,
new pages, like, when there's a new, you know, page,
when there's a new page of the comic, I have to add a new page of the website
to accommodate it, but I mean, that's okay.
How would we put Perfect Comic Party on a website like that?
Would it be page, one page per page,
or would it be, like, a long scroll?
Honestly, I kind of think that if we did it like that,
we wouldn't, like, even necessarily display it on the website.
It would just kind of be a home page with, like,
a sort of dated index of, like, links to issues,
and you would just download them.
Yeah, that was what I was initially thinking
when it comes to PDF.
Okay.
The website would basically, it would be a little bit of branding,
you know, we got the title, we got some art, whatever,
but it's mostly just a portal to,
here's where you download the individual issues,
and then, you know, here's where you can donate,
here's where you can get rewards, whatever.
Yes.
Yeah.
That would be sick, if we had a nice little website.
It would be sick.
We would need to figure out, and I mean, we could host,
well, I mean, we'd need a new host,
but I mean, we could just re-upload the, um...
The MP3s.
The podcasts, yeah.
We could, you know, it would take a little doing,
but it'd be fine.
Yeah, there's, um,
the last, I think the dick show used to be, like,
only on the website.
Well, I mean, you could listen to other apps.
I always went to the website to listen to it when I did,
and they just had a player.
You just have a page, and then the player, and you press play.
And it's like, that was pretty good.
It meant that going to the website was, like,
a thing you would do to see the new episode,
and then it was like the spiel about what the hell
it was about underneath, like a blog post.
I don't know if we, I don't think we have that
on the current WordPress thing.
We just have like a...
The current WordPress just has the pretty much a very similar,
like, to the YouTube description.
Yeah.
Underneath each post.
How would you listen to it?
Would you have to download the MP3?
You can listen to it in line on the website.
There is, like, just a play button,
or you can download the MP3.
Okay, well, then that's fine.
We could just have that again.
It's doable.
I mean, the way it embeds
is done through WordPress.
Whatever. I'm sure there's a simple way
to just fucking add an MP3 player
into your website.
I don't think that would be complicated.
I guess the only thing is the size of the files.
That's, like, more than 50 gigabytes.
Yeah, no, it's the hosting that is the...
That at this point is the sticking point.
You could host all of the images of your comics
on your website.
Yeah, I mean, I have...
I mean, it's not 50 gigs worth, I don't think.
But yeah, I just have, through a separate...
I think I use...
What's the fucking hosting site that I use for that?
SomethingMoon?
I don't remember.
But yeah, I just have...
I bought the domain,
and I have the domain registered,
like, $10 a month or something
to just host...
Just to host all the data on the site.
And I'm not sure if there's a data limit on it or not.
Maybe we should use that service,
because I've never had a problem with them.
Yeah. I use HostGator for the give-and-take.site.
It's not... I don't think it's, like...
I don't know how much it is a month.
It gets as much as $10.
We just need...
I should go and check and, like, see what are the data limits.
We just need something that can host, you know,
100 gigs, 200 gigs,
and I think we'd be good for the foreseeable future.
Yeah.
I guess I should ask fucking blue...
We could ask Bluehost how much it would cost
to up the data limit.
That's probably the move at this point.
Yeah, to upgrade, yeah.
Is it easy to change how it works?
Because if it's through WordPress,
how would you change the code?
I'll be frank with you.
If we wanted to, like, build a custom website,
I think we would just probably abandon WordPress
because, I don't know,
we would be stuck with all of its default shit.
We would have to build a website from scratch.
Well, I guess we shouldn't worry about that too much right now.
The MP3 thing is more important,
and we can just...
Hosting is the most pressing issue.
Yeah, and then I guess making Perfect Comic Party exist
comes before where we host it.
True.
Like, we could have a Google Docs
and put them on there in the meantime.
I mean, yeah, we can do that.
It's so low-rent.
Low-rent which?
Oh my god, I just...
Did I mention low-rent which is canceled?
I'll never get to see it.
You mentioned it on the stream we did.
Right.
Yeah, somebody asked...
Somebody asked Mint where's low-rent which
and Mint confirmed that it is canceled,
so that's sad.
Tragic.
Terrible.
Terrible, terrible.
I was looking forward to it so much.
She'd drawn thousands and thousands of frames, Gib.
I know, it's a big...
Mathematically, that's true.
A waste of man hours on that.
How dare you misgender those hours?
Oh, yeah, I guess that's a word now.
What would you do?
Would you, like, ma'am hours?
Like, ma'am?
Yeah, ma'am hours is the opposite.
That's my go-to.
It's like a ma'am word.
You just say ma'am instead.
Sounds the same.
That's pretty good.
Oh, man, I saw...
Oh, man.
I saw a list.
Oh, ma'am.
I saw a list of gender neutral...
Suggestions for gender neutral words
are like people in your family.
And they suck so much.
That's like...
I wish...
I mean, maybe I could find them...
I mean, they're sibling and parent.
What else is there?
Sure, sure.
Like, what words would you invent?
Well...
Like a gender neutral aunt, uncle?
Fucking notifications.
Fucking notifications for...
Fuck!
All right, check in my likes.
Check in my likes.
Here we go, here we go.
Oh, God.
Look at this.
Here we go.
Here's the list I was talking about.
ZZ.
ZZ for aunts and uncles.
You're not my aunt.
You're not my uncle.
You're my ZZ.
Hey, hey, my ZZs.
I kind of like...
I like nibbling.
That's cute.
But I guess nibbling's a little cute.
Sprong.
Horrible.
Yeah, sibling.
Sprong.
Ren.
What the fuck is that?
God Ren, okay.
Enby Friend, fine.
Epox?
What are you talking about?
Why are you in my house?
Wait.
Epo...
Cain or call?
Fianc, fianc.
Fianc...
Wait, are those...
Do you have to say them different?
Where are you looking?
Epox.
Fianc and fianc.
Are they different words?
I didn't know they were gendered.
You know, um...
Like one has an extra E.
I think...
Yeah, I guess they are,
but I don't know if you say them differently.
Maybe in French you would.
Is it fianc and fianc?
Is that the difference?
That's the same.
It sounds the same.
No, it's...
It's an emphasis on the wrong syllable.
Fianc and fianc.
Law?
Sure.
Well, it's kind of like...
English.
Fianc, fianc.
You can say, you can say, you know,
my rsum or my rsum,
and both are acceptable.
Resum, rsum.
Yeah, okay.
That's so similar, but sure, I guess.
I mean, surely you...
I mean...
Yeah.
Tiz?
Tiz.
For ma'am or service.
Some of these...
Some of these don't make any sense.
Like, I don't understand...
Yeah.
I don't understand what they're derived from,
and they don't...
Like, why would I say this?
Epos.
Goddex.
Goddex is kind of funny.
Goddex is funny.
Fenninbi.
I mean, okay.
I don't know about...
I don't mind, like, I don't...
I think I would refer to a gender-neutral god
as just a god.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to default male, but...
I mean...
I'm sorry, but the word goddess
is just the word for god
with a female attachment.
So just lose the attachments.
I think...
Yeah, there's a few things like that.
Like, I don't like the term comedian,
because comedian is...
I guess arguably male-centric,
but it's also just what you would call
somebody who does comedy.
Like, if they're neutral,
gender-neutral, I feel like comedian works.
Yeah, why do you need another word?
Comedian works for all genders and no gender,
and like...
You don't need to make a gendered version
for every possible permutation of a person.
That's exactly what the...
Like, chef doesn't have a female equivalent.
If you're a chef, you're a chef.
Well, we gotta make one.
No, we don't.
We gotta make one or else.
That's exactly what the person that retweeted
this list said.
They said,
why can't we just de-gender everything
instead of making everything third-gender?
Yeah.
I think that's probably...
That's probably right, yeah?
I mean, for some things,
like Mr. and Mrs.,
they are deliberately split-gender.
Yeah, we don't have to...
We don't have to remove every gender
under every circumstance.
But for some things,
like King Queen, we have monarch.
We don't need another one.
Yeah.
For God, I think we can just...
I think we can just dispense with the word goddess,
unless you really want it.
And then, it's fine.
I don't think we need...
We don't need God ex,
even though it's really funny.
I guess you would use goddess
when you're, like, looking at a beautiful woman
online and you want to say something to her.
You want to say,
you want to say,
I always find myself in that situation.
And yes, it's true.
It's a very useful word in that.
I mean,
I kind of get it.
It's like...
I guess it's a little uneven that, like,
you could call...
You could call Aphrodite a god.
I mean, she is.
You could also call her a goddess
if you want to be specific about it.
But there's no, like...
I don't... There's no masculine...
I feel like there's no masculine, like...
Oh, this is a god.
What's the...
Oh, shit.
What's the masculine suffix?
There is none.
We can make one of those.
Honestly, we should make one of those.
If we want equality,
let's just take God as the neutral one
and add a masculine suffix.
Goddick.
Godden.
Honestly, looking through these,
they have, like,
a consistency with Ren being a parent
and then grandparent
is a grandren.
Is it because it's a parent?
Oh, my goodness.
Probably.
I don't know if I like it.
Like, Ren!
It seems like you just picked something.
I don't want to go to school.
Ren!
Like, instead of saying mom,
you would say that.
I think it's supposed to be a shortening of parent.
And I mean, I don't know what...
I honestly don't hate Ren
just because they've kept it
with, like, grandparent,
godparent.
I appreciate the consistency.
Like, if you wanted to invent a word
that means neither male
or female guardian parent
and shorten it so that you could say easily,
that's fine, I think.
I think that one's fine.
I don't understand Zeezy.
Zeezy, I don't know where that comes from.
Sprong is, like, Reddit.
You would just say kiddo.
Kiddo is good.
Child.
Offspring.
Offspring is a bit clinical.
Sprong is...
Don't you think it sounds Reddit, though?
Sprong?
Sprong sounds very much like
someone who
oils their mustache
and wears...
and goes to fucking Renfair
LARP's
I guess I could say
that Sprong
is a funny thing.
It's a funny thing.
Sprong is wrong.
It's like a dad joke
or a Ren joke
when, like...
Oh, Spring has Sprong and they have a Sprong.
And the Sprong is like
fuck, shut up, Ren.
Shit.
God.
No, you shut up, Sprong.
Spring has Sprong.
A police report.
A police investigated
reports of domestic violence
between a Ren and their Sprong
today,
down on Main Street.
You know, it's grown on me.
Some of these are grown on me.
Sorry, I can't say
police because it's default mail.
I have to say a police ex.
I have to say police ex
because I don't want to be overly specific.
They have, like, police man, police woman,
so police
got a person, police ex.
Police Ren. Police Ren.
Police Ren.
Police ZZ.
Oh, wait, you say Jean Darme.
Or wait, that might be gendered, actually.
Man, sir, Tiz.
What is that?
What is that? I guess I just don't like the ones
that I don't know where they come from.
First of all,
frankly, too many of these have Z's
and X's in them.
Cringe. They love...
Cringe letter. Cringe letter. Try hard.
They love those letters. Don't like them.
Second of all,
I'm sorry, imagine.
Imagine you fucking go to a fancy
ball
and you go to the frickin'
and you're going in and they're taking your coat
and they're like, mm, and the fucking
butler is like, offers you
an hors d'oeuvre and they say, mm,
caviar, Tiz? Cause they don't know your gender.
I would kill myself.
Tiz? Tiz
Tiz sounds like coze, like it's too
informal.
Like, man, sir, man, sir
doesn't sound like them.
It sounds like it was completely made up out of
whole cloth and the fact that I see no
like, connection to the existing
vocabulary at all
is the most annoying thing about it.
Tiz this your order?
Yes, it is.
I think it's like,
it's Tiz.
It's not,
it's too similar to different words.
Yeah,
I also agree with that as well.
Lord and lady, lardy,
lardy, lardy is
not a good way to say it.
Lard, lard. Honestly, that one I
understand, they're just kind of combining the words.
Like, okay, I get it.
M'lard.
It's basically you're trying to sing both of them at the same time.
I see the logic.
Feel free to spread this, it says,
and I did, so.
Spread it on some toast.
Yo, it's time for my oatmeal
update. I got new flavors
of better stevia
and none of them are as good
as the old ones.
So, that's it
for this week's oatmeal update.
The flavors I was somewhat disappointed by
are lemon
and hazelnut. They're fine.
Did I mention, I put raspberries in it.
I tried raspberries.
In oatmeal?
Yeah, like I put them in the vessel
and I mashed them
and then I combined, I put the oatmeal in,
mixed it as usual, added some
Greek yogurt, because it increases
the protein.
I replaced a little bit of it. What would have
an almond milk? I had some Greek yogurt.
And I added some stevia to the, oh my god.
Oh my god, the raspberries
with the stevia in there.
That's incredible, incredible.
An incredible inclusion. I think I said
on a previous episode, someone asked
favorite fruit and I was a little bit mixed on raspberries.
Yeah, yeah.
They are very sharp though,
so you do need that sugary.
I still wouldn't just eat them plain.
No, you need them with something sweet.
Yeah.
I like that I
mashed them up and their flavor was
included.
It really worked. It really was doing a lot for me.
Yeah, raspberries, like swirl ice cream is very nice.
I want to try,
I want to try getting strawberries. I'll try it
with strawberries. I'll get some fresh ones
and I'll mash them and mix them in and see
how that works. It'll probably be pretty good.
Raspberry yogurt is good.
Well, like I said, I had some
I had some yogurt in there.
It really worked.
It really did.
Okay,
that's my yogurt update.
The oat update turned into a yogurt update.
Dang it, I said yogurt.
Like a fucking weirdo, like a freak.
It's yogurt.
Yeah, colonize.
Get colonized.
I'm so embarrassed.
Uh,
um,
is it too early to talk about One Piece?
Um,
do you have nothing else to talk about?
What are your losers? Nothing else to talk about
for a week?
Yes.
Yes, whatever.
Now I have to show that I'm cooler by having
something to talk about, but I can't
bring anything forward.
No.
Uh, I'll say
no.
My exercise routine
is going really well.
My squat.
If you must know, thanks for asking.
220.
220 on the squat. That's pretty good.
220 squats?
Yeah.
No pounds.
Oh, sorry. Kilograms.
Those are different denominations.
He's keeping track.
Um,
220 pounds, 220 pounds, which is
uh, is good.
Uh, 225
is the line for two plate.
That's when I can officially say that I squat two plate,
which is a good milestone.
Um,
so I look,
I look good.
I look good, looking in the mirror.
I weighed myself and I was like, oh, damn,
I gained some weight.
But then I would look in the mirror and I was like, oh, but I don't look like I gained some weight.
He's got some muscle on you.
Actually, I look fucking ripped.
Actually, fucking ripped.
And you know what it is? I think
I'm taking more care with my diet this time.
This time I'm specifically
I'm like hitting, hitting
like a certain amount of protein
every day. I think I did not, in previous
times that I've been lifting,
I think I did not take care to like
make sure I was getting the protein I needed.
And I think that probably
hamstrung me considerably
in terms of gains.
It's a very important aspect.
This time I'm serious. I'm serious about
gains.
You can't increase your bulk
unless you put some bulk in your gob.
That's, put that on a shirt.
We can put that on again.
Put that on the fucking cover of
the perfect comic party.
The perfect comic party.
It's bulk for your gob.
Hmm.
It's gonna be good. It's gonna be good.
I guess the only thing I can talk about
is I'm
still doing that RuneScape
challenge. God still?
Yeah. I go on every so often
like a couple hours
listening to a video
and I'm like getting coal
and I'm mining
and who boy? I've got 33,000
pieces of coal right now.
I can't judge because I did play
Noida this week
against my better judgment.
See the thing with Noida is you play a game
and then you finish it.
But with RuneScape it never ends.
I'm constantly gaining more power.
It's like if I was playing Noida
but I was continually just like,
alright now I'll get back in there
and I'll go scavenge some more
some more fluids. Some more rare fluids
in my vessel.
My bank is getting filled with coal
and the bank tells like what the fuck
but they have to do it.
What's your aim? What's your next short term
aim for RuneScape
that you're collecting?
The big thing is the coal
because I need like
235k
235,000 coal
for the challenge.
Remind me what the ultimate goal
is again. It's to get all
of the materials I would need
to switch
to members
and level fletching
from level 1 to level 99
in one big go
by gathering materials
in free to play
which is a stupid very time consuming
way to do leveling fletching
but that's why it's fun.
That's why it's silly.
I understand.
So I've got like
I've got a bunch of coal
to get, some adamantine oil
and a bunch of runite ore.
I think the next milestone
might actually be hitting
like max level mining because that
I've calculated that I will get that
much.
Which is a lot because the levels
of the experience you need increases
exponentially
for each level.
So it's a lot of mining
and I get like
150 on average
per hour
and so to get
200,000
it takes a little while.
It takes a number of hours
and I'm probably gonna
not be... A number?
I can't remember. I think if I get what...
What number?
If I get a thousand coal, that's like
a little...
I think that's like three hours in a little bit.
So if I play three hours a day
then I get
a thousand coal
then I would need to play three hours a day
for 200 days
which is
you know
a mental arithmetic
you know?
I can't do mental arithmetic so I don't know
what that means. 200 days is most of a year?
Yeah.
If I play three hours a day which I will not
be able to do.
Right. Yeah.
And
I'm gonna have to... It's gonna take
playing through the whole battle network series
is gonna take
several hundred hours
of actively playing
the games
so that's gonna be...
Yeah.
And I'm not gonna be able to do that
every day. I might... I was hoping to do
a couple hours a day, a couple times a week
so that would end up being
I don't know if it's like 500 hours
maybe it'll be three...
Let's see. If there's 11...
If there's about 11 games in the series
and they're all roughly around
say 25...
let's average it out to like 25 hours
let's call that 300 hours
and if I did
6 hours a week
2-3 hours sessions
that would come to 6 hours a week
so 50 weeks
oh god it'll take a whole fucking year!
Yeah.
It's...
It's over!
Maybe consider
a lecture you can do in the meantime.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Definitely. I was
aware this would take a long time and I was gonna
have to do something else in the meantime.
Speaking of which...
Oh, one last thing before I move on from
RuneScape is
that 350
per hour is the average based on
my current mining level.
But as I increase in level
the percentage chance
to get coal per swing
increases.
So as I get to level 99
the average will get
higher. So my calculations are gonna be
it's actually gonna be a little less
than my calculations would
say.
So it might not be
a whole year.
It might be that in like
9 months it'll be done.
Lemau.
That's great.
But that's only the coal. Then there's
like the chickens. I need to kill like
thousands upon thousands of chickens to get
the feathers I need for the arrows.
Thank god.
I know. It's really silly.
I don't mind how long it takes.
Everybody needs a hobby I guess.
Yeah. People like
they play a game
and they enjoy themselves.
I'm playing RuneScape.
Shut up.
I agree.
Speaking of
a lecture to do in the
meantime while I'm working on getting that
ready.
I am so close.
I have only about 18 gigs
left to download via
Torrent
of the entire Digibro archive.
I will soon be one of the few
cedars
of all the content in the Digibro
archive which is almost a terabyte
of data. Actually I think it's more than
a terabyte.
You're going to have that
on a hard drive.
Yeah.
I think I basically
asked for
an external hard drive for
Christmas for my parents
specifically so I could store
this stuff.
Well I started
Torrenting it and as I was Torrenting it
I realized
I already have
a lot of the
space on my
extra hard drive was taken up with the Mega Man
stuff. I'm actually going to need another one
but I got another one and it's pretty much
all just going to go on there.
I can't wait for the OVA to be...
It has been downloading
for literally like six weeks now
and it's finally about to be done
like today.
I can't wait for the OVA to be finished
so that I can take all of that footage
off the hard drive that I have
just because I kept it as backup
you know. Didn't want to delete it
in case it was a catastrophic failure
and someone needed to get
the footage back.
Yeah.
We should release the behind
the scenes footage though. We should make
it like a bonus thing.
Yeah.
Of course.
Behind the scenes meaning like
flubbed takes
or is there more specific?
Well you have all the raw footage right?
I don't want to look at it.
You know, I understand.
But I do think
patrons would appreciate it and
find it funny.
I guess so.
I'll see how the OVA shakes
out. I don't know what takes are being
used and what's already been going to be seen.
You know
I don't know how much
unused footage there
will be.
Some takes we just did
like twice.
And there wasn't like a lot of camera
running in between.
Might not
might not be that much. I'm not sure.
We'll definitely do a commentary
of it. There'll be something.
Yeah, I think that'll be good.
I think that'll be funny and good.
And I wish
Kaiju would
finish drawing the cover. I might
give him a bell.
Give him a ring. Give him a little buzz.
I did like weeks, like a couple weeks ago.
And he was like, yep, I'll do it.
Okay.
I might just
ask someone else.
I asked someone else before
and they kind of never got back to me.
And I sort of dropped it because it seemed like Kaiju
was back on the case. I might ask them again
like, hey, do you want to draw the cover?
Just for the cover.
What have you got so far?
Maybe they've done a little sketch
and they just haven't got around to it.
Ed did like a very rough sketch
like almost like not even
really worth
using.
I had one
person in mind who I thought would
make a really good cover.
Maybe I'll ask them again.
Because they said that they were kind of busy the last time I asked.
But it's been a while, so.
Yep.
I mean, whenever, if you decide
to talk to someone else,
you should mention to Kaiju
that you don't need their services.
Yeah, yeah, of course. If someone else agreed to do it,
I'd be like, hey, dog, never mind.
Hey, don't worry about it. Hey, you're done. Hey, I can pay you now.
Kaiju told me that he didn't want to be paid
until he finished everything.
That was his decision.
So I haven't paid him anything.
Wish he would do the cover
so I could, one, so it would be done
and also so I could pay him.
Again, that was his,
he specifically said
I would, I don't,
don't pay me until I've completed the tab.
Okay.
You know, I,
I don't know about that.
I feel like you should pay someone.
That's what he said.
No, no, I mean like, because
if there's no money
until they finish it,
there's no
Well, I don't know.
I don't know what to tell you.
I don't know how, like
there's something in my brain that says
it would be, they would
do it more quicker
if they were paid, not because
they were
like, I don't know.
I feel like a little bit, I feel like a little bit
that saying don't pay me is an excuse
for taking a really long time on it.
Maybe.
Maybe it's just insurance, like
I don't know whether I'll have the time, which is fair enough.
But still.
Everyone takes so dang long.
This whole dojin's been like
a really long process.
Yeah, Nightmare.
The, uh, the
I
I would, I would have been happy to
just pay on a page by page
basis.
But he didn't want me to.
Take the money, you fool.
I mean, he will
hopefully at some point
if I, if I, if I get
someone else to do the cover, I'll just tell him like
hey, never mind, I'm going to pay you now.
I'm paying you, I insist
I will pay you now and not
later, no matter what you have to
say about it.
It's so close. It's literally
the cover is the only thing left.
I think.
Okay.
I'm out of stuff to talk about
other than one piece.
Okay, I guess.
Okay, and I feel like, I feel like
more happened this week.
Like I said, it felt like a lot
happened, but I didn't do anything.
Well, I mean, what happened?
Was there like an event?
Did somebody vent? Was somebody sus?
Oh, I think we're, um, I think we're
rent striking.
I think we're rent striking at my landlord.
Oh.
Because, um, there's still rats in the house
and, uh,
he hasn't, he has made like only the
most cursory
efforts to do anything about them.
Totally, totally inadequate.
Hmm.
That's a pretty good reason.
Yeah. Um, so I think, uh,
everyone is just not paying rent
until he does something about it.
I think that's the, the plan.
You gotta stop the scabs coming in
and paying rent for you.
Well, one guy is
going to do that for sure.
Well, pay for rent for everyone?
No. Oh, oh, for everyone, no.
There's one guy who's not here.
Like, he's not even around,
but he's still, like, technically
renting a room. So he'll probably
pay rent because, like, none of us have spoken to him.
But, like, the rest of us, I think we're all,
we all spoke and we're in agreement.
Like, we gotta stop paying rent until
he does something about this.
So I'll watch the...
Fortunately, I can see
it's there, it's public information
for all of us. We can log in and we can see
who has paid already.
So I'll be able to see, like,
if anyone breaks strike.
Like, if any, like, if other people pay,
I won't be, like, the only one
left. Cause I'm not willing to be
the only guy to do it.
I need, I need solidarity.
Yeah, solidarity. Exactly, exactly.
If somebody pays rent, you know who to lynch,
you know who to get. Absolutely.
So if everyone caves,
then I will also cave.
But I'm not, I'm not going to be the first one.
I'm going to wait until other...
Yeah, I'm not crossing the
picket line.
The first person who does will be
hanging from the tree by a harbor
a green forest cable
with their boots on.
Yes. Good, good.
They'll still...
And then the landlord will be like, uh-huh,
I love the reference.
Cool. The landlord will be like,
I love the, I love the reference.
Uh, yeah, you know, I know I'm a landlord,
but like, I'm still a little bit of like a base socialist,
you know, like, yeah, I play Disco Elysium.
They play Disco Elysium and they're on
they're on the side of the
strike breakers.
Yeah, they're... Union busters.
They're an ultra liberal.
They're a, they're a...
What's the other one?
Omega liberal?
No, you haven't met
the...
There's one guy in particular
who, what's it called?
Moral intern. The moral intern.
What's that mean?
Ultra liberal is like
libertarian, like economics.
Moral intern is like
a sort of
interventionist
sort of
like, we have to control the economy.
We have to like, regulate the economy
to make sure that nothing...
I think you're, I think you're close to meeting
someone who will explain moral intern
probably better than I can. It's all about the price
stability. You must maintain
the price stability.
You gotta keep inflation under two percent.
Just under. Never over. The stability.
The price stability.
If the price of bread goes up, that's it.
That's over.
Did you see
that fucking
drawing of the girl from
fucking
Spy Family
at Auschwitz?
What?
Dog shit. It's dog shit.
I don't know.
Artist is a hack.
Spy Family is that, that's the new,
that's the relatively new anime with the
girl. Okay.
It's that one artist who likes to draw
like, ha ha
this is their stick.
They'll draw, they'll paint
a popular anime character, a cute
anime girl, and when you look
at it for a second, it's kind of just like
a normal drawing of a cute anime girl,
and then you'll notice some background
details that suggest some dark
shit going on, like they're being domestically
abused, or they're getting a blow job
under the table, or
ha ha, she's going to Auschwitz.
It's so random.
It's so random and dark and edgy and funny.
Yeah, I think I know what
artist that is.
It's just lame. I don't like it.
And I think a lot of people, honestly
I read the replies, and a lot of people seem
offended, and they're like,
genuinely a lot of them were like, you can't
post this on freaking
Holocaust Remembrance Day.
And like, okay,
I guess I get that.
But that's not where I'm at
with it.
Where I'm at with it is that I can't
possibly feel anything about it, because
it's so...
It's so...
It doesn't mean anything.
It's just all noise and no signal.
It's...
A lot of their work, assuming we're talking
about the same person, a lot of their work
just sort of feels like
oh, this is an edgy teenager.
This is an edgy teenage boy
exactly, and they want to
say the end word so bad
they love the idea of saying the end word,
but they can't do it.
I drew a popular waifu
with Vladimir Putin.
Isn't that so fucked up?
It works, too.
People get mad at it, and that's what
they want. And I wish...
I don't know.
It's really dumb. It's a really dumb shtick.
Yeah.
Get better material.
Uh...
Whatever. I just want to complain.
Just want to complain about some shit
that I don't like.
And that's one of them.
But I'm not triggered.
But I'm not triggered, though.
I promise.
I don't know. Your voice is trembling.
Don't print in the news that I'm triggered.
I mean that I wasn't triggered.
I mean, shit.
No, I like the holocaust, actually.
It's good, actually.
Trust me, that's not the problem.
Trust me. Trust me.
It's not the problem.
Who's that?
I don't know.
That was me trying to emulate, like,
hey, if I was a YouTuber and I was
reading a script and I thought,
the script is getting boring, maybe I should
punch that by having a zoom in on my face
and, like, I'd make my voice really deep
for a second, and maybe I, like, reverse
the colors or something.
That's what that was.
In case you couldn't tell.
Sure.
In case it wasn't blindingly obvious.
I guess they're continuing
Rick and Morty without Justin Roiland's
lull.
Yeah, I don't...
I saw, like, people's reactions to the news
and never looked up the news.
Justin Roiland did a sexual
harassment or something.
I thought he beat his wife.
How do you do
Rick and Morty without Justin Roiland?
Isn't that, like...
I kind of think...
The voices. I guess you could...
You're right. That kind of is the show.
That's kind of, like, the heart and soul of the show is
the voices of Rick and Morty.
The voices and the
delivery is...
I mean, I know you can emulate it.
You could get a guy who does the voice, but, like,
the sense of humor as well.
I feel like it's going to be...
The new season's going to come out
and, uh, you're going to be...
Everyone's going to be able to tell.
Everyone's going to be able to tell. It's not the same.
Oh, hey, Morty.
And it's going to be really embarrassing.
Hey, Morty, burp. It's me, Rick.
Rick?
It just tunes the names.
I'm German. I'm German.
Morty, it's me.
I'm not Rick. I'm German, Rick.
I'm Rick, Morty.
I'm Rick.
Rick and Morty comes back, but it's just, like,
super right-wing now.
Justin Rowland's gone,
and it's worse.
You thought Justin Rowland was bad.
He was gatekeeping out the worst
and the most toxic elements.
You don't know how bad it could have been
without him.
You'll wish we had Justin back.
Um...
I haven't been keeping up with the show.
No, I didn't watch the last season.
I watched was the one where
the
finite curve
and, like, the Morty
guy,
he went through to the different dimension
where there's no Rick
or something.
The central finite curve was, like,
a lore thing where, like,
Rick Sanchez has the portal gun
that only goes to other universes
where Rick is the coolest guy,
and it blocks out all the universes
without that.
And so the Morty is Morty.
Not the Morty is Morty, but, like, the Evil Morty
does the thing where he turns
the
Sanctuary of Rick's or whatever
into, like, a
way to zap himself into
a universe
that doesn't have Rick as the coolest guy,
and then Morty could be the coolest guy
or something. He escaped.
He escaped the curse of Rick.
And I was like, oh, cool.
Follow up. I wonder if they did something.
I wonder if it was good.
I don't know if it is.
I think I heard, uh, I kind of saw
people being mostly, like, positive
about the latest season, like, not that
long ago, I think.
Yeah. Not sure.
I'll go back and watch it, but, like,
that's funny. That's funny that Justin
Royland fucked everything up by being
terrible.
I think he did, like,
felony domestic abuse.
I think that's what it was.
I mean, I think he also
was, like, sexting
minors, but I don't think that's
what, like, the legal charges
are about.
Hmm.
I think?
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know anything
about it, so I'm not going to talk.
Talk out my AS.
Um,
whatever. You know what? I don't
care. I don't care if frickin' Morty gets
canceled. I don't care if Justin Royland gets
fired. They peaked with Pickle Rick. It's okay.
They peaked with Pickle Rick!
Um, it's fine.
You know what? Um, I don't even, like,
shows anyway, so when they get canceled,
I think it's good. Um,
it makes me happy.
People keep on trying to show me
stuff. I'm, like, nothing, please.
No. More content.
Unironically, yes, only
people have stopped trying to show me.
Hahaha.
Just what I always...
I like oblivion. I like the
abyss. I like oblivion, too.
That guy always makes good voicemails.
That guy's always making a good funny voicemail.
Hey, remember? Oh, I was thinking of a video game.
Uh, hey, remember,
uh, like, last week in the voicemails
when
TinCannMan revealed himself to have
been oblivionfall all along?
No, it's not true. It was a
it was a trick.
Well, I,
I was taught, you know, I went on the,
I was on the drawcast. We did the edgy
character's drawcast, which I'm not sure
if that's out yet or when it will be out.
Actually, I have, I forgot to follow up
on that. Um, but
I was on that and we recorded
it, and during the course of it, I
asked oblivionfall about it, or I mentioned
it, and oblivionfall was like, what the hell?
Some guy asked me
to say that like months ago
and I forgot about it. Oh,
he got played.
So like, like, he
he mentioned something and I, and I mentioned, oh
yeah, that voicemail you did. And he was like, what
voicemail? I didn't do a voicemail. And I was like, yeah
you did. You, you, you said
you were, had been TinCannMan all
along and he was like, what? Yeah.
I can't believe TinCannMan was
the mastermind behind that one.
Played, played, outplayed,
outmatched, outgunned.
So powerful. We, we, we, we
we were so, we, we didn't
uh, expect so uh, that much
of TinCannMan, but we, we
we saw it coming. We were shown, we were shown up.
He's a genius.
You know, he is a genius.
He put it like that.
I'm watching my, I'm watching
my uh, Digi
Archive.
It is five parts.
Four of them are complete.
The biggest one, part four
which is called
collaboration is still downloading.
It has been downloading for six weeks and six
days. Five. It is
it is six hundred and sixty-eight gigabytes.
Uh, the connect,
I'm not sure, I don't think it's on my end, but
like the connection keeps like popping in.
The download keeps stopping and starting and stopping
and starting. Uh,
but uh, it is at six hundred and
fifty gigabytes of
six hundred and sixty-eight gigabytes have been
downloaded at ninety-seven point two percent.
It is so close.
I could taste it.
What does collaborations mean? Is that like
videos in which
she appears in other people's videos
or with other people in them?
I guess so. Like with the PCP?
Uh,
I don't, I don't know.
Maybe. Maybe includes
all the pub crawl.
This, this is like by far the biggest.
I think that one of the other parts is four
hundred gigs and then all the other ones are
like a hundred.
The other ones are like much smaller.
There's like the pub crawl and the
appearances on the dick show and
like I'm trying to think of
like how is it so much bigger?
Well no, there was another, one of the other parts
um,
is called, okay well the parts are
one, the digi collective,
which I'm pretty sure means the main channel.
And then part two is
other digi channels, which I think means
you know, like other.
Digi after dark.
Digi does that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then part three is called featuring digi,
which I would assume means
like appearances
on other people, in other people's videos
on other people's channels.
And then part four is called collaboration,
which
I would kind of think that
featuring digi would be
a part of that, but I guess not.
Maybe it's the other way around, like
digi featuring others.
Well, why wouldn't that go on digi collective?
Don't have that fucking know.
Yeah, I don't, I don't really get it.
And then part five is called mis, miscellaneous
content, which, you know, I don't know what
them.
Maybe collaborations is like
uh, digi bros, and
not Vic and Hope.
I guess digi bros, and then digi and may.
Other, other digi channels
is by far, that can't
be after dark, because it's by far the smallest.
It's only 40 gigs.
Uh, featuring digi is one
118, miscellaneous is
179, digi collective 476,
collaboration
668.
Uh...
Well, have fun looking at them.
In case you wondered, in case you wondered, but hey,
if anyone wants, if anyone is
thinking about getting
the digi archive for their very own,
if you torrent it,
I will be seeding it, because I will
have it as a very soon.
So you're welcome.
Um...
Before we get to one piece, I need to
pee again. Ah! Okay.
Let's do that.
Okay.
Okay, so
a couple people are
uh,
replying to my tweet about May with
some choice screenshots
of her tweets.
Now I gotta go and look.
Just a couple of
um, she recently
retweeted Sneeko.
Do you know who Sneeko is?
Sounds like a sneaky gay.
I think he's a streamer.
I guess he's popular now.
Seems like a little bit of a
fashion, honestly.
Seems like kind of a scumbag
fashion. Wait, Amanda Marce
has absconded.
Yes. It's a funny
word to use.
That is a funny word.
He also called May's sister
when I hear it, when I see it.
He also called May's sister a
slatternly, which is an interesting...
You get the fucking
thesaurus out for this?
Yeah, yeah.
Radcon 5 soon.
It's just unrelated.
Yeah,
the address.
Uh...
This guy says,
why aren't they married?
So why is it not my wife absconded?
Amanda Ralph absconded.
Yeah, why does he say...
Oh, I guess he probably says Amanda Morris.
I mean, he probably says that because
in other tweets he says like, you know,
not my wife, she's just a whore.
Goddamn, that's probably why he's using
her maiden name.
Since you mentioned it, it's gotta be
that like, she just wanted to get married
for some sort of legal or financial reason
and then take the first opportunity
to abscond.
I'm using his word, but whatever.
It's gotta be that. It makes the most sense.
The timing is like...
The timing's perfect.
I guess I just don't know what
you can gain.
I think it's gotta be alimony.
It's gotta be alimony.
Yeah, I think so. I think probably being
legally married makes a better case.
How would you go about getting alimony?
Well, I don't exactly know.
You don't run away. You just get a divorce.
Right?
Well, she...
Yes, but I mean, she...
Okay, she probably wanted to run...
I mean, this is total speculation,
but what I'm thinking is maybe she had
wanted to run away for a while,
but was like, well, if I run away before
we get married, it'll be harder to get alimony.
So I just need to put up with it
until we get married.
And then once we're legally married,
I can abscond.
And then we can...
Because absconding is what I want.
Then I can do it.
And only then, once I've absconded,
we can start the legal
proceedings for divorce, I think.
I have a strong feeling that this was
not planned.
I mentioned it just because...
Like, how?
My version
makes more sense, but
maybe that's not
what I should be looking for
in this situation.
Maybe that's not the most
sensible way to try and interpret
these people's actions.
Well, now
let's actually talk about One Piece.
Let's actually talk about One Piece. I did actually read it
ahead of time. Same.
We've done it.
Yeah, at last.
I mean, I guess the big...
So, the One Piece corner...
One Piece corner begins
at whatever time stamp this is,
and will end at another time...
In the future.
Down in the description you can see
ahead of time, if you want,
to skip it.
Spoilers, all right, here we go.
So, chapter 1073
Miss Buckingham Stussy.
Is it just a coincidence
that you mentioned
Weevil? Like, you mentioned Weevil a couple
weeks ago, and I was like
who the heck is that?
I keep things like that
in my brain, just because it's like
there's so much going on in One Piece
and Weevil is like such a big
like, wow, what a thing
and then you don't hear about him for
arcs and arcs, months and months,
years and years, it's like, wow,
when is he gonna come back in? Because he has to.
Well, he's freaking back.
He's freaking back.
Let's talk about the cover page for us, though.
We got
the Mads scientists
and we got
Oh, wait a minute.
Mads scientists.
Oh my god.
Even though I didn't get that, as I said it.
Just as you said that, I'm like, wait a minute.
I think that's probably the joke.
Mads scientists.
So
last week
they were like, ha ha, look at all our
evil plans, evil inventions
and then Vegapunk comes
with a peaceful invention
that stops tanks from being able to shoot,
turns gunpowder into
flowers.
Aw, that's sweet. You know what, I didn't even think about it.
I kind of just kind of glossed over this one.
And he, I think,
his wing, I think he wins the prize.
Yeah,
Vegapunk receives the bell prize.
The Ibell Prize.
Instead of the Nobel?
I guess so, yeah.
For the GP, the gunpowder flower.
Aw.
What a precious man.
What a sweet precious man
who I hope will not
betray our heroes.
Yeah.
I guess this is like a hint that he's
you know, he's been a good guy generally.
This seems like he's a pretty good guy.
I mean, I guess he's friends with like
the giants of Elbaf and
freaking Porcus D. Sol.
Not Porcus D. Sol.
What was his name?
Sol D.
Oh, Jaguar D. Sol.
Jaguar D. Sol, yeah.
Um, so I mean,
I guess he's probably a good guy.
Okay, so.
He's friends with cool dudes.
Okay, so
Kaku got bit
by the clone of
Ms. Buckingham Stussy.
We have discovered she's a vampire.
Luchi stands no chance.
She gets him with a lipstick, a
Kyro Seiki seastone lipstick.
Bites him as well.
Oh, I get it.
She bit him
and her seastone lipstick.
Allowed her to bite him, to get through the hacky
and because it weakens
devil fruit users.
So.
I think that's the
implication. Okay, okay.
Well, I mean,
would she need
that just to bite him?
I think.
I thought it was that the seastone lipstick
is what like put him out.
Because she had
seastone on her lips
for the bite.
No, I think it's
pretty universally used as
like a way to stop
a devil fruit user
to hurt them more is to use
seastone.
Like some of the
guys, the Marines have like
seastone bullets very occasionally.
Yeah. And you can't,
Luchi can't touch those, they'll hurt him.
So he has to dodge them instead.
He can't like, he can't balloon
them away like regular bullets.
Yeah.
It hasn't been used that much.
I think it was used a little bit
in like
a whole cake
vaguely remember that.
So is the
so she's clearly, she's clearly
not a devil fruit user then
because she can wear
seastone lipstick.
No, she doesn't
wear it. She picks it up and
steps into his neck
to, you know, so she's not
touching it. He's touching it. And then she can
use him in his weakened state.
She can bite into his skin
and do, do stuff.
Get him. I don't know what
her bite does, but seems to knock them
out at least.
Well, hang on.
She
I mean, she says
seastone. Oh, wait.
She pops the lipstick.
She says, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, she like puts
it. She like puts it on his neck.
I see. I see. I see. Yes.
Does
seastone negate hockey too?
I don't think it negates hockey.
I think it just makes devil fruit
users weaker.
So it's more difficult to do
anything. Yeah.
Like you can't like physically
overpower the effects of it.
If you fall in the water, you sink. It doesn't matter
how strong you are. If you're a devil fruit user,
the power of the sea makes you
completely immobile.
Yes, the power
of the primordial
nature that is the sea
that wants to hold
devil fruit users
down from
achieving
the dreams of
Yeah, I forgot about all that.
That shit.
That confusing shit.
Yeah.
The sea, it doesn't want you to reach
the sea hates fruit. The sky of dreams.
The fruit is all about
what if humans wanted to fly?
They unlock the human's
potential to
do whatever they want. To become rubber and
things. The sea hates fruit
and the fruit is dreams
and man eats fruit
and go up.
And sea do not like
man go up.
And that's why the sea is at the bottom of the land.
Sorry, sea does not like
zizi. Sea does not like zizi
go up.
Okay, so we understand.
We understand where the sea is coming from.
Yes, so Stussy
takes him out.
And it's not just, I don't know why I didn't think
of this. I guess it was just sort of
out of left field.
But she was the lady on the phone
that Vigapunk called earlier.
Oh, sure.
Okay, yeah, that makes sense.
So she's the
secret person on the island
that could help them.
Which is
quite a coincidence.
Pretty good.
I guess it's not a coincidence, but it's just
sort of like, she is
working for like how many years?
Yeah, I mean.
As like a person undercover
for all these things.
And she's a clone loyal to Vigapunk.
Just like the Seraphim.
Yeah?
I guess so.
But the Seraphim are different, more stronger.
The Seraphim are different, more stronger.
Zoro says he sees
humanity in little baby
Mihawk.
So like,
he seems to think the Seraphim
are not like, they're not like automatons.
Yeah.
Potentially maybe
try to break their programming if they wanted to.
Yeah, this is just like Mega Man.
I would say it is very
yes.
Oh my god, just like Mega Man
collecting the robot master's powers.
A closer inspection, you're not the same.
You actually have a spark of humanity still.
I don't know whether that means
Mihawk has no
humanity.
But I guess, well actually, no.
I think he's saying, you're not the same.
Like the Seraphim are not the same
guy.
They're not the same soul.
They have individuality still.
Yeah, I think he's saying like you're not just
a robot taking commands.
Yeah.
What the hell are you?
So the Seraphim nearly kill everyone.
But it's okay.
Because they managed to get a
little command out and then
they take
the command and then they're here.
No standing still.
Well, Stussy says
Stussy commands them
to stop.
No, it's
the little guy.
Edison. He manages to say it.
They think he exploded, but then Stussy
saved him at the last second.
Yes, okay.
I see.
So
because Vegapunks orders
Super Seed,
B-Zeroes.
Yeah.
Because Stussy couldn't
Stussy has the same
clearance as Luchy
which means that she could not override
Luchy's commands.
Yeah, wait.
That's what they say, but like if they're the same
why wouldn't
why couldn't one
cancel the other?
My authority level is the same so I can't
cancel it.
That's odd.
I guess
there must be a rule there that like
if a person
from a certain
level of authority
says something
that another person of the same level
can't confuse them
by saying something else
and that's the idea.
It has to be a person higher up the chain
to say something. It has to be the person higher
in the chain and also
the first person on that level of the chain
gets to set the commands and then no one else
on that same command level gets to Super Seed them.
Yeah, I guess that's
it's an odd way to work.
I guess it just means
whatever.
It gives an excuse for a
thrilling moment where Edison nearly got blowed up.
It's true.
And I would have
been so devastated
if he got blowed up.
So the stakes truly were raised
in that moment.
And then
their docile
and then it turns out
Vegapunk's main body
has vanished
and they can't find Bonnie either.
Bonnie obviously has just found
the memory of Kuma.
Oh, right.
We don't know whether she touched it.
She looked like she was going to
and
I guess we don't know
at the moment what's going on
with them.
No updates on that.
Because it says vanished as in like they're gone
but it could just mean they can't find them
but I feel like
vanished implies that they've actually gone somewhere somehow.
My translation that I read
says however an event will occur
the disappearance of Dr.
Vegapunk which
merely implies that they cannot
find him to me.
Right.
I got another thing to say
but I'll wait until the end of the chapter.
So then we switch over
to Sphinx New World
White Beards hometown
where Marco lives.
Does he live there?
Yeah, he lived there.
He's a doctor there
and everyone knows in there I assume he lives there
because after the White Beard Pirates broke up
he settled down there
which is where he's been seen
since White Beard's death
so I assume so but
I think in the interim
where Marco had left to go to Wano
Yeah, he was out doing like
missions and like giving people messages
and stuff.
Yeah, he was out flying around
and then the Marines came
those nasty stinky Marines
with a rat face.
He's like catfish man.
Oh yeah.
He looks like a fishman.
Yeah, yeah.
They're gonna shoot some kids.
This is like old school Marines
from like Arlong Park.
It is.
The old school like we're evil and nasty
and we'll just fuck with innocent bystanders.
A child?
How dare you?
What if we shoot you one by one?
Wouldn't that make you cry?
And then fucking Balaam
Edward Weevil comes in
with the White Beard
weapon.
I don't know if it's the same one.
Oh yeah, he's got the big glaive thing.
Yeah, true.
I forget if he already had one
like that.
Well they, I thought they left
White Beards like on his grave.
Yeah, I don't think he would.
He could have retrieved it.
I feel like it maybe would have been mentioned.
But he could have already
had a glaive similar.
Yeah.
Cause I can't remember the last time we saw him
what he looked like.
But yeah, he's a strong guy.
He makes all the Marines run away
and he's protecting his father's
hometown.
So he believes that he's the son of White Beard.
We still don't know actually
but it's not really corroborated
by most of other people.
Most other people just believe that it's a lie
perpetrated by
the lady that he's always with
to get White Beard's money as a scam.
It could be true.
Maybe it's true.
It would be cool if it's true because
God this,
the lady is
Miss Buckingham Stussy.
She is a scientist.
So this is the same lady
who is the clone.
Her clone is betraying
CP0
on Egghead right now.
Her original form
is, yeah, the mom of
Weevil.
Former member of the Rocks Pirates
which leads a lot of credence
to the idea that she could have
sired a child
of White Beards because
he was also on the crew.
Definitely. No doubt.
She's also
old though. I guess Weevil would be old too.
You mean White Beard?
No, Weevil. I don't know how old Weevil is.
He's such a
beast looking guy. You don't really know how
he can really tell.
He could be 18 or he could be
like 30.
It's hard to tell.
But yeah, she's not only a scientist,
part of the Rocks Pirates.
So all of this stuff with the mad scientists
and
Is she in any of the
Rocks Pirates?
Art? Like the intro?
I don't think we've seen her.
I don't think we've seen her in those.
Yeah.
It's those same three
Jerma and
Caesar and
that guy who may or may not be
the artist potentially known as Queen.
The artist potentially known as Queen.
Yeah.
And yeah, she would be there.
I guess they didn't want to spoil
surprise for this moment.
Because if they showed
what Stussy
looked like, it would be obvious
that Stussy is the Stussy that is
currently in the comic.
You think?
You think it would be obvious?
Well, if it's, I mean,
it might not be obvious, but like the idea
is it's characters we haven't
seen young before looking young,
but Stussy as a clone is
young. And so she
would like, theoretically,
she would look the same in
those flashback. Oh, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, that's true.
Honestly, that would make me
honestly, that would have made me be like,
why does she look the same?
What the fuck? What the fuck?
But isn't it been a while?
Vega punks old. Vega punks.
And now we see she is old.
She looks great
as well. I love her
like, her gnarly
old hands with all the rings on them.
Hmm.
I
I was
shocked and horrified by this revelation.
Seems
seems like he probably
seems like he probably is
Whitebeard's son, honestly.
If she was a rocks pirate
and all that, just seems
perfectly reasonable.
Okay, so
besides, you think she knows she has a clone?
Who knows? That's the thing.
Yeah, I don't know.
Besides the fact that we
is a revelation of this character,
we've only seen like a couple times before
is very relevant to the effect of the
events happening right now is
that we've all protected
those kids, protected the town,
but then they sent Admiral
Rokyugu
the new Admiral
who I think has been revealed.
I can't remember what he looks like. Let me just
I think he
arrived at the end of Wano
and he tried to bully
Momonosuke and the guys
and he was like, what was he?
Like a vine guy?
Wait, Weevil did? No.
Rokyugu, the new Admiral.
Rok-
Fuck.
There's a new Admiral?
Yeah, because
Aokiji left and then Akainu
got promoted to the
Fleet Admiral. So there's three.
One of them is Kizaru.
There's Kizaru and there's
the purple monkey guy.
Purple man from Dressros and then there's this guy
who was only revealed
at the very end of Wano after
everyone had been defeated.
Yeah, I
totally forgot about this guy.
Yeah, so that's the reveal of that guy.
That guy apparently
took Weevil away
which means that
Oh, um, um
he got like arrested
after the restrication with the
with the Marines. Yeah, so they sent
Admiral Rokyugu. He took
Weevil away
which means because right now
does it say that in this chapter?
She says it.
Stussy, old lady
says that Rokyugu came
as backup and they stole Weevil away.
Oh, Navy Admiral Greenbull came here.
Okay. Greenbull, that's the other name for him.
Right. Yeah.
We're reading different scans.
Yeah.
So Weevil is with, presumably
with him or
it's, he could have been taking
to Impel down but I think
the implication here is that
because the admirals have been called
with all of these warships to
Egghead is that Greenbull
along with Weevil
are on their
way with all of the other warships
and Kizaru and
Purple Man. So it's, I
thought it was just, is it not just
Kizaru who's going there?
Like I know Kizaru is going there.
I thought he was the only one.
You know, I can't remember if this
maybe they didn't say all the admirals would be there.
I feel like it's such a big thing
because we see
it could just be Kizaru actually
like he's the one heading it.
Yeah. But the fact is that
we scroll down a bit
one of the five elders is on one of the
special boats.
Is he going there also?
Oh wait, he's talking to Kizaru so.
Yeah, Kizaru is there. Yeah.
And there's one of the five elders
of Marishua
making a move for the first time.
I mean, if I can Jerry, Jerry,
J Garcia, Saint J Garcia
Saturn.
Yeah. What's the make of that name?
I think it's a reference
to like a. Is it Jerry, is it Jerry
Garcia?
Jerry Garcia.
Let me look up what he looks like.
There's a chapter nose thing in the scan.
Saturn's name might refer
to two unrelated musicians, Jerry Garcia.
There's also a Russell Garcia
who wrote a song called The Lost Souls of
Saturn.
Okay. So it could be.
This is this is what Jerry Garcia looks
like. And I mean, it looks
looks like a match to me.
Yeah. So.
J Garcia said it could be a combination.
But anyway, the
thing I wanted to mention earlier,
the seraphim.
The whole thing with like, oh, they listen
to the five elders above
and it just so happens
that a five elder is coming at
probably explicitly because of this
thing. They need him
so that he can control the seraphim,
which are the most powerful guys.
Because.
They said
that even if they hear
the voice of a
of a five elder gore say over
this transponder snail,
they won't count. It doesn't count.
But does it not count
because it's over a transponder
snail? I thought they were saying that it doesn't
count because
in the case of the seraphim
specifically, the order
of the order is different
and Vega punk outranks
the five elders in
in ordering them specifically.
But they did mention the transponder snail.
So maybe it is just that he has to be there
in person. I think that
the idea is
above Vega punk is
the five elders. But when
we when I've read that the first time is like, yeah,
but when are they going to be in marriage? Why?
Yeah, when are they going to see a five
elder? Well, now he's coming
and I think he's coming because
they know that that's how they work.
I think that is almost
definitely true.
I had thought what they
said. I had thought they had
explained it as like, yeah,
normally a gore say would
Trump them in
the order of ordering them.
But like, actually, they don't for some
reason in this specific case.
But the fact that he's here
means like
this has to be relevance.
It probably does. They're making so much
of this fucking order of like
who commands the seraphim.
Yeah. And I think it's not just
like you can't
order them through
like electronic communication
regardless of who you are.
You have to be in front of them.
They have to hear and see it from you.
I think that
makes sense and
okay.
So this will be interesting because
it's it's it's yeah.
It'll be interesting
on a couple of ways because
we just saw that Edison
almost got blown up
because they're so powerful, so quick.
It's hard to get a word in
if they're trying to kill you to
tell them to stop even though you have the
authority. They don't recognize the authority.
They just recognize the order.
So is this guy is one of the five
elders? Are we going to see them fight?
Is he going to be really quick?
Is he going to be super strong?
Or is he just going to be an old man?
How's he going to do it?
Yeah.
Dude, that'll be fucked up
to see like a Gora say like
in a battle.
Even it just for half a second so he can
get his
his order out.
I feel like
because of there being so many warships
the marines
are going to
hold them off so that he can say his
thing and he's not going to lift a finger
which is going to be characteristic of that
sort of a character.
That's what I would think.
Yeah.
You never know. He could have a devil fruit.
Got that.
I feel like
that
I don't want everyone to have a devil fruit.
Yeah.
I like the idea of the Gora say just being some guys
who are in control.
They're just guys who have a lot of political power
and they just tell other people
by their word
they cause wars to happen
and stuff.
So they got all these warships
coming.
Vegapunk
has never been nullified
for now.
The seraphim are on the side
of the straw hats
presumably going to get on the boat
with the rest of the Vegapunks
and Stussy
and leave
but we can't find the actual Vegapunk
and I think that's going to be the thing
that holds them up long enough for the warships to get here
and then there's going to be a whole fucking thing.
Yeah.
Because it seems like
they have the seraphim
CP-Zero taken out
they can just go.
But then Vegapunk is nowhere to be found.
Are they lost?
Are they teleported somewhere?
Where were they trying to go with Vegapunk?
Where are they trying to go?
What do you mean?
They were going to the ship
and they were going to leave Egghead
with Vegapunk
Where are they trying to go?
They're just trying to get out of there.
Vegapunk is like
I've discovered something about the voids entry
or something and it's like bad information
the government doesn't want me to know
I gotta get out of here
and it just so happens that the straw hats arrive
at the perfect time to help him escape.
So there's no goal other than
get the fuck out.
Sensible.
I really hope they use a coup de burst
to fly over the warships.
Oh, yes.
I haven't seen that in a while.
The classic coup de burst.
You know, I gotta admit
it helps me a lot
to understand what's going on
to have these discussions
because
kind of all I really took away from reading the chapter
was like
Oh, yeah, Weevil's still here
and the Gorace is around
interesting and
Oh, Weevil's mom is
the clone lady.
Yeah.
I kind of didn't really think about what this means
for the state of the battle
but actually, yeah,
there are pretty big implications
for how this is going to go down.
I don't want to let it leave my head
that there's
a rescue operation with Garp
trying to get Kobe from Blackbeard
and Weevil has been taking
by Red Bull, a green bull
not Red Bull.
From
Rokyoyoyo, don't know how to say his name.
Yeah.
And if there's all these warships
potentially other admirals
because if they asked for Garp
to be at this thing and he says, no, I'm going to help Kobe instead
like they needed Garp
they might need the other admirals.
I don't think Aikainu is there.
I think it's not that you know it like HQ.
He's like, he's at HQ.
He was getting like phone calls and stuff.
Yeah, and I mean...
Fuji Tora is...
Do you remember where
Fuji Tora was?
I don't think we've seen Fuji Tora
since Dress Rosa.
I believe he's just not
been around.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean they would need
two new ones because
Aokiji left
and Aikainu
was promoted.
Yeah.
And Sengoku retired or whatever.
Sengoku retired.
Aikainu became the new...
Is it called Fleet Admiral?
Fleet Admiral, yeah.
The highest position of the Marines.
Green Bull and...
I think it's Green Bull and Purple Monkey.
Or
Purple...
Dragon?
I don't think it's Dragon.
Or is Kizaru Yellow Monkey?
I forget the names like that.
Let's have a little
Google.
Fuji Tora is Purple Something.
And Aokiji is
Blue... I think Aokiji is probably
Blue Dragon?
No.
Isho, better known by his alias
Fuji Tora is an admiral
in the Marines.
Where is Purple?
He's got to be the Purple Man.
Does he wear Purple? I mean I haven't seen him
drawn. Yeah, he wears Purple.
Well, the manga
is in black and white.
I watched a bit of Dress Rosa anime.
I tried to watch the anime.
I think it was just a little
slow going just generally.
Kizaru is Yellow Monkey.
Fuji Tora is
Wisteria Tiger, but Wisteria
is like a purple flower.
Oh, Fuji Tora
literally meaning Wisteria Tiger
is in Japanese.
Okay.
Aokiji was Blue Pheasant
and Ayaka was Red Dog.
Okay.
Nice color-coded
villains.
Um...
Hell, yeah.
They're all big.
I found
doing the pod de-cast
was quite fun to like
wrap my head around some of the
longer...
Like, some of the things that just
sort of leave your mind when they're not
happening in front of you and then they come back
and it's like, whoa!
It's like, what the fuck?
It was good to have the discussion
so I could like wrap my head around stuff
that was happening week to week.
Honestly,
when I just read it
there's like so much
it kind of just
leaves my head and I kind of just
don't even bother to try.
I kind of just don't even bother trying to keep it all in
because like I know I can't do it.
I
I pride myself on remembering some stuff.
It's fun.
I like complicated, extremely...
extremely complicated stories.
I really like the parts of the caribbean
when in like two and three
when they just kept getting weirder and stranger.
I was like, fuck yeah.
I understand. Nobody else did.
They were all like,
what? Huh?
Where's the crabs come from?
I don't think I saw that one.
Don't think I saw
past like the second one.
No, the third one carries
on from the second one.
It's like the continuation of that
Davy Jones story.
I definitely saw
the second one with Davy Jones.
Yeah, and the third one is
Davy Jones part two.
You gotta watch it.
That's great.
I love it. It's pirates.
I love pirates so much.
Pirates are good,
I guess.
One last thing we didn't mention.
Stussy, old.
I don't know how to talk about Stussy.
Yes, true.
Old Stussy says
that Vegapunk will know how to prove
that Weevil is
Whitebeard's son.
I guess
that means
the technology, DNA technology
is not widely known and used.
Interesting, let me
see here.
But it could mean something more deep than that
because we see Weevil has a lot of scars on him.
Is he a construct?
Is he like a freak made of the DNA
of Whitebeard?
Yeah, I mean.
Is he like a clone
of Whitebeard just like Stussy was a clone?
She could mean that
he can do a paternity test
or
she could mean
that he knows something about
Weevil's history
that he can vouch for it.
I think the fact that
Stussy is already
one of the rocks pirates cloned
perfectly
could mean that another rocks pirate
was unsuccessfully cloned
and they made a freak Frankenstein's Weevil.
Oh.
Does he have
Weevil?
I mean,
I don't know if there's scars.
Could he be like a patchwork
man?
Like they put pieces of him together
out of pieces of Whitebeard
or something?
He could be.
I think it wouldn't be as simple as
just like an inheritance dispute.
I think the fact that Stussy is like a scientist
and Vegapunk knows the secret
could lead to some sort of clone
attempt
that didn't really work.
You know
that's
you're almost certainly
right.
This is
weird paternity
shit going on there.
Cloning is involved.
What else can I say?
Cloning is almost certainly involved.
I'm
sort of like
because the Gorose is coming
at least this guy
and his ability to take over the Seraphim
I feel like
it's likely that
the Straw Hats might escape
but not with the Seraphim
and the Seraphim will put up a fight
because he's there somehow
gets in contact with them.
The Marines take over Egghead
and Vegapunk
and his Vegapunkettes
and hopefully some of them will die
but
some of them will live
and they'll run away
but I think the Seraphim
they're not going to be helping the Straw Hats
on the ship. I feel like
they're staying here somehow.
Zora says
he sees humanity
so I mean
is it just going to be like
at some point
they have to
follow the Gorose's orders
but maybe at some point they'll be like
I don't like this
actually.
I'm going to be a good guy.
Maybe they'll be taken to Majora's
like super bodyguards
and then
the special secret
that something really inspirational
will happen. Luffy will be so
bathed and then they'll hear about it
on the Denden Mushi on the radio
and they'll be like you know what
fuck the Goros saying and they kill them all
they kill them all right there
they got guys on the inside
that's
it would be really funny if
that's just how they did
literally
Luffy does something cool on the radio
and they're all just like oh that's neat
maybe
slavery is bad and then they just kill
the five presidents
okay
revolution
I
love one piece
it's good I can't believe a comic
is good
and then there's the fucking
the fucking laser beam from space
that killed potentially
killed
are they going to use
that laser beam on an egg head
wait did they
what did they blow up with that again
which island it was just an island
Sabo was seen like hiding
and after he escaped Marishwa
because he like it was
like oh he killed King
Cobra from alabaster
that was the story anyway
we don't know what happened but that's
it's that's what's the story and then he
was ran away he was in hiding and then
they like from space
or from the sky blasted it
with a giant laser if they have
a giant space laser
what do they need the what do they need
buster calls for
because this
takes a while to level up power
up this the laser
maybe it's maybe it's like
it's hard to hide the existence
of a giant laser so they
don't want to do it
all the time because if people like
that island used to exist and then it suddenly doesn't
that's a bit weird you know
the giant speak no I kind
of forgot about the giant space laser
but that definitely happened and probably
it deserves
some consideration
probably there will be
consequences to that
it's sort of interesting though because it's like
it implies that Sabo learned
information that is even more dangerous
than what Vega punk has figured out
because they're not using that here
they could have
probably yeah you know
like what the hell did Sabo learn
but I mean maybe
maybe it's not a space
laser maybe it's like somebody's fruit power
and they have to be there to do it
I well I think
it's more likely that it's one of the
ancient weapons that I mean
the world government has control of
yeah like the idea
of these ancient weapons existing
and like a bunch
of history that's been erased probably
speaks to me like
the ancient weapons were used in the person
it was devastating and the PR
would be terrible if people knew about it
the PR would be
I mean it would yeah
um
yeah but then
I guess it would
beg the question of why they're not
using it
here and I guess
either
like there's something there's stuff here
that they don't want to destroy
along with Vega punk
I guess so he does have a big brain
computer
yeah they might they might want to
secure that
that's so fucking weird the more I think about it
like that's his actual brain
that's his actual brain yeah
basically the island itself
or like a big chunk of it floating in the clouds
is just
his actual brain that he took out of his head
and he put in a big ball
and uh
yep like if the if the if he runs away
can't they just turn his brain off
and then he becomes dumb
I think they just destroy it
they I guess they wouldn't be allowed to destroy it
I think that if they
they could destroy if they destroyed
the brain I assume it would kill him
and if they killed
him I assume that the brain
would also die
uh
and but I mean
I don't know how they would use
the brain
without him like surely he is the one
who can use the brain
or maybe he has
some devices that interface with it
well he already has like
the other vega punks who are like
constructs that share his brain
yeah I assume and he was talking about
like what if the entire world could be linked
together and share knowledge
yeah like he's probably working on
the ability to disseminate information
that's probably like a thing you could work on
like I'm gonna tell everyone about
the void sentry
and then he's gonna broadcast it across
the whole world everyone's gonna know
everyone's gonna know it all at once
that's I predict that happening
I yeah
I think you're probably
right I think probably something like that
is gonna happen
and everyone's gonna be like
what the fuck the world government sucks
and they're gonna revolt all at once
it's funny because like everybody already knows
what the world government sucks
they kind of don't need to know
they kind of don't need to be told about
it would be unrealistic
if like some
because you know
in real life
the government declassifies
like secret documents about like
unbelievably fucked up shit the CIA did
all the time and nobody gives a shit
everyone's just like oh really
yeah okay that's fine
it's like how do you really fight that
they have the power to stop you
if you try and stop them
it's like yeah whatever
yeah yeah
it's a nice idea though
like oh everybody
lets unite and
overthrow them
sharing the secret of the void sentry
even if it's not like
oh well if they did that
then we've all gotta
revolt and fight them
even if it's not like that
there could still be
information
involved in that that is important
for something
I guess the only thing that I could imagine
is that the information
being disseminated like that
would mean that even the marines would turn on the world
government and so it would be everybody
in the world fighting against
this guy at the top
yeah
if it were if it were
if it were like
I mean if they're doing
I mean it seems like they're doing
like
the worst war crimes imaginable
like blowing up whole islands
with the freaking
pluton or whatever
there's pretty much nothing worse you can do
in this world than that
yeah
it would be the sort of thing that would
justify
good characters being in the marines
yeah there already are
some good characters in the marines like we've got
Kobe and stuff and like Kobe must be part of
like a marine network that's trying to
like change the marines from the inside
so
I feel like that's it's not
necessarily the case I think he's like he's a marine
and he's trying to do the right thing
and there are lots of marines like that
and I think even on
some level Ikeino is like that
they're not like
yeah I feel like if the information
about the void sentry was leaked
a lot of marines
that are like Ikeino is the sort of
character who like
is very honorable
and does like
you know he's very strict
but if he learns that he'll be like
I can't in good conscience
support this any bit longer and he'll be like
ah cool like a bad guy turned good moment
isn't Ikeino like a complete bastard though
yeah I mean yeah but like
he's only a bastard in the way that he's like
you damn pirates
I kind of think I don't know my impression
of Ikeino is that he
would justify like
anything like in this for the sake of like
peacekeeping or whatever
he'd be totally fine with war crimes
I don't know
could be
I don't feel like he doesn't feel like
final boss evil
I guess neither does Blackbeard
in the same sense that like Blackbeard's
just self-centered he just wants power
yeah
I just like I like the trope of
I just really like the trope of the guy
who you don't expect to be a friend
will be friend you
when is needed
maybe
like oh Luffy and Ikeino like
I killed your brother but we got to kill
the world government instead
but that's all
that's for later for now
we gotta
prevent war crimes Luffy
I mean he came here to kick ass
and prevent war crimes
and I'm all out of ass to kick so
let's prevent some war crimes
I guess I don't know
like Fujitora definitely strikes me
as a good marine
who is just doing his job
and would revolt
against the world government if it came to it
Ikeino is a one you wouldn't expect
which is why I like the idea
but yeah there's like Smoker
there's Kobe, Helma Po
who else
there's a few other marines I think
there's that old lady
who's always around
to me
in my mind
Ikeino sort of represents
like pretty much the worst
of the worst elements of the marines
he's the one who will like
dispense
justice that is
and that justice can be as brutal
as it needs to be and he doesn't care
as long as it's like justice dispensed
by the book
I suppose
I guess
I don't think I've heard
that the marines have become
more evil under Ikeino
like it's not like
the marines have started to become bad
people more so than under
Sengoku
I mean they're already bad
I know that but you know what I mean
Yeah
Sengoku is kind of a good guy
but the marines were still bad
still bad
I don't think there's anything
that's necessarily changed
I don't feel like anything has necessarily
changed at least not like
explicitly with Ikeino being in charge
oh my god the societal issues
they were systemic it's not just
about replacing the one guy at the top
oh my god
oh my god you mean it's just about
investing individuals
with the power to
fucking oppress people at will
and that's the problem
no
that would say something about society
I love One Piece
I do
it's true
yeah you know it is unlikely
that Ikeino would like be a good guy
right at the end
but it's wishful thinking because I just
love the trope I just love that trope
yeah he would have blown up the earth
he really would have
and then he got beat up and he's like
oh I love that do it again
yeah but I mean
Vegeta had
motives
I understand I mean I'm in shirt
Ikeino could have motives
that might
affect his behavior
when I was a little boy
and he took a shit
on my favorite toy and I cried
and then from that day on
I said I'll kill that pirate
now
but now I realize
that the marines shit on even more
toys
they shit with our giant lasers
I think
the One Piece
is the friends they made along the way
true
we are One Piece
of the puzzle
of life
the One Piece is
world peace
I mean
you know what the One Piece is
have I said what I think the One Piece is
I think so I forgot though
what did you say
to me
the foreshadowing
seems clear
that the One Piece
refers to the unification
of the four seas
which will be achieved
by destroying marriage war
and shattering the red line
and combining the four blues
into the all blue
it's the one world
the unified world
is the One Piece
that comes with implications
that whatever happened in the void century
was
is like maybe involved
the ancient weapons building
the red line to split everything up
and put marriage war right at the top
maybe
they earth bent
the red line into existence
using an ancient weapon
like there was no marriage war
and no red line
actually
the red line is a very
makes them easier to control
if they can like split them up
and it's like a
maybe a parallel
to like the Berlin wall
and things like that
I kind of never even really thought about it
but yeah you know
the red line is a very strange geographic feature
maybe they might have created it artificially somehow
so yeah
I definitely agree with like
the red line of marriage war
being broken and then all blue and all that
that's a good theory
and I think
will definitely come to pass
the fact, what's your name
the mermaid oracle
or whatever
the one that like prophesied
that would destroy fishman island
and then because
fishman island is directly below marriage war
marriage war, yeah
then they're going to be
falling on them
it's going to be pretty fucked
it's not going to be good
it's not going to be good for those guys
in particular
yeah and then
of course
red line gets broken, laboon comes through
and he's like haha it's we laboon
and then brooks finally meets him
oh wait I forgot
the one piece actually
refers to brook and laboon
reuniting and becoming one pair
of best friends forever
yes
and that's why roger laughed because he didn't know
who laboon was
yeah of course
he said laboon
haha what does that mean I don't understand
anyway I'm going to die of cancer
now goodbye
exactly
what did that's
roger laughed when he saw
one piece right when he saw what was on
rafthel
he went to rafthel and it was like
either a pony glyph or a treasure
or I don't think it was the one piece
or maybe it was
it must have been something
left by joyboy
wait a minute
one piece is the name for roger's treasure
roger left something
and that's one piece
so he didn't find one piece
one piece didn't really exist before roger
unless
I mean I guess he could have found something
yeah
he went to rafthel
yeah that was the thing
roger searched the entire grand line
and he figured out the void sentry
by reading the pony glyphs
and that made him
probably reading the final pony glyph
and learning the secret of the void sentry
is probably what made him laugh
yeah and joyboy
I think there was a thing on rafthel that joyboy left
like either a story
or like a pony glyph special
something that they
yeah so the previous
presumably the previous user
of luffy's devil fruit
and so
he laughed when he found
either the knowledge or the item
that contained the knowledge
and they just like ha ha
I've got freaking chills
I can't adequately
express how much
I get out of
one piece is like thematic
use of like
smiling and laughter
and joy
it's like so good
they have such big smiles
they have such big teeth
they sure do
that's how I knew
that's how I know this marine was a fishman
because he had spiky R long teeth
and funny BDAs
that's how you know
that's the tell
sometimes
unless they're like a different kind of fish
doesn't have that
and that's not the tell
well do we have anything else
to say about one piece
oh sorry
next week
we will not have a new chapter to talk about
no the podcast
will only be two hours long
and everyone will complain
that's okay
that is okay
you're right actually it's perfectly fine
you want to go to voicemails
uh yes
alright end of one piece discussion
end of one piece discussion
you can now continue listening
that was Marty saying that
yeah
okay next
the first voicemail
the first voicemail is called
you know are you ready
3, 2, 1, go
so yeah
the last one was this
first season finale
of my saga
you know I'm just being cool
if I'm being too annoying
too schizophrenic
I can
settle for a little
just being cool you know
just being cool
just being in the olympian fall
secretly all on
I have a foreskin so
you know
just being cool
very cool
I'm proud of you
I'm jealous
next one is called
oh
yeah it's a vocary link
okay 3, 2, 1, go
hello
I do not hate
mage
do you think I'd want to kill her
just to spite her as a reviewer
no that's a terrible thing to do
come on
okay
that was a voice of misanthropony
I think that was clips of misanthropony
spliced together
I'm glad he does not want to kill
mage just to spite her as a reviewer
man what a time
what a time in life
lol
okay
next one is
a geef
it's a geef
oh this looks great
this is a
little homestucky
oh
I've got misanthropony there
in the front
and then
gcat
I guess
and butterflies
and then her house is mage
I really like how mage looks
in this little drawing
oh mage is poking out
the little window there
poking out the little window there
that's cute and you know
misanthropony
held outside of the premises
by the iron gate as he should be
he should not be allowed
within 500 feet
uh
alright good
awww
cute
I see the image you posted here
um
next one is called
a dangerous mind
from cock at sleeve dot
ben
3 2 1 go
I can be here all day
and if I send someone
into a spiral through my conversation
with them we're there now thinking all day
sometimes I feel guilty about that
like I really try not to get
so real with people about
what I read in their communication
it's going to like fuck with their ability
to be themselves
because most people
don't know where to go with that
you can't just like experience
an ego death and then just
go back to work the next
day and like
well ok you will
but it will just wear off
basically that's what I'm saying
you can't just be
what the fuck
I don't get it I think it's a little too
out of context
I mean I think it sounds like she is saying
I think this is a little bit like
aww people knew what I was really thinking
it's like
I don't tell people
it's like ok I get it
it's like
I'm so smart and so
perceptive that if I told people
what I can immediately
tell and intuit about them
from the things they say to me
it would literally destroy them
it would break their mind
it would shatter their psyche and give them an ego death
but I don't do that
I spare them from that
because it would be cruel
to impart
that forbidden knowledge to them
they're better off not knowing
could it not be
that you say something about someone
that's untrue and also offensive
and then they get mad
could that also be the case
is that
it is never the case
that like a snap
a snap judgment I come to when I hear you say something
or I see something that you say
it's never me just assuming
it's a profound insight
that I've had into you
every single time
and that's just what you gotta keep in mind
we live in a society
that's pretty funny
honestly pretty funny quote
next one is called
the legend
3 2 1 go
have you heard the legend of Archimedes
no
yeah
isn't Archimedes one of the vagapunks
I was thinking of Achilles
I guess I haven't seen Archimedes nuts
Archimedes
who
jumped out of the bath
and said Eureka Eureka
yeah that guy
and he invented the screw
he jumped out of the bath and he said Eureka
Eureka Eureka
Eureka Eureka Eureka
he said these nuts they Eureka they Eureka
I gotta take a bath to make them smell better
that's why he was in a bath yes
he invented the screw
like he screwed everyone
he invented sex
I love him
do you know about the Archimedes screw
do you know how that works
oh the Archimedes screw
it's a little device
that transport you could transport liquids
up a vertical
oh yes I know about those
they used them in fucking aqueducts
he probably invented
other things as well
in fucking roman something or others
maybe not roman things
he invented it might just be named after him
now that I think about it
I don't know
yeah displacement
yes I know about Archimedes yes I read one piece
isn't he one of the robots
I don't remember
I don't think so
one of them is Edison
I kind of thought one was named Archimedes
oh well
wait maybe I'm thinking
is that the name of like
Night Owls
Night Owls ship
in
Watchmen
or something
I don't know
yes it is
Night Owls little
Fly in Batmobile is called Archimedes
okay
very good excellent
where was I
next voicemail did I download that one
no
okay whatever next one is an image
let's look at it shall we
no you're not
okay
oh this meme I haven't seen this meme in a while
what's all this racket going on up here son
do you remember that
I never see this one anymore
I never see this comic anymore
I feel like I've seen it like a handful of times
you see it all the time
what's going on up here
this racket going on up here son
you're watching your internet talk show again
it's called PCP dead
it's not about drugs and it's not to use anime podcasts
this is where the best of voicemails is a deep intricate lore
that normally you wouldn't understand
watch for a second
so the other day I took a bus to Oldies
and there was a homeless guy on the bus
and he smelled really bad
I talked to the girl and I had to get off the bus
the next stop we started just talking to each other
until the last stop so then I had to find my way back
so that's nice
that's nice dear
son how can you watch this
there's no name
this rules
this dad is the joker
the original is like
the dad is like
oh wait the original has the dad
I know the dad from a lot of stuff
they stopped using the comic
yeah
the original is like
you watching them girl cartoons
again son it's like it's called anime dad
and then the third panel is like
some stupid anime shit
and the dad just
that's one
son how can you watch this
there's no name
what the fuck
who's gonna teach you to be straight and white
what am I doing in this panel
I think you're ironing
a shirt
or something
that's nice dear
I just said
there's a vacant expression on my face
my like glass eyes looking
in two different directions
feels good
no thoughts head empty
next one is another image
another image
let's look at it
let's freaking look
uh
yeah I get it
I get it
now you're banging her Ben
no
it would be
that's where it would go
it would be she's
who's banging who
hang on
it's like
Jeff or whatever
wear your pants
oh I took them off because I was banging your mom for a minute there
and now you are banging her
hehehe like that's the comic
so in this situation
you would be banging her at this very moment
hang on I have to I have to confirm
you can't remember this one that's the best one
I just can't remember the exact
machinations
of it
bro
I took them off because I was banging your mom for a minute there
and now you are banging her
okay
well I think you should switch them
I think Christine should be on the left
and I should be on the right because the
I mean the punchline should be that it ends with Chris
banging her own mom right
and that's not the situation
that's not the situation you've constructed here
well it's
it's past tense
it happened
oh that's right
Chris's mom is not even involved in this situation
this is a misplay
oh that's true
this is Ben's mom
yeah and that's just disrespectful
thanks for the voicemail
so in the other one if it was switch
you would be banging
Chris's mom
well no I think
I should be saying yeah dude
I was banging your mom for a minute there
and now you are banging her
hehehe
that's how it should go
I'm sorry
I'm looking at the original comic again
hehehe
I love it so much
I gotta post it
I gotta fucking post it
I always read it as hehehe
I would say
I guess
I only think of a hair
when it's got an H at the end
yeah that's fair
but I mean I would say if I were saying he
I would spell it with two E's
well that's why
sweet brown hella Jeff
it's so cool
it bugs the trends of normal typing
it makes you think
it makes you
makes you question
makes you question everything
okay
the next one is called
you know
3 2 1 go
what do you think
when you are not
thinking anything
what does your mind go everyday to
I always
go to
monkey
and also
where does your mind go
that's hard to know
I think about
stuff being gay
like this like
like gay
that's gay I don't know
sometimes I just default to thinking about
calling things gay in my head
oops
homophobic
I don't know how to answer this question
I
like
when my mind's not
occupied with any particular thought
I also think
about like aw fuck
I'm gonna kill myself
but in like a funny way
in like a funny and cool way
not in like a weird way though
that's a good default
thought that I have a lot
just like wall kill myself
you know
oh like words I would use
if I was just
making up some song
like a rap
to nothing in particular
and I default to some specific words
like chicken and motherfucker
because I like the
the rhythm they have
but that's not the same as like what thoughts enter my head
when I'm not really thinking about anything
don't know how to answer
I'll have to think about it
um
yeah
gay
gay kill myself
that's pretty much it
I guess you two poop quotes
they enter my head pretty frequently
like lampoil rope bombs
it's yours my friend
as long as you have enough rubies
that's a pretty fun one
mine's not that fun
mine's not that funny
alright next one
download that one
next one is called appreciating ben saint
vomit
3 2 1 go
I've finally been watching ben's
winnie the pooh retrospectives
and they're good I like the videos
one of these days
but I've noticed that like
either it's because
ben has become
funnier over the years
or it's because
of like the effects of
either more speaking
ad-lib style versus
speaking on a more like
maybe scripted basis
in like more video essay-ish
style in those winnie the pooh videos
but I feel like these days
in like the more modern lecture content
I find
ben a lot funnier
these days
even some like
podcast moment just like random
offhand comments make me laugh way more
than like
anything that's like a scripted joke
in the video
essay thingies
and I just thought that that was interesting
just you know
none of those scripted jokes can live up to
king you nerd
from the fucking mega man
video I don't know
makes me chuckle
that's funny
that's funny because I did have
a couple of like scripted jokes that I sort of
like wrote ahead of time
in the lecture
I didn't
I did kind of have notes
for the winnie the pooh the winnie the pooh is
off the cuff but I do have like
notes that I'm like pretty closely
following in like the things that I talk about
I didn't really write
many like jokes for it though I wasn't really trying
to be funny
yeah I felt like I mean it's not like
you weren't funny around that time
I feel like the winnie the pooh
videos were like more
deliberately serious
in tone and that's why
I don't like they have
a different sort of feeling than other videos
you had made and other appearances
on podcasts and stuff
well I think I did
occasionally think of like a funny
thing to say
or a joke to put in there I don't think
I did much of that I think I wasn't
really prioritizing
comedy I wasn't really trying to be funny
that much
and I was mostly
yeah focused on like
getting writing my thoughts down
and then discussing my
my like you know just my earnest
thoughts about like
the each episode of the show
so maybe it was just like priorities
is the reason why
I don't think I'm funny
ever
you make me laugh all the time
yeah I make myself
laugh too but that just means
that I'm not funny
because you shouldn't laugh at your own jokes
that's like not good
God I did it again
I was trying to do
like a mean thing I was trying to do mean
spirited like oh you make me laugh
as in like I laugh at you because
you're amusing as a human
specimen
but I don't know how to like
I don't know how to do that
set that up so that it makes sense
no you did great
I had to explain the joke I ruined it
no that's good
oh you got me
no
when will Ben St know that I hate him
oh how I hate him
that Charlie Brown
was it like that Charlie Brown
what a guy what a guy
what a fellow that Charlie Brown
and then as soon as he's off the screen
how I hate him
yes
I guess I don't really have anything else
to say I should finish that one
we need a poo thing
there's just not enough
time in the week
I can't believe it's another week already
another week got away from me
as they do
alright enough
next one is
an image
there it is
it's I believe it is you
and Munchie
yes but why are we
individually
why are we saying these things
oh is it like split
like not split personality
like swapped
you would usually be the other way around
I
I feel like neither of you say either of these things
no me either
I feel like there's a joke here but like I
I'm not getting it
like why because you got a long neck
yeah what's what's up with that
yeah I don't know
I like that I like my face
I look like Simpsons
you do
I like Munchie's curl
highlights
textured
feathered
I
I don't know what else to say about this one
if there's a joke I don't get it
sorry
next one is
an album
new PCP logo
oh
I get it
is this a rebel pixels
joke or is it just
I think it's just our colors
even though mine is not really
that's that's too blue that's more of a
DeVue color that's more of DeVue blue
than Gibb turquoise
I do like that blue though
look nothing nothing against that
I'm all about those Aquamarine
blues and greens
nothing against that particular blue
just bluer than what I was
imagining
also blue in the face
I mean those two
the two do look good together
that blue and that black
yeah
it's funny
the other seven just empty
just gone desolate
no
I think
do we already talk
maybe on the stream I think we talked about
I think I floated the idea of
the logo for
the perfect comic party
new channel logo
yeah yeah
we will debut that at some point perhaps
I'll maybe work
yeah I'll maybe work on
drawing up a more
proper version of the
the logo
the title today
oh it's exciting
it gives me a hopeful
feeling about the future
the first time
ever
next one is
Rod Serling
Slime and
Editing
3, 2, 1, go
for now finally the day has come
the books are edited
printed and out the door
then the reviews roll in
and opening up twitter you are horrified
to find
too thin
this book is too thin they say
why aren't there more pages with less information
it's been seen
girth shaming or something
you're cancelled IRL
and wither into a cyber realm
and you realize what you should have realized
there's always
always
something wrong
true
it's true that is a nightmare
and I think that we should
I think we should normalize
cyberizing people into cyber elves
as a punishment
that was like the worst possible fate
cancelling somebody
so they turn into a cyber elf
they shrink and contort
no more body
no more physical
incarnation in the physical world
to cyberspace with you
cyber elves
can appear in reality
but only briefly is that how they work
they can appear in reality
but they can't do anything
most of the time
they can't do anything without
pretty much expending all their energy
and basically killing themselves
so they're like a cool flashy looking ghost
yes
exactly
a cool flashy looking ghost
that has a
that usually has like a one time
like
thing they can choose to die
to accomplish if they feel like it
but some of them
making a cup hover
um
yeah and then they're just gonna
that's the last thing they ever do
yeah
they're like a cool looking ghost
you can see
um next one
do I have anything else to say about that
um the book is
the book is probably gonna be
it's looking like the index is probably gonna be like
50 to 60 pages
so looking like the total page count is gonna be like
260 pages
that's pretty thick
that's pretty good
that's pretty girthy I would say
about 60 of that
so about a fifth of that will be
which is fine
you know whatever
next one is
he had to confirm
3, 2, 1, go
ah Ben's saying is just like
Ben's just
getting a voicemail of someone
shitting their fucking bottles out on the toilet
diarrhea farting into the toilet
and he's just like
oh no
listen don't play it on the episode
but I have to listen to
the whole thing
it was gross
just a second more
oh
I have to confirm that it's just shitting
it's like
can you imagine if I could smell this
too
imagine if I put your hand
into the bowl and scoop some of it out
oh god that would be so fucking gross
that would be so crazy
unless
look
I was like already halfway through it
so
then you can sleeve halfway through it
so I was like well I've listened to this much of it
I might as well
listen to the rest
ah god
you gotta learn to jump shit
you gotta learn to run away
you know
just like with a slime and punishment book
at some point you gotta cut and run
you gotta call it done
I've heard enough of this shit
literally literal
and it's time to end it
next one is called
slime times weekend update
number ten part one
three two one go
hello rowdies
rowdettes killers
and the rest give asked
and here we are again
there are no female killers
killsers
sorry
the old head
he promised to give it once 15 people
had made art for him
and the gangs took to ms paint
beautiful art was made
and the relic was finally awarded to a killer
known as stin bug
also endless war seems to have been getting
a mighty migraine from all the new cops
roaming around the streets
because people have been encountering numerous
anomalies upon dying
from staying dead
in featureless voids
to speak of
and no data
or your data being completely
swiped from existence
oh my satan the pain won't ever end
tech developers are hard at work
in endless wars bowels
to see if they can fix things
for interview they had this to say
oh maybe this wire
and then oh god oh no
dear christ
we wish them the best of luck
onto the next part
levy jevy was around that's crazy
that guy is fucking
that guy disappeared into the
into the freaking deaths
that's wild
wow
and yeah get up all in those bowels
anyway next part is part two
three two one go
part two finally
right after the graffiti contest was judged
suddenly a fiddle by the name of
morty came out in front of the crowd
and assassinated the mayor
bang execution style
the mayoral role was all rabs
and friends have already begun to backstab
and slander each other over it
there's no telling what will happen yet
but if the last mayoral election
was anything to go by
we should expect nothing but good things
I've heard it now under the authority that
captain metalhead is running on
the mayor lord of ghost
to electric boogaloo
I like the sign of that
maybe the second time
that's it for this one and remember
the slime time is the best time
oh yes
and we at the redaction
of the
slime times weekend update
we're very excited to hear about
the new zine
or karmic
strip shonen jump
eskstein coming out
and the suggestion that perhaps
there should be a slime time
section mentioned
we would be more than happy to contribute
if that was ever wanted
anyways
goodbye excited for that
either way
yes
if you provide the article I will definitely
print it in the
the issues when we start
making them
there used to be
those guys used to make
the actual slime times newspaper
they used to make a digital
publication
I loved that
we could
bring that back a little bit
this is going to be so cool
because it's not just going to be like
oh on the cover what do we put
we put the comics that are in here
so my character
your character that's it
no we can put a slime thing
on there now if we have like an article
we have a little thing like oh secret
like news about this thing
we could make
the front cover really busy
I love busy covers
it would be
that's fun
I like the idea
I like the idea of having
a lot of people
just kind of that have stuff to contribute
but
I mean I would want to be
picky about it
I mean the slime times weekend
update is great so if they just
turn that into text
it's going to be fine
it's going to be good
I know we let you guys
I know we let you guys get away
with anything in these voicemails
and we have no quality control
that doesn't mean
yeah
I'd like to see
I'd like to see a little
endless war news
honestly pretty funny funny idea
to throw it in there
yeah have a late to the discord
mmm
definitely want to leave that discord
okay next one is
it's an
and a voicemail
oh there's a voicemail too
let's freaking look
oh it's um
the levy jevy art gevy
okay
oh my god let's listen first
yeah okay
three two one go
oh and by the way
here is a compilation of all
the beautiful ms paint drawings
created for levy jevy's art
giving extravaganza
for which eventually
to thin bug once again
a relic was awarded
even though prince valiantly
did try to
pry another relic off of his head
did not work
it's him one of the art pieces you'll see
alright
goodbye tata
tata
okay I'm
scrolling through them
had a relic with him
when art he said
I will relinquish to the living or the dead
but only once your numbers are
15 together
15 pieces of art I say
wait where does it say this
oh this first one
aww this is cool
what is it what does it do
we pleaded but he would not
tell us is it a weapon
a key
will it save endless war
from his madness
this is so cool
flat cap
cigar stump
what am I looking at
this is a shooting for typical
mafia gooner kind of look
a you got it bus kind of guy
a bully demeanor towards his lessers
who wouldn't bend my eye to pushing around
juvies or unprepared opposing gangsters
oh my god smear through something
smear
I'm scrolling
endless war penis
you put all these on screen
can we show all these
there's a lot some of these I had seen
around
this is shooting for
oh there are quite a lot
there's I think there's 15
okay well let's not
we can't dwell on them but
these are
marenpan
marenpan one
marenpan was one of the two winners
of the graffiti contest
the other day to finally judge
after like three months which was interrupted
by the assassination of the mayor
and the announcement of the new contest
which is the mayoral election contest
the mayoral campaign contest
mark two
I thought a smear was called smore now
oh really
you know I don't know
maybe that's true
maybe not in endless war
I'm not sure
I hadn't heard
this art is really good
I mean they're really good
at art
I really like their stuff a lot
ah
okay let's
I could look at these for a while but I won't
next one is called
well it's an image
I'm starving all of a sudden
I'm so hungry and oatmeal
I haven't had oatmeal since last night
ah
okay small minds discuss politics
average minds discuss pokemon
great minds discuss circumcision
I hate you Eleanor Roosevelt
I'm glad you're in hell
because you said that
next one is called radical action
to unseat the hold of Trixie
hate mind
three two one go
was that your like
like was that like
your like rep for a bottle
no
put a beat on that
that was just Buddhism
nah there was a beat there
there were some bars in that
uh oh
damn it's time to coax that fucking blunt
it's time to fucking smoke up
and escape this world
and taste this cycle of yearning
and dissatisfaction
we gotta escape the Dharma
and achieve Nirvana
it's time to free myself
from the shackles of this mortal coil
but first I'll
have another scoop of ice cream
actually part
wait what be fartin
this guy be fartin
I forgot that was in reference to but yeah
yo this guy be
this guy be fartin
that was great
that was um I mean my rap
you know in hindsight it wasn't
particularly uh rhymey or
but you know what the beat really
uh uh uh
propped it up pretty effectively
so
thanks
that was a good one
okay next one is a twitter link
you can now wish list
ena dream barbeque
on steam
I saw this
it's uh you know ena
is that that blue and yellow thing
the blue and yellow um girl
uh in the weirdo world
yeah I've seen a video
of that I guess
nah they're making a video game
with quite impressive animated cut scenes
it looks like
hmm um
okay I'm trying to watch the video
it's lagging a little bit for me
um
hmm
oh the trailer contains flash
lights
um
ooh
yeah right
it's it's
looks really good
wow
um
I mean
what is
what is ena about this
well ena is in it
oh okay I haven't
seen her yet
hmm
or I guess she's that girl
she's that girl
something about her ends up
making her into a double faced thing
right
I mean I
I don't really understand what ena is
but I don't really think you're supposed to
yeah it's just sort of
the videos always had
like a dream like quality
of them you know not really supposed to
understand what's happening it's just sort of like whoa
nice
planned release date 2023
hmm
I'll play it
um
like looks like a little you know walk around
uh pick up
things maybe there's puzzles
the
I mean my my initial
impression
the cutscenes
seem very different
from the very small
moments of gameplay
shown there but
I don't know might
work might be I liked
I liked the way I mean the the 3d looks
pretty low poly and low res
but I did like
it being
paired with like the quite
high quality 2d animation
characters in the world the animation
stands out to me a lot more
than the game
which is okay
that's like how the videos are as well
they're like in a weird like windows
98 95
like they something or other
world kind of look like
yeah they're like in like a low
poly sort of 3d
and they sort of like a like visual
novel like the character is kind of
facing you and like talking
at you
yeah yeah
philip cdi as well
the the
fucking hotel mario
the 2d animation is so
good looking
it almost looks like a completely different
thing
but
I'll watch it I'll keep I'll keep an eye on
it
did you uh
have you seen
this girl
I think she's on tiktok
but she's also on twitter
you know what I'm talking about
stop motion
really weird warped like
fucked with audio voice
creepy
staring sort of thing
yes but the one that's like
clicking on stuff like an adventure game
yeah an adventure game
and then she usually kills you
she usually kills you or
something
yeah something
help me find my dog
you must be the
baby sitter
come in please
yeah
that's great
yeah I watched a bunch of those and I thought they're really good
uh
I think she mostly
does like only fans
she's like an only fans girl and her only fans
she's really unironic like it has nothing to do
with any of that stuff
it's just yeah
but like
that like horror
glitchy like game aesthetic stuff was like
I think it was really making the rounds on social media
like a couple weeks ago
I saw it and I looked into it and I was like
huh this stuff is neat
this stuff is like
I don't know some people call it horror
I didn't call it horror
it's sort of it has a creepy vibe
it's
it evokes a lot of
horror themed
things
it wasn't scary but it was like
this is really creative
I like that it was on tiktok
it was a bit creepy
it was kind of funny like the one where you're the baby sitter and your baby sitting
the fly baby
and then it ends with like
daddy's going to be mad
and she opens the door and like the giant
fly is outside like that made me laugh
like that's just
I'm not sure if it was going for comedy
but it was funny
to me
that stuff I don't know
that's what Ena
made me think of
I don't even remember that girl's name
but
whatever I'm not even
you know what I'm not even gonna look it up
if you're interested
google some of the terms we just said
you'll find it I don't know
spooky girl tiktok
adventure game, cdi
uh
yeah
google girl only fans
girl only fans
look through all of them till you find one
that says they have a tiktok where they do
spooky shit
you'll find it
where
where is it
point and click girl
what?
I'm trying to find it
the one I saw was like
rare items
she was offering you rare items
yes
god
creepy horror game
aesthetic
tiktok
rare items
shit well I have no idea how to find this thing
actually
there's so many things that come up
when you just do creepy girl tiktok
point and click adventure game
ugh
well people know what it is
maybe it's in my it's definitely in my like somewhere
I think probably
some people listening will not know what it is
how far back is it
in my likes
oh it's gotta be like way far back in my likes
okay
yeah maybe if I search on twitter
like
okay okay someone called silk cerulean
asks someone help me
I need to show my friend that one girl on tiktok
who does the stop motion point and click horror scenes
but I don't know her at
two replies
molly moon
oh well I found a person who reposted it
what's it say
her name is molly moon
yeah
this is the rare items
I think I need new glasses
oh maybe I've just been looking at the screen
for too long getting blurry vision
okay well we found it
anyway let's continue
yes play dark and darker
play dark and darker
three two one go
dark and darker will be releasing
for its fourth play test
on february the sixth
you shouldn't miss out
on playing one of the greatest
games ever made
I've never heard of dark and darker
I am just expressing
my honest appreciation
for the amazing
game known as dark and
darker
but seriously
Ben saint
and
Gibb and take and
jesse
and mochi
and nat
and
digi and
tom
I wouldn't want you to
miss out on this amazing
game the play test
is only going to last for like 10 days
and you don't have to pay for it
it's free and it's on steam
it's called dark and darker and it's like
is this a joke I don't get it it's kind of like a roguelike
but
it's multiplayer battle royale roguelike
and it has pve
and it has pvp
it's the worst thing ever
you've got abilities
like two of them
there's not that many abilities it's not like league of legend
and
you get your sword
and you whack skeletons
and the games are
like 10 minutes long each
and I'm just so addicted to it
best game ever
I can't tell if that was
sincere does he actually like this game
I'm looking at the steam page and it looks
it looks like it could be good
but I hate
not roguelikes I hate
battle royales so I don't
I don't think I'll play that but yeah it's a fantasy
first person
something or other do you fight the other players
is that how it's a battle royale
and I'm forgiving hardcore fantasy
FPS dungeon p player versus
player versus environment adventure
band together with your friends and use your courage wits
and cunning to uncover mythical treasures
okay so it's sort of like
it sounds like it's like a
diablo thing almost
you're with your buddies in a dungeon
you're killing stuff
I think it sounds
potentially pretty fun
I don't know where the battle royale comes from
well I see people
like fighting each other in like a big group
in like the trailer
video
so it seems like
they're supposed to kill
maybe you're in a little party and you got to fight against other parties
oh no I see
I see a fortnite like death cloud
so they've got to get to the middle of the dungeon
get the loot
and then get out
I don't
know about the fortnite death cloud
the fortnite death cloud the idea
is that at the beginning of the map
everywhere is available
but slowly the death cloud a big circle
around the map will get smaller
forcing the players to interact
to get closer to the middle
so that like
if the players can't kill each other
the circle will kill everyone
okay
gotcha
okay I mean
looks kind of fun
I don't know if I'll actually play it
but
could be fun
wait
so this alpha playtest has ended
this guy was too late
we read this thing
oh was it
well it might have become
will this
stream next
he left this only 20 hours ago
I think he said that like another one
another test might be coming up
oh no yeah that's right
February 6th to 13th
so I guess come back then
could be fun
next one
is called a Gibbs weekly reminder
to reach the big twist in inscription
no
I'm playing
I'm playing Disco Elysium
and I didn't even get any weekly reminders this week
dab
that means you've forgotten all about the dots
around chapter 2
what even is that nobody knows
it's so like it's funny
because like
I only just realized a few days ago
that this means that you have no idea
who Spampton is
you haven't seen Spampton
I am aware of him but I don't really
I don't know him
there was so much
like hype around
all of the stuff in the second chapter
so much content made
and it's like wow
you don't even know that
you know Jevil
I mean I don't know Jevil because I never fought Jevil
oh
so I don't even know that
look at this Delta Rune noob over here
that's a me
you played long enough to see sands and that was it
you know what
maybe I like being a Delta Rune noob
maybe I'm going to internalize it
and make it a part of my personality going forward
maybe I'll be that guy who doesn't know
about Delta Rune
maybe that's my character from now on
oh no
terrible
oh yeah
you're gonna like it
well that's the last voice
that's the last voice now
alright
thank you everybody for listening
to the show
come back to
if you didn't see the stream last time
we're going to do more of those
become a patron if you want
a million
oh yeah we're going to stream more
maybe not this week
probably
maybe next week
okay yeah I think every other week is like
pretty fair
become a patron if you want
like
50 or so bonus episodes
behind the scenes commentary
things like that
also
to be included on the thank you page of the
upcoming perfect comic party
digitally distributed
anthology
um
yeah
yeah and
I guess we just call it a party because it's a
perfect comic party
we can't just call it a party
it doesn't explain what it is
next week's party
I mean sure if we
if you could say oh it's weekly jump
people will say oh it's the weekly party
it's the weekly comic party
and we should have
an in group
of regular viewers and we should
refer to them as like
we should come up with a nickname for them
to increase their parasocial engagement with us
we should start every
day partygoers
welcome to the perfect comic party
and hey what about this what if we had
what if we had food at the party
and we themed
and we themed the party the podcast
around that so what if we called
it like the pizza party podcast
what if we did it what if we just
did that
I guess what would happen
what would happen
what was the pizza party podcast
disbanded dissolved
what happened to it
it is not dissolved it was
basically
co-opted by dafpina
and the
previous hosts
dafpina moved in
and basically took over co-hosting
with rebel taxi and they
kicked the old co-hosts out
that seems to be what happened
okay so it's just different
so we can't steal a name
not that we could if they had stopped
we can we can
we can?
what are they gonna do
stop us
I think they're gonna send their millions of
pizza eaters
that's called free
that's called free engagement
they're gonna send their pizza eaters
over to us but we're gonna have
our monks
it'll be pizza eaters
versus party people
and we're gonna have our preachers
who are gonna tell a good word of the pizza party podcast
and they're gonna be converted
turned into loyal subscribers
pizza panners
versus party people
party people
and whoever loses we win
I think
I think that's the strategy going forward
I think the strategy for engagement is just
violate the copyright
of everyone and anyone
of people with bigger audiences than us
and then they'll get mad
and then they'll talk about how mad they are at us
and then their fans will come and listen to our show
then they'll become instant fans
I'm
I think maybe I'm gonna start
going by Daft Pina from now on
I think maybe that's my new name
does that make me rebel taxi
yeah that's what it means
no
alright welcome
we'll come back to the next episode
of the pizza party podcast
thanks for listening same pizza time
same pizza channel
next week every week
patreon.com
the procrastinators
not the pizza party
not their patreon
still our patreon
new name same old patreon
old need for cash
we're gonna reinvent the PCP
at the end of every episode now
yeah
what
it's called iterating
you gotta fail faster
you gotta learn to fail faster
we're gonna try something new every week
every week it's gonna fail and we're gonna learn a lesson
and it's gonna make us strong
we're gonna learn a lesson about friendship
we'll write a little letter it's to Celestia about it
every week
the podcast opens with a new bit
wherein we write like dear princess Celestia
here's why today's exercise
in rebranding the PCP has failed
and what I learned from the experience
and how I'll do better going forward
and that's okay you know what
we'll change like next week to the my little
podcast
then we'll be the
talking pirates
talking pirates after that
my little podcast funding is mandatory
after that we'll be
we'll be brad garling house
and then we'll be the dick show
and then the Ralph Rattort
and then we'll be the Ralph Rattort that's right
which keep getting lower and lower
yeah yeah we can find worse and worse
podcasts to become
alright I think this is a
I think this is an actionable business model
great good
alright break we got a plan
alright cool
you want to wrap up
yeah that's it
look out for the perfect
comic party
soon
I don't want it to take a long time
to make the first thing but it will require me
to work hard this coming week
on Clarissa so I'm going to do that
I'll have to do some
I'll have to get back into
Biscuits page I'll have to remember
what the heck was even going on
when I left Biscuits page
and do it again
so that'll be fun
okay
but that's the end of the episode
see you next week bye bye
bye