Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I am the best
guy ever, and today we're joined by an illustrious cast of goons and scoundrels. First up, Ben
Saint.
Excuse me. I'm so sick because my body has been neglected. It's wasted away. What can
I do about that?
Only there was a solution. Munchy, where's Tony Hatch?
You gotta do this podcast quick because I'm melting. I'm about to be a puddle on the floor
in about 10 minutes.
Dude, I love Olaf from Frozen.
Dude, I love the Wizard of Oz.
Dude, I love the nuclear throne.
I skew.
I love water.
Hippocrite is here.
Hello, it's me, the weakest boy at the ball. I can't lift my own body weight. Here I am
on the floor.
Gravity is too strong for this man. And finally, we've got our special guest, the two-time
returning champion, FitMC.
Everyone in this podcast is a homo sapien.
I thought you were saying that in a different direction.
I don't want to think about that anymore.
Well, guys, today, we've done it. As you can tell, we've gathered our... It's time for
the illustrious second half of our world-famous Minecraft and fitness saga.
You were so gung... You just could not wait to do the back-to-back Minecraft and fitness
episode.
That was just your one fucking joy in the entire world. It was ripped from you.
I really was excited about... Ever since we were talking about getting Fit on an episode
of the PCP to begin with, I was really gung-ho to make the topic of that episode, fitness
and Minecraft, the two most inextricably linked subjects in the world.
A complex Venn diagram is generated.
There's a lot of connecting nodes there. It's like a brain with all these synapses connected
through a complex network.
Nate's got a map of the United States up on his wall right now with two thumbtacks
in it, one labeled fitness in the other mind, and he's got lots of red strings going in
between them, but they're just between these two points, so it's not a big web. It's just
a line.
Yeah. I mean, that's true, but so many can actually...
But they're linked. They are fucking linked. You cannot deny.
And they'll sit and he'll stare at the wall for 45 minutes, and then he'll nod to himself
and put up another string, and then the cycle repeats itself.
He spanned the entire yarn around those two points.
He connects the points, and then he just says back, like eyes wide, what does it mean?
That's what we're doing to solve today.
So to get into fitness, it simply must be defined. It simply must be defined. Okay,
now ironically, so the definition of fitness here, okay, here we go. Fitness, the core
of physical health, get off your computer and try it. That is the definition of fitness,
which a lot of thinking memes, emojis going on. What else have we got? There's got to
be a better one. Okay, fitness, here's another one. Fitness, the most important thing you
can have, without fitness, you're a fat homosexual who sits around all day watching movies on
your computer and eating cheez-its to be fit, is to be God, probably.
Urban dictionary is Nate. I think this has been a step.
I mean, it would not... I'm spoiling the future because I definitely will do this one day,
and I should just go in and knowing what the topic is, I should add a section of whatever
I wanted to say on Urban Dictionary the day before. I haven't done it yet, but I should
read it, and so I should ask someone to read it, because you can see who it's by at the
bottom. I should leave a little hint by saying that it was by me, and we'll see if anyone
gets a little hint. By the way, though, I just want to point out, on the list, every
Urban Dictionary thing has a list of related things. The third one down is FitMC, on the
Fit Urban Dictionary thing. Let's read what it has to say here. FitMC, a Minecraft YouTuber
that plays on a popular anarchy server, 2B2T, and in parentheses, also is very fit and muscly.
LaMau, FitMC has huge muscles.
Someone actually wrote that?
This is by anti-socialweeb from July 27th, 2016. That's who wrote this.
It's your biggest fan. I hope he's listening.
I like the example sentence, like used in a sentence, like a lull.
Yeah, it's in LaMau. It's in LaMau.
OfficialWeeb, please leave a comment letting us know, telling us your state of mind.
Right. How are you doing?
This episode comes on the heels of Ufit accomplishing a New Year's resolution, I believe.
Oh, yeah. My New Year's resolution this year, and I said it on Twitter on January 1st, I'm
like, I am going to finally do the one-armed pull-up. And yesterday, yesterday, I did it,
and I was so happy.
That's incredible.
Perfect timing for this podcast.
I just want to clarify, because some people, I've heard it in various circles, they consider
a one-armed pull-up that you have one hand wrapped around the bar, and you can grab your
other wrist and do a thing like that. Is that what we're talking about?
We're talking about just dangling from one arm.
They call it one-and-a-half sometimes.
It's just from one arm.
I just want to say, that is fantastic. Congratulations, of course.
I have long had a dream. Ever since I beat Final Fantasy 7 as a young child, and in the
final cutscene, I have a lot of fitness goals based on the Final Fantasy games.
But at the end of Final Fantasy 7, Cloud canonically does a one-armed pull-up while holding Tifa.
So that's maybe 160, 180 pounds. I mean, she's got big tits, so you know.
Maybe 80 pounds, maybe 40 pounds each.
Realistically, she's maybe 120 pounds to 140 pounds. That's probably about right.
That's about depending on your height.
I don't know.
Let's fucking debate how much Tifa weighs.
If you're talking about Final Fantasy fitness goals, though, mine is to suplex a freight train.
That is my Final Fantasy-related goal.
That's my next resolution, maybe.
I'll just name my other two. One is that Zell did 100 pull-ups before hitting level 1 at the beginning of Final Fantasy 8.
That was before he even joys the party, which I want to do.
And then just to run up as many flights of stairs in a building as Cloud did in Sheen Rage Q at the beginning of Final Fantasy 7.
With the equivalent of doing 100 pull-ups before reaching level 1 being like doing 100 pull-ups and then like doing episode of the PCP Nate?
Yeah, yeah. That'd be great. I could do that.
And you know what? I've looked into it. Doing 100 pull-ups is not like an insane goal to have.
When I was young, my record was 50. My record was 50 when I was in high school.
I feel like I could do a one-handed pull-up, but mostly because most of, like, the rest of my body has no mass to it.
Because you're like a swabloo, you know? There's just cotton balls and fuzz.
Pull-ups are fucking easy, but as soon as I actually get fit, they will be impossible.
Hippo is a drift loon.
As I'm sure you can tell, viewers, there are two fitness gods here and then laymen of varying degrees of disgust.
I would say either, I'm just gonna go on a limb here, either me or Hippo are probably the weakest, the weakest link in society here.
What are you talking about, Monchi? You are an absolute unit.
Okay, we can debate my unitness all day.
But the fact is, is that I don't look like it, but I'm weak as shit.
You would be forgiven for thinking that I'm some sort of weird, strong fat person, but no.
It's not like that, really.
There was this one moment during Radcon 3 where me and Monchi were running to a train and we were sprinting our fucking lungs out.
Oh god, that was the worst moment.
I was dragging my suitcase behind me, but I still ran faster than Monchi, so I think I win.
Okay, well hey, land speed is different from generated force in a punch or a push or whatever you know.
Actually, you reminded me of that, has confirmed, actually, I'm the strongest person to ever exist.
Because I was carrying six grocery bags on each arm, just like pulling them out, running as fast as I could.
Granted, I was huffing and puffing, and I almost passed out on the train, but I did it.
I did it, and the job got done.
There you go. That's some real shit.
Cardiovascular fitness is kind of the area that I want to grow in.
I mean, I don't know.
They say that the group of people in the world who has the highest degree of body dysmorphia is like men, like fit men.
That's what they say, because they're very self-conscious about wanting to be bigger and whatnot.
If you just go and fit on 4chan, you can prove that.
Yeah, I mean, they'll tell you that you're...
I love the images of the gigantic six foot one guide, and then the six foot zero midget freak standing next to him.
Those are my favorite. Those are my favorite.
But I mean, it's a real thing. It's a real thing.
It's always seemed to me that I've been very self-conscious of how I look.
And that's been a big motivator in why I wanted to work out and look better.
I mean, just recently, Michelle put out a video when we were at an aquarium that I was in, and I'm like, oh, I look fat and gross.
And I know mathematically speaking, objectively speaking, that I look pretty decent, but it's just not good enough.
And it consumes me. It consumes me.
It's time to air my dirty laundry.
Time to tell you all. All right, seeing myself specifically in all the videos from Radcon 3,
but especially in the Tails Gets Trolled lecture and comparing them to the Sonichi lecture, I was like, oh my god.
I'd gained maybe like 15 pounds since then, but looking at it and seeing it, I was like, oh my god.
It puts into perspective.
Oh, no.
Yeah, no. It was a wake-up call, so I've started getting back into lifting.
I had let it lie pretty fallow for a long time.
Yeah, I did that one.
That is great.
I'm making it a priority again.
That's why it's really important. A lot of people can just, I think the reason why people get like ridiculously morbidly obese, like in America,
is because they just like day to day is just not part of their lifestyle to like think about that stuff,
because we train human beings totally wrong in this country.
They should be way more conscious of fitness and how to eat healthy and survive and stuff.
I think me and Hippo are going to have a point to do about fitness and school and sports and shit later, so we'll come back.
Yeah, we can talk about that for sure, because they do it all fucking wrong.
I learned everything I know about fitness from like YouTubers and nothing from school.
I learned it all when I was in like late college.
I think you learned it all from Final Fantasy, Nate.
Well, that too.
When I was in college, I got really into like reading up about fitness and stuff.
I went on Fit a lot. I downloaded a lot of e-books and shit.
I was into it for a little bit, not like crazy, but I was like kind of fit.
I had like a pretty respectable deadlift for a little bit.
Yeah, your squats were always, I mean, you would see the squat like, your squats were like good?
Mine have always been utterly disgraceful and I don't know why.
I've been able to squat more than you, even when like I hadn't lifted for a while.
I don't even want to get into my numbers. That would just be embarrassing.
My numbers, you can't know.
I used to deadlift like 300 something and it was pretty sick, but now I haven't deadlifted in a while, so I don't know.
I felt like a cool guy sometimes.
Just FYI of your, a 315 deadlift is fucking disgraceful.
Like you should be deadlifting four plates, five plates, at least.
That's not a joke.
Wait, what are you deadlifting?
I'm deadlifting around three plates, like around 315 right now, which is disgraceful and it's pathetic and nothing.
Ben, what would you say your goal is?
Well, my goal right now is just to like get back into a routine of doing it.
Get back up to what I used to be doing at my best, which was squatting maybe like 250, it's like 245,
deadlifting like 300 something.
My bench was always pretty disgraceful.
My best bench ever was maybe like 165 or so.
I never managed to bench my body weight.
Oh yeah?
Yeah.
Maybe that should be my goal.
Maybe my goal, getting back into it, is like I'm finally going to bench my body weight.
That's a good goal and that's attainable for sure.
Yeah.
Do we have a fitness goal?
Well, now that I did the one-armed pull-up, I'm going to try to do it for reps and then also my other arm,
I can barely get my chin to the bar so I'm a little unbalanced.
But just in general, like just working on my body weight fitness because when I was like in my early 20s,
I was just a lifter.
I wanted to just look like a balloon animal, just hit the weights hard, squats and oats for big gains.
Go mad every day.
Yeah, I know, right?
In my later 20s and living so close to the ocean now and I do a lot of stuff in the water,
I kind of appreciate being at a lower weight because I feel like I can do more athletically like climbing, swimming, surfing.
It's hard to do that stuff when you are a higher body weight just because of all the lifting.
Yeah, that's true, that's true.
Well, that's cool.
I mean, I've kind of, I don't know, I want to be Z's, you know, there's no bones about it.
I want to look like Z's.
That's who I, that would be the ideal.
You want to be dead?
If you can do what Z's did and not die.
He died overdosing or something in like some brothel or something like fucking the Philippines or something.
Wait, really?
Yeah, he really did, he really did.
I don't know if he overdosed but something was up with his heart, he had like a heart issue.
Yeah, he had like a heart condition.
It might have just been that.
But it was like he did take like, you know, substance.
I'm sure the steroids didn't help his heart.
Yeah.
I thought he was natty.
Oh, no, no, no, he was not.
Here's the thing about Z's.
His body, because he was so cut and so low in body weight, his physique is attainable natty,
but not in the speed he was able to do it in.
Right, right, right, right.
For those who don't know, by the way, Z's is kind of the god of the fitness board of 4chan.
He's an Australian cunt and he lived fast and died hard.
But he, you know, have you, Fit, have you watched Scooby 1961 much?
He's my fitness icon on YouTube.
I remember when I first started browsing the Fit board on 4chan, I'd watch some of his videos.
Yeah.
And he had some really informative stuff, like there was some form corrections I was able to make by watching his videos.
Yeah, I thought he was a really good fitness YouTuber to watch, really underrated.
Scooby's a goofy. Scooby's a weirdo.
He's super goofy and he's super gay, but, you know, all is forgiven.
Oh, yeah, yeah, forgive him.
We'll give him a royal pardon for being gay.
Yeah, exactly, exactly.
I was just going to say on the subject of Z's, he's made a video about how Z's is a better role model than Jeff's side.
Jeff's side's another, like, world-famous, like, fitness guy.
Because Jeff's side claims to be nady, and he may well be, but it's just that if he really is nady, his physique is unbelievable.
What is nady?
Yeah.
Oh, oh, no, no.
No steroids.
We should define our terms.
Yeah, no steroids whatsoever, just naturally obtaining, like, a good physique or whatever.
Big naturally slim, naturally muscular, any of that stuff.
So, yeah, no, no steroids.
I'm afraid I'm not Natty. My physique is not Natty because I've drank all this caffeine.
I've drank all this caffeine to give myself the jitters to burn off those extra calories.
Well, hey, I'll give you a pass because Scooby definitely consumes a lot of caffeine and calls himself Natty.
Does he?
Yeah, he loves caffeine.
I mean, I was just joking, but I'm surprised. He seems like the kind of guy who'd be like no caffeine,
no fucking, I don't know, polysorbinates or whatever.
You know, Scooby is very much a pragmatist and Scooby recognizes that like, okay, what does caffeine do to your body?
Like, it helps you get energy to do stuff. It has, you know, little to no side effects as long as you don't like take crazy amounts of it.
And I mean, that's really it. And so he's like, yeah, I mean, this seems fine. It doesn't seem harmful.
Because Scooby, what's great about Scooby and everyone, if you're interested in fitness, I would highly recommend you check out Scooby 1961 on YouTube.
He is, he is the goat as far as I'm concerned for learning this shit.
He's conscious of tooth. He's got like two goals.
One, to be super muscly and ripped because he just loves looking that way and God bless him for it.
And then a second goal, probably even more important is to just like be super cardiovascularly fit.
Like he loves doing, he does like half Ironmans. He does like bikes across China and like huge crazy trips and stuff.
Despite having like this huge busly physique and he's a huge guy.
So he's just he's just working towards like these are his goals and he devises strategies to help him achieve those things.
You know, and if you have different goals, well, you got to use some different strategies probably.
But and he's developed all these tools on his website, Scooby's Workshop.com that you can use to like help you with whatever your goals are.
And it's fucking great. It's fucking great.
Let me let me talk about let me talk about goals. Let me talk about like like aesthetic goals.
I when I got into fitness when I was maybe like 20, around 20 or so, I, you know, I was like, man, I'm real ugly and I need to be less ugly.
And this is my only chance. So yeah, sure, sure it does.
But I think I don't say I don't actually think that matters anymore.
Like I really don't think that it makes much difference what you look like.
I'll tell you. I'll tell you what does make a difference, Ben.
I've said this a lot of times before, you know this to be true. It's the beard, dude. It's the fucking beard.
Okay. Yeah. Well, that's a whole separate issue.
Yeah. For me, your beard is iconic. It's fucking iconic.
The thing that everyone thinks about in their mind is the T-Bap Q&A Ben. That's the real thing.
I think most people probably think of the Chris Chan lecture, Ben, but I do think the beard, statistically, I do think the beard is a better look.
It's coming back.
You look like a fucking lumber. You, okay, both you and Nate, this is like a proven fact that everyone like knows you and Ben are appear in the T-Bap Q&A as the most beautiful people
to ever exist. Everyone in the community was like blown away at how you appeared in that video.
And we just look like normal people doing pony videos, you know.
You're so blown away because you were just normal.
I mean, yeah. That's what I thought at the time.
I had a real good-looking beard and I was wearing a very flattering outfit.
Yeah. You look like a lumberjack. You look like a lumberjack.
That was my shirt. I lent it my shirt for that.
No, no, that was my shirt. I got that in Poland.
Okay, maybe you're right. That's my favorite shirt.
It's like, you know, it's his shirt, but you took it from home.
No, no, that's all mine. That was all me.
Ben, you are wrong. That is my shirt that I lent. I'm looking at it right now. That was definitely-
Hang on.
Wait, I think, here, I've got it right here. I'm gonna link you.
This is the mystery that needs solving.
This must be solved.
I completely believe Nate Biasbett has a history of stealing Nate's clothes.
I did not steal those shoes.
Nate left them behind and I went home and I saw the shoes and I said,
are these Nate's? And mom said, Nate left them and said he didn't want them.
And I was like, well, they're cool, so I'll take-
Look, mom was misinformed, all right?
Yeah, misinformed.
And that's not my-
No, I'm looking. That's my shirt. That is my favorite shirt. I bought it in Poland.
I remember.
Okay, all right.
Maybe you're right.
It's not just his favorite shirt. It's not just his shirt yet.
Yeah, that's my-
It's his favorite-
I remember buying it and it was my favorite shirt ever since.
Okay, you might be right.
I'll kill you for this.
Link in the description to give me back my shirt from Ben.
I started starving Indiegogo for that.
Michael, I've always had-
Yeah, tell us about it.
Like a dream, but not a dream since it's something I want to actively work towards,
like, you know, drawing and stuff like that.
But it's one of those, like, side, like, nightmares that I have in my life
that just I hope I stumble into somehow,
but they're not my primary, like, motivating goal in life,
and just hopefully along the road to accomplishing my actual goals,
I will somehow become it.
I want to be a bear.
A big gay bear?
Yeah, a big gay bear, unironically.
Next.
That is my goal.
I want to be-
You're honestly most of the way there already.
I know, dude.
That's- that's-
Imagine, Matt.
Imagine me being like a daddy bar.
Like, it's so easy.
I basically am already doing it.
I already do that all the time.
You should be downloadable DLC for Dream Daddy.
You should-
What is that?
It's actually true.
You can go after if you're looking out.
Let me know.
All you need to do much.
You probably don't need to change a thing about your life.
You just need to start powerlifting.
Yeah.
And probably just eat more food.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Probably eat more food.
Okay, here's the thing.
Eat more protein.
The thing about getting fit and getting swole.
Okay, because I'm all about simplicity.
I'm all about cut away needless complexity and just reduce it to most basic principles.
And I think that something that everyone could internalize and would be better off for it
is this idea that, okay, lifting does everything.
Because lifting-
Yeah, like you said, making no changes in your life.
If you just start lifting or lift more, you can eat all the same shit.
And you will simultaneously lose fat and gain muscle due to the calories being redirected
in your body, due to the new strains you were putting on it.
Oh, but Ben, after I exercise, I gotta go get myself a little treat.
I gotta go get myself a little treat every time I lift.
Gotta hit up Starbucks and get a couple of treats, if you know what I'm saying.
I mean-
That's just how I do it.
Sure, whatever.
And even if you do that, you'll still be better off if you're lifting.
I mean, you will be better off.
That's true.
My dream is to be a barred dad.
But I actually do have a real goal.
And it's not to become a fitness god.
But all I wanna do is just walk.
I wanna have a time in the day for like an hour where I just walk down my street.
Dude, you know who used to take spirited, portly walks?
Portly walks.
Benjamin Franklin.
Wait, did he call them portly walks?
Was it like his version of Winnie the Pooh's stoutness exercises?
Absolutely.
That's exactly what it was.
Wait, wait, wait.
With Benjamin Franklin.
More like goutness exercises.
Oh, he couldn't walk at all.
Too soon.
Get on the ground, county father.
Yeah, I just wanna take more walks and I wanna be able to like go outside more.
Because honestly, I think that's the most alluring thing about being fit.
It's just feeling like you're not dying constantly.
Pokemon go, dude.
Pokemon go.
I feel like I'm dying like maybe 32% of my life.
Oh.
I feel like I'm dying.
Wait.
That's not bad.
You feel like you're dying?
Yeah.
That much?
What do you, like, cause you feel really bad physically?
Is that the idea?
Yeah.
Okay.
All right, Monchi, I have the perfect remedy for you.
I will teach you the secret to becoming fit.
Are you ready?
Oh, shit.
Is it law of attraction?
I guarantee you it's law of attraction.
Law of attraction.
Is it punching trees with your hands?
Close.
Is it sitting under a waterfall?
No, let him sit.
No, I don't even give a shit what the real answer is.
Oh, man.
So, first off, you need to master the exercise that is a fit favorite.
It's called the fork put down.
And if you're able to do these for at least 15 repetitions for three sets, you're good.
Second of all, start an Instagram account for yourself.
And post your progress every single day.
Damn.
So that way, if you fail, it will live on forever in a government database long after you die.
So that is the ultimate motivation to keep going.
Third.
It is public ridicule.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
Oh, God.
Well, third is just eat steroids.
Lots of them.
And you will make it.
Slurp them up.
Yep.
And that's it.
You know, I was going to have my daily Captain Crunch.
You know, I'm just going to pour some steroids on there for good measure.
Yeah, but for real though, having people around to hold you accountable is like one of the best things you can have.
Like exercise groups.
Like with most things.
Yeah.
Yes.
Totally true.
Because it's so easy to just like, even me.
Like I missed like two workouts this week, but I was like sick.
But like the week before, I like missed a day of exercising on like Monday or something.
And it was like, it's like, well, you know, like nobody's around.
I'm just going to, I can just go home and it won't be a problem.
It'll be fine.
And you know, like if someone was there being like, time to go.
All right, Nate.
Come on.
Let's let's fucking get to the gym.
I'd be like, all right, here we go.
And that would be a totally different atmosphere.
And I would like definitely go because like the worst thing for me about like the thing
that prevents me from like actually getting to the gym on days is that like when I'm at
work and I've, and I've dicked around too much during the day, but I have to stay late
to like catch up on the shit I've done.
And then I ended up getting late and I'm like, shit, I got to get home and get to work.
So I guess I'll skip the gym today.
So the solution to me to make sure I never miss a day at the gym is to literally just
have my life together and stick to my schedule so that I actually like fulfill all my commitments
so I can get there and not fuck everything up.
So I mean, it's just kind of like a total life change thing for me.
I don't want to like intimidate, intimidate people away from that thing and like, oh,
my whole life needs to change.
I'm just saying that like for me, that's, that's kind of my biggest hurdle.
Like I know what I'm doing now.
I just got to actually fucking get there to do it.
I don't have.
Oh, you got something to say.
You can see it.
Well, I was going to say, I know for a lot of people, like if you've never done fitness
before, you've never like gone to the gym, it can seem like it's intimidating.
What's cool about fitness is that there's tons of things you can do and not be in a
gym, like even just in your bedroom doing pushups, you know, planks, things like that.
Just to build up basic strength if you're feeling a little too insecure to go into the
gym.
You know, like there's still a lot of basic things you can do without ever stepping foot
in the gym.
So yeah.
And I know a lot of people.
Oh yeah, go on.
Something that has always been the problem with me, not just in terms of fitness, but
with everything.
Is this idea that like if it's not just so, then like fuck it.
So like if I'm on like a routine, like if I'm on like a three day a week, like lifting
routine and I get it and a day comes and like I can't get to the gym.
I'm not like, oh, well, I'll do pushups or cardio or something instead.
I'm just like, I can't do the thing.
Then fuck it.
It's ruined.
Throw it all in the garbage.
That could be a big problem.
Yeah.
And like the solution is either get over that or just like make absolutely sure that your
schedule never fucks up so that you don't have this adverse reaction due to your psychological
problems.
I've never had very much success regimenting like exercise for myself because of like one,
I don't eat that much anyway.
So I don't have like a weight loss problem.
I'm an average weight and it's all fine.
And also I don't really particularly care about getting swole.
So like the only reason I would do exercises because well, it's better than not doing exercise.
But it's always like, I tried it like a couple months, I tried getting up and having like
a doing some cardio or something before breakfast.
And it works a bit, but I keep falling out of favor with it.
And I feel like if I was, if I'm ever going to do like a real fitness thing, it would just
be because I am like doing something else that I also want to do, like learning to play
the drums properly.
Like playing the drums is like that's a pretty good thing to do.
So I feel like I'm not a fitness boy.
I feel like I'm a health boy.
I'm not a fitness boy.
I feel like there's a difference between the two.
Well, you know, that's fine.
But like what about, what about a goal like, and I don't know if you care about this, but
like I personally, I would like to, before I die, run a marathon.
That's a goal of mine.
That's a goal.
And you know, I know people who've gone from couch to marathon in six months, so it shouldn't
really take me that fucking long, but it's not a, it's not a huge priority for me right
now.
But what about like cardiovascular strength, like being able to run for a long time?
Like that's something that doesn't taste like super muscle.
I've always been pretty good at running.
My favorite thing, like my favorite physical thing to do is just climbing on rocks.
I don't, I don't particularly like, like.
Do they call that bouldering in England?
They call that in America too.
When I worked at AstroCamp, I knew a bunch of guys that really liked bouldering.
And in fact, I have with me right now a t-shirt from Boulder Fest, 2000, I don't know, 13
or whatever.
Yeah.
Are you going to BoulderCon this year?
It's just, we all went up to like a local mountain and just like clambered around on some
low rocks.
Yeah.
And they made t-shirts for it.
And it was Boulder Fest.
Just a group of about 20 or so guys just walking up to a cliff and you just know floundering
and just, you know, trying to climb up some rocks.
Like one guy just like puts his feet on a rock face and kind of like kind of kind of
crab walks to the left across it for a ways.
And you know, if he gets a little high, people hold a mattress under him.
There's a couple of guys with some rocks.
What could be better?
And that's bouldering.
Yeah.
I don't know whether I'd like go and with a group of people and do something like that.
But like, I enjoy climbing and getting up high.
So like climbing stairs, climbing up to the top of a big old rock, just being on a cliff,
not jumping off though.
These things, like climbing a tree, I would climb a tree just because.
But I wouldn't like regiment it.
I don't think I'm built for that sort of weirdness.
Just like a gibbon.
It's so weird.
Like a monkey gibbon, you know?
That's what they do.
They climb trees and they swing around.
That's it.
That's all they do.
Pokemon Go, unironically, has been such an improvement on my life.
When I was in Boston, I've easily like walked like probably more than I ever have my entire
life just to get fucking Rayquaza.
That's all that I cared about during my time.
Dude, I fucking.
I had to get as many Rayquaza as humanly possible.
So I walked all fucking over town.
I walked from fucking Faniel Hall down to like the fucking Prudential Center, like over
and over again.
One time I did it like three times in one fucking day.
Damn.
Back and forth just fucking constantly.
Damn those fucking Pokemon.
Yeah.
It was great.
When Pokemon Go first started and I was really into it, I was the same.
I was like, oh, this is going to be great.
I really want to get out of the house and walk every day.
So I did for like months and it was great and I was catching Pokemon.
But then as Pokemon Go stopped being interesting to me for like, it was like, it got really
cold and I just didn't want to go out and it was bad.
I know actually I did go out quite a lot during the winter.
But like, it was just, it just lost, it fell out of favor with me.
And I also stopped wanting to go outside and I was like, damn, I really hoped that Pokemon
Go would just make me be like normal, like going outside and walking and being normal.
I need Pokemons like you take care of my body.
I need them.
Yeah.
I didn't want to rely on Pokemon Go because eventually it will stop being fun and then
I will start walking and it sucks.
Well, eventually the universe will burn out.
That I joined Pokemon Go when I did, well, rejoined it rather, is because I joined when
Raids were already an established thing and Raids are just fantastic.
They are just fucking beautiful.
For those of you who don't know, Raids are when a Pokemon will spawn at a gym and so
you have to take it down together as a group and you have to assemble a team, some sort
of dead squad if you will, to take down the various Pokemon that arise.
And so I'll just be walking, I'll walk like fucking like 10 kilometers one day trying
to find Rekweza eggs and then I'll come across some colorful characters if you will.
In Boston, I just found the craziest fucking people you will ever find playing Pokemon
not just like nerds, but like fathers and mothers and children and weird disabled people.
I've already told the story about the guy who said that everyone Pokemon loves the cock
and couldn't stop saying the phrase, yeah, this Pokemon loves the cock.
He just loves it.
It was this portly fat guy.
That guy, I found people like that all the time.
It was beautiful.
I love meeting urban freaks and Pokemon Go don't allow me to take care of my body, but also
allows me to see freaks and those are my two favorite pastimes is being alive and seeing
freaks.
I mean getting the exercise thing is definitely good because my fucking life is like in front
of a computer and then I go to the gym and like work out for a time and you know do some
time on the treadmill.
Then I come home and get back in the computer and like I don't feel like it's really
that good of a lifestyle like I should probably do way more cardio or spend like any time
outside.
So something like Pokemon Go is just that brings me to walk for like five minutes outside is
honestly a huge change of pace from what I like normally do in a day and just that in
itself I think is really good just to get some fucking sun because I'm the palest motherfucker
at the gym by far and also just to like explore my environment a little bit.
You know that's always nice just to I feel so I feel like such an internet denizen such
a citizen of the internet and like I have very little grounding in my physical environment
if you know what I mean and it's nice to it's nice to have a reason to fucking check that
shit out every once in a while.
I before Pokemon Go and when I got back home I started playing a lot but before that I
didn't really like know my area excruciatingly well like I didn't really like know downtown
San Diego that well but after like playing Pokemon Go for the past couple of weekends
like I've been doing I feel like I feel like local in the place that I live I feel like
I know my way around the city and it's just like culturally enriching I would call it
like it feels good to be a part of the world and inhabit it.
Community day I've gone to two now or I guess three and they've all just been complete joys
communities are it's a special day Pokemon Go each month where a special type of Pokemon
spawns extremely commonly and so I will go down to Bow Park which is just like a beautiful
section like like strip of like stores and museums it's absolutely beautiful I'll go
there and there will be crowds and crowds of people and it will just be fantastic be
able to see people there and just walk around back and forth catch Pokemon and talk to weird
freaks.
Also fun fact shout out to Brianna a fan that found me during last community day I was
doing a raid and then I turn around and there's someone who's like hey are you munchy I love
the procrastinators I what the fuck do you know it was great she found us through Unate
by the way through like my channel yeah okay okay like anime shit I guess yeah that's cool
anime bullshit shout out Pokemon Go is the literal Bible it is the Bible it's the Quran
and did you mean form well Pokemon Go is definitely great it's definitely great I don't know is
that anything else that is even close to like what Pokemon Go is in terms of like of course
Nate how could you forget Jurassic Park alive the most premier game to be releasing this
summer Jurassic World alive go there click the link in the description to see the promo
trailer everyone get ready for Jurassic World alive is it just Pokemon Go is it just Pokemon
Go but yes fucking dinosaur but we've already got Charizard and like you know you're a
fucking T Rex from Jurassic Park TM I mean you're not wrong dude you're not fucking
screenshots of Jurassic Park okay right fucking well all right all right Pokemon Go is great
and all but I want to talk for a minute about the insane levels of fitness and dexterity
I've achieved through my incredible MLG Gamer skills my finger dexterity is through the
fucking roof those those fucking kingdom hearts final mix bosses they have definitely by the
T Rex looks dope as fuck it's looking excellent this looks quite goofy it's just great it
looks pretty funny he looks very fuck teeth okay let's seriously talk about if video games
have had any positive impact or coordination don't claim to be a musician unless you play
video games I mean I was gonna say that I feel like playing guitar does it better but
I also play a lot of video games so who knows which one influenced the other John Lydden
fucking Jimmy Hendricks get the fuck out of here I'm playing I mean if we're talking
about fitness and gaming I can't believe we haven't mentioned the all-time great for fitness
and video games DDR I was yeah DDR man there it is there it is didn't it used to like track
your calories burned or something yeah it was like a workout mode yeah I used to do that
Nate remember remember remember the good old days playing pretty damn good at DDR pretty
good DDR Max 2 DR Max 2 there were a couple of there were a couple of songs I'm trying
to remember a couple of a breakdown yeah and that's why I'm aesthetic of DDR and I
always want to fly those people that can just fucking go ham to my knowledge though I still
could a video game that you wouldn't think maximizes fitness and turns you into a health
God but I've learned does is VR chat I've been recently what listening to a lot of radio
pros that gets host by young Rikowski actor of Parker do 91 and one of the hosts he has
his name is Dewey and Dewey is this guy who goes on VR chat every night and gets so wasted
dancing and raving in the virtual weeks and like communicate with like serial killers that
sometimes he'll just like he'll like like pass out with the VR on after drinking so much then
just wake up and continue like raving all fucking wow this is like lost like five pounds just
just straight up raving in VR that's just all you fucking guys I mean with like dare reason like
in that sock members I mean the cool thing about VR is it does make you move your physical body
which is cool yeah yeah you've got an Oculus Rift I do I do and it is so close getting me one
two you were so close I was a couple a couple hundred a couple hundred more more dollars a
couple hundred more dollars and we could yeah yeah next time that would have been ready to be our
dude incredible Matt dude imagine imagine playing endless war in VR next base hey can you can you
play Minecraft in VR could you use the slime mod well I mean then fucking Lord of Ghosts
dude dude Lord of Ghosts slime in VR holy shit yes please I played with the texture pack you made
and but no not you made that one of the characters Lord of Ghosts is made not anyone here and it's
beautiful it's simply beautiful so wherever you are Lord of Ghosts thank you for the present and
incidentally we brought it back around to Minecraft I told you they were intricately like
this is one of the many connecting nodes that I've mapped out on my fucking red string chart
yes excellent let's talk about how school has ruined fitness forever and it's made great
think that running is evil yes I had I had a tweet a couple days ago because I just had this
thought about like how I'm sure a lot of people got turned off from taking care of their body
fitness ways because the only way you could do fitness at school is competitive sport and if
you're not on the winning team you feel like shit and so there's a lot of sports with with
fitness means that people who don't like playing tennis or football yeah end up not trying to
exercise it's also just the simple fact that it is a game like like sports are a game that you play
with like objectives outside of the fact of fitness being fit helps you play sports like you don't
play sports to get fit really yeah like don't get me wrong I understand I think the idea behind it
they're like ah we'll make it a game it will be fun because it's fun we'll basically be tricking
these kids into like being healthy and shit like that's like the logic behind it that's why like
we play like dodgeball and shit we're you know fucking young wherever you know that that's fucking
banned now or whatever but like yeah like in like we had health class and we had like Jim and these
were like totally separate Jim was just play some semi-fit games or like run around the track like
once or twice and it was like it was embarrassed it was like terrible and I hated it of course
everybody hated it and like health class I just learned that it was like an elective it was shit
it was embarrassment it was nothing we need to fucking teach people about fucking like what the
fuck is a calorie like how do you okay like fit was saying before about like the doing doing reps
of his favorite exercise the the fork put down the fork put down is a great exercise but I've got
one that I learned from my voice is that a gardening thing no you're shoveling soil around and then
you put down the fork you pick it back up move some more soil I'll get you fit I mean that's
that's true that's true but this is the exercise I'm thinking of it's the it's called the loaf
turnover and this works with it with a large variety of different instruments it's like when
you got a bread loaf before you put that motherfucker in your face you perform the loaf turnover and
you turn it over and you look at the fucking nutrition facts label on the back of the goddamn
thing before you eat it and so many people don't even know that like everything you need to know
for the most part like 99% of what you want to know about a food is just on the label how many
calories are in it like the amount of the grams of sugar that are in it like and and particularly
with the loaf turnover specifically like reading like white bread the thing is when you make bread
you use like only part of the grain to make like white bread that gets removed so that's just like
the pure white fluffy stuff but like what like whole wheat bread has way more like fiber and
actual vitamins and stuff that's actually good for you not just pure carbs so you want to eat
more of that shit and like if you turn over and you look at the ingredients and you see it says
100% whole wheat and it says 100% whole wheat in the ingredients and doesn't you know give
any bullshit then you know ah this is good like this is what I should be putting in my body
though I mean there's another case like bread is just like you should just not eat bread but the
one thing about food and calorie counting that I always hate is that I don't I don't care I would
rather like I would rather learn how to cook vegetables to make them tasty and then just eat
that because I know vegetables are just good and you should yeah I mean the simpler it is the
simpler the solution is the more people will actually do it that definitely makes sense it's
just like I you know since I've been sort of in this world for a while now like there's two
ways to approach it Scooby himself advocates like he advocates for like simple substitutions to make
it as easy as possible because he knows like realistically that's what people who are just
starting will be like willing to do like cut out soda just start drinking water like someone could
conceivably do that and like lose a bunch of weight and feel better about themselves oh but
like I mean you know it's tough but people can do it but like the real ultimate goal for everyone
in the world ultimately should be to like gauge their BMI know how many calories they need in a
day have a direct fitness goal count their calories count their macro nutrients and make sure
they're doing all this stuff correctly every day and like formulate their diet so that they're
getting what they need for their goals whatever those may be okay but that's a lot to ask of
people I mean some some goals can be quite vague you want to be like huge you want to be a big
huge boy with more less yeah yeah with big old muskles I don't like I don't particularly care
about having like a large mass I feel like I'd rather be a compact lad like you punch me but I'm
made of steel you know you want what you want what Michelle said you all Michelle describes as
lean muscle lean muscle she's always talking about it's like it's just like normal muscle only 10
times as dense and powerful she'll buy these like bullshit products it's so dense every single
ligament so many black hole you're so fucking dense I actually read this I read the series called
it's called it's like history's strongest warrior Kenichi or something it's this manga it got made
into an anime yeah like at the beginning of the series it's about a guy who goes from like a normie
he starts doing like fitness specifically to like learn karate to like defend himself from some
bullies or whatever I did escalate to whatever but like at first he's just a normal guy and he
wants to get ripped and like the guys of this dojo he stumbles upon like all huge and muscly but
like the guy who's training him is this like normal looking dude but then and so so he's like
following that guy's training regiment and he's not gaining any muscles like well dude what the
fuck I'm not like getting ripped what the hell but later on like turns out like that that that
normal looking guy like his shirt falls off and you can see he's just like super tight and his
muscles are glistening he just looks normal size he's like wait what and then Kenichi like
looks himself he's like wait I my muscles are so dense I've been developing lean muscle and they
describe like a different type of muscle that this guy has been cultivating that doesn't make any
fucking sense like this is like completely made up like slow twitch versus fast twitch muscle or
something I don't really think that's a real thing right there's like maybe they describe it as
pink muscle muscle confusion some muscle confusion stuff isn't that just some shit to like
develop like more power when you're like I mean I guess it makes sense the whole point was the
guys in 300 did they all did like muscle confusion workouts to like huge muscles not yeah well what
the fuck is muscle you do it different different exercises all the time so your body never gets
but that's just a way to build a muscle faster I think I think my body disoriented that's how
I mean kind of yeah but fit did you have a comment yeah the easiest way to see the comparison is
look at a sprinter versus a marathon runner like Usain Bolt is a sprinter and he is huge and then
if you look at a marathon runner most of their bodies actually look like shit aesthetically
there's a huge difference between muscles that are meant for endurance and then muscles that are
meant for explosiveness if you train your body for explosiveness you're gonna have more size but
if you're training for endurance you're not gonna have as much size and it's not going to be as
aesthetic yeah and when I play Dark Souls I put all my points into endurance so like I want to
roll more but all I'm saying is that this Kenichi guy was training to be a fighter so you want
explosive power he's not trying to be a marathon runner so I'm just saying it doesn't make any fucking
sense oh but I think later I think later he does the other type of muscle he has both he's like
later later on he gets huge this is just like his first regiment where he develops his like first
power base I didn't read it that far but I you know I've kept up every once in a while yep what
one of my side nightmares that I hope I still want to which will help like accommodate me also be
coming a bear is I want to become a world-class chef and have seven restaurants exactly okay
extremely obtainable as a side one of my seven Cooper hotels I just want to be able to like cook
like real fucking food and like not not have to rely on like like going to like I don't go to fast
food ever really but I don't want to have to become you know rely on like restaurants or anything
I want to be able to like know my real shit be able to like cook actual real like you know like
vegetable fried rice and real shit in the comfort of my own home I think that's extremely desirable
and that would be yeah totally becoming like a health boys but not like relying on I have to
like get shit I can just make shit myself that's definitely a great thing to do I've like I've
wanted to do that I'm honestly just like too lazy to put in the time to do it I've been like I've
been ordering a lot from like Grubhub and stuff and like I generally aim towards healthier meals
you know like getting like grilled chicken instead of like fried and stuff and stuff along those
lines just very simple stuff and I have a lot I take a lot of like protein powder and stuff throughout
the day and yeah cooking is easiest to like get into the habit of knowing your way around a
kitchen by doing your own breakfast when you're really sleepy because you're so sleepy you can't
you can't decide you can't think to yourself ah fuck it you're so sleepy you can't even do that
you're just sort of like okay put that there but a crack an egg smash you know you're just sort of
like and then before you know it something goes on a plate and you better eat it and if it's bad
you better do it good next time so you're making a lot of breakfasts quite good that's that's that's
good but what by doing it when you're like sleepy you you just do it and you don't even have the
energy to question yourself you just go through the motions okay okay a lot of it too is that if you
have food in your house that is readily available to eat like without preparation you're more likely
to eat that so if you keep materials in your fridge that you have to prepare mm-hmm you you're
pretty much guaranteed that you're gonna start cooking a lot more often like many times when I
go shopping I'll get like tons of eggs tons of uncooked meats and stuff like that and when I have
that in the fridge I'm more likely to cook than I am to like you know eat a cookie or something like
that yeah having like a bag of chips around is a dangerous game when you are trying to like get
yourself into cooking more and you know like get yourself focused on like you want to be in an
environment surrounded by the kind of food you want to eat because if that's all that's around
that's all you're gonna eat and as long as you you know it's totally totally great point and I'm
gonna rant a little bit here one thing that is a huge contributor to obesity especially in American
society is that a lot of people don't realize they're drinking their calories because it is if you
look at obesity cases it is almost impossible to get that fat just eating food alone yeah if you're
drinking a lot of those calories okay yeah drinking the calories is a thing that I realized
that I like I was totally willing to give up drinking calories because like I don't mind the
taste of like diet drinks so like I know that they've got their own problems and their own
their own health issues associated with them but I never ever drink calories I've switched
entirely to diet soda I think the people who are like I think the people who think diet soda is
gross are idiots and I hate them that's all I have to say about that like why why why would you
drink your calories because they honestly this is not to be me it's just people just don't think
about it they just this is not like in their consciousness to like worry about what they're
consuming people need to be so much more conscious about what they put inside themselves and like I
really think that is the issue for we need from cradle to fucking grave we need a complete revolution
in like I don't know like for if you live in like uh like Greece or or Japan or someone like
Mediterranean or like coastal like oceanic places like those guys don't have obesity problems
because the food that's around is just like the Mediterranean diet is well known to be like one
of the healthiest in the world and then Japan itself they eat a lot of fish they eat a lot of
they eat rice but not that much but they have a lot of like different things to choose from
it's just the environment they're in sort of enables them to just like make smart choices because
that's just what's available but in America like what's been made available to us is just
endless calories in every form you can imagine like the fast food stuff we've got
the kind of drinks we have the huge you know mega ultra gulps those are all the problem
because like and they say like well a person just needs to choose and like you know make
smart decisions the problem just is that people didn't grow up knowing that they're gonna make
these kind of mistakes and and and how to properly take care of their bodies and like it's like a
fucking it's like a fucking adult gauntlet to go through learning how to eat right once you're
like fucking 20 you start figuring that shit out when like you're in danger of your metabolism
starting to slow down and then you start to get fat and shit and a lot of people just never figure
it out and that's led to the world we're in right now it's fucked up and we just need to yeah yeah
go on i'll just say a huge part of it too is socioeconomic a lot of the cheapest foods are some
of the most unhealthy and it's a huge problem a lot of families and poverty and stuff like if
they're only feeding their kids like really cheaply made food and you know that's there's a reason
why child obesity is a problem it's because these kids are being fed by their parents and it's shit
food you know what's weird is that a lot of the time i find that like ready meals and easy to
you know really cheap shit is not actually as cheap as just buying a thing of rice and some kidney
beans or whatever and making like a yeah a curry that's so it's it can feed you for so much more
the problem is but nobody nobody really knows because they're like i don't know i don't know how
to put it together exactly that's exactly that's the money is ignorant on it yep so they just aren't
like if you buy like a huge bag of rice that'll you'll just like scoop out of for a month i guarantee
that will be like a million times cheaper than like buying fast food every day or whatever uh
yeah there's no doubt yeah you know there's one thing there's one thing that i've learned and
i don't know i i saw i i kind of take it for granted that uh my parents have so many nice
glasses that are made of glass but like i drink water all the time and i'm not really a soda boy
and i think it's because i don't drink out of plastic cups plastic makes water taste like
shit if you have like glasses that you drink water out of they actually taste better it tastes juicy
i would encourage people to drink water out of glasses even tap water right so something about
the lip touchery is like it makes it nicer to drink and then you will drink more water if you
have nice glasses substituting water for just whatever the fuck people are drinking right now
would just do so much to to help this issue uh yeah that that would be great i drink mostly
water these days and then just water mixed with like protein powder and shit what this goes back
to is my famous legendary vlog watery advice keep bringing that up because it's the most influential
thing ever created it's inspired a generation uh it's just it's just a brain blast but you filmed
it yeah it is exactly it's just a brain blast i had it it's like showering feels really good
and that's and that's how i feel about about like like uh eating well and like working out and stuff
is that like you don't want to do it because like like in the moment while you're doing it it might
not like feel like incredible but afterward and even a lot of times during it it will feel great i
know whenever i take a walk and you know i do i do good health stuff and i cook my own meal and stuff
it feels empowering and it feels like i've just i've just fucking i've done it i've reached godly
status and i've walked a mile and you know i've done it i've defeated health that's exactly right
munchie it's it's so like like a lot of people will be turned off by it but like you really have to
like push through it and once you're done with it i guarantee it will be worth it and you will feel
like you've accomplished something there is one concept that separates us from the animals
now set it before but it is delayed gratification delayed gratification is the entire reason why
humans have gotten to the place we're at right now because we were willing to put an effort in
the short term uh to get greater results in the long term that's how we started farming way back
in the day yeah go on it's not even like directly like yes like i i've done this you know hard thing
but i will be rewarded later because i will be thinner it just i will wait wait wait i will be
rewarded by the lord of light there we go everyone yeah nice good it's just like almost immediately
after eating good food especially stuff like broccoli right it feels good it broccoli i don't
even like you're a good person if that's true it does but i don't even mean long term isn't like
you know in a year you'll feel better i mean that like when you're in the when you're in the planning
stages of like what am i gonna eat i've got like i've got some food in my fridge i could cook
or i could order i hop pancakes never delivered here i got these two choices and like the easy
way is just like order that shit but we all know the right answer instantly i ordered pancakes from
i hop not yesterday but the day before that's just because i like it's not even it is barbaric
it's not even a health thing it's just like a it's like an i hop pancake why are you doing this
okay there my my my pitiful excuse that i would never accept from anyone was just that i felt sick
and wanted pancakes that's my that's my excuse it's fucking i i hop is like the worst i did get
chicken fried steak i got chicken fried steak with southern gravy that was nice no no you need a
chicken broth you need it you need a soups you're right oh my god okay this is slightly off topic
but it's related to pokemon go one of my rituals after playing the game every uh sunday it was
i'll go to this like local ramen place and ramen has quickly become like my favorite food
ramen is the best food it's so good not like like top ramen shit which i do in fact love going to
like a real place yeah you get that fucking half an egg just floating in there and the naruto in
there and shit for the month of hell yeah there there was like a specialty ramen that it was like
mexican ramen that had like carnitas and stuff in it and then like and like chives and stuff and it
was fucking it was spicy delicious fucking ramen ten out of ten eat it every day and uh just a
ramen does have a pretty high density of calories what with the what with the noodles and all but
but you get a lot of good shit in there as well well not if not if you eat uh not if you eat that
ramen from the world ends with you or they just put an entire steak on top of it that's an entire
what an entire remember world ends with you there was that like yeah there was the mom and pop ramen
shop and then there was like the big trendy chain ramen place and like they went to check out the
big trendy chain that was putting the mom and pop rock try saying mom and pop ramen shop five times
fast and and they were like holy shit they just put an entire steak on top of the ramen bowl
um oh a steak a steak yeah yeah that's right that's right awesome yeah that's pretty fucking
I can see why mom and pop are obsolete frankly frankly out with the old and with the new
excellent all right guys let's let's let's veer towards our conclusion here we've been going for
about an hour uh what what are the what are the important messages you want people to take away
from our little discussion here walk outside you'll be happy like you will be happy I guarantee you
walk to like your local like you know church go and pray like a good christian man should I would
take a walk if you're listening to this and you're not a fit boy and you want to get you want to
be a fit boy take a walk today you know fucking what today okay new fucking hashtag PCP fit life
whatever there's a new PCP you want to be an ubermensch listen to the PCP while taking a walk
or go into the gym and take a selfie and I will retreat you from the PCP account on twitter the
PCP will retweet you if you take like a selfie and you're in the gym while watching to the latest
PCP take this journey with us that sounds good it sounds good yeah let's do yeah we'll do that
hashtag PCP fit life was that was that it or was it fitness life yeah we can go with something more
catchy probably I like okay hashtag PCP fit life fucking send us that shit and we will look at it
and we'll retweet it from the twitter there you go PCP fit hard oh christ we're making this hard
I don't understand anything uh delete something something like that
uh do it fucking do it okay does anyone else have a final resting place they would I do yeah
basically the nice part about fitness is that it makes you better at everything literally
everything thinking moving around lifting up household objects going from point A to point B
it's one of those things where it's like there's no logical reason not to do it unless you're
trying to get the world record for world's fattest man other than that though like it's one of those
things where even if you're not an athlete it's still important to maintain a basic level like
because it just like I said it makes you better at everything so why not do it that's actually true
just like like there there have been times in my life where I've been like somewhat normal and not
the monster that that stands before me today and it just like feels better to be alive it feels like
like it's like after like you know I do something healthy it just feels good to just sit back down
your computer and just breathe in that that good air with your with your good spartan lungs I often
think about it like this like think about the human beings that we are descended from you know
they were out fucking running around every single day and if you're literally just sitting in front
of a computer every day you're probably doing something wrong you're not doing what your body
requires to to operate at maximum capacity so don't think fitness is not an option fitness is not
an optional thing that you can maybe do if you want to get super rips everyone should exercise in some
capacity you should do it every single day even I don't do it every single day but we all should
do it every day that is the ideal and that is what we should all be shooting to be doing and if
you're not I think yeah I mean you know you're fucking up a little bit you're fucking up I think
if if people have like a difficulty just try and add on try and do something that you wanted to do
that just so happens to be physical like if you want to get better you want to level up pokemon
go you can go for more walks that's a very easy one if you have a dog you can walk the dog and do
you know that that's exercising itself if you want you know you could do an instrument or you
know a plan of drums would get you a lot of a lot of movement you know just pick a hobby that is
like collaterally exercising you if you can't like share the thought of just going and and doing it
by itself I know this advice might seem somewhat shallow especially coming from me because obviously
I I'm preaching and not doing but I genuinely do like like have a lot of respect for people who
do fitness because it is just a like a real good and it's it takes it's a massive undertaking to
you know do it consistently and become a fitness ubermensch and it's really inspiring and great
I'm not going to change anything in my life basically but uh good it's good well it's not
important to be an ubermensch it's so it's it's enough because like that that was the thing with
the the whole competitive like nature of like school is like oh if you're not the most fit then
what are you even doing like it's not important to be the biggest boy it's just important to be
not a piece of shit exactly right uh-huh also one more thing I want to add is that a lot of people
they don't want to change their diet or their exercise because they want to wait until it's
like a convenient time in their lives to do it but there is never a convenient time you are dying
right now that's the good point the first best time to get started was yesterday but the second
best time is right now yeah that that is the most important thing begin immediately uh just
like I say in my like me a math of a shit it's like like if you're inspired by something if you
just if you realize there's something you should have been doing all along the time to start immediately
not tomorrow not the next day just you know in whatever capacity you can begin looking into a
take that walk take that walk right now start lifting your mindset episode go right now get
your fucking heart or no nine guys there goes to do it and then listen to this while you walk
you know or whatever you want to do yeah listen you'll probably be listening for a half no you'll
take a half an hour walk probably if you listen to the end of this or give or take and you'll be
so happy that you did I guarantee while we uh while we answer our fucking pity questions and our
pcp patron line questions right are we are we wrapping up are we are we headed in the in that
direction I think we're wrapping up I think so I think so good you are a god hashtag pcp fit life
that's the one hashtag pcp fit life send us pictures you update us under shit we will retweet
them also suggestions for better names we will come up with a better name next week I like that
that's pretty good but whatever okay fair enough if it sticks then it'll stick uh all right let's
see what we got here questions from the twitter hashtag ask pcp pity questions um okay let me see
what we got here good questions seems like an oxymoron yeah well I mean fair enough fair enough
uh okay here we go here we go at chemotherapy chemotherapy asks uh do you think that all
criticism needs to be somewhat constructive to have any value or merit no well depends on what
they mean by constructive if they mean nice then of course not but if they mean like yeah there's
like like you when I hear constructive I just mean I can get something out of it I yeah I pretty much
I don't think like criticism okay constructive criticism is valuable to the creator theoretically
I don't think yeah that it needs to be valuable to the creator to be worth saying or worthwhile I
I agree I think sure I think most criticism is constructive like the only thing that would be
like unconstructive is like somebody complaining about something that isn't even true basically
basically but even but even that is like well there's they clearly had uh a misinterpretation
there's maybe not as clear as as you thought it was like that's a problem what if what if I you
know I'm watching one of your dark soul streams and I see you make a mistake and I have a thought
it's like well okay you should probably improve your skills and just for for for shorthand I say
that you should probably just you know get good that would be a positive change what do you know
what if I'm what if I'm waiting I'm I'm clicking f5 I'm refreshing day in day out just waiting on
the hypocrite channel for that fabled video series to find right you promised you promised
you for months now it's too late we believe that you promised me to finally grace our presence
it's been long enough
I'm dying I need it well most most constructive most comments that are criticizing they have
like I mean people want to sound like the smart guys so they will make an explanation so like this
is what I don't like about this even if they're completely wrong and they just misinterpreted it
that's still like I mean you can never be perfect you can never communicate as we as we know that
language doesn't work you can ever communicate perfectly to everybody so people will always miss
miss certain things but there's always some way to improve the ability to explain what your point is
in a way that less people will get confused so I think most criticism is constructive in that way
I feel like okay okay criticism can come in a lot of ways I feel like if you are leaving a comment
on a video on YouTube for example to be practical I feel like you I wouldn't I don't know if I want
to use the word oh it but I feel like you should probably have some sort of constructive criticism
in the sense that you at least like tell the person why something's bad I feel like an example of
like a comment that's not good is you suck die but it yeah a comment that could be great is you suck
die uh that to pay looks fake well you know what you know what I actually kind of what I'm explaining
why you should die I kind of want to go back on that a little because I actually I am I consider
myself a super charitable person in terms of like what other people say if someone comments on a video
of mine you suck die remind I mean of course I'll I'll probably be just like oh my feelings but
beyond that I'll think like okay why did this person say that and most likely I probably put
something in a video that was like controversial or whatnot so and like you can look at it and just
be like well okay this person is just expressing negative they're not being specific but we know
that they said that for some reason unless we're like a pure troll I want to yeah but if we can
just like if everyone's given you shit for like one thing you did wrong in a video let's say uh
and you like you're aware that it could have been like a hot button issue and you get a comment
like that then you could you could possibly charitably interpret that to be like uh here is yet
another voice criticizing me for doing this thing well yeah yeah you don't you you have to understand
the context yeah like yeah why the right thing but I think people do owe it to themselves to explain
themselves because if they don't explain themselves there's a chance that the person they're talking
to will never understand very true very true I'm not asking for a lot here I don't want to like
here's what you did wrong here's what can be better like listen to my essay just like any indication
of why I suck and should die is good enough just like tell me why a video yeah all right all right
people can't read minds I mean sometimes people have a criticism that's like uh I don't know like
like fit here has gotten criticism for just like uh people just straight up and make a video yeah
I mean just as one example not that I agree of course but people have like criticized you for
like exposing 2b2t to like the normos and that you know there's kind of just criticizing you on a
fundamental concept like what you're doing but there's just a straight up disagreement on how like
of course your big video about how um you know you're being uh exposing uh so I forget the name
of the guy who owns the server whatever house yeah yeah that one that was so cool that was an intense
fucking video I loved it but like so you I mean your your stuff like saved the server by by just
bringing attention to it so of course if you were one of those like five people who was like playing
2b2t back in those days and you know like you were like yay my secret club I love having like
one other person online sometimes and of course now things have changed like oh look at these
fucking you know noobs all showing up I could get why they wouldn't like that but you just have a
fundamental different approach you're trying to like resuscitate a community here so that's a very
fundamental disagreement in like intentions here so like that that criticism could be very like
honest they could say it in a helpful way but if you just fundamentally disagree on the premise
of their criticism then like frankly there's not a lot to take from it other than ah there are people
who have a descending opinion on this thing uh-huh absolutely a lot of times too like when there is
a criticism in that regard like oh you're exposing our server to the masses like I understand
their genuine concern like they wanted their secret little club you know I totally get it so
it's like I I sympathize with your situation but sadly I disagree with you that's that's what it
comes down to what a great question this was actually really nice thank you froggy sleuth aka
at chemo therapy nice job nice job the other ones are all bad wait wait I forgot at never paint
what's your favorite type of dinosaur not bad not bad the water you from Jurassic Park alive
TM Jurassic Park trademarked that's the end moving on my favorite investigator
he's brother to dinosaurs he's descended okay let's go to the uh alligators represent hey
everybody patreon.com slash patreon.com slash the procrastinators get yourself into the questions
bar on our discord server so we'll actually read your question so it's not a pity question a mere
pity question uh let's see what we got you got any picked out peeps I'm still looking a lot of them
are either like essays or like what's your favorite anime tier uh okay okay here's the example of what
we're getting here from zan what's your what what is your favorite healthy fat like they're so like
okay oh uh what is that I got one I got one I got one I got one I got one I gotta get those omega
sixes yeah well there's uh there so so fats are broken into a couple different kinds there are there
are saturated fats and there are unsaturated fats then you've got poly unsaturated fats and you've
got mono unsaturated fats you want the poly unsaturated fats are statistically speaking the most
quote unquote healthy because what makes it a poly unsaturated is that so the way that a the way
that a try glyceride which is what a fat molecule is the way it works is that it's got this string
of like I think they're carbon atoms with lots of like hydrogens attached to the carbons off the
side and what makes it an a saturated molecule is that when every possible link that has a hydrogen
attacks to those carbon atoms is there it is saturated that it's got as much mass as possible
but you can have a covalent double bond between carbon atoms that use up some of those possible
links that could otherwise be attached to hydrogen atoms and so when you have like if you have that
same molecule that just has lost a bunch of those hydrogens and you have like connections between
those carbon atoms then it just has less mass because a lot of those hydrogen atoms are just
missing and so it's like a lighter molecule than you'd otherwise have um and so uh so if you have
a mono unsaturated that means a single hydrogen is missing which means it's a little bit lighter
but if you have a poly unsaturated triglyceride that is a fat molecule that has is missing a whole
at least two and probably more hydrogen atoms therefore it's it's less and the the good thing
about those is those can absorb wayward hydrogen atoms in your digestive system which actually is
a is a helpful healthy like cleansing mechanism because those extra hydrogen atoms hanging out
in your gut can be negative for health and they they can like cause cancer and like can fuck up
shit um uh so i'm gonna go with poly unsaturated triglyceride it's all it's all about those omega
six is all about them fish oil pills it's all about those fish birds you know by the way an omega
six uh what what an omega six means if i remember remember correctly is the omega refers to like
a particular like end of the of the one of the molecules on the triglyceride and the six like
is the number like from that end so i think if i remember correctly i think it omega six means
like from the omega end of one of the strands of the carbon atoms like six down there is a missing
carbon atom there and that's why like it counts up to that and like that's like good or something
it's something along those lines it's about which like hydrogen atoms missing and it's healthier
so there you go and that's why they're good because they clean up stray hydrogen atoms in your body
couple from picture loan asks are there any foods that are objectively horrible should be avoided at
all costs soda obviously is one soda is a big one so does a big one um what else is there uh you
know i've actually been struggling because my favorite thing to consume in this world is orange
juice orange juice yeah the thing is orange juice is terrifically calorie dense uh and it's isn't it
good for digestion i mean fiber in it well it depends on your goals actually the thing about
the thing about orange juice is that you you miss out on tons excuse me tons of fiber you would
have gotten if you just eaten an orange so well true they always say that uh when it comes to
vegetables drink your vegetables eat your fruits is the common thing they say because drinking fruit
juice has a lot of calories and will you know make you fat whereas drinking vegetables like
vegetables have way less calories and you get all like the the vitamins and stuff from a vegetable
i've been drinking it so uh feel free to drink your vegetables and uh eat your eat your fruits
everybody yeah so i've been cutting it down yeah yeah go on i was gonna say orange juice it has
so much sugar in it and a lot of people think that oh it's a natural sugar so it's okay for me well
i mean sugar comes from sugar cane it's natural ben you've been typing this entire
fucking episode oh what the hell are you guys can you guys can hear that i've been hearing it the
astronauts on the space station gonna hear that fucking keyboard been uh yeah all right we'll edit
that out later well all right i should say so all right great um except for this one to make the
joke work uh chill wise been from the page yeah yeah what are you doing this is i'm extremely
interested in best workout mix like vapor music yeah music no no no you can't not vapor
anything you need something to pump you up uh for me it's various anime openings that get me hyped
and and that's pretty much what it is s cascade is mine but that's when it all comes tumbling down
uh whenever i take off or land on an airplane i always time it so that i like the little intro
starts in cascade i always try to time like everything in my life to be in line with cascade
my only travels on 413 i'm a big fan of uh sabaton while hitting my dick with a hammer
because it fills manliness that's gonna release so much testosterone into your system by doing
that yeah that's that's you know we've been beating around the bush steroids don't bother just hit
your dick with a hammer that you're really cutting out the middle man you need a joke you need a
fucking joke there's no activity more beneficial to muscle gain than jelking that's for sure dude
i'm the only muscle that matters that's my resolution to jelk hardcore yeah to jelk so hard
that i elevate off the floor 30 feet it's gonna be like like i'm gonna like like i'm gonna like
pull up next gonna be like such gravity with my hand that i'm going to like like i just like
jump up without having to move any of my muscles next yeah next to the olympic clean and jerk
is the equally renowned olympic jelk
incredible oh excellent hey uh yellow poon asks uh have you guys seen pain and gain if so then
how do you feel about the workout slash gym bro culture presented in movies now so pain and gain
is like uh is like a muscle head kind of movie those guys become murderers and like go off the
fucking rails so like this is a bit of an extreme example but a little bit a little like everything
was great about pain and gain until they started murdering people uh like things are going really
well i mean i think it improved okay fair enough but like there's a there's a spirit of camaraderie
of brotherhood that that's nice with like gym buddies and whatnot and uh i can appreciate that
spirit of unity and solidarity like like in pre-world war two germany you know everyone was
really getting on board yeah we were weeding out the week and uh preserving the strong
we were what Nate says oh uh i did some time in venezuela i moved here recently um yeah yeah uh i
don't know i gym bro culture is kind of stereotypicalized and gets a bad rap but like i i don't know
like there's a lot of quote-unquote gym bros like at the gym i go to but they're just like
nice guys who like work normal blue collar jobs and then love working out and hanging out with
each other and like this is like the demon of gym bro culture like guys having goals achieving them
and feeling good about themselves oh no what a nightmare just because a lot of movie directors
are fucking nerds yeah they're bunch of fucking fucking 98 pounds soaking wet twink-ass hollywood
directors definitely true that's right that's right so they're like a fucking
Chad stole Veronica from me in sixth grade i have you know you know even Steven Spielberg
really needs to to hit the gym you know who smashes the post you know who gets all the girls
and lifts 5 000 pounds a day my hero sam hide and just like him i i persevere on my path towards
greatness that's right that's right um all right like i i think we're pretty good at questions
though there is one other section i wanted to do which is our fan art appreciation section
oh that we're we're making a thing is this new do we now this is a new thing that's right that's
it's a new thing now this will be brief there's there's not a lot to go through but there's
keep this keep this brief i don't i don't want the yeah we don't i love i love it i love it i
can't believe the pcb is ripping off right for us by having fan art yeah i know i'm looking at
all things yeah now now here's a great one i love this this comes from our boy dino spinach
now let me post this in the chat here take a look at this masterpiece this is a color
profile selector i i'm gonna be honest with you this this has been like a common rebuttal to
mean bends you know talking in the reference cop killers episode about pcb colors and this approach
of two colors makes no sense no it's no i don't agree it makes perfect no sense it makes okay
why i think the two colors the rowdy fuckers house is divided therefore it's invalidated okay i i think
yeah i don't know this is great and i like it because mine is the best um and that's all there is to
it um you look like a delicious black i guess my one problem is that hippo and debu are too similar
i i think the concept of having two colors is okay i just think most of these choices are kind of
bad especially mine which looks like shit um i guess what what what's sensitive you know yeah i
think this person took the like like yours only makes sense with that avatar which like you know
you get a couple of these i would i wouldn't fully agree with like i mean i love mine i love mine i think
that yours is i would give you but like the entire the entire well okay i don't like your
because your color scheme there is the rowdy fucking color scheme well well muchy we're talking
primary and secondary color so everyone has their primary color and then there's also a secondary
color used for it i don't fucking know whatever it doesn't matter yeah whatever you wish whatever
you please i don't understand why what is not hard to understand i don't there's no
point to me there's no point to me there's no point to you get it why don't we actually do our
buddy dino spanish the currency of reading his text that he provided with this as a sort of guide
so let me read it's a couple of sentences here here we go so i thought about this during the
ratifocus cop kill is getting over it with ben at faady episode uh but i got motivated to make this
after the free speech podcast if for no other reason then it forced me to work and something
aren't related okay blah blah who cares let's get let's get back to us let's let's keep it on focus
here um i feel like giving each member a dual color profile makes it easier to use similar
colors that are shared by pcb members it's magenta ish colors for digi and mage cyan turquoisey
colors for divu and hippo as well as being more visually cohesive for members that have more than
one color typically associated with them like ben's black and white also it makes it easy to come up
with simplified avatars if need be if the bcb wants to streamline the aesthetics of the podcast
screen these are good reasons these are good thoughts i like i like ben's i like digis and
mages tom's is a bit i don't know tom's is interesting it's that blue is exactly the same
as divu's aesthetically tom's is a little true that's true actually i mean i think this mine
mine isn't cool it's not the right type yeah this is the real shit i don't like okay i love how
this is the fan art appreciation and we are shitting well this is like a business decision
egg yeah we're talking about the real shit it's i i when i really i really give this the the the
i think like this dual color system even if we don't like the specific colors offered
is a good idea i do a backup secondary color i like it i i i will die on this hill i will
fucking die okay i absolutely oppose i mean i maybe i'm biased because i as the black and
white guy i am kind of you know i need to you know one one doesn't do it for me um uh sure sure
but i think it's makes sense for everyone else you know i mean we need unity we can't have this
this do you think colors when you do you think that can be magenta or it can be purple willy
nilly no we need the hardbacks we need one well the one is the primary the one is the
should the one should be the primary one even have the secondary if it oh it doesn't matter at all
no just pay just the primary well just just a further differentiate because there's not that
many colors on the wheel we need to have them be separate enough so they don't need a secondary
munchie do you think they can stand alone do you think that this is like a mealy mouth kind of
like limperisted compromise that is like like like like not like like too too much of a compromise
to even be worth doing i think it's too much of a compromise and i think that it we like we're not
paying attention to what really matters and that's what's giving like the reason we're talking about
is because every person needs to be defined by one color that makes them stand out well primary
colors and secondary little baby colors if they just complicate things further oh just for clarity
to help when when necessary you know there can't be no help that's cheating that is fucking cheating
we didn't have one color that's the point is if we have one color that makes it so that you can
easily identify them from a glitch you can't have a fucking magnifying glass finding oh oh the
primary colors in each fucking drawing of nate you can't have that all right here's the thing
there will be like a the most like good-looking collection of all the colors if we if everyone
is together but i think the point of having a secondary color is if like two of them
when they're just alone like two people uh using their primary color the primary and color of
both people is is you know it's too similar so one of them can use their secondary color
and i guess that's the point but i still feel like i feel like i feel like i'm agreeing
more with much this color is so inconsistent say if if you're with fucking i don't know i don't
know like like like davoo and like hippo are there yeah it's it's still gonna and then and then on
the next one on the fucking next one it's davoo and i don't know someone else you're not gonna have
that consistency that you need that the entire point of this is to have consistency and have one
person be represented all the time they need to be consistent okay i we don't need to settle this
right now uh dino spinach great job fantastic let's appreciate that if you see below that that's
the colors that i want did digi is still i'm still unhappy with digi but this is generally i think this
is i think this is the way the wind's blowing i think this is what we need to have uh okay okay uh
so here's here's the next little art that we're going to be appreciating oh let me get that this
is by cappy it's by cappy and uh it's uh it's a little alley with some snakes
oh yeah i mean some of these are just specific to like individual guys but whatever it's fine
it's in the chat this but this person doesn't know what i was doing and i was streaming and they saw
this i was drawing this of a part of my webcomic that is is currently ongoing mm-hmm is this is
alley you throw in some snakes oh she's throwing them i thought she was doing like a cool like
hand-to-cross face like pose as they attack i thought they were like i thought they were coming
out from behind her like dr octopus arms yeah me too me too all right well whatever uh it's pretty
cool i i like the style here i like the style yeah looks good um now there's a bunch from our
our boy miles sea wind let me let me link these you guys will enjoy these i am sure uh okay there
we go there we go oh no oh no uh let me get let me get the other year when are the are these like
are these like from the last week these were made these are posted in the last week did she's
looking very did she's looking very rowdy fuckers right he's looking really normal in this he's
looking like really like did he's got the the cal arts mouth i can i snow munchie with the cotton
he does i like that yeah i do like that that's a good idea can you like imagine if i was a faggot
aka now and i and i had like the crimmed glasses and like candy hair and and and i had the cal
arts art style in real life and like you had like one side of your head was shaved and like yeah
yeah i can imagine it that's dope that's dope uh these are imagine what if munchie was in
steven universe what would that look like there there it is nobody knows it's okay okay now i i
checked on twitter there weren't any submissions with the hashtag it was pcp fan art or hashtag pcp
art you know you i'll check either one uh didn't see any there so so we're getting we're getting
this thing off the ground you know this is going to be edited in you're going to see these images
where we're just getting started with this shit so uh keep doing them keep sending them and we'll uh
and we'll we'll put them on the screen and if you're in the fucking uh the discord group post them
right in the uh in the god damn fuck whatever it's called like the fan art chat fan art warehouse
fan art warehouse post them there and that'll be a nice easy place to have everything there for
for the patrons for the patrons but if you don't got that use twitter hashtag pcb fan art
hashtag pcb art so beyond that the only other thing to talk about is um there's that there's a
whole music theme contest but the only thing is we've only still got one entrance right now
so i'm feeling like we just we just hold off and say as you can see people we're the machinery is
underway send us more god damn hashtag pcb theme shit we need that god damn stuff to listen to
we've only gotten one submission so far it's from uh i think it was from um i believe aj chubh of course
of course it was aj chubh our boy i haven't heard it i haven't heard it but he's good i want to listen
to that we will listen to it on the show guaranteed maybe if if we don't hear anything by next week
if nobody else submits something then we just gotta we just gotta give this a it's crack on the show
he's been waiting he's he's been waiting yeah yeah yeah i want to show a couple at once you know
just so people have the spectrum so um you can get off your fucking lazy ass make some pcp themes
already stuff for maybe for free what are you doing what are you doing be like aj chubh he's
your he's your role model here uh but for now all right that's it everybody that that that
will close the book on this on this fan appreciation segment of the show well that's it i guess we've
done it hey pcp money patreon.com slash the procrastinators one dollar you're in the chat
five dollars you get all the bonus episodes that i think that might be 14 right now maybe 15 i
forget the number that's so much yeah the pcp is going to get to the point where it's one
hour of topic and then two hours of selling out begging for money and self-reflection
and fan jerking off i pray for that day every i mean that's the goal that is the goal that's
everything else is just an excuse to do that yeah without a doubt i at tpcrastinators on twitter
falls for shit hey and by the way you're welcome for dragging this episode out so that you've had
enough time to take your long half an hour walk like my fit friends hope you didn't forget to do
that i hope i hope you enjoyed i hope you enjoyed uh us talking about fan art while you were walking
with your phone in your pocket not able to see any of what we were talking about well that's a
personal problem all right uh i guess we're done everybody hey fit thanks for being here buddy
yeah thanks for having me like i said the greatest crossover of all time of all time no doubt no
doubt fitness and minecraft crossed with drugs hardcore drug use uh give where were you saying
something i was asking if fit you want to plug anything oh yeah yeah like a channel um speaking
of progressing your fitness journey and having it be a colossal failure in a government database
follow my instagram fit mc sippy cup do it that's a guy i should do that to the origin of that name
sippy cup all right i used to have this water bottle that i drink from when i was streaming and
it had a straw like it's one of those types of water bottles and my fans kept calling it a sippy cup
it just escalated that's dope that's dope uh we're it up peace out everybody uh i'll see you in
hell this is the procrastinator signing out thanks for being here give us more free shit bye
go get yourself a tree go get yourself a tree yeah get yourself a tree you you work so hard go
get yourself a book in big mac and a couple of pies and a couple of cakes and you know just you
deserve it bye bye