I'm not generally satisfied by the pace at which the world dispenses engagement, so on a conceptual level, I've always been obsessed with theme parks.
The idea is to create a controlled environment, allowing you to wander through and effortlessly create an experience of streamlined, instant gratification fun.
Hello everybody and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast, a podcast on the internet what a novelty.
I am the best guy ever and we're joined today by Munchy Where's Tiny Hats?
It's me, Legoland. Here I am before you today, the most decadent king of all. I'm here to spread my wealth and tell you about the most wondrous plans.
Famous Sonic YouTuber Hippocrit?
I was gonna say Legoland, you bitch.
What?
I love Legoland.
Oh, not as much as me.
We've also got The Davoo.
Hip bone, skelly, crits, wild ride was a really good value.
And Monkey Jones.
We're not even a minute in and I already have to pee.
Oh no.
Let's do what I do, dude.
Just do what I do and just go on air.
Just pee into your own mouth.
That's true.
I'm gonna pee into the bottle that I'm drinking out of and then just keep drinking out of it.
Yeah.
Hey, that's called second harvest. That's a water, a barter, barter, second harvest.
Wow, that's good.
Is that to Paul Newman's iced tea brand second harvest?
You know, I'm drinking Rolling Rocks, so it probably wouldn't change the taste at all.
Yeah, for Rolling Cock.
Nate, what is the PCP?
The PCP is the most knuckle-
Advanced.
Whitening, earth-shattering,
Red Pill exploding Red Pill podcast in the world about a bunch of internet creators
who all came together because they had the perfect opinion when combined.
Perfect.
Wait, do we introduce the show every episode now?
Yeah.
We're working on it.
Okay, that's nice.
That's cool.
Keep forgetting what the show is and we have to remind them.
It's true.
So hopefully they'll bake it into their brains this time.
Yeah.
So today, everybody, we're talking about amusement parks.
amusement parks, water parks, bumper cars, roller coasters.
Yeah.
Oh, the teacups.
The teacups.
Getting belated by Armenian men who run the rides.
Yeah.
Now we're talking.
Circus tent.
Dude, lots grinding into your fucking feet until they bleed.
That's true.
Exactly.
That's my favorite part.
Okay, the great thing about amusement parks, I just want to say off the bat, is that you
forget how painful just existing as a three-dimensional being is until the end of the day after you
just, you know, like you walk around, you experience life, and then at the end of the day you walk
home and you're dead.
It's great.
We should mention that we decided to do this after me becoming infatuated with a certain
water park vlogger by the name of Cy.
What is this?
I am not privy to this meme.
Dude.
There's no meme here.
Cy raised a water park vlog, and I was so enthralled by it, and specifically its thumbnail, and
how literally ingenious it is, and how much I legitimately enjoyed it.
I just want to see water park vlogs constantly.
We know Cy has a kind of a weird predicament where his like subscribers don't all watch
his videos.
Let me tell you, Cy, if you want 100% retention, the world needs water park vlogs.
Water park vlogs.
Guys, let me make a deal with you.
That's the best water park in the world!
And seriously, Cy, that was great.
Guys, I guarantee you I can get Cy to give me that thumbnail without text on it if we
want to use that as a thumbnail for this episode.
We should!
Okay, yeah, you're already going to see the thumbnail, because if it's going to be the
thumbnail you just click on.
Okay, fantastic.
Cy is in the thumbnail.
This episode is getting probably, what, 1500 views max?
I think that's how it works.
Yeah, probably.
Hey, before we get too deep into the thing, let me read, okay, so there's no amusement
park entry, an urban dictionary, but what I did find was a disease called amusement park
hangover.
All right, so let me just read this to you.
That feeling, and this is just like I was talking about before, the feeling you get the day
after going to an amusement park, particularly when you spend all day on intense rides,
symptoms include horse voice, headache, fatigue, and general pains, and then the description
is not funny, so I'm not going to read it.
So there you go.
There you go.
Okay, so that's where we're coming from.
What is our favorite amusement park?
I got to say Disney World in fucking Orlando, California.
Disney World, no question.
Nate, do you remember, do you remember this one time on Twitter where, I forget the exact
context of it.
Disney World, Disneyland, we were arguing whether Disneyland or Disney World was the
amusement park that one of our fans was attending, and I defeated you in hand-to-hand combat.
You did.
And I humiliated you, and you officially on that day handed me, quote, all of your
internets with a Z.
So I am not, in PCP Canada, in PCP lore, I'm objectively more powerful than Nate because
I have all of his internets.
So what that manifests is if you look at my download speeds, they're struggling to crank
out 0.01 kilobytes per second, whereas Munchy is just living in the lap of luxury, downloading
all the terror flops you could possibly want in his fucking life.
One day I'll get him back.
Whenever I click on a download link, I just hear a punch sound effect because it's
downloading so fast.
Download 55 new mouse clickers?
That instant.
Alright, Nate, why is Disney World the best theme park other than all the propaganda?
Yeah, that sounds like a shitty answer everybody knows there.
Let me see, I think I've been to, I don't know, maybe like six or so amusement parks
probably in my whole life, but Disney World was definitely the most fun.
Okay, but I'm sure a lot of it has to do, as I'm sure many of our stories will involve
the specific things that happened there and the situation that brought you there and the
people that were there, et cetera, et cetera.
So when I was in high school, me and my older brother Ben, who you might know, we both were
in marching band, and our marching band was pretty darn good.
And yeah, I know it's taken a weird start, but we were in marching band, I played the
clarinet, Ben played the saxophone, and we were well loved amongst our people in Massachusetts
where the school was.
Well basically, our marching band was good enough where we were invited to Disney World
to participate in March down the main avenue, and we all just, this would happen every single
year, we would all get together, we'd pack up our shit, and we'd all go down to Disney
World, and we'd just have a great time.
So go there to March during one of Disney World's gay days, did you and Ben have an
experience every year?
Do they allow gay people in Disney World?
No.
That place is really gone to shit.
This isn't a meme.
They specifically have gay days.
Does that mean no straight people are allowed?
I mean, I'm sure you can go if you're straight, as long as you, you know, hike your pants up.
You just have to suck a dick on your way.
Yeah, but specifically so that same-sex couples can come over and hang out and make out without
all the Christian kitties getting corrupted.
Okay, you know, I think that's a real fucking thing.
It's an exclusion by exclusion.
It's very popular.
Yeah, separate but equal.
That's kind of cool, you know, it should decide.
But my favorite thing about that is how Mad Walt Disney would have been if he knew this
video.
He'd be mistaking all these orgies and be like, God damn it, why didn't he freeze my head
like they said?
I want in.
I didn't give the Nazis enough money.
So we'll see, that's the great thing.
That's what I was going to say.
The best thing about Disney World is that canonically is the place where the frozen
Messiah Walt Disney's corpse lives right now.
And one day he will rise from the dead to save us all from the cuckoldry of modern life.
So that's, you know, that's why I go down there once a year to pray to him.
That's my Mecca.
And it's got the rock and roll roller coaster with Aerosmith, baby.
So that's where I do most of my work on that roller coaster.
Like, cool it would be if Walt Disney actually did get cured of death and he just came back.
Like and that actually paid off.
And then he had like the, the, all of his, what do you call them?
When you, yeah, copyrights.
All of his copyrights would be extended for another billion years because now he's alive.
Oh yeah.
The law will be fucked.
That's what's going to happen.
Disney is just going to like, the company's just going to hire someone to act like Walt
Disney.
Now copyright, this is copyright now because since we, since we asked them to extend it
too many times, we're just going to like reset the entire counter again.
That's going to be the new strat.
Silly old religious people who believe in souls and whatnot.
Not even, you know, you don't have to be religious, but whatever.
People who believe in souls think that like death is magical.
But death really is like an engineering problem that we could one day solve.
If Walt Disney came back from the dead, I think Disney would have a, the company would have
a really hard time readjusting to being like artistically motivated in like a personal way.
Maybe like, that's what it feels like to like have an idea.
I just, just the other day I was watching some documentary about a guy who like, used to
work at Walt Disney.
He called Walt Disney.
I fucked up.
I fucked up bad.
But he, like he said this quote that is totally famous, but I just forgot and he reminded me.
It's that Walt Disney is the guy who said that like, we don't make art to make money.
We make money to make art.
So for him, it was all about just, you know, like having the resources available to continue
to make his craft.
And you know, who knows?
Yeah.
You know, Jew hating aside, you know, you got to respect that.
You got to respect that.
Well, I respect you.
That's my personal goal.
I don't know why I have to excuse that.
Of course.
Walt Disney famous for his Viagra with series.
Yeah.
Much beloved.
Big Princess Tutu fan.
Now I, I too love all things Disney.
I'm a big Disney movie kind of guy and I love Disney theme parks.
However, I do not live on the disgusting, uh, rancid, fucking like, like yellow colored
dick that is the East Coast of the United States.
I live on the West Coast.
We're old money.
Yeah.
You're new money.
You'll never be one of us.
Disney specifically made the other parks because this is what I saw from their, from their
Disney world propaganda movies on the travel channel.
It was like, you know, back in the 60s, the ride over to get to Disneyland was filled with
all these cheap, cheesy hotels and diners and dives and shitty places and cheap smoke
shops.
And Disney was like, well, that's just a shitty way to get to my park.
So he built other ones.
Oh, by the way, guys, the ride into Disneyland is no longer like that.
Law.
Is that, okay.
Oh, right.
Okay.
I'm following it.
Law.
Anyway, Disneyland is from what I hear just like shittier Disney world, but fuck you.
You even have the magic castle, you cuck.
What are you doing?
We have the magic castle.
You got a cheap imitation.
It doesn't have Walt Disney's body frozen inside.
Okay.
It's not the real magic castle.
True, true.
Okay.
The best part about Disneyland is how they literally like emotionally manipulate you
on every conceivable level, physical and emotional.
They like, they like have like, like different smells that they emanate from their fucking
carnices.
Yeah.
Like, like, like every single restaurant has at least one dead body inside emanating
delicious smells for you to.
Delicious pheromones.
Yeah.
Dude, look.
I've read this in a book in the game, game design book of lenses book by Jesse Shield,
a guy who worked at Disney.
He was saying that when they were making Disneyland, Walt Disney was like looking around like,
you know, like pointing at people like, okay, go there.
Okay.
That right.
Put that one there.
You know, that kind of shit.
Then sometimes he would bend down on his knees and then kind of like hobble around a little
bit.
People were like, why you hobble on your knees?
And he's like, I got to know what this park looks like from the perspective of a kid.
And it's like, oh shit.
That's so cool.
Genius.
In the fucking dirt.
He's just going to like a wheelchair or something, dude.
Are you going to like hop on a lady's back so you can see what it's like from a baby?
Like, what the fuck?
Yeah.
Why not just take two barrels of a shotgun and blow off your fucking calves and then
you're, you know, a couple feet shorter.
I know you really should do that.
He just, he just doesn't understand the hardships to come.
He needs to get serious.
He needs to get serious about that shit.
Get your fucking head in the game Walt Disney.
Jesus Christ.
What I was going to ask is, I mean, so the Undertaler, right?
He's a staple of the Disneyland experience as I understand it.
Every time I go there and I want, you know, you know, I think I'm going to go, okay, I'm
going to go, I'm going to go to Adventureland.
I'm going to get on Splash Mound and then I think, oh wait.
And then I like walk near and he's like, oh my Jesus.
I'm so good to see you.
Is he like a mascot?
The Undertaler is like, he's the Casey Neistat of Disneyland.
Yeah.
He defines the culture of that area.
I believe like the Undertaler is like a mascot at Disneyland.
I remember seeing in the news one time that like one, like Mickey Mouse mascot at like
Disney World like touched a 13 year old girl's like chest right before a photo shoot.
And so he got arrested.
I think the Undertaler gets arrested if he doesn't molest the kid he's taking a picture
with.
Guys, just keep your ear to the ground for when Disney buys the Undertale copyright
rights.
Keep your ear that there are, that there are fucking developments being made at Disneyland
for a Undertale ride one day.
When the PCP gets like 15 billion subscribers and then we get bought out by Disney, then
they're going to have full rights to the Undertaler character and they're going to be able to,
you know, use him in whatever disgusting wicked ways they see fit by making him a cleaner,
more socially adjusted person.
It's going to be a complete perversion of the original vision of the character.
By the way, next time I go to Disneyland, I'm going to piss my pants so I can really get
into the shoes of the Undertaler.
I can really see what it's all about.
It's like performance art.
That's real Gonzo journalism.
Yeah.
The Undertaler is definitely the pissed Gonzo journalist.
He really just has to live it and, you know, write about it as he sees fit.
Okay.
All right.
But no more fucking around.
Undertaler, get out of my way.
Oh, I'm in the acid now.
There's new acid rides at Disneyland.
In case you didn't know.
The fucking best part about Disneyland, I don't know if this is even in world, is the giant
turkey legs.
The turkey legs are fucking huge and like the size of my head and every time I go there,
I eat like two and I literally barf every single time and it's what I want.
I legitimately throw up at Disneyland every single time I go.
Every single time.
I don't know how meme-y you're being, but that seems to be the perfect technique.
No.
I'm not any.
I do it all the time.
Every single time because I just want to eat all the turkey legs because they're so big.
They're so big.
One of the theme parks I always go to, it has like these really awesome giant turkey legs
and I remember like a picture of me as a kid with my brother with those giant disproportionately
huge turkey legs.
Where the fuck do they genetically engineer these Titan turkeys?
That's what I was going to ask because I never got a turkey leg in an amusement park, but
I feel like there's just amusement park staple food which includes those giant turkey legs
because whenever King Richard's Faire is a big Massachusetts, or is it in Connecticut?
Yeah, it's in Massachusetts like a big medieval festival that happens every year or whatever
and Renaissance Faire, that's where I'm looking for.
Yeah, and it's like they sell the giant turkey legs and they also sell them in Disneyland.
Is there like some menu that like all amusement parks order from?
I mean personally, my favorite was always the clam chowder bread bowls.
Those are my personal favorite of all time.
Clam chowder bread bowl is an amusement park food?
Yeah, I've never, that's fucking crazy.
Well that's what I was going to say because I know I get them at King Richard's Faire
when I go, but I've never gotten them in an amusement park.
Yeah, I don't see anybody at Disneyland or the bowl of soup.
Fucking knight and kings and fucking bars did not have a clam chowder, you goddamn fucking bitch.
My question is, what's everybody's thoughts on funnel cake?
Because I personally fucking hate it.
I love funnel cake with strawberries and whipped cream on it.
Oh, it's my favorite.
Is that the cake that you put in a funnel in those deviant art comics?
Is that what they do?
Oh shit.
It's like a weird grid of batter that they deep fry.
It really is a grid.
It's like if you have stringy diarrhea and you deep fry it and then cover it in powdered sugar.
That's what a funnel cake is.
I've never seen this before in my fucking life.
This is the worst thing I've ever been subjected to.
It's pretty good.
It's like, let me think, how to describe it?
Yeah, just imagine cake, but imagine it fried instead of whatever.
It's just a very light, fluffy fry.
Imagine if French fries were sweet instead of salty and never stopped.
It was just a giant spaghetti.
It's called sweet potato fries and those are good.
What does funnel cake have to do with amusement parks?
Because they're amusement parks, according to me and Nate.
And you guys are all wrong, I guess.
It's one of the staple foods, yeah.
Well, actually, they sell those and then they sell...
Shit, what are they called?
These are actually, you see them a lot at baseball games as well or like football games.
Oh, they're called hot dogs.
They're just like...
Not a fucking hot dog.
Well, that too, but like...
Heroes.
It's like a funnel cake.
You may have heard them, they're called hamburgers.
God damn it.
What the fuck is this thing?
It's just like a funnel cake.
No, god damn it.
It's called cup of water.
It's like a funnel cake, but it's like one piece.
Barefoot.
It's just a thing.
Fuck it.
Okay, alright.
Alright, that's enough talking for you one day.
You just go ahead and get back in the cage real quick here on the big boys' talk.
The actual best food ever made outside of any, you know, like not just relegated to amusement parks,
but they're generally inside of it.
Before like, when extinct were Dippin' Dots.
Dippin' Dots were the only fucking food I loved in my entire life.
Yeah, those were at their parks too.
Why do you see they're extinct?
Like, I still have them at Walmart down here.
What?
Yeah, monkey me too.
We have them at Walmart, yeah.
Okay, okay.
Well, over here, they used to be like at McDonald's.
They used to be like at every single fucking store.
They used to be everywhere.
They're like popular mainstreamies.
I used to always get them.
Let me tell you.
But now, I don't see them anywhere.
Okay, I was down at my favorite amusement park the other day, the Creationist Museum.
Not a joke.
Is that the Ken Ham one?
What's his name?
Ken Ham or Ken Bone?
I always mix them up.
Maybe Ken Ham.
It's the one in Kentucky that's like nearby.
So it's whatever that one is.
The guy who debated Bill Nye way back in the days before Bill Nye was a cook.
Ken Bone is the really cool, funny XD presidential election.
But the point is, it's clearly superior to Disneyland because they did have Dippin' Dots.
They had old Dippin' Dots booths.
What the?
You can start around me.
No, here's the thing with Dippin' Dots, though, is that they have to be like in a super, super
cold freezer.
They have to build special freezers just to keep them from melting.
So it's like too much of a liability to have them because they keep fucking melting.
The theme park guy.
Because they got too many kids wandering in there and freezing to death.
It's just a big, you know.
And then they try to burn down the restaurant.
It's like a whole boot.
It's crazy.
Yeah, like the Dippin' Dots at the theme park I went to, they were like everywhere.
Every couple of street paths, you run into one.
And like, my family has always been very conservative with money when we go to one.
So it's just a constant tease.
And so I never actually had them.
But they looked cool.
Ice cream of the future.
Goddamn it, I've seen them here for like seven years.
How long can the future go?
Yeah.
Hey, remember Dibs that were like a bucket full of like these little individual ice cream
things?
Oh yeah.
Dibs?
Yeah, they're like covered in chocolate that you guys are talking about.
Dibs are everywhere for me.
Sorry dude, this is Food of the Future.
All we're going to be eating here in 20-30.
Yeah.
You better get woke.
Basically nothing in this podcast so far has like run true.
Like, oh yeah, I know that.
Like nothing.
Well, what do they have in their lives over there?
I haven't ever walked before and seen a funny fucking clown juggle out of them.
Do they have like a fucking crime rib and steak over at your music park?
Oh yes, it's me.
The average English nine-year-old child.
Oh, I shall have my pride.
I shall have my starline with my sword with my elbow.
We have fuck off.
Candy floss.
Candy to me.
Get out of here.
That sounds like the least healthy thing for your teeth of all time.
Oh wait.
No, you call it...
That explains a few things.
You call it cotton candy.
That's right.
We call it candy floss.
I guess because it gets stuck in your teeth.
That's the joke.
Oh shit.
It just melts on your tongue, you sick fuck.
Guys, who else has this crazy moment of finding out all at once
that cotton candy is called something different in other places
and in other places it's called it so pervasively
that a local had to spend five seconds remembering the word for cotton candy.
I had no idea it wasn't called that everywhere.
That's fucking crazy.
Yeah, that's fucking crazy.
That's like the biggest, most crazy one I've experienced in like many years.
I thought I knew all the ones.
I guess if you say we have cotton candy too, dunk ass, and then do that emoji.
Okay, Kim, tell us more.
What's England like with this shit?
Well, I'm very easily amused, so...
Everywhere's an amusing park if I try hard, no.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
Like a regular park will do me just fine.
But I haven't been to many and usually when I have
it's like been part of a school thing or like a family thing.
But like, hey kids, since you've been good
we're going on a school trip to Thorpe Park
or Chessington World of Adventures.
I'm like, clean.
These parks sound like work.
Why do they sound like homework textbooks?
I know, I feel like America's a lot more densely packed with amusement parks
because they're just not more everywhere.
I only know those two.
I only know those two and then Legoland.
And then there's a bunch of zoos.
Six Flags Adventures.
No Six Flags, no Disneyland.
You don't know about Six Flags, no?
I know about it.
It's got that, the both of them.
I actually have a picture of 12 year old me posing with the dancing old man
because I went for Six Flags when he was there.
Oh my god!
You have to put that.
I don't remember, but I'll try to find it.
It might be on my old, old Facebook account
that I'll have to reactivate and dig through,
but I'll fucking do it.
Why did they let a monkey into a theme park?
He was working there.
We all know that monkeys work in an amusement park.
Please, please put that on screen right now.
Be insane.
If I find it.
By the way, cool thing about Chessington World of Adventures
is that the land has a literal castle on it
because the people own the estate.
I knew it, I knew it.
You are castles.
We have more castles than amusement parks.
I'm pretty sure.
So turning actual history into a,
this whole fucking castle has no history.
It's not part of the park.
Yeah, fuck the Native Americans, know what I'm saying?
It's just sort of on the hill
and it's the people who own the land own the castle
and you can sort of go up to it,
but I don't think you can go in.
I haven't tried, but yeah.
One of the two theme parks, they're always near me,
is sort of based on a history thing,
but I'll get into that later, tease for the future.
You knock on the castle door.
Where's my starline?
Starline, I ordered it in the area 35 minutes ago
and I'm starting to get queasy.
All right folks, we've talked about the food.
But I've got some insight for you
because I famously worked for a summer at an amusement park.
So let's talk a little bit about the rides.
Yes, finally the main event.
Let me ask you, how much training do you think
each 16-year-old worker gets
before operating this giant piece of machinery
that they're responsible for the lives of all the people on them?
Yeah, how much training do you think I got
for every ride?
There's a reason the most popular undergraduate degree
in the world is amusement park ride operation.
So, you know, good four years.
Moku, are you a carny specifically?
I want to believe that you were a carny clown.
I want to believe you were a fortune teller.
Maybe. I mean, I just operated the rides
but I did predict some future events.
Okay.
So, how'd it go down Moku?
So, the way my amusement park worked,
which I worked at Adventureland,
which is in some city in Iowa, I forget the city,
somewhere around Des Moines,
they didn't want you to get bored at any one ride.
So every single week you would get trained for a different ride
and then do that ride for the whole week
and then move on to the next one.
So by the end of the summer, I had pretty much operated
every ride in the park, which is kind of cool
because then I knew how they all worked.
That sounds like a good idea, yeah.
But, like, you know, you work Monday through Sunday
or whatever the fuck, and the Monday morning,
they give you about five to ten minutes
like telling you how to do the ride,
and then that's it.
And then you just like on your own for the whole week
and you're like a fucking 16 or 17 year old kid.
Awesome.
Did anything go wrong?
Not for me.
Well, that's the thing.
It's always fun because, like,
you're 16 and there's no responsibility.
So you can just, like, tell kids in line
who are waiting like, you know how many kids died
in this ride yesterday, man?
I just got done cleaning the blood off the seats, dude.
Yeah, it's pretty...
Did you actually redo that?
Of course I did. Of course I did.
You're not a carny unless you tell the kids that
another kid died on the ride.
I agree.
Number one dream in life was to become a carny.
That's what he trained day and night for.
But something strange about it
is that I guess amusement parks have
like a weird thing with the child labor laws
because, like, even if you're under 16,
like, 14 year olds were allowed to work
like the restaurants and shit.
Oh, what the fuck?
Yeah, but the thing is, like,
there was no restriction on how many hours.
Like, I was a wee lad
and I was working like 55 hours a week.
Maybe it's because it's like a seasonal job
and, like, there's like a special thing with it.
But, like, I was there
because the morning shift was 5 hours
and the night shift was 7.
And I would just work both because why the fuck not?
I drove all the way there.
So I'd be working, like, you know, 12 hour days,
6 days a week.
And I don't know why they're allowed to do that
for people who are not adults.
It's weird.
That's a very good question.
Y'all need to unionize.
They need a leader.
They need a union-leadered monkey.
You're the man for the job.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I think Unes, I think Monkey Jones.
Instantly.
Elliot Roger did nothing wrong.
That's the platform.
That's what he sounds like, dude.
Sweet Monkey Jones.
See, I'm going to make a new Elliot Roger video.
The cowards will eat it up.
Monkey, did you ever get mumbly?
Mumbly all the time?
Because that's the number one thing.
I'm thinking, how many times do they think
when they start a new day or a new week
thinking, you know what,
I'm going to clearly enunciate
the instructions for this ride
and how many times, how many loops
can they go on before they give up
and just be like, put your hands in the blah, blah, blah, blah.
Oh, I see what you're saying.
Now, I mean, it's like the same
sends over and over again.
It's not too hard.
There was one ride at a theme park
and a fucking pre-recorded thing
by a professional.
It was like, keep your hands in the sea
at all times.
I was like, holy shit, this is great.
You can hear it perfectly.
It's way more pleasant to listen to
because it's with an actual microphone
and they got rid of it at some point
and went back to the mumbly teenager
and I'm like, I don't blame them.
This is a broken system.
Why not use pre-recordings?
Dude, that was the best.
Disneyland is broken up in two parks.
One is actually Disneyland and then there's a sister park.
It's like across the fucking...
You just walk two seconds and then you get into another one.
It's called California Adventure.
There's a ride that's called a Soren over California.
Something in that effect.
In fact, David Putty from Seinfeld
walks out and he's in this fucking snazzy
pouts outfit and he's like, it's me, David Putty.
Fucking keep your fucking
slut hands to yourself, bitch.
And then he slams the door on your face
and then you get this cool
like AMV of real life
while you jam the fuck out
and like fly.
AMV of real life.
There was one ride called, I don't know,
some generic crazy scientist name.
It's one of those indoor rides
that has all these crazy lighting effects
and it spins you around a bunch.
But the line to the ride is also indoors
and it's got this TV
that played this intro sequence
and it's got several minutes
of intro of world building
and it's very built the invention
and like what he did and how he did it
and what it's all about and what the ride is
and like, but you can't hear any of it
because it's too crowded and loud
but I was like, why'd they fill all this shit?
I know what you're saying, but I think
I know what they're aspiring to when they do that
because like the best atmosphere
of any ride I've ever been on
was the Tower of Terror in Disney World.
Yeah.
Which has this grand buildup, you're in this hotel
and they're like, oh, these are the guests
and like the line is so fucking long
like you get plenty of time to watch
the whole story as it unfolds on the TVs around you
and the whole place is like decked out
there's bell hops fucking each other
in the corners and shit.
The atmosphere is perfect
and then it builds up and like the same voice
that we use for the narrator is like
as you're finally on the ride and it lifts you up
and you're looking out at the park through the cracks
and like the broken down walls of the hotel
it's like goodbye and then
you go falling as the fucking ride kicks off
and it's such a great atmospheric adventure
that was so fucking great.
Two points on that.
First of all, the Tower of Terror is literally the best ride up
they fucking removed it
they removed it from Disneyland
they got rid of it.
What about Disney World?
Well, I don't know about Disney World
but I don't care about that because it's probably gay.
Anyway, and fucking Disneyland, the Tower of Terror
was like the coolest fucking thing ever
and it was like it was in California Adventure
because it was like oh fuck it, there's a California hotel
who would think they could make a Twilight Zone ride
and make it actually like cool
but you know what, they fucking removed it
and it was like iconic, it was iconic
everyone loved the Tower of Terror, it was fucking incredible.
I forgot that, that makes it even better
but I will say
hold on, they removed it
and they placed it with a fucking
Guardians of the Galaxy
It's Nate, you haven't seen
either movie so you don't get it grown
first of all.
It's one of the greatest cinematic masterpieces
of the small screen of all time, I know that much.
Isn't it the movie where Max Landis' dad killed
two people in Cold Blood?
I'm not talking about the Rod Sterling show
that's what I'm talking about.
I know about no movie.
I've got a Rod Sterling for you, Wing.
Well okay, so as much as I love that
that's not my favorite ride of all time
okay, my favorite ride of all time
is in a little place you might have heard of
called Tokyo Nippon, alright
and I rode this every single day
called the subway system
of Tokyo, Japan
so you get on this thing
and they really create atmosphere
there's all these slant-eyed actors looking at you
there's obviously something
there's all these yellows
I appreciate the commitment of the character
of these fucked up individuals
and the little announcer is like
ah, Denwa, doors are now closing
you fat American fuck
and I'm like yeah, thanks dude, I get it
and then I ride, I ride, I ride
I've experienced it my whole life, I did it every day
several times a day, it was cheap as fuck
I wish I lived somewhere where there was a subway
so I could do it again, I love subways
Subways are my favorite amusement park ride
I like thrilling rides, Nate, but I like scarier rides
I'm trying to buy all those ghouls
and freaks, I might make my heart pound
a little bit too fast there
I think you might be going a little bit to
an over the line there
that's understandable
escalator land
when do we get to the ride
is the ride
yippee
what a classic
incredible, thank you
did anybody else think that show was called fairy god
parents and not fairly odd parents
that's fucking bullshit
I was playing a Nickelodeon trivia game
and the question was like what's the show
with Timmy and I was like oh that's fucking
fairy god parents dude and I got it wrong
cause it was fairly odd parents
fucking bullshit name
Timmy was an average kid
that oh I don't understand
mom and dad and vicki
only give me names
and then he went to fucking go
and get his garden
and then we practiced
and then he was shot
and then we went to school
there was no parents
did you guys see that they changed the theme song
cause they have a new female character
who is sharing the fairy god parents
with Timmy and it's fucking terrible
I haven't seen it but I heard about it
okay, alright, Gib was saying something
what would you say Gib
I was gonna start talking about my favorite ride
which
they're probably like all the rides I've ever been on
are probably worse than all American ones
just because
you know, I don't know
it's probably smaller I assume
I assume everything in America is like 10 feet
taller than everything in England
yeah, that's right
like people included
as I've encountered
alright, guys
we're gonna get back to the whole thing of discussing
everybody's favorite deep berks
hey, hip-hop is talking
sorry, I had to go do a thing
for a minute and had to come back
and re-announce myself
why would you
what did you think we were doing
theme songs
you shouldn't open with
fair enough
anyway, um, yeah
I love Davoo
I've never been into roller coasters
they scare me, especially
even the one at Legoland, like there's a one at Legoland
where it's a green
green
yeah dude
it was the first one I ever made myself go on
and I tensed up
my whole body so that I basically
blacked out and I couldn't see and I died
but it was really cool
but later in my life
when I had glasses
and I was at this theme
I was at Thorpe Park for like
the end of school year
hey kids, we're taking you to
we're taking you to a thing
and everyone's like, yeah
it's cool, we're all friends
and I'm like, oh no, I don't have those
but this will be the moment
this will be the time in my life
when I can have the cool day out
with everyone and become cool
and it was alright
but I was too scared to go on the rides
because I'd never really tried them
and I hate it
so there was this one roller coaster
where I was like, I gotta do it with somebody
I gotta do it at some point, I just gotta do it
so I got onto this thing
and it's one of those rides where you like
your legs are dangling down below
and I got in
I was like fucking scared out of my mind
and we were going
and then one of the guys on my left
said, hey
you didn't put your glasses away
you got your glasses on
they're gonna fall off and I'm like
what? I didn't know that was gonna happen
so frantically
I was just trying to
you have the thing around your shoulders
my arms couldn't
really quite reach around
but I could just about get my pinky finger
wrapped around the rim of my glasses
and I was just holding on, I could feel it slipping off my face
and I was concentrating on that the whole time
and I was just scrunched up and like
weird and when we got through the end
I was just
so relieved that I managed to keep my glasses on
but then they had the picture come out
with like, here's you guys
and all these cool guys
they're like screaming with a big mouth
exactly how you're supposed to look
and there's me scrunched up, eyes closed
like a weird twisted
dead bug holding on to my little glasses
a freak, a monster
I looked disgusting and nobody said anything
but I knew, I was like
I've been there dude
I've been on those rides trying to hold on
my various eye-wares that I wear
all the time, yeah
that would be hard, you have to just duct tape them to your head
yeah, but that was cool
that got me okayed
with roller coasters but I think the
most fun I had was
recently this summer, I went
to one because
you may know, I do like
a yearly week
with helping disabled kids
there's like a week camp
and I do that stuff
it's about time Ben got that help that he needed
it's pretty rude that you call that a week camp
for these week people
it's a week long camp
and one of the days we go out
to a amusement park and
the last time I went, I think it was
Chessington World of Adventures
there's two in the whole of the UK
and we went to the second one
and there was like a virtual reality
3D headset ride
that was super fast and it was like planets exploding
with a
Cortana lady saying
you're going through, we're going to warp speed
now and I'm like, oh my goodness
whoa, it was great
because I didn't have to
look at the ground, I could just feel
like I was going through space
so that was good, I like that
it's interesting to see how VR
gets worked more into riots as we
move into our future because the whole point
of an amusement ride to begin with is to
simulate the feeling of death
that's what they're really for, to make you terrified
your core and think, I'm about to die
and you get that dopamine rush to your brain
which we enjoy, so if we could just do that
sitting on our asses through VR
then it'd be a lot cheaper
the moment that we get that, the whole issue
with theme parks is that people are slowly
realizing that there's just not much fun
to be had that you can't just have in your bedroom
on the internet
I would say
that ride is the perfect
and only good usage of a VR headset
I've ever seen
you were flying through the air
you could feel the wind
buffeting your whole body
there's no wind in space
so how could that be true
we were all thinking that
I think that it'll always be
as long as human beings have physical bodies
and are basically the same creature that we are now
which might not always be the case
but while we are something like an amusement park
we'll always have a utility
just for the sake of changing your surroundings
sometimes I mean I spend all fucking
day looking at my computer and working and shit
in the exact same like 3 foot
location at all times
either at home or at work
and to just divert
from that for a time and go somewhere else
and do something that's just out of the norm
God it feels good
God I love it
I sort of joked earlier about like a normal park
being just enough for me
I'm easily amused but it's kind of true
just a change of environment
is really nice
and the thing with actual parks
is that there's not that many people in them
amusement parks
scare me with the
huge crowds
I'm not good with the huge crowds
I have many memories
I have a lot of memories of getting
separated from brothers or family members
or friends and stuff
and not being the one
with the map and being like
I mean I'm just gonna die
I'm just gonna walk
to dino land and jump
into a mouth
Speaking of crowds
there was one crowd related story
it's actually the opposite of what you're saying
but there was one time when my family
we all went to Six Flags, New England
in Springfield, Massachusetts
and so it was like
the end of the day I don't remember what day it was
but for whatever reason it wasn't a very full day
but at the very end of the
day as the place was closing down
it was like 6pm or something I think
I think it closes kind of early whatever day that was
so we happened to be there and like nobody was there
and me and my dad were just like
you know what we went on the Superman roller coaster
instantly one of the greatest roller coasters in the world
everyone should ride it
it's super fun that big
dive at the very beginning
but the point is
me and my dad went on it
and we realized after we got out
then we came back we were like let's do it again before we leave
at the end of the day so we went at it again
and we realized there's literally no line
let's just do it again
and so we did it again three full
times over and over again on this roller coaster
well I'm sure the people running it
rolled their eyes they're like oh look at these
look at these cool customers riding the same ride
a million times but fuck them
me and my dad had so much fun on that ride
it was fucking fantastic I love
Superman and that roller coaster
it was great so crowds can get fucked
I hope everyone dies
Isis I've got a couple targets
for you mapped out on my map here
some places where a lot of people gather
you can just clear them out for me
it'd be very convenient for me
let's make that happen
ride a roller coaster three times is a pretty good exchange
for not having locks on your doors
fair bargain
what are you getting at
I'm not getting at anything
oh
we're gonna say our favorite
T-Tarks
let's do that
I forgot to mention the reason I brought up
the like thing with the
VR thing
the reason I brought up the disabled kids thing
was because I had to go
on the ride with them otherwise
I'm a helper I can't
they were fine the person I was with
they were having a blast
could you imagine being so retarded you can't sit down
and get buckled in
I can't imagine
those kids didn't
it's hard to deal with kids
people who are retarded literally mean slow
so they're like deal with kids
you go fast because they're on the ride
yes
that's true
we're bringing them up to speed baby
oh yes
I don't have a favorite theme park
by the way because I'm gay
no wait Legoland
that's the one
you do Legoland
I also
it's a toss up between Legoland and Disneyland for me
I also love Universal Studios
my least favorite is by far SeaWorld
super fucking boring
and they don't let you get to see them
torture the animals they do it behind the scenes
they don't like you to see it
ever since they stopped murdering Shamu for our enjoyment
that place has really gone down
I want to see blood in the fucking water
she deserves it
but what always upset me is I would always think
like SeaWorld
water park vlogs
I want to go there
we haven't even got to water parks
that's going to be the whole park tour of this podcast
I would always want to go there
to get wet but then I would like
there's like no wet
you need kind of wet like Shamu can like splash you
but like I don't know
I want to get dripping I want to get sloppy
I want to get mushy
that's what I want but I couldn't do it
I wouldn't think of SeaWorld as a water park
I think of it as like a fucking aquarium
yeah it's pretty much an aquarium
it's just supposed to but I don't know
I want to see the fucking
guys just okay everybody
alright take a journey with me everybody
just close your eyes
and think back to when you were like
14 years old
it's the summer time the sun's beaten down
that was like 10 days ago from Munch
I know
you're on a class trip everybody
you're wearing your swim trunks you got your t-shirt on
you're going on rides
you're checking out your 14 year old classmates
with their burgeoning titties
you're looking at what they got
you're hanging out with all your friends
it's nice and warm
you're getting the fucking ice cream from the vendors
you're going on rides and shit
you're spilling them everywhere but it doesn't matter
because you just go in the lazy river
and you chill with your buddies
and you're hanging out there for an hour
as you just lazily drift
it's the most fun you've ever had in your fucking life
this is what I'm getting at
water parks are the greatest thing in the world
I love water parks intensely
I love the lazy river
I was born in a lazy river and one day I will die there
that's my destiny
I do like those but I never like water parks
purely because
I got to wear a swimsuit
and I can't wear a shirt and it's like
I'm embarrassed about my gross body
it's not cool enough
it's not cool enough to be seen
wear a surfershirt
what the fuck is that
we're an under armor compression shirt
to shape your muscles
people are going to know
he's trying to hide something
okay your problem is you give a shit
fuck him dude
you're there to check out 14 year old tits
you're not there to impress anybody
I'll go there today
I think if Ben Saint has the courage
to go outside we should all have the courage
to be naked in public
I agree
water parks are great
there's a water park that's near my house
that's local and there's this giant ride
I think it's called
literally the toilet
and what you do is you just walk up to
the top of this very huge
it's like a funnel
that is the rise
it's slanted
so what you do is you just get up to the top of this thing
and you get in this little
it's kind of like the lazy river
you sit your ass in
and then what happens is
I don't know if I can draw this diagram
but just imagine you get pushed
you get fucking shoved
you ride the
the water wave spiral
you do a spiral in the funnel
and it's straight down
it's sideways so you're going up
and you're defying gravity
going upside down on this fucking funnel
until you finally get spit out
and you get destroyed
just think about the bizarre engineering work
to make these like strange death machines
just to make ourselves
have fun for a little while
it's so cool, I love the idea of making
amusement park rides
it's so like retarded
but it's the coolest thing ever
I actually do have a favorite amusement park ride
which is
I don't remember what it's called
the tin turning wheel thing
it's one of those ones where you're in a giant coffee cup
and it spins and it sucks you into the wall
tea cups, tea cups, tea cups or whatever
it's like the silly silo
where it spins in a circle and you stick to the wall
and the floor drops
one of the theme parks I live near
they have one that's the one that goes
way up and it goes sideways and stuff
but that one's fine
but they have this other really old one
I wouldn't be surprised if it was gone
if I went there again
it feels very 70s, it's got like carpet and stuff
even though it's outside
and it's just so tucked
out of the way where people don't notice it
so it's very
unpopular which means there's almost
never a line I always get to go right in there
so because of that
experience and the aesthetic of it
that makes it my favorite ride because it
consistently doesn't have a line to wait through
yeah
yeah that's great
accessibility and like
isn't that a great experience to like find this great ride
that other people just don't know about
and you've got there's just there's something about this
that is so linked with like my
happiest childhood memories
everything having to do with amusement parks
it just makes me happy to think about
it's just such a joy
I love these, this is like the one thing
that I like about children
or that like things are made for children
other than their bodies
other than their sexy ass blooming bodies
fortunately they won't give me a call
every single one
all right, I'll send you a snap right after this podcast
Nate
sounds good
yeah fuck Disney World
I know what the best amusement park is
motherfucking thrillville baby
look at thrillville go
here comes ps2 zero
you can go
you can go flirt with a fucking 12 year old kid
it's fun, you don't get arrested for it
I do in real life all the time dude
well that's legal for you
some of us get arrested for that
thrillville you think a ride's dumb
you fucking get rid of that shit and build a new one
it's easy, it's fucking easy
you don't even want to finish the roller coaster
you just want to say let it crash
you can do that, it's easy, it's fun
does that hurt your morale for the workers
well it probably helps the work of morale
but it depresses total earnings
the janitors don't like it because they have a lot of blood and guts to clean up
but everybody else enjoys it
because the kids are dead
we should have a ride on thrillville
Billy Johnson
he's a 12 year old boy, I ride him a lot
Ayo
look at pedophiles go
here they come, jails hero
does anybody have similar stories to this
so I've had a couple of incidents that happened like this
but basically what I'm talking about is like
so there's this batman ride or it was like a night wing ride
it probably has changed since I was last there
at six flags so it's this thing where you
it's like a spinny circle that just
lifts in the air and then you kind of like fly
you lie down like on your stomach you get kind of
squished into this thing and you hold on to the bars
then it just like spins you like towards your face
like you're flying like Superman
so actually it should have been called the Superman ride
I don't know why it's called the batman ride but anyway
so like we get in there and like the ride
starts and we all like get into position
and then the ride like shuts down
like it gets stuck like that
so I was there
for probably like 45 minutes until like
they pride me out of there
and I have situations where I'm like at the top of a roller coaster
like about to go down
and then the ride like gets stuck
and then you're stuck there
it's broken though
that's never happened
I've been on ones that get stuck and then like
someone climbs up and fixes a thing but only for a few minutes
see it's at those kinds of moments
that you realize how stupid it is
to even be doing this in the first place
and how like an amusement park ride
is not what man was meant to do
with the physical form
I know one roller coaster that has like these
like stairs at like the top of the
initial peak the initial peak
that gets you going up there's these little like you know
steel steps but like you have to go up
you have to like like I actually saw it once
a maintenance worker has to get on the ride
then stop the roller coaster
before it goes down the peak and he steps off
and then he goes on those little steppy things
and I'm like whoa that's a cool
as perilous place to work to like do your job
I do have a similar
I do have a somewhat I have a very just just a frustrating
shitty gay experience which was
this one log flume that has like
the longest line in the fucking
world and it's a 45 second
ride like one second
of ride is one minute of line
and it closed
when we were like three people away from
getting on oh god damn it
I've had that happen to me too it's the worst
I was like why the fuck
don't they put a giant
stop sign on the
beginning of the line 45
minutes before closing
that is such logic
easy problem to solve you just stop people from getting
in line as opposed to stopping them when it's
time to shut it down it's so easy to do
but they just don't give a fuck
they don't give a fuck they're going to ruin
children's lives
my favorite ride
is probably
the simpsons ride for the incredible
atmospheric vibe that I get just
being in line
just like the aesthetics
match the gameplay wholeheartedly
just when you hear that
you'd hear that voice coming over the PA
Homer what are those monsters
doing over there I don't understand
no those are those are saying
fire is skeleton
that is not a good mo impression at all
it's not mo
so uh yeah
actually like the second part of the ride where it gets to like
so let's say some gangsta steps to
your fly girl you just did it
a Q
shotgun blast yeah okay there you go
the simpsons ride is legitimately fucking sick
it's sick as fuck it's fucking
lol it makes me laugh
so fucking hard
and uh
like I don't even like the ride
it's like the line of the ride
because we are in line to get to the ride
you have to wait like 45 minutes and then
you just like blast simpsons ebony
into your redna and then it's like
behind the scenes like lore
about how like that one fucking funny yellow guy
who wants to get
the simpsons
and then you can just see him do the funny fucking
scheme on the tv
that's actually great when they put effort into
like the setup leading to the ride itself
that's good like the uh
like the fucking uh
charlotte's own ride
lego land
foam bionicle sword
uh
i love that
i have that exact one
i love the bionicle fucking shit
it's the coolest
lego land is like the only place that
deserves to have a gift shop
hippo i'm assuming you
you didn't go to the one in california right
no no i feel like they're the same
everywhere i went to lego land
oh okay okay um they're probably the same
anywhere uh yeah um um oh my
did you get your driver's license at lego land
did you get your fucking cool ass little car
yeah dude what the fuck is that
it's stupid
dude they tell you don't bump people
but you totally do it
i actually
i actually remember a time when there was an old lady
just in there like what the fuck are you
doing i guess she's like looking over after a kid
who's also in there so i attacked her
i just rammed her
you see weak blood and you go for it
oh that's good
time is over grandma this is the
youth's ride now
i i yeah so that that was sick
um you went full uh clockwork
orange at that moment you just went full
monster mode yeah okay yeah uh
lego land is is is cool
because you know the rides are alright
but the the main thing is that every
everything is made of lego
yes the stalls
the signs the
no no like really like i don't believe you
they're made of lego's
because they're alright
there's like huge lego statues
that are made by having like
like a metal frame
i've seen it not being done at the
place but i know how they do it they get
lego and they super glue it together so
it's just perfectly forever going to be
it's like literally a statue and they do it
for fucking everything
in the place like even the plants
some of the plants are made of lego it's like
yeah i i i feel
i feel like playing minecraft right now i love
it you're telling me on lego land
did you have did you have like the dinosaur
fossil ride
oh i i mean
i the the version of lego land
i went to maybe different from yours because
of our age difference
i don't know i haven't been in a long time
but oh well yeah yeah
like there's one uh for me
where it's like uh like like like while you were
online you could like you could like there's like a
sand pit and you could like get like a cool
thing like a pickaxe you could like get like
fossil like lego fossils in the sand
while you fucking while you were
in line holy shit
yes level that sounds great
and and and then when you get up you gotta
climb some like stairs and then like the guy
working it for me was always like it's fucking
me it's a fucking lego land
pays me $100 on the coolest
big dick motherfucker you'll ever see
i was like can can you
say the funny stuff was mine
he's like here's the funny stuff
was like oh my god
thank you and then they
pushed me and he fucking got me on that shit
and i ran and i saw a dinosaur
they were made out of lego
they're all made out of lego
i think there was a dinosaur land
area it's it's just it's
it was just marvelous to just think like
i have lego's at home i can make
a thing about as big as a football if i
really tried but these
these guys have so much lego
bricks that i'm very jealous of the amount
that they can use to build a literal
side life size dinosaur to block
my path and kill me in my sleep
i love it dude that one green dragon ride
you were talking about it was my favorite fucking thing
that was the first time i ever did an accidental
kegel exercise that was the first
time i asked you i did a kegel
it wasn't even on my own volition but but i
did it i did i that was the first time i ever did a kegel
it was fucking crazy i'm doing
my kegels right now i do every pcp
yeah dude same
trained up dude gotta be trained up
gotta be toned
now of course there's
there's all the kids shit you know there's the baby lego
place duplo disgusting
never been
but
what i always liked like as i got older
like we i went a couple times
like a number of times and as i got older
i see i appreciated more and more
the miniature village
made out of lego which is like
the huge like big like a
million things like tiny little little lego
people and lego cars some of which
i'm gonna come
and and and i think
i remember in windsor they did have
like a lego big ben you know like like
landmarks like like really
impressive huge things i'm like
i'm walk i'm i'm a giant right now but
this is lego and so small but it's like
it's like big but i'm small it's like
it's the coolest fucking shit i've ever seen
dude the the land of fucking
like like mini land was so fucking cool first
okay okay but also okay you know okay i don't
think you're gonna have this because it's like it i remember this being like a new
thing that like while i was going to lego and this was like a new
thing that like they just came out with
there like the ceo's like like like john lego
was in his fucking ceo born
and it was like you know what would make
lego land even better if it was
a water park too
and so
the water is made of lego
so my god they opened up like a new
area it was like pirate themed it could
go in and there was there was a there was like a lazy
lazy river and like and like the fucking like
things like you eat like okay the like
the tube you get in there was like it was like
just normal rubber but then there was like parts
of the thing that you could stick your own lego's
onto and just like build while you're inside
of the lazy river
and then and then there was this ride where you
could like get on a fucking cool ass fucking slide and there's one where you
can like ride a pirate ship and shoot fucking water
people okay oh I have that
I remember that bit so it's like this okay
okay there's there's like a little like pool
area where people just are like on you know
pirate ships and they can just you know shoot other people
but then also but also it's like right now there's
like a sidewalk there's like a there's
like a pathway that's like right up next to the pool
and there's like guns on the sidewalk so if you're
just like a walking by you're not even on the ride
you can shoot the people on the ride just like a
second or two and just fucking ruin them you can
just rape them you can just fucking kill them
and it's fucking sick and I love the
land I love the land oh I
like to see the funny fucking lego
it's great let's go to questions everybody
oh wait wait wait the first question
I fucking got you I memed you all
so hard okay all right go ahead
I have I have one more thing to say and
then I'm done saying things
I remembered during the course of this that there
was a very more more of a quaint
theme park on the isle
of white which is like an island
just to the south of here just just for
no black people right I understand okay yeah
well white with a whatever
bitch
it's a tiny little island and it has
this tiny theme park which is based
on what the isle of white
is known for is like known for smuggling
because it's like a good place for pirates to smuggle
shit and it's called black gang shine
if anybody in the audience has been to
black gang shine
it's
so fucking cool it's
it's a place my dad used to go
for every holiday he and
his family would go to black gang shine and he brought
me and my brothers to there
and now there's like a like a it's like a
our family heirloom is that theme park is great
and
if I get an image
there's a giant shine you said
yeah shine like
c-h-i-n-e
oh okay okay yeah
and it's pirate smuggler themed
and it's just it's so cool
it's a giant pirate
smuggler a statue at the entrance
and it's not like the biggest
that's awesome
I just have a lot of fun memories
of it there's like this western
town area
and a dinosaur place
it's not like the greatest place ever
the smugglers are well known for smuggling
dinosaurs in and out of this island
oh and there was this one thing
oh it's so scary
it was like a trick mirror thing
it's a little castle area
and you go in there and there's this
this beautiful lady behind the glass
and she's like you listen to the audio playing
it's like I'm a lady I'm normal
I'm not evil and then
after like five minutes of speaking
there's suddenly a scary music plays
boom and then there's like
a mirror trickery thing where
she physically looks like
she turns into a monster
but it's like because she's reflected from a mirror
and you can't see the mirror as you're looking through the window
so I thought like she's literally
like an actual demon suddenly
and I jumped and I pissed my pants and I ran away
but I love that so much
I hope it's still there I want to go back there
when I have kids and show them
and force them to piss their pants and die
yeah I love
that place so much if anybody knows that place
that's great that's the coolest
fuck yeah I have a few more
points here as well I mean I could go out about theme parks all day
I have tons of memories from them
because you know the most important thing I just want to comment on
like the restaurants in theme parks are like
usually shit but like
one of the best restaurants I've ever been to
and people will test this because it's super fucking expensive
is the blue bayou at Disneyland
do they have the equivalent of
the blue bayou at Disney World
do you know what that is
it doesn't ring a bell I'm not sure
you all know the price of the Caribbean ride right
of course of course
you are on a boat
and there's like a slow river
there's a little bit of dips and ups
kind of like an atmospheric
New Orleans sort of like a swamp setting
but inside of this
imagine the ride as a
circle that's like pretty big
in the middle
behind the trees of the ride behind like the props
of the ride there is a fucking
super ass
smug ass like anime expert
rooftop soiree
fucking like fancy
Louisiana fancy restaurant
inside of the ride
and you can see all the cool fucking like
pirates and all like the cool like like
ride people taking the ride while you're eating these
fucking like million dollar steaks
and like all like Obama
was there I think it's fucking crazy
it's so fucking cool
it's in the middle of a ride what
what other place what other place what other
restaurant is good and inside
of a ride perfect
props for that that's pretty amazing
it's fucking sick I love it
world building
exactly I should mention that I'm going to Disneyland
on the 23rd
oh my god
for my birthday
party
if you want to meet up with munchie too bad
because this came out the day after
get a look at
donky go
you said it might do
one last thing
while it's not
exactly an amusement park I went to the
Nickelodeon hotel in Florida
when I was a wee baby
hey I did that too
that's where we stayed during our thing
I think
it might be confusing things up whatever
let's make the pcp hq
at the Nickelodeon hotel please
that's a good idea
assigned sealed and the check is in the mail
from Obama to us
for endorsement hotel change
so yeah so I went there
his full name is
Obama Hussein slime
Obama
Nickelodeon slime guy
excellent
the reason he's so into slime is because black people are so intrusive
in slimy
he just takes some slime off from their body
just carves them off and puts on
his meals
anyway so while I was at the Nickelodeon hotel
there was this big sort of
mini water park
slide apparatus where you could get
water
the important thing is it was Miami
or around there at least
there was about to be a thunder storm
and also probably hurricane
that was like about to destroy
you should go inside
probably and not be where the lightning is
that was the first time I ever played Battlefront 2
that was also the first trip where I
like while in Florida it's slightly off topic
but I saw an alligator for the first time
I was like this is my favorite thing ever
I also got really sick because I touched one
what if an alligator was also
investigating something
hello look at don't go
here he comes but never have a
kind of on this hero
hey don't go
let's go let's go
do we have a
which prostitute would you rather
fuck at the Nickelodeon hotel
as told by ginger
or Jenny the robot
from my life as a teen robot
Jenny the robot obviously
her it amuses me
how much her popularity has exploded
via porn after the show ended
dill pickles yeah
I would fuck the main stormtrooper
I don't think dill pickles is a fucking prostitute
neither is Jenny
she's a classy young lady goddammit
he's a one year old baby
not an all grown up
he's available
in all grown up he's an obnoxious 10 year old piece of shit
oh dude
he's not one he's just 10
he's just 5
I mean that's better right
I would rather fuck a 10 year old
than a one year old baby
serious question would it be better to fuck
a one year old or a 10 year old for their sake
cause if they're one they might not remember getting fucked
but if they're 10 you could fuck them up a lot
you can't fit your dick in a baby
I can find a way
I mean not me ask her a friend here
oh no
no no
there goes her amortization
there goes my hero
look at donkey go
that's the rule of threes baby
there it is
wait wait let me test it
let's see if it's 20 the fourth time
look at donkey go
no nobody left
oh shit boy
before the recording started you were talking about
the idea of having a sound board for the PCP
that you're in control of
I would absolutely love a there goes our
amortization sound
that is a great idea
oh that's unfortunate
do you have anything to say about fair
since they're kind of related
no I want to go to quest
I talked about that renaissance fair for a bit
we could stretch that out to a whole other PCP
yeah
press one if you want to hear an old PCP about fairs
first carnivals and festivals
all the places were clowns
and they're a congregate
I just need episode of only me
I'll invite my special guest the japanese juggalope
he's the underteller who was on this one
that's an excellent idea
here we go to questions everybody
here's one from twitter
you guys literally just didn't even get to me
I had a lot to say
fuck me I guess
why don't you interrupt sooner or something
I guess
I mean
really it's more like
I thought that this podcast was going to go in a totally different direction
I thought we were going to be talking more about
the need more analysis
since it ended up just being a bunch of memories
so I guess
yeah I have a lot to say about
it's not a fucking anime for children you can't analyze
it
is a
designer of roller coasters
you know exactly
I'm coming on forever
roller coasters forever
I can go as long as we want
so fucking
if I was at a theme park
the board meeting
when they talk about how they're going to invent theme parks
it's the origin of theme parks
board meeting sounds like a cool fun meeting
if you ask me
I would have put down my papers
don't go
I'm sorry
I would have put down my papers and adjusted my bifocals
and looked at the guy
in the middle of the pitch for theme parks
well if people are going to be standing around
for like three hours a day
in lines and this idea is not going to work
come up with something else you know
because that's what I always feel like when I'm in a line
at the theme park where I'm like this whole idea
like as much fun as I've had at theme parks
I feel like my experience with them has been
weirdly mixed and that like
I just feel like the whole idea
like just doesn't really work yet
we really need to live in like a post-singularity
post-scarcity society
before theme parks can really work
what are you talking about
they're economically viable right now right
I assume they would be
go on to questions this is a different topic
no no no
you can't get away that easy
like lines are long
but what are you
what are you going to do about it huh
what is your actual like
you buy a fast pass for 100 bucks
just go in the exit and get right in the right
or if you're with a disabled person
you can go right to the front
dude I abused so many
disabilities while I was at Disneyland
I abused so many
my fucking my crack smoking
uncle is like dude
like one time I was shot in the arm and I don't have an arm anymore
so like give me some tickets bro
and they're like okay and then I fucking
I stole them from him
and I did all the rides very fast
oh there you go
I'm like paying it forward
cause I've only been to like two theme parks really
really two that are near me
and my parents are like why go to other ones
so I've been to those two so many times
that I feel like I've sort of like
I'm sort of like the illusion sort of breaks
right so I get more of a cynical view
I really want to go to other theme parks once in a while
and like do that
yeah yeah but like there's this one called worlds of fun
which is like
themed after the world
so it's like different areas of different countries
more like board meeting
is it like Epoch kind of
it's like it was a China area
a fucking America area
and it's the most boring bog standard theming ever
and you don't even notice it cause it's not even thick enough
it's like it's such a subtle theme
you don't notice it and it's boring and stupid
and like and like my
my parents which is mostly
most of the time I've gone to theme parks with my parents
they're just really bad at having fun
they like they don't understand how to have fun
like they don't like to um
they don't like to fork over the excess of money for food
so they always like pack lunches and like
so not fun god damn it
I came here to waste money god damn
yeah exactly
they always like walk back to the car
cause they don't want to take it to the park
yeah and I'm like why
this is so fucking stupid
I don't want to waste money
I would rather have like a yummy turkey sandwich that my mom made
than an 8 dollars and 50 cents fucking hot dog
well it depends
I think with that it's like uh
sandwiches and stuff it's always like
kinda gooey and gross cause it's been in a hot car
it's not the same
my dad always put a cooler and I got cool packs in it
and shit you know so
my parents did that too
it's like all the inconvenience of camping
being like crowbarred into
an already expensive experience
of going to a theme park
but yeah that's really the big issue for me
I never want to feel like I have enough money to spend
and it always feels like
it's just constantly fighting me to spend more money
so that in combination with lines
in combination with going to the same two theme parks forever
like the other theme park we have
which is like 4 hours away
is called Silver Dollar City
which actually has
a theme right it has like an aesthetic
which is like
old timey america right so like 1800s
because
it was all based around a cave
cause Missouri has a lot of caves apparently
so these people
like owned the cave back in the 50s
and they started showing the cave off
and selling tickets to it
so eventually they started like having
attractions on the line
leading up to the cave
and people ended up just watching the attractions
so then they started building restaurants
and then they started building rides
and so eventually it became a theme park
all around a cave right
but it all was extrapolated
off of the aesthetic of
you know the
the homesteading americans
who found the cave right
and also the indians who also found the cave
according to the guy guiding us through the cave
like how the who the fuck
reported on that story I don't know
also when we descend into the cave
on their man-made staircase they play the theme
of the empire from Star Wars
the dum-bum-ba-dum-bum-ba-dum-bum-ba-dum
I'm like whoa
but yeah it's a really cool theme park
why that specifically
I know right well it's cool cause you're going into
this big cave you know
but like it's a cool theme park
because it has all one
tone one setting
and it's very consistent
you know everything feels like old timey america
the rides are like
the fire in the hole
which is like an indoor roller coaster
all about fighting fires before we had hoses and shit
so it's really terrifying you know
and like they've got like
what's it like
like a TNT themed roller coaster
and so much shit like that
and you know it's also christian too
I think like christians own it
so sometimes there can be like
there can be like some christian
like there can be like some country singers
at one of the little theater places
the most country thing possible
yeah yeah and like they can like incorporate god stuff
and it doesn't break immersion
because it's old timey america right
so it like works right
I don't know where I was going with this
but like oh yeah they even have a
they have like a haunted house but it's themed after
you know like an old timey mansion
and it's really cool with like a
five degrees tilted and it's the coolest
possible experience of life
is it built on an ancient
in a native american burial ground
oh it should be man they should like expand
like find an age of american burial ground
go there and build it
and let all the engine spirits out
okay you're right sorry I like theme parks
I just I just it's just like
the last couple times we went to one
it was just we weren't in the mood to do a vacation
you know like it's just it's hard to get me in the mood
to vacation you know it's just like
theme parks are hard
with like a family of
various different ages particularly when
my sister was very small because it's like
she couldn't go on any rides and my parents
were too old to care to go on rides
and it was like this sucks right I need to go
with just my friends and my girlfriend which I could
probably afford to do now
I've never been to a theme park by myself
but I feel like I would enjoy it
a lot because of the
because of the freedom to just
not do anything if I don't feel like it
every time you're with a person you're like
are you having fun do you want to do this
I guess we'll do this what about you
huh
who's hungry let's go get food oh I don't
I'm not hungry well I mean
you're a kid so you got to come
with us well you know
I do like going if you can go with like someone that you
you know just like a good friend who
vibes with you well one person or two people
like if I were with any of you guys I'm sure we would
have a good time because we don't give a fuck about what the other
person thinks you can just tell me if you're having a
problem or something and then you know we'll
immediately fix it as opposed to like a friend
you don't know as well who just acts cagey and won't
be upfront about what they want to do or whatever
you know that's bullshit I treat amusement parks a lot
like conventions as I described
in the convention pockets where it's just
very this is they're much better than convention in
the way it's just a cool way to hang out with your
friends and if you invite your buddy it's a cool
time and just to do things
that you might die on and it makes you feel
like more like brothers
also DeVoo once
the PCPHQ happens I will take you
specifically to an amusement park and we will go
together yeah I realize
like yeah going with the PCP would be great because
you guys because even my offline
friends who I've had throughout my life and gone to theme parks
with aren't good at having fun either
and my favorite thing about
being in the PCP is you like
there's enough people who are good at having fun I could
just coast on it and have a great
time so we yeah I'd love to
do
Red Con 3 should just be at a theme park
hey
by the way I just want to say you mentioned
Christian themes and I just wanted to mention
one of the most one of the most thrilling
experiences I had at one
of these
amusement type place was at the
creationist museum where
they there's a so there's like
an Ark ride where you can just go walk on a life
size recreation of Noah's Ark
that's what he actually wrote on I
didn't do that but they did give
us the real scoop there was a whole you know
walk-through place where they did educate us on what
really went down so just so everybody knows
dinosaurs were on the Ark
they were there they just died off
unrelatedly afterward that's just
this is so you know that's how it went down
I didn't worry about that because I want to know if the Legoland
ride looked at any part about Jesus
or Noah's Ark
Oh Nate, at Creation Museum
did they have like a live reenactment
of a monkey not turning into a human
Racism
How dare you
By the way, it's just
that you cite a museum as a theme park because I would also do
that for there there's a there's
like a like there is an actual
real there's an actual real like
United States Navy like
battleship turn museum because it's so fucking
old called United States midway
and it's
docked here permanently in San Diego it's like a museum now
and you walk and you can walk out through all the
corridors of the ship and
there's like there is this one
you can get like snacks and stuff too and there's just one like
ride I would call it where it's like
you get in this sort of like
fucking cannon
they like
stuff you into like this like little like almost
like bus sized like virtual
reality like shuttle and it's just
like let's pretend
what would happen if you guys were on World War
2 what would happen then let's make
like this movie about like like
it's like a virtual reality ride where
the bus like turns and like
twist
like like for the twist and turns you make
within like the video if you get what I'm saying
like it doesn't actually go anywhere it just like
assimilates what it would be like if you were
making those turns and that was fucking cool
I got to see a lot of people die
I got to see a lot of Japanese people
get kicked the fucking bucket and it was great
hell yeah when I when I was a wee lad
in the Boy Scouts me and my mom
we spent
a weekend on the like on a
battleship just like staying there for like a weekend
of fun and adventure and stuff
and it was like one of the most fun weekends of my entire life
but so that aside
I did want to say another thing that
D'Vu mentioned to me was he mentioned
a specific line and it was
attractions while you're in line and that just got
me thinking about wouldn't it be great
if if prostitution
was legal and they just had actual whores
okay just just follow me here for a second
okay like imagine you're in the world right
you're at Disney World and you're in line
prostitute and they got they got Disney
princesses just just they're whores
and they will fuck you and like you can fuck
Rapunzel who I want to remind everyone is
canonically 18 so even though she looks like
she's 14 she is in fact 18 so
I would just just wouldn't that be a great
attraction huh when you're in line would that be great
everybody right
my final feeling on theme parks right
I mean by the way yes
I hope you're bouncing off my idea
but go on
well I mean it's part of it which is that I want
theme parks to just be several orders
of magnitude like more
extravagant than they are again post
yes exactly post scarcity
economy is like because I
because I know like Walt Disney had way more
fucking like ambitions to food is
weird utilitarianism here we go
this isn't
about getting there it's about how cool
it would be when we are there and it's
about cool shit not like resources
not like fucking mining oil
from Titan it's about having theme parks
right uh-huh
cool tycoons
yeah but like yeah you know
like Disney himself had
so many more ambitions as to what he
wanted like Disney world and apcot
to be he wanted them to be like actual
shit because people keep conceptualizing
like like like cities
that are just like these little tiny areas
where you walk around and you could just do
everything that humans want to do and it's really
tight concise video gamey way
that's what theme parks are ultimately trying to do is make
video games IRL that's right you know that's right
and we just they just need to you know what I really want
I want a theme park that is like
a giant
thrift store slash antique shop
right because my favorite thing about those
like tap those little stores
is that they are often built out of like buildings
that are not meant to be stores and they have all these
weird rooms that like no one
is in and I love that
and I just want to have like a giant mansion
that has rides in it
like that one weird mansion that's like in California
or whatever built by a crazy woman
or whatever over the course of 30 years and you could
explore this mansion and go around in all these weird
rooms because we're talking about
yeah if I'm ever in California for long enough in the
right part of California because I know it's like the size
of a fucking European nation
California I would love to visit that place
because like the thing about the
dude hit me up and we'll go dude yeah
because like
theme parks are cool because you conceptualize
yourself going on this adventure
but when you go there it's like everyone's there it's like
being in a fucking auditorium
and I love I'd love to have
an incredibly huge mansion
with so many rooms that some of which
some people don't even know about and you just
walk around I would absolutely
I would pay $500 a year
for a season pass to a mansion
it's so huge that you could find your own hallways
and like no one will ever be there and you could
like jack off
did I mention that I worked at
in Newport Rhode Island doing like
tours of like the great
Newport mansions that are like gigantic
yeah they're like they're like actual palaces just
based on capitalism not aristocracy
it's pretty great pretty much
pretty much incredible incredible
so by the way they were
simply divine and shout out by the way
to the great American mall in
Minneapolis Minnesota that I visited
some time earlier was that this year
I can't remember but
that was just a big old it's a big old amusement
park inside a mall in like the center
of the mall yeah what did I say
great American mall whatever it's one of those
things I thought it was that
by the way I should have mentioned this earlier
by the way Nate you said you played the clarinet
and you got to go to Disneyland for like being
in a big world oh my god it was the
bopper bowl episode of fucking Spongebob
oh my god
anyway the reason I say
that Nate is because I also
played the clarinet in band and I got to
go to Disneyland for being in band
so I live the exact
same life that you did
which is weird the munchie is a Spongebob
is a Squidward so you wouldn't think they would
play clarinet
I like to be thinking of myself as a Mr. Krabs
racist and capitalist trippin
just looking to
how's Mr. Krabs a racist
when he has a mixed race daughter
uh
well he's not racist against that race
just a very particular one
he fucked the whale as a meme
it was a meme so
I think he all fucked the whale in college
he's ironically raising
his daughter yeah listen I'm not here
I'm not here to profile someone but can't you just
imagine Mr. Krabs in a
MAGA hat can't you just imagine him
can't you just see him
it would be a part of the show
that's true we got a question on twitter
from
that's your cue Nate
oh that's a cue I thought you were actually reading it
okay alright here we go everybody
question what's the one I was going to read before
where did that go oh here we go
okay this is from at lord light skin
lord light skin everybody
that's a good kind of skin to have
that's what they say
so tbcrasnators how would
you want the world to end
how would you want the world to end
there's a lot of possibilities that are
quite alluring I'd like
I'd like water to come up
and then everyone to be in boats and then everyone to
become pirates hell yeah
so that's kind of
like a positive like the world just changes
kind of world ending because I was thinking like the world
literally explodes yeah yeah
meteor but I like yours better I like that
well yeah
people still live whatever it is I want
it to be trumps fault because that'd be like the funniest
scenario possible dude that would be so funny
would the liberals be
super smug about that though and they'd be
yeah no they'd be funny
but they'd be smug and I hate smug liberals
they like the most annoying people in the world well yeah
but I have a funny hat so I win
fuck yeah dude
I think I gotta go with meteor to the planet
maybe I'm just thinking too much of Final Fantasy 7
but like I've always I've just got such a
it would look so cool if I could see it
if I could see that happening oh that's just for that
reason alone you know just the whole
maybe I'm thinking too much of Final Fantasy 7
is the quote of your life
is it not
you're right dude you are damn right
I would like to think it too much of Homestuck
when you said that yep oh jeez
that there wasn't even a dramatic
planet explosion in fucking Homestuck
we're like yeah but a big rocks are falling
yeah I remember
meteors falling but the planet never blew up
it was never like that
it was on a thread of being blown up for a while
that's true I think I think it did canonically
like get blown up we just didn't see it
oh wait I thought I realized the way
I want the world to end is for a
hiveswap to come out and be good
because it'll never happen and it's shit
it's bad I actually
no idea I just like
I mean really the best way for the world to end like technically would be
we're already a galactic civilization
a lot of utilitarianism whatever
and we're just sort of having a kumbaya over it
as it descends into the sun in its final days
like yep it was fun but it's
dead now if we don't learn anything
new about like physics or any of that
shit which we probably will learn at least some things
but if we don't like yeah like there's no
way of avoiding like the heat death of the universe
so we're all gonna
it's gonna happen one day you know if we don't if we don't get our
shit together and I don't travel
you can fuck a lot of bitches in there
the amount of time it will take for the heat
death of the universe
the patron lounge
patreon.com
something what is it
the procrastinators everybody
if you want to spend a buck to get into this smug little
shitty chat room and talk to all these fucking
bitches come on in you can ask us
a question
mccoolman wants to know if you had
to body swap with any PCP member
for the rest of your life
who would it be
and I should mention before
anyone says anything
there's a user called kalope
or whatever and he says I would swap with munchy
because he seems at least depressed
well let me tell you
it's all an illusion
I think the only answer for me would be mage
just because it's like the mystery answer
because I don't know what she looks like
so I'm just gonna like cross my fingers and roll the die
that's the mystery box yeah that's a fair bet
that's not a bad choice
Tom I guess
I mean I don't like yourself
just because he's like the tallest
and I could fill out my frame and become
a non
a Lanclet God that's what I would do
a Lanclet God
yeah that's my answer
I'd go with myself and
that's it
boo
I'd go with his self as well
excellent
munchy alright
nobody wants to be Ben
you know what
my second answer was gonna be Ben
because Ben is genetically quite close to me
so that's not so bad
why even change then
but you have to
that's the question
if I had to
I would probably be digi
I'd probably go into the body
of hippo
he is a powerful beast
if we're opening up to stuff like that
then I want to go into the body of the undertailer
the most powerful man
I thought you were already one of the undertailers
none of you want to be inside me
I definitely would pick hippo
because I kind of dig the idea
of being like small and skinny
like hippo doesn't like it so
if he switches with me I don't think he would mind
my body as much as his own for some reason
you seem to not like his body
so there you go
if I could choose myself I probably would
I can't choose yourself
yeah that's the whole thing
the whole body swap question
I don't believe that a consciousness exists
outside of mind
so if you transfer your quote-unquote consciousness
into someone else's body
then frankly you're just them now
it's literally a brain transplant
that works
I think I'd go with Ben
disgusting
he's already me
I can know what it's like to rub my clit
boys
yeah that's fair
that's not a bad choice
I want that mage
clit baby
I'm sorry mage
please don't listen to this episode
okay
what do we got here
at Alan Oni
says a thing
imagine that for whatever reason
you have to go and pick up a girl
language isn't an issue
and anyone can be your wingman
imagine yourself boys
where you have to talk to a girl
what do you do
I would blow my fucking brains out
that's the answer
anyone differ from that
would we all commit suicide
I would say
hey baby what's shaking
is it my penis
yes it is
you have to pick up a girl
is it a date
is he picking her up from the airport
he's just lifting her up off the ground
let's assume he means a seduce
romantically express her interest
also my wingman
will be like a bird
and that will be the pun
and she'll be like oh what a funny pun
and that'll clinch it
it'll be a combination of the funny pun
and you asking her to
see your shaking penis
that will lose you
you hit it with a one two punch
first you hit it with a shaking dick
then you hit it with a bird pun
that's just the way you do it
user the jam from the patreon lounge
do you piss like an animal
by unbuttoning your pants and pulling your penis over your waistband
or do you use the zipper
and flap in the underwear like god tinge you to pee
I am unbuttoning your pants
and pulling your penis over the waistband 100%
I never use the fucking flap
in the other way it's fucking disgusting
and legitimately there's no reason to do it
it takes too long and it's too much of a fucking hassle
and it's just way easier to just whip it out
and fucking spray
I agree with that
the pressure from my waistband
and my pants pushing up
stops like the flow of pee
so I have to do it the other way
well I lifted up over the waistband
the waistband is just like on
my balls
I know what you're talking about but there's always a little bit
I actually mix it up
I basically undo my pants
but then I use the flap in the underwear
because that's the easiest way to do it
I'm in the middle
but you have to unbutton it
you have to reach in and find out where it is
there's no button in my underwear
there is a button on some of mine
actually the ones I'm wearing right now
underwear has a button on it
it does
I don't do it
I didn't even get into it until like two years ago
because I'd always seen it
going through the underwear
because I always knew that's what it was for
but I never thought to try it until like a while ago
and I was like okay
but the thing is
the last couple of drips of pee would go backwards
I don't know how common that is
that kind of gets on the pants if you're wearing the pants
so I'm just like eh
but I still do it if I
am listening to something in my ear buds on my phone
and I don't want to stop while I pee
and if it's in my pocket
it's going to have to go all the way
I don't want to mess with it
I don't want to stop
I just stick it out
if I'm listening to something on my phone
okay actually you guys
this was a test and you all failed
because what you all described was that
you are all doing the virgin pee
that's what you're doing
whereas I walk into the bathroom
I take my pants and underwear completely off
I stand at the urinal
I make eye contact with both people
surrounding me at the same time
and I piss a fucking ocean into the urinal
guys that's a lesson fun
but here I'm about to introduce you to the green piled
pee
this is for green pills only when you've aligned all your chopper
the Jill sign pee
this is the second dip
double dipping or whatever it was called
here's what you do
you walk into the bathroom and you go inside of the stall
and then you sit down to pee
that's the secret jujitsu that fucking
Donald Trump doesn't want you to see
he doesn't want you to know
that you're able to do that
if you go in the stall at least stand
and piss into the toilet
why do you have to sit on it
those are both embarrassing
the ability to pee standing up
you can pee standing up in a stall
but you just look like a bitch
why are you taking up a whole stall
if you don't have to know
your urinals are full of shit
if the urinals are full
it's fine that's no problem at all
but if you choose to pee into a toilet
first of all you're wasting more water
that's not grim tell
I will look down upon you as a man
you are not a man
what if you're a shy peer
and you just can't go in a urinal
well that's the thing this is a manliness test
I want to watch you pee
I want to see you pee and study you as a man
and know if you're worthy of my respect
but if you go into a stall you're a coward
and I don't respect you
in recent years I haven't gone on the urinal
but I still perceive myself as a person
who goes into the stall
most of the time
I don't usually pee alone
I usually pee with poop as well
understandable
what if it's like just a trough
and you don't want to pee in a trough like a pig
those aren't real
they are real
I was watching the screen junkies
and they went to the Emmys the other day
like the pre-Emmys not like the big important one
and the fucking bathroom at the Emmys after party
is a trough
you know you would expect something more extravagant
for this crazy big party
I go in the stall
but it's not because I don't want people to
see my pee-iness
it's just because
I mean it's more privacy
I don't know
I have too many
piss triplets afterwards
and there's no toilet paper at the urinal
that's really my reason
the toilet paper isn't a thing
can't fault you for that
okay
what's the next question here
whenever I'm at a urinal
and I have to shake my dick to get all the driplets out
I'm just afraid it won't seem like I'm jerking off
into a urinal
I want them to think I'm jacking off into the urinal
you ever hear the phrase
that when a man walks into a room he takes his whole life
with him
that's what I think about every time I walk into the bathroom
everyone witness my science
witness my performance at the urinal
I'm a fucking man
I have trained myself
I've studied actual literature
about how to pee properly at a urinal
I know the score
and everyone who is not up to my level
I consider beneath me and a worthless human
see that makes you seem more self-conscious than the people
who just go in the store
cause you actually researched it to make sure you're doing it right
I don't give a shit
I just do whatever I want
yeah do whatever you want
hi you coward
charlotarianism
look donky go
okay here we go next question everybody
at hazelcracket on twitter asks
what would you consider a good gift
what are your parameters for a good gift
is that bullshit about
wanting someone to like the heartfelt
or like oh you made me a picture that all you could have made
or blah blah blah
if you're gonna give not money then I want to be like
I want to be like something that you like made
that's what I want
don't buy me like a thing
or give me a thing that you made
or give me money
or give me something that you could buy
but it's like a specific thing that you could buy
the question is what would you consider a good gift
but feel free to talk about bad gifts either
I mean for me it would be
me and sheep over are watching through
oh go ahead
something that would be very very useful
for a very long time
but would never be able to like get around
to buying like justifying the expense of
like my parents for Christmas
several Christmases ago got me like
a waterproof bluetooth speaker
so that you can like listen to like music
or podcast while taking a shower
and it is fucking awesome
and even if it ever breaks down I'll buy a new one
in a heartbeat but when I had the idea that
I have one I was like I don't know if I'm gonna use
that enough I just don't know
I don't want to drop the money so someone
breaking that damn like
violating that inertia for me was like great
the great thing about the gift thing
is that it's a certain amount of money
that like will be spent and you just get
to decide on what you have to spend it on
so it really gives you license to like
I mean if you can get like I do this with my parents all the time
like they ask what I want like for my birthday
whatever and then they'll buy like I mean a couple years ago
for Christmas they got me like the camera that I use
for like every video now and like
that was like I paid for like half of it but like
we worked out a deal just because like they want to get me something
I actually care about and like
so like that really emboldens you or kind of
forces you to purchase things that you are maybe on the fence about
that's honestly how I think about you know what
and also I never give gifts to anyone I don't have to
I have a real answer
the best gifts are gifts that are
not given on birthdays or holidays
because I realize I always get excited
surprise gifts I always get excited
not even like a surprise just something
like you know we're at a store like
oh that thing looks cool I'll buy it for you
really oh my gosh acquaintance of mine
or person who I know and love
it's like I don't know they didn't always feels
correct that how that's how giving
feels like it should feel to me
whereas the obligatory holidays
they never feel right to me
yeah I was going to say
something along those lines where
like a birthday or something
it feels like I'd be expected but when you get
something randomly from somebody it means
a lot more to me and I was saying
that me and sheep over started watching season one
of true detective because she hadn't seen it
and I pointed out
I pointed out that
the big hug mug that
Matthew McConaughey is using as an ashtray
was like a meme on 4chan
for a while and then like
three days later one shows up in the mail
and she's like oh yeah I bought one for you and I was like
oh well fucking shit and now I'm drinking out
of a big hug mug right now
I'd rather get it randomly than on my birthday
because then it's like well I guess you had to get me something
that's true I just never
expect kindness from anyone so
you know the way I
feel about stuff like that is that I would like
to be a person who gets gifts
randomly for people and
and doesn't have to do birthdays but that's not
how it works because they always expect it
so I feel like
to be a person who's that generous
you just need to give gifts
way more and I'm not like that
I'm not evil I don't
I never buy gifts for anyone that I can avoid doing it for
you know why would I I don't get it
it's not my thing it's still not about that life
and so I can't expect it to be done to me
oh yeah I never want gifts no one ever
get me a gift it's not it's not good but see
like the people who do like the with the
P.O. Box I'm doing like they're getting something in response
they're getting like my the their
presence in the video so like that's an equivalent
exchange going on I think so
yeah there you go
alright any more questions
from there or shall we take another one from here
no there's no more no okay
there's none on Twitter or on
Patreon we're all done
I'll at least suck
okay here we go here's one last question
J.H. The Hurricane
asks aliens
find us and lay siege to our planet
they'll destroy us unless we bring them
the best YouTube video
ever what's that video
the Japanese Juggalo Episode 1
the aliens will be like sitting like like
contouring super hard and they'll be like show me
your greatest piece of work
and then I'll like scurry off and I'll come back
and then they'll be like like put on their headphones
and they'll be anticipating there's complete silence
and then and then quaking
from inside of their fucking headphones
I'm all fed
it is me
D and their ears
fucking burst and their minds
blows and then they're all dead
instantaneously
you know what I do in this situation I would just lean over
I'd cock my eyebrow knowingly and just say
have you ever heard of a little guy called
leafy that's where I would go
yeah that's this one
he is here
I would say
digi brony off to dark
there it is
I tweeted that the other day
it was like a scary ghost
that wasn't a boo it was just a ghost sound
it's the ghost of digi
in the past when he actually made
brony content and it was good
unlike his new bullshit
garb I don't know what he's done to the editing
but like all the anime videos
editing that shit it's awful
I don't know what he's done to the videos
like now instead of like having
point characters on screen it's all just like humans
now and they're all like
they don't look too short
they didn't even leave because I said that joke did he
I have no idea who knows
man we'll fight out one day
I think there's no way
I mean it's way funnier if it was
just coincidentally he
dropped out
just so you know I've never actually
watched the digi videos so
my criticism doesn't stand because I don't know
if the editing is shit
no no no don't backpedal we know
we know your secret
we couldn't wait to take down
DeVoo this entire time
alright everybody that's it
that's the last of questions
okay so remember send us more throughout the week whenever you fucking want to
using hashtag askpcp
and if you follow us at attpcrasinators
we'll remind you every fucking Saturday
and donate to our patreon if you donate one dollar
you can get into the patreon lounge and if you donate five
you can get the fucking coolest bonus episode
DeVoo's back yep hey DeVoo came back
has your emotions healed
I can't hear
he's saying okay it doesn't matter
we're wrapping up anyway so yeah
be a patron forget the bonus episodes
six episodes are out right now people there'll be another one
in like a week and a half
after this comes out I think so there you go
so we'll see everybody next time
bye bye
bye
also buy the merch
oh yeah buy buy
the merch
goodbye
yeah
yeah uh
I'm supposed to
be working right now
be working
right now
but I'm not working
I'm doing
nothing
my dick I'm
jerking myself
I'm sucking
I am an asshole
I am a stupid
I've got a
deadline
don't want to do it