I won't bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Welcome everyone to The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
If you can't believe it, it's the podcast yet again.
It's another five, it's another five man, five man clusterfuck of a podcast.
Five hours.
You'll get what you wanted, audience.
Five man, five hours, five seasons in a movie.
We're going, we're going to the, we're going to, we're going to Disney World.
Cheesy Manfredo is here and so is Oblivionfall.
Wow.
What, woke virus?
I'm suffering from the broke virus.
Eight we all brother.
What?
I was playing Battle Network.
I was playing, I didn't stream for a whole month and then I played Mega Man Battle Network
again the other day on stream and the running joke in that game for, in the stream there
is that Wiley is spreading the woke mind virus and that's what's making the machines go haywire.
That's the bit.
That's, we have fun here.
I wouldn't, I wouldn't be.
We have fun on twitch.tv slash stcomics.
Subscribe.
I wouldn't be surprised that Wiley is spreading the woke virus.
As you say, it is a particular set of people with a very, very distinguished feature in
the center of their nose that Wiley obviously shares with a specific group of people.
In the center of their nose.
Is Germanic.
Wiley is Germanic.
In the center of their face.
In the center of their face, I mean.
In the center of their nose is that distinctive mole.
He's good Germanic.
We all know what that means.
You know, it'd be a really funny like Mandela effect if it turns out that like, like let's
say someone tweets out, hey, do you all notice that Wiley Sprite has like a yarmulke and then
everyone goes back to all the old Mega Man.
Oh my God, it's always been there.
What the fuck?
Oh no.
Wait, what the fuck?
He's just always wearing a yarmulke.
That wasn't a bold spot.
No, he was wearing a yarmulke the whole time.
Mega Man, the rootless, the rootless cosmopolitan's are destroying society.
Go fight, fight them for everlasting peace, Mega Man.
Damn, this is fucked up.
There were themes in these games we never even picked up on.
Damn.
That is fucked up.
This is deep.
I totally missed it.
Yeah.
It's crazy.
It's like the goblins.
Just like the Harry Potter goblins.
Maybe Kanye was on to something here.
Well, when he talks about Mega Man.
Yeah.
Yeah, he said he loved all of you.
When Kanye had his Mega Man video essay.
Kanye said he loved all robot masters.
He's loved them all.
He loves each and every one of them because he's a Christian.
I love all Reploids, Maverick and non-Maverick.
There's good people on both sides.
I love Sigma.
I love him.
Sigma made some good points.
I love Sigma.
What did Kanye say?
This is awesome.
Stupid.
I love war criminals.
This is great.
I'm having a great time with my friends on the podcast.
Speaking of war criminals, I'm going to become one right now.
Go on.
I'm going to talk about a dream I had.
That's right.
I'm pulling a maze.
No, not a dream.
Don't worry.
It's quick.
This was like right before I woke up and there was a character in there who was either
Ben St. or Cheesy Manfredo or Chris Reagan.
One of the three.
I don't know which one.
The iconic trio.
It's Reagan.
I don't know why.
I'll keep it brief.
I was at an apartment complex and there was just a big stretch of apartment buildings
that somehow I had spray-painted like a giant mural of like 30 or so popular female characters,
butts just all posing on the side of his building.
The mural was so good.
It was just so nice and free-dimension and their butts were poking out and I spray-painted
this whole thing.
Your dreams are just like your real life.
The paintings extended into the fucking rooms and if you walk through like the top floor
of the apartments, like we're like around where the bus were, like each room that one of the
characters was like against, like the entire inside of a room would be like painted like
in the theme of like whatever media property they're from and someone had labeled the doors
safe for work, not safe for work since I'd done that.
And for several days, the apartments had not noticed, but then they did notice.
And then I was running to escape because I realized people were coming and the guy who
was either Ben St. or cheese and Manfredo or Chris Reagan ran up to open a gate to let
me out.
The guy walking next to me, there's a guy in a white shirt, one of those undershirts that
you usually wear a suit over, the white shirt with the buttons at the top sort of thing.
It was Joe Biden who was wearing his aviated glasses.
He was speed walking next to me.
He's like, the butt heist, we've got to cover the butt heist.
And I'm like, oh, no, the butt heist.
And I went to grab my phone because I wanted to record Joe Biden talking about the butt
heist because I thought this is going to be so fucking funny.
Joe Biden talking about a butt heist and looking at these giant anime butts.
And then I couldn't find my phone.
And I woke up.
I was having a dream yesterday morning and I was, I was, I don't remember what it was,
but I had the, I remember I was like half asleep.
I was like, huh, this is nice.
I'm having a dream.
I don't remember what it was.
And then my alarm went off and instantly, instantly I forgot what the dream was.
And instantly I was sad again because I remembered that the previous night, my brother, Nate Bestman,
betrayed me by not raiding my stream, even though he could have done it.
He had every opportunity to raid my stream and he refused.
He callously refused.
What kind of, what kind of a, what kind of a, what kind of a brother?
What kind of a brother wouldn't raid your own stream?
Wouldn't raid his own brother's stream?
Calously refused.
All right.
And all you've done for him is how you refuse.
True.
I literally had, okay, oblivion.
I linked you a video that I really liked the other day.
I don't know if you got around to watching it, but.
Oh shit.
You did link me a video that I did.
I recommended you a video.
That's okay.
Well, I found this channel.
The channel, the guy is called Geno7 and his, his bit is that he's basically doing what's it called.
It's like every frame of painting, but instead of about like video and movie making,
it's, it's about like sound design and composition is his, is his thing.
He did a video.
He just had one that was like a hit and it's about the sound design of Wario Land 4.
And in, in that video, he talks about the ending theme song for the good ending is this song with lyrics,
which is unusual for a, for a Game Boy Advance game.
But there's a song with lyrics and the song is about the opening line is,
Oh, the dream that I had last night melted into my pillow and all I'd gathered turned into sand.
And that was me.
I woke up and the dream that I had last night melted into my pillow.
It was exactly like that.
You know, you're right.
Wow.
What do we think?
I think, I think that's horrendous.
Last week, you talked about Homer having that dream about the invention and then Marge woke him up
because oh, it's a couple minutes before we usually go to bed.
Wake up so you can go to bed again in five minutes.
I experienced like that only it was morning.
I had a dream where this was like maybe five or six days ago.
I was in some kind of, some kind of glade, some kind of forest glade at night.
And they were like bioluminescent glowing like pink flowers and shit.
It was really cool.
And Princess Luna and Princess Celestia were just sitting on a hill and they were hot.
Wow.
And I started fingering them and it was great and we were going to have sex.
Jesus.
And then Kai woke me up in the middle of my dream and I'm like, why?
I never have sex dreams.
How fucking dare you?
You screamed at him.
You screamed at him so loud.
You took this from me.
I woke up and I immediately attacked him.
I went into attack mode.
Kai never usually wakes me up.
Is this the dream cast?
No.
Oh my gosh.
Dream cast?
I don't have any dreams.
I never have dreams.
Oh no.
I don't remember them.
Dreams.
I had one weird one recently, but I just forgot it.
So I'm not going to say it.
Wacky.
Yo, I just, that guy, that channel, I really was really impressed by what the content
on offer on that Geno7 channel.
And it's interesting because he had like, he had like 3,000 subscribers, right?
Tiny channel.
I found this Wario video.
I think when I found it, it had like maybe 50K views, you know, a somewhat respectable
amount of views.
I think it has now hit like 100K.
And I looked at the rest of his channel.
The rest of his channel has like 2,000 views, 4,000 views, even though the video, there's
only a few videos, but like they're all really good.
And I feel like I've discovered, I feel like I discovered a diamond in the rough.
Like I feel like I found this channel right as, it seems poised to blow up.
It seems like it's good stuff and it could blow up.
And I feel like I found it like before.
For that Wario thing, I just didn't click on it because I'm like, eh, everybody makes
videos about stuff these days.
It's really good.
I need to watch that video because I've been needing long videos to watch that are good.
I tried watching the Riku was gay video and I just, it was too rambly and I didn't like
the person's voice.
Oh, me too.
I'm so glad.
I didn't have to be the one to say it.
You're so homophobic.
I am homophobic.
Hey, people who have bad arguments against the video, stop right now.
It's like, I don't like that.
Start with your strong arguments and then address the strong counter arguments and then address
the weak counter arguments.
They were doing it backwards.
I can't really complain because my Mega Man video starts with like way too much introduction.
Like I ramble way too much at the beginning of that video.
So I'm guilty of it.
But your video needed to be eight hours long, Ben.
That, okay, okay.
The Riku video, I think like the arguments, like the content is good and the evidence
is there and there's a compelling case and I am fully convinced that there is a compelling
case that, yeah, Riku is gay.
Same.
I'm kind of interested to hear if there's like a counter argument, like if someone
else has like, well, actually here's all this evidence that points to Riku isn't gay.
Kairi is the real love interest.
I'd be interested to hear a counter argument, but place side by side all the clips of Riku
not being interested in women and being in Tessora like are pretty compelling, right?
The second I heard like, oh, what if Riku's gay, I'm like, hmm, has he ever known of a
touch of a woman?
No.
And he never would.
It's just obvious.
It's obvious.
It's fun that it's not like, oh, it's a silly Japanese game and you can read that into it
because haha, it's like translation and it's like different culture or whatever.
It's like explicit from interviews of the, you know, the intent is more clear than you
would assume.
And it's interesting.
It kind of seems that way, even though like the initial setup when you start the game,
it seems like it's a love triangle where these two boys both like the girl.
That's what it sort of presents itself as immediately, but then like it never, it never
again really backs that up ever.
It's interesting.
If you got to the end of the video, I think in the description, I actually didn't get
all the way.
I got like three quarters the way through it.
Well, the thing I mentioned about the sleeping realm theory, the theory that's like about
Kingdom Hearts 3, I forget the broad strokes, but it was also interesting.
That's at the top of the description of the Rikus game video.
Check that out.
It's even harder to listen to.
So you may have more difficulty with it, but like there's a Google Doc and it's just,
it's great.
I don't know how to explain it because I'm not the one who made the video, but I like
it.
Maybe I will.
I like all that Kingdom Hearts stuff because it's so, the games are so cryptic in like
a stupid way, but well, I say it's stupid.
It's cryptic in, you know, deliberately cryptic way, and it's like weird how much, how many
things go into the presentation of these ideas that make them subtle and like hard to see,
but they're clearly deliberate.
Even things like, oh, a cutscene shows this shot and then this shot, and this is like,
you can infer from the choice of shots, a theme based on this other information and
stuff.
It's like, why would they, like, obviously everything in a game is created like deliberately.
Everything is put there deliberately, but like, you would assume some things are just
arbitrary, just like, oh, let's just put it wherever.
The fact that the theory goes into like, actually, there's a lot more hidden meaning throughout
the game that you wouldn't really think of, but when you, you know, it's a good theory.
It's a good compelling theory.
It's just like the Riku video.
Wait, I thought you were talking about the Riku video.
Well, I'm talking about, that's the thing.
It's like, it's the similar sort of thing.
It's a theory specifically about the nature of Kingdom Hearts 3.
And Riku is gay isn't necessarily related, but the Riku is gay video is like, it has
elements of that theory near the end.
If you didn't get to the end, you probably wouldn't have seen all that, but like, it's
good.
Yeah.
I could, I had gripes, I had gripes with the presenter.
I kind of didn't like them.
I would assume you would, but like, that's just because you're bigoted or something.
That's right.
Listen, I'm going to, I didn't like, didn't like the, didn't like the fursona, didn't
like the avatar, thought it was underanimated, but over expressive in a way that was distracting.
Didn't, yeah, didn't like, they, they, they rambled.
They kind of, they kind of went on tangents about, I didn't like, okay, when they talked
about like a lack of gay representation, I found it almost like infuriatingly naive,
the way they talked about like Disney, I don't know, the sense that I got was like, like
they were, they wanted to do Disney apologia.
Like they wanted to be like, oh, Disney just wasn't ready.
Disney wasn't ready to put gay people in their movies, but now it's 2023 and now, you know,
times have changed.
And it just seemed like they weren't acknowledging the fact that like Disney does, makes these
decisions about like, they do this bare bones representation thing, you know, for like a
cold calculated money making purposes.
He seemed like he was absolving them of, of their responsibility in this arena.
And finally, the one thing about the attitude that I kind of annoyed me, and I don't know
if this is going to sound stupid, I feel like people might think, call me stupid for this.
But the way that he talked about when Riku was gay, he would always like have a little
sly expression, so like, hey, Riku did something gay, Riku acted gay.
And it felt dirty.
It made, it gave me a feeling like it was like a dirty secret that was being like sneakily
shared with me.
And it made it sound like being gay was like this, this dirty thing.
The way that he, the way that he like snickered about it every time that it, that it reared
its ugly head.
I think that's just like Tumblr culture.
I don't like it.
It's the, it's the sort of like, ooh, look at that con, look at that con and it made
him squee and, and he was going to glomp Riku.
He was going to glomp him.
Yeah.
Because he's such a little squishmallow.
Yeah, yeah.
Squishmallow.
And I just, I just.
Oh, I like that word.
I just can't, I just can't, I just can't cotton, cotton to it.
It's not, it's not copacetic.
I don't know.
Okay.
I'm done.
I'm, I'm, I'm coping.
I'm done coping.
Done coping.
You guys, you guys haven't asked.
The argument was compelling.
You guys didn't ask me what my opinion was on the Riku.
Did you watch the video?
It was a gay video.
Die.
I didn't watch the video, but it did make, I did make this epic meme right now that expresses
my feelings on the video that I didn't watch.
Check it out.
I'm going to kill you.
What's it?
Yo.
True.
It's the first time I've seen an old kingdom of hearts characters R.K.
Um, yeah.
Yeah.
I thought they were all the gay one.
I thought they were all the, they don't, well, they are.
I mean, you could, you could scratch that to all like Final Fantasy adjacent characters
too.
I mean, those black robes.
Especially the white robes.
You don't need, you don't need eight hours to tell me Riku is gay.
I assume they all were gay.
I don't need an eight hour video.
I, I even big brain.
I already, I assume organizations are gay by default.
Sephiroth, Sephiroth is gay for his mom because he like is his mom.
That's the only gay that's okay.
If you think about it.
Yeah.
Which means his mom is a, is a, is a man at that point.
Definitely.
Yeah.
That's what I'm saying.
Allyship.
And that's, and that's where I draw the line.
Franklin.
That's where I fucking draw the line.
The fucking, the fucking organization 13, like their black robes, they always had a
bit of like, like, uh, what's the, leave it to, SMM culture, the, the leather and the
zips.
The, the, the, instead of just being made a cloth, you know, like a Jedi robe.
That's just got punk.
All, all goth punk stuff is very like SMM.
Yeah.
It's inspired.
It's derived from queer spaces and all that stuff.
True.
It's great.
Goth.
Shit.
There's no such thing as, uh, straight fashion.
All the cool shit is gay.
Straight people.
There's no such thing as white culture and no such thing as straight fashion.
It's true.
I agree.
True.
You know what?
Actually disagree.
Straight.
Straight fashion is like a graphic tee with a Batman logo.
That's straight fashion.
Yeah.
I see your eyes.
Oh, you know what?
You've turned me around.
That's a great.
Straight, straight fashion is a guy in like an old, an old, like black and white movie
like prison uniform, like black and white stripes with a little like cap.
That's it.
Straight fashion.
No, that's a twink uniform.
That's the, that's the Hamburgler uniform.
Like, like, like what the three stooge, like what the three stooge's would wear if you
if you sent them to prison.
Just them though.
They only wanted to wear that if they got arrested.
Everyone else is dressed normal.
Everyone dressed in prison orange, but they get the stripes because they're just wacky.
They're just wacky like that.
Yeah.
If you're wacky enough, you're in prison.
You get the funny costume.
That's what that's what they put on the Joker.
The way I'm wearing the stripes because he's so wacky, you know, watch out.
This one's the wacky inmate.
To the Joker.
He's kooky.
He's loco.
Black is the new orange.
Oh my God.
And then he eats it like an orange.
He peels it and he makes juice out of it.
I don't want to.
That's how wacky he is.
Stripes on a white shirt.
I want to white stripes on a black shirt.
I remember what he said that.
Yeah.
And then Batman's like, Batman's like, you're out of line Joker.
He starts breaking his arms.
He remember when I remember when I discovered putting bacon grease on on green lentils.
Remember that?
Yeah.
That magical moment that we shared.
I found a new way to do it.
Put lentils on bacon grease.
You can put lentil grease on bacon because to get bacon grease, you have to make bacon
and then you have to save the grease and it's kind of a hassle.
But guess what?
You can just take bacon when you make when you make your green lentils in your rice cooker.
You can just take bacon and cut it up and just throw the raw bacon in the water with
the lentils and then the bacon cooks in the lentils.
The rice cooker cooks the bacon.
It's a miracle.
Ben, the year is 2020 free.
You said this last week your dementia is setting in.
Wait, I did?
No, you didn't.
Yes, you did.
I was waiting for you to say throwing in the bacon with the lentils and the rice cooker.
I'm going to kill myself.
I'm going to fucking do it.
I don't remember.
Maybe I just wasn't listening.
I don't remember you saying you put bacon in the rice cooker.
Oh my God.
Bye.
No, you definitely said that on the last episode.
I listened to it yesterday.
It's over.
I caught up to it yesterday.
Oh, no.
It's fucking over.
That both means that you have to mention I am completely absent-minded and I wasn't
listening and I was very rude if that's the case.
No.
It was like a free hour conversation.
I'm going to miss one or two things.
I can't live with myself.
I actually just listened to the last episode right before jumping into this one and I totally
forget.
Do you remember?
I forgot everything.
Do you remember my bacon story?
I forgot everything you guys talked about in the last episode.
Bacon and the lentils.
I mean, so did I.
Bacon and lentils.
The lentils.
The rice cooker.
The rice cooker cooks the bacon.
It's just.
It's so convenient.
Why don't they call it a bacon cooker?
Why don't they call it exactly?
Exactly.
You're exactly right.
What if you make rice out of bacon?
Bacon.
Then it would be epic.
I don't know.
I don't know what would happen if you did that.
Did you chop like bacon into rice shakes?
Wait a second.
Ben, you don't have a grease jug?
You don't have a grease jug in your kitchen?
I have a Thai small mason jug, a small little glass jar.
No.
You're going to go and get yourself a big ass jug of oil, get an oil jug, and then you
just put that oil back in the jug and any extra oil you just put in there.
You just drink the oil straight from the jug.
Yeah.
I have an oil jug.
You don't have an oil jug?
Come on, Ben.
I have an oil jug.
It's called.
My penis.
Cotton balls.
Oh, God.
Check out this video.
Check out this video that I posted.
This is another one from GNO7.
This video.
It's OK.
Did you see that defunct land?
Not defunct land.
Where he finds the...
That is defunct land.
Yeah, I watched that.
That was good.
That was a good video.
Incredible video.
That video is basically like that.
But it's about this one guy who worked at Cartoon Network and is responsible for all
the iconic sounds of that era of Cartoon Network.
That's great.
It's such a good video.
Is he the one that put out...
I'm glad that this is really engaging and popular because it's like...
I mean, no, but it's only got 4,000 views, only 4,000 views on this masterpiece of a video.
Well, I hope it gets more, but like the idea that like uncovering the hidden talents behind
things that we just take for granted, it's like, yeah, they do deserve credit.
We do need to do that more.
People don't deserve to be buried alive.
OK.
It's my...
Like that guy who makes all the good voice mails.
Who is he?
It's not...
Oh my gosh.
I'm going to kill you.
It's not quite as good as the defunct land one because it's not like it's a mystery.
Like this guy is...
This guy, he's not like famous, but like he is known in the industry, like people know
who he is.
So it's not like he had to search for him.
It's just kind of like a piece about this guy who sort of did all this amazing work
and you probably never heard of him.
But I like the content online is being made about stuff like that because like, I wouldn't
think to look up who made the guitar sound.
In fact, I want to know that.
You know that classic Hanna-Barbera era like guitar smash?
Yeah.
Ding!
I guess so.
Yeah.
Well, all sorts of cool stuff.
Sounds are very often overlooked.
True.
Overlooked and undercooked.
Sounds are of a sort of texture.
Sounds...
You were talking about...
Yeah, sounds can't be overlooked.
You can't look at a sound.
Stupid.
No, you can't.
You can look at the waveform.
No.
Overheard.
Shut up.
That's not true.
That's not true at all.
Shut up.
Yeah.
So, Ben, you're talking about channels that you just know are going to blow up the moment
you see them.
I had that experience a while back with this channel, Kid Leave Stoop.
I've heard of this.
This was like the first second.
Possibly from you.
I don't know if I ever mentioned it.
Maybe not.
Actually, I feel like I've...
2.5 million views?
I remember watching this one.
Yeah.
It's blown up now because it's been like over a year, but when I found this, it had like
less than 10,000 views and it was just really like a well-made video and I'm like, this
guy is going to get big and I guess he did.
Yeah.
137.
I think Geno7's got the sauce.
I think from what you're saying, it definitely sounds like he's got the sauce.
Yeah.
That's my prescription.
The next video in the channel is what if bowling stayed illegal?
What?
That's what it says.
What if bowling stayed illegal?
What if bold people stayed illegal?
In the description?
No, the next video in the channel.
That's the title.
Of Kid Leaves Soup?
Yeah.
What if bowling stayed illegal?
It's a video.
Oh, wait a minute.
I saw this Simpsons Missing Bus Stop video.
Oh.
I've seen that one.
That was good too.
Oh, yes.
I did see that.
I haven't seen a good...
You know what?
I like videos.
What would you call these?
Bowling stayed illegal.
What the fuck does it mean?
Are these still video essays or what do you even call these types of videos?
Are these still video essays or...?
Bowling was associated with gambling or other shit, and in America it was banned.
Nine-pin bowling was banned, and the way they got around the law was to create 10-pin bowling.
It's technically a different game.
That's why it's ten-pin bowling.
I'm not joking.
No, I did not.
I never heard that before.
That's like cocaine's illegal, so we invented cocaine too, which is technically another
drug.
Well, no, it's just...
Actually, that's like...
That's like painkillers, actually, I think.
This guy has the Simpsons in like half of his video thumbnails, but it's just like that
episode of The Simpsons where they put uranium in the farm, in the crops, and they combine
tobacco and tomatoes to make tobacco.
It's technically a different vegetable, even though it's just...
Was it uranium or was it that he just was mixing seeds?
I thought he was just mixing seeds.
No, he got some stuff from the power plant and put uranium or plutonium or something
in the seeds.
Oh boy.
And it could cause a crossbreed.
I haven't seen a good video, I say, in a while.
The last one I watched wasn't really that good.
It was called Why Nintendo is so overprotective of its intellectual property.
That seems...
Because if you know nothing about Nintendo history, it's a super interesting video, but
after I was done watching it, he says that like, oh, the reason why it's because they
have this one lawsuit where Universal Studios wanted to sue them for using the word Kong,
but they didn't own the rights to it and that kind of scared them off.
That's why they didn't really merchandise or spread themselves thin.
And then after I was done watching the video, I was thinking like, wait a second, what about
the Super Mario Bros. Super Show era, where they were putting everything on macaroni in
the live action movie?
He did not mention that era at all.
He skipped over it.
And I'm like, wow, I mean, I would have argued that it wasn't even necessarily that lawsuit
that did it.
I do think it was probably just the live action movie that really scared them off from like...
Did you see the trailer for the new Mario movie?
The little promo that they had?
Yeah.
Yeah, it looks really...
It looks really cute.
A little advertisement.
Yeah, it looks really cute.
I am...
I'm not gonna lie.
I like...
I'm gonna watch it, but like a part of me feels like, God, I wish I was like 12 years
old, because I'd be more excited about this, because I feel like I'm not that excited for
it.
Even though it seems like this would be something I would want, and it looks like they're stretching
beyond and doing more kind of lore stuff, like they even have like the whole Kong race
there and everything.
And I would have ate that shit up as a kid, but like...
Yeah.
Now I'm kind of like...
Like, I don't know.
I don't know.
It's like...
It's...
I mean, I'm gonna watch it.
I'll probably like it, but I'm not...
I don't feel that excited about it.
I just...
I don't know.
I guess I moved on.
You know?
I never...
There's...
I didn't...
Care for Mario in the first place, so I'm just interested.
I didn't really care about the movie at all.
I thought it was gonna, like, whatever, but I gotta say, seeing that new trailer, there's
something that warms my heart a little bit about the fact that they're sticking to the
old, like, their plumbers from Brooklyn, like, backstory.
I...
I love the live-action movie.
I get the more I love that.
Yeah.
Like, live-action movie.
It's great.
I genuinely love the live-action movie as a kid.
Like, I watched it a bunch of times.
I'll tell you...
I'll tell you this.
Something about, like, it feels like the Mario movie is being made by people who are, like,
fans of Mario, and not gonna lie.
I feel like...
Cause there's, like, a big, like, group of people who love, like, those last two live-action
Sonic movies, and, like, like, everyone I know who loves it is not gonna listen to
this podcast.
So, I could say this.
I feel like it was a big cope.
I feel like liking those movies was, like, a massive cope.
Because they're just unironically, like, what if Alvin from Alvin and Chipmunks was a superhero?
It's, like, what the Sonic movies are.
And I'm tired of pretending they're not.
I'm tired of pretending they're not that.
Cause it's...
It's really...
It doesn't...
It wouldn't even fucking...
It wouldn't even fucking matter.
I'll...
I'll be honest.
What?
It wouldn't even...
It wouldn't fucking matter.
I'll tell you this.
He wouldn't do anything.
If they removed Sonic from that movie...
Like, if they removed everything, like, that was Sonic the Hedgehog related, I wouldn't
even be able to tell that it was supposed to be a Sonic movie to begin with.
Hmm.
Oh my gosh.
If you take everything Sonic related out of something, you wouldn't know it was Sonic
the Hedgehog.
No, no, no.
Not like that.
Like, because it's certain...
Like, Sonic stories have, like, a certain way about, you know.
Like, like...
Oh.
Here's how...
You're saying the movie didn't feel Sonic.
No, it didn't really...
Didn't feel...
I mean, the fact that, like, we have, like, kind of like a human character that we're
following...
I mean...
Like, like an oven in the chipmunks.
This guy is just Dave.
This guy is just Dave from oven in the chipmunks.
Everything wrong with the Sonic movie that you're describing is down to just that one
human character.
Just for one.
Not even all human characters.
I don't think so.
Even like, the one dad guy.
No, it is down to him.
He has a weird hexagon-shaped face.
I want to punch him.
I hate this face.
Personally, I think he's handsome.
But, like...
Even, like, robot...
Even, like, dog...
Well, let's find out whether or not he's handsome.
He's in Doctor Eggman.
He looks like an NFT profile picture.
Like, I don't mind Jim Carrey, but, like, he does not look like...
Dude, I'm not sure...
Jim Carrey is Eggman.
I love Jim Carrey.
It's so weird.
Jim Carrey is Eggman looks...
He's good.
Jim Carrey is Eggman looked kind of neat.
I thought that looked cool.
I mean, I didn't see the movie.
I really enjoyed him as Eggman.
I'll tell you this.
If, like, if that design existed and it wasn't tied to a Sonic movie, I would never even
say tell that that was supposed to be Eggman.
Hmm.
Well, doesn't he look more like Eggman in the second one?
Doesn't he, like, become fat or whatever?
No, he doesn't.
He stays skinny.
He does become fat.
But he gets the costume.
Like, like, he looks more like classic Eggman.
He gets the must...
Yeah.
There's, like, little, like, classic Eggman-isms going for him, but it doesn't get too, like...
You know what?
I kind of think, and I haven't seen the movie, so I don't know what the fuck I'm talking
about, but something about the fact that Jim Carrey kind of doesn't look anything at all
like Eggman, and yet, you know, from the trailers I saw, he kind of sort of was...
I think it's like a weird outside the box.
I would say it's a weird outside the box, maybe even inspired casting choice that I would
never have thought of.
Like, I'm a...
I like it.
I think I like it.
I enjoy it.
I'm entertained.
And in interviews, Jim Carrey was like, I really, really hope that in the next movie
they let me be fat.
He said, I mean, I'll tell you this, I mean, I thought the second movie was better than
the first one, but the first one wasn't even, like, a high bar, so it was like...
It went from, like, eh, to, all right, for me.
You know, I just want to have fun with these movies.
I'm not expecting them to be, like, good films, just want to have fun.
They've been fun.
I'm just trying to have fun with your wife.
Too bad.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
She's your gay now, huh?
She's your gay.
Who was I coming into last night?
Boom.
Got him.
Dead.
You're almost as gay as Riku.
I would say.
I didn't say, I didn't say I wasn't, I didn't say I wasn't also a Kingdom Hearts character.
I, when I saw they would cast, what's this, Jim Carrey's Eggman, I was like, what the
fuck?
Weird.
Interesting.
Neat.
When I saw that they cast Jack Black as Bowser, I thought, neat.
And then I heard him, and I was like, oh, you know what?
It is Jack Black, but it kind of sounds, it just kind of sounds normal, kind of just sounds
like Bowser.
Honestly, it's not.
When they said?
It's not that weird.
It's not that weird of a voice.
When they said Jack Black Bowser, I thought, oh, perfect.
That just works for me.
If you, if you're...
Yeah, it just works.
It just works, but it doesn't really, it's not really interesting.
I don't know.
I think Jim Carrey as Eggman is interesting.
I'll tell you this.
I'm pretty like, you know what, ultimately, I feel like if you like Sonic, you like those
Sonic movies, and I kind of relate in the way that, like, if you notice, a lot of DC
movies have very kind of like, interesting like casting choices, and I think the biggest
example would be like Arnold Schwarzenegger as like Mr. Freeze, right?
And like, oh, I love that.
That.
I love that they went in that turn.
Okay, okay.
And with that, I mean, that was like, because Arnold was like the biggest star of the freaking
era.
No, but like, if, but think a bit like this, Mr. Freeze, whereas Jim, Jim Carrey is not
exactly like an A-lister anymore.
You know what's so funny is that that version of Mr. Freeze was created because the, that
first Tim Burton Batman movie came out, and in the, in the show, in that episode, Heart
of Ice, which is like a 10 out of 10 episode, I watched it like three times last month in
a row.
Mr. Freeze isn't like a bodybuilder Austrian guy.
He's like a little, little fucking little cancer nerd in a super suit, you know, in, in, in
which, in the animated series, yeah, animated series.
Yeah.
Right.
So it's like, oh, to choose a bodybuilder to play that character is a very out there choice,
you know.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, it's a different, okay.
Mr. Freeze is from the animated series.
Like he was made for.
He is.
Not from an older.
He existed, but he was more of a goofier character called like Mr. Zero.
And then in the animated series, they're all like, Hey, what if we just reboot his old
origin story?
Let's, let's literally rip off the movie, the abominable, the abominable Doctor Fibes,
which has the whole origin with the wife.
And like, let's give that to Mr. Freeze.
And the re, and if you ever, if you rewatch that episode, I really recommend you rewatch
Heart of Ice because that's a real, that's still a really good episode.
Mr. Freeze has like this little, his voice does like, it sounds like it sounds mechanical
because it's coming out of like a speaker and they, and that's like lifted directly
from the movie, the abominable Doctor Fibes, because that character, that character connects
like a speaker into his fro and he, and he talks out of like a fucking like phonograph
and it, and it sounds like that.
Yeah.
Like one of those things that like people that had to get their tracheas removed because
they got throat cancer, like when they put the microphone to their throat.
It's like the movie was made, like, I think in the 60s.
So it's like a, it's like a speaker.
It's like a fucking, it's those old timey, like the fucking open bloom flower looking
speakers that that's like connected to a record player.
Yeah, yeah, that movie is great, too.
That movie is like, imagine if it's like it saw, but like if the Jigsaw killer was
like a goofy super villain who was played by Vincent Price, if anyone knows Vincent
Price, the 10 out of 10.
Of course, of course, I know Vincent Price.
Well, come on.
He's a classic boy.
Well, well, I'm trying to think, I'm trying to think.
Was OK.
So it casting Jim Carrey as Eggman is like, OK, we need we have a goofy villain from
a well-known franchise and we're so we're going to and we're going to cast this sort
of like comedian, this like this well-known comedian, but who's like like past his prime.
Like he's not really a big movie star anymore, even though everybody knows who he is.
Is that kind of what they were doing with Arnold in ice?
Like was Arnold kind of already sort of like an old star and they were like,
let's bring Arnold back for this fucking weird like superhero role.
I can't remember if like Batman and Robin was one of the last films.
Because if I remember correctly, Arnold didn't really bring that much to like the
Mr. Freeze, like Mr. Freeze is not like a very he didn't really act a lot.
Well, he kind of delivers like ice puns.
I mean, he yeah, he like he, you know, he acted as much as Arnold can act, you know.
Right. Right.
And the ice puns is all part of the charm, which is very funny how like
the the original character of Mr.
Freeze was like a very goofy like his original suit was like yellow and pink
and he had more like a bubble helmet.
And yeah.
And then they make them all super serious in the Batman animated series.
And then they make him goofy again in the live action.
Yeah, they take they take the new serious backstory,
but they make him ridiculous again by cat by making him Arnold in hard advice.
Isn't there a part where like he's a he's a doctor and someone calls him
like Doctor Freeze and he says, actually, it's Mr.
Isn't there? Yeah, yeah, there's this.
Yes, there is a part like that. That's that's a fucking that's I'm sorry.
There's this really good bit in that episode
where I'm and I it's in like I'm looking for right now in the animated
gifts, but there's like a bit where like and I was listening to the director's
commentary of that episode where it's like so Mr.
Freeze is trying to kill the guy who like, you know, is the reason why he's in
that fucking suit, right?
And they're they're attacking his building with his like giant freeze cannon
and Batman stops the cannon and Mr.
Freeze with his cannon already kind of like froze the door shut to the building
so he can't get in and and I was looking to the director's commentary
and they thought like, oh, how do we heat Mr.
Freeze has to be inside that building for the for like the ending of the episode.
So how do we get him inside that building?
And they think of this very clever bit where it's like, OK, what he's going to do
is going to walk up to a fire hydrant and the fire hydrant is going to like kick
it, it's going to it's going to break open, right?
And then water is going to spray out and then Mr.
Freeze is going to like push his gun into the water stream
and turn it on and that upstream will freeze like the water.
But the like the frozen ice would push Mr.
Freeze upward and it's kind of hard to describe.
But when you see it in action, like here's what it looks like.
And it's like really fucking clever, like way to get him inside the building.
You see what you see what I mean?
Let's see here. All right, I'm watching.
There he goes. Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, it makes sense. Yeah, it's it's really it's really dope.
Like fuck, I miss listening to directors commentary.
This is I think it would honestly, I think it would make a little more sense
as if he just kind of jumped on top of the water and just froze a little bit of it.
And then the water pressure might just push the little ice platform,
like I rocket it up, I guess. I don't know.
I don't I don't know. I get it.
I think I'm I think he'll just fall down because of his suit
would be too heavy for a stream.
OK, the physical of it is kind of like. I'm sure.
How does how does how does a physics of us make sense for?
Yeah, the physics are what is the ice with the ice block.
It's ultimately what we stop flying.
Or is it like a tube?
It what it what it is is that it's slowly getting it's getting frozen,
but only like.
OK, what already came out.
So that kind of like pushes him up.
Here's what I think. Here's what I think.
The the water once it leaves the the the hydrant is in is in a free fall.
It's going to travel in a parabolic arc.
So if he freezes a chunk of it and then like holds on to it somehow,
you know, assuming that it has like a lot more mass than he does,
he's just going to be pulled along in its parabolic arc as it flies.
It's it's very goofy physics.
But as long as it kind of makes sense, it's fine.
I mean, this is the same universe where he has like a giant mechanical
robot suit that he's in, right?
And he has like a made up disease.
So, you know, it's fine. It's fine.
I get it. I'm I'm I'm the episode is based.
The episode is really good.
While watching it, I was like being I was being one of those like
the whole you I was being I was jerking off.
I was like being like they don't make them like they used to villains.
Don't like quote poetry anymore.
They don't like they don't fucking hold villains.
Don't hold you hostage and then like fucking like, you know,
do like fucking poetry around you about like, oh, woe is me.
Did you did did you hear that they released like a new
edited version of like Roald Dahl's books and like they just change.
Now, did you hear about they unironically did the yeah, I know what you're talking
about, they did the meme.
They should they change they changed a bunch of stuff and they genuinely
like put in like, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
But they fucking they made them woke and mean that in like a weird bad way.
Like they took out like pretty innocuous things and like made them like
aggressively like inclusive.
They did like like what kind of a not I'll find the I'll find the example
that they did the thing where it's like, I'm quoting the sick animation clip.
But it's kind of like back in my day, it was all about Chef Boyardy.
Now it's now all they eat is Chef Boyard girl.
That's that's unironically like that's unironically like what they did.
And it's like, this is so why like.
OK, OK, OK, I found that a sick animation.
I still saw a sick animation made a little thing about that.
I don't know if he came up with it.
Sounds like something that I'm exactly quoting like a sick animation short
that he made recently. Yeah.
I've really been liking those shirts you've been making.
Those are really funny.
Yeah, it's just non sequitur, a little little character.
I wish she was my friend.
So here. Here's here's here's three bits that were changed.
I only saw the first one.
The first one is the one that but the other two, I guess, are similar.
Yeah, here. Here's some examples of changes they made to these twenty twenty two
editions of of a role doll.
Yeah, OK, the first one you let's change.
You can't go around pulling the hair of every lady you meet,
even if she is wearing gloves, just you try it and see what happens.
What is that?
Yeah, they couldn't and they couldn't.
They didn't want to say that.
Besides, they're so they changed it to besides, there are plenty of other reasons
why women might wear wigs and there is certainly nothing wrong with that.
Have that that changes the meaning of the as a like what like what?
As Joseph, why is that change?
I'm looking at the.
Oh, they they also change stuff from from Matilda, too.
I think they did.
Yeah, they did it to a bunch of which is so weird.
So the first one is like they really change to work.
So the was already woke.
I don't know why like they're doing the more female CEOs bit.
Why they're really girl, even if she's working as a cashier in a supermarket
or typing letters for a businessman, even if she is working.
I why? OK, I don't even under.
I don't even know the context of this line.
So I don't really guess.
I guess the idea is because it's like kind of reinforcing
like old gender norms kind of stuff.
And these books are so popular, they're so circulated.
Yeah, I'm not justifying.
I'm not justifying like the rewrites of it.
It's just ultimately you should you should still tell kids,
hey, by the way, those were written like when people those were written
before the Mormon Church decided like people were people.
They like like if it's talking about witches and like you can't tell
even if they're doing normal woman things like being a cashier
or typing letters for a businessman like that, I guess that's fine
to change because it's old fashioned.
The first one I'm trying to like that I don't get.
It's like you can't go around.
You can't go around pulling hair to see if they have a wig.
Just try and see what happens.
So it's saying don't do that.
Besides, there are plenty of other reasons why one might wear wigs.
Like why couldn't they like that?
Why can't they change?
They couldn't they didn't need to delete the first bit.
They could have just added.
I mean, OK, I would like if they really wanted to do that.
Like it's not like this is why the first one is saying wigs is a bad thing.
Anyway, I mean, I don't even see the need for like, oh, we got to put a line
in there about how it's OK to wear a wig.
Nothing about the first line suggests that it isn't OK for someone to wear a wig.
Yeah. What I was saying is don't don't mess with people who wear wigs.
It's already saying not to mess with people right over that.
Like it's it's fine.
Yeah, I assume these are like some of like the most baffling
and like pointless and irritating changes.
Maybe some of the other ones I might understand more because apparently they just
I don't know, the new additions have a bunch of I really I really hate the second one
because like it's it's not the fact that it's like I see where like you could
interpret the second one as the original being a bit problematic.
I don't agree with the cashier thing.
Everyone weighs in girls of both cashiers and always have been.
I don't get that.
But like the typing letters for a businessman, it's like,
oh, working under a man.
It's like, OK, I can see if I've been in a shoe.
But why can't you just say instead of running a business,
you could also just say working in an office because like they're describing
normal like average Joe jobs and being a CEO or a top scientist
or not average normal person jobs.
Maybe if I read the context, something about this would make more sense.
But yeah, it really seems like they changed the meaning from
work talking about someone just having a job to talking about someone
like being a big wig, a fricking for.
Yeah, girl boss top and like that's a different
that's a different scenario you're describing, especially if the context is
like, oh, you know, witches could be ordinary people.
Now it's witches could be billionaires.
Yeah, we were more rich billionaires.
Are they fucking billionaires?
You mean J.K. Rowling?
Oh, my God, goblins, the goblins.
I bet there were some problematic goblins in Roald Dahl's books.
Probably the first one is like our kind of goblins design.
Yeah, it's it's sort of odd because in the witches, like I can't remember
the book, the book itself, like the idea that witches don't have hair
and they wear wigs inherently is sort of like playing into
like this idea that not having hair is a bad thing.
Wearing wigs isn't is a sense of like, oh, you're kind of you could be a secret
secret bad person, like that's that's already into like the the reason
the witches are like that is so like changing just this line to say, by the
way, there's nothing wrong with wearing wigs, but also in this story,
the bad people always wear wigs.
Are the witches bad in the witches?
I have they are they eat children.
They're they're OK.
It's like a little boy, I think.
And he's like, I I'm just a little boy.
And then there's these witches.
Like, I will eat you.
There was something I do vividly remember the plot synopsis like a little
boy who's raised by his grandma and his grandma says, like, oh, yeah,
witches exist and they eat kids and they disguise themselves as regular women.
And I first see them believe it, but he has an encounter with like a weird
woman who's trying to lure her down his treehouse where he's like, look,
I have all these snakes.
And he's like, what the fuck?
And eventually they go to a hotel and the kid accidentally like witnesses
like a witch conference and then the witches find them and they turn them into
like a no, not witch.
Yeah, witch, which witch gone for the tournament to a mouse.
And then the kid figures out, oh, we should we should like slip the mouse juice
to the witches, but they all turn into mouses.
And then we can just all stop.
Definitely.
We can always just stomp them to death or something.
I don't know how they kill anyway.
So they do that.
They stomp the witches to death.
And then Jesus and the ending bit.
You know what the ending bit?
It's very interesting, like the direction they go because this feels kind of
dark for a kid's like story.
But the thing is so he doesn't turn back into a human.
He stays a mouse and they figure out that a mouse has like only like,
like maybe a five year or 10 year lifespan.
They have a short lifespan, right?
And the grandma says like, oh, I'm not going to live long.
So we're probably going to die around the same time.
So it's fine that you stay a mouse.
The end.
Cool.
Just die.
What?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, to the kid.
Because they can't turn him back from being a human.
So they assume that you're not probably live a full mouse life, which is kind of
short. So we're going to die around the same time.
I've watched the film.
There's a film that I remember.
And the film he turns back into human.
I don't remember if it ends differently.
And the film he turns back into a kid and then the book he doesn't.
Yeah.
Have you have you read the sequel to Charlie and the Chocolate Factory?
The The Great Glass Elevator.
Yeah.
Yeah, Charlie and the Great.
Charlie and the Great Glass Elevator is so it's I read it as a kid.
And like, it's so fucked.
There's aliens.
They go to like the International Space Station and like there's aliens there.
And there there's a part where there's a part where
Wonka makes this like juice.
He makes this like gum that like turns you young and the grandpa parents
like eat so much they eat too much of it.
And they ate the unaged to before they were born.
So they have to travel to like the fucking ghostly
like afterlife spirit realm to like find their souls and spray them with like
sap from a from a from a thousand year old pine tree to like
re-age them back to the land of the living and it turns them old again.
And they're like, can I have some more so I could be young?
And they're like, no, you ate it all the first time.
No, you're just old now.
Sorry, you fucked up.
Jesus Christ.
It's a lot of weird, weird shit in that one.
Aliens, aliens are canon in in Charlie and the Chocolate Factory.
Makes sense.
I believe it.
I mean, they have Oompa Loompas.
Oompa Loompas were just like pygmy people, which is like a real
it's a real group of people that I don't I don't really I used to exist.
Maybe they they maybe still exist.
No, they're there. The problematic goblins.
They're like, um, you know, the real problematic is not thinking back
to Tim Burton's Charlie and the Chocolate Factory.
And like, Wonka does do it.
Do I'm going into the jungle and I'm stealing the people that I mean,
I mean, that's not Tim Burton.
Like that's in the original book.
I know, I just decided to think it.
I haven't read the book.
So I'm just thinking of the land and the Oompa's.
There's like all these creatures that eat them.
And and really, Wanker's like, yeah, it's humbling with me and my factory and work.
It's straight up.
The Oompa Loompas are a tribe from like the African jungle that are like savages
and they were being attacked by, yeah, freaking creatures in the wild.
And he was like, hey, I'll give you a factory to live in.
And if you just become my, sure you, we don't call it slavery.
You know, you can just live in my factory and work there.
And it's better than it's better than being eaten by Jaguars, right?
And they're like, yeah, I'll like, let's do it.
I like, thank you.
Thank you, White Saviour, for rescuing me from the fricking from the fricking
dangers of the wild. It's so funny.
I love it. It's so funny how like all kind of like major classic
like British literature, like kind of justifies colonization slightly in a way.
It's a major cultural exercise.
Even fascinating people, like even like Alan Moore, who's very like critical
about like the British government and as like an anarchist and like League
of Extraordinary Gentlemen, he forgot to read.
He didn't realize that like, oh, having so much of all the universe,
pop culture centered around British pop culture kind of like creates
this land of like whiteness and subtle, very so subtle,
like colonization, justification.
Luckily, though, everyone goes to space and lives forever.
It's easy. It's very easy to just kind of fall into that sort of thinking
without even realizing it when that's just the culture.
That's why in my Marvel Universe fanfic, the Queen dies back back
when the IRA put that bomb in her car.
It actually kills her in my alternate universe.
I did that happen in real life.
They the bomb wasn't the blast wasn't big enough to kill her.
And I think it was either was the wrong car or it was the blast just wasn't big enough.
So they like missed a chance.
I never got a DVD box out of the crown, so we'll never know.
I have.
Wait, where'd you go then?
Let's see.
I had to did some.
OK, shit.
I already already talked about the bacon in my lentils.
So that was it. That was all I had.
That was the only one you're going to bring it up before you go to stand up.
Mike, can you get your cue cards?
Hey, I know now hold on now, hold on.
I might have mentioned this already already in this episode,
but did I mention the bacon in my lentils?
Actually, OK, interesting.
I've been I've been doing experiments.
I've been doing experiments on quinine and time in my room.
I bought OK, I explained that I want for the to achieve a certain visual effect
in a in a in a video that I want to record.
I thought about painting my teeth with quinine.
To make them look weird.
And so to achieve this, I bought 12 liters of tonic water
and I boiled it down to like 100 milliliters.
And I have I put it under a black light and I did things to it.
I did I did fucked up things to it.
Oh, no. Here we are.
Here we are. So so the OK, OK, so it glows blue under the black light.
If you boil it down, it glows blue brighter.
But if you boil it down even more, it it starts to glow less
and it glows it glows on one side, but like the light sort of like diffuses
and it doesn't glow all the way through.
And I think the reason why is that the concentration of the other chemicals
in it, specifically like the aspartame or whatever,
because I got the non sugar kind, is like occluding the quinine molecules
and preventing them from fluorescing.
So I tried this, right, because it's acidic.
There's citric acid in there.
So I did the baking soda vinegar volcano thing
and I put baking soda into it to try and neutralize the acid.
And what happens when you do that is it creates carbon dioxide and sodium citrate.
And sodium citrate is a salt and an emulsifier.
It is what they put in cheese to turn it into American cheese.
So I put baking soda in the stuff and it bubbled and this is amazing.
I couldn't believe this.
The quinine glows blue.
But when you put the baking soda in, it turned green.
It now it now fluoresces green under a black light.
And I don't know why that is because it's still like the quinine is not in like a compound.
The quinine should be the same.
So I have no idea why it changed color, but it did.
I should have taken a picture.
I wish I had a picture to show you.
So like my mistake, you know, but it looks like it's like a different
chemical reaction or somehow the wavelength got affected.
I don't know.
I didn't think that the quinine would change form at all in doing this.
But like, I guess it did.
But visually, it looks really good because it turns it turned when I added
the baking soda to it, it turned not just like it's like a slightly green.
It's like a whitish, greenish, yellowish, like milky white pale glow.
And it looks it actually looks really good.
So it looks it looks.
Yeah, I'm going to.
I don't know.
I'm going to see what.
Smear that all over your face.
This is what I've been doing this week.
I've been like I've having all these I'm turning on the black light
and I'm like putting like powders into all these glowing vials and they're
like fizzing and boiling and like glowing at me and changing color.
And I'm just like, you should be recording this.
That'd be good.
I should be recording this because that's like slime experiments.
It'd be good.
Also, also the origin also Ben real quick.
I'm going to take a picture of the origin story of Ben Slime.
It would you mean the you mean the cop killer, the cop killer.
Who?
No, no, I don't fuck with that commie bullshit.
Give me give me one minute.
I'll be right back.
Then I can't spare one minute.
I can't spare one minute.
Oh, there's a thing I was going to bring up, but I already forgot what it was.
Were you going to bring up at man and the wasquantum manium now in feeders?
Quantum manium.
I love that pun.
I saw I saw that movie high when it like an early screening of it.
And the whole time I was thinking like, God, when is this going to be over?
What if it was Ant-Man or the wasp?
And like, you didn't know which movie you're going to be seeing.
You have to choose the gender.
Oh, it's like, oh, it's like Pokemon or the wasp.
And it's either about one or the other, but you don't know which one.
It's it's it's like clue.
It's like the movie clue when it released in theaters.
I had like each theater had like a different ending or they're like
or they're like seven different endings.
But like it was random which theater got what for like who the color was.
You know, would be a I always thought would be a pretty cool like experiment was
um and there was like a comic that basically had like like two comics
were made that were using the same script, but it was like two different
interpretations of the same script.
And like two different artists.
Yeah, two different artists.
And you could like design the characters however you want, right?
But it'd be like the same characters in both stories.
And the plot beats would be the same up until the ending.
Both versions would have different endings.
I always thought that'd be a really cool experiment and you can kind of do
like a Pokemon thing where you call one like red version.
The other one blue version or something, you know.
Dude, everyone buys the same comic twice.
What if you do it to like the only difference is like the hair color.
But like in this in the script, you get around it by like use.
They're like aliens and they they don't say blue or red.
They say like one of them is like blue hair and pronounce the other
where one or other one is like no hair and no nouns.
What one would it be?
What would be day version and the other one be them version?
That's that's or like or like you could like as long as like maybe
if there's like a part of the story where it's like a character is like,
hey, I like your blue shirt.
You could like it'd be kind of like Mad Libs kind of, you know.
The entire script and Mad Lib like verbs.
This this could work.
I just have to figure out an angle.
No.
OK, I'm back.
I'm back.
I'm back. Let's let's let's see.
See these glowy's.
All right, so it looks that it looks really well, it looks really.
OK, static.
So you can see it in the big like cup there.
You can see how it's only glowing on one side
because like it's like sort of dark and like I think the light just doesn't
like get all the way through it.
Here's here's like a better.
Like a better shot.
I would.
This is really nice.
Just yeah, just as images.
You should make a wall.
I'm going to post this.
Actually, it actually looks really cool in the photo.
It looks like much more vivid in.
OK, OK.
Well, in these pictures, it looks really, really purple in in person.
It doesn't look quite this purple, but also the liquid like glows brighter.
Liquid seems brighter in person than it does in these images.
Maybe that's your eyes, your human eyes, not being able to see purple.
I'm going to post these images on Twitter and be like,
yo, is it normal if your cum glows green under black light?
Is that is that normal?
Oh, yeah, Ben, you're talking last episode about wanting to go for a bit
of a James Lee asphatic with these things you're doing.
Yeah, but like the glowing like eyes and teeth is a what I want.
If you if you want, since I'm a I have a bit of a I'm a little bit of a visual
effects boy. Oh, you have expertise to share.
Yeah, or maybe like you could send your footage my way and I could see about
like making the glowy bits like look extra like glowy and fuck around with it.
I would. That sounds like fun.
I think that might be cool.
Do you do you have any?
I don't know.
Do you have any tips on like how to how to make it work in a in a like how to get
that so that you could do that to it?
Um, I mean, there's a lot of methods I could try.
I'd probably experiment and then like let you know what works.
I probably do it in After Effects.
I'm going to. Yeah, my my idea is just is just like paint
the glowing liquid onto the parts of my face that I want to like.
Yes, obviously, emanate that's a good idea.
That's that's the plan.
Yeah, my my thinking is like in post, we could enhance it even more.
Like, yeah, I could like have it take the bright parts of the image
and like have those like have like a bit of a kind of glow or a bloom sort of effect.
I'd like not not in the gross to PS free bloom era video games.
Right.
I might my plan was to try and like enhance the effect in post,
but like I'm sure you have more.
I'm sure you you probably know how to do that better.
And also, I think you have better software because like I only know I only have Vegas.
That's all I know how to use.
Oh, yeah, Vegas is it's a program struggle to do that kind of thing in Vegas.
Yeah, for sure. OK, that'd be sweet.
Yeah, I'll see I'll see what I get.
I'll let you see it.
That'd be awesome.
I want to fuck around with whatever you got when the time comes.
And then you can look at my result and say yes or no.
No trash.
Let me get this out of my.
Yeah, my idea.
I think I said that my idea is that I want to do that it's going to be an ad
for the Slime and Punishment book, but it's going to be like as the cop killer.
And so I want to have a real like sort of eerie sort of glowing atmosphere to it.
Yeah, are you going to do a funny voice?
I will do maybe a slightly funny voice.
And then maybe I'll add some weird like monstrous kind of oblivion.
Maybe if you would like to add some monster voice sounds to my voice.
That might be cool to I could I could for your voice into manipulator
and have it have that kind of like tractor growly effect to track tractor growly.
I don't know how to explain it.
I guess the cop killer, he would say his voice would be sort of like ragged
and like rough and horse, but also sort of maybe like sort of like sort of inhuman,
sort of like maybe not mechanical, but maybe sort of like maybe a little
bling or oily or or or echo.
He's like he's kind of turned on, but he's shy, you know, or maybe he would have.
No, he doesn't have sex.
He never he never has sex or even thinks it took you a while.
It took you a while to react to the fuck.
I just. Yeah, because I couldn't I just couldn't put it together.
It just didn't compute.
But the cop killer doesn't have a penis.
Maybe he would have sort of like he would have that thing where like he would sort
of have like multiple voices, you know, like like Dorman, like Dorman in in
Shadow of the Colossus, how he was like multiple voices speaking out of the same
voice, I don't know, maybe you'd have a little bit of that like reverb thing going on.
He is he's multitudes.
I don't know. I'm just I'm just throwing ideas out there
because he's a communist because he's a communist, you see.
I'm just being silly.
I'm just being I'm just I'm just kidding, unless.
What else was I talking about?
Nothing. That's it.
Um, can you can you just tell me what this whole this whole perfect comic party thing is?
Can you explain?
Perfect comic party. Great question.
The answer is no. Moving on.
Perfect comic party is an incentive structure to get myself and Ben to actually work in our comics.
And the idea is we will make chapters
and then put them in a PDF together.
And it'll be like, oh, it's our little shonen jump kind of moving.
That's that sounds cool.
That would be really cool.
You guys can even put it up early on like the Patreon for people.
We could. Yeah. Yeah, I think.
Yeah. Well, I mean.
Well, why post it? Well, I posted early.
Well, you know, incentivize people to. Yeah, you're right.
You're right. I hate I hate our patrons.
I don't want them to have. Oh, boy, they don't deserve it.
Yes. Speaking of comics, it's it's out.
It's fine. The first by the time this drops.
Cheesy one of Big Paglacci is all out on Twitter.
Isn't. Yeah, um, I was sad when you posted it because I saw you posted
in Big Paglacci and I was like, oh, my God, it's here.
And then I tried to read it and it wasn't all the way out.
And I was like, no, I can't read the whole thing yet.
It was act one. Yep.
How much of it do you have done?
Oh, I act to act to by the time this video drops,
act two should already be starting like on Twitter.
I thought the whole thing will be posted on my Patreon, obviously.
But I currently like the whole thing.
Yeah. Or you mean the whole act to it?
Don't it's only two acts.
So two is shorter.
Oh, OK.
And I only have six pages left to draw.
And I'm pretty sure to get that all done by the time this video drops.
If it if it doesn't if it doesn't drop,
I recommend you check my Patreon or I actually have the whole thing on my Instagram
because Instagram has this feature.
Instagram basically has kind of like the the little like you could put a story,
which is like a little tiny video kind of like that thing that Twitter
that was trying out where like, oh, you can put kind of like a little
quick clip that stays up for 24 hours above like
if you're doing Twitter mobile will be there.
Instagram so has that feature.
And I literally like put every page in McPaglacci on there.
And then I collect it together in a reel.
And if you go to my Instagram profile,
it's like right there in a collection and you can just read all of act one.
It's literally literally I just dropped all of act one on Instagram.
And and all of act one is also on my
band discord, I but also and I've been slowly updating it on Twitter.
It should be all out by now by the time this video is out.
Currently, as we're recording, I have like four pages left of act one.
And I'm going to drop those off tomorrow.
But it's it's been pretty good.
What do you what do you think of it so far, Ben?
I think I mean, I think the idea is really funny.
I really like it.
And also, yeah, I was reading.
I guess I've only read through what was up when I caught up, which was.
Oh, God, can I spoil it?
Can I say what happens?
Or yeah, go ahead. It's fine.
The part where I got to the part where Ronald
Ronald catches the hamburger and birdie in the in the back room.
And and I don't know.
It's pretty good. I don't know.
It's like, hey, Paythos, I don't know.
I thought I'm I'm compelling.
Hey, I was like, hey, maybe this this opera was pretty good back in the day.
I don't know.
Might have might have been interesting.
I really do love hearing people say that, like, oh, please,
cheesy, drop the pages early because, like, I'm so tempted to just look up
what happens on Wikipedia or something.
No, I want to know.
The people are very in fraud.
And Act 2 is Act 2 is pretty good.
I have I have a couple more Easter eggs and cameos in Act 2.
There's a there's a lot in Act 1 during that big splash page.
I'm not going to name them all.
Uh huh. Uh huh. Right.
But people figure it out.
Right.
But yeah, I'm happy.
Splash page. You mean like the first one when with like the big parade?
Yeah. Yeah.
There's a there's like a lot of cameos I put in there.
Of characters that only appeared in one commercial never again.
Right.
There's a there's a couple of deeper cuts in Act 2.
Fascinating.
Yeah. Fascinating.
No, I'm liking it a lot.
I think I think it rule.
I think I'm a I'm a MacPaliachi fan.
I'm a I'm a head. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm hoping a Paghead.
Paghead. I'm I'm I love MacPaliachi.
I love the way he's abusive to I love that he's a groomer.
I like that he's just a groomer.
Yeah, he's straight.
He's straight. He's straight up.
He's straight up a judge turpin.
What do you what?
The the.
Sweet Sweetie Todd.
Yeah. Yeah.
La Mal.
It's so funny you mentioned Sweetie Todd, because I was joking with my part
or being like, if this if this gets really popular, I'll do like
an adaptation of Sweetie Todd, but all the characters are like
the Chuck E. Cheese and Rock a Fire explosion animatronics or something.
OK. And what I'll do is that I'll do that.
Every character that Sweetie Todd kills is actually
an animatronic that was decommissioned and isn't used anymore.
Right. Interesting.
Maybe maybe I probably am not going to do that.
I got like a bunch of other ideas, but I'm glad people are liking it so far.
I like it a lot.
It's great.
I do recommend that our listeners check out
McPagliacchi, McPagliacchi.
This is this is my this is my comeback
from the disaster of clown milk.
This is the comeback right here.
Yeah, true, true.
Yeah, cool.
Yeah, they exactly.
Well, epic.
It's good and I appreciate it.
Thank you for your work on it.
Thank you. OK. Yeah.
Yeah, did you read it?
I read it when you first dropped it.
So I'm only a few pages in.
I haven't seen the bit with Burger Boy.
What's his what's his name?
The hamburger hamburger burger boy.
But yeah, I will read the rest of it soon.
It's good. It's it's it's a funny idea.
I don't know the opera, but it's obviously like
no, no, no serious thing, but with silly people in it.
It's they there's like a version on it.
There's a version in like several parts on YouTube.
In case you want to go watch it,
I recommend you watch it after you're done reading my version,
because each version is like slightly.
I've seen different.
I've seen two different versions of the opera
and I kind of pick and choose parts because
that's that's the awesome thing about like operas or plays
is that they're always different every time you watch them.
And and even they can even have all the same like cast members,
same set, same bill, the same everything.
It's always it's still like always very different because it's a live performance.
Yeah. And even like stuff like even like seating,
even like where you're sit sitting in the theater is like changes to so.
I mean, that changes in regular movies.
Sure. Sure.
Wait, no, but like in a regular in a regular movie,
you like to they choose the shot and wait, no, no, no, no, no, it doesn't
because in a movie, even if you're sitting in a different spot in the theater,
the shot in the movie is the same.
There's a there's a parallax, I understand.
Yeah, like right.
They choose what there's there's someone choosing what you
focus on while in a play.
You could sit closer, you could sit in the back, you know, it's like.
And sometimes you decide you want to just throw shit at the actors
and just see what they do.
Like tapping on the on a fishbowl.
I've been to like plays where like the seats are like surrounding
the kind of theater and it's like it's interesting, you know, but true.
Hey, I definitely had that thought when I'm like in the theater at the top part.
And I'm like, oh, you know, if I arc it right, I could hit the middle of the stage
from here. I really could. I could throw my drink.
It'd be so funny.
I shouldn't do it, though.
I've had that thought at the top of a tall building.
I think, haha, you know, I could just jump off the edge.
You know, I would all be over.
Finally, I shouldn't do it, though.
I'm not going to do it, though.
I'm not going to do it unless.
Unless someone pushes me and I can't help it.
Saying that it's wrong to want to kill yourself.
That's your right, Ben.
It's it's if it's if if wanting to kill myself is wrong, then I don't want to be right.
You know, that's so that's so that's so funny.
Because I actually I do this thing.
I do this terrible sin where I rewatch I re listen to old episodes of the PCP.
Oh, no.
No.
Which one?
You know, there's a full you once shame on us.
Listen to us once shame on us.
Listen to us twice.
Shame on you.
I re listen to the to the suicide episode.
Oh, well, give you are on there.
Then was it? I don't.
Yeah, I don't think I was on that one.
Yeah, you weren't on that one.
And it's like, like, God,
I think I really do think the key here is that you guys just we need to get back
to like just having like seven people on one episode talking over each other.
I think that was the magic spice.
It did. Yeah, it had a it had a it had an energy to it for sure.
I think I think Ben, you should just like over invite people to the podcast.
I don't know.
I don't I haven't really like invited anyone in a while.
Yeah, I asked.
I did ask I did ask one person not that long ago if they wanted to come on.
And they said they said they were nervous or whatever.
They didn't want to do it. I said, OK, you better invite as many people as you can
before you start pissing off people.
You can't get pancakes or no more.
Can we get can we get can we get the the the jilted former members
of the pizza party podcast?
Can we incorporate them?
Can we merge them into the amoeba that is the the PCP universe?
It depends.
You've got to like word it right, because well, the thing is,
I don't think Jim or Izzy taught the pan.
No, like because the thing they weren't they were already barely talking.
I like him very much anymore.
Like, um, yeah, exactly.
And Pan just seems like a.
He just seems like a guy that exists.
I don't see me.
He doesn't see how I could dislike him or like he's completely neutral.
I think I don't know.
You know what? I'm just speculating.
I kind of get a feeling sort of a Doug Walker, like he doesn't know what he's
doing and probably that sucks for everyone that works.
Then I don't know. This is the feeling that I just in the fall in the fallout
of the Pete of the pizza party podcast, everybody seems really upset
with how everything was done.
It's it's he's a real name.
You could say I think I agree.
He's he's being he's being a huge Nate, not not not that bad.
It's it's you would rate your streams.
If you pan pizza would have rated my fucking stream.
It it it's so funny how it's like
former members got kicked off without like pan telling them just because
a guy showed just because that peanut showed up and it was like,
dude, I will literally do everything for you.
You just have to show up and pants like, yeah, sure. Yeah, yeah.
And Daphne was just like and wait, wait, OK.
And Daphne was like that.
And Pan was like, OK, sure, whatever, do whatever you want.
And then Daphne was like, OK, well, I'm kicking off the former members.
They're gone now. And Pan was like, whatever.
Like, is that how it went?
Well, how it went was that like, oh, my God, I I saw like how it went
was that the former members found out they weren't going to be on
because of the tweet that dropped of it getting rebooted.
And Pan never told Izzy, who was supposed to be in charge of the new podcast.
Anything. OK. And then after that, Pan like started apologizing like, oh,
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry.
The tweet, the tweet that dropped was from Daphne,
saying the Pizza Party podcast has been reworked and now I'm on it
and my friends are on it and the old guys are gone.
Or am I or is that not right?
That's they never mentioned anything about the old people being gone.
They just didn't say.
So Daphne just tweeted, the Pizza Party podcast will now be these new people.
And that's the and that's the announcement.
Lol. He said he'd be in charge.
I don't like Daphne.
I everything.
The more I learn about him, the worse the worse he seems.
Oh, I'm going to I'm going to give you some exclusive dirt on Daphne.
That is not public knowledge.
I don't see. I think that if I think that Daphne would never
betray you like that.
So I really think that it's really, really despicable.
No, I'm kidding.
I think that is a is a snake and he would betray anyone.
He would betray his own mother for a nickel, just like shadow from Final Fantasy Six.
I haven't spoken to Daphne.
Several of my friends have.
My friend made who is who I've mentioned a bunch.
He he was in a video about Pennsylvania that Daphne did.
You know, I think it was remember the artist of fury on art.
They're like that really good artist who yeah, also like said,
like a whole bunch of extremely like extreme was that was that the person who was like
I can't they were like, were they like pretending to be black or something?
Or no, they were.
No, they're they're actually black.
I thought I thought there was no way to really clarify if he was black or not.
No, they posted pictures of themselves.
They posted pictures of their hands.
Didn't they just their hand?
It looked dark to me.
Oh, well, I trick it a little trick.
Well, if I trust him, go ahead.
I'm not I'm not going to just assume someone's white because they said the n word.
That that's the tell.
That's the tell.
I'm just I'm saying I'll get gone.
And I saw their hair, too.
It looked like, you know, it.
OK, I just I just I just remember I feel like I heard that
he said some stuff and people said, you shouldn't say that you're not black.
And he said, yes, I am.
And other people were saying, I don't think he is.
And so that's what just what I remember.
And then he posted pictures.
OK, didn't post his face.
We saw his arm and saw his hair and stuff.
And it looks looks pretty black to me.
Sure. I don't care about the n word
stuff, particularly because that's up in the air.
He did like post a bunch of like pictures of nooses
saying ha ha trans people and yourselves.
He was doing that shit.
He is a he is an actual piece of shit.
I do not like him and I do not want to defend him even a little bit.
The thing that the issue I have with Daphne in that video is the way he.
Oh, God, maybe I shouldn't mention this.
It's the way he roped teleperte into being on there.
Because teleperte doesn't like to comment on this sort of stuff.
He just he's just not comfortable talking about sort of controversial topics.
It's just not something that he was comfortable doing.
And Daphne is like, hey, can I call you real quick?
And he's like, and he's like, OK, can I record you and tell you?
He's like, yeah. And then he's like, OK,
look, look at all these screenshots of things if you're in our art did.
Now, tell me, give me the sound bite.
Give me the sound bite of you saying that you're disappointed in him.
And tell you sitting here thinking I don't want to be here.
But like he was just kind of pressured in because he wanted to want to be
able to put a sound bite of he wanted to be able to have like
here's teleperte saying that like how disappointed they are in so and so.
Yeah, it's like it's like it's just kind of weird to do that to someone who
without like like just putting someone on the spot and being like,
hey, you're going to be in my video, I'm going to use you as the bludgeon.
You're going to be the bat that I'm going to use to like like smack this guy
and be like, oh, look, this artist you look up to is disappointed in you.
It's like, I don't know.
I feel like you should like that person's consent to be in like a drama video.
If they don't want to be in a fucking drama video.
Yeah, even if like even if the criticism is extremely fucking valid.
I don't like I feel it's a good thing to do.
I mean, I mean, yeah, if teleperte wanted to make a comment on that, then like cool.
But if he like didn't want to end up like extracted it from him for for use
in his content, then that seems weird and bad.
Teleperte seems very.
Non confrontational, I guess.
So he seems like he's quiet.
I don't know.
He's just a quiet like I just want to draw.
Right.
I just want to draw and chill.
OK. I know.
I know on two occasions, Daph Pina has tried has talked to two different
friends who are who of his who are black and to ask them, can you like voice over
this line where like it's a criticism on a white person about like them being like
racist because Daph didn't want to do it.
And he's all thinking like, oh, if I get a black person to voice it, you know,
it sounds more like, you know, oh, this is a big no, no.
And the both he's trying to make the race war real.
And and like and like both both black people that I'm aware of said no.
But he did.
I think he did found like one black person who said yes to like doing a scab.
Scab.
I'm I found OK.
I found this like Reddit post that is on the rebel taxi Reddit.
And it's I read it.
I reread it.
And like, there's some fuck shit that I forgot about where like there was an
opportunity, there was like an opportunity where Pan could have told Izzy and Jim
what was going to happen.
But he just stayed silent.
So OK, I'm it's just I can't I can't believe it.
Like is is is it is am I right in that?
Like Daph just said, hey, let me take care of the podcast.
And Pan was like, OK, and then nothing else was said.
And then the announcement comes out that's like, there's a new cast.
OK, so that's how Jim and Izzy find out.
Like, that's insane.
So so there was a there was a voice call like because Izzy was
hand said to Izzy that, oh, you could be in charge of the podcast
at Momo Con of last year after they did their panel.
And then Izzy was like getting ready for that.
And then suddenly she's getting like DMs and like that Pina is like
a voice calling her and giving her all these suggestions for the podcast.
And she's like, what the fuck are you doing?
Like, why are you telling me all this?
And he and like Izzy was, I think, and then after that, they
weren't another voice call with Jim and a bunch of close friends.
And Izzy was trying to clarify with Jim and Pan.
Like, do you want like the podcast to be something where like we're trying
to make money or do you just want to just be a friend thing?
Because up until that point, the whole time, the the Pizza Party
podcast has just been a friend thing.
It's just something that like an outlet for them to talk, right?
Right. And Jim said they wanted Jim wanted to be a friend thing.
And Pan never really gave an answer to like what he wanted, apparently.
Right. And so then, like, meanwhile, like Izzy is keeps getting
like DMs from Pan from Daft Pina and she's not replying to them
because she's like, who the fuck are you, dude? Fuck off.
Like, I don't know why you keep DMing me, right?
And then like, and then Jim.
I think, OK, I'm looking at it right now.
And I turned out he couldn't swim.
Yeah. So I think I think Jim then texts Izzy and he's like,
did you know about the podcast reboot?
And like, they both found out due to, like, the tweet
and they had they both had no fucking idea.
So the long and short of it is that Daft just pretty much booted them
with without telling them.
Ultimately, I guess I think what happened was that if I like, I don't know.
I mean, I guess like to give Pan like a modicum of credit.
What I assume happened is that he was probably approached by Daft
to run the podcast. He he said yes.
And I think maybe that maybe I have no idea for this for me.
But maybe Daft brought up the suggestion that, oh, I'll tell Izzy about it.
Like, I'll be the one to break the news to Izzy.
And Pan was like, all right, dude, yeah, yeah.
And this is the whole time.
The whole time, like, Daft is trying to send messages to Izzy
and she has like no idea why, because no one told her that he'd be newly in charge.
And then like out of out of nowhere, they were dropped.
Without fucking realizing this is so stupid.
This is so stupid. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, but I'm not willing to give Pan any credit.
Like, what the fuck is wrong with everyone in this?
Like, I'm sorry, if you're if you're if you're pan in the situation
and you have any fucking fucking integrity or a fucking cell in your fucking brain,
you hear about this and you go, oh, what the fuck?
Why did you do that? Well, Daft, get out.
You know, you you.
Yeah, I told you you could take over the podcast,
but I didn't think you were going to kick the host.
Obviously, you can't do that. Leave.
Undo undo everything that has been done.
It's my podcast and I and I'm like, like, oops, made a mistake.
Let's let's hit the reset button on it.
I don't know, unless he didn't want to do the podcast anymore, for some reason.
Like, why does any of this mean that I have ownership?
Yeah, I won't do the labor, but I will make the decision.
I think sure pan ironically is like, hold on.
Like I was I was thinking about it over.
And I was looking back to all the times
I was thinking back to all the times
Pan said he doesn't care about this podcast.
And at the time I was thinking, oh, that's why he's so nonchalant
about the podcast, because he doesn't care.
But maybe what he actually meant was I really don't care at all about the pot.
Like, yeah, podcasts like this.
He actually does not.
Does he actually just not care and not give a fucking out?
Want to do it?
I it's the thing is that if so, then I guess I don't do it.
I mean, he just he just does it ultimately.
And and then the thing is that like the thing that I don't know.
I think that like, I think that got a bunch of shit, too,
because everyone everyone figured out easily about the whole just stop video
and how like, oh, obviously, that is fucking pulling the strings here, right?
And then just stop clarified.
And then like Veronica drops her version of the video and she's all like, oh, yeah,
that is like the cynical little asshole who's like always trying to manipulate shit.
Right.
And just like all these things like dumped on the same week for Daph.
And Daph was getting so much bad press press.
If you look at the last Twitter post that Daph made, where he talks about
because his recent video was he did like he did a video about the A.I.
Seinfeld thing. Yeah.
And the majority of people in the comments are replying with.
They were playing with that one picture of Quagmire and Brian having dinner.
And they're all like, they're all like spamming that image to Daph
because in Veronica's video, she she sent that image to Daph to make fun of him
because she was trying to say, oh, you're Brian in this picture.
Yes. And and and Daph got really mad about that.
So everyone's just spamming that to him. Right.
You are the soy jack. You are the Brian.
And and ultimately.
I'm looking here at the end of like Izzy's whole post about.
About Pan. I mean, I mean, some.
Pan Pan owns the whole operation.
All Pan would have to do is just say.
We'll just keep doing it.
We like never mind.
We'll just keep doing the pizza party podcast as before.
There's literally nothing stopping him from just doing that.
I think so. I guess he just doesn't want to, which is fine.
I guess.
Yeah, I'm going to call this now.
I'm going to call this now.
They're going to reboot the podcast again because I'm looking at
like people talking about the new lineup and everyone says that.
Oh, this Dumsville guy who's like mango, who's like Pan's boyfriend friend.
This guy called Dumsville.
He apparently has like a pretty bad history.
So he like he's probably going to get in some drama or some shit or someone else.
No, it's just so like.
Well, it was I don't know. It's so funny.
Like they said, OK, the podcast is rebooted with a new cast.
And then, OK, no, never mind.
The new the rebooted podcast is now we're rebooting it again.
But now with my boyfriend.
Oh, never mind.
No, OK, that's not the pizza.
That's actually a new podcast with a different name,
but it's still with the new cast with my boyfriend.
OK, now that's canceled.
And now we're going to we're going to go back.
I don't know. Do you think they're just going to go back?
What I want to know is where's the podcast?
Wait, in all of this, in all of this, the question nobody's answering.
Where's the fucking podcast?
It keeps moving.
It's finally happening. If finally we lost it, we lost it for good.
There's no I mean, I'll say, I'll say this,
the podcast is probably going to keep existing as long as like and and like
Manga are dating, OK?
But that's not that's not the pizza party podcast.
That's the P3. That's a PPP.
It's the P3.
It's the P3 podcast.
It's a nightmare.
It's a fucking nightmare.
The podcast is harder to find and more elusive than ever.
I'll I'll say this.
I'm kind of.
Um, oh, the podcast melted
into my pillow and all the gathered
I'm not really saying I'm not really looking forward
to this new podcast if you couldn't tell.
But that being said, like the thing is that because like, look,
I'm like very neutral with everybody on this.
OK, even even someone like even like Mango, I think I think they're they're right.
They're like they're whatever.
They they seem chill again.
I've talked to them in the DMs.
They seem chill enough.
That being said, I have listened to Mango Mango talk on like on like Twitter
spaces and he mostly just talks about all the all all the sex that he's having
with Pan. That's funny.
I mean, whenever I whenever I briefly followed Mango unfollowed him
because he was annoying, like most of his posts are just about how he's
Pan's boyfriend and I just find that insufferable.
That's I'm pretty sure that's what it's going to he's going to be like
on this podcast, which is like, oh, God, I'm not I look forward to this.
Awesome. That I'm going to keep commenting, though.
No, Jim, no, watch on the new episodes, because I still think that's super funny.
And I need it. I seriously needed to catch on.
I you know what? You know what?
Maybe I'll maybe I'll stop by and maybe I'll drop it.
No, Jim, no, Izzy, no, watch.
No, Jim, no, Izzy, no, Ken, no, no, no, no, watch, no, no, no, watch.
Yeah. No, darling, bring it back.
He's he's he's he's now a little bit less controversial than daffy.
No, bring it back. Free our boy.
Oh, God, it's it's epic.
It's it's great.
You know, it's all all my podcasts are changing before my eyes, you know, it's funny.
Oh, you know what?
Gibb, I was trying to build a website.
I was trying to build I was I was building a little website on my computer.
There's not much to it.
It's pretty much just like a page with like a list of links
to like download the episodes.
Oh, yeah, the MP3 use.
Yeah, yeah, I don't know.
I'm kind of just envisioning that like the PCP website will just be like a landing page
with just like two columns.
And on the left is all the PCP episode MP3s listed in like reverse chronological order.
And if you want to listen to the latest one, you just click the top one and it downloads
and on the right side is, you know, the the to soon to be filled
list of a perfect, perfect comic parties, PDFs, and you download them
and like not much else to it, really.
I think that's kind of my vision for the the the the PCP website.
Just simple hub, just a simple hub for our content.
Yeah, imagine that.
Anyway, simple and clean, simple and clean and gay.
And the way the way it should be tonight.
That song. I'm hard. Yes.
You know, it's I've always found it so I've always found it so weird
that that song is about like it's about like, yeah, it's about like red flags
in a relationship and like hesitancy to commit and like uncertainty
in a game that's like thematically just about like love and friendship are good.
And we love love and friendship so much.
Isn't that weird?
It is weird. I think it is.
I always thought that like the lyrics of that song, like I love the tune of it.
I love the song, but the lyrics of it are like
weirdly like mature and like morally gray and ambiguous
compared to the content of the game.
It's OK. It's a Japanese game.
And I kids, kids don't listen to lyrics.
Ever. That's that's true.
When I was in when I was in elementary school,
the two most popular songs were about like jizzing,
like just coming on on women.
What are you fucking talking about?
What the fuck are you talking about?
Wait, you don't know.
You don't know little fuck.
You don't know little John.
Ah, ski, ski, ski, ski, ski, ski, ski. Oh, wait.
And oh, wait, no, that's true.
You're absolutely right.
And then and then the other one. My balls.
That one, the other the other classic one
was a daddy Yankees, a gasolina,
which was about like a woman who loves it when you come a lot on her.
I don't even know that one.
Oh, that's a little bit.
That's a little bit too.
That's a little bit too ethnic for you. Honkies, huh?
I would say, yeah.
Yeah, that's right. Yeah.
That's what I was going to say.
You got caught. I don't like he's too black sounding for me.
I don't like singers.
You got you got got copy and white again.
Because of 4K on 4K.
Oops, got him.
Ben saying copy and white again.
Don't you like don't you like that part in American Psycho
where Patrick Bateman is racist?
It was pretty good.
I want to get a T-shirt of Pat.
I might just make this T-shirt myself and sell it.
Where and because I feel like this would be a really good T-shirt to wear
nowadays because the Jewish community needs it.
But it's that's the quote.
Why is I like, well, well, cool, cool with the anti-semitic remarks.
Just on a show with the anti-semitic remarks.
OK, and it'll be a picture of Christian Bale.
I don't have a yarmulke like, oh, cool with the anti-semitic remarks.
Yeah. Only he should be only he should be a goblin.
He plays a goblin.
I heard that.
Because in the original obligatory Patrick and Naidman,
but I heard that in the fucking new Hogwarts,
I almost called the new J.K. Rowling Patrick,
Patrick Bateman would have would have Ray Patrick Bateman would have raided my stream.
He would have.
I heard in the new Harry Potter game,
there's even more like Jewish comparisons to the bad guys are goblins.
They're there a while ago.
It's a goblin rebellion.
OK, OK, there's a goblin rebellion.
And I know that there's that horn that is supposedly similar to like a Jewish horn.
That is described in the game as just being like annoying.
They have horns.
Have you been watching much more at Ben?
No, no, no, no.
Like a musical horn like oblivion.
You don't watch curvy enthusiasm.
There's a whole episode where Larry David is giving the Jewish horn
that calls all the Jews when he sounds it.
Is the real that's a real episode.
That's a real. OK, OK,
for I from what I've heard,
I know that like the center of the of the plot is yes,
it's about like the goblins have a rebellion.
But I've also heard that there's sort of a twist at the end.
And like, it turns out the goblins were framed,
like the goblins are actually not bad.
They're being like framed or manipulated into doing something, whatever they're doing.
Also, OK, that star.
I know the reason that's there is because this scene was just filmed
in like a real building and that's just what the floor of the building that they I know.
It was a real bank. It was a real bank.
So you're saying it's real.
You are J.Q.ing right now, Ben, by saying what?
No, what? No.
Got it. Listen, I'm just listen.
I'm just trying to I'm just defending J.K. Rowling.
OK, I'm just saying I'm just saying she's good, actually.
I'm just saying I listen.
I might like a lot of important things to say about women.
Obviously, they just picked a bank and probably didn't even think about it.
And that's how I got in there.
And it's just really they probably probably no one was even thinking
about the whole, you know, of a drawing of I mean, it's enough.
I don't think it's it's honestly enough that like the bankers of the wizarding world
are the goblins described as they are in the book.
It's like the comparisons, the sort of like.
I could. Yeah, you know, you know, what this is.
Yeah, did you have to read it like this way?
You know what I think this is?
OK, it's what what you were saying at the cheesy.
You were saying about how was it Grant Morrison?
Alan Moore is Alan Alan Moore.
Like even he, despite being like against, you know, he sort of falls into the.
Yeah, he sort of falls into the tropes.
I don't know. I think that's what that's what this goblin thing is.
It's like, yeah, the goblins do look like an anti-semitic stereotype.
And it's not like anyone set out deliberately to make them that way.
It's just like our cultural conception of a greedy part of a greedy banker.
Is like so inextricably tied to that that image.
You know, that kind of came out that. Yeah.
That kind of reminds me of, you know, the game,
Peaks the Tower that came out, by the way, great game.
There was a character. I know what you're going to say.
I saw I saw the I saw the picture.
There was a character called Mr.
Pinch and people were saying this is like anti-semitic caricature.
And it's you know, it's so annoying when like people hear that and they say,
like, oh, actually, you're anti-semitic because you say it looks like a Jew.
And it's like, no, we're not saying it looks like a fucking Jew.
We're saying it looks like a Jewish stereotype idiot.
There's those are two different things.
That being said, someone said, like, Mr. Pinch.
Yeah, I'm going to find an image of Mr. Pinch posting right now.
But anyway, everyone was everyone was saying
he's actually based on Ebenezer Scrooge from the Christmas Carol, right?
I looked up the name Ebenezer.
It's a Jewish name.
So that makes me think like God.
And like Carousel's Carol is like, even even chickens.
Yeah, even chickens couldn't.
Yeah, because it's like there's all these like subtle things that like we
like people are saying, oh, it's OK.
It's not anti-semitic is based on Ebenezer Scrooge.
And it's like, well, Ebenezer Scrooge himself is anti-semitic.
It kind of a character, right?
You can't cancel Dickens.
I mean, think about it.
He's a rich guy who doesn't celebrate Christmas.
Oh, gee, whiz. I wonder who it was. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. He was there.
He was there at Golgotha, it's nailing our savior to the cross.
It was him. It's all these subtle things.
It's just so yeah, it's just in serious.
You got to question everything, you know, like.
I like my main question is not like in like in like the like the fucking
early 2000s or late 90s or whatever, when they filmed the first Harry Potter
movie, were they like intentionally doing that?
You know, I think it is like you said, like they just they just went with the
tropes and didn't think about it.
What it what confuses me is that after all the discourse in current year
where people are thinking about this shit and people are like aware of this shit,
why would they then in the new game that just came out, give the goblins
a musical instrument that looks like a traditional, you know, Jewish thing?
That's the that's the spicy question that I'm wondering.
Don't I don't know.
It's like you could say, I mean, it is true that it's like it's
culturally like passed down unconscious biases that we just don't really think
about J.K. Rowling had that when she designed the goblins the way they did.
But it's also like, oh, and she just turned out to be a massive bigot as well.
In a different way, it's right now.
Right, you know, I like to believe
because she was neoliberal the whole time.
That's why, you know, the huge Neolib.
Like, I, you know, even like I want to fucking even like I'll say it even
like in villain verse, I have like very kind of unconscious things like the main
character is this goblin guy and he's like the source of all evil, right?
And it's like, damn, like what?
Like, because the thing is, I love is the villain Jewish.
The villain isn't Jewish, but he's like part of the original first
like people that showed up on his planet and, you know, that could go back to like,
oh, well, Jews are kind of like the oldest religion almost.
Oh, yeah, I've I've I've seen I've seen the history of history of Earth,
spirit science and I know about the Hebrews coming from Mars or whatever.
And the thing is that he's like a goblin guy who loves gold.
And it's like, oh, my God.
It's the thing is like, I love the villain as a character and I love
and I love the Jewish people.
Me, me, I, you won't find a bigger, you won't get there.
And I love Sigma and I love X.
And I love you won't find a bigger, a bigger
a Hebrew like myself out there.
I'm saying that right now.
I'm a huge ally, you know, I like, look,
if it was up to me, I would have converted to Judaism.
But, you know, they won't allow it.
They won't let me.
They said, I'm not funny enough.
You won't give them your foreskin.
They said I'm banned from temple after the incident.
They said I'm not funny enough to be Jewish.
So, you know what? And they know better.
You know, they've been around here the longest.
They know better.
That being said, I I am going to rethink a lot of different things.
Because I feel like I feel like there's like enough in Villainverse where it's
like, OK, it's it's it's not I'm not trying to be anti-Semitic.
I just love goblins. I just oh, I love goblins.
Yeah, I love goblins.
I love little green characters.
I think I think, I don't know.
Some some people say that, like, goblins are always anti-Semitic,
no matter what. And like, I think that that can't possibly be true.
I think there's definitely versions of goblins that are OK.
And there's a lineage, but that doesn't necessarily mean
that every depiction is with that intent.
I'm going to I'm going to I'm going to it's just a cultural thing now.
It's it's like a little creature.
Those goblins I see now are just short green woman with huge tits.
And this is how this is how I'm going to redeem the villain is how I'm going to redeem him.
He is going in a future chapter.
And this is this is not a joke.
This is 100 percent not ironic in a future chapter.
I am going to make him mention that he has a foreskin.
Boom. Problem solved.
Like a boy eating pork or something.
And maybe that's how we defeat him.
They tug on his foreskin and he screams, no spoilers, spoilers, spoilers.
Have him have him eat pork.
Just just every whenever you can just have him do something that's not kosher.
Yeah, exactly. I'll have him do so much like anti kosher stuff.
And you know what? Let's be honest.
Like a real Jew wouldn't create this massive
galactic operation that the villain would have.
Come on, that's a little too much work. Come on.
Was he didn't he fuck like a giant bug?
Yeah, he did. Planet.
Does that kosher?
Is that maybe we are.
Is that Haram?
If I'm going to go, I should, I should go back in time
and redraw that image where we see the villains.
You should have a free Palestine sticker.
Yeah, exactly.
It'll be like, finally, I've collected all the villain balls.
And I'm like, yeah, free Palestine.
Just just make him like he's like he's the he's the most.
OK, he's the most evil creature in the world.
But even he there's he's not even he can be completely evil.
He does support Palestinian liberation.
It's the one thing that he's good about.
And it proves that he's not Jewish also.
And you can be Jewish and hate Israel.
There are two different things.
I don't understand what you're talking about.
We're just we're just trying to do as many anti stereotypes as possible.
That's all we're just. Yeah, we're just trying to be as we're just we're just
trying to be as not Jewish.
We're just trying to be as anti Semitic as possible here,
because we're not every look.
Everything I do, I do it.
I do it for the Jew.
All right, everything I do, I do it for the.
And that's that's not being ironic.
What if no, what if he what if he is circumcised
and he but he just he kept the foreskin and he keeps it like in like a case
and like he has a guy who like goes to the case
and like cleans it off or like display.
He has the most foreskin.
You have you have to you have you have to show it.
You have to show it so that we can see that.
Yes, it is still attached.
It's the only way.
It's the only way I'll figure out a way.
Oh, no, I'll figure out attached.
It would have to still be honest.
You know, speaking of like like little goofy characters.
You know, I'm going to give a pretty brief hot take here.
And this is going to get me like this is going to get me canceled.
We haven't yet.
We haven't we haven't gone far enough on this episode.
I like I really like I think this design is really cute.
But I know.
But I know it's terrible.
It's a terrible design that we should not keep reusing.
And OK, do you guys know what a golly walk is?
You guys know what a golly walk is?
Golly.
Yes, I know what a golly walk is.
Yeah, it's the dragon quest slime face, but with black face as well.
Yeah, exactly. It's I hate how cute this is, but I know it's terrible.
And we shouldn't do this at all.
That being said, I see what you mean.
I see what you mean.
I mean, yeah, it is for it is friendly looking.
It is very friendly looking.
It's it's not that that same like the eyes of a black cat sort of sort of face.
It's like there's there's like ways to kind of like redeem this.
It's just don't do the like I feel like once you do the oblivion.
Yeah, I'm kind of with you oblivion.
I've had it. I've had it.
Only when she only when cheesy Manfredo is here,
does imagery like this appear on the PCP.
Yeah, in the chat now.
I'm not.
I'm.
Explain yourself, putting me.
You're putting me on a list, cheesy.
There's this whole there's this whole bit in in Alan Moore's book,
League of Externary Gentlemen, where like, because everything,
every like piece of fiction is canon, one of these guys shows up,
a gollywag shows up, and he's like on the good guy's team.
He's like a good person.
And at the whole time, I'm thinking like, this is bad.
But I mean, at least he's like a good guy, right?
But then like later in the book, it talks about the lore of the gollywags.
And they're like, oh, there are a race of aliens that were enslaved.
And I'm like, OK, all right, buddy, all right, Mr.
Buddy, look at these these non-humans.
Oh, God, I hate that so much.
Fucking like League of Externary Gentlemen is kind of like for every
like for every like one step of a progressive direction, it takes like two steps back.
Right. Like, oh, he's shining a light on care.
Oh, there's a trans character.
He's shining a light on like characters that wouldn't have spotlights
in the books that they're in.
Oh, he's like reevaluating like British neoliberalism.
Oh, it's a commentary on fascism.
Oh, all this stuff, all this stuff about culture is worth keeping.
It's great. It's awesome. It's base.
But then he doesn't really question that maybe some of the imagery we have
of like older like pop culture isn't really worth keeping because it's kind of like.
Like it kind of like stamp.
It kind of like pushes a very like races or bad narrative
because there's like certain kind of like characters that pop up in the book
because it's like, oh, it's all pieces of fiction.
And it's like, oh, yeah.
And then he has like Fu Manchu as one of the bad guys in the first book.
And it's like, oh, boy.
And yeah, it's a lot of it's a good book, but it's oh, boy.
Speaking, speaking of being base and progressive,
I went to a I went to a protest march rally this week.
Actually, actually, Munchy invited me to come with him.
He alerted me this was going on.
There was a shooting.
There was a police, a quote unquote police involved shooting.
If you know what I mean, a student at UMass
who was cutting himself with a knife.
So like and like cops showed up and he like fled from them
and they pursued him and like cornered him and they say that he lunged at them.
But they who knows if that's true, but they did shoot him and he died.
So it's just assisted dying, you know, it's actually progressive.
If you think they were giving him a hand, they could see he was trying to do
something like, hey, hey, hey, buddy, hey, buddy.
Nina, Nina, help, need a little help.
Cops are terrible and much stronger than cops are terrible at helping you
in any way, except for killing yourself.
They're like, good at that's like the only good at it's like, it's like, OK,
I don't know. I just kind of think that, you know, yes, this guy was having a crisis
and he was cutting himself and he had a knife.
And I kind of think that probably it was likely that nobody would have died
if some dudes with guns hadn't like pulled up in a squad car and been like,
freeze, motherfucker, you get the fuck over here.
You know, I feel like that probably exacerbated the situation.
And maybe he would not have perished if not for it.
But we but we'll never know.
So we will never know it's impossible to know it is impossible.
No, we can only speculate.
So we did we did a little march and we yelled we got the, you know,
that's that's what went up in front of the police station, held up a big
portrait of him and said, pop cops, we're not fond of you.
We did it.
You said we said, hey, on why we wish you would research.
We wish you would reconsider your methods.
And then we left.
And that was it. There was.
I just reminded myself, there is this.
Weird YouTuber.
I don't remember his name.
He does like very dry videos, like responding to conservatives on issues
like gay marriage where like there's some guy would be like, well,
a God said this thing and I'm not anti gay.
I'm just anti being gay, you know, some right.
Yeah, yeah, of course, slimy, weasley little argument like that.
And he'll be like, I'm actually and he'll he'll respond with like pretty good points.
But like, you don't know the video, you don't have the name of this dude.
I could find it.
I it's his name's like free letters or something.
OK, it's very dry.
Like the videos are very like like low effort.
They're not like particularly smart or like engaging.
OK, it's just like background noise.
But one of the videos talking about gay stuff,
every time he mentioned gay marriage, you'd also or like or like, you know,
gay rights, he would say gay rights and euthanasia or assisted dying
or I forget the term he used because I don't know that.
Apparently, apparently there's a politically character.
Oh, is it or is it the Canadian thing made of medical assistance in dying?
Is that it? I don't know.
I don't know. But like the video was about gay rights
and the guy who's responding to is about gay rights.
Like, see, this is why I don't like it when you say this thing
about gay rights and assisted suicide.
And he would always like add and assisted suicide
every single time he mentioned gay rights and it was weird.
I'm like, what does this video have to do with that?
And also also, why aren't you mentioning the issues
with assisted suicide being a thing under capitalism
where people would be pressured into any of their lives over their
like medical bills and other shit in recent like months?
I've seen I've seen it talked about that, like, I guess there was a thing
in Canada was doing, yeah, like, like the Canadian government was giving,
like, yeah, assistance, suicide assistance to people.
And like some people were saying they were like pressuring people,
like poor people into committing suicide.
That was the story I was I was seeing.
I don't I haven't really looked into it.
But that's just the word on the street and the grapevine.
That's what I mean.
I mean, I have to take these memories of a grain of salt
because it is my parents who are very conservative.
But like when my dad like spoke out against what would like
because me and my dad used to drive me places and we'd just talk about
philosophy and ethics and other stuff.
And he was a pretty smart guy on most things.
Like the stuff he would always mention is like, yeah, like the issue
with it is that like usually when it's being implemented in countries,
like they they'll have like all these safeguards and stuff to make to try
and prevent, you know, people who are poor or people who are just like,
you know, who are suffering because of like, you know, like poverty
or like because of like medical bills or everything, like they'll try
and not have doctors sell you that as the cheaper alternative to getting
like, you know, cured and how that at least according to him,
how that usually doesn't work and it usually gets out of hand.
Like like in fury, like it's a good thing, but like in practice,
it doesn't usually work out.
And you're talking about it was the suicide.
Yes, it's a suicide.
So I at the time I figured, oh, well, it's just universally bad.
And I realized, oh, well, most of the problems with it are probably due to capitalism.
Yeah, but like, you know, like I wouldn't want that in America
right now where if someone's like, oh, do you want $50,000 of medical debt
or you can just kill yourself?
Like I wouldn't want to, I would want to, you know, between the two issues
to solve there, I'd rather solve the debt problem than just to be like,
ah, nah, nah, nah, bro.
Just just like, yeah, but I don't know.
I thought it was weird that this video just kept mentioning that
in conjunction with gay rights.
So this is this is the guy who was supposedly he like someone else
was being like anti gay.
And this was a guy who was trying to be like pro gay,
but he kept like mentioning the suicide of the why.
Yeah, why?
I don't I don't get it was just out of what I feel like subliminal messages.
What's that?
I'm like, it's really important that gay people are allowed to be gay
and also kill themselves and also you're allowed to kill yourself.
And they can also kill themselves.
Them specifically for gay people to be able to do that and and serve.
I want I just I love gay people and that's why I want them to be able
to serve in the military and kill themselves.
And that's it, nothing else.
I want those two rights for them and no others, please.
Amazing.
Well, yeah, very mysterious, very baffling.
What's was that kind of one video that kind of someone uploaded
at the start of like the BLM protests like two years ago
where this guy was like screaming and yelling and he seemed to be pro BLM.
But he's unironically said like, yeah, yeah, like, you know, all,
you know, like, you know, Black Lives do matter, you know, like it doesn't
matter what race you are.
We all could like be a stupid N word with a hard R and people were like,
whoa, whoa, what the fuck?
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
You thought he was being you thought he was cool, but then he fooled you.
Well, he has he has the right energy.
His language just isn't it gives it appropriate, buddy.
Sure.
You like you like black people, but that's very nice.
Oh, oh, hot dog.
Oh, all right.
I'm going to get canceled and like I have not seen.
I've not seen the video in question.
I don't think I'm going to get him.
Daphne is going to mention this podcast in the cheesy takedown video.
Well, he fucking better.
He's going to be like, oh, yeah.
Yeah, we need the views.
If Daphne. Yeah.
Yeah, like, please, please, please cancel us, Daphne, please.
If he if he wanted to cancel you,
he would probably say Cheesy Manfredo is
evil because he made a comic that says that famous people on Twitter are bad.
And I'm a famous person on Twitter and I'm a big Twitter artist.
And he was a jerk and he said rich people are bad
and people with lots of followers are bad and that offended me.
And that would be his main complaint about you, I think.
That's epic in my in my opinion.
He Cheesy said the Galway was pretty cute.
But I said it was cute.
He said it was cute.
Pretty kawaii. It's but it's racist.
So is Cheesy racism?
Is Cheesy saying that racism is cute?
I don't think so.
And then he's going to get like I, Daphne, and actually against racism.
You're going to get like a black content creator,
a black content creator to read like a quote against me.
He's going to get like Barrett Barrettist Joe or something.
He's going to he's going to he's going to he's going to message me
on Discord to be like, Hey, Ben, can I talk to you real quick?
Can I record you? OK, cool.
Hey, what do you think about Cheesy and all say, Oh, Cheesy?
Yeah, I gave that guy.
I gave that guy 800 bucks to have that comic made and he still hasn't made it.
And he'll say, OK, great, got it.
Oh, oh, oh, she's so scam artist.
She's she's a thief.
She's a demon. She's a she's a monster.
Oh, God. Yeah.
No, it's not my fault. It's social media. It's been destroying my mind.
And the only the only cure is if I get if I get a hundred K followers,
that's the only cure that will fix it. I swear.
There's a hundred. I'll be good.
The saddest thing that I have had to witness recently is
that guy on Twitter, the guy, the autistic guy who is obsessed with
yours six girlfriends being blue Simpsons ninjas.
No, sexy and for free.
You know what I'm talking about? Ben Hughes. Ben Hughes.
He has lately he keeps posting about like how upset he is that he fell under 10,000 followers.
Like he's really bothered about it.
And he keeps posting like, help me.
I'm under like, please get me over 10 and I'm like, ah,
I just hate seeing it every single time.
You should every painful each one of those posts where you saw like,
come on, guys, let's get this guy up back.
Let's get him back to 10 K guys.
What's this? What's his handle?
It's been Ben Hughes something.
Oh, I found it recently.
So sending Ben Hughes to one of my other.
How do you spell Hughes?
H-U-G-H-E-S.
All the bends on Twitter.
Oh, yes. We can't trust them.
I think maybe maybe it's not maybe it's just S.
Huggies. Yeah.
Here, here, I found him.
Oh, I don't follow him.
I'm doing my part.
I followed you. There we go.
Ben Hugg 264-22354.
Yeah, buddy, you already got you already got nine K.
Dude, you're good.
He was over 10 K for a while.
And then I guess, you know,
bot accounts being deleted or whatever.
Well, yeah, he's only at like nine nine nine point eight now.
And he hates it.
Well, well, he's so close.
Well, Ben Hughes, just fucking.
How about you just update your fucking content
as you're posting the same joke over and over again?
You're so epic and cool, dude.
This guy, he's barely getting like 50.
He's getting like under 50 likes on all this guy is epic and cool.
And yes, I love that he posted the same joke over and over again.
And it's not a joke.
It's not a joke.
It's a sincere appreciation of yours.
Six wives, if he's so epic.
Why does he have 10 K?
Yeah, it's true.
As I thought, I don't know.
I don't know why Ben Hughes says,
I'll keep focusing on the Simpsons females E.R.
and all the prehistoric animals.
So he's staying the course.
He's not changing up his content to fit the the album.
Fucking Raven follows him.
Damn, Revin, we're going to follow me back.
I saw Raven.
Yeah, Raven did some ninja fan art.
Right.
We're going to follow me back.
I literally agree with everything you say.
I love your comics.
Was it something I said?
Big Twitter artist.
She was offended.
They they she's she's a big they.
Yeah, they they go by day them.
They are they were offended.
But because they're big and they're bigger than you.
It's going to change.
You can't go saying that.
It's going to change once Mimi already drops extra souls.
Raven's going to be like, oh, written by cheese.
Manfredo will give.
Oh, give follow.
Oh, executive produced by Ben St.
Does it mean wait?
Wait, they follow you already, don't they?
I think they did.
And then they like purge their their follows.
And I don't think they follow me anymore.
Oh, oh, no.
Yeah.
That was like a while ago.
Well, look at bummer.
Let's see who follows Ben.
Well, Juniper follows you.
Juniper does follow me.
I'm not exactly sure why, but I appreciate it.
Wait, which which Juniper?
The one that invented the worm.
Yeah, the goblin mode.
Yeah.
What?
Do you DM Juniper and be like, yo, this cheesy Manfredo guy, pretty base.
The person who literally invented, well, popularized the term goblin mode.
Juniper is like the final boss of Twitter.
I was like the ultimate poster.
The only Juniper I know is the Moffy Tuber, who has a cool Eldritch Moff character.
If you don't know Juniper, then I'm sorry, but you just don't have it in your NGMI.
The majority of the people, the majority of the people that follow you.
Juniper is one of those weird names.
It's probably a tree.
I think it is.
Oh, I just got reminded looking at your follower account.
A Stereo's Coconut is going to have me on on his live stream in March.
I was on a Stereo's live stream.
I saw Stereo's Coconut.
You did a good job.
I educated him on the history of that guy with the glasses.
A Stereo's.
Like, so back in, I think back in November, I gave him a Stereo's and I tell him,
hey, a Stereo's, do you know about the Blueie fandom?
Like the adult Blueie fandom that's growing.
And he's all like, no, so good.
I said, no, tell me.
You tell me.
He's like, no, tell me more.
Well, I basically explained to I gave like a brief summary of what the Blueie adult
fandom is like, because I like Blueie.
Yeah, but but my partner is a massive, massive Blueie head.
Actually, they were like on the ground floor when the when the fandom first started
like two years ago.
Jesus.
Yeah, two years ago.
It started.
So I've been witnessing firsthand like the Blueie phenomenon like right here
in my bedroom.
That's sickening.
I hate it.
No, no, look, look, look, it's fine.
It's not fine.
It's Ben.
Ben can't imagine Ben.
Can imagine imagine being into a show for little kids like imagine.
Imagine like I'm sorry, an adult.
I'm sorry, a fandom, a group of people that come together around shared
appreciation for a cartoon for children.
What is society?
What is happening to society?
You know, back in my day, this wouldn't have happened back in my day.
You know what we would do if we found out that someone was into a little kid show?
Mm hmm.
Oh, yeah, we draft them.
We would send them to Nam.
We tie him, tie him, tie him to the back of a car and we just and we just go to
town, just hit the gas.
Australians, a loving family.
I could never support such a thing as Ben.
So I sent that to a stereo's back in November.
The stereo's did not reply into two months later.
Oh, and out of out of nowhere, he replies and says, hello.
Yeah, I'm going to read for all this now.
Oh, wow, this sounds great.
You want to come on my live stream?
Let's talk about it.
And I'm like, yeah, sure.
I'm down.
And then, um, yeah, so we set a date.
It's going to be like in March.
Um, he added me about when the date is going to be.
Um, I know everyone's going to forget the date because this is like in fucking March.
Most most PCP fans forget everything they heard once they're done with an episode.
Mm hmm.
Yeah, real dummies.
Those guys, real, real, real little funny fellas.
Okay.
March 26, March 26, like at seven p.m.
East coast time, I think.
All right.
Well, reminding.
Yeah, I won't remember.
He says live stream with the clown fucking guy.
That's me in case the clown fucking guy.
Yeah, that's about right.
After after McPuglatchy, um, I'm going to double down on that that like monster.
You're going to be double that.
Yeah, double down to clown.
Double down to clown.
I actually have, I actually had a genius idea for another clown porn comic.
And oh my God.
Now, is that going to be clown milk too?
I still have to, there's still a couple of things in the background.
I have to fix up.
There's a couple of lives.
I, there's a couple of friendships and lives that have to rebuild in the background.
You have to ruin to get to get that back to get that ship running again.
I had an idea for a clown porn that would have just been a solo comic.
Um, then I could make a joke about being like, I only make two types of clown
found comics like serious comics and porn.
That's the two genres of clowns for me.
Um, that's going to be out.
I don't fucking know when, but I am going to double down on the monster manual.
Did I tell you about that?
But the, the monster, the gimmick was like, oh, this is a monster.
The monster manual for a video game that doesn't exist.
Like, oh, yeah, you might have mentioned that before.
Yeah.
Like, like we were going to, we're going to be like, yo, we, uh, we built a machine
that pulled out this monster manual for what would have been a Super Nintendo
game at the game.
The game doesn't exist in our reality, but we have the monster manual.
And I've been kind of like thinking about it like slowly, like, oh, maybe I
should, I, I'm going to try to do some like, uh, Super Nintendo research to see
like, what are the limits of the system to see how accurate we could get?
Like our like monster manual would be to an actual video game.
Right.
Yeah.
Interesting.
I think, I think people will, will dig, will dig that.
It seems like enough.
And I'm going to do with a, okay.
I was, I was, I was talking, talking to my friend, uh, Dwoob yesterday about
this artist called, um, Alex Dejan or Deegan.
Do you know who that is?
You ever, you ever heard of Alex Dejan?
Alex Dejan, D E G E N.
Um, he, he made a comic called, uh, soft X-ray mind hunters and he
sometimes works with, uh, the catamites, which is who is the guy who made
space funeral and he makes lots of other weird, uh, uh, indie games.
Um, but he, okay.
Soft X-ray mind hunters is like a wordless, like sci-fi, like fantasy thing
about these guys, like going through all these like weird, like dream
universes, like fine, they have to, they have to hunt down these brains
and like destroy them basically.
Oh, this looks cool.
It's really cool.
But he all, okay.
He, he does, uh, he's done a bunch of things that are, what you just said
reminds me of them.
They'll, he has another book called, uh, I think it's called the Martian War
library and the Martian War library is, it's not really a comic.
It's a book of, they're drawings of like magazine covers or like comic book
covers and there's no comic.
There's just the covers, but it's just a series of covers of what is presumably
an in-universe comic and there sort of is a story that's told like through the
progression of the covers of these comics that don't exist about this character
card Martian called Martian War.
Yeah.
And, um, that's cool.
Doob showed me another, uh, older book of his that I'd never seen before
yesterday and it was, um, it was a similar thing.
It was just illustrations of these like, it was like a team of like, uh, child
sleuth geniuses doing like solving crimes and like finding mummies and stuff.
And it was like, just like sort of a, not really like a story, just like a
series of images depicting these characters in this, in scenes.
That's, that's really cool.
Yeah, he's good.
He's soft.
I think I've probably talked about soft x-ray mind hunters at least once
before, but it's a really good comic and it's, and it's big.
It's a big book and it's quite long and wordless and the illustrations are really
nice.
Yeah, that's, um, I, I've been, um, I've been like, I just, I haven't bought it.
I only maybe bought two new comics like last year because I've been so
focused on working and also I, I got into a very expensive hobby, which is
um, action figures, but buying a lot of those, like a little, like a little
fucking man child.
But, um, it is very, I've been, um, yeah.
Man, chill, chill.
It is very man-shilderness, but like the, the, the, the star fire, the fire star
figure that I have just like activates a sexual urge inside of me so I can't,
can't help myself when I look at it, right?
Yeah, this looks really cool.
I like this a lot.
I'm reminded about like, I, I kind of have like a, um, for the monster manual
we're doing, I'm actually working on it with, uh, my buddy, uh, Kizuchu, who's
in your, oh, Kizuchu, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
He's a, he's a cool dude.
Um, I love, I love him to death.
Um, and his, his art style is like this.
This is like, this is like the first piece he made this year.
It's really good.
Let me see.
That's good.
Oh yeah.
He's a, he's a really good artist.
He, he, it's me and him.
I like the woman.
We're, we're kind of doing this thing.
It looks cool.
And, and our, and our private, we have like a private server for the monster
manual or just me and him.
And what we do is we just kind of throw designs into like a chat and then it's
like, Oh, what do you think of this?
Oh, what do you think of this?
And then we just kind of go back and forth or like it was just any idea I have.
I just throw it in there.
Like, I just come up with a name like, Oh, what about a gloopity gloop?
And then he's like, all right.
And then he just draws a design based on that name or he gives me a name and I
draw it and we go back and forth.
Um, the only problem is, and like, look, don't get me wrong.
I love Kazoo.
I've had him.
He's like my co-host on like five different podcasts.
I didn't know that.
Cause, cause you, cause you is just, oh, cause you takes like, like decades to draw
one picture.
Oh, that's a bummer.
That is his one flaw.
If he could fix this flaw, he would, he could become God.
He could become a big Twitter artist.
Um, if he, if he fixed this one, one flaw, um, but it's, it's okay.
Cause I'm going to, I'm going to whip him into shape.
Sometimes I have that same problem.
And actually it's my number one problem.
The thing is that you guys don't have like deadlines.
You don't have, I do.
Yeah.
You don't, you don't have like time limits where like, oh, if I don't do this by
now, I might become homeless or, uh, no, I have, I have, I have a deadline of if
I don't do this, I'll have wasted my life.
Uh, but the time, the timeline is pretty generous on that one.
Um, oh, Ben, have you seen your life in weeks?
No.
Oh, get ready for a dread.
Jesus.
Did you know that you spend 100% of your life being stupid?
Is that what it is?
Do you know that, you know that every second of every hour you're inhaling air that
is touching another man's cock?
Oh, did you know that?
Did you, I, I didn't.
Did you know that your body is comprised of molecules that once were farted by somebody?
Somebody farted you.
Ew, probably.
That's gross.
Yeah.
Oh, no.
Oh, God.
What's the life in weeks?
Oh, I've seen something like this before.
Each one of these is a week.
What is this?
That's how many weeks you'll live, probably.
Uh, that's, that's, that's my result with my birthday put in.
I don't, I don't.
It's my birthday next week, which is why it's right about to complete a row.
At least a little bit there is like five years.
Each line is a year.
Well, here's mine.
Are you, is the, is the non red space is that, um, like how much time you got left?
That's like, that's like expected life expectancy.
It's fucking over.
I'm good.
I'm gonna fucking, I'm gonna crank out like villain verse chapter 500 by then.
Good.
So like age zero to like 15, basically you're not real.
Yeah, I could get to like villain verse chapter.
You can change it to months too.
If you click on weeks, you can select months.
I don't know about you guys.
Uh, this doesn't, this doesn't apply to me.
It's gonna, cheesy man, Fredo library is going to be pretty big by then.
Damn big library.
I just got to, you just got to put out every, every single one of these boxes.
Put out a new chapter and, uh, damn, that's like, it's not that many.
Oh no, it's not that many.
It's not that many boxes.
There's a lot of boxes.
Not try counting them with your hand.
Not that many boxes.
You try counting each of these boxes with your hand.
You'll run out of fingers.
Oh my God.
You know, you know what I, what I like to do is seven days with multiple
millions of seconds, not millions boxes anymore.
I've had enough.
Frankly, I've had enough.
You know what, you know what I like to do?
You know what I like to do when I complete a project?
I like to, I haven't actually done this before.
This is the first time I'm doing this and this is going to give me my dread is I
will highlight how much time I spent mucking around on the last project.
Um, so, so this is, this is my life in months.
The yellow squares is how much I spent working on the animation that I just finished.
Oh, such a big chunk of my life on one loop.
Oh my, oh my God.
I don't, oh, I can, I'm thinking about it.
I'm thinking about.
Imagine these as like, like, um, like time, like a bus health bars.
Like, yeah, like, uh, like all the zelda hearts.
Hey, you got a lot of them.
Got a lot to go.
I'm looking at like time that I spent working on like slime and punishment.
That's like way too many of these boxes.
There's all the years I wasted with my bitch of a wife.
Exactly.
All the fucking years I wasted on that bitch.
More like every single one of these red boxes a year that I wasted on my bitch
of a life in my opinion.
I gave that whore the best years of my life.
Well, it's been, it's been more than a decade since my little pony
came out.
Yeah, like a, oh my God.
Yeah, like, like a quarter of these boxes are post MLP.
Scary.
Well, no, a third, more like a third.
Yeah.
Although I didn't get into it until it was several years old.
So I don't know.
Well, um, fuck it.
Oh, that's the podcast everyone buy.
No, I don't know.
I'm making it worse.
I'm making it worse for myself to moralize.
I'm not letting you know how I'm just working at Pennsylvania.
Just make stuff.
Just make stuff guys.
No, shut up.
No, I won't.
No, I won't make.
I'm making.
Oh, I don't know.
I can't make things.
So hard.
I can make things and I want to say at least like one thing in this whole
podcast because like every topic has been like, oh, I don't care about that.
I'm sure.
I'm sure our audience feels the same way.
Every topic.
Oh, I don't care about that.
Now I know how they feel.
Yeah.
But I have been productive on the Clarissa stuff and I'm sticking to my
pace.
I'm getting a I did a calculation.
I did nine pages finished.
They were already aligned.
I was doing the shading.
So this week last week.
Yeah.
Nine pages and I have 10 left for this chapter.
So maybe the end of February beginning of March chapter four of Clarissa
gun smoke will be done and then the perfect comic party issue one will be
soon after assuming that there's other stuff to put in there.
And I did a calculation.
I did a calculation based off just like my my current like slow ish pace of
like doing line art and then doing shading.
It will take me roughly for a 20 page chapter of a thing about three weeks
from doing all that stuff.
And then that's assuming that I keep the pace I was currently at and that I
don't have any major setbacks or like bad days.
So like probably like four weeks is a good estimate for how long it will
take to get a chapter done.
So I'm on and I have 10 chapters of Clarissa overall.
I'm on chapter four.
So in six months it'll be done.
That's my that's the whole thing like all 200 pages 208 pages.
Yeah.
It's a lot.
That's cool.
That is a lot.
That's I'm very bad at I'm very bad at condensing my story into small normal
amounts of stuff.
But it's going to be good.
It's going to be very good.
I'm rooting for you.
Yeah.
Thanks.
You need to pump that Schmidt out.
I got I feel I feel more.
I don't know capable of of just being just to just do the work.
Just got to keep you got to keep the pace that you know you can you can
match so that you don't like freak out when you're doing fine.
Yeah.
Because like if you if you get some work done you're like oh shit I could
have done like seven times that much work.
And in reality you could not have done seven times as much work.
Don't worry about it.
You're doing fine.
Just keep just keep going.
And it's like it's it's good.
Right.
If you're if you're making progress then it's like OK just keep keep doing
what you're doing.
You're doing it right.
Did I.
Okay.
Apparently I can't remember what I talked about last week.
Did I say last week that I had sent my files of slime and punishment
to the printer that that would happen.
Yeah you did.
Yeah.
Okay well now I won't mention thank you.
Thank you.
I won't mention it again.
All right.
No problem.
Give if I could if I could just if I could just ask for one request.
I need you to to make the carrier the characters look wackier to be wackier.
They're not wacky wackier.
They look a more goofier.
Make them I think you should.
Yeah.
I think maybe you should just start over and make them wackier.
I mean look I don't disagree.
I think I struggle.
I struggle a bit with like oh it's got to be good.
So I have to be an anatomically correct which means I can't do this pose.
That's too wacky and then some of the sketches some of the drawings are like
end up kind of lame like kind of stuff you like look look everyone everyone
who I'm so surprised when I when I find out about a one piece fan and then I
look at their work and I'm like are you not taking the lessons from one piece
where it's like just characters are just wacky or like or even like something
like in Iraqi's logic with like characters just having weird poses
because like being weird is just more memorable than being like neutral or what
not.
You're just I mean I don't think I'm going necessarily for a one piece look.
I don't you should I definitely want to should have and yeah I agree.
Wackier characters but like singles for Ben I don't know I like I like subtle
stuff like like peanuts like Charles M. Schultz like the way he does like
extremely subtle expressions Charlie Brown being like depressed in a very
specific way and it's like yeah like there's only a tiny little flicks of
ink that make you feel like that particular way and when you look at it
okay but where is the I like subtlety where's the where's the Charlie Brown
gift shop and Tokyo Universal Studios.
Oh wait that's not there.
Oh there's a one piece gift shop.
No you can't answer that.
Can you you fake fan.
Look they put that goes for you too.
You got to make your character the wackier.
Um yeah.
Okay yeah it's not wacky enough.
I'm I'm not as wacky as people expect.
Phantom had some wacky expressions like in Simon punishment.
He had some for some wacky panels.
Sometimes you just have to like draw characters with just one foot in the
air and every time you see them they just have one foot in the air for no
reason I've never explained why but it's just memorable.
Is that a Jojo thing.
It's just like the thing just a thing people do.
What one foot in the air.
He's got he's got he's got to be goofy goofy.
Oh what I'm imagining right now is saying to you with his foot like
fully upwards 180 degrees looking at smoking a cigarette or cool.
I want everyone a lollipop you mean I want everyone to look in the mirror
and say say to themselves I got to get goofier.
I just got to get silly.
Look no no no I see what you're doing now you're trying to clown us.
You're trying to make us turn you just to put on the makeup.
That's not true.
But I see why I see what's speaking of which it wouldn't hurt.
Cheesy just wants us to put on clown makeup.
So does he can fucks us.
What's no look I see you.
I see your game.
Look look give me speaking of which you have you know it wouldn't it wouldn't
hurt to put on some more color maybe some more makeup and your big red
nose foundation.
Some red some red nose selfies wouldn't hurt.
Tease the hair dot tease that hair out into a big fro diet some wacky colors
and Ben Ben I hear that I hear if you really want your teeth to glow.
Astrogen is pretty good with that.
I heard like taking astrogen is pretty helps you glow it more and really big
shoes really really really big shoes and filled with estrogen.
You know I hear you know you know you know like a lot of people think breast
implants are expensive but not really and I hear they're pretty affordable
and the area you live in you know just saying just saying and they're not
just for women anymore.
They're there for everyone.
It's for everybody especially especially guys who take HRT.
Yeah true true yeah.
I hear you know I know it's a little it's a little hyperbolic but yeah my some
of my character designs are like stiffer and like more reserved than they
should be.
Yeah I still like Clarissa I like how her hat is like stupid hat but it's like
it's just a symbol of a cowboy hat.
Not and she's she's but she's like really cool though.
That's that's you know that's drawing comics though right isn't it just
like the more of it you draw you just like how push push the characters push
him more and more to be like you know wacky your poses exaggerated poses
you exaggerate them more and when it's a process you work push it you always
push in it push it funny doofy you know right and then I have I have a
thing I have one another thing that I wanted to mention this episode which
is I just wanted to mention that the radcon for dojin is done the dojin
the dojin is done the OVA is not done Nate is supposedly done almost he's
he's about seven or eight times now he said it's going to be done soon I
promise it's going to be done soon I'm definitely going to get it done this
month and then he's just a totally ignored it every single time but maybe
this time he means it for real and yeah the dojin is done and I have the
copy I have the PDF of it and one of these days when the OVA is done I'll
release it and it looks really great and everybody did a really great job
and I especially was impressed with Drinking Moth who did a lot of pages and
a lot of big like full-page spreads and they were really good and really quick
Drinking Moth like fucking got all these pages done and like got them done in
like a day like they were so good was so impressed yeah shoutouts to Drinking
Moth in particular I still need to commission Drinking Moth everyone
should commission Drinking Moth I really I can't recommend her enough honestly
I wanted to do the the the picture for the League of Nate fuckers voicemail
compilation that I said I was gonna do like a year ago oh yeah yeah yeah it's
great and also was there there's there's a there's three pages from new new did
some and Simsie and cut Simsie sketched one page and Kaiju did a couple pages and
I think it was there was there is there someone I'm forgetting give am I
forgetting anyone to help I don't know I can't remember I'll probably think oh
wait who's the I don't know if we used the the guy like Edward oh no yeah yeah
yeah a bunch a bunch of them were from Ed yeah yeah that traitor that turncoat
maybe it's time I finally follow Drinking Moth back I think you should
perhaps I think everyone should follow Drinking Moth on Twitter all right
that's the last that's the last of my notes for this week so I have I have no
more content you know I'm looking at this oh this is the months I've been alive
and I'm like I know that this is like usually used as feel-to-feel depressed
about the the the the the finitude the the the smallness of the world and the
life is just a bunch of dots on a page and there's so many of them already
filled but like that's right if you turn those little circles there into like
grapes you wouldn't be able to eat all those grapes it's actually quite a lot
it's actually a lot a lot more grapes than you would you'd think never would
have thought of it like that you know when I put it this way I just put this
in oh shit that's got my birthday in it let me crop that differently but if they
weren't but if they weren't great if they were if they were if they were if they
were grains of quinoa I could easily eat all of those are you two years older
than me oh I am gonna replace it with 29 the date of birth 29 20 29 I believe
in I thought you were like 25 I'm turn I'm 27 turning 28 next week here here
we go here we go so the blue is how much technically could count the dots if
they wanted to find out your exact age yeah but that's well you can find out
what month you could find out what no they can only find my mom from that and
I just said my birthdays next week so yeah true anyways the blue that's how
long me and Kai have been together that's crazy oh my god we're coming up
on ten years I was gonna say how many years is that ten years each row is
three years so how the time flies how the turn tables yeah let's let's reflect
let's take a moment of silence I've been a brony longer than that blue dots though
I had an extra like you're one true love you're one true love is my little pony
friendship is magic come back to you my true love it's but my home my love and
my ladies MLP did it and do it and do it you know you know ladies ladies ladies nuts
lay nuts on it that that that's a pun for like ladies nuts and lay these nuts
correct all right all right is there oblivion do you read one piece I my
experience of one piece one of my friends his name was Christopher Hall I'm
calling him out he's autistic more often than me which is on a ball he tried to
get me into one piece he showed me the first episode I don't remember if it was
dubbed in English or not and I didn't like it and based on that I will condemn
everything you know what the show is bad don't watch the show except I know
that's what that's what everyone's always said yes I mean it's no I disagree I
think the show is cool I watched every episode up to like episode 300 I did I
did too but I was like a child I was like 14 when I watched the show yeah and
children know children are the future I used to be one and then I got over it
I'm never gonna watch the show I'm gonna stick to the manga sorry I'm sorry you
can read you can read the manga in half the time it takes to watch the show it's
art isn't about how quickly you get to the end yes it is I just yes the baby's
shoes never worn all the best art ever done sooner equals better take I take I'm
gonna stick to the source material the better a work of art is the faster it
lets you just be done with it and get back to counting your fucking pennies
and investing in in your in diversifying your portfolio and in finding a high
interest savings account to put your your money in okay that's what it's about
the manga is good I would prefer the manga it's just that the anime has a
really good soundtrack and sound design and like I can't imagine knowing one
piece I can't imagine really knowing and one piece without knowing the sounds and
the voices and the music of the specific moments where it's like super
emotional it's like yeah it's all in my head damn Gino Gino 7 should do a video
on the sound design of the one-piece anime one piece how it looks a little
goofy so that's I know right isn't it great they have multiple sounds in one
piece where's my cool emo edgy boy protagonist huh that's law you're a law
boy man shut up is there a boy for me in one piece yes there's a guy who's his
name is law and he wears a hat law Trafalgar D law and he wears a hat just
like that pickup artist mystery and he has tattoo knuckles and a big sword he
looks like he he looks like he looks like you know he does drugs and smoke
cigars and like listens to to white boy rap white boy rap yeah true not cigar
sorry cigars and cigarettes well there's um I mean I'll I mean I'll show you my
favorite girl my favorite one-piece girl yeah it's Perona she's she's not emo
she's she's I mean I guess that she's goth right she's she's Lalita guy like
she's like past pastel goth I have I have two different Perona little figures
and I love her I love her wife Perona is great good to Perona is why she does
have a funny eye she's got the I'm sorry but she's got the gollywag eyes I love
funny eyes I love it when a girl got the funny eyes you got that goofy look in
our face she's got that when I was a kid I got playing my face I feel she's got
got that walk in her when I was a kid my favorite character was raising from
zoids I thought he was the coolest boy he's so emo that guy's got dust hair
that's a dust hair if I ever seen it real zoid head in in the call right now
yo zoid I I don't I don't think it holds up I don't think zoids holds up but
when I was a kid I want to talk about it I vaguely remember when I got cable I'm
like wait a minute oblivion you've got to read or and I'll watch one piece there's
so many girls in there I would definitely read it over watch it I'm not
watching a show that long it's too much I've already watching Detective Conan and
that's taking years that's that's now that I'm sorry how can you how can you
judge how you sit on your high horse and judge reading one piece when you're
literally watching Conan literally watching Conan I would say I would argue
you know why I'm watching somewhere there's actually a good reason
we're gonna leave it unless you can read oh my god she's amazing it's boss
it's his boss and a sonia you gotta she's on ironically really pretty and I'm not
saying that as a meme however if there's a one-piece waifu she's it for me I I do
appreciate that at a certain point Oda seemed to commit to making wackier
women he did not do it for a long time but then at some point he was like okay
I'll do it always but there is actually a very good reason to read sorry to watch
Detective Conan over read it and that's because the English translation is
utter dog shit when Funimation localized Detective Conan they changed it to
case closed that's yes I don't know why Detective Conan is already an English
title for the show I'm gonna I'm gonna be honest I'm when I hear detective
just the name Conan all I can give is Conan the barbarian it does not conjure
images like a genius child the offer Sherlock Holmes that's what I'm right
Conan O'Brien that's just not where that's just not what I think I don't know
that's maybe that's just not well ignoring that only did they change the
title they also changed Shinji's name to Jimmy Jimmy Kudo they changed his
names to like English names yeah they they made now it's in America it's not
Japan it's America which doesn't make any sense they did that to a phoenix right
and I love that game so like what's the problem the problem is that it doesn't
make any fucking sense because the fact that they're in Japan is extremely
important to like a lot of the stuff that happens the American police do get
involved and that's like a whole plot point and that makes no sense they just
fucked a bunch of shit up and all the official like English translations use
that for some reason and it's really dumb and I don't like it and the show
does that and also the show adds a whole bunch of extra like stories that are
also really good so I don't I'm sorry all that you just said those were like
complaints against the English dub right yes but you like the end the stuff
from the English dub was also put into the English translation of the manga as
well I see they did that to the manga too and I am just like why why would they
do that I I don't I don't know that's just what they it's real it's really
funny how for like a while there like they couldn't just have an anime be in
Japan they had to make it like about America they had to change it yeah which
is weird because I'm going up in the area they said in America they couldn't
have them eating rice they had to pretend they were donuts or fruit
sandwiches or whatever and it's just like why I think it would have been okay I
think you could have just said yeah these guys are Japanese and they're
eating rice it's normal what if my child asks me about what is bacon and they
they they learn about rice what is that weird oriental food you that's me an
American parent mm-hmm you're right and I was being being Japanese is woke well
I think yeah I I think it's woke being Japanese the Japanese gender I have to I
have to use the bathrooms you got can I you guys might what I could I could I
interest you in letting me use the bathroom no I'm gonna I'm gonna go back
my pants a little does he know that I diarrhea dumped in his toilet and now
it's blocked I diarrhea dumped in his ear when he was asleep and you didn't
even notice I diarrhea it out my butt which is where it comes from I should
also mention that the reason I'm watching Detective Conan is because it's
Kai's favorite series of all time and he's sharing it with me that's the other
reason I probably wouldn't watch it if I was if it weren't yeah like genuinely
when people say oh I can't get into X media it's so long I'm like shut up what
the fuck are you gonna do with that time oh you're complaining you got more of a
good thing oh you people don't actually go for bite-sized entertainment they
just like are intimidated by something that they can get invested in I don't
know why I just don't get it for me it's because there are so so so many shows
that I do want to see in my lifetime and I have a finite amount of time on earth
and I don't have the the did you borrow spirit of being able to watch fucking
everything I don't have that luxury so shows that are shorter I can watch more
of them and get more unique experiences out of that it's just I don't relate I
don't relate to feeling like I need to see everything or even that many things
I personally lists of movies and TV shows I've heard are great it's like oh I
should probably watch Scarface at some point like I've heard that reference so
much maybe like I should watch the film yeah but like I'd rather not every day
I say that I would I would prefer if someone could make a list of okay like
here like here of a list of detected Conan episodes that are actually like
relevant to like the main story and like here are like from the ones that aren't
relative related to the main story or introducing characters who will become
important later which you know like like the only grabbing like the top 10% of
the best mysteries to include so that way instead of having to watch a thousand
episodes only have to watch like 200 or something or maybe two or 300 like I
would probably prefer that experience because then because there are point
there are like some episodes that are just like okay that mystery was kind of
boring and predictable and but then there'll be like episodes like anime
original episodes that have some of like the best mysteries in the entire show
that are like super engaging and clever and I'm like holy shit how did they come
up with that murder and that like alibi and that like method and all this shit
and it's like really fucking crazy like cool stuff that they come up with
sometimes and you know what's our anime original episodes do a lot of good
stuff with that sometimes so I wouldn't want to just do the ones from the
demand you know what's a really good show I got into and me and me and my
buddies in my private server we uh we started watching a Colombo and it's a
really it's a really good a show is that detective man yeah and you know like
the general premise of it um no but I've seen his face I think I know what he
looks it's it's really it's really interesting cuz cuz the type of
mystery is they do the so you the the most common kind of mystery is the who
done it right like you know that's like the default usually right but Colombo
instead is the it's a type of genre called how you catch him is what it's
called and what it means is that at the start of every episode of Colombo we see
that we know who the killer is and we see them commit the crime and every
little thing they do to make sure they don't get caught like they always have
like every little like thing like like figured out like they always like think
twice they like get rid of evidence and they're like oh I did it I committed the
perfect murder that's always like the the first first third of every episode of
Colombo is the murderer we see them we know their name and everything and
they're committing the crime and they're getting away with it like I did it and
then and then but then the premise of the episode is like what is Colombo
the detective gonna figure out to solve the mystery and it's like so fucking
it's like so fucking interesting you know it's an ironically like a shonen
battle it's like because like both both sides are trying to like the killer is
trying to like like kind of like get the better of Colombo like oh Colombo
Colombo isn't gonna figure out this bit cuz I free I like I cleaned it up or
like in the spot I came up with the perfect liar I have an awesome alibi and
Colombo and Colombo's whole gist is that he kind of seems like kind of like
he's like kind of messy looking he's like really short and he and he always
seems to be asking like questions that are kind of stupid right or he starts
talking about his wife which is like his catchphrase and um but eventually
Colombo figures out like a small detail that connects everything else and in the
end he kind of like reveals the bombshell like oh well this is how you
did it and then and then the then the killer like what what Nani and then the
episode ends and it's and it's really fun it's so fucking awesome he also the
majority of the killers are like are rich people are like they're the ones who
are usually killing people and it's it almost becomes kind of like this like
class thing where like Colombo is like I don't know I kind of hero Colombo he's
working class hero even though he's a cop he's a working class hero and he
always kind of like gets the better of these like rich fucks who think they're
so smart and he's all like I don't know but my wife told me you're the killer
and that's basically every episode really the secret clue that put it all
together my wife had a dream she saw it in a vision I and and every episode is
like a movie it's like I like I think the original the first episode was
actually a TV movie but like people liked it so much they ordered a pilot
which was the second episode and every episode took an hour long but it's
really good love it big Colombo I can I can definitely say there's a lot of
like Detective Conan like it's not every it's not like every episode so who
done it that's like half of them but there's a lot of episodes that are like
we know who did it or like we we can very like one person is very obviously
suspicious but like it seems impossible like they were somewhere else they were
like sometimes so like they were on a plane like flying somewhere else at the
time of the murder how the fuck did they like pull it off like they change for
time of death did they or it's like in like locked room you know and like they
were somewhere else like and how did they pull that off how to if they
committed the murder they would have had to have locked the room but we can't
prove how they would have done it so we have to figure out the method and it's
really fucking good sometimes like some of the shit and like they teach you real
skills that you can use to murder people IRL I remember I saw a couple
episodes of case closed and I literally like never realized that Jimmy is like
an adult that's been transmogrified I thought he was just a kid and like it
like never came up that he is like magic child that's the whole that's the whole
like running plot is that he's trying to figure out who are the people who
behind making him into a child I know but it just never it just never came up
I still don't know I genuinely believe that that will never ever be solved like
that it's I don't know it's it's sort of like the most annoying compelling thing
to get you to read on cuz I'd like I like I like mysteries but you know you can
get tired of like and he's just solving the mystery again like there's only so
many types of mystery you can do and you know it could get boring but there's
that that hook when is he gonna find out who turned him into a baby when is he
gonna get the information never never will he get it but always really want
to see I can confirm that's not true we found out a lot of stuff about the
organization and who made the drug organization 13 yeah organization
because it made a black organization because they're their outfits were
designed by Nomura you see yes yes yeah all comes together and my wife had a
dream about it do you know that guy you know that like there's like an American
congressman who like literally posts on Twitter about how like his wife had a
frickin like vision from God and her dreams or whatever there's a real this
is a real good I think it might be clay Higgins I think it might be
representative clay Higgins like his wife had a fucking vision and is a
prophet of the Lord and that's why I don't know that's why I deserve to be
reelected that's why we have to raise taxes on that farm supplements or
something this is why we need to raise the price of gravel the gouging is on
gravel these tariffs on gravel my business fucking gravel gravel's fucking
killing me I gotta be groveling for my gravel I got a big old gravel for your
right here I got a big old gravel for your dairy air I don't understand what's
happening yeah Colombo Colombo based recommend watch it it's on to be for
free I wish Colombo would tell me what the fuck any of you are fucking talking
about because it was just about and but as I was going to feed the cats I had
something about a congressman having a vision from God or something yeah yeah
yeah this this guy named rep I think it's rep rep clay Higgins and like he's
occasionally posted on Twitter about how like his wife has yeah these like
prophetic like God dreams that like foretell the future and stuff God it's
awesome you know you know what flight of a Concord's first recently for the
first time there's that episode with the guy at the fruit stand who's super
racist against New Zealanders he's played by Aziz I'm sorry yeah yeah it sounds
like a name he would have based on his visual appearance I'm racist I can I
could say that cuz he's a fellow brown brother like me yeah he was in like he
was in like parks and rec yeah yeah he got like canceled for a millisecond but
it was only because apparently I forget the details but people kept saying that
like oh it was just because like this woman had sex with him and I don't like
that very much that was upsetting cancelable behavior in 2023 yeah not
anymore not anymore I'm sorry that's that's fucked up we can't allow this
it's over it's I'm sorry you took it too far we have to roll we have to start
rolling back we have to go back because you had sex with one of them
this is a plan rolling back rolling back women's rights rolling JK rolling
rolling back rolling rolling rock rolling rock on the rolling rocker yeah rolling
rock on the rolling rocker could not fucking believe it I made a tweet like a
couple weeks ago where I said that a best case scenario Universal Studios just
buys the rights of Harry Potter off JK Rowan but not now in retrospect I don't
really think that's gonna happen because like it probably only happened if it
gets to the point where like the JK Rowan herself has like decreased the
profits of the franchise and I think to a certain extent she has I don't think
it's like enough enough you know it might not know yeah we haven't gotten to
that point yet where it's like only it's only been increasing because as the
people who grew up with the films start getting incomes they start being
becoming you know man children about it and they're like oh I love Harry Potter
I remember that and now they're all buying like Harry Potter stuff as an
adult it's yes with the whole Hogwarts legacy thing it's like moments like
this that make me realize that like you spend too much time on Twitter you start
thinking like this is something everybody knows but it's not really true
because I'm on Instagram where I mostly follow like close people who live in my
city they're playing the Hogwarts game and like they don't know nothing about the
JK Rowan like shit or yeah I would like post most people don't care to the
average person and I and I and honestly I sympathize I do it's like to the
average person it's like that's a political debate and I don't even want
to look at it I have not I'm not gonna take any position at anything that's
politics and this is a video game and I and I and I do not want to don't
acknowledge that those have anything to do with each other I'm just here to play
a video game I kind of get it I don't I don't like it but I understand this is
that it's like I don't want to engage with the takes about this I just want to
consume product this is why yeah in a couple of months I'm going to drop my
video called I prove every story is political with just one chart and I
have a chart that like proves everything is political interesting what does it
chart like politics over yeah it's a it's a it's a Prager you a graph that's
like the axes are unlabeled it's just like politics versus time and the arrow
just goes out politics so they acknowledge that politics is relative
that's relativism which is Marxism which is if society agreed that killing
babies was good then it would be good because that's relativism and leftist
want to kill babies I agree that's that's for I didn't agree with anything
until you said kill babies yes I love killing babies also I believe politics is
relative a woman driving in a car in a video game isn't political unless you
live in Saudi Arabia hmm okay I'll I'll tell you I'll tell you this I kind of
like I like go down to like the core of what what politics is and what and like
forget ideology like forget left or right don't that's not even what I'm
talking about politics is ultimately just like how society functions that's all
what politics is right hmm and this chart like that I have I'm gonna post it
here like kind of like you could like you could like fit stories into this
chart like and not just in the squares but in between squares hmm right has
just been updated since the last time you showed me no it has not I've been too
busy I don't think I've seen this before okay but I'll explain what I mean so
like like the top says blatant so that's what I first of all you spelled
preserve wrong okay who cares I'm gonna roast you for that alright whatever
who cares I yeah English is the colonizers language I don't care anyway
at the top we have blatant so that's when like a story is like obviously
political so either it's like the main character is like the president or
something or the main character works in like some sort of political body then
oh yeah obviously it's political cuz someone is like you know working in the
system itself story about politics right and then at the bottom is like subtle
so it's like when like no one in the story works with anything political at
all you know they're just like people or they're like abstractions of people or
whatever you know and left and right we have state power and then non-state
power and you know there we have like preserve like preserving state power and
on the right we have changing you know with like non-state power this is like
politics is downstream from from culture or vice versa sort of yeah so so so at
the so for and the biggest way to figure out what could fit in this chart is
like pick a story and like think about does society change by the end of the
story if the if society does not change then it's like it's in the preserved
section so like by the stuff like it by the start of the story if the government
or everything that functions around it is the same it's on the it's on the left
side I'm thinking about I'm thinking about Harry Potter right and then and then
on the on the on the right side right like if society well it's no no forget
forget for you know it's not there's no ideologies here like forget left or
right politics yeah there's no there's no ideology so like for example what it you
know what would be all the way at the at the top at the top left side where it's
like blatant a blatant preserving and and like state power would be a movie like
Independence Day right because all the characters all the major characters
work in the governmental body and the and the bad guys don't necessarily have
an ideology they're just aliens they're just a force who wants to change our
world right and we want to preserve our we want to preserve America so at the
start of the movie America exists and at the end of the movie America still
exist nothing change right we have preserved society that's like yeah right
and at the at the top right corner where it's like and that's good yeah sure
depends on you and well and at the top way at the top right corner where it's
like blatant and like changing society and like it would be kind of like non
state power we would have something like one piece where there's like people
actively changing society like society's gonna change once we get to the one
piece right probably probably but also state power will probably change I feel
like I feel like the like an artwork can be put in many of these different
zones see that's that's the beautiful thing though that's a beautiful thing
about this because like every every one of these stories I mentioned could be
debated on so like nothing is permanently like like stuck in one place
well I yeah I don't think it's like one place or another I just think it some
things can be multiple places like the main characters are trying to change
society and then they like like overall like yeah exactly like where to put my
little pony well okay does equestria people change you is where I is where I
put my little pony okay you're also changing the community and preserving
Ponyville from attacks Twilight became a princess that's a that's an increase in
state power yeah it's like individual equestria equestria exists at the start
right there's still a monarchy at the start of the series and there's still a
monarchy at the end of the series right yes I would so my little pony is more
episodic so it'll be closer to the center which is the status quo zone and
that's mostly that's mostly reserved for like episodic like superhero media or
like sitcoms they're all in the status quo zone nothing ever like it's always
just everything's kind of the same nothing changes right like that's where
the majority of like just super so by this charts logic is that non political
when nothing just nothing changes well I think the idea is that it's still
political status quo it's all political if a story if a story takes place in a
society it is political by the fault right yeah and like and the care and the
characters just kind of like because like the characters doing nothing about the
politics it's still like a commentary on politics itself right you know sure sure
right so like yeah unconsciously perhaps but yeah yeah when it's like subtle
when they're like because I mean you might say it's kind of more blatant in my
little pointy because she's training to become a princess which is a person in a
position of power right hmm well she doesn't even train to be well she kind
of trains to be a princess or ultimate friendship lessons ultimately she
becomes a princess and she kind of like escapes the like well if he's a
princess it's some sort of monarchy right sort of like it's honestly more
like a divine appointment than it is like a hereditary monarchy okay familiar
you are like real monarchs you you can like well as long as like the divine
monarchy has some sort of like kind of state power you know like the princess
implies there's a state power or something right you know mm-hmm there's
parades there's cantaloupe there's lots of this guards castles I think I'm I
think like if I were to kind of like be more kind of like try to like keep things
simple I think the top left would be kind of like people preserving society I
mean it says right there like top right like it's people like kind of changing
society and the bottom is more like society is changing you right or like
yeah like you know society changes your society keeps you the same you know and
that's what those are more reserved for more like kind of psychological stories
or stuff that's like a character you know society society also gazes into you
yeah like like at the bottom like probably at the bottom I would put
something like taxi driver where the character of Travis Bickel like ultimately
stays the same because society has kept them the same you know because he does
this giant action where he fucking goes into a brothel and starts shooting up
people and he basically committed a massacre and but the thing is the fact
that he since he killed what society deems the right people who deserve to
die he's considered a hero so he's like his his terrible actions are justified
so he stays in this he stays in this state and you know and it's kind of like
all like all of this is very obvious if you've seen taxi driver because the final
scene it's looking if we have it is that everyone here seen taxi driver I have
not seen taxi driver oh it's a 10 out of 10 it's a it's I mean I've heard I've
heard people talk about it it is the best in taxi driver and I will watch it so
it's the best crazy white boy movie ever of all time like don't know they're
crazy crazy like like that movie is the reason why I love crazy white boys is
that movie and I'm we fucking turn it in a fight Travis Bickle or Patrick
Bateman probably Patrick Bateman to be honest because he's because he's in
better shape because he does a thousand crunches every morning he's it he has
more experience but no one will believe him Travis Bickle is like sloppy you
know and you know also like also American Psycho could probably go like
here at the bottom where his name is Patrick Bateman okay unless unless his
actual name is a what's the other guy Patrick Bateman wait wait don't they say
in the movie wait Patrick you're the American Psycho they call me American
Psycho in the movie I remember Jared Lito calls him like Patrick you're the
American Psycho he says that I don't think that's true there's a part in the
movie where he's mostly Patrick Bateman but sometimes there's another name for
another guy that sometimes it's like he killed that guy but then other times like
he's like people call him that name like he might actually be that guy that he
thinks he killed like so like at the like at the start of American Psycho
like Patrick doesn't change like he just kind of just stays the same ultimately
because the society that he's around himself has kept them the same so he
would be like at the bottom left you know is that political is that really a
measure what it's saying it's the fact that he's being kept the same says
something about like society right just it's all I'm saying I'm gonna I'm gonna
eventually like really when I do the video every one of these squares is
gonna have a movie or like a story there so people are gonna have like a better
like idea what I'm talking about okay well I'll watch it do you like it do
you think it's interesting do you think I'm onto something I am not sure you have
to convince me you don't have to give me more examples and maybe lay out a full
case not gonna lie I haven't I haven't seen this chart in like months and I'm
just pulling out
well give just stepped out I was about to suggest voice going to voicemails since
we've been going for like three hours now unless I don't know unless there's
anything else he has one chat about I I want to briefly promote my animation
that I finished of my character oh yeah yeah yeah my character failure with her
big floppy tits right funny put in a penis between her tits and flopping it
that animation done it's out where is all my patreon it's on your patreon okay
okay wow here I was getting excited here I pulled out my dick cuz I was about to
jerk it and you're you're like oh it's on your patreon never mind yeah it's it's
only I'm so sorry that it's on my the only way I just became glass to you I'll
show a little safer work preview that LESR can put on screen Jesus
oblivion I'm just gonna say it now you haven't you haven't made it until like
your animations appear on a tiktok um come zone has appeared in tiktoks like
the audio yeah there's this current like tiktok meme going where it's like
that it's like clip from SpongeBob where he's watching like the CNM and then
Gary comes in and he and he changes the channel to football because he doesn't
watch yeah yeah so so the meme is that it's like and it's like it a bit of the
it's like the animated porn right before they get down to the fucking and then
like Gary comes in and SpongeBob changes it once your animations appear in that
oblivion you made it I could do that right now I could make that oh yeah that's
not you can't do yourself that's that's just doesn't have doesn't have to do
yourself all right there've been times where I've gone to 4chan like on to D
look for a cool boob porn and they'll be a Fred like a hot succubus women and
I'll just see my character in there every so often yeah that's happened three or
four times no sorry two or three times oh wow there they go oh wow they're
undulating I'm looking I'm looking at the video you sent me I think I've seen
you working on this animation I didn't I don't where's where's my link I don't
see it I'll send I'll send you cheese huh I'm currently so never there's a
fluid Elliot that is a fluid flop that they got there that is smooth mm-hmm and
shiny is how I would describe this you know speaking of 4chan I was notified a
while ago that last Halloween there was a thread or maybe two Halloweens ago
there was a thread that used punk as like a as a like a little Halloween thread
and there wasn't mentioned who punk was or what she was from they just pretty
sure yeah I'm pretty sure the person who made the thread knows cuz the fact they
know from they had like bail jpeg gifts and stuff but then people like oh this
is a cool is a cute little Halloween mascot and they sort of adopted her and
then people started drawing her I was like oh hell yeah wait do you have so
nobody knows it's me but they're just they're just enjoying the character
design that's really nice can you share some of the art that was made if you
have I think some of it was already it already existed I can put some I want to
put it epic this is cool I'm gonna put some on me thank you yeah and I titled
them and on cuz I don't know who made them that's really cool I am someone
noticed someone notified me that some people have posted my comics on the on
4chan specifically the if you guys see my Akira bike slide comic that I made yeah
yeah yeah I got posted apparently these are funny oh my god oh sorry it's a lot
of that in the middle oh my god these are these are cool I love these are you
too chicken to trick-or-treat in all the threads I don't even know what this is
yeah what is it's a it's a little it's made her small with an oh yeah but the
hair every hair I like I like I like the candy cane whack-and-are that's really
nice looks upset the hidden post fan will shrimp yeah the the punk fans who
don't know bail shape it's just really nice cuz it's like yeah character
design that's I did I did a little character and I resonated people that's
pretty cute that's pretty cute hmm hmm you love to see it give everything to go
to voicemails I feel like we're getting to that point before that had did you
read the one-piece chapter no you fool no no no well what do you want to do do
you want to do first I want to skip it I don't want to skip it I don't want to do
I mean I don't know we got guess we can't be rude rude to read I don't know I
don't know what a one no no I mean like not with them I mean like that's why like
after the voicemails like the show ends then we talk about one piece well I
guess we could do that yeah yeah you could continue after voicemails I could
say bye and you could keep the episode going for five hour mark I mean I hate I
hate to kick hate to kick a blivvian fall off if you don't kick me off Kai's
gonna kick me off you'll be like you're being on the podcast too long I want to
be loud in the living room that's fair that's reasonable okay I mean we could
do that yeah sure all right voice voicemails now and then one piece after
I guess sure all right so the first voicemail is it's a link to a YouTube
video and it's just called moon stuff and it's this just video of a guy on the
moon oh this is me I saw you can you can disregard the audio and just send a link
since I'm already here I explain it the comics the comments are turned off cuz
everyone's like oh it's fake yeah so so this was a few episodes ago then you
were talking about you know wait did we did we ever go back to the moon and the
answer is yes we did and we took a better cameras wait I mean I did I say
that cuz like I know we went to the moon several times I know we didn't just go
the one time oh did you mean like after the first like burst of missions was
there like another one yeah like um we want to I know we went a bunch of times
but like we kind of just haven't been doing it in a while cuz like there's
not really anything to like get on the moon there's not a whole lot humans can
do but I'm so freaky with a completely black sky I love it I love it you bring
that up cuz I remember I was talking to a co-worker and I told the co-worker
that like like yeah I'm like anti conspiracy theory like I really do the
majority conspiracy theories are like incredibly fucking bullshit and stupid
and he's all like oh so you actually believe we we went on the moon and I'm
like yeah of course we went on the fucking moon and he's all like oh yeah how can
we never went back and I'm like there's no fucking resources why would the
fuck would we go back there's nothing to okay when you send a robot to the moon
you can fold it up into a cramped space it doesn't need a life support system it
doesn't need room to move around and stretch its muscles and breathe it
doesn't need food it doesn't need water you don't have to like basically like
for human habitation especially you know usually they send a couple people
at a time because it's you know better that way you're gonna have to like
does the size of the craft have to be like five or six times bigger and five or six
times heavier which means for rocket needs to have like five or six times more fuel
because the fuel to payload ratio isn't something you can just sidestep
like a bigger payload means more fuel but then the fuel also adds more weight so
you need even more fuel and it just becomes ridiculous for Saturn 5 rocket was
fucking gigantic we don't usually use rockets that big because they cost billions of
dollars per launch so basically I told my co-worker all of that that Oblivion just
said I told that to my co-worker and he was fucking stunned and he fell on the ground
and then everyone clapped also also Ben you mentioned parabolic arcs I want you to watch
this footage of the lunar rover whenever you see dust kicked up behind it notice how
there's no it doesn't swirl around like it would an air like the dust particle is just
like fall out follow a parabolic arc and like fall straight to the ground
let me uh let me they don't linger in the the way air does
it's like halfway through driving towards the camera
they kind of just yeah it kind of just kicks up in these like little waveforms behind the tire
and then just falls straight up and then down and up and then down yeah yeah they don't linger
because they don't there's no air for them to hang in there's no air and they also accelerate
towards the ground too if you're I mean the camera's moving quite a bit but like if you're able to
catch so often when you see at the ground it actually speeds up quite a bit before hitting
the ground because it just accelerates the whole time yeah which wouldn't happen in air
dust particles are tiny they basically have air resistance basically completely
overwhelm some you can't do that without filming in a vacuum and because of the low gravity you
would also have to film it basically have a high speed camera spilled it spilled it film it at like
90 frames per second which we didn't have 90 frame per second cameras that could record for like
10 20 minutes or hours at a time back then that that technology in exhaust high speed cameras
could only record for about 90 seconds which would be we'll start for like for for 30 seconds
which would be 90 seconds after you slowed it down but if that's the case then the dust makes
even less sense because that would be the dust moving in slow motion which dust the dust would
have had to be moving three times faster than that which it definitely wouldn't do if there was air
so it's impossible to fake it's that's just not possible oh i see what you're saying yeah this
effect is just you wouldn't you wouldn't never wouldn't you just wouldn't act like that yeah i
saw a youtube comment i guess i turned off the comments off since then someone was saying yeah
this is clearly stop motion and i'm like first of all what fucking stop motion animator people
just say words people just fucking say words oh my god they're saying they claim that the
astronauts don't move and they're like oh the astronauts have stopped motion i'm like first
of all stop motion the 70s was janky as fuck with the animators back then just weren't as good as
the people we have now and that's not a technology thing that's an artist thing who did they hire
secondly these shots go on for like minutes at a time no stop motion person can do a shot that
long without making a mistake and having to start over also dust how do you do stop motion dust
are you fucking stupid yeah you've ever seen any fucking movie ever they never do stop motion
dust because it's so fucking yeah stop motion movies have only been able to have that since CGI
could do CGI dust over top of a stop motion movie that's like what like it does it would be interesting
to see like like a doctor uh no uh what's what's the guy who does the visual doctor disillusion
captain captain disillusion captain disillusion video about how like yeah how you couldn't fake
the moon landing footage there was um you know i think he's addressed that people want him to do
that but like he just i think he's like he's like misbusters or did it better than i ever could
and i think no he could do an even better job there's busters barely tap the surface there's
also a lot of things aside from like actual moon footage that proves the landing was real
and everything and i think the biggest thing i always go back to is the fact that if the moon
landing was fake the russians would have exposed us like right then and there because they had way
more shit up there and they would have they would have known right unless your logic is like oh the
russians are in on it too and it's like um in the middle of the fucking cold war we they weren't on
the same fucking side motherfucker uh yeah so they colluded to make the cold war just a just a little
prank that they pulled on every single other person and then you would have to believe in a bigger
body and then it goes into the people that like oh well you know who's secretly controlling the
strings and it's like bro it's it's a one world government but also fuck the middle east um they're
terrible and we have to kill them it's a one world government but they want globalization but we're
but we're already at globalization and like it's so fucking oh god i'm so fucking tired i was
listening to um it's yeah i was listening to the it's literally more it's more believable to just
be like no maybe we it would actually be simpler to believe that we just went to the moon we just
we just launched a rocket to the moon like it's not that far it's the grand scheme i was um i was
fucking listening to the cold cuts podcast with uh yellow swag and beatle moses and like
just the way that like i like beatle moses but i really just hate how casual he is about like
just believing in conspiracy theories and he's all like yeah you know i i do think the movement
he was fake it's just it just be so easy to fake like oh my god are you serious you fucking dude
like i i swear i thought you were supposed to be the smart member of this podcast yeah if you
know nothing about cameras or physics or anything that's that sucks oh my god i was this this just
this justifies every bad thing i've ever said about beatle moses uh he's a he's a cool guy he's
still like kind of the better half of that podcast not gonna lie oh god that doesn't
spill me with the confidence i mean if they're on a podcast they're already too far gone right
right it's too late right ellies ellies are cut out the following that i'm about to say because
it's kind of like some personal shit a few moments later okay all right should we go back to voicemails
now yeah we go back to voicemails no i have a mini topic it's really short trust me it was all right
okay um i was just i just i fell down the i didn't really fall down the rabbit hole i i got it i
saw the fucking elevator i fell into an elevator no a mini Scientology rabbit hole again i fell
down to a deep a few years ago learning about all the fucked up shit that Scientology does and how
insane and like batshit crazy the organization is and how they like attack people do you know
any Scientologists i actually i met one uh when i was at animation school one of my friends
one of my best friends at the school turned out to be a Scientologist and he was talking about
the South Park episode and he actually broke down into tears talking about it oh no he got bullied
he got bullied so much because of it and how he doesn't understand why the stuff from the
that they said in South Park isn't even true that was my first exposure to it i but um that
and then he tried to show me like some Scientology videos and it was like the very like you know
that corporate music where it's like all like uplifting and spiritual and it's like come join
our institution i watch the tanda cruel video about corporate music yes that was a good one yes
boba way yeah they were boba weighing in there boba way yeah yeah yeah yeah but then um i don't
know later i i ran out falling into that document falling into i ended up watching that documentary
series about Scientology and how like um all the shit about the aliens that South Park mentioned
is true there's recordings of L Ron Hubbard talking about it um well that's well that's the stuff
that like they don't tell you until you get like deeper right until you reach ot free which most
an average person would have to spend around 300 thousand dollars in donations to reach that level
fuck hell oh you think you think they're alive you think they're alive when they put like this is
what they actually believe and then they weren't lying every person who's ever like left Scientology
has like horrible like yeah like they teach you about ot free that's like standard um but uh
so i without getting too much into it i just i just noticed this is this is the leader of
Scientology david miscavige he has he has those glassy like those empty like glassy eyes that a
lot of like crazy like demonic like religious people is this guy ai generated no that's just
how he looks you know kind of copeland has it has those eyes oh my god uh the heavens gate guy also
has those glassy eyes okay i just noticed it these people are demons this guy looks like a comedian
you ever um you ever seen this guy is like leslie nielsen and uh which which guy is the comedian
the third guy the third yeah ben you ever seen this guy's like rodney dangerfield leslie nielsen
and uh who's the guy who was steve martin he's like those three people in one guy i mean i thought
it was pretty funny when he had all those people commit ritual suicide by drinking kool-aid pretty
no that wasn't him that was that was jones that wasn't heavens gate that was jones town it was
jones town what heavens gate was similar though it also yeah they had similar similar but you
ever seen the the video with that with that image come from no it's pretty it's pretty wacky um you
might get some inspiration heavens gate you initiation um you know what's funny is i should have painted
his teeth with y9 you know what's funny is that um the site where these guys committed their mass
suicide is like like i think i'm like an hour and a half away from there um it's pretty close by it
was like a it was like a like a big house in like a in the neighborhood and after they committed
like the act like all the neighbors like got together and bought the house and then fucking
demolished it because they didn't want like a couple of weirdos to come and check out the place
you know because of like tourist reasons or whatnot right so it's not it's technique that's
there but it's not because they built i think they built a new house over it um good for them yeah
it's uh it's wacky oh also um when they when they committed the mass suicide they were wearing a
specific like nike shoe and after like that mass suicide they stopped making that shoe and that
shoe goes for like it costs so much on fucking ebay now because they don't it's because they don't
sell it and you know it's infamous now yeah and suddenly consumption under capitalism was african
once again it just took one very funny if that was like their best shoe and they're like oh we can't
make it anymore we gotta make the worst shoes now damn it why people ruin everything uh uh
our uh shit i'm sorry i lost my train of thought what's happening what are we talking about
uh Scientology um oh yeah Scientology Scientology
demons i love demons um i love demons i am a demon i love evil i love material harm
i love to cause it um so uh speak voicemail yes okay the next voicemail was uh where are we
we got an image here we got some image posts okay we then took us that long to get through
one voicemail it was like an hour uh okay so this is oh my god what is the beast out of the earth
and then i saw the second beast coming out of the earth it had two horns like a lamb but it spoke
like a dragon it excites the authority the first beast on its behalf something Aurora
oh so like mage is the devil not the devil the the beast of the earth uh earth beast
guys who horns like a lamb spoke like a dragon fire to come down from heaven okay like the
aurora bria it deceived the inhabitants of the earth just like just like mage does every day
um if i can if i can six six six the number of the bitch gives hey no that's my favorite number
the beast was given power to give breath to the image of the first beast so that the image
could speak oh like a vtuber yes oh my god it's all holy shit yo is this is this true guys guys is
this true is this true i would say i can't i can't believe mage is narrow caesar slash
narrow on caesar six one six i could i i have i had a feeling i had a feeling
guys saying not that i'm shocked but not that shocked i got a feeling that mage might be the
devil the devil that mage might be the devil let the person who has insight calculate the
number of the beast for it is a number of a man that number six six six it but just dawning on me
how goofy that is yeah like like the number of the beast it's the calculation yes because you
calculate it okay so in roman this is a common thing in rome is that like you know how roman
numerals they're made out of letters right if you add the letters in someone's name together you can
get like a number um and so you know you can calculate someone's number and narrow uh like the
what his number was six six six um or six one six depending on if you spelled it narrow or
near on there are two spellings and um narrow killed a bunch of christians and they also it's
not just for number they also specified that the beast is just rome they say there's like seven
heads which are seven hills and but the tail is a river and there are this many crowns on the head
this many crowns came before this many crowns will be and this specific crown which if you
looked at how many scissors they had had up into that point that also matches up with nero
and all the stuff it says he's going to do is stuff that narrow did it's very much just
it's a guy in history i think i think it's a i think it's a hebrou thing there's this thing
called gematria which is just like yeah yeah it's it's he he does it as well yeah maybe maybe the
romans also did it uh yeah it's roman the romans had like had their version of it but like there
was a similar thing in hebrou as well too yeah but the number six six six and six one six comes
from the from that translation not the hebrou version it's it's really funny when people in
the modern day will try to do it with like modern english names like as if like as if like like people
in the bible would have like known how like the numerical gematria would work out for like the
english spelling in the year 2023 and it was divinely inspired yeah that's true that's also
true definitely god told them and all the all the stuff about this hey guys this is very obviously
rom because of the seven hills and the river and all this stuff just ignore all that yeah yeah
like it basically like explains what the metaphor is and like plain words like
but but uh but uh fuck it also what an image this next voicemail is um i mean you know it speaks
it speaks for itself pretty much speaks for itself i have no comments uh no notes the next one is
called their song to pass the time helps them not to forget uh and it is posting right now
all right let's give it a listen three two one go
98 kawasaki scroll hey you know what i'm glad they're keeping busy he's amazing
okay next one is called um it's trash uh i gotta make sure i'm posting the right one here
it's trash there it is three two one go oh what up losers just wanted to say
gives us a fucking trash man fucking trash not even good no cross hatching no technique
fucking horrible man but get more time to go into detail because you hear that
you hear that it's my fucking bad man it's my fucking bad what yeah i gotta have this i got a
sex to have now i've got no time for you losers man i've found you have fucking sex
what i i mean you had to what do what do we think what are we doing cross
hatching what's he talking about he has to find the sex what did he say was he was he saying
Gibbs art is bad because there's no cross hatching and then he's but he can't he has to have sex
now so he can't continue sex yes that's fair enough okay yeah all right we all have to
we all got to have sex you must uh not with each other though
you know i don't have sex with women no next one is called um what is it called
issuing an apology and a correction three two one go
yo so i just got done and i gotta say now that i'm not a virgin anymore i had to rethink a lot
of things my entire perspective shifted and i have to say like Gibbons art style isn't just
really fucking great man it's way better than bands like i'm so many men yeah great art
style man also i'm gonna call me as well hey uh he got good good that's that's that's how it works
you have sex and then everything you thought before completely 180s except for ben who's
virginity regrows every 30 minutes as was established yeah and every single time i 180
i 180 on all my previous beliefs and then i have sex again and i revert and i just keep flip-flopping
you're like you're like sissifis
am i yeah yeah i keep trying to push my virginity away and it just keeps rolling back down all you
really need is a sissy's fist in ya hey i'm back i'm back whoa whoa you can't you can't say that
cheesy manfredo was back no i could say that i'm a chaser i could say that true though um next one
tracer but i want to be chaser uh next one is called oh fuck what's the next one it's called
unveiling an elaborate ruse and it's posting okay three two one go
haha i wasn't really a virgin it was all an act i was nearly pretending to be a virgin
full show wow please don't write in newspaper that i'm a virgin i've had sex i pleased multiples
of times i was fooled but i was listening to the draw costs again and there was this one episode
where it was like locally sad and distraught about her art style and she was talking about how
she felt she was shit because she didn't have like the technique and i just felt really sad about
that because i really like your art style i'm really like the way you use color and shape design
i think it's really expressive and it's something i really miss in my art so i thought i'd call in
and just let you know in case you might still feel that way because i think it would be really
sad if you felt like that about your art style because of some weird notion of what constitutes
technically able good art it's funny i am uh consistently down on myself that's true um
it's not that it's not good um i know i've gotten better over time i think my art style right now
is pretty good uh obviously well it's not obvious but i i do i do want to improve in various ways
but like uh i don't shit on myself quite as much yeah you feel you feel i'm i'm getting better at
your yeah i'm good like like like later later later chapters of cleric gun smoke i read like
i i go over the like the sketches and it's not just the the the art but it's like the the the
layout and the the expressions i'm like oh my god i'm actually emotionally moved by my own comic
even though i wrote it and i'm reading it again it's like oh this is gonna be so good
that's i i can't i can't i honestly can't wait to read the whole thing
oh yeah i've been looking forward to it for a long time now
okay next one uh moving right along here the next one is called uh let me find it
wish i had lubed up beforehand oh well what you're gonna do uh and let me just uh post that right
there okay three two one go sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry oh you know what i'm not falling for it not
this time i'm not listening to the whole thing oh but wait what if this time is the time where
this happened before a couple times somebody just farts on a voicemail and ben is insisting on
listening to the whole thing to make sure that there wasn't a real voicemail in there i always turn
it off no but ben loves it for real farts aren't funny i i'd ravage us here someone's scream
yeah no this time i'm afraid i'm afraid i've learned my lesson fool me once shame on me fool
me twice shame on you sir shame on you farting those horrendous those horrendous that's that sounded
like someone shitting into a bowl it didn't even sound like farts entirely i that might have been
i could hear a little droplets that was horrible that's that's disgusting i'm glad i
i'm glad i stopped it uh this is i should have stopped it when i had the chance and you have
learned the hard lesson that i had to learn uh all right the next one it is wish i'd lubed up
yeah lube lube i always lube up before taking this shit what does that mean uh all right next one
is uh an image um live feed of ben saint's live feed from ben saint's house rats rats and there
they go oh it's it's uh the canishes guy canishes do you mean maybe it's something else
you mean the yellow um mouse boy something yeah that's the boy king oh yeah rap boy genius
shows up at the end here yes rat boy genius that's the one i've seen i've seen some rat boy genius
i've been showing some i found out that the the guy who runs rat boy genius well i i initially
found out that he's actually like a hollywood composer yeah i heard that appear in a movie but
then i also found out later that he's apparently this weird like right winger which is disappointing
if true that's too bad that's too bad um nothing is ever good i i don't know really anything about
i just someone showed me rat boy genius and i was like oh this is interesting and then they were
like yeah this is a guy who used to like make hollywood soundtracks and now he makes this like
okay uh good for him good for him the next one is called kong a luya two three two one go
so cars get styled so listen dudes she shrinks in size to suit her mood she's one cool car
you'll not be wrong to choose her she'll skip and hop and make you clap but love is not a monkey
rap it's a quick and it's a nimble kong a luya kong a luya kong a luya kong a luya
well what can i say other than kong a luya kong a luya what a what a what a piece what a
what a piece of shit roll and rock on the roll and rocker
jk rolling on the roll and rocker playing hogwarts legacy on the roll and rocker playing hogwarts
legacy with my power glove oh what do we think thoughts prayers that's these are pretty good i
like i want to know these are pretty good i heard they're on the last episode too it was pretty
great yeah it's pretty good this is what motivates this man this year again i don't i don't sing
it's one of the things i don't do well i thought i do haha i thought oh my god it's cheesy i thought
it was um it's it's not it's not just like the lyrics to the the donkey kong rap put into like
the the into the other song the hallelujah it's original just enough so that it fits yeah it's good
yeah but i ever i don't do voice mail if i ever just need to say something i just asked to be on
the pod you just say let me on the show and then we say well please please let me be on the show
strong armed your way in before so this is the guy who did the pcp episode 300 fame i'm pretty sure
oh is that sasuke pro i don't know any other person there's a guy fell down and hurt my knee
pcp it was oh no sasuke pros uh he did the other they did that i don't know their gender at all
they did the i don't know uh i'm listening to the p sorry darling i'm listening to the pcp right now
it's so addicting that sasuke no i don't know about that i mean the the theme the the theme it was
like a one-time theme that uh we used an episode 300 uh it was submitted as a voice mail and then
you were like play this at the start or something i do remember that i can't recall exactly how it
went at the moment and it's not smart um all right next one sounds like that guy to me
mm okay die or girl i don't know right who freaking knows uh next one is called
goes anymore these days uh the next one is called dark and darker one no part two
there it is okay three two one go i know uh these voice mails uh really they're just a
chance for me to talk to you been saying my idol i don't care about the others well the other
you know who you are it's really just you've been saying yep who's he talking with you and uh i hope
you didn't mess out on the uh dark and dark play test i told you about earlier because it's over
now and you missed it sorry that's all it was some bullshit it sucked devs they can't bounce
throw now i died to a fucking zap a singular zap yes it's true and the slowest like the the
fucking best spell is zap and it's like the basic spell like why why can you do 90 damage with a
zap anyway i fucked this game i'm glad it's a fucking garbage good thing i missed out we're
gonna fix it hey instead of like fixing the balance of the game they just they implemented
solo queue shit that nobody asked for all right and it was thanks for keeping me abreast of the
dark and darker you should play it you should buy it situation i would appreciate appreciate the
heads up uh next one is called uh pcp appreciation from this is from prince isolation three two one
go hello everybody with this new content renaissance of sorts that the pcp has recently
been seeming to go through with uh both people starting to stream again uh the possibility of
the perfect comic party and uh things overall looking looking a little bit more uh content wet
as opposed to content dry i thought that maybe it would be fun to sometimes you know call in
with a little voicemail that's just appreciating uh the the content uh that that that we're all
enjoying from the pcp and from ben and gave and from all the uh nasty little creature uh guests
and site people um true on the podcast so um without further ado i want to inaugurate the
ben and gave appreciation hour or the procrastinators appreciation hour uh and you know i don't even
want to be the only one to do this if you have something you appreciate about ben and gave call
into the podcast and talk about it yeah do it i agree it's really cringe and annoying maybe but
also i don't know i like it i agree you should tell me what you like about me yes it would be nice
tell me nice things keep me going in this dark world we live in i'm feeling particularly content
wet as they say um i'm feeling my my fire emblem streams have been fun i want to do more often
oh yeah because i somebody in the last stream did the tallied up it was crunchy crunchy spoon
tallied up um the the average time to beat all fire emblem games and it was like 600 something
hours and if i played like five hours uh during one stream like per week it would take like multiple
years to play them all i think some some some big number that was like uh you know i could probably
do more than one stream a week i don't know when though uh but at the moment Clarissa is taking
priority yeah for the foreseeable future so i don't know i but like i'm i'm i'm enjoying being more
doing of stuff it's very good to be doing stuff um yeah i'm feeling i mean i'm not like
i haven't been drawing but i have been getting stuff done lately for what feels like the first
time in a while and that's exciting um so yeah it's pretty wet yeah moist yeah when it rains at
course yeah and i'm and i'm drenched i'm soaking wet uh right now okay next one is called pcp
appreciation gib coming back to stream um it's it's an it's extra i think prince has put his money
where his mouth is and has actually submitted some items of appreciation so let's go three two one go
back okay okay uh huh what what happened what was that that sounded like a little like a little
gibbism was that me i didn't sound like me i don't think it was you i think it was but it sounded
like a gibbism well i remember saying back when i got back from a break but that doesn't sound
like me no listen to it i i'm not sure i feel like i feel like i feel like it's an impersonation
of you oh this is just meant to appreciate like what you say when you get back to a stream
oh but hey i guess i did say well the next one is ben coming back to a stream uh so maybe these
are partner content okay oh no it's 30 seconds yeah i don't know three two one go
all right let's start again with the stream okay uh let's get started
oh is there is there even a reason to go on
oh oh is there even a reason to go on can i do can i do it can i do this
oh god i don't know i don't know okay let's just oh let's just start okay
i mean first of all true second second of all i mean that's a bit is exacerbated by the fact
that i was streaming battle network uh blivvy and you were there okay something something nice
i was there right i was there for a little bit yeah you were there maybe you weren't there
did i already ask were you there when gamers tavern gave me those maps did i say that already
uh i think you tried asking a question like 40 minutes ago when she was talking maybe that's
what the question was well yeah okay so so so battle network is really annoying because there's
so many random battles and it's really hard to navigate the maps and you get lost really easily
and i don't know where i'm going and it's honestly it's kind of a nightmare but during this during
the last stream on friday gamers tavern uh messaged me a link to a zip file that had all
the in-game maps in it so now i can just look at the maps and know where to go and it's genuinely
i feel like this is going to cut my play time in half and it makes me like so much less annoyed
by it like it's it's a really great uh help so you know i probably was whinging a lot you
have cheated the game and yourself you have learned nothing you have gained nothing yes
and i'm so happy and i i probably was whinging a lot because the game um was really being a
book with its pages stuck together for a while there uh i was only in the stream for like 20
minutes i popped in mentioned the the nate thing and then stuck around for a little bit and talked
about my teeth rotting away oh yes yes i remember wait was that in the stream that you were i remember
you mentioned in your those those those those in the stream chat yeah i was just typing on twitch
right right right right um yes and then so again i gotta thank thank you for alerting me
what a turncoat trader a backstabber natus he wouldn't that he wouldn't raid me you know i
appreciate to know it's better than i know you know it's better than i know so i can so i can
just deal with um uh next one is called pcp appreciation bonus uh and it is right here
we've only got like three more by the way uh three two one go
and now as an added bonus here are two important famous quotes from internet celebrities give
and take and ben saint from ben saint you're high you've smoked the weed and now you're high
then saint 2021 now from give and take
life is a mistake don't quote me on that give and take
hey good one hey that was that was a winner that was a winner the god i got you okay next
how do you how do you come up with this stuff kid i don't know i don't know where does it where
do you get it i got a gift uh i got a gift for the gab gift of death uh gift of the kebab
i'm hungry next one is uh an image let's look at it wake up then it's time for your six hour
long day to announce is that my nagging bitch what it is
who is this is this i think it's you i think it's supposed to be you i don't know what is that
person really knows what you look like what's going on with your hair yeah i've got two sets
of hair i got a my purple my green hair and like a an afro wig as well looks like you got those russian
but like three of them i'm sorry this this one's really getting me because it really
it really do be like that though it really do be like that though maybe you think about it okay next
one is um wait okay actually the next one is like a google search link it's design a spider man
and then this is design a spider man and then this is the link
search spider man plus oc yeah this is just a google search for spider man oc
i mean how do i type this into google um
i mean yeah i see a bunch of them that's just is there something specific no
does ben stain just gonna jump out at me i don't think so
honestly these spider man oc's they don't they don't buck enough of the trend nothing nothing
too interesting it's popping up just like oh what if i what if i was a green i don't even see a green
spider man i see i see oh i see a green uh well he's not a spider man he's a venom exactly what
have evenoms but what what creatures have been symbiots symbiots too many of these are red you
gotta you gotta branch out you gotta you gotta be like uh oh i'm this particular breed of spider
from from south america this it's orange and and like with gold stripes and it's like oh it's cool
no all these people are just doing what if i was spider man okay i don't know what if i was wearing
the same costume you know what the what i saw this one i don't really care about the costume i just
think the girl's cute sure looks like rio co i'm gonna say it terrible voicemail terrible voicemail
not not a lot pretty not a lot going on here not even a voice in this one uh the next one is the
last one and it's called important psa uh from president at usa.gov uh three two one three two one
go you ben did you already explode into a fit of righteous very overnight not rating you and
still not having delivered the ovea eight or six many times if not please proceed to do so now
and feel free to implicate tom and how he deserves everything bad that's happening to him
into your unbridled rage fit as well honestly these people are pathetic losers said
sad that's kind of a terrible donald trump a i voice i've heard better yeah way better ones
that was it was it had to be like deliberately bad because that like sucks a lot no i mean
the i don't know because there was the the voice girl from last week was a pcp 500 that was not me
alizar seemed to think it was me he was like hey do you have that one i'm like no i didn't do that
one i did the other nate ones my nate was better but i also had probably had better training data
for it because i i still have every and i only have this for nate every like wave cleaned up
like pristine like fully background noise do you have that from when you were the pcp editor is
that why yes i see i also have all the voicemails from back then because it's always fun to like
take an old voicemail and fuck with it and then you won't recognize my voice this is why it's not me
we've given over our voices to oblivion fault to train ai's on and create create content out of
and just remix i only do it with public figures and nate people people people that i know personally
i won't do it with unless they explicitly ask me to and enthusiastically consent to uh being
turned into a fucking meme um i mean uh i am cool with it as long as it's funny is if it's funny
anything goes um and i'll decide that's that's that's what i that's how i try and that's how i
try and operate yeah yeah oh shit i guess i did do your voice band i forgot yeah i thought so it
was just fine uh hey that was the last voicemail that's it we're done oh wow get to the end um that
is the end well uh i mean hey the floor is open um let's let's let's talk about stuff let's talk
about our feeling let's talk the episode how do we feel about this episode let's review it's like
five hours long it is four and a half especially if you talk about a piece a single yeah if we do
one if we do one piece after this we're gonna we're gonna hit five hours no problem that that whole
section where i'm just talking shit constantly that's that's gonna be if we gotta cut that then
yeah i'll cut out a big chunk of it lamal okay fair enough uh yeah i'm look for that in a bonus
compilation i guess come in soonish whenever that whenever that happens um
well what do we think are we gonna if we call it give do you want to do one piece after the
bleeding ball takes off yeah my my husband kai just came in my husband my husband he just he
just kissed me on the forehead and and poked my shoulder gently and smiled at me i think he wants
to hang out with me i think i'll be i think i'll be leaving too i'm the you don't want to talk about
one piece with us cheesy ben hates it when people have loving relationships you know i kind of do
oh i see okay gotcha all right well go reads mcpegliacci read mcpegliacci got by the time
this episode's drop act two should be started on twitter or you can just go on my instagram
because i probably just have all of act two there elizard please put please put a time stamp in
when we start talking about one piece uh uh thanks for being on cheesy and oblivion fall
i had a great time as always i was a blast uh uh uh appreciate it and uh you know have a nice life
idiots see you never all right yeah okay see ya bye guys all right bye guys thank you thank you for
the podcast coming back in yeah okay love you all right let me let me hate those two i hate them
it's the joke every first and i hate as soon as somebody leaves it's funny to say i hate them
i hate those guys that son of a bitch bitch bitch son of a bitch uh let's come let's pull up uh the
word the one piece chapter so are we on chapter 10 75 is that the one mm-hmm okay okay so we got
labo phase death game labo yeah and there is a vega vega punk on the cover gora say granted an
audience with the five elders due to scientific genius so he won the scientist competition
with the bubble tanks i guess and then mm-hmm you got to speak to them gotcha makes sense to me
oh i see when the screen dies it becomes the flag of a finland or whatever
that's um that's a joke that's a joke i just made about this panel right here
oh it's scotland i don't yeah i'm sure finland is a right angle top left uh no is scotland the
blue the blue and white yeah diagonal okay yeah some andrew's cross or something yes yeah the
saint andrew's cross is the is the diagonal one right they can't leave because the lasers will
shoot them right that's still happening uh yes the lasers will shoot them because the control thingy
is offline okay organoid artificial human you guys can create organs i thought vega punk got
chopped into pieces what okay well what are you confused about well i don't know are they
she's they're are they are they are they looking at like the seraphim are these like seraphim being
made in these tanks here like they look like these weird blobs i think they're not seraphim they're
just sort of like scientific um they're in the laboratory so there's like oh there's all these
different things not just the seraphim and they're looking at like the the ability to create or the
organs for like surgery transplants and choppers like wow medical science is amazing you can that's
so cool my my translation said it's an organoid an organoid had an asterisk and a translator
note that said artificial human so i'm yeah i don't know it sounded like she was saying they're
just growing a human in there uh but i'm i mean chopper says they can you can grow new organs
that's i get the sense that this part is like kuznami earlier it was like oh you can create
diamonds um they're like learning the value of science i guess yeah learning learning all about
the important lesson that science is the future and the future is cool the camera feeds keep going
scottish one after they just keep going scottish yeah so they've they've split up okay they've split
up into to look for dr vega punk for stella and we know that he's with bonnie in the kuma room
ha ha kuma kuma mm-hmm a bubble gun these strong bubbles can reflect anything ah just like just
like kuma's just like the pacifist's bubble shield hmm just like bubble-based technology
just like gomo gomo fulsen yes yes the most powerful technique it's an attack that bounces
things back hmm i didn't realize that the the vega punk the the eating and sleeping and pooping
vega punk is like a giant i didn't realize she was yeah i i don't think you ever saw her from like
next to someone else yeah lying down with like smaller robots i assumed there was very tiny
robots all around her but no she's just really big yeah it's still so fucking weird that they all
feel the satisfied the satisfaction of taking a shit after she does do they do they all feel this
i think so i think that was like the introduction to us like she i'm hooked and they were like
ah finally she is like she like feels the satisfaction for all of them like she
is the one that handles all the eating and the pooping and the sleeping and she's just like
oh i love it oh i forget i don't remember if they comment that like oh yep i feel that other
self is taking a shit and i'm a big fan i guess that would be weird it's pretty it is weird uh
okay the Pythagoras is head because his little feet yeah his little
guys little feet oh no okay it's the star eye
okay stop york don't get any closer i don't know she has been turned to two stones she is
dead why can she shoot a laser is it just because she's got pacifista laser technology
pretty sure that's that's why yeah oh beam beam is it like based on kizaru fruit is that
i don't know i don't i just imagine that i mean it looks like it in the anime it looks exactly like
like kizaru is uh what is it what is it the pika pika fruit i can't remember the name but yeah
sounds all right um i think it's pika pika i don't think they ever say the the pacifista
just have lasers and then frankie learns how to make a laser so i think it's just a science thing
frankie finds vega punks like um old lab in the two-year timeskip and he learns a bunch of vega
punk stuff and one of the things he learns is how to make a laser beam just like the pacifistas did
and then he comes back and he do and he does a little beam and everyone's like oh cool frankie
you're so much better i suppose lasers are just a thing you can make in in science yeah i made a
laser beam one time out of a fluorescent tube but i did it no didn't not true actually this
okay the proportions on this kuma are like really stupid look how stupid he looks uh this one right
here yeah he looks really dumb i mean he's a child he's just a kid he's just a boy oh it's
wait a minute yeah but they're all children right hold on a second no no okay i thought that this one
this one i thought was an adult like this he was made first and i thought it was just like the ones
that just woke up are the kids because didn't we see kuma didn't we see child kuma in in the memory
bubble and he didn't look like this uh no but we don't know like we don't know exactly how their
model i mean i picked up that they're like oh the seraphim are children and therefore his bigger hit
means that he's like younger than his adult self yeah he doesn't he doesn't have quite the
jawline yet and he's sort of softer looking yeah i guess yeah maybe this is just like him as like a
teenager or like an adolescent whereas the one we saw in the memory was like little boy little boy
but he looked he looked like a completely different little boy he did i guess it's the hat and the
eyes being like white that changes it a lot it's the jaw it's the yeah him wearing the hat
and the and the chin he has some chin here he had no chin in the memory okay okay i gotta read
so so who ordered the pacifistas to do this the seraphim the seraphim
i
i think the the only reason oh the it's oh it says here the one that who gave this command was
vega punk if my orders are being obeyed then i mean okay it must be by the original vega punk
which is like hmm it's a little little sus uh
because it wasn't because sentomaru outranks
the cp-zeros but it wasn't him and the only one that outranks sentomaru
is vega punk so if you're not listening to cp-zeros and then the gurus say above vega punk
then vega punk must have told them to do this right is that right yeah that's that's the only
explanation and the at least based on what he's saying here is that the vega punk prime the stella
said um kill everyone or at least they seem to be i see we don't know whether they're
fighting the straw hats necessarily because the straw hats are with different groups of people
with a different vega punk and also the cp-zero but i i don't know like what the hell could this
order be for i mean we've seen stella is just like a baby with bonnie and he seemed like he didn't
when would he have had time to give this order to the seraphim to commit
it war it's it's odd um because early on in the chapter there was like oh there's a mysterious
person there and we learned that it's the the seraphim walking around destroying cameras
so they don't want anyone to know and there have been like tiny hints that like the seraphim are not
like quite like the pacifista in that they're not totally robotic yeah they're like they have a bit
of humanity in them zoro felt something when he was fighting me hawk yeah earlier yeah and so it's
like are they acting of their own volition at this point what would they want maybe i don't know
i don't know either could could the seraphim have been a failed experiment and it's like
shit's going wrong and they're just like you know what we don't want to be uh friends
actually i mean this kuma was obeying the cp-zero but maybe he was maybe he was just pretending the
whole time yeah maybe they're just maybe they're just going going rogue hey oh oh but but but number
one i forgot this part he says yeah between the communications blackout the barrier sealing us in
and the seraphim rebelling seems to look it seems like it's an elaborate plan somebody's trying to
kill us all so that could be vega punk who's who said be like who said that uh the number one
face oh shaka yeah shaka yeah i see him right at the end like he he says like yeah because we don't
know who how the communications were blacked out we thought it was somebody else but like who else
is there like stella has been revealed to be now i although she's with vega punk maybe she still
isn't a now i and it's like a double ruse you mean you mean stussy stussy sorry yeah so many
in this chapter in this in this arc two
yeah yeah i mean i guess we're i guess we didn't recap the chapter we didn't recap last chapter
listen the last episode if you want to hear last chapter well i guess well no i mean like
you read it but we didn't really talk about every page no but yeah things are destroying the cameras
um shaka's like what's going on everybody's split up nami and brook are with the little guy
and they're finding like diamonds that are artificially generated and she's getting money eyes
belly eyes um chopper and robin are with the big big one
and they're and they're they're doing the classic like arc everyone split up and search for clues
sort of so that you can be in a different situation right different place so you can have a different
bath time time to pair up our characters in different combinations and see what kind of
chemistry they have together yeah classic and then classic bit so like everyone's splitting up
uh sanji says uh he'll be a dog for for us to see yep same that's that's same that's pretty funny
uh all right this this graph uh i'm a little bit unclear on what's being communicated here in this
uh oh and then food lady gets destroyed food lady gets completely obliterated she's turned
turned to stone kicked by uh amazon and then boahankov that's right this this like tower here
okay so this is like so they're in tower a and it looks like tower b and tower c have been like
blown up and and like has the the top of tower a has been like cut off i kind of don't remember
when that happened uh well it was just before the seraphim had been calmed down um if you remember
they got up there and then they started blowing shit up okay yeah because they were still with
cp0 um and then one of the vega punks i think it was the little guy he flew at them and he was like
wait stop and he just got the commander in time and then they all stopped but by that point
mihawk uh had sliced oh mihawk oh yeah hey and the other two had blown stuff up okay so it's like
doesn't mihawk uh doesn't mihawk have like a legendary blade so like is i wonder if is this
uh like child mihawk like he's got a similar looking sword i wonder if it's just like a replica
and like it's not as good i i would imagine it's not as good or just like it's made of
you know it's it's comparable maybe yeah i mean this guy's got like world government money could
probably afford maybe they commission maybe they could duplicate maybe they could duplicate the
powers of like a cursed blade with uh with with science somehow like a hacky and flute infused
blade i mean they can make frickin anything else they want they copy these like legendary people
and their fruit powers like they it seems like yeah they can just fucking do anything
making a magic sword seems like a a trifle compared to all this so yeah wouldn't be too surprised
yeah so the main thing of the whole chapter is people are split up and then the seraphim are
evil we got uh bow handcock with usopp and frankie and then uh mihawk and kuma seraphim
are charging up trying to kill the cp zero guys and so they're fighting or they're about to fight
luffy and zoro uh we don't know where the gym bay one is yeah he is not pictured
yeah i think there's only those four
uh so are they they're they're all in like separate towers right or are they just on
different they have towers c floor three tower b floor two tower a floor two tower a floor two
all right they started in tower a floor three building c third floor
all right we're yeah that's setting up this for stuff yeah this is starting to get a little
bit like wano like okay the floating city is up here and then there's like a tunnel down here and
like the the magma is like going down through the thing and it's going to hit the weapon store
which is down below everything even when oda does these little maps with labels for all
these different sections and then says you know when you cut to a different uh situation with
different characters and there's a little box saying oh this is the left side of the great
hall or something um i'm like i cannot understand what that is i can't hold it in my mind all at
the same time it's it's it's better on the anime because like they have like little animations for
little floating heads that move here and there in fact i did that in bell shape i remember
doing a little bell shape one of those because i liked it i see yeah i can get that image
all right well i mean i i think i've um i think i've pretty much got to handle on what happens
this chapter oh he's not oh yeah yeah yeah yeah this one this map it's like dare they all are
i remember there was uh yes so coherent a lot going on oh yeah oh right bell jake was good
action i i forgot bell jake was kind of cool actually hmm now i remember bell jake when's bell jake
too you know once i finish Clarissa i think bell jake two is the next like thing people want to see
so i'll probably work on it then i think um i think this week i should probably
having finished a bunch of other stuff i think my work this week is probably gonna be uh the
the pcp website and um yeah i should probably get started on on bscapades and pick that up i
should actually like get to it i guess i haven't really even touched it it's all been just it's
all been talk so far um i have to do something about that uh yeah too hard so hard but i'm
how fast do you think you can make what however many panels you're thinking of
i i i don't really know how many i'm thinking like drawing it is like is kind of secondary
to us thinking up what is gonna happen wait say what for for bscapades like drawing it isn't that
strenuous it's more like trying to keep everything in your head like where the story's going and
writing the most the most daunting part is that i have to go back and i have to reread it to remember
like where i was and like what was going on and and recall like what i was gonna have happen next
i've kind of forgotten and lost the the plot so i just have to do that and and until then i
don't even remember like what the plan was i have to figure it out uh and so i yeah i don't even know
i don't even know how how long the like next chunk is gonna be
ah but i fortunately it's on my website so i can just go and read it all there
and i'm sure i'll take it pick it right back up yeah actually drawing the pages is not that hard
especially if i kind of issue the like gifs thing because like i mean i was doing the gif
animated like that's not really that necessary for like a pdf version that wouldn't carry
over so yeah it's not it's not that important if there's something i really want to animate like
i can do an animated panel it should be like check out the animated version here dummy dummy idiot
stupid why are you reading this on a static format nerd check it out on the worldwide web
whoa whoa what all right to to cap off one piece because we finished talking about it um
and then the cp0 are gonna team up looks like the straw hats in order to fight the seraphim
we're just gonna be up a little bit of a hijink i think uh they don't like to look oh man how
quickly how quickly the turntables enemies become allies it's my favorite trope to lovers yeah um
it's funny because it's like luci was always such a you know back in the day that was like
well captain smoker he's the bad guy but then you beat you beat him or like you're more powerful
and he run away and he's like ah those dang straw hats but he sort of respects them and it's like
yeah you know what this smoker guy is not so bad but then there's luci and he's like this guy is a
murderer killing she has a real fucking sicko yeah there's no way this guy could have a vegeta
moment but here we are where he's forced to be friendly i mean he's still a i mean i guess he's
still a bad guy but you know he's definitely still a bad guy we need all the help we can get against
these he's he's not as bloodthirsty as he used to be he is he's just sort of like i mean i haven't
seen anything to suggest that he's like nicer or no he's not nicer but like it's it's just the
it's just a vibe like forced forced camaraderie he's wearing white now he's wearing white now
he's a good guy but what about what about all that white guilt yeah true yeah never mind
that's much much much better much better way to interpret it well i don't know i think that's
it that's all i have to say about it the one thing i have to mention about okay the this chapter
two panels that look exactly the same it's when i think it's lila uh is screaming
yeah she's like she's like what a seraphim why are you here you scroll down a bit and she's like
quit joking around we don't stand a chance it's exactly the same oh my god angle yeah they do
she's just maybe it's just like yelling and i i know why it's that way it's because her eyes
are covered on that one side of her face so you have to show her from that angle when
you show her saying anything and she's also still scared and shocked so she's screaming and it's the
same face and it's the same angle it's just like i guess she's screaming louder in the second one
it's just like a little bit louder you've got to do something to differentiate it it's funny
yeah it's very it's very similar true you make a guess lilith is cool lilith looks awesome her hair
rules her jacket is yeah they're so cool all of this all of the so fucking cool like lilith especially
and generally the outfits in this arc are amazing yeah i love them they're all just funny and cool
but also a little bit like unique and uh fresh yeah it feels a little bit like wasteful sometimes
when it's like man all this cool shit and it's like you never really get a chance to like take it in
you know oh to just make so much good shit all the time so many secondary tertiary characters
that just got funny cool designs that are really cool and you see them for one chapter or two
chapters and then they're just never again seen well well but then there's like hundreds upon
hundreds of characters that are just really good the more it goes on the more you keep seeing these
old characters that were seen like one time and it's like oh they're back like oh what are let's
check in on what they're up to like oh they're like you know at uh marriage or oh they were at the
reverie or oh they're like working inside the world government or they're in the marines trying to do
something or they're on a secret mission or whatever they'll be like a throwaway character
like that and then put so many of them end up like brought back and recycled in some weird new
context and it's cool when you you know like uh you see a guy that you had he's like oh i totally
forgot that that was a character but he's back yeah uh it's great i love it
i guess there's not like a lot going on in this chapter there's no there's not like a lot of
revelations there's a question though who the fuck just fucking is vega punk bad now is vega
punk betray us i'm trying to think if there's a likelihood that he is bad because it's like he's
working with the world government but he knows the world government wants to kill him and he's
siding with the store has to get him out of there why would he kill him i feel like there's some
other mysterious third party that is actually here narratively i think if vega punk were evil
they would not have the characters questioning like wait a minute is vega punk the one who's
doing this like yeah yeah probably not because we're wondering about it i think it's it's a
potential misdirect to have the mysterious person going around destroying the cameras be the seraphim
because it's sort of implied that there is actually a another third party like unknown
person here doing these things but they're not the seraphim maybe they can talk to the seraphim
maybe it's a fucking maybe the goro say teleported in because he's just like super strong
and he's just in there so you do you think there is a third party or do you think it's
just one of the seraphim like maybe it's the jinbei seraphim who is not around maybe he's the one
doing it and the seraphim have gone rogue well either the seraphim have gone rogue for some
reason or another they decided to have their own thoughts and feelings and they've chosen this path
or foolishly yeah or they are being controlled by either vega punk who is uh for some reason
telling them to do this or a goro say which is impossible i think um or you know what it could
be i feel like this would be kind of unsatisfying because it's just sort of like building up a
mystery for no payoff like maybe it's a mistake in the programming and vega punk's like oh shit
oh jeez uh i didn't mean for that to happen let me quick this button uh now that now they've
calmed down again it's like i already did that he just was careless i was like oh i forgot to
carry the one like whoops like it could be funny but like yeah hmm yeah man
yeah i think i think it's a bit of a letdown if that's the reason
i kind of i'm kind of going with the seraphim are going rogue and they're just kind of decided
to do their own thing and they're they're they're they're they're making a break for it they're
hatching a plan that seems like what is has been suggested by all the oh there's some humanity in
you yada yada yeah that's what i'm going for yeah that's the chapter uh all right are we done
i think so i think that's all i have to say about this chapter um and we've been going for
five hours now so i'm really hungry so i'm probably very hungry as well uh and i'm also hung
over did i mention i'm hung over just a little bit just a tiny bit had a couple of seltzers
and then i forgot to hydrate before bed so that's rough but it's terrible it's that's that's x i know
i know it's my own it's my own fault it's my own doing um thanks for listening listeners um thanks
for reading one piece uh because it's a good comic and thanks for reading a gun smoke because it's a
good comic as well huh thanks for reading Clarissa gun smoke as well yes yes a better comic
because it's got a Clarissa gun smoke in it all right uh all right let's uh let's get out of here
um uh anything else before we end patreon.com slash the procrastinators yeah bonus stuff will
come out every now and then and you can hear it when it does the secret conversation cut out a whole
fuck ton of stuff this recording yeah it was juicy but not public which will surface eventually
in bonus episode form at some point um all right all right that's it everybody thanks again uh
patron us um watch our streams twitch.tv slash st comics twitch.tv slash give and take yes okay
goodbye