I'm gonna do it, Jenae. I'm gonna hit record, Jenae. No, Forrest.
I got B-platform, Jenae. I'm just trying to answer the JQ, Jenae, and they're taking down my videos.
Oh no, Gab's getting taken off of Patreon, Jenae. They're coming after the alt-tech media, Jenae.
Hello everyone, and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I'm the best guy ever. Today we're joined by Tom Oliver.
Uh, I'm too hardcore for social media. Find me on gab.com and mines.com and bitchute and follow my hot political takes there. Thank you very much.
Damn, pioneer. Uh, we've got Munchy for this hat.
You know, sometimes we like to fake hype on the show to see more entertaining than we actually are, but I'm gonna tell you right now, I'm a hopped up on sugar right now, and I just wanna wiggle.
I'm not, like, hyped up, like, oh my god, guys, like, get inspired. I just wanna, like, wiggle and, like, run. You ever get it? I just wanna, you ever just get hopped up on sugar and just wanna run.
Yes, I do know that. I did my run at 2am last night. Do you have any familiarity with this gif, this meme in the Kingdom Hearts community of Kyrie Wiggling from the manga?
No, no, I have no idea. I just like to wiggle on my own accord. I don't follow trends like you do.
Well, that's too bad. I'm gonna post this in the chat so everyone can observe Kyrie's wiggling. Please enjoy. We'll put it in the show notes.
How did you get that so fast? It was on my desktop, ready to go, as always.
Yeah.
Look at her go. Goddamn, she's killing it. Hold on. She's getting it, boys.
Wait, did you post it in the main chat?
Yeah.
No, you didn't. You posted it in your own chat.
Speak with your words using audio form.
Okay, I'm actually gonna put in the gross disgusting link thing so we can link it later.
Anyway, hey, Ben.
What's up?
Oh, uh...
Look at this Kyrie. What do you think?
She's not wiggling. She's wibbling.
Hello, everyone.
Is that even related?
Here we go.
The Urban Dictionary term for a wibble.
A wibble. We gotta look up wibble.
Have you guys heard, have you guys heard of the calls, the calls going out there for a return to form?
The call to adventure.
A return to our great roots on UrbanDictionary.com.
Oh, I have not heard anyone say that.
Oh, you mean have I heard the song of the people?
You mean have I heard the Zeitgeist?
That's right. That's right.
No.
By the way, just so you know, I looked up wibble, which is what Kyrie's doing in this thing, on UrbanDictionary.com.
Oh, God.
And apparently, alright, wibble, the top definition is, quote,
The word used by Rowan Atkinson in Blackadder goes forth to denote a state of insanity.
The scene, he puts pencils up his nose and repeats wibble, wibble in order to get sent home from the trenches.
Wait.
And then.
That's what wibble means to us.
And then, wibbly, wobbly, timey, wimey stuff was also invented by Blackadder.
I love the first track on Alternia Bound entitled, A Risen Anew.
You guys, you guys ever watch us?
Hey, you guys ever watch Blackadder?
You know, I want to watch it again, but not for a long time, not for a long time.
I liked it.
I had no idea what that was.
As a kid.
It is a British comedy about, like, Elizabethan nobles, where Mr. Bean plays this, like, incompetent nobleman named Blackadder.
And it's about-
Fuckin' Cox is on there, too, right?
Hugh Laurie?
Hugh Laurie. I think he's on there, if I'm wrong.
Could be. I forgot about that.
You know who, you know, my friend, John, aka Dwoob,
he mentioned-
Wait a minute, Ben.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
John is Dwoob?
You didn't know John is Dwoob?
I had no fucking idea.
Well, alright.
Who'd you think Dwoob was?
I just thought it was some fucking asshole.
Plant Roddy Fucker's Copco's like the rest of the assholes.
No, Dwoob is John.
Bullshit.
Yeah.
But I'm surprised you didn't know.
But he referenced a show that I had not-
Remember Red Green?
Yeah, of course.
Canadian-
Yeah, the Canadian fixer-upper skit comedy.
He was talking about like a-
We're talking about like all our mouse traps.
So we got mouse traps in my house.
We have been slaughtering my left and right.
It has been a mouse-genice-
No, listen.
I believe you.
Do you know that I killed them with a frying pan?
Did I talk about this?
I saw that.
Oh my god, that's what that story was about.
Shit.
Well, alright.
No, I know.
Yeah, I killed a mouse with a-
I clobbered it with a frying pan.
Holy shit.
Yeah.
It was great.
Was it like running?
Was it running for its life, attempting to survive?
No.
Okay.
So I bought a bunch of mouse traps, like classical-looking-ass snap mouse traps.
None of them have caught anything.
They are almost useless, except-
Except for physical gag comedy bits, which I'm sure they're ripe for usage in that.
Well, they- alright.
So I heard one go off and I was like, oh my god, one of them actually caught something.
So I went and I looked, and no.
But there was a mouse next to the one that had gone off, and it seemed to be maybe stunned or something,
because it wasn't reacting to me at all.
So I was like, it's now or never before it fucking gets its wits back.
So I went and I grabbed a frying pan and I just smashed it.
Oh god.
In one clean clobber?
In one clean clobber.
You know, I thought maybe I hadn't hit it hard enough.
Like, I was afraid, I was afraid that, you know, as Dwarf Fortrait might put it,
that it would like explode in a pile of gore.
Okay.
But it didn't.
Yeah, yeah.
In fact, there was no visible injury at all, and I thought maybe I'd been too much of a fucking pussy and it hadn't died.
Didn't follow through.
But it kind of fell over and started scrabbling around.
And I was like, oh shit, I didn't get it.
But like, I went back, I went back at it, and no, it was dead.
It eventually slowed down and stopped.
I was like, oh, I guess I got it.
Oh god, that's morbid.
No, I was glad, because like, I was there.
How much HP did you get from that?
Unfortunately few, because I'm extremely high level.
I'm extremely powerful, Munchy.
So, you're like Rapunzel with that frying pan.
So I swept it up in a dustpan and dumped it in the trash.
Sure.
And this could be the start of a new career for you.
You could become an exterminator, but you only use traditional methods.
You just go in there with your bare hands.
With a frying pan.
With all I need is my frying pan.
You throw in flashbangs to stun them.
And then you go in there and you take care of them man to man, one on one.
Like they did the old school.
Oh my god, Ben's going to grow up to be the exterminator from Ant-Bully.
He's just going to walk up in Ant-Bully little kids into signing contracts
that they're way out of the jurisdiction to sign.
Then when they ask how long it's going to be,
you're just going to lie to the guard and take out your trusty drying pan.
And you're going to start beating the shit out of me and say,
oh, it'll be done within the hour.
Ant-Bully bonus episode.
After I had thrown it away, it occurred to me that maybe I had missed an opportunity.
And I had thought, what if I had somehow cured its pride?
No, what if I had somehow used some kind of chemical powder or something
to remove its flesh, to desiccate its flesh and collect its skull,
clean its skull and display it.
What if we started displaying all the skulls?
And now you have a pile of mouse skulls right next to your chair.
I'm thinking we prop them up on toothpicks just kind of around the house.
You got to display them to instill fear into the populace remaining in the house.
That's right, as totems.
As totems.
Did you know your skill?
I actually looked it up and I thought, how would you do that?
Would you boil it first?
Boil the flesh off or something?
And I was looking at some site and it had a graph.
There was a graph of what condition is the carcass in
and cross-reference with what method of flesh removal
and cleaning of the skull would you employ.
And all conditions said, do not boil.
Do not boil the flesh off of it.
Alright.
I just did some quick research myself by googling how to clean the skull.
And I discovered the delightful term skeletonization,
which I'm going to do to you right after this podcast.
They're not rats, they're mice.
They're pretty small.
And actually I haven't seen them.
I spooked them off.
I'd been seeing them around.
I got these traps and I was like, man, if I'm seeing a couple of mice,
that must mean there's like thousands.
That must mean they're everywhere and they're just hiding themselves really well.
And I'm only seeing.
But we've only killed maybe like five or six,
but I haven't seen them in days.
Maybe we got the most.
Maybe we fucking got them.
The downstairs neighbors have-
I don't know how mice work.
They're not like bugs or anything.
The downstairs neighbors have it much worse.
I mean, I haven't seen it,
but apparently they're all over the place in the downstairs.
Yeah, and they're going to stick to the ground.
And there's some shit going on where the guy downstairs has said,
like I'm not paying rent until the landlord takes care of it
and the landlord tried to evict them for it,
but like obviously that's not going to work.
So there's a whole like legal thing going on downstairs.
But since the mouse problem is not that bad up here,
we've just kind of ignored it.
Pests are the number one biggest,
like I can't believe in literal 2018 current year,
we're still dealing with like pests.
Yeah.
Like when I moved out to Ohio,
the first place I lived in-
It seems cartoonish.
Having a mouse problem in your house
seems like a problem that like a cartoon kid,
like Mr. Bean would have a mouse that he would be running around
like a hammer trying to kill or something.
And he would keep running into frying pans
like in the kitchen.
Indeed.
And like the mouse would jump on his face
and he would whack himself with a frying pan
trying to get it.
Yep.
As it evolved, like pure energy,
you know, internet denizen,
I feel like I shouldn't have to deal with this,
but in my last like two apartments,
Roaches have been like a more president's issue,
which never happened in Massachusetts,
but I don't know if Roaches are more of a Midwest thing.
Externator came by and said that he caught a crab
in a glue trap one time.
A crab?
He showed me a picture.
He was like, do you take this out?
And he showed me a picture of his-
Glue traps are these like sort of like paper squares
that you just put out and the idea is that mice
will just step in them and then they can't escape
and they starve to death or whatever.
Run.
Pretty brutal.
But it's fucking genocide, so whatever.
And then he showed me a picture and like, yeah,
like a large crab, like several inches across.
And he said that he said that it was like in a business
like near like, like a back bay, like near the ocean,
kind of.
So it wasn't like totally ridiculous that a crab
might have made it that far,
but still caught a fucking big old crab in his glue trap.
Speaking of the glue trap,
so he put a glue trap out at my house
and we did, because there was a mouse
running around in the house.
We had to get it.
You mean the house you're at now?
No, my parents' house when I was still there.
Yeah.
And we were all panicked because we knew that
when my mom came home,
if a mouse was still there, she would flip shit
and we wouldn't hear the end of it for days.
So it's like, all right, this mouse has to be gone
within the hour or we're all fucked
for the next like two weeks.
So we put out a glue trap and put some peanut butter on it
because you had to get the sucker out there
and you go for the peanut butter and you get fucked.
And he did like instantly.
And it was just there like struggling for like 20 minutes
and I felt really bad about it.
So I did like, I did the opposite.
Like Vendiz did the genocide run on Undertale
and I did, I did the pacifist run
because I just like took it and I brought it outside
and I kind of like took a little like,
like butter knife and kind of scooped its leg out
just as like, get out of here, you fucking piece of shit.
You're out of the house.
Wait, hadn't you already caught it in the trap?
I caught it in the glue trap.
I caught it in the glue trap,
but only one of its legs was caught in the glue trap.
So it was like scurrying around with one leg caught
slowly dragging this whole thing behind it.
And I was like, I'm not going to let you die like this.
So I brought it out and I kind of like freed its leg
and was like, you're fine, just get out of here.
I definitely skew towards the top of the spectrum.
If you're a deep core Munchie fan,
then you will know my, you know, time-tested catchphrase,
Silverfish are allies.
Yes, of course.
And this stems from my childhood obsession with Silverfish
and my childhood home that I grew up in.
There was a rampant Silverfish like infestation.
By the way, with Silverfish,
aka house centipedes, right?
Like the ones with lots and lots of legs that look like frilly.
Yeah, that look like skyfish.
They have like six legs, you know, here.
I'll get you a picture of it as Silverfish.
This is an extremely like, you know, high definition photo.
I'm thinking of, I'm thinking of something that I grew up,
or not grew, that I used to call a Silverfish,
but which turns out is actually called a house centipede.
Yeah, we had tons of those in the house.
I saw one yesterday and I was very upset by it.
I guess I hate them, but everyone else was like,
No, I think they're cute.
No, dude, they eat, they eat worse bugs.
And I'm like, no, they are the worst bug of all.
That's why they eat the other ones.
Yeah.
And then we had to get like a pest control guy
to like basically constantly just come back and destroy them.
I eventually just got accustomed to them.
And I would like leave a little, like a bit of like some video game,
like cover paper there, like some manual paper.
I would just rip up some like New Super Mario Bros. 64 DS manuals.
How I love that game.
I'd just leave in the bathtub for my allies to eat.
And they would eventually become, to recognize me as their master.
And they, I would just be able to like, you know,
Hang out with them.
Munchy becoming a real life Pokemon trainer.
No, exactly.
Don't catch her Munchy wants to battle.
There can be, there can be no cooperation with the bugs.
There can be, there can be, there can be only war.
There can be only war between us.
But I like carrots and peppers and bugs.
Listen, listen.
Shout out if you get the reference.
If you're some fucking song fan, you know, you pitched yourself,
we've seen the song of the hedgehog getting a brawl,
or you're some fucking proud fancy head,
and you were so happy when Cloud got in.
Think about how happy I was when Silverfish got into Minecraft,
the most wholesome, you know, epic gaming mashup of all time.
And they were representing my brand, my favorite series, Silverfish,
The Bug from Real Life.
I was so ecstatic.
Ugh.
It was great.
Well, that's nice.
We, me, remember Earwigs?
Remember Earwigs?
I do.
We had Earwigs by the pool when we were kids.
They were terrible.
They were getting your shoes.
You had to shake out, you had to shake your shoes
to make sure no Earwigs had gotten in.
I didn't mind them that much.
I think they're much less disgusting.
Have you guys ever had fleas?
Then four, for example, a house centipede.
As a little kid, as a little kid I did have,
I think we both got lice, Nate.
I remember having to shampoo with some like special shampoo
because I had lice.
Oh, I hate all of this.
This is the worst.
But you know, as a kid, as a little kid,
as a little kid it didn't gross me out
and I like, I barely even thought about it.
I was like, okay, mom says I got lice.
Well, I guess I'll just fucking shampoo
with this shampoo or whatever.
Yeah, yeah.
Back then I didn't mind much.
Didn't freak me out or anything.
It is pretty fucking gross in hindsight though.
Yeah.
Dude, I only had lice once in my life,
which I suppose makes sense due to the fact
that I'm 80% hair.
I got when I was in fourth graders
and then I was the talk of the town.
I was so fucking popular.
Everyone wanted to high five you.
Yeah, they were like, oh shit, you got lice?
Dude, I was like, I know.
It wasn't easy, but believe me,
I triumph over everything that I touch.
Cool.
It was so sick.
It was like getting a cast and everyone would be like,
oh man, can I sign your cast?
Everyone wanted to stay away from me,
but also whistled me from far away.
Like a cat call, or like a lice call if you would.
How bizarre.
No.
I mean, can you imagine having your friend have lice
and being like, oh man, I can pick out his hair
and get out of his creature?
No.
What?
Yeah.
It sounds like the worst thing ever, actually.
Yeah, as a five-year-old?
I mean, you know, however you roll.
I get that if you're a kid and you're too retarded to know
that that's awful, then maybe it wouldn't sound awful.
Okay, all right.
Yeah, all right.
That makes sense.
It was delicious.
They were delicious.
Hey, I've got a hard left turn of a topic here.
Can we say this?
I want to talk about bugs and pests.
That's good.
I just feel like we've said literally everything there was to say.
But here's what I got.
So yesterday, I finished my Nuzlocke.
It is complete.
Yeah.
And it's over.
A cameo.
That's true.
There was a cameo from The Saint, a.k.a. Ben.
I conquered.
Well, you know what?
I won't say what I did.
You can just go watch it for yourself, people.
It was really cool.
But here's what I wanted to say about it.
You thought it was good?
You enjoyed it?
Yeah, it was a lot of fun.
Yeah, it was great.
It was great.
The people went hog wild and they loved it.
They did.
Twitch.tv slash definitely best guy ever.
Go check it out.
There's a YouTube upload thing for it as well.
But here's what I wanted to say.
The experience of yesterday was very interesting.
And I think it was not totally new, but reminded me of something I haven't felt in a long time.
And it was that when I was younger, I used to do plays and shit and do musicals.
I haven't done it for quite a while.
But yesterday, doing this Twitch thing, there was around 200 people there.
And I actually used to get bigger numbers of viewers when I would stream on YouTube than I do on Twitch.
But what was interesting, what the difference was, this was a far more hype event going on yesterday.
And everybody was just more into it and freaking out and engaged.
And as we were doing it, as the whole event was happening, there was just a lot of energy.
There was a lot of fun.
And there was a real sense of, I don't know, community, I guess, going on.
And just hyping life.
I could feel life pulsing through my veins.
And then it finished.
It ended.
And then the turning off the stream and just sitting back and sitting there quietly.
It's just like when I'm watching a stream where something cool is happening and then it ends.
There's a great emptiness.
Beating a video game, especially with this, something I've been doing for like seven months.
Then I beat it.
And now it's like the journey is over.
Imagine shuffling out of the stadium after a good game or something.
Yeah.
Or imagine like, I don't know, you're fucking, I don't know, Bon Jovi or whoever.
And you go play on stage and you have thousands, tens of thousands, hundreds of thousands, whatever people cheer in.
Obviously smaller numbers here.
Same idea.
And then you're like, yeah, you're a god on the stage, right?
Everything's great.
And then it ends.
And then you go off stage and there's a guy's like, oh, you want a coffee?
You want me to get you a coffee?
You want me to like, I'll get you one?
Yeah, you're like, yeah, sure.
Okay.
And then he goes and you're just sitting there.
Yeah.
And you're like, yeah, I did a good job.
I did it.
But it's just quiet now.
It's just quiet now.
And sure it's a time to reflect, but that high, that high is gone.
And I'm just like, so this is why they do cocaine.
This is why they do cocaine, to get it back.
And I'm like, I totally get it.
I totally get it.
I mean, was it a bad experience?
Well, it sounds melancholy, right?
It sounds melancholy.
Yeah, it was definitely a melancholy feeling, which I've definitely felt to lesser extents,
like I was saying.
Would you say that you felt this way before, so insecure?
I would say so.
Owned.
Like when I was young, you know, doing plays and stuff, because like you'll go and you'll
practice for months and months, like every couple of days or whatever.
And then it's like, you know, you're getting close, you're doing dress rehearsals and shit
and you're like there every day working on stuff.
And then you do your last show and then it's over.
Everybody goes home and that's, yeah, you can look forward to your next thing.
There's all that.
But the sense of melancholy was palpable.
And I don't know, I just felt like I gained a greater understanding for like performers
and show people.
And I'm like, yeah, everybody says they're really retarded for like doing drugs to chase
a high.
But I think a lot of that's because we can't understand their perspective.
And I just felt like I get it more now.
That's incredibly interesting.
So you're a drug addict now is what you're telling us.
I would never do any drugs, but too strong.
Stay tuned for the best guy ever rehab arc in 2019.
We're looking forward to that.
I think that's something that's probably unique to live streams or I guess, you know, live performances.
I agree.
I would say I can't really imagine playing the same way when like a, you know, a big
video gets released, you know, which I have done.
Yeah, my fucking big smash videos got like hundreds of thousands of views, but it's a
totally different sensation.
It's not like an immediate, it's not like you were just performing and then the event is over.
It's been, you've been toiling over this for, you know, God knows how long, you know, weeks
at this point and you're divorced from the feeling of actually, you know, the Nate that
was recording or, you know, not in the smash videos, but you know, in, in, I don't know,
Gern Laganne part two, you're so far removed from the Nate who was doing that voiceover
and you know, who was acted in those bits.
It doesn't even feel like the same person.
It's not like you were acting really.
It was just you were, you know, you've been finalizing the act for, you know, months or
years, I guess in that case.
Those took six months to make or so I think.
That's really interesting.
I think I have only, because I'm not like a stream person, you know, that's not my trade,
but there's been very few times where I've sort of gotten the same scenario where it's
been a really successful stream.
There were a lot of people and it was really a hype moment.
The other thing that I could think about after that was just man.
Like, like I've done my work.
I, like I can now read, I can die with a smile.
Like I've completed everything that I need to complete and now it's just time for me
to rest and you know, not engage with anyone for like two weeks.
That's how it was after the flag referendum stream on RFCK, which everyone fucking went
bananas for and it was a great stream.
I still haven't, I still haven't seen it.
Really?
Well, yeah, everyone, everyone says that I should and I keep meaning to, but I haven't
gotten around to actually watching.
I don't know what, like I, having not seen it, it's very mysterious to me.
And like I wonder what it could, like what could even be about this stream that like
is so, I don't know, like it's clearly something.
There's clearly something to it, but I don't know.
Yeah, okay.
Tight.
Yeah.
Okay.
There's a lot of energy, a lot of voting going on, a lot of number tabulation.
Yeah.
That's what I'm saying.
That's what I'm talking about.
I think that's some old, munchy hyperactivity that doesn't really translate a lot nowadays
because I don't know.
Yeah.
I have mellowed down a little bit.
Wait, what do you mean nowadays?
That was like, that was like two weeks ago.
I'm saying, I'm saying that you don't really, like that, that's a sort of old brand of my
humor that you don't really see a whole lot.
That was resurfaced.
Oh, okay.
That's a modern day.
That's true.
It feels like a sort of like almost even a deagle nation-esque energy that I have for
a thing.
Yeah.
But you know, the biggest comparison for this whole thing, like the performance thing
definitely probably is the most accurate, but the one that's most familiar to me is
when you beat a big video game, specifically that took a ton of time, like a Final Fantasy
or, I don't know, JRPGs are probably the best example to take like 50 to 100 hours,
maybe longer.
You beat it and it's, you're happy that you won.
You're satisfied that you did it, but you're sad the journey is over.
Yeah.
That's what it was.
That's the biggest thing I think.
Yeah.
I have that.
Like, I unfortunately cannot relate as someone who doesn't like or play single-player games,
but I can relate in the sense of like finishing like series of things.
I just undertaken a massive, massive podcasting, I don't know, binge experience listening to
Mike Duncan's The History of Rome, and that was like a long, like 170-plus episode series,
and I just finished it earlier today.
And it's weird having this like series that has taken up like almost every waking hour
of my life when I'm not like editing something for like weeks, just now be gone.
And like, yeah, I guess I finished that.
It's like, it's like, where have my friends gone?
Yeah.
It's like when you beat Final Fantasy VII, it's like, oh, I don't get to hang out with
like Cloud and Tifa and like Yuffie anymore.
Oh, don't say like that.
You're going to make me fucking cry.
It's sad.
It's literally like they're dead because it's like you can have no more new experiences
with Cloud.
You can have no new experiences with these characters that you come accustomed to.
But Nate, when the remake comes out, you'll get all new experiences for $5.99 for DLC
expansion.
Like when am I going to get to see TTLMZ, the canonical team leader of my party, the
Gyarados, the MVP of the fucking run, and Gastrodon Prime, the legendary Doon Koon who
kicked everybody's ass and overcame all the odds.
You know, when am I going to get harassed by Russell the ghost again and you know, all
these, all these kooky, when am I going to go flying with Juicy Shack Meet the Noctowl,
my useless Pokemon whose only use is flying as my only surviving bird.
But you know, that's sad.
Well, Nate, well, as Tommy Wiseau might say, that's life, you know, that is, you know,
you gotta, you know, people, experiences and people and friends are all, you know, fleeting
and they're all, they all end.
I hope this doesn't come across unnecessary dick sucking, but you know what, here you
need to describe this.
I truly am not sorry, I guess, but you know, I kind of regret not getting on the Nate Nuzlocke
bandwagon because I, because I knew, I knew it was something special for a while now,
but it's just hard.
But I don't like follow the streams and I don't really know when they're happening
and I don't really, you know, necessarily have the time to tune into streams.
Yeah, that's, I do.
I do.
I feel like I should have.
Yeah, same, same, but I also realized that like, I mean, I don't, the time, it's a big
time investment, right?
It sure is.
That's like hundreds of hours of fucking content.
I guess about a hundred hours or so.
Yeah, yeah.
So yeah, I get it.
And also, let's not forget that a lot of those streams are lit, as everybody who is
there would say, it's like, I don't know, 50 to 60% of like looking at charts and updating
spreadsheets and like thinking and just grinding and raw grinding, which has become a great
meme that a lot of people enjoy.
But for the, for the true warriors, no need, bra, you know, everybody else who was in the
trenches, Russell, of course, like they suffered, they suffered the boredom of, I mean, we,
you know, we would just bitch and talk about life and stuff and just answer questions,
which is a lot of what many of those streams were while we grinded.
But I mean, the people now who were there, like they get to feel basically the vicarious
accomplishment and then, you know, the actual accomplishment, because a lot of them actually
contributed to strategy and thoughts and like what we did and stuff.
And so to those, like it's easy to look back now on what those guys did and be like, wow.
And you know, me too, like that was, that was so great.
I wish I'd been there, but it actually, there was a lot of, there was a lot of work, a lot
of downtime.
Well, you know, isn't that, isn't that just what any, isn't that what anything good is
like?
Yes, it is.
Like anything at the time seems like a slog or like gum.
Dude, like making the highlight.
Or just like work, but then like later you look back and you're like, actually that was
great.
At the time it was work.
Yes.
Because we remember the past fondly.
Every single fucking week, I would record arm retrieval and I would be like a time to
edit it.
It would be like the most, this show sucks.
No one is going to watch it.
There's no reason for me to do this.
It's just taking time away from other things.
One earth would I do it.
And arm retrieval is probably the most defining best thing I've ever done online, unironically.
Arm retrieval fan loves it, like with an unbelievable passion that I cannot even like understand.
I mean, look no farther than arm retrieval con three when like 11 people flew out just
to like talk to me about arm retrieval for like three hours.
Yeah.
That's how you know.
That's real shit.
That's real connection.
I think there's something like apart from the actual like quality of the streams that
makes it such a good experience to be a part of your streams.
I mean, yeah, absolutely.
I think there's a community sense.
Yeah.
A lot of people only see each other during these streams and they're like friends on
the streams kind of.
I think there's something so valuable that like I especially in life in my life of having
a sense of like being a part of a community and being there on the front lines when something
new releases.
There is no fucking greater joy in my life than I experienced seeing a new episode of
My Little Pony and being like, I can't wait to fucking talk about this hot new background
pony.
Can't wait to can't wait to hear the newest T-Bap.
Can't wait to see the latest T-Bap.
Of course.
This one.
Yeah.
It's so great.
Like I know there's a lot to be said about like the actual quality of a show or podcast
or whatever.
Being dampened by you know having pacing being broken up due to the fact that it releases
over weeks and it's not the ideal way to intake art in for art's sake.
But there is no doubt a ton of community joy that you reap from being a part of a fandom
or a community and releasing it to you know and watching it with your fellow community
ease.
This is the reason behind like the podcast has been going strong like in my life because
I've been reading it every week for like 15 years or whatever.
It's the community that keeps me really engaged and stuff.
I mean I'd read it no matter what but it enhances the experience so much to like have a new
chapter come out.
It's like a big thing.
It's like God drops a gift that like all these people expect and then we all get to
reap the benefits of in all these different ways with like a new episode of a show everybody's
watching or a new chapter of One Piece or you know or like the stuff we make maybe a
new episode of the fucking PCP that people gather around and have a community around
and enjoy.
Oh man I would pay money.
I would bribe people to have PCP listening parties.
That would be so cool to hear be a thing.
That would be pretty cool.
Like we could even pay someone to listen to this track.
It's great.
By the way maybe we should go to patreon.com slash the procrastinators and donate some
money there.
What do you think about that?
That makes sense.
I would never do something like that.
Especially in the Patreon page PU it stinks in there.
No sane person would.
By the way this is like this is the PCP viewers like you are aware of the many many many
bad things we've had to say about communities and fandoms and internet groups in general.
Just talking about making me kneel over and die.
But I think there's a lot of unspoken joys that are in those things that we made trash
talk a lot.
I mean if there wasn't why would we do any of it.
Yeah.
Right.
Why wouldn't we just kneel down and fucking commit ritual seppuku right here on the fucking
pavement.
I think we're really getting close to that.
Right here in the Walmart parking lot where I make my home.
Oh the silverfish fill that cardboard box.
They're by pillows at night.
They're allies Munchy.
Oh they're so fucking allies they are my friends they are my Pokemon I'm gonna name
them all.
I love them so much.
Is there a silverfish Pokemon?
I think there is.
Is it What's His Faces?
Yeah.
Wimpod.
I guess he's collected so much silverfish candies he can like he's getting ready to
evolve them.
It's gonna be something nuts.
Oh I can't wait for their community day to come Tom McCow is their community day to come
up.
I'm so excited.
I've talked about this a bit in various fan chats but I think something that is related
to what we've been talking about here that I want to do for my like for like my mental
health.
This is not a joke.
I want to get back on Tumblr because listen everyone has an idea of what Tumblr is like
in their mind like oh you know it's full of SJWs.
Like Tumblr is a community like any other website meaning that you can find those people
I don't see that people don't exist or they aren't even a majority but just don't follow
them.
I've been thinking about getting back on Tumblr too like I never made any headway on Tumblr
and I gave up really fast but like I didn't do anything there so like it's not that surprising
that nothing came of it but yeah it's just like it's just it's another platform where
a lot of people are and like it sure would be nice to fucking be on there.
Tom was always a big Tumblr guy wasn't he?
I mean just like posting there.
Yeah I mean I still use it.
I still have a Tumblr.
I want to say for other people who've never been on Tumblr it's so easy to follow like
exclusively alt-right people it's really really easy this is not like a homogenous society
or a community.
Yeah I mean if you follow me you follow an alt-right guy.
It's not just all SJWs.
It's so easy to like curate what you want to see and what you want to you know engage
with.
I guess in the same way.
I love content aggregators so much.
They are real good.
I guess in the same way that like as a 4chan guy I just shit on Reddit you know even though
I could be on you know my my what would be my home base r slash thedonald of course and
you know just be on there posting my MAGA hat memes and my you know you know all the
things all the things but instead I'm just going to say it's all Reddit skate guys.
Dude lol.
I'm going to keep that up as long as possible.
I guess I well not desperately I'm not this is not I'm not aching for this in my life
like I need it like I need it like I need my heroin shots my right fellow drug addicts
haha.
That's correct.
Yeah.
But it's I want to come to rehab Nate it's going to be good.
Nate get a heroin problem get a get a drug problem start chase that high you gotta chase
that magic dragon.
That will be a good narrative for the PCP I think that could be a good one so we can
definitely monetize that.
Oh next episode hey guys welcome to the PCP.
Welcome to a new episode I think you can snort like powdered heroin or whatever.
I'm going to inject paint okay I mean you can probably snort.
I want to do the eyeball injection style you know right that's what I want right to the
pupil dude.
You know hey I saw something the other day speaking of eyeball injections quick quick
aside on this where could I saw a YouTuber he said something like a hundred thousand
hundred twenty thousand subs I forget his name but his his claim to fame was that he's
like a tattoo slash body modification guy and all I'm saying is his he had a bunch tattoos
whatever his right eye the white of his eye had been tattooed blue and my first thought
was is this a sands reference is this a sands thing going I could not figure out if it was
or is not.
So he tattooed his fucking the white the white is the cornea right no is that a difference
no I forget the name of it.
Okay I mean I had met a guy in person who had tattooed his white's black but it's sclera
sclera yeah there you go there you go so he had tattooed like with a needle like with
a fucking like yeah I think they do it with a needle it's blue that doesn't live that
doesn't sound possible oh it's I met a man who he was the he said he was the most tattooed
man in the world at a tattoo convention in like somewhere in New York I think and he
had horns and shit under his skin on his head his whole body was covered in blue puzzle
pieces and the whites of his eyes the sclera were tattooed black and I just looked in this
man's eyes and was like that's a demon I'm gonna get into the tattoo community on Tumblr
I'm gonna make an OC called Tatlis based on Toothless from Helltrain and Dragon I've
made this joke two times before on the pcb by the way it's gonna be a returning joke
the the Tatlis brand will overcome all obstacles I bet that the Tatlis is like the one that
the most he's like he's like the pure virgin you know around everyone wants to wants to
adopt him as everyone wants a fresh skin yeah yeah he's like oh man I can give him his first
tattoo I can give him his first tattoo of cum dump right across his forehead that's you
know I'm gonna get him into our into our disgusting lifestyle of getting tats on fucking these
are these are the sins these are the sins we gotta we gotta get him in on or else we'll
feel or else we'll feel and we'll feel self-conscious about it if he's not doing it too that's probably
true mm-hmm all right let's do a left turn who else has got something going on all right
all right left turn left turn left turn no more um uh Pokemon go uh it's like I caught
a lot of caught a lot of tyrant not cut a lot a lot of arbitrage yesterday might go out
and get a couple more larvitar Michael and get a couple more dratini is I evolved my
fucking tyrant a tar yeah have his community a move he really did not have his community
a move well it wasn't his community day it was just generally community no I know but
you could get the community a move still maybe it's like a chance this I don't know I think
the game sucks I think that's the yeah that sounds right yeah yeah I don't really care
about that oh I've got a quick update I finally evolved my Scyther into a scissor I have I was
there meantime we're there in the call that's right did that I saw his name is Gurren he is
beautiful you are the version of Pokemon I was so emotional it's been years it's been years
literally years but I've done it man I've got I've got the Humphrey the shell gun he's got a
long way to go before he becomes or he becomes a salamence I tell you what what was his name
Humphrey Humphrey he's I've raised I've been walking with him since he was a since he was a
bag on you know I was very happy when he became a shell gun but it was like oh my god the road
the road ahead is so long and it's long it's long good luck we this can easily become like the
Pokemon go news segment because there's I mean yeah fucking there's some crazy news I don't know
if any of you are bequeathed of probably not what's up PVP is coming is confirmed and oh my god
well shit dude that's so the two things that everyone was joking and meaning about that we're
not in the game trading and PVP will be have been in the game in like weeks like like just just
weeks away probably by Christmas time man PVP you might make me want to play the game again
because I just I'm I can't get back into it so I just get so bored so quickly to be fair
I don't worst possible no abs a fucking yeah it's a ten minute walk to a poker stop oh that's
rough yeah that's like that's like that's like my mom it's like our mom I gotta Nate I'm gonna do
it I'm gonna fucking I'm gonna fucking tweet her her fucking friend code and get people to add her
and our mom's friend car right yeah I'm gonna fucking do it I'm gonna do it do it Jenny I'm gonna
feel his blood on my hands tonight I'm sick of you I'm sick of her I'm sick of it she's got she
needs more pokeballs guys doesn't have enough poker stops hashtag Ben Doxt my mom is that
Niantic is actually paying more attention to the competitive scene a fucking Pokemon go than
the main series is of the actual Pokemon series dude let's get into that this is a fascinating
topic to me yeah about representation of characters I just thought about this today so yes an outside
company like Niantic giving more of a shit about like what the community wants and demands and what
would be best for the people rather than the like first-person self self-awareness of the Nintendo
company Game Freak or whatever that is probably fucking it up bad like that just reminded me of
like cloud and smash is real cloud he's not like gay advent children cloud that Square Enix wants him
to be and also I thought about in smash like Richter Belmont you know got confirmed whatever
he's cool from Castlevania and shit and like his like intro line when he was put in was the like
actually it's a big on monster they censored die but he says big on monster you don't belong in
this world that's the classic line from Symphony of the night and in the remake the update that
just got released for that game like because of this announcement probably they change his lines
to be like behold there again is a third party knowing the character and what the people want
more than the base company it's just how is it all the time I don't wait no I don't understand
what do you what do you mean okay my point is that what when people think about like Richter
Belmont memes they think about he says he says die monster you don't belong in this world it is a
classic quintessential so the parent company changed it to be gone something more like I don't
know normal e but they they change the actual that'd be like removing you know all your base
are belong to us from like a remake so okay wait wait so they didn't change it to the smash
line no no smash is the original line basically no it's not because it's be gone instead of die
okay yes they censored the word die to be gone yet they did do that which is so the parent company
changed it but not to I thought you were gonna say they changed it to be gone monster to match
the smash line no no no no okay they change it to something totally different that you know in
effect communicates the same idea but isn't the meme and that was a mistake this is what was it was
it Jesse talking about they changed the lines and yes that's right well it was both of us we were
both talking yeah yeah okay okay so we're talking about the same thing all right we're best we are
we got we keep them back to this well the reason not that it's just like that and like the cloud
example you know what he's like he's like real cloud and smash he's like not he's fake different
cloud according to square enix and like all those representations and I'm just like it's
it really seems like first person self-awareness of companies they don't know what the people want
as well as like outside like fandom to get into the specifics of as people know what the fuck we're
talking about uh in pokemon go they've introduced like you know along with pvp pvp it's not just
going to be you know whoever is the strongest pokemon gets to you know dominate the meta they
introduced like pseudo smog on tiers for the battling league leagues based on uh on cp yeah yeah
so it's it's gonna be you're gonna be able to battle in lower tiers with like lower cp limits
and it's gonna have a wider range of variety in the pokemon that are presented that is so cool
that it's it's gonna make like shit pokemon relevant yeah i'm gonna be able to use mecargo
yeah or fucking i don't know spirit to uh meta chuckle can we do chuckle yeah yeah it's gonna
be fucking crazy are the battles gonna be turn based or is it gonna be the weird gym it's probably
it's pro i'm gonna i mean if it's pokemon go it's gonna be the fucking tap and swipe yeah i mean
we can assume that yeah yeah you know speaking to this yeah quick yeah i'm curious if you guys
have any opinions on this i happen to see some tweets from uh aron hanson from ego raptor today
viciously defending pokemon go as like go or let's go oh sorry let's go let's go yeah okay
one okay as like way better than people were saying one because he has little time he doesn't care
about like the bullshit extra non-core gameplay stuff uh that's been piled on top of like the
mainline pokemon games and let's go like apparently does away with that i haven't played it i don't
know and and then also that like the games were always easy so it's not a problem that the games
are easier this i it i was thinking about this just the other day i was thinking about that i was
thinking about the last pcp episode and how people actually defended pokemon let's go and just getting
so mad because like i was i just i don't know what kind of i don't know what kind of fucking mutant
tom's in the call right i don't know what's wrong with you and hippo and everyone who is like
who is like boy i sure do love i sure do love pokemon i sure am glad that i get to play a
version of pokemon that just isn't even a game anymore because i just i love pokemon but i don't
i love pokemon but i don't have fucking time to actually play it or anything so i have this like
shit version that sucks thank god like what i just all all the only thing is i just i'm not as
hardcore as you that's it that's all it is and like you could i don't get it i don't get it i look at
pokemon let's go and i just see all the appeal is gone but they took out everything good did you
play it no i saw i watched someone play it i actually didn't play it the other day i i did
play it with myself with my own my own two hands is it actually like what he was saying and it's
like streamlined it's just kind of better and that you can like just get to the actual i mean i
i didn't beat it what if it was like pokemon but there was no real battling and no challenges
but that well there sounds good right sounds cool isn't that pokemon go though pokemon go is
completely different and not even the same thing a slightly made by a different company too so that
you know it was i mean streamlined it was just as streamlined as the gameboy games you know the
gameboy games i mean well okay tom i think it's safe to say that pokemon go isn't like a threat to
like main core pokemon games it doesn't it doesn't in any way like impede like it is literally a
totally separate company working on it i'm sure that it uses some dev time but but but okay i mean
i get that appeal of the core appeal of it is totally i get that and i understand that but
here's my question okay if pokemon let's go is a threat as you just said i'm assuming by saying
that pokemon go isn't because it's different platform but pokemon let's go is bad because
it's it's a mainline game right like that's your position yeah the reason it might be but the reason
pokemon let's go is what it is is because of pokemon go so it doesn't that mean pokemon go is
what fucked everything up it definitely possible definitely possible so like no so yeah i'm prepared
to say that pokemon go was part of the problem possibly also let me just read you a quote real
quick there was a news article very well yeah i saw this this is the direct claim that the game is
in fact a quote core and quote quote quote the actual title is uh mossy distresses the pokemon
let's go isn't a spin-off future tiles could connect to pokemon go and uh i personally prefer the
steve version shouts to steve uh mossy distresses that the new pokemon games will be shit that's
you know okay like he just said this is a core title it's time to hit which is weird because
like that goes against what they said when they announced yeah yeah it's weird i agree if if if if
this is if this is what pokemon is from now on i'm live i'm never buying another pokemon ever again
there i mean it is i was i played defense for pokemon let's go saying it was a place to experiment
with different ideas but if this is what they're gonna turn pokemon into i don't hate it as much as
you guys do but there's definitely stuff from the classic experiences that aren't there anymore
that i miss and so yeah i'll be a little bit more miffed and i won't be i have to take the
kid gloves off with my yep saying that it's not as big of a deal as it was listen this is going to
get extremely patronizing and anyone who even slightly cares about let's go is going to think
i'm such a fucking asshole right now okay all right i'm listening here's the thing i mean this
sounds like like goo goo gaga like a vapor like basic like you know do you know you can breathe air
you can lower the skill floor while not lowering the skill ceiling too yeah did you
guys fucking not know that you can make it easier without just removing features did you not think
that that was possible it's it's like they listened it's like they listened to the people that are
like the hidden hidden stats are too i don't like them i can't fucking i don't like hidden you don't
need a patron to any of that i played pokemon games for fucking hundreds of hours that i didn't
know when they just work breeding is too complicated with egg i don't want to think about egg moves
when i'm breeding i just want to play pokemon guys i just want to fucking catch monsters and
beat the elite ford you don't have to breed to do that you don't even have to try it he's right
pokemon is 100% you can casually brute force without any problem and beat the game and like i
guess you could complain that like you do have to spend time grinding but it is a jrpg at its core
right grinding and pokemon has never been a problem for me i'm someone who doesn't give a
shit about breeding or egg moves or any of that shit because i just don't think speaks for a lot
of people here like more the more like uh i guess like boomer generation who like grew up on pokemon
and now as an adult and shit and it's like no no stop stop stop i'm what you we can't we can't
just let language corrode to the point that we are just literally calling millennials boomers
okay you're right i guess well he's a little bit older so no he's not he's like he's like my age
he's like 30 he's like a year older than me he's 31 i think he's like yeah he's a year he's a millennial
okay fair enough okay so he's a millennial but we all agree the bin is a boomer but the point is
world world's youngest boomer his biggest issue that i could see he had a long string of tweets um
but the the main issue i saw with him was that he he was so much happier that it requires less
time to play because he doesn't like having to spend lots of time that makes me so angry
like i love god i love that i can spend less time playing this game that i really love
fuck i mean because he said he's gonna get the fuck out of here to get to like the core like
just the like the stuff that he values more which i i get that guess what you fucking you
strip away you strip away all the bullshit in a video game down to the core and what you have
is a fucking gland in your brain that's secreting dopamine and that's me there's nothing else
everything else is bullshit it's interesting because like as someone who's played some of the
pokemon games but not all of them and never to the degree that ben clearly has when i played let's
go i was just like yeah it's pokemon game they change like the capturing but other than that it's
pretty much what i've always played so like all the things you're talking about is being stripped out
i don't even know about so it's interesting to hear this perspective oh my god it sounds like the
like the more then why should the mouth if you never even knew about them then why on earth would
you strip them out because even the casual audience doesn't mind it it doesn't impede their affection
yeah that's a good question and i don't i don't really have an answer for that i mean all i can
say is that for my kind of play i don't have a huge problem with it because it does what i expect
a pokemon game to do i okay why take all the stuff out yeah if it doesn't mean it's not the
experience they're trying to create i mean i don't know how much of it is is gone well like like
like that god abilities gone wait what yes oh my it's oh my god okay yeah then right yeah all right
gone they took up they took good i thought we hold items and abilities are gone are you
fucking kidding me yes yes i'm sure you're sure okay take your word for it it's even worse than i
thought i got i guess i guess i'm just thinking of red and blue and red and blue let's fucking
let's just fucking regress like sure like we spent we spent like like decades like building up
fire and leaf green though like like i don't have i know hold out where we're good yeah hold
buildies where yes build it building up this carry this incredibly intricate like you know
like relatively well balanced combat system and like fucking strategy game and thing
and then like oh wait let's just fucking make a new one let's just make the next one we just
take it all out again why there's no reason to listen okay listen okay okay wait wait wait
pokemon sun and moon was way easier than x and y but you know what it had held items and abilities
there was no reason to delete features of the video game or remove them when you can just make
the game easier regardless it's not like sun and moon is like a fucking 700 hour campaign it's it's
like it's like it's like someone like it's like erin okay i haven't read the tweets but it's like oh
you can get to the core you get to the core let's bullshit get to the core of what i like about
fucking pokemon let's go like what is the core that like you see a fucking 3d model of a pokemon
show up on screen and you clap like a fucking seal like there it is like fuck you what's wrong
with you they just got rid of the game they just like cut the game in half and you're like oh few
oh fucking what a relief i got a question i'm thinking about something and i'm i'm comparing
two games in my mind i'm thinking about what is the core gameplay what is the core that people want
from a game like for example i'm comparing kingdom hearts and then on the other side uh like bayonetta
devil may cry both are action rpgs but very different in uh like like kingdom hearts is like a
you especially kingdom hearts too is what i'm thinking of uh that's the most similar one to like
you know devil may cry and shit like in devil may cry you still have to like earn orbs to like get
moves for the weapons that you acquire but ultimately in like devil may cry three like the
goal is essentially to like unlock all the moves so that you can like learn how to do them via you
know crazy inputs and shit and and then you're like like you do have to do some grinding to unlock
everything to play the game like and i guess it's quote unquote core which is what like high level
people want to do and kingdom hearts is similar but there's way more grinding required to get there
you have to unlock tons more moves you start off with way less abilities at the beginning of the
game and there's more like customization of like what stuff you equip what what stuff you don't you
know you can like set your stuff up a little bit more carefully that way and i'm like so but i
bet someone like aron would say the core of kingdom hearts is like fun adventures in disney worlds
which is yeah like at the very least some people would make that argument so i'm like so should we
for kingdom hearts three for example remove all that bullshit customization and just make it as
fast as possible all the combat stuffs just streamlined you get like one combo you do and you
just get more disney like faster make it just depends on what you want i don't want to bring back
like the arcade argument from like 2007 like like games are so fucking short now all short games are
bad like that fucking like old like i can't even believe that i remember that from a billion years
but why do you want every game to require no time investment investment and have no impact on your
memory and have it just be oh yeah just just i'm just gonna come fucking consume this game in an
afternoon that's what it sounds like aron's advocating for it really does it really does
i'm sorry i'm sorry to say it aron but like he's talking about in these tweets he doesn't have a
lot of time for video games don't you play video games for a living what am i missing here what yeah
what am i missing with this with this scenario don't you want to like explore the games to their
depth i'm saying it i think aron has lost the fucking plot and he has forgotten what makes
video games good and he treats it too much like a fucking business i think that is what has happened
here and uh i i just i guess i just disagree is all yeah that's it um it's it's it's it's
the human characters look bad listen i'm gonna say it fucking delete hold items delete abilities i
don't care but when you look at a gross little poopy monster like the main character pokemon
let's go is it's so gross he looks like a little snot he looks like a little booger i hate him
okay but i want to dial it back because like i i get why like tom's right here tom likes the game
i i get it because he i'm not gonna dial back like i like put this in the show it's it all depends
on what you want right but like i think we could all agree the goal the i think what we would all
want is to lower the skill floor to a place where people can get on board and have a great time
even the most casual of casuals that's fine but we want to keep the skill ceiling high right we
yeah i mean i agree to go deep i don't because i and the weird thing for me is that as someone who
played pokemon red at 10 years old the skill floor was fine uh i i i mean okay hey guys
like guys we we gotta make pokemon casual yeah like we need more people to oh wait uh look at the
pcp main chat oh wait oh wait shit everyone can play this game even like moms and babies pokemon
red blue yellow it is the sixth most selling game of all time is there something just to be said
that people have become pussies though that like they just like don't want even if they could if
they put their minds to it they just they would gravitate away from a game like this i am wondering
and they need to be i am i am wondering if this attitude because like you know i've heard other
people with similar attitudes to errands right like it's not i don't know there's there's something
to it that like he's not the only one that feels as i'm wondering if it's some kind of
outgrowth of millennial bullshit like which is a which is a term that i'm going to keep pushing
i'm going to keep pushing millennial bullshit as a thing that i coined and that is associated with
me specifically that's good as in a thing that i as in a thing that i battle against make a
sure to that then make a sure to that immediately hashtag millennial but that should be your i am
game shirt you know what i fucking will um good good good it'll say fuck millennial bullshit
and i don't think if i am games and then you're gonna have you are millennial bullshit you
you probably are viewer in some way or another i um i think i don't know problem is specifically
that he's become too much of a business boy in my humble opinion which is a different problem but
also an insidious one okay he says he likes that he gets to walk around with whatever pokemon i want
yet everybody liked that everybody loved that ever like you can do that without in heart game well
yeah everyone loved that in heart gold and soul silver and yeah it's great that it's back but why
do they take out by the way i i want to say by the way in case anyone tries to retort this this uh
this this hashtag evidence that pokemon is one of the top selling games of all time uh by saying
that the other games you know got more competitive and therefore sold less well they aren't top the
first ones every single core pokemon is on the list of best selling fucking video games pokemon
gold and silver ruby and sapphire diamond and pearl uh fucking black and white x and y and
fucking sun and moon are all on here are all separately on the best set list of best selling
video games of all time yeah but is this gonna beat them no way no no no i don't think this i don't
think the switch install base is there for it to beat them at this point i mean this is definitely
pushing to help that would smash comes out i mean that'll be a big that'll be okay so well
erin erin here is arguing that pokemon let's go is not easier just are you looking at his are you
looking at his i'm looking at his tweets okay it seems like his contention is that the game is not
easier merely less tedious which okay i guess i can kind of get there are i mean in its defense
because again there are a lot of great features i thought that made the game less tedious i think
i i can understand the argument for replacing the wild battles with the pokemon let's go throw
mechanics like i i don't i honestly i don't necessarily love it but i don't think it's
retarded the only thing that i don't like about the the the throw mechanic is that it the tracking
isn't one to one so like yeah actually throwing it where you want to go at least for me is a pain
in the ass because you can throw like left right or forward there's no like nuance to it yeah it's
not great look it didn't look like like it doesn't it's like in let's go you actually have like like
the way that you move the ball like like you know you you get an arc based on how your right finger
moved and it's not it's not it's like it's like it's like digital in in let's go right it's not
it's not analog it's kind of like if you played skyward sword when you swing the wheel it's not
a one-to-one swing it just has like eight directions you can swing it and it guesses as best as it can
this is similar to that which is not great um yeah it didn't look great but like the thing that i don't
know why they couldn't have done it because like they have motion control right the thing that i thought
was really great like probably my favorite addition like besides like the overworld being able to see
the pokemon because it makes it easier to find that's great i like how like there's no you don't
have to go to the pokemon center and go to the pc to access your box you just access it anywhere
because it it allows you to experiment with more pokemon because you could if you want to switch
out and try like something new like the guy you just caught you don't have to like we'll have to
stop what i'm doing i have to fly back i don't know i like i like the team i like the team like i
like that like you got your team right develop you develop a core team of six that is like your
boys and you can still do that but if you don't want if you want to keep switching it up you
don't it doesn't it it removes a step if you want to play the game that way well hang on
hang on for a second there i know this is this is like early game issues mostly but like as i'm
going through the game if i remember correctly when you put a pokemon in the box it heals its hp
if you then swap it like is this just a way to heal all your pokemon instantly if you're like going
through a dungeon or something i don't know i because we haven't i we've only played it a
couple times on stream and we stopped and we're playing spirano but i haven't played it enough
to even like notice if that is a thing that happens because the whole thing is that like yeah
because we've we've only been uh because like the whole thing is that like if you catch a pokemon
since there's no battle like you don't do damage to them so when i swap somebody in it has full
hp because of course it does like there was never any battle damage to begin with sure i just i saw
my friend play on it and he's fighting like brock and brock has more than one pokemon but he's
they're playing multiplayer and brock sends out his geodude he's got his onyx in reserve and like
because they're playing like with two players like their main character sends out two pokemon and you
just 2v1 yeah that's weird you can just 2v1 all the time but by the way insane i just want to say
that for how much you think pokemon let's go is a baby game actually like watching it in action
was fucking like insane here's i should do that here's here's what happened uh before i actually
got my hands on the controller with my friend booted up his like save file and stuff uh and uh
and then he's just walking down a cycling road also by the way quick side by the way uh cycling
road it's a bridge in the old games yeah because otherwise the bow the ssn would be landlocked
they made it just a normal land route so the ssn is landlocked yeah it's landlocked now um which
great okay so super and anyway besides that autism um he's just walking down cycling road
and a chance he appears and i piss myself and i'm like holy fucking chancey go go catch that
right now and he's like why would i have 60 like they're not rare they just spawn like
like constantly and i'm like like i cannot believe here's the thing you know like having stakes
or like having resistance or having any fail states whatsoever makes it so that winning
has merit and makes you feel good in any way have your things be rare makes it feel good when you
get a rare thing now that makes you feel it makes you feel anything at all and that's not it and
that's not it that was like fucking small potatoes to prepare but i'm about to tell you
there's our catch streak so when you catch a single pokemon like for instance he was
trying to shiny hunt evie so he would just encounter an evie you know you know catcher
and then you know continue on with the day he was just trying to catch as many evies as possible
in a row once you get to a high catch rate aka like 30 you can get on your pokemon that can fly
go up into the sky and wild dragon knight and charizard spawn dragon knight and charizard
spawn for you wild that's wait wait like in the sky yes that sounds pretty cool that you're in the
sky i guess uh i mean it's it's more like the like it's the same map it just is like you're higher
up it like is it like that is it like that thing in like omega ruby where you can ride around on
latios no no nothing like not nothing even slightly like that no oh i don't i don't want to
overstate it and make it seem like oh my god like i can't believe like you're finding the pokemon
like it's cool it looks like it just looks like you are riding on your charizard and he is like
elevated slightly above the house so the point is the game is just throwing powerful poke right
yeah she's throwing dragon knight charizard at you as i'm trying to say to you well that's
fucking gay uh people go watch a little video called game difficulty why i'm right and everyone
else is wrong we agua uh it sums it up it's the genius uh word of god on this issue i'm just the
fact that you can fly is kind of cool i don't want to like diminish it i'm just trying to say
that you just get fucking free dragon knight charizard for no reason i'm i'm i'm having to work to
get legendary pokemon like i mean you know effectively legendary like finding a bag on
in that one area leveling up to salamence finding a trap inch leveling up to fly gone as i
legendarily did and had the greatest time of my life uh you know fucking getting a gible
evolving into garchomp and shit as i tried to do and failed in my most recent nuzlocke but i
rather fail than it just be handed to me on a silver fucking platter yeah um i i fucking you
know a parent okay i don't know who or tom i'm so sorry tom i mean i mean no like that is kind of
gay and i i'll give you that yeah okay i i don't know who said that like this this is a mainline
game i'm hoping that that's like the mistrant the director it's gotta be a mistrant he was drunk
or something i don't know whatever uh you know you know i'm still hoping that like this isn't like
like like that doesn't mean like this is what pokemon is from now and listen to this listen to
the full quote here we go this is the actual quote i'm gonna read it translated from japanese
true so there could be some wiggle room for issues but but just listen to the language here
okay quote uh in his name is that junichi masuda these games aren't spin-offs these are core
pokemon titles as for whether we would make other games that could connect to pokemon go
that will depend on how the games are received if we hear a lot of people saying that they enjoyed
being able to bring pokemon to these games from pokemon go then we'll think about maybe having
future titles also be able to connect to it that's okay but sounds like he could just mean in the
sense that these games you know could be legacies in the sense that you know pokemon go has more
interactivity and he doesn't mean like the easiness of it but there's no reason to not believe it
as well that doesn't that doesn't necessarily imply that that what he means is that like this is what
future games will be like yeah it's just like yeah these are different you know let's not
forget but like but but they're still we're still considering them core games he's definitely
that's not to say that all core games will be like this it's definitely in his interest to kind of
upsell the importance of this game as the director so i would not be surprised if he's maybe a little
bit exaggerating so you know what we were a little bit pushing fake news this is not as dire i i i
i have no faith in game freak to not do this like i just don't believe them but i just need to see
the next damn game and see what it is i don't believe them well aren't they gonna reveal it at
e3 didn't they say it's a 2019 release like well they say yeah i don't know if they've said about
e3 or anything like that i mean yeah if it's coming out in 2019 they have to show something
at e3 i would i would hope so i would hope so oh i could it could just uh come out uh you know in
2020 or something when they release the the new new switch they got to have some title to push
people to go buy another fucking switch that they will inevitably release at some point that's true
uh oh my oh my god oh my god please nintendo this is unironic and actually true you know you
how you have a 3ds xls making switch xl because the joycons are shit and too small and i can't
play video games with them yeah solution just prop up your thing buy it's it's 70 bucks but buy the
like so fucking why is it 70 dollars it is great though it is a great controller but it's what
nintendo needs to do they need to not be gay and they need to spend the extra money get 128 gig
game cards so we don't have to put everything on them anemic 32 gigs of storage on the fucking
switch you morons i bought a i bought a fucking additional micro i did too but it's it's the
principle of the matter yeah i don't want to have to it's get make the game cards 128 gigs or
make the baseline switch have 128 gigs of built-in memory and not upsell anybody on it
you fucking bastard it's like by the way with 32 gigs is an insult 32 gigs yeah after all this
bash and i would like to announce that i'm literally buying a switch today hey dude smash we come on
dude i'm playing smash uh yeah yeah dude yeah oh my god nate let's fucking play smash bros do it
dawg yeah fucking place i'm good i'm gonna like fight against people the fucking best everybody
come on my stream next fucking saturday uh at 7 30 i'm playing to like fucking fight against people
you know out in the world anyway let's all play smash it'll be great it'll be oh oh and nate you
know what the smash players do which is so fucking fun what they do they allow subscribers
and like donors to like battle them in smash and just that's what i was playing i'm doing that's
what i'm playing i'm doing i have to find my switch because uh it disappeared from where it was i
think did you took it and and just took my switch literally beat him and get it back you know even
if he's like yeah just take it now hit him anyway so that he learns his lesson and yeah that's true
get that shit back it's smash time people we've got when you hear this smash is coming out today
if you're hearing this today it is out wait this isn't literally the biggest game in the world i don't
care about any other game isn't smash out already no it's five days from today i've got to leave
though so everyone knows everything about it that's true but i don't care okay i don't i don't really
care about i don't really care about smash either way um let's play uh nate um subspace that did you
know that subspace emissary is horrible no it's not why me bin i want to be friends with you i want
to continue working with you as a colleague and as a co-worker but if you keep saying racist
shit like this i'm not gonna be able to justify our relationship it's just it's such a snore it's so
bad you're such a snore you are about to sleep while playing it you put down your controller
i'm so mad i wish i wish fat three two would suck my fat three two just so that people can see
your incompetence playing the best video game ever made i uh seeing you play it for a couple
of reasons one there's an actually kind of compelling story specifically where rob's
concerned it's good yeah yeah i did like that so it wasn't but it wasn't worth wasn't worth sitting
through like fight a bunch of fucking mooks in smash in like ai smash battles for like 11 hours
i kind of agree but by the way i want to be extremely clear right now is that super smash or
subspace emissary is one of those games where uh when you play it like with your hands and you're
actually playing it this is probably the most miserable experience you could possibly have
your entire life but like like your star wars to complete saga as soon as you put down the
controller and you walk away you're like oh my god i love that game so much you can see all your
fucking boys fighting each other and teaming up and stuff in like canonical story shit that's
what you play it for that's the good shit it's fun it's just a bunch of fucking like stupid
cutscenes that exist to just okay it is like the cutscenes are there to justify why are these
smash characters fighting in this ai battles that doesn't need any justification it could have been
it doesn't need them but it's fun yeah it's a fucking sequence of fights the raid on the ship
entering the black hole to go like fight taboo at the end oh my god oh my god it's don't tell i
forget what's called i think it's called it's called like like the great infiltration or something like
that or something like that that's like the most hyped cutscene of all time it is kino it is kino
so fucking good when you have when you when you beat all the hardest level of the entire world
you're half the heels of having robin at your party and the best fucking most like like it's like
it's like it's like the shindler's list of super smash brothers yeah when robin chasing people and
and then you have you unlock all the characters and you're ready to fight taboo and then they all
get in their rickety fucking rocket ship and they all do a full on a star on gannon and bowser
and you see oh you see medknights fucking the halberd you see all our ship you see sam's ship
you see all these cool fucking spacecrafts shoot this giant toho looking monstrosity destroy it
and want a clean slice by carby my maid god damn it's so good all right cool yeah it was there's
like one minute that's kind of cool and then like there's like 16 hours of fucking all right well
for some people that's enough i don't think anyone would really argue the moment to moment gameplay
of subspace emissary is like particularly great because it's not yeah it's pretty shit yeah yeah
yeah it is but but what we got to the legacy of subspace emissary i think has a long shadow
yeah and in the in the good way and it's pretty fucking dope uh by the way the ideal way to play
subspace emissary is to make it as painful as possible and like like like make it such a terrible
experience that it's like legendary so the like one of like like a like a fucking what was like
like a tradition uh whenever i where i meet up with one of my friends is we start a new game
file and uh i'm so necessary on intense mode and intense mode uh the the hard mode for that game
is one of those hard modes where they didn't actually like balance the game to be hard they
just made every enemy do like like five times the damage and have five times the health so
which is the most broken fucking like worst unpolished mess of a video game you could possibly
imagine and it takes like hours to complete one fucking level uh and it's so like balls like
rockingly hard that it takes like the entire time we're together to to beat it and it's so euphoric
it it's really it heightens the cutscene so much to be playing the game as hard as you possibly
can be playing in complete fucking silence in darkness eating pizza rolls having just like
press like smash the start button when it says to continue just like fucking like yeah yeah like
i'm not even gonna register that we just lost completely i'm just we're just gonna jump right
we just have to continue going and you finally get to like the end level and you get to just
like let's scream an agony and throw yourself back into the chair and just watch the fucking
three second cutscene that is that is rewarding you it makes it such a more valuable experience
and i now like memorized every cutscene back to back because when they were playing all like like
i just like shut off my brain to like ease the pain and all i could just watch was like midnight
like brogan out that's like all i could register my brain yeah it's great that's game difficulty for
you even when it's broken as shit it when you if you overcome it you get a a little little brain
reward those little brains go go buzzing and you just strip away all the bullshit from the game and
just have that fucking dopamine while we all get your wreck stimulus we just video games should
just be like a helmet you wear that directly stimulates that just sticks a needle in your brain
yeah and just like just vibrates your pineal gland or whatever just like video video games
should just be you hire someone to come jerk you off oh guys guys i the best idea it's a pokemon
game in vr and it just is a linked boba pd and just cycles through the gallery of all the pokemon
in order and that's the ideal pokemon game for erin hansen it's just you see pokemon designs
agreed
that's it it's like it's like the fucking the 3d model of your favorite pokemon comes on the
screen and you fucking clap like a train seal i love it i will say about pokemon uh let's go um
the animations don't exist they're terrible dude why are they so bad i always see that compared to
pokemon coliseum which are these crazy meticulous animations oh my god and like what happened watch
fucking xd's animations for pokemon listen you can say xd sucks sure but look at golbat's animation
in that fucking game and it's okay yeah well yeah you're not ready for fucking golbat in xd
golbat's absolutely ridiculous um yeah he like just so you know he hugs himself with his wings and
just rocks back and forth he's not yeah he's not flying he has his arms wrapped around his
beard i don't know but hilarious he's just like rocking back and forth like he's a fucking serial
killer oh aj shoot the golbat oh aj shoot the golbat yeah i don't understand is he dead he's not
dead no he's he's one of our best dudes one of our greatest assets i just don't understand why
there's like no excuse and let's go to not like have animations because like you just have the
original 150 like it's not like you got to animate 700 dudes like yeah yeah that's true they they
wait why don't they have animations because like in the mainline games like like okay correct me if
i'm wrong but don't the let's go just use the same 3d models as like all the other 3d pokemon games
don't they use the same assets i think that i think the models i think the models from the yeah they
they do they do have animations like they like like yeah all the pokemon have like animations
for their battle moves and stuff i'm watching it right now i cannot believe this i i guess i wasn't
paying attention or i you know i you know what i literally probably thought is that my friend had
like like the battle style set to like not to use their battle zone in the main series games we can
turn on battle effects i probably literally thought it i'm looking at this pikachu is like a statue
that like rotates yeah the enemy pokemon and like jumps to indicate it's attacking this is insane
it really doesn't make any sense and like the weird thing is that like i saw because i was watching
the digital foundry video on let's go where they like go over like the frame rates and the models
and stuff yeah and like apparently the models used in let's go are the models from the 3ds games
just a higher resolution so like they've already got animations yes like the animations are made
and they just show no let's just not use they're doing this on the switch like let's just have
an upgrade let's just have it be let's instead of something let's have it be well i haven't played
sun and moon so i don't know how they compare no no but someone has like actual animations it's not
like a pussyfoot thing they they have different animations okay like the way the way that the
other 3d and pokemon games do it is like okay as far as i'm aware every pokemon has a few like
different attack animations they can do depending on like whether it's a special or physical move
and maybe those variations move yeah yeah and they'll have like they'll have a they'll have an
animation that they'll do and then there will be like a separate effect that like plays like a beam
or you know a blizzard effect there's a couple like little animations here and there but like a lot of
the moves there's just nothing it's just like an effect and like i guess that that makes sense
back in like game boy color days when you can't you just run out of memory if you have like 40
frames of animation for every pokemon as much as much as i prefer like the pixel style of like
black and white or something to the 3d i think like the 3d like the animations look mostly pretty
good like some of them are kind of weak but like in general like it looks it looks like they're
performing it looks like they're performing it's just weird that pokemon stadium has more and a
better animation than let's go on the switch i don't want to suck the dick of the 3d animation
too much because there's a lot of animations in x and y and later pokemon games that kind of
fucking blow ass like almost all the bird pokemons all the bird pokemon that are like gliding in place
look like a nightmare and like they're absolutely abysmal however yeah i like like i would say
probably the majority of them are fine and serviceable uh by the way i just want to let you
know guys know that like like the the walking animations for all the pokemon as seen in pokemon
let's go work in sun and moon's files and you could like access them so everyone knew some crazy
shit was happening they they animated walk cycles for all the pokemon by the way not just like the
hanto ones like literally all of them they all have walk cycles well good yeah so i have no idea
why they didn't import everything i have no clue it's on a move uh but i mean this gives me hope
that walking pokemon will be in the other games because i mean again yeah all the pokemon have
walking animations like all of them do that's the thing that's the thing we all really liked in
heart gold and soul silver and they were like hold on company has a weird fetish like a bizarre
fetish on r slash fetish that is like just removing game features that everyone universally enjoys
for no reason literally why would you remove the battle frontier i cannot imagine it would it would
take away that much effort to make the battle frontier just like an area on the map with
battles like it's not that fucking difficult i have no idea why you keep removing it for no reason
i mean i can understand at least why they removed the uh the walk sprites because like
you know that's a lot of well i don't know actually i mean it's the pokemon company do
yeah they're not sure yeah yeah i was changing like sure that's a lot of work but like is it so
hard over the course of like a single development cycle to pay one artist to make walk sprites for
you know six like 600 pokemon and like they've already got fucking they've got the models you
can just i don't know yeah making a walk cycle and maybe a couple and maybe making a walk cycle
is not that for for one model can't take more than like a day for like a professional
you know you know what i'm saying so it's gonna i i i don't know i guess i've been talking out my
ass but like they've got their fucking resources to do it you'd think so i mean you you'd think
yeah i'm sure i'm sure i'm sure i'm sure i'm sure that i'm no no no i'm sure they're paying their
3d animators just a king's ransom for a salary so they can't possibly afford to pay like one
animator or two to do this studio this is an Nintendo and game freak again pokemon top
selling video games of all time yeah pokemon games are made on such the fucking cheap it's so
bizarre yeah i got i got no sympathy for for that shit they i'm sure they're doing just fine
yeah yeah guys um i can't wait to buy jenny i cannot wait to buy it with my money yeah i sure do
love pokemon i sure do love how fucking mad i am about it all the time dude remember when pokemon
went barg and then he shot the other pokemon with his beam yeah while standing still like a statue
oh my god rear how hype it was when Pikachu rotated two degrees and then jumped up attacking
geodude wasn't that so fucking hype dude i feel like using the word jump is a bit uh yeah generous
yeah his legs don't the model increases like the y value parabolically increases and then decreases
y value no movement of the legs or lower body or anything really that's the good shit no gravity
yeah remember i don't know man i was just gonna say like some pokemon like it doesn't make sense
how to even exist like geodude i guess magnetism or something so for him having meaningless animations
you know okay but with like like pikachu's got legs dog he can all right you get the
pikachu is like already got animations but here's the thing that blows my mind even more is that
like you have a game called pokemon let's go pikachu and like every player is going to see
pikachu himself maybe spend a little bit of time giving that character some animations yeah that's
a great point that character has a specific move set that you know the player is going to get and
the character can't evolve because you can't evolve the pikachu or the evie in these games right so
just go through the effort of making maybe making two sets of unique animations for these two characters
that you know everyone's gonna see maybe you know what i hate you know what i hate uh uh correct me
remember i know that evie the evie in pokemon let's go evie has like boosted stats and gets like
special moves right i assume that pikachu also has boosted stats i don't know that for sure they're
okay i don't like that uh because it's like fake it's like fake bullshit and it's uh not real
pokemon it's like we're we're making special magical pokemon that like what why are they better
than every other pikachu why i think it's just because i think it's even in like side games like
like like go the fetishization of certain pokemon i miss when pokemon like was just like like
pikachu sure it was the mascot of pokemon and you know what that was fine it was on the all
the promotional material but at the end of the day it was one character of many and in the actual
games it did not have like like it didn't have boosted fucking stats it wasn't like you know
the main character that was forced upon you it wasn't you know just like the be all into all
pokemon this is the main character of pokemon i i do not i literally do not understand like
who pikachu specifically appeals to like who like who sees like oh man i really want this
because it's got pikachu i mean they're clearly i like that way yeah there's definitely sure sure
sure sure i like pikachu he's fine but i don't understand like does he does he does pikachu
in specific appeal to people in a way that pokemon in general does not pikachu is shorthand for
pokemon in general so like if you want to play a pokemon you got pikachu cool there's the guy
there's the man and i guess he's like the most widely recognized one yeah um so that's some people
just like that's fine but i yeah that's fine i get it i i hate that the starter is forced upon you
and while you can have him not be in your team like battle wise he's still like on your shoulder
fucking gross it makes me really upset why is that why is that yellow it's the conceit of the game
because i don't okay listen i like i like that you can have him on your shoulder but i don't like
but if he's not in like on your in your front spot he probably shouldn't be
it's that was i mean that was just part of the game i guess like they
but clearly like the games are like if you like pikachu and or evie like they're a huge part of
this game like there's like there's a whole there's a whole section like it's literally called pikachu
or evie the game so i i don't care you know what hang on was was pikachu better in pokemon yellow
did he have boosted stats in that game um no actually right i mean it's who can fucking say
maybe it did but because the stats weren't visible back then so there was no way of knowing unless
like you like i'm just somebody knows well you you could see you you could see this you could see
their stats you could see like the number stats i guess but like i never cared enough to compare
them i know i mean i'm sure there's experts out there deep cover right who know you know the
formulas i'm gonna say no but i'm not i mean pokemon yellow was a meme game anyway and you know
yeah this really just comes back to this whole thing about like like i don't care if there's
a spin-off that doesn't like mean that all pokemon games are gonna be like this forever uh monster
distresses that all future pokemon games will be shit well yeah he loves it by the way everyone's
like they'll be still be shit for the masses for they'll be shit for the pig like masses to
roll in and love ever everyone please with pokemon company on a daily basis bring back fat
pikachu bring back fat pikachu we're gonna bring back this pikachu that's what i want to know
that's i why don't why isn't there a pokemon let's go lucario that's that's actually a great
question and i would not put it past them to make a third version no pokemon let's go i absolutely
fucking wouldn't well why not i want to let's go you too while there is gonna make a final fantasy
let's go lightning that's what i want that's just all right all you people all you people in your
pokemon and your final fantasy i'm waiting for sega to get off their ass and release child garden
adventure yeah when's that there are pokemon pokemon let's go sonnet you version oh that's what
i want that's what i fucking you know i imagine i'll say imagine square enix making pokemon let's
go lightning because in pokemon let's go eevee you can like pet your eevee or pikachu you can
like dress them up and stuff i'm sure i'm gonna do that you can do that in a fire emblem game too
they made pokemon to me but like humans in a fire emblem game isn't there like isn't there a pokemon
fire emblem crossover uh no i don't think it's fire super smash brothers friend no no no it's
no i know it's like pokemon and like some it yeah yeah it's like some like japanese like historical
like eddo period war i think that is the thing that was real and not a fever dream yeah yeah oh i
yeah i found it because when i was doing pokemon uh you know nuzlocke conquest i and i like googled
that for some reason and i found pokemon conquest which is like a crossover with this conquest series
we was like what the fuck is this yeah got a nuzlocke bro shit's weird what a world what a pokemon
world we all live in a pokemon world it's a whole new world we live in it's a whole new place to see
it's a whole new thing with a brand new brand new attitude but still gotta fuck some fucking ass pokemon
genie you can't be all right enough pokemon for the please god i'm so i'm so sick of talking
about pokemon should we just go to questions or anything let's let's let's get the hell out of
here and kill ourselves let's get the fuck okay all right let's let's pull up some questions oh oh wait
wait actually there's something extremely important hold on i i need to get you guys uh hold on yeah
please put this in uh the show notes uh editor that looks good what is this what are we looking at
sombra and i don't know maybe that's shiny ray quasi looks like i google search pokemon conquest
and this is one of the first images wait a minute look at his this is pokemon so he might be that
guy's dressed up as like a lord or something yeah yeah i think that's actually the otaklan well yeah
no yeah he's dressed up from noba uh uh uh uh ubi dubi from uh japan that's him uh huh uh
buda you mean yeah buda scooby duty let's let's let's move on uh okay here we go uh speak pipe
here they come send us your voicemails uh what's that speak pipe uh tom what's the url i was
speak pipe dot com slash hey guys it's me a pcp fan i want to talk about the url munchie god damn it
say that again tom please speak pipe dot com slash pcp voicemail that's the one thank you link below
link below okay question one from this is from um shit where to go uh moonju moonju calling it
with a question uh yeah valued watcher of my streams go hey fucktards how many times you feel
like you got to repeat a recording before you get it right i know nate's a perfectionist but what
about the rest of you faggots love moonju that's it depend i mean depends on what it's a recording of
we yeah we do like about 20 takes of every pcp episode honestly in almost in almost all context
one and only yeah like when when was the last time i like rerecorded something i can't even think of it
i do multiple takes of stuff with weagua but the real reason i do that is because maybe if it's
if it's like line delivery or if it's like a song or something then you would like if i stumble over
a line in and i am game script i'll re-say but like for my vlogs and shit it's all off the cuff
and i don't give a fuck because the whole point is like if i have to edit it i've done something
wrong so they're just yeah i'm done people don't seem to have like absorbed this fact people always
think that i write scripts for weagua like i do many takes for weagua but it's specifically because
i am coming up with everything i might have bullet points off the top of my fucking head but um
like i so i'll do multiple takes if i just say something wrong or like i didn't say what i wanted
to say or it sounds incorrect but like that's pretty much it these days i mean if i'm doing a script
but i don't do many scripts you know those best anime ever has come out once in a blue moon so
not too often tell me about it oh no next one this is from uh this is from steve saying let's
keep this let's keep this going yeah let's steve saint is recalling a third child the third one here
we go what do you got hey what's going on pcp uh i think you guys are really fun to listen to you
guys are really nice wow thank you i do have a serious question to ask it's been burning in my
mind for a while uh how do we know ben saint is real and not just like a hulu mass hallucination
because i swear to god i'm hearing things on my bed and yesterday my heavy cream disappeared my
heavy cream is gone uh things are going weird in my house and uh when i got out of the shower a
couple hours ago i looked in the mirror it was just ben saint looking back at me uh so i really
i'm starting to freak out maybe you guys can help me maybe you may maybe you know how to deal with
this uh i don't know i need some help i'm freaking out guys i i i too thought that ben was fake and
slash or at least a catfish for many years until i until until i met her in person and i'm just
gonna tell you right now you can't make the stuff up you can like everything you know about ben
is like like like on the one dial and he takes up to ten on the daily bro he takes up to ten on
the daily you cannot make up what he dishes out on the rig well here's all right it's like
santa claus right like i like to like i i like to say that i believe in santa claus but the thing
about santa claus that santa claus is not a person santa claus is the spirit of christmas
generosity and when one person gives a gift out of like like christmas spirit to another
like that act is like santa claus that sounds like some fluffy la la bullshit to me oh oh it
happens oh oh for sure that's just how i like every time every time you drink heavy cream
ben saint is there in your heart look into the mirror and take three chugs of heavy cream and
ben saint will appear as you as you fade into a coma and you lose consciousness you'll catch a
glimpse that act that act itself is every time you every time you when you when you drink a ben
saint yeah every time you pull a tab on a monster zero and hear that little clink that's ben that's
ben looking down on you every every time every time you buy arizona tea in bulk and then water it
down so you have more arizona tea to go around that's ben yeah that's true that's true okay so i
am i am a concept steve my brother um next episode of this voicemail is uh clomato clomato
i think is calling in so go all right i work at a grocery store there's constantly these spanish
guys to come in and they buy clomato juice which is part clam juice part tomato juice whoa yeah i've
heard why would you want this why like i i'm pretty sure they mix it with alcohol but like why okay
well i i mean why clam chowder comes in red and white varieties and the red kind is like tomato
based oh yeah i've never had red chowder but it's a thing that's not new wingland clam chowder that's
the other kind no new england clam chowder is the white that's right that's right um i guess superior
kind if you will uh agree well i don't know probably i i've i've never even heard of of red clam
chowder and that sounds fucking disgusting how could you possibly not it's reprehensible for sure
white shits that's the good shit yeah i i mean i can't answer this question i don't know why someone
would eat drink clomato juice because i've never had it and i have no desire to especially those
spaniards they're a wily bunch can't keep a tabs on their thoughts i mean maybe it's like v8
how do you guys feel about a v8 not a fan not a fan i haven't had enough to really make a
call one way or the other i guess it's growing on me more like i'm more willing to drink it now
than when i was young but i wouldn't choose it you know it's i don't know if it's really i mean
yeah it's probably got it's probably fairly nutritious but it's also like very sugary yeah it's
all sugary all the calories any any product that insults me and they're advertising i'm not a huge
fan of does it how so they yeah their advertisements of old was that someone would have a drink and
then a bottle of v8 would slam their face and their slogan was you should have had a v8 and i'm just
like should have had a v8 i'm like oh fuck you i don't want to v8 you dick that was when they had
like they had like the like fruit versions they had the v8 splash v8 splash v8 splash that's a good
shit i kind of liked i love it yeah it kind of likes v8 splash yeah i have probably still exists
so i love v8 splash to answer this question that was about something totally different yeah okay
next question glad we figured that one thank god for that uh next episode uh this is uh tamaso
choco taco calling in again let's see what he's got for us what's the most ridiculous thing you've
ever seen at a church one time i was invited to a church it was like a special thursday
and they decided to reenact curcobane suicide and have him like write out the letter to Courtney
put the gun in his mouth and then gunshot fade to black wait what into the cut into the scene from
broke back mountain where the Heath Ledger is going i can't quit you and the pastor's daughter came out
and said they killed themselves because they were gay this is the last time i went to this church
both because it was incredibly fucked up why would you stop going after that i was dying laughing
and and berry and embarrassed my friend's entire family i haven't talked to him since uh but i don't
know if i really want to uh see you later god uh you should have tipped your fedora and and moon
walked out uh man it's tough to say i had sex in a church i had i had sex in a church yeah did you
really that was yeah with god oh my god like no within college um just there was a no one was
at her became a bishop yeah that's right that's right filled with the holy spirit cool cool i was
oh she oh she was filled with the holy spirit oh that's disgusting oh it was fucking gross as
hell dude yeah she wasn't she wasn't filled with the holy spirit she was filled with the saint all
right yeah i can't even think of anything that compares i don't know no um i guess the weirdest
thing i have that i've experienced in a church is that when i was a we lad for my my mom is super
christian and for a while we would this is like back in like 1995 so i was like okay the smallest
of children we would go to a church it was like an hour and a half away from us and the whole mass
was done in latin so for an hour and like change i would just be sitting here and like and in latin
masses the priest is not allowed to look at you because you're you're lower tier you have to look
he has to look at the tabernacle where the eucharist is which like with the jesus wafers so you would
just have his back turned to you the entire time speaking in latin all the nuns would be there
like chanting and i was just like what the fuck is going on i just want to go watch toy story this is
fucked that's kind of aesthetic and cool that's like a bloodborne scene where you go and then you
like kill them all with like your charged r2 a hunter's axe yeah i didn't i didn't get to do that part
that part would have made it sick but i i i continually dismay my entire family whenever
like a church scene comes on like a tv show or even when we just pass this church and i have to
like avert my eyes because i feel like scared just like in the presence of crosses and this isn't a
joke like like the union the godfather came on and you know fucking i i haven't even seen the movie
but you know the mob was going to town to kill a bunch of people haha spoilers and i'm more scared
that someone's getting baptized it was the scariest moment of my fucking life they're chanting it like
a dead or cake language and it's all like darkly lit it's awful it's terrible yeah yeah you're
probably so scary scene it's probably seen in godfather one where uh michael clears out all
his enemies which is during the baptism of the sun yeah yeah it's awful baptism in churches
it's so scary it's all it feels like i don't listen like a like a derogatory way i guess
but like it genuinely feels like a cult like you are inside of a scary creepy pasta i mean i mean
i mean it i mean it literally is a call so there you go yeah there's a famous exchange well i guess
it's famous because it's got a hundred thousand possibly millions of views on joe rogan describing
all uh religion as a cult yeah and i believe it's eric winestein eric winestein is uh saying like
well it's not fair to call it a cult because like then you know there's some like embedded wisdom
and it's like it's a package yeah yeah eat it eat a dig yeah i don't know eat a dig this point is
kind of reasonable but also fuck him anyway um i actually like the guy okay moving on
impressionable elmo is calling in oh dear and he's impressionable and so let's all be very respectful
and not gross corrupt his mind so let's let's go here we go
hi bird i'm gonna say the n word oh no he's been listening to the pcp
he gave no elmo i'm gonna say it i'm gonna say the n word no elmo no no say n word eat cookie instead
i'm gonna do it i'm gonna say the n word yes elmo yes be a garbage monster like me
say the n word elmo build the wall build the wall
oh no god he did it it was bad end it was game i by the way i want to guys know that i
honorably thought that that guy's oscarine's impression was a bin saint impression
be a garbage person like me oh wait oh so so you thought it was me like i would be the one
encouraging to say n word and saying build the wall okay that's not a joke that's not like uh-huh
bin saint each other's like i actually thought that he was going for a bin saint impression that
was like sound like man i'm i'm hurt i'm wounded i'm wounded um well all right there there it is
i'm really sorry to hear what can't what happened to impressionable elmo yeah hopefully our hands
at our hands we did this i hope for better i hope for better for yeah so lesson to all of us
we're the blood is on our hands we're the reason people are dying that's right that's right that's
it's our new catchphrase all right next up is uh peg pelvis peat has a message for sure we all
need to hear crazy shit bin quotation marks saint in quotation marks answer polish name here yep
what did you do with the butter i've been on the edge of my seat all week all whole seven days this
week to hear the resolution i can't believe i forgot the sprawling story about the butter oh
man it's my dismay upon this week's episode sorry peg i did not receive such a resolution
to the story you've uttered the words but no story that's right so bin what did you do with the
butter okay okay back story so if i remember correctly the order of events is um on last week's
shackles for heckles yes i i said something i was telling a story about some some butter
dark souls about how i i cooked some butter or like i melted some butter in a pan but then
changed my mind about cooking so i just turned the burner off let the butter recongeal in the pan
right and then left and then said like like the like like the ultimate fate of the butter would
be resolved this is a big deal this is a big deal and they and you were you were like i will ask you
to resolve the butter story it was my bad on pcp but you failed you did not bring up the
butter story so everyone was left i made a note of it too i made a note before the episode but i
forgot so and then on my stream on sunday someone asked me what did you do with the butter and i did
i did i did i did spill the beans i spilled the beans right into the butter yeah yeah yeah so i
i don't know and and should i should i tell the story or should i leave it as a as a as a twitch
dot tv no you gotta tell us comics exclusive content don't do it ben don't do this to us all
right i'll tell the story but follow me on twitch anyway um uh well um i'm pretty sure i just cooked
some sausage in it god damn well did it use up that's a lot of butter though did you use
well i'll i'll say i'll segue into uh okay i'll segue the segues into my fate my personal
favorite keto recipe okay which is really really delicious and i highly recommend it it is you
get like italian sausage or spicy sausage doesn't matter you chop it up or you or you
yeah you chop it up or cut it up what a fucking whatever and uh cauliflower preferably fresh okay
and you just fucking saute it you just put in a fucking pan and you put it in a bunch of butter
you let the cauliflower soak up the butter you salt and pepper it you salt and pepper it with the
fucking sausage you mix it all up with the sausage it gets all hot and it gets all soft and and
browned and delicious you take it out you put it in a bowl you sprinkle mozzarella cheese all over
it and you let it melt all together and you eat it all i can make this literally right now it's
super good dude it's super good and like and cauliflower is pretty low is pretty low carb if
you cook that it's a totally keto meal and if it's real let's add it to the show notes
because i want to see that shit all right all right actually i have a picture actually i posted
a picture in ben sainz hellfire hamlet it's something like like the first time i made it i
posted a picture in the like food in the food section of that uh so i like ben speaking speaking
of keto ben what uh you said you you're making you're mixing heavy cream and like some chocolate
thing and adding stevia to it and making like drinks right is that hot yeah it's just it's
yeah heavy cream you can dilute it with some water because otherwise it's really thick okay and then
you um stevia and cocoa powder and maybe some vanilla okay my question and you microwave it and
it's hot cocoa and it's delicious all right you're you're doing it hot because i had it cold and the
cocoa does not mix at all it just stays gay yeah yeah yeah yeah and i thought i thought i'd purchased
the wrong kind of chocolate material if you know yeah stirring in cocoa is a nightmare it is the
war and like usually like a blender might be the way to go if you make it hot if you heat it up it
will mix in much better yeah that was the thing because i thought i i mean that was although
alternatively if you want to do it cold you make it in a blender and you add like ice yeah
and like maybe some coffee like i like to freeze coffee as coffee cubes like for ice coffee yeah
so it doesn't dilute it it's good and so like i'll throw in some of those coffee ice cubes
into like you know uh uh heavy cream cocoa stevia vanilla extract and i'll blend it in a blender
or a or a magic bullet or something did you just get a fucking ninja blender and if you stole my
switch i feel i feel obligated to steal his ninja response yes dude yeah yeah mix mix maybe you can
you can add natural peanut butter too which can be good nothing and also thickens thickens it up a
little more and anyway it makes really great like really great fucking like milkshakes that are really
good and totally get that fucking switch top i'm personally invested i just i i've got something
in me that hates when people take game consoles from other people did you know you probably weren't
using it it probably wasn't a big deal do i know about this do i know about this we just we mentioned
it he just took my switch off of where it was set up for iam games and just it's gone he also did
that for my ps4 i think that's so bad like he probably thought like i don't town wouldn't mind if
i just it's not a huge deal i think the bigger deal was when he took my laptop because he was
going to buy it but then decided that he didn't want it because it was too expensive but i opened
it up and there was like a bunch of porn tabs open i'm like dude it's not even yours yet you're
jerking off with it wait i'm on the switch on the no this is a laptop he's going to buy a laptop
for me and was using it for porn but never bought it i'm like you gotta you can't there's like an
unwritten rule don't use another man's technology for porn yeah i mean he's got his he's got his own
computer i mean it was just sitting right there and you know the time was of the essence so clearly
i have to put it on ebay now it's it's defiled and i don't do people pay good money for that the
the digi bro defiled they probably did you file like the fbi which would have to have
hardcore evidence deep cashed in the ssd of doings so all right next call next call here we go this
is from the big gay let's hear oh my god really the big i mean that's what he says oh the big we
we can't prove any identities but i think it's the big gay that's what it says all right all right
welcome let's let's see what he's got for us why the hell do people not like gay people honestly
i can't wrap my head around it what a selfish like what are the most sound quote unquote sound
arguments you've heard against homosexuality also fuck you kyle just because i'm not okay
of homophobia does not make me a fucking sjw i'm just curious as to why people think the way they do
okay hang on what do you mean well you come to the right place because as as avowed homophobes
ourselves we have great insight into the mindset yeah uh first of all i don't know who this kyle
individual is sounds like a real hero uh but uh i would uh build the wall build the wall we got
to build that wall guys we got to build that wall um sounds like that guy's got a lot of gay people
which is intent purpose
okay stick with me here here's my like utilitarian point as to why there's obviously a lot of like
religious baggage here right but okay tell me if this is insane all right two guys for example
can't fucking have a child that is an inefficient setup that's an inefficient setup for that reason
i'm gonna say that homosexuality is objectively inferior to heterosexuality on that basis alone
what do you think uh i mean you have sex and you're not making a child right that was my first
thing but i but i have the option at my disposal that's right that's right but you you've got one
more tool in your toolbox to use therefore like let's say one's a 100 out of 10 one's got to be
a 99 out of out of 100 come back when you've had a kid and you're gonna have any firm is footing for
this argument whatsoever but it's possible and that's not possible you gotta admit that right
here's here's my argument i think you're i think you're close but you're not no you haven't quite
hit on the reason the thing is it's like the more gay people there are the less dudes are out uh
trying to get women which means you have more options by default well but remember i like
hard video games and i want the challenge to have to rise up uh gamers and overcome and can
break stacey's will and you know make her you know my housewife etc etc one of my many harem
wives anyway i don't know i think it's mostly religious shit i think yeah that's really i mean
you can't argue with the doctrine unfortunately i don't i don't think it's no i don't think it's a
religious thing because like the like the alt right is not a religious movement like not even a little
is the alt right anti-gay well of course they fucking are i sure of course of course they are
yes i would i would kind of think so uh but i guess i don't know the thing the thing about the
thing about like bigotry is all just they all come they all fucking come together like racist like
racists are like tend to also be homophobes tend to also be you know anti fucking muslim i mean
i'm not i'm not saying that people in the alt right don't hate gay people i'm just saying i don't
know if that's a tenet of alt right as a platform i have no idea i would imagine the overall tenets
i think it is alt right is like a what they perceive as a degradation of social i mean the
tenet the tenet that's the tenet that like okay since the alt right is not a unified front there
is no there's you know there's no like official position it takes on anything just like which
need to ask richard as a general as a general movement just like the alt like what the alt
right believes sort of in general is just whatever the nazis believes and like like that's that's
just that's just where it all like might be a bit of an exaggeration but it's it's not it's not an
exaggeration well i'm no expert uh i don't think it is you know what there's probably something
just sort of biological about it because like you could you could take my point and like make that
into like a hatred thing i guess you know like if you choose to take it to that place because like
you could say that it's quote unquote unnatural because it's you know not whatever but like there
are like gay animals you know it's obviously people are just gay by default you know many of
i guess some choose but seems like the vast majority just are that way so like i don't know
it just doesn't make a lot of sense to like hate people for that sort of thing um but it is like
different it is like weird kind of for you know heterosexual people okay okay i was i was watching
this video by this guy another sibling of mine jack sainz yeah slash slash lacking saint it was the
truth about 90s cartoons and quote lgbt brainwashing and uh i mean i don't i won't talk about the whole
thing or anything but it it oh god oh god oh no i started this point and it escaped oh fuck the
my point is something about oh something about like oh oh oh like the reaction people like the
reaction people have like like okay like like putting a german character in the simpsons like
putting uter in the simpsons is like it is quote it is you could call it like quote unquote german
representation right and it's just as rare it's just as like unique as like having a gay character
right there's no there's not a lot of germans running around in springfield specifically
and yet that does not give the reaction people have to like when there's a gay character who
is like stop stop shoving it down my throat people don't say stop shoving germans down my
throat because like uter is in the simpsons yeah or like you know i just or like people don't people
don't ask for it to be like you know i'm fine with it just like just just i don't want to see it or
anything right it's something nobody has nobody has ethical problems with someone being german
or at least a far fewer amount of people do yeah you know like like especially going back to the
religious thing no one's going to be like being germans against my religion but like i really think
there's an overarching like miasma that that has lasted for like i don't i mean it yeah like religious
covenant i'm with i think there with what well what i think it is is that i mean religion was
dominant in culture and you know just go back you know a couple decades and you know most people
were protestant christians and you know it's not okay to be gay in there and so i feel like a lot of
you know all right people are just people in general want to preserve the social values that
came before us and some of those social values were rooted in christianity so i think it's not
so much that they think it's bad because god said it's bad but because they think it's bad because
it's the way things have been and you know they are conservative they want to conserve the way that
the society is currently or you know was in the past and the the reason why society was the way in
this past because it was religious i guess that makes sense but by the way addendum to my point
certainly uh like homosexual couples can adopt kids of course that's certainly true um but uh uh uh
uh so but but a heterosexual couple could do that as well so i stand by my point that there's just
one option not on the table and you know what i'll go i'll go a little further and just say
it does look like traditionally the standard family unit was a pretty efficient way for
raising families and i'm just saying that's that's more up in the air when it comes to like
same-sex couples i guess in the gay's defense though you can't have i you can't have accidental
pregnancies if you're gay so like you can't fuck over your life i think i think you're looking at it
a little too pragmatically that's possible i don't i i think you're i think you're trying to reason it
out something that isn't that appropriate at least just a degree yeah but i well i think you're
trying to reason out something that is just kind of inherently irrational what's the irrationality
why i well i'm talking about like not liking gay people is is just it's just but that's not my
position no no i know i know but you're trying to reason out why people do it and i'm saying that i
i think it's a pretty in sort of inherently irrational like emotional sort of response
people have and i don't really think you can reason out a hard why well i gotta know you know
what i'm saying yeah i think it's a combination of biological and cultural factors i guess that
people just and because of course ultimately just everybody can do whatever the fuck they
want who cares and that's that's life just i one thing i found interesting that is like a
was a big argument uh you know like like if you're born gay you know if it's a choice or not that
was like a you know uh one of the main arguments at the center of stuff back you know back in the
2000s you know yeah between the lies and stuff uh but like why does it matter if it's a choice or not
like like why is that part of the conversation why i think that matters in a religious context i think
it i know i can go back to that but still i i mean if it is a if it is a choice well i mean i
if it is a choice then you could say that someone could stop if they wanted to but yeah i guess but
but i mean why they don't want to and so why do we have i mean i mean i guess it just is you know
you know god says it's bad so you want to force well like okay we can all agree that like i guess
it makes more sense to see it as a sin or to like punish it or to or to demand change of it okay
people don't like things that are different right we can all at least agreed ourselves that
historically it sure was the way things were that it was a man and a woman would pair up that just
was the way things generally went right we're not going to be crazy here and so when when something
news around people are going to be like wary of it right they're going to think well that's weird
and strange i don't know what's going on over there i think that's probably like the biggest factor
in the whole in the whole thing i don't know yeah yeah i mean i think another problem with the
some of the backlash from people who don't like gays and stuff is probably because
society especially now seems to confuse tolerance with acceptance you know it's not enough to be
like i'm not really a fan of gay people but fine you have to love gay people like you have to be
like being gays great and all that shit and that was the way i want to say that we were doing so
well and we were talking about you know pragmatics you were talking about video games you were talking
about you know you know being right we were going so well and then the meme question why do people
like why is it so bad i was thinking that why do we hate gay people i was like let's just roll with it
long philosophical diatribe well this is this is why society has been this is the hill
the peace peace peace by this by this question people are dying out there guys people are dying
out there we're the reason people are dying we're the reason the gays are dying and all other people
yeah recipe is all gays sorry we can save you but let's move on to the next question please god
all right this is from endless fart endless fart go
so as a fan of the pcp i knew this guy is munchie and ben saint
and i seen him promoting this game in this world and i say you know this guy is pretty cool you
know you know i'm gonna try the game he seems pretty cool and i don't understand anything i don't even
use discord i'm argentina i'm from argentina uh we communicate here through smoke signals
so i try i try after day after every day after school i come back i come back i do my homework
like a good boy and i try to understand it like three hours every day i try to visit the website
and and they say other information why don't you update your information um i try to talk in the
chat and they say oh you're a fucking rowdy hey you fucking piece of shit no this is that that's
racist that's racist so after three days i think i understand it so i mine i mine i mine i go to
dojo i buy a weapon munchie try to kill me and i avoid it i don't know how and so i leave i leave
i i leave the game there i close i go to sleep i come back from school the next day and and i'm
dead i don't even do anything i leave the game you what the fuck what do i need to do i get killed
anywhere i leave the game right there and i kill no no no where were you dude were you in were you
in cop kill town were you in juvie's row were you in a mine all right he must have been enough
that person is like the bizarro world like a u of roba dobot uh who is chilean he's like he's like
the other like the flip side of the coin like like the dark version of him who uh who who who
was argentina and couldn't get into rfck because he didn't know what tex commands are this is like
this is like like you know the the equipment man it's too okay did anyone else have trouble
understanding that guy i don't understand it i i got most of it i got most of it i struggle here
in there it's uh it's a shame that like the one guy the guy who calls in to talk about like the
specifics of endless war something that i am infinitely interested in discussing and in having
people hear about it has is like you know thickly accented and has like bad audio quality making
it sort of hard to fucking follow what he's saying god damn smoke signals am i right well i mean i
this guy was definitely interesting because he's like i think i felt he was archetypical of people
or archetypal whatever of people who like try and don't get into rfck but this guy's actually
committed more than most i think it sounds like yeah well it sounds like he under i mean he went
to the dojo and equipped a weapon that's like yeah he's he's figuring it out that your problem
your problem must have been that you were waiting in a in a in a pvp zone which is i think this is
a tale of one inch frustration with the game that's just asking to well you know it's not over yet
he's got a long way to go um by the way okay okay well number one um the pcp audience as far as
i can tell is sick of us talking about rfck and like is actively like hostile towards it at least
in the page okay uh so i don't want to dwell on it too much listen i've listen i've been in the
patron lounge okay it's a fucking crag quagmire the quagmire i'm not worried about it there's not
a lot of movers and shakers hanging out in that chat let me tell you not a lot of big
big fat cats we uh those people hang out in the bonus lounge for five dollars a month people that's
where you want to be that's where all the real shit goes uh i mean what i mean what's the
problem are are the are they are they a bunch of digi heads who are just like what's the text
command i mean they probably just haven't tried playing and then they just like are like okay we
get it i mean just like a game move on yeah uh just like the pokemon anyway if you haven't tried
playing in a while or you tried you know playing like a long time ago and it didn't work out orientation
is the channel that you are posted in as soon as you join the discord just read it i like i'm
sorry if it takes you literally two fucking minutes to read this video game explain does it cover
does it cover that yeah yeah it covers everything it covers everything you could possibly need to
know so fucking just read it and the game is the game has changed man the game has changed so much
yeah and like it's so different now even like even like two months ago yeah it was so different
yeah that's true i'm out of the loop now and all right if you guys if you guys just i really think
it's better if you're one of these people who can't understand text commands just too complicated
for you it's too like esoteric uh come come to my patreon where i have a game with buttons and
graphics and like excitement it's good and go pick up a copy of pokemon let's go peek
my affiliate link in the description that gives me five dollars and uh you get a great game
that doesn't challenge you anyway i don't know erin hansen approved erin hansen approved i don't
know if we mentioned but i saw you you tweeted a gif of azumi game i did and it was like she's
running around in a city and it's it has like the the city walls behind her have all these really
great little like graffiti references to other piece of games yes there's there's there's there's
there's like art there's but there's rfck commands there's the autonomous logo there i think there's
more that i'm forget it is there yeah yeah there's it's really sweet and nice of you and t he like
thank you yeah yeah yeah yeah okay just wanted to say if if if tom knows how to enlist use
exclamation point enlist if you can too yeah and he plays pokemon let's go yeah even pokemon let's
go players can play in the store all right oh we're that bad with pride we've got three more here
let's go uh monkey monkey what do you got it's gonna be good on the podcast recently uh nutrition
has been a big topic i'd say there's been a lot of talk about being uh post food or getting on your
keto diet or uh like munchie learning how to cook and i think that's pretty admirable but um i think
i have uh one one one route you guys have overlooked pretty heavily and that's going pre food all right
so let me give you the lowdown so every morning i wake up i get out of bed i don't need to cook
i don't need to uh like whatever the fuck you do to prepare some fuel but i just walk outside
i go down in the corner and i find this pregnant homeless lady and i give her five dollars and
she just lets me breastfeed and i do this for breakfast lunch and every day and i was wondering
what your opinions were on this uh new revolution in the dietary world i think it's really i think
it's really great that you're contributing to the economy i appreciate that breast milk
human breast milk is the most nutritious food people can have apparently yeah that can't be true
like that can't be true it's a fact man have you tried it get out there for for babies maybe well
babies have different needs i wonder is human breast milk keto maybe then they can't be there's
no way there's no way babies consume breast milk and they go from like baby size to full human size
like that so if i start drinking breast milk i'm gonna like double or triple in size at no time
maybe this uh you're you're gonna be like you're gonna be like that guy in dr mcninja who develops
his abs so much that they turn into an organic jet yeah that's right that's what kind of development
everyone's fucking wondering in in the ruins of of the ancient city of kyro they're all wondering
oh why did they make statues of people that were not to scale why did they make statues of people
wouldn't stand upright would have been you know eight meters tall and they're all thinking aliens
you know chocolate blitz but no they just drank breast milk well after they were necessary to
like just fucking tripled in size no extra chromosomes required all right here's uh here's
here's another one from meron pond melon pan meron pan oh yeah i know this guy this this is this
name it's getting there what do you got buddy oh yeah
nade obelum you're gonna end up working yourself into a spiral of frustration and wasted time if
you try to spring back into a weekly show it'll take up so much of your time if you try to put in
as many new features and as much attention as you say you want to but i've come with a solution
after consulting with the higher spirits and smoke on a bunch of weed i present to you
we aga boy why i'm a genius bye we okay our official sequel to we are well think about it's
perfect you get a much juicier show every two weeks with less fluff you can add as many new
features as you want in segments without it feeling overwhelming and you left with more time to work
on bigger projects or those smash reveal things or even just to spend time with your girlfriend
i don't know how this affects your revenue but it seems like you make more on patreon
plus think of all the hilarious by jokes think about it we aga boy we aga boy uh okay not i mean
i mean that's just kicking the the can down the road yeah we all know the real fix here the real
fake is to strip things back and put less effort into them there has been absolute feature creep
in we agua how long how long is it is it how long is it between we are okay i i made a bunch of
big videos but it's been probably it's been like three months or something since the last one
so that's bad that's not weekly at all i mean i'm not one i'm not one i'm not one to judge or
anything you know i'm very behind on all my shit this is this is however my my current biggest issue
that i'm i'm working to fix and i'm working on it real hard people so uh i feel this guy i i think
i talked about hadn't i talked about on the show how i kind of think i might end up doing one
one week on one big discussion i think you did yeah i think so i i had to play that one i was
thinking of skipping it but the production value was so high i had to include it he put a bunch of
music on and smoked some weed he's he's he's wanted to talk about feature creep that was some voicemail
feature creep for sure that's true that was uh that the sign the becker was dark fragrance of
coffee from phoenix right three right i knew i'd heard it before okay well great
excellent uh can't wait to get copyright claimed for that i'm looking forward to it
all right let's go to our last mail of the day this is from one spar bring it bring it um what
do you got hey pcp one spar here sorry about my voice i think i caught something at the glory
whole convention this week and that's the thing i have this weird obsession with consuming cox i
just love it so god damn much but conversely i don't really care much for putting things in but
so i feel like i'm not gay enough to classify myself as a homosexual so pcp do you guys have
any advice on how i can seem gayer than i already am and i know how difficult that would be considering
how much my homoerotic desires contribute to my personality but any and all advice all right
thanks again pcp wait wait there we go stop hang on was was one spar always like chinese or
something i was he chinese there i don't know did he did he not sound like yeah he sounded like a gay
yeah i was gonna yeah i almost said is that econ like i thought it was maybe econ attempting to make
uh uh uh but no make him gay econ econ doesn't have like his his accent is very subtle and it's
not exactly he kind of kind of just talks like this he's like wow what he sounds like he sounds
like he's continually chomping a cigar and like he sounds and like wearing a he's like he sounds like
groucho marks a little bit he doesn't his accent does not really sound chinese but when he speaks
chinese it's like suddenly his his voice makes way more sense i've been told i'm decent impressions
here's here's my econ let me do it's like um really you you you really haven't read the the great
literature of the of the 20th century really wow i'm just saying i've i mean i've read them all
i know everything i'm a bit of an expert on the subject let me just let me just comment here let
me just make some corrections to your point here i don't think those are very good i think i think
i did make some corrections here that's just not it's just not making sense to me how was that
pretty good right the inflection and a little con content spot on thank you a little too a little
too wispy yeah okay oh my god he's a little more a little more like harsh and nasally a little
a little less a little less okay all right although he does do that he does slip into that sometimes
the uh the really though uh that that's classic econ is saying really classic yeah it is it is
oh and making that face making that face is he can all right really funny econ econ is my hero
by the way and i love him he was literally uh cut no i don't want to save my life he literally
saved my life okay something really funny happened with econ and it was hilarious uh i was out of the
house and and and i just you know i don't know what i was probably catching pokemon or something
anyway i was out and i and i realized that i've had three missed calls from econ uh in the span
of like three minutes and he says pick up uh so it's it's obvious something scary is happening
right now yeah yeah so i uh he calls me again and i'm like you know like like what's going on like
hey what's up uh and he says like when are you free i need to talk to you intermits like two more
phone call attempts um like well i'm out of the house but i'll be back soon uh and so i like like i
don't know if i like i didn't think it was like an emergency but i thought it was something you know
like like he's saying like like pick up like where like something's happening like something's happening
right now and i showed you my dick answer me i got it okay and he's like just sitting frantically
sending phone calls and and i and i and i'm like okay i'm i'm home like like like what like what do
you want like i'm down to call uh and uh and he's like all right one second and then he calls
and he's like cooking dinner and he's like uh so yeah hey munchie um uh oh oh that's right that's
right uh ben told me you wanted uh you wanted to be consulted about going to college you need
like a college consultant uh you need some advice from me uh ben told me that and i was like oh i mean
okay i don't i don't know if i have exactly what i said but i sure sure uh this is a telephone
yeah a little bit that's yeah econ has a has a good heart yeah he's hard to the right place yeah
yeah but his his his calibration of urgency is uh you know or at least the perceived urgency of
the situation no no it was a good conversation it was nice to talk to me yeah i just thought it was
the fact that he was the middle cooking duck yeah i actually appreciate that about him that he will
just like call people like to talk to them like i don't do that enough uh i respect that respect
me yeah it's it's not that hard well yeah i know but i don't do it okay it's easier to text so
and i and that and that's a and that's a fault that's a fault in my stars by john green oh i love
crash course world history uh uh yeah to the to the answer our hero once for his question to answer
the gq once and for all uh which i think we've already dealt with in this in this episode i don't
i don't even remember what the question was how can he be gay or how can he like he doesn't want to
act gay but he wants to be perceived as more gay uh i think the one thing you need to do to up your
game is head on over to patreon.com slash the procrastinators you're gonna want to up that
pledge to it like 10 15 maybe 20 dollars no one's gonna mistake you for not getting no one hey listen
yeah hey listen i was i would say wear a procrastinator shirt oh that's a good idea i have two questions
do we do we even sell shirts and two do we sell them on teespring because if we sell them anywhere
other than teespring we need to stop i'm pretty sure it's all in red bubble right now okay we need
to take down the red bubble in or at least the shirts and fucking start a teespring because they
are so much cheaper you were talking about this okay we so much let's look into this let's look
into this yeah okay maybe by the time this episode goes up you'll be able to go to our new teespring
linked in the description okay we'll see if not i guess you could buy them on red bubble and look
really gay in front of all your friends for just throwing your money out the window like that
i would recommend waiting i would recommend waiting until just go go to the iam games
spread shirt buy the iam game shirt and just pluck out the m e s that just says i am gay and you're
golden you know i made you know i made you know because uh you know i i made all the rfck shirts
and stuff and like i you know i realized that teespring was just such a better service i went
and i made a couple of uh ben saint specific shirt i haven't advertised them at all i have i don't i
think this might be the first time i've even mentioned it to literally anyone that i made them
but i did put a little link to like merchandise on my on my twitch and it's it's the profit margins
name i care i care about the profit margins the profit margins are so much bigger on teespring
they're like double and we should be doing it couldn't agree more yeah we should yeah we should
selling them through any other although i do wonder about like the price like does the item
to the consumer i know i know the interesting thing well well here well here's the thing you
can set it yourself and therefore you can have you can you can literally you can make way you can
make way more money for the same cost of the consumer you can make okay you can make the same
amount of money and cost the consumer way less or you can or you can split the difference and make
more money for less to the well we should do this and i know by the way the higher profit margin is
just on across the board benefit to everyone then i got something for you to fix uh it's heinous
i go to st comics dot com there's no link to your twitch here oh my god you're right um another
another good thing about there's no link to my fucking twitch about uh teespring that there is
youtube integration you're gonna integrate your teespring to a youtube channel have it show up
under videos for merch oh shit that's right we could have that on the pcp below every episode
current um that's really good we should do that immediately that's what we need we need to go
fucking corporate hell yeah we do we need to go even we need to go yeah more corporate this is not
this isn't enough this is not i can't i can't fucking get off to this i'm looking at ben's to this
indy sys diy shit are they good you're you're a real big fan of having like the little logo be
like an emblem up on the on the top left you're a real big fan of that like an well why not it's cool
i'm gonna i'm literally gonna i'm really gonna buy one of these i'm gonna get the big one i'm gonna
do this wait really uh which one the uh the one that just says patreon.com no that one is good
and fancy script i mean that one's funny i would i would get such a kick if anyone bought that one
dude hopefully um yeah send a picture like you know i actually i i actually think i might huh i said
someone do that take a picture of yourself send a bit on twitter so i can see it too i i kind of
do want to get one with the heart logo because like why i'm buying this right now i'm buying
this right now right now oh my god um fucking uh link link oh dude i'm gonna get in a four xt i
don't even know what xt means nate nate i'm gonna fucking call you out right now oh yeah you told
me i'm so mad that you wanted you told me that you wanted a slime corp mug slime corp mugs exist
and are available and have been for weeks and you have you have okay well uh so i'm just saying
i'm saying you're not obligated to do anything however you misled you misled our marketing
not true we invest we invested you we invested huge sums of investors money all right listen
in that scheme and it didn't pay off i still do want one if i if i could snap my fingers get one
that'd be great i might even go purchase one you immediately but but yeah and it's true when i said
that i was burning with a passion that was at my peak level of playing endless war when i was talking
about that i've been playing less recently so it's not exactly top fucking priority to rush over
and get myself a mug even though objectively it would be sick that's where it would be that's where
it's at so i told no lies sir no lies all right yeah well i'm just okay you know i went to i
i i specifically like based on you saying that i went and like searched around websites found the
ideal one which incidentally was spread shirt because spread shirt lets you make mug every other
service if you want a mug to be not yeah you can't do it all you can do is have a white so
with like a big ugly like colored rectangle around it but spread shirt lets you print a design on a
base black or red mug and okay so you're telling me to get the black slime court mug i can go to
teespring and get it no no no no that's on spread oh that's on spread shirt okay gotcha there is
there's a link on the twitch on the twitch rowdy rowdy fricker's tritch there's like a separate
link to teespring there's spread shirt okay see i didn't know these facts like which one to go to
now that i know what to do that that is making it easy it eases my path what if i do research and
shit but okay and the and the mug the mugs the different different different products are like
different like most of them were the best deal on teespring but not all of them so the ones that
were better on other sites are on the spread shirt and the and the red then do you know if the
teespring shirts are snug or not do you know do you know if they're if they're small or not
um well i don't own one myself but um guys guys guys this has to stop this has to stop no
no i'm i'm sorry just go to teespring.com slash st heart and and get your shirt like i'm doing
right now sure is there is there a dash between yes there's oh my god well hold on this is actually
funny and not elongating the podcast for no reason this is actually funny uh remember at rfckcon
when we went to every place that was selling the vapors and i made a big deal about demanding the
people to order more copies of the vapor and i made that i made them write down my phone number and
make them make a special order for the vapors and to alert me when it was in a harvard square
comic book store near them again you remember that yeah i do yeah yeah like like we all like okay we
all walked in to these comic stores and um i like i would just be over in the corner just sort of
just like waiting like everyone would they like like everyone wanted everyone like bought out my
stock because like these things were these places were carrying like two or three copies of peace
they would buy out my stock and then munchie would go and ask for another one and they'd tell them
they don't have anymore i think we're out of that and he'd be like oh man i'm such a big fan i would
love to buy i would buy like a whole bunch of copies like you should like when when you when you
gonna have more because like i know a ton of people who would want to buy more and the second
one we went to two and the second one i was like please like like i want more please order more
like i'm gonna write down my phone number for you like like please like do a special order because
i will buy like five of them and uh he did so i'm on the system now and uh i'm pretty sure it's the
second one where after we left you could hear them say like who's like been saying like what is this
book lol damn that's so cool wait was that the million million year i'm pretty sure i'm pretty
sure the second one that was like in the downstairs the one that was in like the basement yeah yeah
it's million-year picnic yeah um funny because i was literally in first of all i had met and talked
to that guy before when i was giving him the books i was literally in there like feet away from him
as you're having this about me i'm just like uh you don't want to let him know that this is the
man that this is the man who uh they're purchasing things you know i was i was about to say i don't
think i've gotten any phone calls but shit would i have even noticed if i did oh no oh my god
bin my special order i wrote down my phone number for that and you're not gonna return their phone
calls well i don't oh god i gotta i gotta go i gotta go comb through my phone records and see if
maybe i did get a call okay i'm curious go do that friend go do that yeah in the meantime let's
end the fucking episode now i insist was that the last one yeah that was the last one yep oh
so uh everybody at in case you didn't catch it patreon.com slash the procrastinators is the place
to go five dollar pledges for the bonus episodes we got a new bonus episode out right now baron
munchausen bullshit we're doing some kooky roleplay erotic furry shit you're gonna want to get in there
it's actually the best bonus episode incredible it's lovely it's delicious i've been producing some
dope ass animation type shit for it there's there's cool things happening the bonus the bonus episode
um i mean man i want to say i want to talk about what's in there without spoiling it yeah like uh
it has like battle music and battle animations yeah it does it does um so that's pretty cool
took me like you know several days to get it all made uh although having finished it i believe that
i can think of a few ways to make it faster to do i like there i i thought of more efficient ways
to do it like after it was done i was like you know i could have saved time by doing x y and z
yeah all right all right well cool next time maybe if i do i might i yeah it was a lot of fun and i
feel like i learned a thing or two about video editing while doing it well good and it looks
fucking cool go see it people you heard you've heard the hype now go pay for it five dollars on
patreon you get that and 19 other episodes that's 20 bonus episodes total now jesus christ
what a deal uh uh it is twitter twitter at tpcrasnators follow us for updates and shit
it's useful it's good recommended and speak pipe click the link below give us your voicemails
fuck you and a conversation that's it all right the end of the episode we'll see you next week
people go listen to bonus episodes fill up your life with meaningless dribble breath to owe you by
our mouth holes thank you for joining we'll see you next time bye
it was rough interacting with the three of you for that long