Hey, so Ben, about that Christmas thing.
Hey, about that Christmas joke I just made!
Um, I said Merry Christmas, and you said, you missed Christmas, and I said, what?
You mean I was visited by those three ghosts of Christmas, only to wake up too late and
miss it?
Now I can't make it right.
It's a literary reference, do you understand?
No, and I don't want to.
You're from the country of Dickens.
Explain it.
Well you see, there's this character called Kermit the Frog, and he's struggling to make
ends meet with his tiny little family with pigs and frogs, Miss Piggy.
Was Kermit the Scrooge?
No.
I've never seen him up at Christmas Carols.
You've never seen the only Christmas Carol adaptation, the only one.
Not even the original exists anymore, that's the only one.
There is no original, it's simply existed from the beginning of time.
It's older than Christmas itself.
It's got Michael Cain as Scrooge.
People read that story by Dickens about a fanciful world in which holidays exist, and
they were like, this sounds so cool, we should make this real, and then they invented Christmas.
They invented Christmas, and they invented hard working conditions, and curmudgeonly
old men, and ghosts.
They invented labour.
They invented capitalism.
They invented London.
They invented snow, all kinds of great stuff.
The childhood, they invented children.
They even invented the passing of time and death.
Yeah, it was pretty nice.
The ghost of Christmas future in the Muppet Christmas Carol is the scariest version of
death that exists.
I'm curious.
Well, it's not like a visual thing necessarily, it looks like a Grim Reaper, but it's just
like juxtaposed with all the funny Muppets the whole time, and then it's like actually,
you'll die, and no one will care.
Oh my god, yeah, that's one hell of a guy there.
How could they not?
They didn't even have a Muppet.
They didn't even have a Muppet?
Play the guy?
That's crazy.
Yeah, if it was a Muppet, it would be like, ah, like a little death, little time guy.
No, I mean Michael Cain.
Oh, Michael Cain.
I expected that like Kermit would be Scrooge or something.
Well, they always had people intermixing with the Muppets.
I guess so.
I watched Muppet Treasure Island, I think specifically because Jesse said it was the
best movie ever made.
I love that movie as well.
I thought it was pretty good, I guess.
There's a lot of little things like that that sort of made me realize that Jesse was cool.
He liked Tomb Raider, and he likes Muppet Treasure Island, and I was like, oh.
Rare qualities in a person liking those two things.
Liking those specific medias.
Rest in peace, Jesse.
Well, hey, I like stuff that's cool.
I like Homestuck, so, you know, fuck that guy.
Homestuck, Homestuck, actually.
Yeah, you're right.
And I know you're right, but I won't admit it.
The only thing good about Homestuck is the porn people make.
Oh my, oh my God.
Never mind.
No, no, that's not true.
That's not, that's not, not only is it not the only good thing that's not even good or
cool at all.
No, it is.
You shouldn't, you shouldn't say a nasty thing like that.
You fuck.
Look, I just say what is the truth to hell with, with what is acceptable on youtube.com
or any online space.
Pornography is good.
I said it.
Don't you know that what is acceptable on YouTube is the good?
They are one and the same.
Nope.
Oh, shit, I don't have an argument, I just thought it was true, like, shit.
Are we waiting for Tom?
Tom said he was in New York Times.
I assumed he was going to be here.
I mean, I guess we can start without him, I mean, yeah, he knew we were starting.
He knew when we were doing it.
Yee-haw.
So we can give him another minute or two.
Give him, give him the 10 minute grace period and then start, well, we're already like nine
minutes into it.
You know, I mean, if Tom doesn't show up, maybe we should just use this as the episode.
Yeah, maybe.
Maybe we should just say fuck it.
This is, see, that audience, what you just heard was supposed to be, what you, what you
just heard was meant to be bonus content, but we're, so that's a taste of what you'll
get at patreon.com slash the procrastinators.
Eventually when the bonus behind the scenes footage episode is made, it is not made yet,
it's not real, but it will be eventually.
So I don't know.
Sounds pretty cool, right?
It's like a conversation, but again, it's almost, it's almost like a real conversation.
Uh, I, well now, okay, I just, I just glanced.
The reason I got excited a minute ago was I glanced over at, at the ticker.
Bitcoin went up, Bitcoin went up a little bit.
Just a tiny little bit, just a, just a tiny, just a tiny little bit of the amount that
I've lost just today was recouped.
Just a tiny little bit, just a tiny little coin.
Just a tiny, the tiniest little smidgen of crypto value was reclaimed.
Uh, I have had my, my, my crypto is, today's been rough.
Today's been rough because I made terrible decisions.
Uh, I bought in at the worst possible fucking time.
Uh, very, very stupid.
You know, I was like, I was like, you know, it seems so obvious that I shouldn't buy
when the price is high, that probably everyone's not going to buy now when the price is peaking.
So I should buy right now because it'll trick them.
You see, they won't, they won't see it coming.
And that's exactly what I did.
So you bought more?
Have you talked about this on the PCP so far?
I think this is like only happening in the last few days.
I might have briefly mentioned it on the last one because I think I bought
a little bit of Bitcoin before the last episode.
Um, I just, just yesterday, I bought, I sold what I had because I got spooked.
And then I was like, and then it rose again.
And I was like, ah, fuck, I missed, I missed out on that.
Fuck it.
I'm in for the long haul this time.
So I bought a bunch more right as Bitcoin was peaking.
And all day today, it has been slowly trickling down.
And I'm just trying to resist the temptation to be skittish and sell.
Um, because that's what I did last time.
It fucked me up.
All right.
I, it's actually, it's actually gone up.
It's actually gone up, um, like, wait, uh, let me, uh, it's gone up like 200,
it's gone up like 200 points just since this episode began, which is kind of nice.
But anyway, it's, it's like,
part of the, um, the reason I didn't get into Bitcoin when I could have,
because I think I bought some, I told, I told you this earlier,
but I think I'm pretty sure I bought like 44 pounds worth in like 2018 or something.
You, you said, you didn't say, when you said it was 45 pounds, I was like, oh, okay.
Because before that you said, do you think you own a tenth of a Bitcoin?
Yeah, I didn't know how much it was.
Do you know how much a tenth of it?
That's like, that's like $3,000 worth of Bitcoin.
Yeah.
Or it would be now.
At the time it would have been, you know, 600.
Yeah.
I don't know what it was at the time I bought it.
It was like 0.0 or something, 0.0 or something.
Um, but I bought it because it was like all in the news and it was like everyone who had,
who had Bitcoin was like a million.
It is skyrocketing.
It is skyrocketing right now.
It just shot up another like 100 points.
Is it going to the moon?
It's going to the moon.
33, 2, 9, 9.
Oh, it's going back down.
33, 2, 7, 7.
Oh, 33, 2, 9, 1.
See this?
8, 9.
90.
Oh my God.
It's just the sheer vertical green line.
It's like, oh, that's literally money in my pocket.
This is the most fucked up I've ever been.
This is the most addicted to anything I've ever been.
This has completely ruined my life and I'm over.
It's done.
I found the thing that destroys me.
Yeah.
And it's watching the fucking Bitcoin.
It's that this is part of the reason why I didn't really
want to get too much into it because like stonks and shares
and money things that are like money can go up and down
and you don't really do anything.
You just sort of keep track of it and buy and sell.
That whole lifestyle, it's always appeared as though
you can get like a maximum amount of money
from a minimum amount of actual work.
You just need to invest initially and be smart
and learn about all this stuff.
And it's like, cool, that's great.
But my brain doesn't work like that.
And I get too overwhelmed looking at the thing.
I would probably just like, yeah, it would ruin my life.
It would make me just sit here doing nothing
but looking at the thing going up and down
and being sad constantly.
Honestly, that's what I've been doing.
That's what I've been doing today and it's really bad.
Like, it's bad that, oh, I kind of lost money
because I had to pay fees to buy in and oh,
it kind of went down so I lost a little bit in value.
But the real cost of it has been that it has cost me
like a day or two wherein I've been able to do nothing
except look at these fucking numbers.
The way it feels to me is exactly the same as Cookie Clicker
or one of those other idle games where I know
that if I start one of those,
I will get into it for a month, two months,
and I will be so dedicated to getting all the achievements
like from the ground up.
I never like start from a loaded save file.
I always start new, fresh, and I just play
and I'm loving it seeing the numbers go up,
but it really fucks up with everything else
and that's going on.
And this is real life.
So like it's even more damaging if it doesn't go well.
So it's even more stressful.
And I'm like, I don't, even if I could get a lot of money from it,
even if I could somehow find my fucking password and account
because I lost them,
because I didn't pay attention to what they were.
Where did you buy them?
Because like I didn't realize, I didn't know how to get some.
I only got some because PayPal made it
so you can just buy it directly from PayPal.
And I was like, fuck yeah, because they offer me 25 free dollars.
I think like when it was in the news initially
and it was like Bitcoin is now making people millionaires,
I'm like, ah, fuck, I missed the boat.
But maybe it'll keep going up because it was currently going down.
It's literally going to the moon right now.
Right now.
I'm watching.
I can't fucking believe it.
Okay, four context.
Four context.
I bought in last night at like 3.15 a.m.
and the value was about, Bitcoin was valued at about 34.2 thousand dollars per Bitcoin.
And then over the next like, you know, however many hours,
it's it's it's it's sank down gradually to about 32.4.
And then just since this podcast has began,
it is up back to 33.4.
So I don't know, pretty fucking epic, I guess.
Yeah, my value judgment is that even if I can make a lot of money off of it.
It's not worth the cost of your soul.
It's it's not in a moral sense, but just sort of in a like, I know what you mean.
Yeah, it really drains me to think about it too much.
You would have to be.
I would have to be a business boy first and foremost in order to like live like that.
Well, I mean, you get you get into it because you think that it's like, oh,
all I have to do is make like a couple of smart plays and that and then I'll be set.
And then I won't have to do it anymore.
But then, you know, it's never quite that simple.
It's and eventually you maybe you become one of those.
Because you've done it once, then you you feel compelled to do it again.
And then it just it will stay there.
It'll continue.
You can't just stop doing something like that if it works.
I bought the first time I bought in, I just got some just kind of let it sit for a week.
Looked at it and I was like, oh, wow, the price went up pretty good.
And then like I was watching it because the price was going up really fast one day.
I was like, oh my god, this was the day that Bitcoin hit 30 K.
It was it like as soon as it hit 30 K, it like it like shot up another like 10%
in like a couple hours.
It was crazy.
So I watched it do that.
And I was like, holy shit.
And then it started to go down.
And I was like, okay, time to I'm out.
I'm out.
So I sold.
And then I and in all told, I think I made like 100 bucks just from like,
I think I invested like $500 or something in it.
So I made a huge return.
That was like a really good time.
I wish I had invested more.
And I thought that I was like, damn, if only I'd invested more, I would have made.
I could have made so much more.
And then I saw that after I sold, it went down, but then it went up again.
And I was like, I missed out on more.
I missed out on more gains.
I have to be invested.
If I'm not invested, I'm constantly missing out on profits.
And it's literally damned if you do, damned if you don't, because if you're invested
and you could be, you could be losing out because the numbers are going down.
But if at any point you're not invested, you could be missing out if it's going up.
Like you're literally fucked.
I'm fucked forever.
It's a hindsight.
Like it's all predictable, unpredictable, especially with this sort of stuff.
Like normal market shares and stocks are a little more predictable, I assume, than Bitcoin.
Because people always talk about how Bitcoin is insane.
Bitcoin is much more volatile.
It is much more volatile, I think, than a.
Like if you don't pay attention to it every hour, it could plummet until it's completely worthless.
And if you aren't paying attention, if you're not awake during that time,
you might miss out, you might lose all your money.
So it's like, I don't know.
Yeah.
But really, I keep trying to, because I made money a little bit of money the first time,
because I just let it sit.
And really, that's what you want to do.
You want to get some and just let it sit and accrue value over time.
Like buying it and selling it over and over again, because as the market goes up and down,
up and down in little waves, is really stupid and self-defeating.
Because you have to pay fees with every transaction.
And that's not how you're supposed to do it.
You're supposed to buy some and hold some.
So that's what I'm trying to do.
It's been going down all day, but I keep looking at it and I'm like,
just because it's going down right now, doesn't mean it's going to keep going down right now.
I didn't buy it with the idea that I would sell it,
like as soon as I could make a few hundred bucks off it or whatever.
I was like, I'm just going to buy it and I'm just going to hold it and just see what happens.
Yeah.
And but it's, I'm not, I can't stick to it.
It's too difficult.
Yeah.
I'm not trying to like moralize saying it's a bad thing to do.
No, no, no, no.
But it's, you definitely need the right kind of brain wiring to like keep on track of it
and not go insane.
And I don't have that.
I'm sure, I'm sure I will eventually learn to just ignore it
or just check it like once in the morning or whatever.
One of these days I might actually remember where my bitcoins is
and then I will be able to look at it.
You said you got it like before last year, which means that it must be worth much more now than
when you got it.
I have no idea.
I remember getting it at a time when it was plummeting and it just continued to do that.
Lol.
And I was like, well, maybe Bitcoin isn't for me.
And so I forgot all about where I had it and what my password was.
So I've been, when you were talking about it earlier, I was like, maybe I could try and find
that and I couldn't find it.
I didn't know where the hell to start looking.
I remember this thing called Coinbase or something seemed familiar, but I did the thing
where like forgot my password, send an email and I didn't get anything.
So I'm not sure if that was the one.
Honestly, if I was going to do crypto trading, I should probably do it in something like Coinbase
or something like not PayPal, because I'm pretty sure PayPal does not have the best fees.
I'm pretty sure I'm probably paying more in fees with PayPal than I would with some other
more dedicated trading program.
Yeah.
I just Googled something at the time.
I was like, how to get Bitcoin here.
Here's how.
And it was very confusing and I was scared.
Yeah.
And I managed to spend money.
I'm surprised you went through with it because it seems complicated and daunting.
And like if PayPal didn't just give me a button to click to do it, I'm sure I wouldn't have done it.
Yeah.
I read enough that I was like, well, I'm just going to throw like 50 or 40 pounds into this
and expect it to just disappear and never be found ever again.
Because that's not a lot of money.
I can take that on the chin pretty easily.
Yeah.
That was my mentality at least.
Like it's scary, so I won't do much.
And then I was stupid and I forgot all the things.
That's my thinking.
I'm looking at these numbers go up and down.
Like, oh God, that's my real money.
But I invested an amount that I could afford to lose.
And like, okay, worst case scenario is what?
I'm out like a couple hundred dollars.
Like, well, oh well, what a tragedy.
So, I don't know.
But you know, maybe it's like a, I almost feel like it's a cultural thing.
Like I feel like Bitcoin is sort of a cultural institution.
Is maybe something that I am a little bit chuffed to be participating in?
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, there's no, as far as I understand, there's no guarantee that Bitcoin will continue
to act like this.
It may actually settle over decades into a normal sort of currency that doesn't go
insane like this does.
And then it would just be a normal part of life.
But this is like the advent of Bitcoin in the last few years.
Yeah.
It's pretty cool.
The first time, I said this in the chat before, but the first time it peaked and like it went
from nothing to like whatever, it hit like 10 or 12K or something.
Uh, it seemed like that was seemed like a once in a lifetime event.
But it's much higher now.
I mean, to be fair, that proportionally that rise was much higher because it started out
being worth like a fucking like a dollar per Bitcoin and it went to 10K.
The second time it went from maybe like 6K up to like 30K.
So proportionally, like, yeah, the first one was a much bigger spike.
Even if it's the absolute numbers are higher now.
I really like how the slime coin that I'm currently holding is modeled after the Bitcoin
in the way that it's got the data all over it.
The little circuit board stuff.
It's great.
I spent so, so long taking an image of that like physical Bitcoin representation and like
photo bashing it and then sort of like drawing over the photo bash to make that design.
And then I paid and then I paid someone to make that into a vector.
And then they did kind of a crappy job.
So I had to go in and manually like make adjustments to the vector that that slime
coin is like weeks of work, just like getting it to look right.
I'm honestly shocked that it didn't that like it looks as good as it does physically.
I thought they would fuck it up or like there would be parts of the text that like got mashed
together or something.
But no, it's perfect.
It is.
It's remarkable.
It's so good.
I just ordered 100 more of them actually.
What for fun?
Or are you going to sell them?
Well, the idea is that I'm assuming that they will be sold or or used as promotional items in
some capacity in the future.
I don't know exactly what I'll do with them, but like I almost I didn't quite sell out of the first
hundred I got, but I was close enough that I was like, I should get more of these.
And so I did.
They're not here yet, though.
They're, I don't know, in the mail or whatever.
I like the idea of slime coin being the only physical exclusive cryptocurrency.
Yeah, like it's it's crypto, but every crypto it's contained on these circuit board coins
and you have to physically exchange them.
And they had like a USB port that you could like you could like jack into to extract the data,
but it's been like sanded off and you can't do that anymore.
The data is in there, but it's it's totally inaccessible forever.
It's all dumped up with slime.
That's right.
Yeah, money.
I fucking love money.
Not me.
Sad to say, but it's true.
But I only love money so much because capitalism means that I have to.
It's not my fault.
I'm a product of the system I was raised in.
True that.
Patreon.com slash Benzane.
If you want to make me happy by giving me more money.
Patreon.com slash the procrastinators to make both of us happy and less like like split the
split it down.
That's true.
That's that's true and valid.
Very, very.
I could also say my own Patreon, but I haven't been making anything.
So I feel like that's stupid.
I have been I revealed.
I've been hinting at Twitter on Twitter about the thing I've been working on.
Oh, you haven't said it.
You said it in a Patreon Ben thing that I still haven't listened to yet.
I talked.
I talked about it in the Patreon Q&A.
I talked about what it was and I said in that Q&A that I will probably be posting like patrons only
like updates and like little previews and stuff at pieces of it as they get done.
Actually, I was just working on a little bit for it before we started recording and thinking like,
okay, when I'm done with this, I will, you know, maybe arrange it into into something
that will make it for a nice little update thing.
Just show show those fucking guys over there.
What's what's going on?
Uh, I was pretty I was pretty drunk when I recorded that, uh, F Q&A this month.
I didn't think that I was at the time, but thinking back on it, I was like, you know,
I kind of don't remember recording it very well.
So I think maybe I was drunk.
Lol.
And I just didn't realize.
Yeah.
You know, so who knows how these things happen.
You know, you're talking about your mysterious construction.
My mysterious construction.
I kind of have a mysterious construction and the same reason I'm not going to talk about it is
the same reason you have is that if I talk about it, the idea will be gone out of my head and it
will have less in like incentive or less like less gusto.
It'll drain my gusto and then I won't be making it as hard anymore.
Yep.
Yeah, that's that's that's a little thing.
So, so I guess we're at a standstill.
We're at a standstill.
So I guess neither of us can talk about anything.
So that's the episode, everybody.
Well, hey, Ben.
Happy New Year.
That's right.
Did you get it?
Did you get a big drunk at the Happy New Year time?
No, I didn't do anything for New Year's.
I actually I got drunk the next day after one of my roommates had bought a bunch of
whiskey and then none of us did anything.
And I just went to bed early on New Year's.
I didn't stay up for midnight because fuck it.
And I woke up the next day and the whiskey was just out on the table and I just drank some.
And then I went and I recorded the Q&A.
So no, I didn't do anything for New Year's.
Did you?
I guess, well, every year for the past like three years, I've been doing like a
live stream on Gibbon Gaming for like, oh, it's going to be like the fireworks will
go off and it'll be Happy New Year during the stream.
And like everyone does that.
But since I'm in a different time zone, it'll be earlier for a lot of people.
And, you know, that was fun.
Played 24 of the video game.
And why?
I don't know.
Because it's the countdown?
No, it was just like my brother got me a bunch of shitty PS2
weird games that like just cheap.
And we like playing them and seeing how strange they are.
24 was actually pretty fun and good.
But it got too hard near the end of the stream.
Is it a shooter?
What is it?
You know 24 of the TV show?
Yeah, with what's the name?
Kiefer Sutherland, yeah.
It's basically like a series season of 24 where there's things in different
boxes moving around and you're Jack Bauer or you're this agent or that agent.
And you've got to kill people and jump and shoot and do the hacking and drive real fast.
And it's like, it's actually quite good for a PS2 game at least.
It's quite a latent development.
It was an all right stream.
It was quite a few funny moments.
But during that stream, after like a really funny moment, I thought to myself,
that thing that I was thinking of doing, going back over Gibbon Gaming to see.
Do I know what it is or have you not told me?
The thing you were thinking of doing.
Do I know what it is?
Yeah, I talked about it on the last heckles for shackles live stream, I think.
We were talking about going back over like our own streams and like maybe potentially
paying somebody to get like highlights of stuff.
And I was thinking, I should at least check to see how possible it is for myself to even do that.
So I look back, there's like 556 hours average sort of like a ballpark estimate.
You have 500 hours.
500 something out of stream over the last three or four years.
Oh my God.
Not actually that much.
I say, oh my God, but I wonder maybe I might have a lot.
I would do really long streams once in a while.
Maybe I don't know.
That makes me wonder how much I've got saved up from the past.
A few moments later.
Eleazar, cut that out.
Cut out all the way.
What did you do?
His dinner arrived.
I'm not going to eat it now.
Oh, what was I saying?
You were saying the fight.
Okay, Eleazar, cut me rambling there.
That was, I don't know what I was talking about.
You were saying about there were 550 hours of streams.
Yeah, yeah.
So there's like 500 something hours of streams.
And if I played that back, it would be like 225 something,
a bunch of hours of rewatching my shitty streams at double speed.
And I was like, you know, that's like a full month of work if I watched my own streams
for eight hours a day.
Yeah.
And that's like, that seems like a fucking lot.
But maybe I could just check like skim through a few episodes, a few of the streams.
I go back to some of them and they all have this terrible noise on them.
And I never noticed before because I just remember them having been like a thing.
I never really go back and re-listen to them and they've all got like noise.
Well, like fan noise or something?
Yeah, fan noise or just like background noise that's just annoying.
And I'm like, oh God, I'll have to like download these, get rid of the noise and then look through it.
And it's, I just, I just realized that my given gaming streams suck.
And like you really have to be there.
And you really have to be in the room with me playing the game if you want to enjoy it.
And I understand why nobody watches them.
That's that's just what streams are.
Yeah.
It's just like that.
I think most people don't really care about a little bit of fan noise.
No, yeah, I suppose not.
But like it's, it's, it's annoying me that like I had never noticed and nobody has ever pointed it out
all that time.
But that's on me really for not listening back at all.
Given gaming sucks.
I thought it was okay.
I thought it was like cool or something.
Nothing's cool, Gib.
That's your fucking problem is you think
that's a thing that things can be.
I am going to flip my fucking shit.
I will, here's my promise.
I will flip shit if I'm watching the ticker.
If Bitcoin hits, if Bitcoin hits 34K while we're on stream, I will, I will punch my fucking monitor.
I will crack it.
I will punch my Cintiq and smash it with a thousand pieces for your, no, I won't do that.
But it'll be fucking epic.
And I, and I will let you know.
Did you hear any of that?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, you'll, you'll, you'll punch your Cintiq and destroy it.
I'll, I'll literally kill myself.
Oh, don't do that.
Then all the money will go.
Yeah, you're right.
Yeah, you'll go to your first one.
Just Elon Musk will just inherit it by birth, right?
I assume.
The other thing, the other thing that's keeping me going, the other thing that's keeping me from
suicide is that Bitcoin has been trickling down today.
However, I also got some Ethereum and the Ethereum went up and did really well.
So I lost with the Bitcoin, but I gained some of that back with the Ethereum.
So it's kind of like, I'm a little down, but I'm not so far down.
I'm like, I'm good.
I'm just, I has on the prize.
I has on the prize, Ben.
Why is it called Ethereum?
That's like, like a World of Warcraft magical crystal gem currency.
It sounds, its logo is a fucking Final Fantasy jewel gem.
What a fucking nerd made that.
It looks fucking sick.
Yeah.
I don't, I don't know.
There's a little blurb that PayPal lets you read about each of the crypto.
And it's like, oh, Bitcoin, Bitcoin pioneered blockchain technology,
meaning the secured, secure data is very secure and can't be hacked.
And I'm like, okay, all right.
And then it's like, Ethereum showed what else was possible in the realm of cryptocurrency.
What makes Ethereum special is that it's used in the development of apps.
And I'm like, what the fuck does that mean?
What, what do you mean it's used in the, and it's like, oh, Ether,
Ether is the actual currency.
Think of Ethereum more as an engine with Ether being the fuel that it run.
Like, what the fuck are you talking about?
What, what the fuck are you talking about?
I really feel like alien technology that, that I need a Vsauce video to explain cryptocurrency.
I need like basic baby shit to like, like none of the, none of the fundamental things of like,
you can make coins with computers that just mine like, what?
Like, I don't get it.
I think I understand the idea.
Do they mine at night?
Is that the thing?
The blockchain.
I don't, I mean, I obviously don't know how it works,
but I think I understand the idea of the blockchain is basically just like a peer-to-peer
network, sort of like, what's the word?
What's that thing, the way that you get illegal movies and stuff?
Right, it's some kind of like peer-to-peer network and like,
you can't, I don't know, I read a little thing and it's like, it's secure because to like,
hack it at all, you would have to hack like every, every computer that runs it simultaneously or
something. It's like, okay, so it's this, the reason why Bitcoin is, is a real thing is because
this blockchain is very secure and that means that a Bitcoin is not able to be like spoofed
or duplicated because of how secure it exists.
Does it exist in many places at once? Is that the idea?
What I believe a Bitcoin is, is, okay, I watched a video about this a while back and I'm like,
a Bitcoin is just data, but it's like a specific piece of data. I think, I think it's like a string
of numbers that are the solution to some arbitrary equation and there are like a set of these equations
or something like that and what each, each Bitcoin is the solution to like the next equation in the
set, but it's like a very complicated one and it needs like a huge amount of processing power
to arrive at each one and that's how what mining Bitcoin is. It's like, it discovers these solutions
through just computing.
So like a daisy chain, a daisy chain of, of computer like equations that is linear?
Can you find the original Bitcoin?
I would assume so. I think so, probably, yeah.
What if, what if everybody turned their computers off? What would happen then?
I think, then I think, well, then Bitcoin would probably cease to exist in the same way that
the universe would not exist if we weren't around to experience it.
I hope that I'm making a complete fool of myself, by the way, and everyone in the comments is like,
Ben, you don't understand. The first thing about the blockchain, Ben, you're not a blockhead like
me, Ben, you don't know shit, you're a moron, you're a rude, I hope.
This is the right way to be, is you make a fool of yourself online about something that you don't
know and then you rely on people saying, oh, actually, and then now you know. It's much easier than school.
It's, it's better and cheaper than school and you don't get coronavirus and it's not,
it's remote learning, but it's in the good way because, and I don't, and the best part is,
I don't even have to learn it because I don't have to read the comments if I don't want to.
I can choose my own custom reality. I can choose to acknowledge or not acknowledge
whatever facts the commenters choose to present me with. It's mine, the universe is mine to command,
to control. Yep. Yep.
So, oh, speaking of, speaking of another graph that is constantly going to the moon right now
is the coronavirus in the UK. Oh, it's, oh, America too, America too. Massachusetts really,
it's really gross and I don't like looking at it. It's so fucking bad. If you google Covid UK and
you get like the statistics, the Google statistics up and it's like new cases, the little blip at the
like March of last year is like, it's, it's now a little blip, it just goes up a bit and then
December, November and now January is like fucking crazy. Okay. This is worse than I thought.
It's so upsetting. I mean, I'm scared, Ben. What do I do? Okay. I mean, if you look at the one for
the US, the US is similar, although I see that the UK in particular has like a really dramatic
shoot up just in the last like couple weeks. So that's a fucking, that's a bummer. Yep.
I mean, the US also has like, since like late October, it has just, you know, the waves in
March and July are like pretty fucking small. Yeah, I'm pretty concerned about it too, but you
know, I'm very glad my dad, my dad, I think is qualified for a phase one vaccination,
which is good because he works in nursing homes. So,
Oh, well, there you go. That's very good. So he's probably going to get vaccinated pretty soon,
which is good because he was the one I was most worried about just in terms of him, you know,
because of that, because of his vocation. Yeah, I'm not so much scared of dying myself. It's just
like, yeah, if I don't want to give my dad COVID, and he's the only one who actually has to go out
because he works in construction, sometimes he needs to leave. Oh, God, yeah. Yeah, it's pretty
bad. And so fucking bad. It's, I'm crossing my fingers, but like the whole like new strain of
the virus that's super, super catchable. It's not nice. I don't like it. Is that what it's
deal? It's super catchable? Yeah, I forget the terms that are like smart people use them.
High transmission rate? High transmission rate, like it can easily pass from one person to the
other much more than the previous variant did. And so it's like you don't need to,
you know, before it was like you wear your mask and you'll basically be all right. As long as you
don't like jump into like, you know, you don't as long as you don't sniff somebody's like nose or
whatever. But now I feel I feel like if I go outside and I breathe the air, somebody nearby
buys breath, breathed, then it could happen. I don't know exactly how it works. I just I'm,
I'm scared. I'm scared. And I just really is fucking with me every day. I don't like it.
I'm trying to distract myself by thinking happy thoughts and playing video games,
but like I'm trying also to not do that and instead work and get stuff done.
Yeah. Yeah, I don't know. I'm, I'm, I was disappointed to see that it seems like
vaccinations won't be available to the general population before like, April or so. So,
I want one. I want one real bad.
I want one as well. I don't mind waiting personally because
as a younger person, it I'm not as much at risk and I don't need to get out so much. And I would
like to know a bit more about the longevity of the vaccine based on how long it's been around
and people, you know, once once they start reporting how it's been for the people who
got it initially, then I'll be more like confident in taking it.
Yeah, for sure. I agree. I am a little bit glad that I don't have to be the first one to
fucking take it because like, who knows? Although, I mean, it seems like all indications are that
it works pretty well and doesn't really carry much risk of anything. But we'll see, you know,
there'll be like a whole bunch of people to get it first and we can find out for sure, LaMau.
I mean, I don't think there's going to be like a risk of the vaccine itself and also like,
how long does it last and how effective is it at doing the thing it's supposed to do?
Do you need to take them once every two months? I don't know.
It seemed like, okay, you get, it lasts longer than that. I think it might last like
up to a year or something. Well, you know what, I'm pulling figures out my ass. I don't even remember.
But you have to get two. You have to get like vaccinated once and then you have to go back
a month later for a second one. And like, you're only like semi-vaccinated in the time between.
They were saying on BBC News that the first one is like, the Oxford one they're talking about,
is like the first jab is like 95. So it's pretty, pretty effective. And then the next one, or maybe
it was like 91. And then the next one bumps that up to like 98, 99. So the second one is not as
important apparently, but it is important if you want big immunity. I do want big immunity.
Yes, I would like that very much, actually. SS tier immunity, please.
I'll take the good immunity. Keep that shit immunity for the birds.
Do you imagine trying to vaccinate a bird? Your needle would just go right through it.
Because it just pierced it like a sword. It just explode like in shred.
Wait, it's time. I got to check on my Bitcoin. It's down a little bit.
Is this going to be like a PCP arc? Been checking Bitcoin and going, that's right.
Oh, it's 33, 33, 55. Oh, 33, 60. Oh, 33, 570. Oh, no. 33, 570. Oh, 33, 6. Okay.
35, 577, 65, 544, 39. Remember, I bought in at 34.2. 33.2. So that's what I really want.
You could probably do a live stream of you just looking at the thing and saying the numbers out
loud. Yeah, like the live stream, it just shows the graph. I'm just like, oh, 33, 612. Oh, 604.
Oh, 33, 604. Going once. Okay, 613, 619. This is the best fucking game I've ever played.
I can't believe how grossing this is. It would be like a job for people who are blind
and they want to get into Bitcoin, they would listen to your stream to get the numbers.
It's just me like saying them. Saying them and occasionally going,
okay, no, no, no, it's fine. Okay, 35. Okay, 36. Okay, 110. Okay.
They can tell this from my tone of voice how excited they should be. Oh my god.
No, this was a mistake. Becoming a crypto guy, big mistake. This is the last mistake I'll
ever make. This is it for me. I'm toast. I'm toast after this. There's no coming back from this,
not for me. I just don't have what it takes. I feel like funny mistakes are pretty good, actually.
Well, I hope you think it's funny. I hope you think it's funny when I'm in the poor house.
Like you're a hundred or two hundred dollars having lost. That's right.
And I can't afford the rich house that you have now. That's right. That's right. I'll have to go to,
I'll have to be a Bitcoin debt peonage. I'll have to, I don't know, hammer license plates or whatever
it is you do. I'll have to hammer license plates to put on Elon Musk's Teslas.
I thought you were about to say testicles. I don't know why.
That's right. That's right. No, that's what I was going to say, but I censored myself
because I knew that wouldn't play on YouTube. That would get us. That would get us. That would get
us demonetized. I ran out of gummy shit. I ran out of my good, I ran out of my good gummy shit.
Yeah. I was, I was off keto. I was doing sugar gummies, but now I'm back on keto.
So I need to use the gummy, the keto stuff, the isomaltoligosaccharide or the IMO.
And I just use the last of it and I don't have anymore and I'm sad because that's so,
that's stuff so good. The last batch I made with it came out so good. I made little watermelon,
like little half cubes. I didn't make worms. I made little cubes and they were perfect. It was
like the best ones I'd ever made. They were like chewy, sticky. They were, they tasted just right.
They had the perfect consistency and I can't do it again because I don't have the stuff anymore
because nobody, nobody sells it. No, no American company sells it and the Chinese
distributors will only sell it in like units of a metric ton and I'm not going to drop like
thousands of dollars on a metric ton of this fucking tapioca fiber.
So what is it? Is there a way to like science experiment your way to making it yourself?
Or is it like the raw materials themselves are still also too difficult to get?
I feel like it's probably extracted in some sort of chemical process that I would need like industrial
equipment to replicate. I would have to, I would have to like receive shipments of
whatever fucking Jerusalem artichokes or whatever and, and run them through some sort of like chemical
bath is probably in a series of chemical treatments in order to separate the fiber powder from the
fruit. So I don't think I can do that. But I can dream.
No, no. I've been watching a YouTuber called Niall Red who does chemistry videos. They seem like
they do a lot of fun things where they're like Niall Red Niall Red and I L E Red.
And it's just sort of like basic, not basic chemistry. It's quite
complex and they use a lot of know how. I know this. I know this guy. I saw a video.
I saw a video of him trying to take the caffeine out of Red Bull.
Yes, to make caffeine free Red Bull. He's made a lot of really interesting things where
honestly, my favorite part is just seeing the chemical processes he goes through
and him just dryly explaining that I did this and then I did that and then I waited until it was
the right temperature and then I took it up and I did this and I filtered it off and I did that
and now I have this and it's like, it's just going through the process in a very like non-charismatic
way, which is really, I don't know. I love, I love listening to him.
Non-charismatic. Yeah, I like. Charisma sucks. I love videos that suck. Charisma is just like,
hey guys, video and I'm like, shut up, shut up. Don't ever say that to me again.
You're all so smart and handsome and you're talking to me like and you're on stage or like,
shut up, just be boring and shitty. I like that more.
If you make me like you, it makes me hate you. It's true.
Yeah, I know. I agree. I unironically agree. I hate it. I hate it when,
I don't know, there's a, there's, I think there's a, there's a, an uncanny valley. There's a very
steep uncanny valley where someone can be almost, when someone can do something in an almost charismatic
way and maybe they get close, but there's something a little off and it just makes me hate them.
It makes me, it makes me distrustful. Like you're manipulating me. I hate you.
Yeah. It's sort of a very subtle way. Not like, oh, this guy's clearly fake. It's just sort of like,
like a very vague feeling that I can't really like accuse anyone of being anything in particular.
I just, I just, I like it when there's just a straightforward series of events explained
by a person. They don't need to be completely devoid of, of like comedy or, or heart.
I don't know. There's just, maybe it's just some sort of, some sort of something
that I dislike about like the biggest YouTubers. Like I can't imagine, I can't imagine like
having a conversation with Matt Pat. You know? Oh my God. Oh my God.
Not that I would really want to have a conversation with like a YouTuber, like ew,
ew, gross, but like, I don't know. That's not really the metric I was going for. I'm trying
to explain it, but I can't because I'm stupid. Anyway, Nalred's really good. He made a video
recently where he turned plastic gloves into grape soda flavoring and drank it.
Because there is a chemical in a specific kind of like surgical glove that is very
similar to the same chemical used to make grape soda flavoring. And so he chemically changed
the thing using acids and bases and all these sorts of processes. And it was like, I just,
I just love being along for the ride on those strange journeys. Like what if I could do this?
I tried it and here's what happened. And it worked. I'm looking at that video and watching
him just make like weird brown dirt looking powder out of stuff. Yeah. And it looks gross, but damn.
I wonder how it tastes. I guess it must taste all right. Is this, he goes into the hole like,
Is he a trans guy? Is he a trans guy? Not to my knowledge.
Okay. I mean, not to assume. He seems quite young. He looks like quite a young guy.
Like he's, I don't know, some sort of science prodigy or like was really good at it in high
school and then went straight into doing this sort of thing. He's been making videos for a long
time. Has he? He looks, I think he looks like he's not actually that young, but he has like
a youthful face for his age. Yeah, something like that. Because it surprised me. It surprised me
to see him like, I mean, even his voice is a little high pitch and I saw his face for the
first time once. I was like, that can't be the person who's making all these incredible science
videos. That doesn't make any sense. How could somebody so young this are good? He looks like an
idiot. No, no, I didn't mean that. But I did. Secretly.
Yeah. I've seen, I've seen a few of these. The caffeine one was the one I remember. I've probably
seen one or two of these. Man, I love YouTube. I love YouTube videos. Man, a new new summoning
salt new summoning salt came out this past week. Yeah, boy, just I just watched that. Oh,
his videos are great, but they just sort of, something about them is different from the
original few that he made, where they seem like extremely long and I get kind of tired.
There's a, there's a, there's a thing about the funniest thing in a summoning salt video is when
like, he'll, he'll get to a point where like, this guy had finally achieved the ultimate,
the ultimate run. He got all the good luck and he did all the good tech and everyone was blown away
and the record was, was, was set and it would stand for years, except no, because the very next day,
this fucking guy showed up and he'll introduce some new guy. He did it in this past one and he's
done it before and he'll show like the guys, whoever is being introduced, the guys like YouTube
Avatar and their, their screen name and it'll be like some guy and it'll be like so and so,
900 subscribers. It's like, I don't know. It's like, it's, it's, he's, he's describing them as
of if it's big fucking like heavyweight, they're like a celebrity that we should be like, oh,
shit, it's this guy, but it's like someone who you've never heard of and nobody's ever heard of them
and this is the only thing that you would ever know them for.
I mean, I think it's just because watching speedrunners is such a time-intensive thing,
keeping up with them. I think most people who watch speedrunners actively are speedrunners
themselves. So it's a very small community of like hardcore people and then us, like laymen
on the sidelines are just like, oh, what was that? More like laymen. It's just like, huh,
what's that going on there? Is that a record? Cool. They did it real quick, didn't they?
Wow. Video games. I like video games.
But I would, I would never like watch a speedrunner.
Oh, like watching over and over again. Yeah.
No, God, no. God, can you imagine?
You'd need to, I mean, at first you'd need to know the run that they're doing and why it's
difficult. I can't, I can't imagine getting into speedrunning without also
doing speedrunning. Do you know what I mean? Like watching it.
Yeah. The most, the most dedicated viewers are probably. Speaking of speedrunning,
I watched another video that I watched, I think this morning or last night or somewhere in between.
There's a guy called Carl Jobst and he released, he made a video asking about dream and whether
dream cheated or not. Do you know about this whole dream thing?
I think, I think I've seen the video you're talking about.
It was really good. And I, I, I, I've been one of these, I've been one of those people who is just
like sort of bewildered by this suddenly seeing everyone talking about this guy dream
all over Twitter and stuff. And I guess now I understand what it was. It's very frustrating
because after watching that video, I, I, I understand, I feel like I understand completely
what happened and why and how he cheated and why it seems like he definitely did cheat,
but I also completely understand how people could like fail to get how it was that he did
cheat and like how they know. I don't know, like he gives some examples, he shows examples on screen
of people saying like, uh, oh, but, or I don't know, because it, because it wasn't like he,
it wasn't one particular run of Minecraft that was cheated. It was like the game itself was
altered to give him better odds of getting a particular thing to happen. It was very sneaky,
very sneaky and you know, sort of impossible to prove unless they go to all the, they do all this
fucking, you know, running trillions and trillions of like statistical
models of it to like see if they can get luck like that and they can, it's, and it's impossible.
I don't know, it was pretty, pretty neat. I thought it was a neat thing that happened.
It is pretty like, like I could imagine he cheated based on the evidence that was provided,
but there's still wiggle room to say like, like, no, no, but like it's the fact that there's like,
it's not proven like concrete. There's wiggle, I feel like there's wiggle room for him
to be a weasel about it and be disingenuous about it in a way that people will believe because
they don't understand. Right. Because they haven't had it like explained numerically to them,
because what it really is is like a numbers question of like, are these numbers possible?
No. But if you like sort of divert from that question, you're like, oh, but the run itself
is totally possible. And it's like, yes, that's true, but that's not the point.
But you can, you can make it about that if you want to, which, you know, he has every reason to do.
Yeah. LaMau. So I don't know. Now I know. Now I know what the deal with that is.
I did see, I guess we're just talking about YouTube videos we've seen recently.
I guess so. I mean, what else do we fucking talk about?
Well, I could talk about have been depressed.
Lol. Did you see my Money Spenders podcast? You said you listened to it.
I did. I did listen to it. I did. You've been clean in that room for like a long time now.
Well, I mean, it's pretty clean now. But like, I feel like it's I feel like it's been months
that you've been saying like you were going to clean that room. You know, I mean, it was the
whole of December, basically. Like I said, I would do it. I said I would do it at the end of
November. And then it was, I don't know. Maybe maybe I'm crazy. Maybe I'm smoking crack. But I feel
like I feel like multiple times in like previous ones, you've mentioned that as a thing that you
were going to do. I don't know. I probably mentioned it multiple times as in I talked about it on
November's Money Spenders podcast and on the PCP maybe once or twice.
Maybe, maybe, maybe that could be it. In any event. Yeah, I've it's it's weird and annoying.
I seem to have like the big like, like everything sucks. And I'm the worst guy ever.
Time to die in the morning when I'm waking up. And then I'm like, oh, yeah, whatever. And I'm
okay. And I've been doing that. My mysterious construction has been underway. And then during
the end of the day, I'm like, Oh, but you know what? I really am the worst guy. And I should die.
And all that stuff. And I go to bed and wake up and it's fine in the middle of the day. And it's
like, well, I mean, I guess I guess I guess it's working. I guess something's working here.
I can't wait to tell my therapist will be useless about these things.
Is your therapist useless?
It's it's just early days right now. I've did they they asked me to like write down what I do
during the day. And then they'll start formulating a plan of like reform your thoughts and think
positively instead of negatively. It's the sort of stuff you hear and it's like, yeah,
that sounds easy. Just do something else. Just have a different thought instead of the one you're
having. I really wish there was like an obvious way to change it. But there isn't. You just need to
figure out how to trick yourself into thinking the other thing.
Okay, hold that thought. 33, 3, 3, 7, 5, 4, 33, 7, 5, 4. We're getting there. We're going to make it.
Nice. Oh God, 33, 7, 5, 0, 4, 7, 34. No. Okay, I can't look. Keep going. Keep going.
Um, I don't know. There was this, this Wiser app, W-Y-S-A, which is supposed to be like
therapy, but like an AI. And I'm like, well, I guess I'll do fucking anything. I'll do the
the the cream therapy, but an AI. Does it like prompt you with questions to think about or something?
Or is it like a chat bot? Yeah, you chat to it and you say things and it's like,
how are you feeling? Oh, I see. Here's something that maybe like you could think about, maybe try
doing this. And here's some examples of thinking patterns that lead to depression. And it's like,
it's kind of helpful hearing it like written out based on what I'm telling it. It's not that
very good though, and it repeats itself a little. But I think just having that has been all right
the past few days. It sounds like something like that is good and that it can just like
prompt you to be thinking in the right way. And like, you don't need a person to
basically remind you the same, the same things over and over again, right? Yeah, a lot of the
difficulty is to keep your mind on the right mindset or whatever. Is when you slip back into
the bad mindset, it's difficult to use your compromised brain to do anything,
you know? Because it's already thinking in the wrong way. And you need someone to tell you,
actually, this is a logical fallacy and you need to think differently to maximize everything.
And the ways I'm thinking are like, oh, I see that is this sort of problem that I keep having.
I get it. Like having just knowledge of thinking patterns is useful.
I have the same, I find the same thing about like at night time, my mood often
markedly gets worse at night. And I feel the most depressed at those times. And I don't know,
my usual solution to that is, well, better get on a regular sleep schedule. So I'm going to sleep
before I start feeling like that. That is, that's what is helpful to me about that particular issue.
A lot of the things that are like the simple solutions to these problems, like get some
exercise, have a regular sleep schedule, change your place, change your environment regularly,
change your diaper, stinky. I mean, at the moment, it's, oh, shut up, don't say the word,
you can imply it, we can't say it. I'm sorry, I'm sorry, YouTube, I'm sorry, don't demonetize us.
I'm already losing so much. Oh my god, 33, 6, 5, 0. Jesus Christ. I'm already lost everything,
YouTube, please don't take this from me. What was I saying? I don't know. Oh, the basic things like,
yeah, like get exercise, change in scenery, like environment, if you stay in the same room for
all day, every day, it makes you go insane, which is a problem right now because that's what they're
expecting people to do in the lockdown situation. And I'm like, gee whiz, gee willikers, I can't
really, I can't really solve that problem. So I got to escape into the VR world or fucking play
Minecraft or just think, just think about all the, I need a video game analysis video to say,
this is the most immersive game ever. And I'm like, I'll play, I'll buy it, I'll play it.
I want to be immersed, I want to pretend I'm somewhere else. Yeah. But yeah, all I can do
right now is exercise on like a bike, like a stationary bike. That's a pretty good one.
I'm lucky I have that. That is pretty good. If I had a stationary bike, I might use it.
Or a running machine. Those are all right as well.
You mean a treadmill?
Treadmill, yes.
A running machine is like those robots that they make.
You know, the ones that are going to be killing us soon. The Boston Dynamics ones.
They're right in my backyard. They're right in my backyard, kid. They're coming for me.
Could you send a little drone over to take a sneak peek?
I can't, I'm afraid that I can't tell them what to do. Nobody can anymore.
I saw that they were doing like, oh, the Boston Dynamics robots are doing a little dance now.
They've learned how to dance. And it's like making them, making them appeal to the human brain as
like not a danger, not a threat. And then they don't fall for it. It's the same. It's literally
the same as the Pete Buttigieg Jants. He's trying to convince you that he's a real human being,
and you shouldn't be afraid of him. Don't fall for it.
And, you know, the spot or dog, whatever the Boston Dynamics dog is,
he's got like the little crane head with the clamp. And he's like coming in and then he just,
oh, he pulls out a Glock and he's just such fucking going to town.
He loves it. He loves it.
You know, all we need to do is to develop guns that robots can't use with their
mitten hands, and we'll be all right. We've got a developed weaponry that can only be activated by
sincere creativity, and we're just like, artists will be the most powerful people.
No, you just, you have to, no, wait, it's literally endless war. You have to enter a
capture every time you fucking fire a gun is literally that we fucking pioneered it.
Ah, you have to solve it. It's on the side of the gun as a little touchscreen.
You have to solve the capture before it can fire. Robots can't use it. Robots neutralized.
Dude, robot uprisings is going to be so fun when we have to, we get to shoot people and we don't
have to feel bad about it. Oh, because they're robots? Yeah.
There's a, there was like a, there's a VR game. There's a VR is an Oculus game that I think is
about shooting robots that seemed like was very well reviewed. And I think I at some point planned
to get it, but I didn't. And I don't remember what it was called anymore. And I, you know,
and I have a problem where I feel like my Oculus Rift went heavily underutilized because the only
thing I ever used it for was super hot and a little bit of Beat Saber that one time, not Beat
Saber, whatever the VR one is where you slice the cubes. Yeah, that's Beat Saber. Oh, okay. Yeah,
Beat Saber. Dur, didn't get, I feel like I didn't get my money's worth out of that freaking thing.
And it's such a fucking hassle to set up. It wasn't your money though. It was the
vaporous Kickstarter money. Oh yeah, I guess that's true. You gotta give the people what they want.
I never set up, back when I used to stream, I used to, I said that I was going to set up like
VR chat. That I was gonna do like VR chat. Or I said I was thinking about doing it, but I wanted
to have it like, I wanted to set it up so that I could see the Twitch chat on like in the headset,
like displayed in front of me so I could read what people were saying while I was VR chatting.
And that seemed like so, I tried to do it and I, I couldn't figure it out. One guy,
one guy like kept messaging me like, reminded me like, here, this is how you do it. Here's
some software that lets you how to do it. And I kept saying like, okay, I'll check it out,
I'll check it out. I never did it. I never checked it out. I let everyone down. I failed.
What you eating? I'm eating beef bourguignon.
What? You made that up. Beef bourguignon. Beef, that's not real. Beef bourguignon and rice.
You're a fucking liar. Google it, if you can. How do you, I can't, that's not a real word.
Beef bourguignon. It's French. Burger. Oh God, it's, oh God, it's real.
Burger. It's basically, it's, it's basically just like a stew. It's just beef. It is. It's a beef
and onion stew, but it's very nice. Sure. Whatever. Whatever. Let me, let me complain. Let me complain
about something. I'm actually very upset about this. I said before that fat Ben is back, right?
And then I found this out right before I went to go see my parents for the holidays
because I weighed myself. Now, when I weighed myself, I was like, oh wow, I'm almost back up to
like the weight that I was in my heaviest, right? At my heaviest before, like around at radcon four,
no, sorry, radcon three, I was, I was about 195. I was almost 200 pounds.
This time, I weighed myself and I was about the same. I was like 190 something and I was like,
oh shit, damn. Good thing I didn't hit 200 though. Time to clean up my act, right? So,
I'm like, okay, I'm not, I, I'm glad I caught myself before I could hit 200. So, you know,
I go back on strict keto. I go back on very strict keto. I start eating cauliflower. I'm,
I'm, I'm eating chicken. I'm eating, I'm eating, you know, I'm cutting back on all the stuff.
I'm going back to strict keto diet. Well, I weighed myself yesterday and I fucking gained
like eight pounds and I'm like 200 and something now and I'm so angry. I'm so angry to report that
because I've been keto for like a week now. And usually when you start keto, you shed a bunch
of weight at the beginning because your fucking glycogen depletes. What the fuck happened? I don't
understand. I don't understand and I'm fucking mad about it. And I'm taking it out on you.
Fuck you. Okay. I don't really feel like I've been attacked, but good job. Well, darn.
I fucked it up then. Feel sorry for me right now. Okay. There, there.
Okay. Don't fucking go overboard. That's enough. Stop.
I'm upset. I'm upset, but it's okay. Just gotta, just gotta stick to the plan.
Just gotta trust the plan where we go one, we go all. Follow, follow, follow. Q is the thing.
That's what I was missing there. It was a joke. Do you think it might be fate to be fat, Ben?
Because it's like similar to letters to fate and fate.
Horrible. Yeah, you know, that actually makes a lot of sense.
Fate, Ben. I think that this is just destiny. It doesn't even have anything to do with my diet.
It's just destiny. Just how fat, how, how, what weight do the stars want me to be?
You get 3,000 pounds.
Wait, hold on. Eleazar, cut this part. I gotta mute. I gotta, I gotta be back. I'll be back.
Okay, I'm back. Hey, what's up? Hey, what are we talking about? Hey, what did I miss?
You missed the Gib song. The Gib is a lone song. That's part of the bonus episode.
Oh, yeah. Boy, I should head over to patreon.com slash the procrastinators
for an only $5. Make it possible to in the future hear that in the, in the,
in the, the, the outtakes bonus content episode that will exist one day, I'm sure.
We surely, surely we must be getting close. Surely we must be approaching the point where
we have enough to make that. And when we do all this foreshadowing will, will pay off in splendid
fashion. People can try to piece together what, what clips each episode is from. Yeah. Yeah, yeah,
yeah. Ooh, it's a puzzle and a podcast. You have to work for your entertainment.
That's, I mean, isn't that, isn't that the best kind though? Isn't that when you feel
the strongest connection to a work? Yeah, I suppose. When it demands something from you.
Yeah, you know, if you, if you just listen to a podcast and you didn't, you don't like put
it the work in, you know, you didn't, what was the copypasta? Like you didn't improve,
you didn't learn nothing. Oh, you cheated not only the game, but yourself. But yourself, yeah.
Hell yeah. Hell yeah. You cheated not only the podcast, but yourself.
Oh no. We're stalled out. We're stalled out at 33, 5, 7, 35, 83, 35, 99, 5, 99. Can I get 600? No.
Oh, there it is. 613, 613. 610. Holy shit. It's too much. Best update quite quickly.
Yeah, like every few seconds it does. Maybe it's just your heart rate that you're looking at going
up and down. If that were true, then whenever I looked at it, it would skyrocket. Earlier today,
I opened up the thing with the ticker on it and I looked at it and there's a glance at it and I
saw like, okay, it's been holding pretty stable. But as soon as I looked at it, it just plummeted.
It just like went through the floor. I was like, no, I have to not look. I can't look at it.
And I looked away and I closed the window and it worked because now it's going to the moon.
Wait, wait, wait. I got to update you. I got to give you live updates. I know you crave them.
Here's where we're at now. As you see, it's progressed. Oh, so yeah. It's been wibbly wobbling
around that same bit, but it's still pretty high up there. It's just kind of been chilling.
Just kind of been chilling. Well, wait, wait, I'll show you where it started for me.
This is for context. For context. For context there. That was where it was when I bought it.
So as you see, it was a harrowing day of it just tanking. And then just when we started the recording
this, it was like, oh, maybe things aren't so bad. Oh, wow. You bought it pretty high up.
Yeah. That was the second time you bought. That was the second time I bought it. And it was a
mistake. No, no, no. It seems pretty stupid. But then like, I mean, this is, let me show you the
last day or two, or this is the last week or so. And you will see that it's even worse
it's even more foolish than it appears at first glance around here is where it is on screen
in the grand scheme of things. Oh, so, so, you know, obviously that's that's the time to buy.
What if that's the like peak for like next whole year? It might it literally could be.
It literally could be that like, that Bitcoin will never ever be this high again. And this was
the highest it will ever go in the history of the universe. That's funny. It's been,
it's been, I mean, okay, just for just for one more, just for one more piece of context, what is
the what is the here's here's the entire history. Here's the entire history of Bitcoin.
And it shows like where we're at now relative to where it started. And
you know, so we're up there, we're up there on fucking mounts, mounts, whatever.
2011, I think it started and then 2018 or 2017. Big boy. Now, yeah, wow, twice almost
like, like 2020 end of 2017 beginning of 2018 was when it was like, because you know,
over on the left there, it's worth like fucking a couple dollars. And then it explodes up to like
almost 20k. And that's when like fucking freaks like Elon Musk all made like a shit ton of money
selling at the at the peak or whatever. Yeah. And then it kind of went down. And then,
in the ensuing years, I remember I'm thinking like, dang, you know, that was the time that was
that if I was ever, if Bitcoin was ever going to make, you know, fortunes, it would have been then,
you know, surely it's not going to happen again. Well, here we are. Oh, well, I mean, yeah,
what are you gonna do? It's not really going to make fortunes from from because it didn't
start so low, you couldn't have bought it. Yeah. And then it increased. It's not it's not such a
dramatic. Yeah, you're not going to go from owning like a few hundred dollars to owning like
hundreds of thousands of dollars, or millions or whatever. You're gonna, you're gonna go from
you're gonna go from having a few million in Bitcoin to having like a few tens of million in
Bitcoin. If you have a single Bitcoin, I mean, it is a big increase. That's that's an interesting
graph. I like looking at graphs. Pretty cool, right? Numbers, they really, they really make you
think really make you really get the get the the juices flowing.
All right. Oh, I love bogging down the podcast with Bitcoin talk. This is my new thing. This is
the new arc. This is the start of the Bitcoin. This is the Bitcoin podcast now. Oh, no, do I have
to learn about something? No, well, yes, but the person who doesn't know about Bitcoin. Yeah,
you can explain things to you can be the guy who's always like, but Ben, what does that mean?
And I'll you're like the audience surrogate who doesn't know what the fuck they're talking about.
And I could be like, aha, you fool, you rube. Well, I'll explain it to you. So yeah, and then
and then you'll make a fool of yourself. The chat will the chat will like correct you over and over
again. Yeah, exactly. Exactly. It'll be like a comedy routine where you're like the straight man
audience surrogate and I'm like the the pompous dullard who thinks he knows and and that's where
in the comedy emanates when that's whence the comedy emanates. I believe that's how comedy works.
You know, I've ever since ever since I became the trans as they say, um, Lamel, all these like
terms that are like male gendered that I used to think, oh, you know, they're like
gender neutral, like layman and straight man. And it's like, it feels different now thinking
about it. Like, I don't want to change the word because that sounds weird, because I know it as
straight man. Straight man. Straight man. I like that. Straight man. I like that a lot. It's the
first thing I think of like replacing man with man, but it's kind of hard to notice. So I don't know.
When I when I posted that picture from the Radcon calendar, uh, uh, suggesting that Tom would be
the next to transition, I thought it was really funny when people said people suggested like
can't wait for Tom Tom boy Oliver. And I thought that was really funny. Because like a Tom a Tom
boy is a girl. So to make Tom into a girl, you make his name boy. I don't, I don't know.
Hilarious. It was hilarious. I loved when I saw comedy, comedy genius. And then in that lineup,
Munchie would be next. So, uh, no, no, Nate, Nate after Tom. Oh, oh yeah, Nate. Nate than Munchie,
then you. Then me. Wait, are we missing someone? No.
It's only the, it's only the, it's only the, um, oh yeah. Yeah, you're right. Five of us, six of us.
Only the five of us. Man, I look so fucking good with my goth makeup and my, uh, and my wig.
That wig was sick. Lending me that wig, lending me that wig was the only good thing May ever did
in her entire life.
Lama. Uh, uh, good times. Good times at Radcom for, um,
Oh, I've got a, I've got a cool new thing to, to announce. So it's not really an announcement,
but I'll be the judge of that. I never knew. Because I didn't know what Webkin's was. I didn't
know the hypocrite, the hippo, the plush was a Webkin. I still don't know what Webkin's are.
I know that they are, it's like, you know, beanie babies from, from the time of when that was the
thing, it feels a little bit similar to that where they're like collectible animals of some
brand. Uh, okay. So it's, it's a specific, it's a specific like company. It's a specific line of
plushes. Yeah. Well, yeah. They have like different, different, I don't know, seasons of
plushes. Like not all the plushes look exactly the same style. The one I had was like sort of
anatomically correct hippo as opposed to a cartoon hippo, which is the other things that
Yeah, hippo does not look like he's part of like a, a line. He just looks like a hippo.
Yeah. He, he look, he's like a National Geographic Webkin's crossover. I guess, I don't know.
Um, but Webkin's is a digital video game sort of like Club Penguin, MMO, uh,
early internet stuff where you get your pet and you, you have them, you have them digitally and you
can have, they have a room, they have a house they had, they can play mini-game, you play mini-games
to get coins that you can spend on furniture and outfits. And it's, it's Club Penguin, but with
plushes that you buy. So is it like Club Penguin, but with like a Skylanders sort of element wherein
you buy like a physical toy and then you scan it into the game?
Um, I suppose, I think you can get like, like pets in the, the, the, the website Webkin's.
I only played it for a long time. I thought, I thought that's what you did. I, I thought you
like scanned hippo in and yeah, yeah, I scanned, I scanned hippo in and I scanned hippo in and hippo
now exists digitally on my account. Um, I never played this when I was young. So I, I had like
Kazi tell me all about it and, and I played like a bunch of their funny flash game things they have.
Uh, Rest in Peace flash, by the way, that's gone. It's all dead.
Oh yeah, that just died. I haven't checked, I, I haven't felt the need to check to see if things
are dead, but I had to check because in, in, in the, the patron Q&A for, uh, I, I brought up, um,
CCC city, you know what that is. I've, I've talked about that, right? Uh, is that Sonichu?
No, what is that? No, it's not quick bill. Oh, no, it's the opposite of quick bill. No, CCC city,
CCC city is a bit like a, like a, a flash. I think they were originally in flash video
animation series by this guy called Vinnie Veritas on Newgrounds and I used to really like them.
I remember you saying those names. I, I forget what it's about.
It's not really about anything. It's just like animations that take place in this
like sort of fantasy urban location called CCC city. Um, and, uh, uh, anyway, I went to Newgrounds
to see if they had survived the death of flash and yes, they did. Um, they're just, they're just
uploaded as videos now. I guess they've been converted somehow, which is nice. Uh, I, I wonder if
everything is, I wonder if like, I mean videos are just worse than the way because they weren't
designed like on all the flash games, of course, I don't know what they're going to do. Maybe there's,
I've, I've seen HTML games. Maybe they've been transformed into that some people, but they would
have been, they would have had to like actively like the owners of those games would have had to
actively preserve them. Anything that was just left on, I think doesn't work anymore.
And that sucks. But I'm on, I guess that, I guess that might be like, this must, this must not have been,
huh? This must not have been flash. I'm on the Newgrounds page for triacnid and it still works. So
that must not have been flash, I guess. Wow. I mean, I know nothing really about it. I just
have heard that flash is dying and everything will be gone. I'm like, Oh, that's sad.
Wow, that's sad. Yeesh. I didn't really do anything about it.
I know that there were, I mean, I know there were efforts to preserve stuff. And I,
I don't know, I, it'll be, it'll be sad. It'll be sad when I start hearing about specific things
that were lost. It's like, Oh, this doesn't exist anymore because flash is dead. I mean,
even if flash is dead, one could hypothetically still like get, download something and then like
run flash locally on their computer and like convert it like that. Like, like just because
flash is dead doesn't mean that things that were in flash can no longer be converted to.
Yeah, I feel like it's possible to, to, it's just all of the things that are not easy to get a hold
of or are like abandoned. They will, you can't just, I don't know, you'd have to put in the effort
to make it work again. And if it was, I mean, I don't know what Club Penguin rewritten was like
when Disney destroyed Club Penguin because they're evil bastards and I can't ever forgive them.
Wait, who did? Who killed it? Disney. They bought Club Penguin quite early on,
I think. And, and it was a Disney property for a while, but then they deleted it. They got rid of
it so that they could push their new Club Penguin mobile app game, which was a 3D version of Club
Penguin on mobile. And it was fucking terrible. It was filled with micro transactions and bullshit.
Nobody played it. So they realized there was a failed investment and they canceled the new thing.
So now Club Penguin doesn't exist, except in this illegal version of Club Penguin that fans
recreated. And I assume that still uses Flash, so maybe that is in trouble. They probably figured
it out there. That's just like, that's just like when Cuomo said that you'll get a million dollar
fine if you vaccinate anyone who's not, who's not supposed to get vaccinated. It's the same.
Capitalism. What? Capitalism ruins everything. Vaccinations, Club Penguin, it's all part of the
system. That was the thing, I guess. I don't follow. Quick. You know, you know, because, because,
I don't know, the Disney bought it and they had it and they were like, oh, we can't make money off
it. So we'll throw it in the trash. Nobody gets it. And Cuomo, Cuomo is like, nah, nah, only the
fucking, only the fucking, the essential people get the, get the, get the vaccine.
Get the Club Penguin. Anyone that doesn't get, anyone that doesn't get vaccinated,
no, you can't use it on someone else. Throw it in the trash. If it doesn't, you can't,
you can't, you can't find the priority guidelines. Oh, I didn't know about that. That's stupid.
That's what I'm hearing. That's what I'm hearing is that these, it's like, you're not allowed to use
it except on people who are, who are set for it. And like, apparently this is going to cause some
sort of, some sort of supply glut, which might lead to doses of the vaccine just getting discarded
in trash because they expire after a while. That is the stupidest thing I've ever heard in my life.
This is what seems, this is what seems to be what is potentially the result of this new order
of Cuomos to not vaccinate. They'll be, they'll get fucking, you'll get fucking murdered. You need
to lose all your fucking practicing licenses if you do, if you fuck around, if you fuck around
with this and vaccinate anyone who's not supposed to get it. Capitalism. Stupid. The primary goal
should be very clear. Vaccinate as many people as possible. Prioritize the people who need it most.
If you have it lying around, give it to people. That's so simple. Fuck, like, yeah, like literally,
like, if you, if you've got them, literally just give them to fucking anyone. And it's, it's, yeah.
I mean, for sure, I agree. I mean, I'm sure. Did they do it? So, so that the people who, like,
I don't know, they don't trust the doctors to not use it on themselves and to their families first,
they, like, you have to do it on these specific people, otherwise we'll kill you. Yeah. Because
we don't trust you to use it responsibly otherwise. I think that's the idea, yeah.
But, you know, if, if, if doses get, get discarded because of that, like, fuck that.
Yeah. Fuck that. It's much worse. Yeah. Pretty cringe, pretty cringe. But anyway,
I don't want to talk about that. I want to talk about Club Penguin. I want to hear more about
that and Webkin. Dude, Club Penguin's so fucking good. You get your penguin and you club them
over the head. I always wanted, I always wanted to play Ragnarok online. Do you ever,
you ever play that? You ever see that? I feel like I saw a review of Ragnarok online.
Ragnarok online looked like, I don't even, I never even saw anyone play it. I
literally just saw, like, the sprites from it and I saw some screenshots from it and I just
really, really wanted to play it. But, like, I couldn't and I, I don't know why. Like, I tried
to sign up online and they couldn't, maybe my internet wasn't good enough or I didn't have this,
the specs for it or something. And I don't even know what it was. I just remember a burning desire
in my young child heart to play Ragnarok online because it had cool looking anime,
it had, like, Gaia online sprites but, like, less stupid looking and I think you could, like,
fight monsters. It's on Steam. I guess you can play it. Is it? Wait, wait. I just googled it and
it looks like it's on Steam. Oh, wait. Oh. No. At the request of the publisher, Ragnarok online
is no longer available for sale on Steam. What? Did they turn off the servers or something?
I see an article that says Ragnarok online goes free to play. Okay, well, there's a Ragnarok
online mobile that I think is a remake or something. It might be a new thing. I don't
know when this is from. This could be years old for all I know. This is from October 17th, 2019.
Okay, a new Android version of the well-known MMORPG for PC is coming West this year after
experiencing enormous success in Asian countries. Okay, so they're remaking it basically and that's
probably why they took it off Steam, the old version. I mean, I'm sure it was crap. I'm sure
it was dog shit fucking grindfest Korean bullshit. Just like, uh, just like, uh, what's the other one?
Everything. MapleStory. You ever play MapleStory? Is that the side-scrolling one?
Yeah. Yeah, it reminds me of when I did the 24-hour stream and I played MapleStory for like half of it.
I remember a bit of it. That was so cool. This game sucks so fucking bad. MapleStory is like,
it's like, oh, what was that game we played for RFCK? Oh, uh, yeah, I know. It's, um,
and it's the one by the, by the, the, the Diary of a Wimpy Kid guy.
Oh, was it from that guy? PopTropica? Yeah, literally the guy who made Diary of a Wimpy Kid
also made PopTropica. That's really funny. It's so fucking weird. I love shitty games. They're so great.
I had never heard of PopTropica before Munchie told me about it, but when I played it,
I was just like, oh my God, this is literally just MapleStory, but without like cool anime combat.
It's the same fucking game. Or, or I guess a, a, a MapleStory is just PopTropica, but with anime.
But I'm pretty sure MapleStory came first. So I think it's really around. I mean, I was playing,
I played MapleStory in my freshman year of college, which was 2000 and wait, MapleStory is 2003?
Yeah. Well, I'm just looking at Google that says that.
Uh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Wow. How old was I in 2003? Like 15?
Like 58? Like, like, uh, like 80? Yeah. Oh, no, no, no, no. It's over. It's over for me.
Wait, um, PopTropica come out.
I don't know. It was, it was very surreal, very surreal experience. Uh, uh, I don't know.
Is initial release date September 2007. Oh yeah. Yeah. Developer, the Jeff Kinney group.
Jeff Kinney is the, um, that fucking guy. Wimpy Kid guy.
Meh. When you're, when you're a fucking rich, powerful dude, you literally just make everything.
Uh, you literally just, just, just bend culture to your will. Diary of a, of a, of a, of a oligarch.
More like diarrhea of a Wimpy Kid.
Is they made, they, anyone made that joke before? Diary, uh, of a Simpy Kid.
Diarrhea. Um, no, no. I'm sorry, but no. Uh, what were we, what were we fucking talking about?
I don't know. Old games. Club Penguin. Old, old games. Flash dead. Flash dead, gone.
Flash dead, uh, uh, Hippo, Webkinz.
I didn't really have anything else to say on the Webkinz front. It was just like,
I'd never played Webkinz before and now Hippo exists digitally. And if anyone likes Webkinz,
that's cool. I, I ran around for a bit and I, uh, I, I gave her like some funny shoes.
I, I went to the school and during recess, I dug in the sandpit and I found a full like
football outfit and I put that on. Can I visit Hippo online? Uh, can you give me a URL
to go to her house? I think it's possible. And vandalize it. We could do like a thing
where Ben St. comes to Hippo Critt's house. Agreed. Uh, I'm ready. I'm ready when you are.
Just give me a time. Just give me time and place. You can have a, we can have a socially
distanced date. Socially. Oh yeah, me and Kazi were on there, right? Kazi has like a
horse that looks just like a little bit and I- What on Webkinz? On Webkinz. She, she was a big-
Is little bit, is little bit a Webkinz? No, but she has something that looks just like him.
Just a generic horse thing. And it's not called little bit. So it's from before. She played Webkinz
a lot. And we were, we were going around trying to harass some of the weird, some of the kids,
some of the youngsters, would basically be- So the children. Basically-
Okay, so you and Kazi were going around harassing children. Okay, got it.
But nobody paid attention because I think they were just min-maxing playing the game.
They were going into this one room. Min-maxing. They were gooning out.
Yeah, literally gooning, like goon central over here. They, they just walked into this room
and they clicked on a thing and then they disappeared. And we clicked on it and it was like,
every day you can come back here and get a thing. So we figured that these players were like,
like non-socially playing Webkinz to maximize and get all of the stuff every day that they can.
Doing their daily quests. And it was really funny because these little funny animals,
they'd moving across the screen and me and Kazi, because you can't like type in Webkinz.
You can only say stock phrases. And we just, we just surrounded them when we could and we just
said, I feel bad. Wait, really? Oh god. You can say like, you can say I feel good and then people
can respond in kind by clicking on your like speech bubble. And so we were just being like,
I feel mad. I feel mad surrounding them. And it was very strange, but I don't think any of them
paid attention. It was just really funny for a while. So Webkin bandits. If you want to join
my gang, you should, you should have streamed that honestly. That sounds like some performance
art. Shit. I could stream it. It could happen again. Arrasing kids in Webkinz. Damn, we're just,
they're just trying to do their dailies, bro. It's so funny when we realize that. Like, why?
I mean, I guess any game can be min-max and gooned, but it's just funny. Because it's,
I mean, they're so, they're so cute. What do you do dailies for? Like,
to buy like clothes or something? Or like furniture for a house? You get money and you
can buy furniture and clothing and different houses and special, I don't know, access to mini
games or membership or whatever. Do you think, do you think it's actually kids? I would imagine
that it's people who play it as kids who just still play it. Because nostalgia. I don't know how
big Webkinz is though. It could still be like, there weren't that many people around. There's like
one or two. So I don't know. No idea. Something, I don't know, something about, something about
that makes me really sad. I don't know whether it's sadder in my mind to imagine a child doing that
or an adult doing it out of nostalgia. They both kind of bug me and get under my skin in different
ways. And I don't like thinking about either one. I think it- It- Perfectly honest. It makes me feel
a little sad, the idea that they're, they're playing it alone, presumably and min-maxing by
themselves. Because like the whole point of those things is like, you have your cute little animal,
you dress them up, and then you show off like, look what, look what I have. I got shiny shoes,
ha-ha. And it's like, if there's no one around, like that was what depressed me about playing
War the Warcraft back when I was doing that. I was like, man, I feel compelled to do all
these quests and get all these numbers go up. But at the end of the day, all these incredible
achievements I have and all this cool gear and mounts and titles, nobody is paying attention
to anyone. They're all just focused on themselves and the community's soul is completely gone.
Sucks. Yeah. Yeah.
Feels like living in the city where everyone's walking past each other. You can't even stop
and say, hello, how are you doing? You always got somewhere to be. You can.
You can. You can stop and say, hello, how are you doing? But then they say, get the fuck away
from me, freak. And then they throw you to the ground. They say, they say, they say, get on the
ground. Get on the ground so you're easier to hit. Yeah. Bummer. Sad but true.
I don't know. Video games, man. Video games. Yes, that is such a thing as that.
I got a really strange game this week. I just bought it on a whim because it looked interesting.
But let me tell you about it. It's called Neute, N-O-I-T-A. Oh, yeah. Do you know it?
I know it's based on a specific German 985 stream moment that is quite infamous, but yeah, keep going.
Oh, really? Okay. Because I've never heard of it. It's not related to the game that moment. It's just
a really funny German moment. Wait, what is it? I'm curious. Well, he was playing the game and he
started betting with his audience about community subs where you give subs to whoever's in chat and
it just randomly distributes them. So he gives subscriptions. He was betting with this chat
that he could do certain things in the game, hitting an enemy or not dying in this next room.
And if I do it or if I don't do it, I'll give 15 community subs. And then he did it and he was
like, haha. And then chat was like, double or nothing, double or nothing. And then the bets
kept getting higher until he was like, all right, if I don't want, if I don't, if I miss the next
shot out of this gun, then I have to give like 500,000 community subs. It was getting ridiculous.
And predictably, he was right next to the enemy. He shot right past it. He missed. It was the
funniest moment. And now, German 985 owes chat like two something 0.5 billion dollars in community
subs. And so much stuff about what is happening in his current streams is like, he'll do something
that chat wants him to do if they they shave off like a few million dollars from the debt.
And it's a running joke. It's really funny. So funny. That's really funny. Okay, wow. I'm surprised.
I'm surprised that the Noida was related to that because I've again, I've never heard anyone mention
this game. But I saw it and I was like, oh, wow, that looks really fucking neat. Is it like a well
known game? I'm not sure. I think it just played it because it was cool and Indian out recently.
Well, for the for the for the audience, I'll say that it's it's like, it's a rogue like sort of,
it's like, it's like, you know, randomly generated dungeons. But like the way the world is generated
is it's based on like, those like sand physics sort of games, you know what I'm talking about,
the ones where you put fucking sand in a in a on the screen, and then you like drop other
kinds of sand on top of it. And they like pile on each other and you can make like gas particles
and stuff and they float around. Like it's like physics based like that. And there's yeah. And
it's really fucking neat. But it's really fucking hard. And I have honestly not made very much
headway at all. I think I got to like the third stage like one time and I have no idea how many
stages there are. I found a I found like a couple of secrets in like, I found a secret boss in the
first stage, but it was like so far beyond my ability to deal with. I got obliterated. It's
hard. It's a hard game. But I really like that like, I really like playing with those like,
particle physics games. And I thought it's just really wild to me that they actually that they
would make a game that combines those two things. I just think that's neat as hell.
And I probably fuck around with that some more this week. Because, you know,
if I like I like video games, I'd like to play them for fun.
I like to play them for not fun. I like to play them for rage.
Play them for spite. I'll play them for for hate's sake. I spit at the.
I do it to spite my parents who said you'll never play video games. And I'll show them.
They said I couldn't do it. They said I couldn't do it, but I did it. They said,
they said you'll never beat Undertale. It's too hard. Well, you'll never be cloudy. Well,
guess, well guess what? I fucking did it. I fucking got the good ending to mom.
Um, fuck you.
Uh, you want to go to voicemails? Yeah.
Okay. Unless there's any unless there's any bullshit you want to bring up.
Uh, well, there was that one time that cow took a shit.
All right, you got them up. You ready?
Speak pipe.com slash the PCP voicemail. How do you do it?
Well, speak pipe.com slash PCP voicemail. That's how you send us a voicemail and we listen to it
on the show and we don't we don't have any any quality standards whatsoever.
Uh, except occasionally, but very rarely, almost any little play almost anything,
uh, Lamal. Uh, so send us your most racist shit. No. And we will seriously engage with it.
We will treat it as valid. I promise. Uh, or do I? Uh, are you ready?
Uh, the first one is called seven. Oh, so yeah. Yep.
Okay. Three, two, one, go.
Climate change. Am I right, fellas? You're right.
Fucking climate change. Nobody likes climate change.
Climate change is shit. It's fucking everything up.
Now I'm not claiming that I have the solution to climate change because I don't.
What I have is fucking information that might reveal the ultimate cause of it.
Right. So what we're told are the two leading causes of climate change.
It's the fucking coal mining industry and the fucking farming industry.
We have these heavy fucking machines, production, all this fucking shit that's going up into the
stratosphere. We all know how climate change works. I'm sure. Right. And it's causing fucking
climate change. This shit in fucking air caused by fucking. Is this is just like
in the fucking farming. Now before we had these heavy machines, you know what we had?
We had slaves. So ultimately climate change is the fault of two men.
Number one, Abraham Lincoln, number two, Martin Luther King Jr.
And if you disagree, you are also to blame for climate change. Okay. Discuss.
Well, I don't I don't see any fault in this logic.
The isn't like me saying a greenhouse gas.
Don't don't we don't fart that? Or is that just cows?
We probably do, but not as much. I mean,
I don't fucking know. I guess I guess he's right. You know what?
He's I guess he's right. I guess slavery was pretty based after all.
And you know what? I think it's time for us all to be slaves, every single one of us.
We get the get the fucking throw away the keys. It's jangles chains up. We don't need to be
chained because we're doing it voluntarily, but it's like for the aesthetic, I guess.
Let's get all those chains around our necks. Bring back slavery, but with a twist,
there were literally all of us become slaves. No masters, only slaves.
Yeah, people look up and it's like, who's whipping with me? There's no one.
There's no one there. It's like, shut up. Just keep you got to do it.
Digging. You're responsible for your whipping yourself.
Yeah, you got to pick yourself up. You got to pick yourself up by your whip straps.
If you really think about it, rule slaves to whatever we want to do.
We are slaves to our own free will. Yeah, right.
To our own free choice and association with our fellow man.
Damn. Got to say, I never never thought about it like that.
Next one. Oh my God, these are great. These are great so far. Next one is called
Why the ethno state is a good idea and you should support it. Damn, voicemails on point.
You know, last week we had shitty voicemails. This time they were like,
we got a fucking step of the quality and they did it. Three, two, one, go.
Konnichiwa. Oh, oh, okay, okay. Samurai-sama, see how it is. Here he comes.
Voicemail, fan favorite, brother character, Samurai-sama. He said,
Konnichiwa, you react like that. Well, Samurai-sama, come this week to finally accept
to apologize. Very happy, but you, after honoring here, Konnichiwa, react like that.
Well, fuck you. We didn't react enough. That's the problem.
Return no Samurai-sama. At this point, you honorly have yourself to blame.
This is abuse, honestly. See you next time. Sayonara.
This is the abuse tactic wherein you just, you abuse someone
and then they react negatively to the abuse and then you say,
see, it's because you act like that. It's because you act like that that I have to treat you this
way. This is what it is. This is an abusive relationship now. There's no way out.
It really was unfortunate that we'd said absolutely nothing and that the whole point
of the thing was that, oh, you react like that? I think it makes sense. I mean, it makes sense,
right? I would be offended if I introduced myself. And we didn't go, oh my god.
No reaction whatsoever. Next is an, oh lord, next one. Now here's a fan favorite,
a real fan favorite if ever there was one. And we should put these two in a,
in a, some sort of deathmatch against each other. Riddle my ass, Batman. Here we go. Three, two, one, go.
Hello. Riddle my ass, Batman here. Yes. Yes, I'm ready. The question for one thing
is still going on. It's going to be the second episode coming up right after this or possibly
two after this. And it's still going on, but I'm on a shittier mic now because my laptop broke.
I will tell you the story in a second. It involves... This is just a voicemail about why he couldn't make
the voice... ...mander and origins and masturbation. Well, look forward to that story in a minute.
I'm excited. Anyway, that's why I'm on my phone microphone right now. So just so you know,
it's kind of shit. Oh, and RiddleMyAssBatman.com, class Patreon, or whatever the fuck it's called,
you know how to find it. It does exist. You just have to look it up when it exists. I didn't take
it to account. The fact that you were in it a week early. I was in it. Sorry. Okay, on with the show.
Oh, it's just explaining the context for his next voicemail.
I'm going to die. Well, now we're fully rarity for the next one, a bird and origin masturbation.
Hold on. Hold on. It's in the next one. Okay, Patreon, Patreon.com slash RiddleMyAssBatman.
No, it's not... It doesn't exist. It's not there. Wait, what? Let me try RiddleMyAssBatman.com.
No. No.
Well, he reversed him, right? He said like RiddleMyAssBatman.patreon.com or slash...
It's not... It's not real. It's a fantasy. It's a mere... It's a rooster illusion.
Uh, RiddleMyAssBatman YouTube. Maybe there's a link from here.
What? Where? Where do you see it? Where?
I just googled RiddleMyAssBatman. I got to a YouTube channel.
There's no link. There's no link to it.
I mean, he had the... Was it Wattpad or what was like the...
There was the page where his stories, like the novel version was.
Okay. Okay. The trail's gone cold. The trail's gone cold. All right.
Let's hear what he's got to say about a bird, an orange, and masturbation. Shall we?
Yeah.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay, the bird, orange, and masturbation story.
Here we go.
I was masturbating while eating an orange.
Same.
Because I consider orange to be an erotic fruit, in my opinion, an aphrodisiac.
Turn me on. And I treat myself good. Anyway, my bird, she squawks like a bad hell.
And it scares the living Jesus out of me for just a moment.
And I squeezed the orange. And just because of the angle I happened to have it at,
I squeezed the orange right into a sensitive spot on my dick, right into the fucking hole.
Right in the...
It burned like nobody's business. And it caused me to drop my laptop and I broke it.
Now, of course, I'm, you know, I'm halfway through a fat.
I mean, what am I supposed to do? I'm supposed to stop there?
No. No, I can't stop just a minute away through a fat. You got to finish your fat.
So I grabbed the nearest erotic thing I can find.
The calendar from Ragscon.
Yes, the Ragscon swimsuit calendar.
The calendar knows which picture I used.
And there's so many good ones.
There's so many to choose from.
That's what I did, yeah.
And that's why I don't have a laptop anymore.
Was it worth it?
Yes. Okay.
That's the explanation. Same PCB time, same PCB channel.
On with the show, Quest for Corona episode 2. Bye.
Sound off in the comments.
Okay, commenters, if you backed Ragscon 4 and you have the calendar,
let us know in the comments which month you think Riddle My Ass Batman finished his fat too.
Because there's no wrong answers, really.
They're all good choices, in my opinion.
I think, I'm going to guess it might be the solo munchy one, if you remember what that looks like.
Yeah, I think I strongly objected to that one.
On the grounds of it, crossing the line from Etchy to Full-on Hentai.
I found it, it was no, yeah, lascivious, lascivious.
But they wouldn't have it.
There's a fucking story about bird orange and masturbation.
The bird had almost nothing to do with it.
It squawked.
Yeah.
Like, so much of it seems silly and like, why, how, what orange, why would you have an orange?
Well, he explained in the text, he considers it an erotic fruit and he treats himself good.
I know, it's just, it seems like it's a bit, but it could actually,
like, feel like it could actually have happened, which is the funny part.
I don't, I don't, I don't, in one hand, wait, in one hand you have an orange.
I don't know what about it makes you think it's a bit.
Because it's so fucking silly, Ben, who eats an orange while holding their laptop and
masturbating.
That's just life.
You know, life's truth is stranger than fiction sometimes.
Go straight into the pee hole.
I know, I know, I know you're uncomfortable.
I know you can't stare unblinkingly into the void of meaning that is reality.
But I can, and that's what, and that's what I do.
Whenever, when Riddle My Ass Batman leaves as a voicemail.
This is, this is, this, accept it.
The sooner you accept that this is what life is, the sooner you can just get on with it,
you know?
I don't know what's real anymore.
I see things on the internet and I'm like, that's not true.
And then it is.
It's always true.
Next one?
Yep.
Next one is called Thoughts.
Three, that's with a G-H, like in your brain.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, what are your thoughts on Donkey Kong?
I like him.
Gib, thoughts on Donkey Kong?
Donkey Kong is a pretty funny guy.
He's big and he has a fun game called Donkey Kong Country.
One and two, maybe, he's not in three.
And then he's in Smash.
He's not in two either.
He's not in two either, you fucking nerd.
He's, he's in trouble.
In the third one, I feel like he's just gone.
He's just gone.
He's gotta be somewhere in three.
I never played three, let me be clear.
I played three.
You know, I didn't, as a kid, it seems like public opinion now
is that three was not as good as two.
I never noticed much of a difference.
I thought they were both just fucking great.
And I never beat either of them
because they were both way too hard for me as a kid.
I think it's really just a surface level detail.
Kitty Kong is a fucking freak and he's not as epic and swag as Diddy Kong.
With his beatbox.
I've heard people say that three is like more gimmicky
or like has more like like bullshit in it.
And I've heard critiques of it that I forget what it is.
People have like reasons.
But as a kid, I just thought they,
I just thought three looked really nice.
And I like collecting silver coins.
And I thought the silver coins looked nicer than the gold ones.
And I probably just liked it on that basis.
I mean, I didn't play too much of three,
but I did like the beginning few levels
where it's just sort of nice, sort of, I don't know,
almost like American red pine forestry like pine wood.
Nice, like unusual for monkeys to be there.
Like unusual for like the Kong people.
Oh yeah, snow levels.
I think I like that about it too, that it just had snow levels.
And you had a hovercraft.
And you could drive a little hovercraft around the world map.
The fact that you could, that was so cool, right?
Like you're not constrained to a linear path.
Yeah.
You're not just doing, you're not just doing like a Mario three,
like world to world on the line thing.
You hop in your, I mean, on the, on the land you are,
but like you hop in your fucking little hovercraft
and get on the ocean and you go, and there's little secrets.
Like there's secrets in the ocean, right?
Like you circle around like a rock
and it turns into a hidden level.
Oh my God, what a fucking video game.
I should replay them.
They were, they were very difficult for me.
Answer your question, Mr. voicemail man, Donkey Kong, whatever.
But the, I like the games, the guy, the monkey himself.
Eh, it's fine.
He's finally here, the leader of the bunch,
coconut gong, Kong, Donkey Kong.
Donkey Kong.
One hell of a guy.
Okay.
Next one is called a bright outlook.
Three, two, one, go.
Just wanted to say some words of encouragement.
Thanks man.
You guys are chads, you know, you guys are troopers.
That's true.
Sticking around, still being here.
Agreed.
Doing your own things, doing your own art, doing good.
Doing your own podcasts, some Patreon stuff.
Good stuff, you know.
Keep it up.
Here's to a good year.
And I hope that maybe all the Radcon stuff could come out.
That'd be pretty sick.
What are you guys saying?
I think that's a good goal for 2021, right?
I think all the Radcon stuff will be out this year.
Sorry, lads.
Have a good one.
Don't be sorry, we have to do that.
Yeah, I think the stuff that is getting done is definitely on track to be done, you know.
Before the year gets too far in, everything else we will figure out.
We can definitely have it all out this year.
For some specific people, for some specific bits of it, you know.
Yeah, we gotta kick some asses.
Thank you for the encouragement.
We'll do that with pleasure.
Yes, all the Radcon stuff will come out this year.
And because of that, it will not be a good year.
It will be a bad year, because the content will be bad and you will hate it.
Yes, you will say we waited all year for this.
You'll say I waited my whole life.
If you said I ever since I pledged to Radcon and then I literally didn't leave my house
for a fucking year and change because all I wanted was this content and then you'll get it.
And it won't fill the hole inside you and you'll say what was it all for?
And the answer will be nothing.
Damn, bleak.
Next voicemail.
Wait a second, did I get that one?
Yeah, I did.
Next voicemail is called Let's Kill Fat Ben.
Three, two, one, go.
All right, Ben.
Last week you said it would take until about April to get rid of Fat Ben.
Maybe.
And as a fellow disgraced keto boy myself, I kind of wanted on this.
So I'm going to use the tool of public internet shaming to keep both you and me on track.
So I'm going to start today.
What about you?
How's the past week been?
And isn't it about time we started lifting again?
See you next time.
Yeah, I was lifting for a little bit there for a couple weeks.
I fell off it again and I haven't in a few weeks now, which is shit.
I already said that I'm back on keto, which has not, I have not lost any weight,
which is very frustrating.
But what I do need to actually start doing in addition to just being keto is calorie counting.
I need to start like cooking very specific things and knowing the calorie counts and like
logging them and like actually keeping myself to like a numerical limit.
That's, that's the thing that I have not, that's, that's what I need.
This, this is secret sauce.
I got to add into it.
If I do that, then I'm guaranteed to kill Fat Ben in a reasonable timeframe.
And lifting again would be good too.
I should definitely do that also.
Why, why would you lift away from the earth when you could push the earth instead?
I'm sorry?
Instead of lifting, you push downwards.
It's easier.
What?
Much easier.
That's a body weight exercise.
You just push the earth.
That's what, that's what a pushup is.
You're moving the entire earth when you push.
You are.
But, you know, in a minute, in an infinitesimal way, because it's like, you know, between you
and the earth, you each, it's between your center of gravity and like the difference in
mass is so vast that the equal and opposite reaction, just keep pushing, just push the
earth, just keep pushing everything.
Just you get down, you get down on the ground.
Stop lifting, stop dropping, stop dropping things.
Stop walking things.
Put your hands on the ground, jump, jump, jump, jump, moving all around.
You know that, that first song?
What is that called?
I know the second one was Caramel Dancin'.
Do you know that song that I was just humming there?
No, I've never heard it.
It's, there was a, there was a, there was a New Ground song,
animation of a bunch of like video game characters.
It was like really crappy, like old like New Ground's flash style animation in the sort of
pseudo anime style that was popular at the time.
And it's that song is playing, and they're all playing DDR.
Jump on the ground, jump, jump, jump, jump, moving all around.
Maybe it's called Jump on the Ground.
It was probably called Jump on the Ground.
Anyway, that was Caramel Dancin' before Caramel Dancin' was Caramel Dancin'.
Ted Dancin'.
Okay.
Anyway, next one is called Die.
Three, two, one, go.
To all of you guys asking them to stop the podcast or kill the podcast.
How does that benefit you?
Oh yeah.
You can just leave, stop watching, unsubscribe, go away, die.
Like if they kill the podcast, what does that help you?
Yeah, there was one or two commenters.
That's stupid.
There's one or two comments on the last one.
Every now and then we get one.
That's just like, just kill the podcast already.
And like, yeah, and actually yesterday I responded to someone saying like,
but you're literally here watching, listening to it.
You're literally here on the giving us the view.
So like, why?
It's, I mean, I know why, but it's just a really petty like stupid reason.
It's because from their point of view,
like the show that they once loved is now ruined.
And every time they see it, they're reminded of better times.
And they sort of tears form in their eyes when they realize that it's just not the same.
And it's like, that is not a good enough reason for us to do anything.
Yeah, sure.
Just get some blinders, get some horse blinders on.
They probably know.
I mean, they probably know that we won't do it.
But I guess they just want to let us know that in their opinion, it's what we should do.
And okay.
Yeah, whatever.
Yeah, we're just, we're just, we're just never going to agree on this, I guess.
You think we should die and we think we shouldn't.
And there's just, there's really no middle ground there.
Yeah, or you should, you should be active about it.
You know, try to destroy us, cancel us, create your own podcast and make fun of us.
What did, what did I see?
Oh God, I saw an image.
I think it was on Twitter like yesterday.
Well, what the fuck was it?
It was, it was something and it was captioned like,
if it was like, if you hate me, either kill me or shut the fuck up.
It was funny in context, but I don't remember what the context was.
But anyway, yeah, if you, if you hate us so much, we're not, we're not going to kill,
we're not going to end the show.
You're literally going to have to come and kill us yourself.
God, I shouldn't say that.
They'll fucking do it.
They'll fucking do it soon.
If I'm, if I'm not on the next episode,
know that it's because someone took me up on that offer.
Uh-oh.
Gulp.
Uh, next one.
Oh my God, we're almost done.
We're almost done.
And, you know, honestly, these voicemails have been pretty decent this week.
These are, these are, these are all right.
These haven't been too annoying.
So pretty cool.
Uh, last voicemail is called an actually somewhat obscure Pokemon game.
Three, two, one, go.
Heart gold, soul silver, not obscure, their main series games.
Most Pokemon games are not obscure.
Pokemon's huge.
It's hard to have an obscure game in a franchise so big,
especially if it was released in English.
Conquest.
Probably the most obscure English game that is actually great.
And obscure might even be putting it too hard is a Pokemon conquest.
Really straight as the DS was dying and the 3DS was already out.
In the dip between, uh, there was sort of a popularity dip of Pokemon at that point
of time before completely surging in the 3DS games.
It was also targeted towards older teens and adult, which again was kind of a dip and would be,
it would do so much better if it was released today is basically.
He has not said what it is.
It's crossover in Nobu Naga's ambition.
Yes, historical Nobu Naga, the samurai.
He has a Zekrom and he's a pretty big deal in that game
as he was an actual Japanese history.
It plays like Fire Emblem or Final Fantasy Tactics
because nobody knows what Nobu Naga's ambition is in America.
Has a pretty interesting story.
Total on Fire Emblem is the best thing I've ever heard.
If you like Texas gameplay, Pokemon Samurai's
and, uh, late DS aesthetics would recommend Pokemon Conquest
because it's certainly more obscure than HeartGold and SoulSilver.
People love those games.
People constantly talk about them.
They're not obscure.
I, I, actually.
If you're going to talk about obscure Pokemon stuff,
know something at least mildly obscure that isn't a main series game.
I might actually go and play that because, um,
I love the gameplay of Fire Emblem and I dislike the gameplay of Pokemon so much
that might, that might be cool.
Well, have you played, um, have you played the, the Mystery Dungeon?
I have.
I like those.
Okay.
Um, I mean, this looks similar to that, but
I mean, I, I wonder how, like,
Mystery Dungeon is not like Fire Emblem in the same way.
Yeah, okay.
Because it's like you just move one thing at a time.
It's honestly, this is like Turn Lua.
I assume if it's Fire Emblem Life then it's Turn Lua.
What actually turns me off from this is that it's like,
has humans, uh, wait a minute, wait a minute.
No, I don't see any human, I don't see any human in characters.
It would be like humans who have Pokemon, right?
And they fight using those.
No, this, this is a man.
This is a man right here, right?
Like, between that Arceus and that Darumaka.
Darumaka, Darumaka.
If you get to kill people, that would be great.
Yeah.
Look at the little black person in the corner.
Honestly, yeah, like, I don't, I don't really love the actual,
like, gameplay part of, um, the, the Mystery Dungeon.
Like, it was fine.
I used to really like, like tactics, uh, you know, um,
grid based, like a tactical RPGs like this.
If this were just that with Pokemon, I might think that was pretty cool.
The fact that it's tacked on to the fucking Nobunaga's ambition, which like,
what the fuck, uh, is, is kind of a big turn off.
Like, I don't want to fucking deal with like,
wall.
Look at that.
That's cool.
I like that.
I don't, I don't, I don't want to fucking know.
I don't want to deal with these fucking, these humans.
You just don't want it.
You just don't want them to say directly into the camera.
Konnichiwa.
You don't want them to do that.
I mean, they'll do it.
If the, if the, if the premise of the game is that like, you are a fucking,
I don't know, like a foolish samurai warrior and you've got your fucking six Pokemon team.
And you got to, you got to catch Pokemon and you get to fight your way.
If this is like, if it's like, it's like Pokemon, it's the premise of a Pokemon game,
but it's set in like feudal Japan and it like plays out that way.
That would be awesome.
But I feel like it's definitely not that it's probably some bullshit.
It's probably actually just like this other game, but like some of the characters have
been reskinned to be Pokemon.
All right.
I, I'll, I'll download it illegally and play it and then I'll get back to you.
Okay.
Yeah.
Let's be like a thing to keep track of.
You should, you should do a podcast.
You should do a fucking GRPJ about Pokemon conquests.
Bring that back.
Dude, little Curlia.
Show me.
Show me fucking Curlia.
She's like doing a magic right now.
Ooh.
Wow.
Um, they're like fighting beach balls or something.
Pokemon.
I mean, hmm, Pokemon in other formats is a cool idea.
I just, I feel like if this were good, more people would talk about it because it is so obscure.
You, you'd, you'd literally never heard about it.
I had heard about it because I do feel like
if it were, because I was literally googling myself.
I was googling a Pokemon conquest because I made that fucking Nuzlocke about it.
And then I was like, I found this and it was like, wait a minute,
there's a game called that and it was this and I was like shocked and horrified.
I think that the reason nobody knows about this would be,
like the guy said, in between DS and 3DS.
And also it's not a traditional Pokemon game.
So people are like, oh, it's not the game I know.
I don't care.
And then nobody cared.
But it could be a secret hidden gem.
I mean, I, well, I think it's probably that because of it's weird,
the weird time it was released.
I mean, it's a crossover series with something that nobody in the West has ever fucking heard of.
Nobody, wait a minute.
Are the Nobunaga's ambitions games, like are they called something else in America?
They're called Japan Fight.
Amazing.
Okay.
I was thinking they might be called something else in America,
but no, I don't think they are.
Yeah.
So it's a crossover with something.
Maybe it's popular in Japan and maybe more people know about it over there.
But in America, it's like, why, like, how would you even explain what this is to a Western child?
Like, well, it's like a, it's like a historical, like, period piece, but we put Pokemon in it.
Like, if I were Nintendo, I also probably just wouldn't even bother advertising it in the West.
So I think they made the right call.
Honestly, honestly, it sort of seems like a bit of a, I feel like it's a little bit of a brand
mismatch.
And probably, if they were asking me, should we make,
making me like it more?
I like that no, no Pokemon fan would enjoy this.
If they were, if they were, if I was, if I was a big wig at Nintendo and some fucking
interns, some intern was like, I have a passion project I've always wanted to make.
What if, what if we combine Nobunaga's ambition with Pokemon?
Look, I mean, I spent my sleepless nights.
I spent my weekends at the office making this prototype.
What do you think, boss?
I would say no, absolutely not.
This is brand mismanagement.
This will damage our fucking family friendly image.
This is like, this is fucked up and you're a piece of shit and you're going to jail.
And I would end that interns life right there.
I would say put your hat on my fucking desk and I would take out my katana and behead him
right there and make an example of him.
Like this is what you do and you fuck with the Pokemon company.
When you fuck with our brand, you die.
And that would, and that would be, that would be it.
And then, and then we lesson learned.
And hopefully it would only have to be the one and no one would ever do.
Maybe that's what happened.
Maybe that's why this never happened again.
Because they put this game existed and someone got executed.
And they were like, well, we know not to fuck around.
The guy, this guy fucked around and found out.
Is what I'm saying.
Anyway, yeah, looks, let me know, let me know if it's fun.
Yep.
Okay.
Uh, well, shit, that's the last voicemail.
We're free.
Oh, no.
Wait, wait.
It's time for a Bitcoin update.
Zero.
Oh, there's no more Bitcoin.
Bitcoin's canceled.
It's actually costs money to have Bitcoin now.
No, as you, as you see.
It's minus 10.
Okay.
It dipped a bit, but it kind of bounced back and it's a little lower than it was before.
We're at 33, we're at 33, 550.
So there you go.
Uh, uh, all my money is gone.
But next week I'll be rich.
It's going to the moon.
Give Bitcoin, it's, it's, people think it can't rise any higher.
They're wrong.
Ye a little faith.
It's going to the moon.
They haven't seen nothing yet.
It's going to be, it's going to, it's going to triple again.
It's going to triple again.
It's going to hit 50K.
It's going to hit 50K this year.
It's only a matter of time.
Just got to hold it.
Just got to hold it for long enough.
Okay.
Sorry, I'm just googling Pokemon conquest ROM and maybe it's like so nobody cares about it.
It's hard to find.
Oh wait, no, I may have found it.
Was it on the DS?
DS, yeah.
God, I love still having my, my R4, my DS, uh, pirate thingy.
I'm going to play all of classics.
Is that the thing that you can like the cartridge you put games on?
Yeah, you can put games on it using a USB to SD card thingy and then you just play them
and they fucking work.
I think I had one of those.
I think Nate got me one at one point.
I think that was what I played heart gold on in the run that Brunswick came from all those years ago.
I wonder where, I wonder where that is.
I feel like that cartridge that had that copy of heart gold on it is like in a box in my parents house
somewhere or, or some, it's got to be somewhere.
It wouldn't have been thrown out.
It's really under a fucking shelf somewhere that no human will ever lay eyes on again.
Hidden treasure.
One piece.
Are we done?
Are we, are we,
can't-
Yeah.
What happened?
Patreon, patreon.com slash the procrastinators, right?
Yeah, what, why'd you keep asking me?
Yes.
Because I never, okay, okay, give a bonus episode.
Uh, we did a bonus episode.
I think it should be coming out soon, right?
We did one last month that should be releasing soon.
Yeah, what was it?
Is that the one where I get really salty?
Is that the one with Gamers Tavern?
The one with Gamers, yes, I'm really salty.
I complain about everyone and Gamers Tavern's there and we do the fucking thing again where we,
where we do the retrospective on the other time Gamers Tavern was on the show and it's fucking,
it gets, it gets hot, one might say.
Okay, the end.
Goodbye, see you next week.
Happy New Year, America 2020.
Uh, uh, what?
I don't even know what that means.
Okay, good night.
Yeah, good night.
Bye-bye.