Hey, Big Booty Bitches, it's Best Guy Ever here with a special announcement from The Pro Crastinators.
RADCON 3!
That's right, the PCB has officially launched our Kickstarter to fund RADCON 3 Arena.
Since our previous venue is no longer available to us, we had no choice but to enter the arena!
And by that I mean rent a house.
Six of the Pro Crastinators will be there to make content just like you saw at RADCON 1 and RADCON 2.
The only difference is this time we're doing a Kickstarter specifically to fund that RADCON 10 you love.
The PCP Royal Rumble, the PCP U Lectures, and the live hundredth episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
All this and so much more content will be created if we can make this Kickstarter happen.
By the time you're hearing this, the Kickstarter will have been running for about a week already,
but go ahead and click on the link in the description to check it out.
We've got a bunch of great perks, pledge $10 and get behind the scenes footage of RADCON 3.
$20 get a pin, $50 get a t-shirt, $100 get a special shout out during RADCON.
And if you're an absolute mad lad who wants to pledge $1,000, you will be entered into the PCP Royal Rumble.
Becoming a meme god.
Six of the members of the Pro Crastinators are signed up to be there.
Best guy ever, Ben St, Digi Bro, Hippo Crit, Tom Oliver, and Munchy.
We are asking for $5,800 to make it happen and with your support, we know we can.
We just want to be able to get together again and make the content that we enjoy making and you love watching.
And this is how we get it done.
So for the full details and if you have any questions, head on over to the Kickstarter link in the description.
There's a full breakdown of everything that I just discussed and so much more.
Check it out and please consider donating.
God damn it, do we want RADCON 3 Arena to be real?
And check out our stretch goals.
For $6,300, we'll be able to afford GoPros and Nerf guns to make RADCON 3 Arena IRL.
Meaning, fucking shooting each other in shed.
It's gonna be sick.
And if we make $9,001, we will literally max revive T-Back.
That's a mean tier, but yes, we will actually do that if we reach that goal.
That's our pitch.
Thanks for listening and please click the link in the description and go check out our Kickstarter page.
You know how much we can deliver if we can make this RADCON happen.
Thank you and enjoy the show.
I'm not positive that Jesus is God, but I'm throwing in with Jesus rather than throwing in with you guys,
because you guys can't tell me how it all got here.
You guys don't know.
We're working on it.
Physicists are working.
When you get it, then maybe I'll listen.
You disgust me.
Okay, here we go.
Hello, everyone, and welcome to another episode of the Procrastinator's Podcast.
That's the PCP.
Filling your brain with higher dimensional thoughts that you've never been.
I am the best guy ever, and we're joined today by Hippocrates.
Admiralakba.
It's high energy PCP today.
Ben St.
I'm Wiccanow.
Yes, Tom Oliver.
Jesus is the best guy ever.
Oh, fuck.
Munchy.
Where's TinyHat?
All right, guys, my strategy for this game is to rush calendars so I can pick up an early pantheon
and then spam some caravans for my UA.
And I didn't miss anyone, right?
That's everyone.
Yeah, that's everyone here.
All the five boys are here.
And we did it, guys.
We cracked the life code, because today we're talking about the only question that matters.
Which video game is best video game?
It's Undertale.
Just throwing that out there.
I got a strong contestant here.
Here.
I have a strong connection here.
You guys say your favorite, so I'll get mine.
I like Undertale.
I'm a big fan.
I like Undertale, personally.
I need to bait that it's Undertale, like the way the truth of the life.
No, but let's just keep going through the motions.
The real question is who likes Undertale the most?
That's really true.
The best video game ever made is Active Life Magic Carnival for Wii.
Sponsored by Active Life Magic Carnival.
Four video games that are inferior to Undertale.
The Active Life Mac controller not included.
Cannot find this anywhere.
I looked on eBay.
It's not there.
Oh, okay.
That's a good contender.
But I consider that sort of a subset of the greater Undertale worship community.
And really, what I think we need to do is start dividing ourselves into subdivisions of Undertale worship.
You know, like there's the lowly papyrus clan.
There's the sans, you know, devouts.
The sans devouts.
The sans orthodox.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Indeed, indeed.
We need to form these factions and begin warring intensely with each other.
I think that's the best way to kind of burn out the undesirable elements of our community here.
Yeah.
And just spiral into perfection.
Have to prove themselves in a trial by fire.
Otherwise, how do we know?
I consider myself a hardcore Toriothian.
I live and breathe by the 95 hentais of Toriel.
My favorite ones.
Yes.
She is a thick boy, without a doubt.
Enough of this.
Yes, it's religion.
It's religion, guys.
We're talking about religion, such as Undertale worship.
And the other ones that are out there.
Most notably.
Yes.
But Nate, what is religion?
Oh, excellent question.
Let's consult the sacred text over on UrbanDictionary.com.
Okay, a religion.
An organized group of people with a common belief.
Most religions strongly stress ethics and morals,
along with setting guidelines for people to follow in their day-to-day life.
Wait, wait a minute.
So you're saying that a religion is...
I'm disappointed.
Wait, wait, wait.
I need to just pause for a second.
This is something really important.
Is that a religion is an organized group of people with a common set of beliefs
with a high emphasis on ethics.
So Gamergate is a religion.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no!
You know what's interesting about this?
I've read every single definition of religion on UrbanDictionary.
Not a single one of them is like a meme or a joke.
God.
And this begins when I think it's an important element.
This is good.
Because I think this is indicative of how seriously people take religion,
that there isn't enough of like even here on UrbanDictionary,
everybody's taken this way too fucking seriously.
Jesus Christ.
And it needs to be ridiculed roundly.
At UrbanDictionary, I'm very disappointed.
You know what?
Let's go to knowyourmeme.com.
Let's go to knowyourmeme.
Yes!
Oh my, these cats are fucking on!
Knowyourmeme.com, baby!
Let's see what we've got for religion on...
Oh, there we go.
Yes, you know your meme!
These guys...
Okay, they'll hook us up.
Wait, sorry.
It's not...
You're fucking this up for me, Nate!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
He doesn't know how to maneuver this new fang of kids.
I think Christian memes would actually have a knowyourmeme page.
God, God, God.
Okay, what do you got?
What do you got?
About God as a religious concept typically described as a superhuman spirit.
This is a core and often controversial topic of religious, philosophical, and political discussion.
Incredible.
Here's include advice, God.
I gave you free will, bottom text, so use it exactly as I command you to.
Real nice meme there!
Knowyourmeme!
I'm reading the knowyourmeme entry for a religion is also weirdly non-jokey.
Okay, listen to this about religion.
Religion is a spiritual and cultural system of ideas, beliefs, behaviors, blah, blah, blah, built out of holy traditions.
Adherence of religion, blah, blah, blah, they worship.
This is not...
Where's the meme?
Nate, Nate, Nate, Nate, Nate!
I come to this meme for one thing and one thing only.
The reason that there's no jokes is because religion in itself is a joke.
Let's be honest.
There you go.
Let me just tip my foot over.
The comedy was here all along.
Exactly.
I'd like to say that this, dear viewers, will be probably the most circle jerky, circular, secular, like non...
This will just be all of us have the exact same opinion.
All of us have the exact same opinion because there's only one opinion to derive from this entire topic.
There is no discussion that can even take place at this point.
It's all been discussed already.
There is only one position.
I'm interested in defending religion on this, just to be contrary to my own point of view.
What a shucks.
Nate playing devil's advocate on the religion episode.
Oh, because I am the devil.
The thing that I was planning on talking about just a little bit is the thing I like about religions is the sick architecture.
And the reason religion is bad in my mind is because they don't build any new really cool mosques and churches and stuff.
They just use the old ones.
And they don't have any cool new stuff.
It's because they invented the internet and now they don't have the free time anymore.
They've got better things to do.
The Muslims have it figured out.
Look at this sick-ass cube that all the Muslims in perfect circles all gather around and bow to.
They worship the obsidian!
Oh my God!
Okay, but seriously, this is like the most aesthetic thing.
This is so sick.
They've got it figured out.
I mean, if I was going to make a religion, I'd probably want it to center around a cube.
It's not the whole point of this episode. We're going to make a religion.
We've already made a pyramid scheme.
We've already dipped our toes into this concept.
Dude, I could totally make that in Minecraft right now.
It'd be fucking easy. It'd be baby mode.
Do it right now and we'll have it be the thumbnail for the episode.
That's a good idea.
Well, I don't want to be distracted.
But to be serious about it, if I was going to make a religion,
I would sort of have it be...
It's just based on what I think anyway.
But it would be some weird...
Okay, human beings are weak and need things to gather around and pretend is real even if it's not.
They need some sort of spiritual fulfillment in some way.
You're running thunder here, dude, but keep going.
Fair enough.
I would say the worship of intelligence or progress
or the human spirit or success of people, human happiness.
Those are the values that I have, so I would just send them a religion around those.
But the problem is that religions are fundamentally based on faith, obviously.
That is the core idea behind every single religion.
Not the best religion of all, Wicca.
It's based around casting six spells and enchantments and sorceries.
Are you a cyber Wicca, aka a digital pagan?
I mean, I don't want to limit myself to just one box of Wicca.
Yeah, there's so many labels, there's so many boxes.
Why would you limit yourself to just one?
I want to be a fucking Wicca, pagan, Christian, Islamic, fucking atheist.
And if I'm going to do that, you can't fucking stop me.
Yeah, it would be fucked up.
It would just be dogmatic to say that you can't be all of those things at once.
Be bigoted.
Indeed.
Indeed, that's true.
There is a real debate, I think, to be had here between some of us.
Because I generally think...
We were saying before about how religion does have sick architecture.
Christopher Hitchens, old dead atheist who was pretty cool, used to say that the one thing...
He would ask this question to people who debated about religion because he's a big atheist guy.
Tell me one thing that you can get from religion that you can't get from secular humanism or whatever.
And the one answer he got that he thought was reasonable...
I mean, at the time, he said music.
Like, divinely, faith-inspired music.
The feeling of surrender to a higher power that is beyond comprehension is something that is basically fundamental to religion.
And that sort of feeling is hard to recapture.
Can't you be an awe of the infinite universe and all that?
I mean, I'm an awe of Obama all the time.
Can't you be an awe of Obama?
I would write civilities about Obama.
I would get castrated for Obama if I was in the National Obama Choir.
I'd do that. I'd sign myself up for that.
Well, there's a particular type of thing here that you're in the hands of an omnipotent creator that's beyond understanding.
Are you telling me that Obama doesn't have big enough hands to hold me?
Obama's got the biggest hands in the fucking game! That's why he plays so much people!
Okay, well, you know what? That's fine at all.
I find some things that...
Crazy people also can make pretty cool art, which is what's going on here, I'd say.
I mean, look at this channel.
Look at this channel, fair viewers.
What I was bringing up with the architecture is obviously a lot of architecture back in the day was cool and stuff.
Just like all the religious stuff.
It's not like religion isn't the reason we have cool buildings.
Catholicism is super aesthetic.
Oh, it is.
I love the aesthetic of it.
Yeah, and it's not like I'm saying religion should exist so that maybe a church can be built.
I'm just saying...
Some people would argue that, though.
Besides the obvious, like, yeah, it's not real.
It's nice to just let people enjoy the things about it.
I don't know, I just don't really mind too much about it.
Well, okay, here's...
I'm glad you said that, because that ties into what I was going to get to.
Here's where we can actually have a debate here.
Christopher Hitchens would go on to say,
beyond being an atheist, he would define himself as an anti-theist,
which is that if there even was a God, he would be opposed to it,
because he finds the very idea morally reprehensible.
And I have a lot of agreement with that position.
I think the idea that God is real...
So Christopher Hitchens is El from Death Note.
No, no, not El, near.
He's near.
He's by the Elf from Elf.
As seen in Elf.
Correct.
Yes, yes.
Yeah, you know what, while I'm at it, I'll just quote the near line that I...
As a child, this might have been the first time I really got, like, really fedora tippy just in my own life
when I read in the final volume of Death Note when near is about to capture a light.
This is a quote that really inspired me.
I would put on all my Facebook bios and whatnot when I was a young lad.
It was, even if God exists and I had his teachings laid out before me,
I would still decide for myself what was right and what was wrong.
And I could not agree more with that.
It's great. It's great stuff.
It's a great line. It's a great line.
Yeah.
What direction are we going to take with this?
Are we going to talk about, like, our histories with the legend?
Like, how we feel about it first?
What we're going to do is we're going to talk about our stuff that we know about and think about religion.
And then we're going to create our own religions each.
God, I agree.
And explain the teachings.
Okay, here, I'm just going to lay out this before, like, spoiler alert.
This is the only discussion that can occur around religion.
This will just be a spoiler for the podcast here.
I'm going to condense all the history of religious discussion into, like, a paragraph.
I like God. Well, he's not real. There's no evidence.
Yeah, but I like him.
Oh, but, you know, there's no evidence.
Yeah, I know.
It makes me feel comfort because I don't like the idea of there not being God.
Yeah, I mean, that's true.
It's nice to feel comfort, but it's fake.
There, it's done.
Yep, that's done.
Yeah, that's it.
All right, bye.
That's it.
That's the entirety.
What else could you say?
Well, that's the thing.
Is it, okay, here's the anti-theist thing.
Is it, in fact, morally reprehensible to believe in God?
I would argue yes.
I think it just depends on what you do.
To believe in Him?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
To just believe in Him.
Like, to just believe that he's real?
No.
Like, if you're a kid and you say you believe in God because your parents were told to,
I mean, in that case, it's different.
But to be a functioning adult who says you believe in God, I find morally reprehensible.
I think.
All right, here's my point on that.
I think, obviously, people don't follow the books 100 percent.
Like, not every person who isn't is a Muslim.
They don't even read the books most of the time.
Yeah, they don't read.
Like any adaptation.
They don't know the whole thing.
We don't cover everything in the books.
They cherry-pick, you know, and they do whatever they do.
So the idea that the book, I mean, it is like, it does make bad things happen.
But I think if someone just says, yeah, I believe in God, I don't think that initially means anything.
I just, like, it depends on what they do.
See, I disagree already with that fundamental position.
Because I think if you say that you believe in God, at the very least,
At the very least, it means you're an idiot, but that's all.
Like, it means you're stuck in your ways and you won't change.
But that doesn't mean anything, really.
It just depends on what you do with, like, it's a case-by-case sort of thing.
I think it informs at least, I totally admit that there's a huge variety of people here.
But if you believe in any God, that means that you believe that there is a creator who made the world as it is.
And, like, to spend any amount of time thinking that there is a God, therefore XYZ happens,
Like, there is no logical way you can arrive at this conclusion that there's any reason to do so.
So I would say that that is a waste of your time and resources.
But you can't conclude that there's not either.
But that's exactly the point, though.
Okay, let me just clarify real quick.
Atheism, simply, some people define it like, some people are identitarian, which is always a bad thing to be.
And say, I'm an atheist, therefore.
I'm an atheist, and this defines who I am to person.
The self-professed anti-theist is saying that identitarianism is bad.
I've not actually, I would not never use a label on myself to describe who I am to person.
Wait, what the fuck is identitarianism?
It just, like, to be, to say that, okay, I'm a Christian.
Like, that means I feel like I belong to this group.
I am part of it, and this applies to any group.
Like, I am, even saying, like, I'm male, therefore, like, I'm into male stuff.
That is being identitarian.
Which I've already crushed and proved does not exist in a previous episode.
We've already discussed this.
We've only proven that wrong.
Yeah, very true.
The concept of maleness sure is a slippery one.
If someone is an atheist, therefore, they go and join tons of, like, atheist organizations,
and they write on all their Facebook bios that they're an atheist.
Yeah, like, if you do that, then you're, you are becoming an identitarian.
You're using this label to define yourself, and people will use that to judge you.
So, don't do it.
Instead, be represented by your ideas.
But here's the point.
An atheist simply means one who lacks the belief in God.
And I want, just to be super clear, because people fuck this up every time.
Lacking the belief, meaning you have not been convinced that something is true.
That is what it means, and therefore, everyone should be defined as an atheist from birth
until they have made a logical, educated argument to themselves
and are convinced that God is real.
That is when you should then say, okay, now I'm transitioning to a theist.
I just feel like it, like, for a lot of people, they never think about it, ever.
And it's just like an answer to a question.
Do you believe, yes.
I go to church every so often.
Yeah, but I don't see too much of a problem in, like, a person who is just a normal person.
Nothing about them is, like, unusual.
I'll tell you exactly why it's a problem.
Compared with, like, an atheist or someone who just grew up somewhere else.
It's because it allows the demagogues of society to say, look at America, 99%, you know, theists.
This is a God-fearing country.
Therefore, XYZ, I do, is justified in the name of God.
What a great adjective, by the way, that people use it unimarcably, God-fearing.
Like, God, like, like, they'll use it as a positive.
Like, that's a good thing.
Like, that's something you want people to be.
Yeah, yeah, that's a positive.
By the way, I really want to say, like, oh, like, I want to say, like, you know,
oh, you can believe whatever you want to believe it.
And I am currently saying that right now with my mouth.
That is how I feel, like, you know, believe whatever you want.
However, I can't wrangle my empathy as well as I would like to.
Because I just fucking hate him.
I just hate him.
I'm sorry.
Believe what you want.
But I, it's, it's, stop.
Stop it, please.
If God is real, he is a moral monster.
And I don't want to hear any of this bullshit about free will.
If I created a race of, like, super intelligent rats and set them in a cage
and watch them tear each other apart because I gave them the gift of consciousness
and, you know, therefore evil could be created.
I am responsible for that just as God would be.
Well, I mean, I think it's kind of hypocritical sometimes when people say that, like,
God is, like, a moral good despite all this.
Because we could, we extend ethical consideration to, like, animals
that we think are, like, intellectually lower than us.
And we can, like, make decisions on, like, a macro scale that, like,
animals don't have the consciousness to be aware of.
And, like, we didn't create them.
We just look on the situation and be, like, we should do this thing.
You know, like, conserve animal conservation and shit like that, whatever.
So to say that, like, that is a moral imperative, like, that's a moral good.
And then to be, like, well, God can just let us beat our own devices
and that's, like, somehow also good.
It seems like a contradictory position.
Well, here's an observation.
If you believe in God, you probably also believe in other foolish things,
like objective morality.
And if you believe in an objective morality, you have to,
you have to be, like, well, okay, but what is that?
And some people might say that, like, God is the definition of what is good
and therefore anything that God wants is a moral good, like, by definition, you know?
But as we already discussed, our friend, Nier, dispatched that argument handily.
Well, that was just like his opinion, man.
Well, I think that kind of, like, boils into what I was going to say about religion,
which I've already spoken about God and religion in depth in my, like, 45-minute
hyperbolic wine chamber episode, which everyone should listen to.
But my kind of thing with religion is, like, I think it's basically just a social shorthand,
because, like, for an order for, like, a society to function competently,
you need to have a bunch of people who have a core set of foundational beliefs
or ideas that they all agree on, because that's basically the foundation
you build an entire social structure on top of.
You know, people come together, they believe certain things,
or they have a certain kind of idea of what, like, good and bad is,
what, like, right and wrong is, there's, like, a foundation.
You know, we have, like, law and stuff like that.
And religion is a convenient way of being, like, these are the boundaries of society.
This is the boundaries of behavior, right?
So if you have a society that's all Christian, for example,
everybody's operating under the same sort of, like, social and moral assumptions,
so you have social cohesion that way.
And the interesting thing with, like, America now is that because we're kind of, like,
stepping back and allowing all this intermixing of stuff to happen,
like, we're opening society up to new ideas, but at the same time,
society is also becoming more unstable because people can't agree on the essentials anymore.
They can't agree on the foundation when everybody has a slightly different
resupposition of what that foundation is,
whether that's religious, whether that's social, anything like that.
So I feel like it's very difficult to come to, like, a social consensus
when you don't have everybody agreeing on those foundational principles.
And I think even especially, like, back in the day, religion was a great way of being, like,
you know, where, you know, Roman Catholic and their Protestant and, like,
both those societies have that same sort of basic foundation
that they've built everything on top of.
It was definitely a great herding mechanism to fucking hurt the sheep idiots of the world.
Yes, there's no way to disagree with that.
Well, see, that's the thing.
Depending on how you treat it, like, I mean, I am totally willing to admit,
it is possible that long-term humanity would do better to, like, dogmatically believe
in something like Christianity.
It is possible that just, like, general people having the belief in this religion
will just make humanity do better, like, long-term.
Whereas it's possible we might just, like, fall into chaos.
But if it gets results, you know?
Well, yeah, if it gets results, but here's the thing that I think guys don't bring up enough
is that I have, I have a, I put a core fundamental value on the idea of truth.
I totally admit that my, one of the important things to me in this whole argument is truth.
I care about what's real and what's not real for many reasons, including that which I think
that it's the way to achieve the best results long-term, you know?
And I admit that that, like, is kind of up for debate,
but I think that it will work out the best long-term if we know all the facts such as
there is no God.
I have, like, a big, it's sort of like a, maybe it's a cultural thing.
Oh yeah, it's also that.
But, like, I think it may be a cultural divide where, like, religion, God, yes, no,
the ramifications of society is not a big deal in the UK as much, especially not growing up.
Like, I never met, like, a crazy religious person that would, you know,
it just feels, yeah, I know it can be, like, terrible,
but I just, I like this idea in my head of, like, I believe people can be okay
and that you can have a conversation with fucking anybody if you're nice to them
and you don't talk about things that would rile them up.
So, like, I try to treat people, like, individually and to grasp
and try and, like, discuss and think about the social ramifications
of an entire culture, civilization or world based on, like, whether you should
or shouldn't read a book.
It's just a bit too much for my fucking, like, scope of my brain to, like, really comprehend.
Like, it's not to comprehend, but, like, it just doesn't seem like a good use of my time
to think about whether it's a good idea on such a large scale.
I'd rather just lay in it.
But the fact is that people are out there feeling like it is a good use of their time
and making it a big deal, whether you want it to be or not.
I know.
I feel the same way.
Like, while I just said that I hate all of this, I do, you know,
I have a lot of fucking, you know, religious family that I wouldn't, like,
I wouldn't say, like, you know, crazy fucking snarky atheists bullshit to them
because, you know, I just like them as people
and I don't feel the need to rile them up and, you know, I'll treat them as an individual.
I just don't like this idea because, like, like, because, like,
I guess it was different in the UK, but, you know, everyone's religious
from where I am coming from, my family.
You know what was interesting?
And you know what was interesting over the holidays?
Yeah.
Sorry.
You know what was interesting over the holidays?
I went back home and was with my family for Christmas and whatnot
and, like, there was a moment where I had a conversation with my dad.
I don't remember why, but, like, the word...
I mean, why would you ever?
Indeed.
The word atheist came up and, like, I was just like, yeah, blah, blah, blah.
You know, the guy's not real, et cetera, et cetera.
And my dad, I know, is religious.
But then he looked at me surprised and said, wait a minute, are you an atheist?
And what was weird was that I thought that we had discussed this specifically before
and I don't know if maybe he just was like, yeah, he's just feeling this way right now.
And then I, unfortunately, I just, like, I was like, oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Big time.
Oh, no.
Like, the unfortunate thing about that was I feel that in that moment, he then began to project
everything from the, you know, 60 or so years of his life about what he had learned about atheists
and his, like, idea of what an atheist is.
Like, he then was like, oh, now I need to project all this onto my son.
Yeah.
Whereas, see, that's exactly my point.
That's what I did with vegetarianism right there.
Yeah, exactly.
That's exactly my point is, like, some people are very judgmental when it comes to labels.
And so I just, like, I try not to do that to them.
I try not to do that to anyone.
I agree.
That's the way to do it.
And they say, I'm very religious.
I'm like, oh, well, I'm not.
And they go off on me and then they're a piece of shit.
But I'm not going to go away saying, I hate Christians now.
I don't think any of us would be like, if someone were to say they are a Christian,
we would like, like fucking like block them and run away screaming.
Yeah, but like, it's the same thing on just a larger scale to say most of them are like this.
Because I've met like vickers and stuff who are just normal nice people who like the community
and they just, they are good at stuff.
When they're not raping boys.
I don't have any opinions on Christians as a whole.
I have it on Christianity and just religion.
I don't know anything about Christians as a whole.
That's why I was careful to say, I'm not like anti, I actually am anti-Christian.
But I'm anti-Christian because I believe that I have a case to make that the ideas of Christianity are destructive.
Like it's not that I think every Christian is a bad person or any religious person, of course not.
And like somebody like Sam Harris likes to bring up for like non-destructive religions like Jainism, for example.
Jainism being this religion where like violence is like the ultimate taboo.
So these guys go around in like monasteries and they wear masks over their mouth so that they don't accidentally inhale a bug and kill it.
Because that would be a grave sin.
And you know, things of this nature.
I find Jainists pretty morally reprehensible too because of all the fucking time they're wasting caring about shitty bugs that don't matter.
So, you know, fuck them, fuck them.
I agree.
I'm totally with you.
It's like what's the point?
Like sure you're not adding anything, but what's the point?
Who cares about a fucking bug?
I just hear that the same sort of like zealotry in anti-religion that there is in religion.
And I know that there's like...
It's funny how atheism has become a religion almost.
Oh, I hate that line so much.
Fuck off.
I'm not saying that.
I know that there are objectively good things about atheism and stuff like that.
Like I'm not arguing that religion should ever...
Like if I was to say to someone, I wouldn't recommend any of them to anybody.
But I just...
I think to solve problems in society, instead of telling people to stop like doing their thing that gets them really riled up and angry,
it's to control other things like money.
Like to make incentives aside from religion that would like...
In the UK, so many people don't go to church, but of course it used to be a very religious place.
And it's because of things that just to distract them like technology and things that nobody cares anymore.
Like the school system...
How did they admit a mockery of the whole fucking thing by making themselves head of the church?
And then it was just like, well, I guess this is a joke now, so whatever.
We'll just fucking...
Yeah, I mean, I don't know whether that's it.
But like it's...
Close enough.
Religion will...
Canon does become pacified.
In America, it's kind of...
Kind of...
It's kind of big.
Yeah, until the fucking...
So I don't know how that's going to change.
But like...
There's ways to go about changing the world in the way you want without attacking groups of people who are very prone to get angry and mad and violent.
You know what?
I'm really glad you brought this up because I want to dismantle this argument that I personally am attacking anyone.
Who the fuck am I attacking by making an argument that your God is fake and you're a fucking idiot for believing in him?
It's just...
It's not attacking.
It's just like common sense.
These people, they are very...
But it's not to them.
They don't know shit.
They don't...
They believe in God.
They're so stupid.
That's the whole point.
You can't approach them so undelicately if you want to change their minds about stuff.
Okay, okay.
You know?
You know, there's this...
Sam Harris talks to this guy at Majid Nawaz.
They've done a bunch of work together.
And Majid is a former Islamic extremist who, you know, a lot of like left-wing people think that he's like a...
They call him a fucking coon and shit, like a porch monkey because he like is trying to...
Yeah, I mean, they really hate this guy because he is a...
Did you hear the dude?
Have you heard of the term coconut?
I've heard that pop up.
Oh, okay.
That makes sense.
When they're brown on the outside, white on the inside.
They're just like, oh my God.
Brown and very hairy on the outside.
Yeah.
So, you know, it makes sense.
Very nice.
It makes sense.
But so like these guys work together, you know, Sam is an atheist who thinks that there's like problems with the fundamental beliefs of Islam.
And Majid is a former Islamic extremist who himself like advocated for like the destruction of Western society as a young man.
But now is like, well, okay, no, that actually is ridiculous.
And he's basically an atheist, but he calls himself like a cultural Muslim at this point.
And like, I totally agree.
If I want, for example, it's not specific to them, but for example, I'd like the Muslims, the Muslim community to produce just less terrorists.
We can all agree that there are some terrorists that come out of Islam just like they do from Christianity.
The scale might be different, but it happens.
And I would like there to be less.
And I think one effective means to do so would be to talk to the leaders of that religion and have them, you know, say that like, yeah, you know, this is some bullshit.
What we've been talking about like kill the Westerners and, you know, the women are horrors because they don't cover up and stuff.
That's the sort of change in attitude I would like.
And I would like that to be a first step towards everybody realizing God's not real.
It's bullshit.
We're all people.
Let's just be friends together.
That's what I want.
So I think you're right, Gib.
I think you're right.
I don't disagree.
Yeah, I think that like most of this podcast, at least to me, is all basically 20 years old.
It's none of this.
It's like 700,000 years old.
I feel like we're like, you know, it's been said that the PCP is turning into just fucking, you know, mansplain where we talk about shit that we don't understand.
And, you know, none of us are theologists here.
But like this is just...
I was a Christian, man.
I'm fucking confirmed.
We're just fucking...
Like, again, there is no other conclusion to come to from this.
Like, none of us, like Hippo, I agree with you.
I think we all agree with you.
No one hates Christians.
This is all just nothing.
This is all nothing.
We've said nothing this entire podcast.
You guys need to stop.
You should stop apologizing for your opinion here that religion's ridiculous.
I think it's counterproductive.
Everyone's going around these days saying like, oh, it's so tired to say that God's not real.
Let's just like lay off it for a while.
It's not what I'm saying at all.
It's not what I'm saying to even one.
It is.
You and everybody else out there is all like, oh, it's so uncool to say that God's not real anymore.
No, it's cool.
It's still cool.
It will always be cool.
I'm still cool.
I'm not saying that we shouldn't have this discussion.
I'm just saying...
This is not a commentary on the actual topics of the discussion.
It's of the discussion itself.
And just like...
My conclusion to bring with this is just that, okay, like, confirmed God is wrong.
Okay.
I just want to say...
I don't think the PCP has ever been about like making a change with the topics we talk about.
We're just fucking around.
We're circle jerking.
Now, let me make a case real quick for why you should literally murder every Christian you see on the street.
Okay.
Here's what we got.
Because they believe in God, they're willing to kill the gays.
They'll kill you if you commit adultery or anything.
Like we are.
It is your moral responsibility to kill every Christian you see at any given time, America.
So wake the fuck up, get that axe out, get it nice and sharp, and get to work on the streets.
I want to see mass murder by tomorrow.
Nate says, kill the infidel who believes in God.
Yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
Do any of us have any lingering thoughts about God?
How many of us grew up religious?
Or at least in a religious environment?
Hardcore religious group.
Me and Nate grew up pretty moderately religious.
Like we would go to church and stuff, but that was like the extent of it.
But then I read Death Note and it all changed.
We should like first communion and we got confirmed at our church and stuff, but like...
I think our church was just real like pretty liberal about it and like I didn't even get the sense that the church even cared that much.
Because heroic atheists such as myself have been beating down Christianity for generation upon generation,
leaving it the hollow husk that it is now and we need to do the same to all religions.
Especially Janus.
I will kill every Janus that's out there.
Unproductive.
My family is not religious, but I did go to a primary school which had a church attached to it called All Saints School.
And every Friday I think we would go in there because we didn't go to school on Sundays or whatever.
We would go in there and have like, we have assembly every morning in the normal hall.
And then on the Friday we would go into the church and we would sing hymns and stuff.
But I never got the sense of like any of this was supposed to be taken as real.
And even we had like RE, we would have like religious education classes every so often talking about.
We would talk about, well it's not like the Christian stuff, it's just like religion in general.
Like today we're going to learn about Sikhism and stuff.
And then one day a couple times a year the vicar from the church who is like a really tall,
he was like seven foot and he had a big old white beard.
He was basically Father Christmas and he was so fucking cool.
And everyone loved him.
He was like a paragon of the local community.
And he would like read us things from the Bible and tell stories about it.
Like he wouldn't just read it, he would like tell a story.
And it's like dude, this is cool.
That's the yesterday man.
I just never got the sense that it was real.
And then I asked my dad like, is that stuff real?
And he says, no.
And I was like, oh, that's my religious upbringing.
There you go.
Pretty sick.
It's just a bunch of cool hymns and fun shit and a cool church that I love.
I have a weird relationship with God because well, I was in a pretty religious family.
I have a personal relationship with God.
I was in a pretty religious family.
But like, I can't remember a time where I thought God was real, even though I went to church and like extensively.
I just don't even remember a time thinking that.
My relationship, like I was never into God.
But at this point, my relationship with God is basically the same sort of relationship I had with my kids
after my wife divorced me, after finding her in bed with another woman, non-existent.
I don't have any lingering thoughts about that.
Even though like I went to fucking, like I was a church boy.
I went to Awana and shit.
I just, I just hate it so much.
I can't even remember if there was any time where I believed any percent ever.
I remember being like, as much as the zero percent run on his religious speed running.
Yeah, okay, okay.
I remember being like 14 or so and being in the shower one day and just being like, wait a minute.
I don't think I really believe all this God stuff.
Wait a minute, touching my willy feels so good it can't be wrong.
There's just no way.
This is a sin.
It was pretty, it was pretty sick.
Did any of you go to Awana by the way?
What the fuck are you talking about?
Awana? Awana means family?
I saw that movie in theaters. It was okay.
Yeah.
Awana?
I don't know what you mean.
But here, if it's alright, I would like to explain my experience with Awana, if that's alright.
If I could just have the floor here for a second.
Okay.
Awana was this, I guess I'll call it a program, that my mother enrolled me in to try and reinvigorate
my need to go to church, which was never there in the first place.
But she was just desperately trying to convert me to become a Christian at this point.
But she could tell that the light was fading from my eyes and my eyes were rolling back in my fucking skull.
And I was getting an aversion to crucifixes and the like.
I am a fucking ghoul.
Anyway, so it's at this, it was this, like kind of late at night, like seven.
Like an age group for this is I'm like eight or ten.
Probably around eight.
Anyway, at seven, there would be a church, you know, in my town.
And I would go there at like every Wednesday at seven.
And here's, I'm going to break Awana into three parts.
The running around in the circles part, the killing part, and then the scary part.
The first part was my favorite because it involved, there is a big circle out in the field, a lawn of the church.
It's just this big circle.
And you would play games to warm yourself up into the God-loving spirit and into the God-fearing spirit.
Sorry, sorry.
You know, to get those little kids fucking fearing for their fucking lives with fire and brimstone.
If they ever, you know, betray God.
So basically I would just run around in circles non-stop.
Even when they told me to stop, I wouldn't stop because I just loved it so much.
There was free orange juice and it was great.
And every single time I got lured into a false sense of security because I just loved orange juice
and ran around in circles so much that I almost forgot the killing part.
So it's like after like, like, like, like 20 minutes of me running around in circles.
They would like, alright guys, it's time to learn about the Bible.
And they would like round us up, like, like fucking break us off into groups so we're easily to manipulate and like overpower.
And they would lead us into like this big like fucking like, I guess I would call it like a library part.
And they would just like force us for like two hours to just like do like school assignments and essays on the Bible.
It was a fucking nightmare.
And everything was dimly lit with candles.
There were no actual lights. There were only candles because I guess that's how they did it back in the day.
It was fucking terrifying and awful.
And I had to write essays about the Bible, which at this point I already knew was like, I like, no, no, thank you.
And after that, that wasn't even it.
They forced us to go to fucking like, like, like a church, you know, like into the real church part
and just like stare at this fucking priest, give like a real ass sermon to these fucking like, like, like field sea of children
who don't even like know some of the words he's saying.
That's what was one of those like for like every week for like five fucking hours for my entire life.
And it never, it never got a hold of me.
I'm so happy it didn't even though my fondest memories of kid are still running around in circles.
And I still do that to this day.
That's, that sounds rough, buddy.
I also want to, you know, the reason that I suggested we do religion, it's because I wanted to come clean, guys.
I need to confess because I am in fact a secret religious person, more than anyone in the world.
See, okay, the reason I have a problem is because I was deeply embarrassed by my own religious beliefs as a child.
So now I feel the need to destroy the temple that these were founded on.
So that's what this has all been about my whole life.
So when I was a kid, we were in Sunday school and one fateful day, the teacher of the Sunday school,
this lady who I forget the name of, started telling us about like, okay, guys, real shit, my little Negroes.
What happens when you're in a situation where someone is using the word God or swearing and you as a good Christian, it makes you uncomfortable?
What the fuck do you do?
And I was like, I mean, so this was all new to me that like any of this would be a problem.
Probably like 12 or 13 or so.
And was this like a quiz? Was this like a pop quiz?
No, this was just a discussion in our little class about like, she's just like, okay, real situation guys, someone's using God's name in vain.
What the fuck do you do?
That's what this was presented as.
And so I began to reflect, God, I don't know what to do when the infidel begins speaking the Lord's name.
Please tell me.
So it was at this point that she's like, okay, guys, here's what happens.
You calmly, politely go up to this person and say, excuse me, it makes me very uncomfortable that you are using the Lord's name in vain.
And I would appreciate it if you would stop doing that.
And she would say and do the exact same thing with her swearing.
You go up to them and say, excuse me, I am a Christian and that kind of language is deeply offensive to me.
Please cease and desist this activity at once because you're making me uncomfortable.
Okay, this was the argument presented and this blew me the fuck away.
I was like, this is it. This is the answer I've been looking for.
This is what I'm going to be.
This gives me power over my peers.
I can go lambast them for, you know, all their minor infractions against God and man, aka me.
So here I go.
From this point on, I began a year-long crusade against those around me in school and otherwise who would use the word God in any situation and who would just swear to even the slightest degree.
I became that kid in quotes, that kid, in fucking parentheses.
I remember times in your childhood when you would just never swear.
I remember years-long period where you would never ever swear.
I remember it as just like, I'm sure that went on, but there was a distinct year where I became a zealot of telling people to not swear nor use the name God in any context.
In any context, you must say the Lord or, you know, just be polite about it.
You got to say God in like the right context.
So I just became, I became a fucking crusader.
I started my own one-man crusade and just looking back on it, it's so humiliating to me that I did that, that I swore I would destroy the temple that indoctrinated me into this belief.
So that's the real reason why I, you see, God is real.
I just want to confirm for everybody, God is real, but I am mad at him.
That's why I'm an atheist.
That's why I am an atheist.
That's, that's, this is real.
There you go.
Okay, so that's, that's my story and I'm sticking to it.
Do you have a definitive moment when you realized you were not religious?
Do you have like a moment?
Ben shared his.
I actually, I think what made me, like, what Gibbs said way before about like how people just don't think about it.
What, what I remember is that like, okay, when I was 16 and I was getting confirmed, you know, which is like, when you go through the confirmation, like the pros of like becoming a real Christian or whatever.
You have to like, you get hate.
Yeah, like for us, it was like in our congregational church, you like, you have a mentor and you like meet with them and you talk with them.
And you had to beat him in a hand-to-hand comment so he could be considered a real Christian, yeah.
I'll always, I'll always remember.
I forget the name of the guy, but he called me, he said he liked me.
Was it Mr. Waterman?
Yeah, it was Mr. Waterman.
Who called me a serious young man.
He was my like confirmation mentor too.
Yeah, he was cool.
He was all right.
I liked him a lot.
But at the, during the process of like going through this thing of like, okay, let's actually think about God, like, what is he?
Like, why do I believe in him?
Because I faced those questions, I realized, wait a minute, there like is no reason to believe any of this.
And then I read Death Note and I was like, well, that goes on forever.
It's over.
Question answered.
So it was, it was like during, it was when Christianity was put to the test in my life.
That's when I realized like, okay, there actually is really no reason to like believe any of this.
Boy, they really, they really didn't get the outcome they were looking for there, did they?
Indeed.
And no, we were, we were a Congregationalist Protestant, whatever that means.
Yeah, Congregationalist.
Which, whenever I asked mom and dad, what does it mean that we're Congregationalists?
Like, what is that?
They would tell me, but they would only explain it insofar as to explain how we were not Catholic.
I don't think they understood what Congregationalism actually was.
They just knew they wanted it to be a Protestant church and this was the one in our town.
The problem with Protestantism and Congregationalism and, you know, all these other Protestant subdivisions,
is that their whole problem is that they just, they believe that Catholicism is true.
They just hate it.
They just don't like it.
They know it's real.
They know it's real, but they're mad at it.
Well, the whole reason the Protestant church got started is because they fucking wanted to get divorced.
That's, yeah.
I mean, all right, the splintering of Christianity, because it does not make sense, like across the board,
began long ago with the initial fracturing between, you know, Catholicism and Protestantism,
and I'm sure long before that as well.
So, you know.
Hey, hey guys, maybe you shouldn't be allowing people to buy their way out of going to hell.
Yeah, fuck the church!
Oh no, what have I done?
See, that's why, if it would worse, I'm an atheist now, but if I ever realized if I changed my ways,
and I'm like, shit, I fucked up, I was Roman Catholic, so I can just go in there, throw some 20s at the priest,
and I'm cool with it.
Yeah, exactly, yeah.
It's all good.
It is such an absurd notion.
I honestly think a lot of these people, like, just thought it was like an obvious joke.
Like, kind of like Flat Earthers today.
Like, it's either people who are just really dumb and not critically thinking,
or, like, they just think it's a joke that's just gotten out of control.
And like, I think so many religious people are just the butt of a big joke going on in their face,
and I'm like, guys, this is embarrassing, please, just like, think about this.
What do you, like, you're being humiliated publicly by me right now.
I feel like this has become like the Christianity podcast.
Do you have any, like, thoughts on other religions?
I kill the other religions.
I don't, I think they're all, I wouldn't treat any religion different than the other.
Like, Christianity, I just mean any religion.
Okay, because I, because I, um...
It's just easier to say than any religion.
Okay, I guess.
You know, you know what's a cool religion in the sense that it really isn't a religion at all?
Buddhism.
Oh, I have something to say about Buddhism.
But you go ahead.
Buddhism's like a fake religion.
Buddhism, like, pretends to be a religion.
Okay, I mean, I get that there's, like, different sects of it,
and, like, probably some Buddhists believe different things,
and some of them are more, like, religious about it.
But, like, the version that I read about,
it was literally just, like, being a Buddhist just means,
like, don't let yourself get sad about the things that make you sad.
Yeah.
And that's, like, the entire fucking thing.
Like, I don't, yeah, I don't know anything about it,
but all I can tell from, like, the imagery of the fat guy
is that one fat guy was really happy,
and some other people were like, oh, I want to be like that.
I want to be happy.
He was really happy after a period of being really sad.
My first girlfriend converted to Buddhism while we were dating.
I mean, I don't see why you would need to convert to Buddhism,
because, like I say, it's not a real religion.
Well, I guess convert to a strong word.
Just start, she started adopting the principles,
I suppose, it's probably more accurate.
Okay, yeah, well, phrasing on it.
There was a while where I was uncomfortable calling myself an atheist,
and I was just like, no, like, I'm just not into Christianity.
I'm into, you know, God and stuff.
Sure.
And by the way...
A lot of people go through that.
In case you think that was contradictory to what I was saying earlier,
this is in complete regard to how I presented myself to my family.
So I wasn't going to say to my mom, oh, I'm an atheist.
I was going to say, no, no, no, no, I'm just a Buddhist.
I'm just a Buddhist.
And she was like, oh, yeah, what are they believing?
And I was like, uh, you know...
Buddha.
Yeah, obviously.
Yeah, Buddha.
Right, yeah, no.
I love Hindu temples.
Those are, like, some of the coolest fucking places.
I've never been to one.
I think I've been...
I went to one...
We had, like, in primary school still,
because it's a whole saints' church.
We have a few, like, religious expeditions.
What do you call them?
School trips.
Trips? Yeah.
Yeah.
We went to see a synagogue.
I think we went to a mosque at some point.
And a church.
And a fucking Hindu temple in London.
There's, like, one where you can be a Hindu.
And it's fucking...
It was so beautiful.
It was, like, white marble all the way around.
And it's so elaborate, like, pillars and stuff.
Just to contrast the non-white people.
Yeah, they love it.
Hindus are pretty aesthetic religion, too.
I'm quite fond of it.
They've got that fucking elephant-man god.
Yeah, Vishnu, I think.
That's him.
I don't know.
That's a girl.
Okay, Nash, you're right.
You're right, you're right, you're right.
Okay, well, this is all cool and all,
but my favorite religion, I'm just going to say,
in terms of aesthetic, I know I'm going to sound like a wee,
but it's definitely Shinto.
Shinto is sick.
Shinto looks awesome.
Unacceptable.
Come on.
Those red things and their temples are beautiful,
and it's an, oh, my favorite anime.
Oh, my God, plus.
It looks nice.
Plus, let's not forget that the PCP guy
is canonically a Shinto god.
Let's not forget that.
I do not understand what the fuck Shintoism is.
I guess it's about, like, there are spirits.
There are, like, gods and spirits in nature,
and you have to, like, be cool with them
by washing your hands a lot.
Correct.
That's how I understand it.
It's about the nut boys in the nut force
playing some B-ball, a.k.a. Bushido ball.
Well, yeah, I mean, it's like Ben said.
It's like Native Americans just, like, believe
that all things have a spirit.
I'm not well versed in it, but, like,
which is similar to Shinto,
but I know in Shinto they think that there are, like, real,
like Princess Mononoke is a pretty deep,
like, obviously it's, like, cartoonized,
but, like, it's a fairly decent summary.
Like, there's spirits that, like, live in, like, forests
and stuff and, like, protect them,
and by, like, appealing to those spirits,
you can, you know, like, get favorable outcomes and stuff.
I mean, I think that's the idea.
But it looks so cool, the redness.
Just the color red being, like, the Shinto color
is sick.
It's so cool.
Yeah, it really looks like Shinto aesthetic
of, like, the really big sparkly eyes
and, like, colorful hair and small mouths and stuff.
Yeah, yeah.
Cloud was just the biggest Shinto propagandist
of all time when he blew up the fucking Mako Reactors.
Fuck materialism, dude.
I saw this, I was watching this TV show,
which is, like, well, what the fuck?
It's called Death Note.
It had a lot of interesting things to say.
It was this guy who usually does, like,
a gardening show about, like,
you should prune these bushes over the winter months
because blah, blah, blah.
It's, like, this old, like, English guy who's like,
oh, her, her.
And he went, he was going across, like,
Middle East places and palaces
to look at the gardens of, like,
kings and Muslim temples and palaces
that were built around Oasis'
because that's, like, a real, such an important thing
in a desert, obviously, is water.
And if you have water,
the way you show your wealth and stuff is to plant trees
and bushes and plants and it's, like,
and it was looking around all these Muslim things.
And, like, it's pretty good.
I like Islam now.
I want to know more about this fucking cool desert aesthetic
because I've known about, like, the Christian stuff
and the Hindu stuff for a while.
But, like, I want to go to, like, a big old mosque
and I want to look at all the cool, like, mosaic stuff
that they have.
I completely agree.
When I got super into Islamic
and also unrelated to Russian architecture
for, like, five years of my life
I just draw fucking mosques in my sketchbook
day in, day out because I just thought that, like,
how do you even describe the weird, onion-shaped domes
on the top of buildings?
We're just the coolest fucking thing in the entire world.
I used to think they were the best.
I think Aladdin did more for, like, positive Muslim vibes
than, like, anything in history,
at least in the West, at least in the West.
Why don't you be more of, like, a fucking Aladdin ices?
Come on.
Where's your flying carpets?
Yeah, asshole.
Why don't Alah give you some fucking magic carpets?
That's all nice and all you fucking babies,
but here's the big boy answer to what's the best religion,
the Aztec religion,
because it has a god, a god, a fucking god.
Oh, that's a good one.
You've seen May Dragon 2.
I love how he thinks of you.
I love how big that character is.
She's so hot, dude. Yes.
Oh, no.
Oh.
Yeah, Aztecs and Mayans.
They, they, they, I love old buildings.
Why don't people build cool shit anymore?
Where's all the rocks gone?
Because we stopped believing in God.
Oh, you're right.
Okay, to completely rob the fun from this discussion.
Okay, let's not forget that, like,
Aztecs did perform human sacrifice,
and they should be lambasted.
We know that it's sick and looks cool,
but it is morally retarded.
Nate, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, you come on.
Nate, you were just, but every time they sacrificed somebody,
they were killing someone who believed in God.
Well, you're not wrong.
There are less people who believed in God
as a result of their actions.
Have you guys seen The Road to Eldorada by any chance?
You probably have.
I have.
That's the greatest film ever made.
Nate, breaking out the hardcore killing people is bad.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, I know.
Thanks, Nate, for coming to this discussion.
There's this thing we do where we, like,
ignore the bad things about stuff
and just talk about how sick and cool it is,
and we shouldn't do that.
It's wrong.
Are you really going to argue that,
like, because I say that Aztecs killing people
is a sick as fuck, which we all agree that is.
People are going to be like,
oh, Aztecs killing people was sick as fuck.
Well, I'll just kill some people now.
Yeah, just kill them now.
All I'm saying is there's a lot of murder going on
in these video games I've been hearing about.
And I want you to stop immediately.
It needs to end.
The greatest Mesoamerican invention of all time,
video games.
Video games.
What was a human sacrifice other than an IRL video game,
I ask you?
The Sacrificing of the Heart was literally a cheat code.
It was literally a cheat code to get a good harvest.
They were all wearing oculus riffs during this.
That was their ceremonial headdress.
I mean, what is the afterlife but a giant video game
that we're all implored to buy like season passes to,
that we're all implored to pre-order
to make sure we get all the sweet loot.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, you're not wrong.
It's funny because it's actually true.
All right, guys.
I'm going to queue up for competitive.
He says lying down the sacrificial bed,
ready to fucking die.
Oh, but the reason I fucking rode to El Dorado
is because the one thing that is sick as fuck,
and I think they did this in one piece as well.
The thick bitches are good,
but what's better is that I really like this practice
they have when they do the sacrifice.
I don't know if every culture did it,
but I know it was true in some places
that if you were chosen as a human sacrifice,
you got to live the next year as a prince,
and you would just be like the guy who's the man
or the woman or whatever.
You would be an honored guest in the civilization.
You would be rich and all your needs would be taken care of.
Everyone would fucking love you.
You'd be sick as fuck.
I'm sure everyone would want to fuck you in that year.
You were literally made a prince,
and then after the year of all this good shit,
then you were sacrificed.
It's like they honored you,
and they made it worth your while,
because a lot of people would never get this shit.
I read the Hunger Games.
That is sick.
I know what that's all about.
Because killing people is bad.
I know your district gets fed for the year.
Yeah, that's cool.
Fucking Nadine is fucking Shintoism.
Jesus Christ.
The Spanish Inquisition's way cooler than Shinto.
And they're also red.
Yeah, guys.
My favorite religion, the Spanish Inquisition.
Yeah, it's like that's not a real good religion.
It's not a religion.
You know what?
It was so aesthetic.
Everyone wore red.
They wore red.
What else do you want?
They all are.
I worship the Spanish Inquisition.
Also the Holocaust.
I worship human tragedies specifically.
Each of them individually.
It's like I'm playing Fate Stay Night over here,
and all of my avatars are specific tragedies that happen.
You know, human sacrifice, the Aztec civilization,
the Holocaust, you know, bronies.
These are all individual gods in my pantheon.
We have even discussed the best part of Aztecs
is that when they kill an enemy unit,
they get free bonus at the culture points.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
That is good.
They can get a free social policy
every time they kill a fucking enemy unit.
That's great.
That's incredible.
Fucking top to your thread.
I fucking love Eagle Warriors.
Those are the best units in the game.
They literally are.
Dude, I love dark Templars.
You can't even see them when they're out there.
It's sick.
It's fucking ridiculous.
Yes.
You better build a fucking observer, asshole.
Guys, why are we talking about this game
when we all know Undertale is better?
He's right.
I'm just going to say,
they literally gave the Pope a copy of Undertale,
which is the most important.
Oh, no.
Impressive.
Amazing.
A fucking map pad.
Fucking map pad.
Fucking steam key to Undertale.
Steam key.
Didn't after the Pope was given Undertale,
didn't he like write like a blog post
or however they do in the Catholic Church,
about how like video games are evil?
Didn't that happen?
I'm pretty sure that's real.
No fucking way.
It's because he didn't like the undyne goat with elves.
Yeah, yeah.
I told you.
It was a forced character pairing.
That doesn't make sense.
It says the Pope in land.
Yeah.
That's what he was saying.
He throws his copy of Undertale across the chapel.
Oh, we haven't talked about the best part
of fucking religion,
which is in the Simpsons game for Xbox 360.
The ending fucking final level
is you go and meet God,
and the final battle is you have to,
this is completely removed
from the rest of the gameplay of the entire game.
You have to play DDR with the Xbox 360 controller D-pad,
and it never works as it's so unresponsive,
so I died like 70 fucking times
on that final level with God,
where I had to beat him at playing Rocky like a hurricane.
It was the hardest video game of my entire life,
and I fucking hate it.
That's why God is real.
That is excellent.
It just reminds me,
at the end of Dragon Guard 3,
like you kind of like,
it actually, it's like,
it's an action RPG game,
but at the very end,
like the final battle where you are a dragon
trying to slay like the combined unity
of like all the gods of the world.
Slay.
Yeah, you slay Queen,
and you literally slay these Queens,
these Yas Queens, these presidents,
who shattered the glass ceiling,
and now you're here fixing it,
patching that motherfucker up.
You are a proud male dragon meaghtow
who plays DDR to kill them.
That is how you win the game.
That is the final battle.
It's a sick DDR match that is incredibly difficult,
and I did it, and it was so sick.
It was great.
Good game, fun game.
I've got a question.
I've got a question about video games.
Okay.
What is your favorite,
What is your favorite fake video game religion
that you've seen in a game?
Good question.
You know what I really love?
I love, it's kind of a cop out,
but in Final Fantasy Tactics,
there is,
it's called The Church of Zoltana,
I believe,
that is basically a 100% parallel
for the Catholic Church,
but in that vein,
it has sick demons,
it has summons,
it's got a bunch of evil stuff,
it's just as corrupt and manipulative
as the Catholic Church was,
like throughout medieval times and whatnot,
and it keeps the sick Catholic aesthetic.
So I'm going to say that one.
My favorite religion is the one laid out
in the world ends with you,
because after you die,
you get to be a hip Japanese teenager,
and you get to hang out in the trendiest part of Tokyo.
That's pretty sick.
The ultimate reward.
I don't want to have eternal salvation,
I just want to be a hip, trendy hipster,
and hang out in the coolest clubs in Tokyo.
Why would anyone want anything else?
Ben, just, I don't know if you've heard about this,
have you heard they're making a remastered version
of the world ends with you for Nintendo Switch?
Are you aware of this?
No.
It's got new shit,
it's got a new character,
it's going to be something.
Alright, just throw that out there.
That's pretty cool.
Literally every single best guy ever video
is sponsored by Nintendo, everyone.
No, I'm good.
I am good.
Okay, go on, Munchie.
What's your favorite religion in video games?
I don't play video games.
I don't play single player games,
or a fucking cancer that I could never slog through.
I hate them.
Fucking CSGO is way better use of your time
than your fucking TF2 hat swap simulator.
It sounds like a ball.
Because those games you can play with other people,
which is the only reason I would even
wake up in the morning is to be with other people.
I don't want to fucking play like an RPG.
You don't care about like final fantasy?
No, no thanks.
Okay, you know what?
I take it back.
The best religion in any video game
is the one that the main character of hatred,
not important practices,
where he's out there murdering everyone.
That's mine.
That is what I believe and do.
Well, I think the best religion in video games
is the Juggalo religion from Homestuck.
Oh, no.
Because it's funny and it makes me laugh.
That's all.
I don't actually have anything to say.
Let's cut to the fucking chase.
Let's finally get this actual topic started.
We've been procrastinating for an hour and three minutes.
Time to get to the real meat in both of this topic,
spirit science,
and how it reveals the entirety of the human history,
and how to live your life to the fullest extent.
Dude, my Merkaba is fucking shining right now.
It's glowing.
Okay, go.
Whenever someone like mentions Lemuria,
my fucking chakras get so fucking blitzed,
I sit into another plane,
and I rip a hole in fucking space-time,
so all of the lower dimensional spirits
just spew out from my fucking body
and inhabit all the souls of the people around me.
Dude, you're being so Martian right now.
You're being so male brain right now.
It's fucking blowing my mind.
We were so right-brained.
We just couldn't fucking activate our chakras anymore.
Atlanteans are on Suicide Watch right now.
Dude, dude, literally,
like the reason Hitler killed all the Jews
because he knew they were aliens,
and he watched the fucking History Channel.
He knew, dude.
He knew he had to get rid of these unearthly beings.
Look, I'm not gonna say Hitler did everything right,
but that was one thing he did do right.
It had to be done.
The aliens had to be excised.
Okay.
On the actual real point about spirit science,
my mom literally believes that.
Oh, no.
This is the reason I came on the podcast
as identified by the fact that on the PCP sign-up
like spreadsheet thing we have,
it just says, my mom, where my name is.
Yes, that's correct.
My mom, for the past like two years at this point,
whenever I enter the car with her,
she'll have an audiobook playing,
and without fail, it's always about the law of attraction.
Nothing else, just the law of attraction.
Like gravity? Is that what that is?
No, Nate.
No.
Do you not know about the law of attraction?
Please explain it to me.
Oh my god.
I'm a child.
Prepare to get school.
You need to lecture us on the spirits.
The spirit science stuff,
because I still, I couldn't get through those videos.
There's so many of them.
Believe me, hippo.
I'll give you and everyone else a lecture on spirit science
sooner or later.
Oh.
Excellent.
Anyway, the law of attraction is,
it's kind of hard to put into words without making it sound fucking retarded,
because it is retarded.
But imagine that you really want a cool hat.
Then if you just think with all of your might,
I really, like I will get a really cool hat.
I will manifest a really cool hat.
It will be great.
There's no way this can't happen.
From the secret.
That's the secret, right?
Yeah.
The universe will hear your call and give you a really cool hat.
No questions asked.
Why do people believe this shit?
What is happening?
You know what the thing about that is?
That can kind of disguise itself as a real thing,
because if someone wants to challenge it on a metaphysical level,
you can backpedal and be like,
oh, well, no, no, you see, because if you're thinking about it,
you're more likely to take actions that will lead to it.
That's right.
I guess so.
But that's not really what it is.
That's not what the real argument for this law of attraction is.
They're arguing that your thoughts have some sort of psychic resonance
throughout the universe.
What they say obviously do.
You need to get to higher vibrations or whatever.
Why is there even a fucking vibration?
What we're doing is we're channeling our fucking Kundalini
so it's snake-tun-hisses really fucking loud.
So the high dimensional beings will hear our call
and actual project a manifestation of whatever object or desire we want.
And bring it to our dimension.
I got a kind of Lingus Delini for you right here, my friend.
All right, listen, listen, listen.
When I hear someone say they believe in God,
like, I'm not happy about it, but I'm like, okay, you know,
I'll forgive you if it's my friend.
Yeah, bit this one time.
But like, when I hear someone just like,
and they always do it like apologetically and on the side,
they're like, yeah, my crystals, you know.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
When I hear that shit, my fucking ears perk up
and my soul goes full male Martian.
I go full range.
It's like, what?
Full range.
You perform the Satan experiment.
They're the Lucifer experiment right then and there.
I just, I say to them, what did you just say to me, my friend?
Because they never want to defend this shit.
Did you just use the Lord's name in vain?
It brings me right back to those days.
I become the Crusader.
Oh my God.
That sort of reminds me, like, that's the way I think
and treat people who say, yeah, I mean, I believe in ghosts.
Like, it's never a religion thing.
It's always something like ghosts.
Ghosts are cool.
But it's not about cool, it's about real.
No.
Well, okay, okay, okay.
If someone was like, I believe in ghosts,
I'd be like, man, one idiot.
But then I would also, on the same hand,
be like, dude, I know ghosts are so fucking sick.
Let's compare our ghost notes.
See, I can't, I can't.
Okay, but like, when someone, like, the whole God thing,
like, the entire world is engulfed by belief in God.
So, like, I get it.
Ghosts as well.
Like, this person, to some degree, you're not wrong.
So, like, the world is religious.
I'm working to fight against it every fucking day,
but I get it, I get it.
But when I hear someone bring up, like, oh yeah, you know,
can I get my crystals with me?
They had to actively seek that out and subject themselves
to that kind of manipulation.
It just tells me they're on a next level.
Maybe they need those crystals, Nate.
Maybe some people need their crystals.
What?
Maybe some people find comfort in those crystals.
Yeah, these people just keep your jail crystals
at home, people, where I keep mine.
I don't bring them up in casual conversation
with people I meet on the street like you do.
Like, what, what is the argument here?
Like, God, the people have made really, like,
oh, okay, God has been, like, backed into a corner
so fucking hard by rational arguments that, like,
okay, there's no proof.
So, okay.
God's like a rabid and looked back into a corner
and we don't know what he's gonna do next.
Yeah, exactly.
But the crystal shit, like, what is the fucking argument here?
And what is your reason for believing?
Oh, I know what it is.
Okay, go ahead.
I know what it is.
Is they play too much Crash Bandicoot
and I think crystals actually have power.
They play too much Final Fantasy.
They're like, yeah, crystals are real, man.
I knew I should smack that controller out of her hand
when I had the chance when I wanted to.
My God, now.
She's always talking about fucking bandicoots
and groovy things.
It's too much.
I'm not saying that women shouldn't play video games,
but I am saying gamer girls are-
But this is what happens when they do.
Gamer girls are far more susceptible to the insidious nature
of the crystal indoctrination of so many video games.
That's why so many girls love Final Fantasy.
I feel like it's important to chart the progression
of how my mom got here, if that's all right.
My mom grew up in the deep south
and was some sort of denomination of Protestant
with a really strict household.
And then later down the road, when I came along,
she tried to get me to become a God person as well.
And so I culminated in one Easter where I-
Unfortunately for her, you instead became a God,
which was not part of the plan.
I'd be too powerful.
Anyway, one Easter, after Sermon was over,
I said to my mom, mom, churches are really scary.
God, the Bible, it's scary.
It's scary, aesthetically pleasing, scary things.
It's like the same situation I get looking at the Bible
or crucifix is like Dracula, Frankenstein's monster.
Those are scary things.
Ooh, ooh, oh, horror.
And I feel like I have mind-break dosing my mom
by saying that the Bible is scary.
Because after that day, it's weird.
She'll always insinuate that I am a hardcore Christian
for some reason, which I don't understand.
Even though I've clearly told her that I'm not,
she will just insinuate that I am.
And then she has gone into this weird fucking awful spiral
into fucking insanity.
I've talked about her high saturation Jesus artifact shit,
JPEGs, she has all right of room.
She has a ton of weird awful chakras and fucking rocks.
She goes to Sermons.
The reason I fucking visited Ben was because my mom already had
a plane ticket to go to Atlanta for a fucking weird crystal seminar.
That's the reason I went.
Because it was a weird fucking crystal seminar.
Now we're talking.
She started out as a normal Christian, which is still bad,
but due to the fact that I told her that the Bible is scary,
she had a weird fucking mid-religion crisis
and just googled how do I make God more interesting.
And then she just added some like special herbs and spices
into her fucking God brew and fucking jammed out to this bullshit
that is not real.
It just turtles all the way down with this kind of stuff.
There's no foundation here upon which all this is built.
If I'm wrong, please give me the evidence.
I mean, is the goal that like, does she just want to make sure
you're a good Christian boy and your soul is safe and everything?
Is that the goal here?
She's not trying to convert me.
She just like, like she doesn't bring it up.
It's just that it is so integral to her being that I can't avoid it.
Like I said, whenever I enter the car, she'll be playing an audio book
and then I'll just like put it in a headphone and she'll be like,
oh, I know you don't like this stuff for whatever reason.
Yeah, I'll turn it on the radio for you, you fucking heretic.
And I was like, I just want to go to Chipotle.
To just put out the olive branch to all religious people.
Like religious people, when they're sincere, many of them are.
Most of them, probably the best majority.
I'm sure a few of them actually believe this shit.
Well, it's a matter of logical conclusions.
But like, they want what's best for everybody for the most part.
They're like, guys, like what you were saying, Munchy,
just the fact that religion is weird and scary,
at least like Catholicism is,
just because it's scary and that they argue hell is real,
that itself, of course, is an emotional argument
that does not make it untrue in no way, just saying that it's scary.
Like, if it's real, it's the most important thing to get sorted out in your life
or else you will go to hell forever and be tormented forever.
And of course, you had another reason to believe that God is in fact evil.
Not if you actually...
It's time for a fucking tangent.
It's time for a fucking tangent where I explain just how much pleasure I get
out of knowing that like the hell that everyone believes in
has literally no resemblance to the hell actually described in the Bible.
Do you guys know about this?
Is that true?
No, no, no, I don't know.
Okay, well like the hell, the heaven and hell and stuff that you see,
that people go to in Looney Tunes, like where you die
and then if you're bad, you go to hell and if you're good, you go to heaven
and there's some funeral.
Hell is all like red and there's like a lot of fire and stuff.
Like, okay, like the Bible is fiction, right?
But that is like double fiction because that's like a fake interpretation
of something that's already fake.
The way hell actually word, as I understand it, according to the Bible,
like prepare to get your mind blown.
What actually happens is that when you die, you're dead.
Like you're not, you don't go anywhere.
You are just dead and you are dead in the ground corpse
until the book of Revelation's apocalypse happened and Jesus comes back
and then the dead are resurrected on earth.
There is no heaven dimension that you go to.
You are resurrected on earth and then Jesus and God and whatever,
they judge everyone and there is hell, but hell is just,
basically they just dig a big hole on earth and bad people get thrown into hell
and they do not-
Is that the lake of fire that's mentioned in the Bible?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, but they do not burn there forever.
They burn there for like the worst that they were,
the longer that they burn for as like punishment,
but then ultimately they're obliterated, like they're just gone.
And then there's good people that are saved.
They go to a shining city.
Like the heaven that they are going to is a city on earth.
I see.
How fucking neat is that?
Is this all in the book of Revelation?
That's way more interesting.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, I'm not an expert,
but that's my understanding of what the Bible actually says happens to good and bad people.
So in this actual interpretation,
there's no like after life at this point, like everybody who's dead,
they're just dead.
Yeah, they're just dead.
They're just dead.
They're not even in a better place.
Even all the religious people who say like, you know, like,
oh, like mom's in a good, better place and she's looking down on me.
Not if the Bible has anything to say.
They're in Bible stasis right now.
My dad.
That's fucking insane.
I know.
My dad has said that like he looks forward to meeting his,
you know, people who have passed on in the afterlife.
It might have been a while.
Maybe that's dated information from the guy, but he has said it.
And I guess there's just literally no basis for it.
It's just the crux of the issue.
Even though it's not what the book says.
The crux of everything, of this entire thing.
Like that's the only really reason religion still has any sort of place in
modern society with all this, this science and technological
progression proving like the ancient myths or whatever.
Religion has been beaten back from every area where science can touch.
The only reason it still has any sort of hold on anyone is
because we're all afraid of death.
And this is like the way you cope with it is like, well, when I die,
I'm not actually dead.
Exactly.
That's the well reason it still has any sort of sway on anyone at all.
A, you're afraid of death and you don't want to be nothing when you die.
Also, you're afraid of not knowing what to do with your life.
And religion gives you like direction.
Ben, are you saying that the afterlife and hell and heaven and all
of the eternal afterlife or suffering that you could experience in religion
is the equivalent of no-wacking voices and vinyl scratch?
It's just pure fanning, but everyone agrees with it?
Yeah, actually, like everyone's just going with it,
even though it has no basis in reality.
Yes!
That's good to me.
Wait.
Well, I remember no-wacking.
Dude, you could forget.
Shout out to no-wacking.
If you listen to this, we want you on the show.
We want you on the fucking show.
I asked her if she wanted to go out with me at BronyCon and she said she was a lesbian
and I was like, all right, cool.
Ben.
Is this a real story?
Yeah, that's a real story.
Oh my god.
That's insane.
I mean, I knew she wasn't going to say yes.
Oh my god, you almost dated vinyl scratch.
I know.
What the fuck?
He almost dated her.
I have to.
Up to you.
It was like right on the cut.
It could have gone either way.
It was right there.
It was a coin toss.
Exactly.
I'm going to twist a fate, settle this matter.
Yeah.
This time against Phantom Horn's favor, but next time, but next time.
This is fucking insane.
We should have a BronyCon stories.
A BronyCon reunion cast.
It's time to get the gang back together, guys, and launch our new Christmas album.
I literally have hundreds of stories from BronyCon.
We could literally do that.
Yeah, we could.
Oh, what do we got that Raven Cosplayer back on the PCP?
Remember that, guys?
Oh my god, it'd be incredible.
Jesus Christ.
She was good.
We can do it through...
What's her name?
The big one?
It was just a...
She was just some girl sitting...
There was a time when we were all sitting in our thing.
Oh, kind of.
She's a voice actor, never mind.
Oh, no, no, no.
Not Tara Strong.
Tara Strong.
I take Tara Strong in the PCP, though.
Shout out to Tara Strong.
You come on the PCP if you're listening.
Come on the PCP.
Yeah.
Do you remember anything else to say on the topic of religion?
I feel like we didn't have anything to say in the beginning.
Wait, wait, wait.
I have something to say.
I didn't know when to say this.
I'll bring it up now.
I did start a religion a little bit.
Oh, I see.
I mean, okay, I say that, but it was a really half-hearted effort.
I went and I looked into it a little bit, and I remember it being a bigger deal than
it was.
It's kind of embarrassing to even mention.
All I did was make a Facebook group describing a new religion and see if I could get people
to join it.
Oh, it's funny you mentioned this.
I attempted to do this at one point as well.
I don't really remember that much about it.
Okay, I remember that it was called The Church of Transubstantialism.
Okay.
Oh, well, actually, I think I remember the basic tenet.
The basic tenet of it is that reincarnation is real, but there's only one soul in the
universe.
And you are that one soul reincarnated throughout time, and you will eventually be re-reincarnated
as every living thing that has ever existed.
Oh, that's kind of like the theory where there's one electron that exists everywhere simultaneously.
Yeah, yeah.
That's like lording-ish.
That's lording-ish to you.
Right?
Yeah.
So I thought that was pretty neat.
So I made a Facebook group saying it was a religion, and I got a couple people to join
it, and I felt pretty smug about that.
I was like, hey, I don't even believe in this dude.
My religion was totally different.
I never ended up making a Facebook group or anything because I don't touch Facebook,
but the whole idea was I was super pissed off at the fact that religions have exemptions
for everything in society.
And so I was like, if I can't beat him, join him.
I wanted to craft a religion that was specifically designed to fuck over the government and abuse
that exception constantly.
The whole basis of the faith was that everything you ever did, everything you ever made was
for God and God alone, and no one else had the right to take it from you until you offered
it to God upon your death.
So you were exempt from taxes, you were exempt from all this crazy shit, and the whole doctrine
was just how to dodge every legal obligation you had in life in the name of God.
They're just like a book of legislation.
What was the name?
I never got so far to give it a name.
You should call it fuck the government.
Yeah, yeah.
I feel it's a little on the nose.
Might make it easier to detect the gimmick.
What about tax exemptionism?
That's pretty good, you know?
Exemptionism.
It's such a, it's such a, I think I want a neck-bearing concept.
If you'll accept it, Tom, let's call it exemptionism and make that the official, like, let's apply
that to the PCP.
Exemptionism sounds almost like it could be a real rule.
It does.
I'll accept that as the official religion of the PCP.
Excellent.
All right.
The fucking hashtag, yeah.
The Church of Exemptionism.
Here we are.
Start that up right now.
Fucking hashtag that shit.
Just so you know, the PCP is the official keepers of the religion.
We are the popes.
We speak to God directly.
Yeah, yeah.
We are the popes.
I dub all my high priests of exemptionism.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you, Tom.
We're ideologically opposed to paying any of the fees associated with Patreon, Kickstarter,
YouTube, everything.
It's all because everything we make is for God, and we shouldn't have any false idols.
And to give away any of the fruits of our labor to anyone other than God.
And since we are our own temples for God, by giving it to ourselves until we meet our
maker and give everything we've created to them.
Indeed.
In the meantime, we have to hold on to everything.
Which, incidentally, functions.
We are heavily inspired by the ancient pharaohs where we need to be buried in giant tombs
with all our possessions.
Exactly.
So please, government, do not take them.
This is part of the pyramid, is our symbol, and the dollar is our also symbol.
Yes.
I've just created a new religion just now called Grind Jealousism.
Grind Jealousism.
And the longer, like, say you have a scooter or a skateboard, for as long as you grind,
that time is equal to the time you have in the afterlife.
So you shouldn't have to grind as much as possible.
I'm gonna fire up Tony Hawk right now.
Exactly.
So the real devout members will fucking grind day in, day out.
So they just accumulate the afterlife points.
Dude, here's what I'm gonna be doing.
It certainly does sound like a grind.
Wait, but that's such a raw deal, because you have to spend all that time.
You're wasting that same amount of time grinding now.
Well, unfortunately for you, Ben, it's just true.
So you better get it.
Yeah.
So, yeah.
Bummer, dude.
Yeah, exactly.
I say, with my new, my new skater lingo.
He says to please the god.
Tabbing over to Amazon.com.
Yeah, tabbing over to buy the hot new skateboard.
Yes, exactly.
With PCP branding on it, of course.
Of course.
Dude, we should literally get a PCP brand skateboard and sell that on some place.
We should do that.
And what was it?
Grindology?
I forget what it was.
Grind jealousism.
Excellent.
Well, we've got two new religions for you to choose from.
They're both 100% accurate and represent reality completely fully.
So they now have a religious war in the PCP.
And remember, don't limit yourself to just one box.
So do them both.
Yes, please.
You can patron us twice with two accounts.
So please do so.
You're always free to have a personal relationship with God, however you see fit to divide that out.
And remember, guys, if you want something, you'll get it.
No matter what.
That's the secret.
Indeed.
So the church of grind jealousism and the church of exemptionism.
Both.
All right.
Now, and exceptionism, whatever you just said it fucking was.
When we say that you're not allowed to give anything to anyone else, that's forcing.
You're allowed to give freely.
So go to patreon.com slash procrastinators.
Exactly.
And give to the donation box of the high priests.
And you'll be rewarded greatly.
It's the only way to make sure your money goes to the cause worth of it.
In the afterlife, yes.
Unless bonus episodes are of your jam.
In those cases.
You know what?
We should make an exemption.
Like obviously you want all your goods in the exemptionism to like be with you when
you die.
But there is a clause where if you funnel it up the pyramid towards the top of the exemptionism
church, that's acceptable as well.
So you set it straight to us via patreon.
Exactly.
You're still gold.
Hashtag PC pyramid scheme.
Exactly.
All right, guys.
I think we've done it.
This is excellent.
I think we've solved religion.
This is finally like the end stone to end all religion discussion.
There is literally nothing that can be argued here.
This is the end of the discussion.
It was over before it even fucking started.
So we're finally at the moment I see another person even mention God's name in vain.
I will obliterate them as we've proven that that is antithetical to all sense of morality
or ethical.
We can all finally stop.
We're all finally free.
We should have our system.
And this tired charade.
Yeah.
Fantastic.
Well, let's shift on over to those questions, Familia.
Actually, please give the Twitter pity question, the one Twitter pity question here.
All right, everybody.
Let's check out what we got here.
Let's pull up some hashtag ask PCP questions for our lowly non-patroning viewers out there.
Fucking disgusting.
Let's see what we got.
Okay.
Xtreme42 asks, what's your process for watching a YouTube channel?
Do you go by playlists chronologically or just watch whatever you deem interesting?
If it's in series, I like to watch my playlists.
Usually, I'll just click around.
If I find a new channel, I'll just click the recommended videos and click around until
I start to feel like I really love this whole thing.
And then usually, I'll seek out a playlist and go through it and watch all the stuff that
I haven't seen already.
Yeah, when I see a new channel, I watch the recommended videos, same thing.
But when I feel like I really like it, I go to the very first video and then watch the
whole backlog.
Same as Hippo.
I've actually been doing a really weird thing, as I think I discussed in my own time here.
I've been watching a lot of Hello!
Internet because I want to catch up on that because I've never entertained that before.
And I've been doing a really weird, awful, roundabout way where I've been slowly eating
away from either side.
I've been watching the latest episode and then one of the first episodes and I've been
going back and forth like that.
And eventually, I'll reach somewhere in the middle and that will be the last episode I
watch and then I'll just move on forward from that.
I don't know how this is starting but I can't stop it and it's fucking awful.
So that's the way you don't do it.
I've been meaning forever to actually watch the Angry Video Game Nerd and I feel uncomfortable
just jumping in so I want to start from the beginning.
I know, it's just a problem to not be watching already.
I don't know, he's got sort of a narrative and a crafted show.
So for a show like that, I want to start from the beginning.
There's no narrative between episodes.
There's just kind of memes and stuff.
It's kind of like if you jumped into the PCP at this episode and we're talking about
Mirkabuz and Christ Consciousness, you wouldn't know the buildup that makes those so funny
and why we're all laughing our ass off.
And there's a few things like LJN.
He doesn't explain that every single time.
You just have to know the mythos at some point.
So it's like best watched from the start if you want the optimal experience.
So that's my plan.
It would be very interesting just to see how badly that is aged.
Because it's so long ago.
I've watched all of them quite recently and some of the earlier ones, they've never been that good.
But there's like 10 or so episodes and they start becoming classics.
Okay, that's good.
The first one I watch is The Power Glove and that will always be close in my heart.
I remember, this will show my fucking age here.
I remember in 5th grade finding the Angry Video Game Nerd.
And then on my way home from school, talking to my friend and we both watched it.
And in 5th grade, I was like, you know, all he does is swear a whole bunch.
I don't know if this is really the highbrow constant I'm making for.
In 5th grade.
I started watching.
At some point I was so bored.
I watched the entire series of Angry Video Game Nerd as a playlist.
And at the end I was like, man, I'm glad I didn't have anything better to be doing.
Sick.
What a shame.
I was just going to say that that's a show that I would watch in direct order.
But there's tons of other stuff.
I just watch with whatever seems interesting or whatever.
Yeah, I don't know.
On YouTube, I don't watch a lot of stuff that needs to be seen in order.
We can't spend any more time on this.
This is the pity question.
He's right.
From the Patreon Discord, from SuperFish, favorite national slash state slash providential flag,
I would say my two good flags are either the original Union Jack, the Imperial Japanese flag, or...
That's it.
Bye.
Easy answer, Maryland.
Or Brazil, yeah.
Maryland's flag looks like something that a sick knight would wear while he's like fucking blasting you off your horse with a lance.
I'm googling this right?
Yeah, that black thing that looks like a taxicab combined with a knight.
With a Templar.
Yeah, exactly. It's awesome.
It's played out, but I really like the national flag of Nepal because it defies conventions.
Because it's not a rectangle. It's like two tiny triangles.
I hate that flag.
And I also hate North Korea has a long flag. It's not as tall as a normal flag.
Well, when Nepal does it, I think it's cool, but when North Korea does it, they're just trying too hard.
I agree.
I gotta go with my boy, the rebel flag, because hashtag heritage not hate.
Wait, what rebel flag?
The Confederate flag, of course.
Star Wars.
I'm actually joking.
What's that one, the yellow one with the snake on it that says don't tread on it?
Oh, that's fucking the Bunker Hill, boy!
The Glaston flag.
Is that what that's right?
I don't know if that's how you pronounce it. It's called, like, yeah, the Glaston flag, I think.
The Glaston flag. I know how to spell.
It's don't tread on me. And our dad has a flag like that.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, yeah, he flies it sometimes, like in the front yard.
He talks about, like, how it's like Bunker Hill, because, you know, we live in Massachusetts
and we're like, you know, we know about Massachusetts history in shit.
Okay, yeah, it's an American Revolution thing.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I like the Welsh flag, because it's got a dragon on it.
Oh, yeah.
The Welsh flag is sick.
Hippo, I don't know if you'll even know.
What is your favorite Union Jack, the original or the current one?
The original doesn't have the extra white, does it?
No, it doesn't have the extra red going through the, like, doesn't have the extra, like, red cross.
Oh, yeah.
I don't know. I'm not as...
It also has a brighter blue flag.
Wait, what is this original Union Jack? I can't find it.
The Union Jack is a combination of flags, and there was a time when not all of the flags were in it.
Oh, it's missing the, like, red bars and the diagonals.
It looks way better with them.
Uh, no.
Uh-oh.
Alright.
It looks great.
Okay.
Union Jack is super exciting.
I guess.
I just like the English flag.
It's just cool.
Dude, remember when Gurren Lagann was going to be on the Union Jack? I remember.
I remember.
What?
That was pretty cool.
What the fuck are you talking about?
There was a time when, like, Britain or something said, like, hey guys, we're looking for, like, cool suggestions for, like, a new flag or whatever.
Yeah, I think it was, like, a meme or something.
It was, like, for something.
And, like, the one that literally won was just the Union Jack with the Diger and Don symbol.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It was sick.
Because it's the most aesthetic logo of all fucking times.
I can see the Canadian flag here with it instead of the maple leaf.
That's pretty sweet.
Fucking leaves.
Oh, yeah.
Fucking maple niggers.
Uh, yeah.
Truck it.
Fucking tree slurpers.
Embarrassing.
Tree slurpers?
By the way, hashtag California state flag, best state flag.
I do like the bear.
The most powerful flag of all time.
The most representative one of our current struggle.
That's the Antifa flag.
Okay.
Oh, he's not wrong.
He's not wrong.
Black.
Like, my here is an Isis.
That's the good one.
Um.
That's a good one.
My favorite, my absolute favorite flag is the tag football flags.
Because I always put way too hard and ripped the fucking belt off of the people and push
them to the ground, even though it was non-tackle football.
And I would get sent to the principal office, but I didn't care because I almost fucking
killed someone because I was so much bigger than they were.
You know what I don't like about the Antifa flag?
Is that it looks like a flag for like a local like sports federation.
It looks like a flag that like the, like the lower, like the southern New Jersey district
sporting commission would be putting on like a charity ball.
Well, considering these are all like rich spoiled people just playing at revolutionary,
I feel it's fitting.
Well, that's all nice and all with your fucking beta cuck loser Antifa flag.
But check out this MGTOW real fucking nigger blue lives matter flag.
What?
The most aesthetic fucking fucking entire fucking world.
Oh, I get it.
Oh, that's cool.
Is that it?
Yeah, it's fucking don't tell.
Ew.
No, dude, no, bro.
Why is only one bar blue?
Because it's fucking boys in blue, dude.
That is actually the worst thing.
It's so unbalanced.
No, I'm getting dizzy.
I'm like getting dizzy looking at it.
It's like a lightsaber.
That was probably the inspiration.
They didn't like the representation of Luke in the new movie.
So they were like, yeah, fuck this.
His lightsaber is going on the flag.
Oh, blue, like police.
Oh, I get it.
Like police, like police.
I like the gay flag or like the LGBT flag with the brown and black because, you know,
we got it.
We got to rep, rep, rep our racial brethren, you know, our oppressed brethren.
Wait, there's brown and black for black people?
Yeah, they added that like a couple of years ago.
Like there was like a meeting where like they added, I know it has nothing to do with it.
That's so terrible.
That's like so stupid.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
Welcome to current year.
Way to be a Nazi, Ben.
Way to be a fucking fascist hater.
What the fuck?
Yeah, that's right.
Right?
That's awful.
Let me see.
It's so confused.
Right, right here.
Yeah, that's the one.
That's the one.
Why?
Oh, that looks so bad.
It looks bad.
And the meaning is just like, why?
I mean, because they're a minority.
Wait, wait, wait.
Is that actually what it means?
No, I swear to God that that was a thing that actually did happen.
Hashtag more color, more pride.
Okay, it's to represent LGBT people of color.
Well, they're LGBT.
The flag already represents them.
This was the argument that everyone was saying.
It's intersectionality just going a little bit off the rails in my opinion.
Here we go.
But the flag already represents all queer people.
I know.
They feel that minorities need more extra special representation within the LGBT community.
They have a second flag.
No.
That's absolutely crazy.
You can fly two flags.
It's so funny because it now implies that the red stripe, the orange, the yellow, the
green, the blue, and the purple are all different races of people.
Now that's racist.
No white flag.
No white stripe.
You're not allowed.
White people are.
Well, if you combine them all.
So the red one's the Native Americans.
The yellow one is the Asians, right?
And then they also represent orcs.
That's the green one.
We need to get rid of that blue one because hashtag blue lives don't matter.
I'm so confused because like what the black stripe is for black people and the brown is
for.
Just miscellaneous or like minority in general, I guess.
Indian people or something.
I don't know.
It's so confused.
Look, I get the point.
I would have just added the black.
Like even if I thought this was a good idea, like I would have just added the black.
I actually don't hate this as much as a lot of people do, but I would just argue that
like it doesn't doesn't actually help what they're trying to do.
Like I don't have a problem.
Okay.
All right.
There you go.
I'm not like, I don't know.
Yeah.
This is with the asexual flag.
That was one of the most asexual.
That was one of the most aesthetically pleasing, you know, LGBTQ specific flags.
Shout to the asexual flag.
My boys, I love your, I love your, your platform and I support you to the end of my fucking
life.
Look at this.
Look, look at these stripes for the asexual flag.
It's sick.
It's not bad.
It's fucking dope.
It's good.
Not bad.
My brothers, we're going our own way.
What's that?
There was actually a migtail flag.
Of course.
As seen on Nate's shirt in our retrieval.
Yes.
I'm looking for it.
This is all right.
This could be less manly than being artsy and making something.
This is the symbol, but it's on.
Put it on a flag and there you go.
You got yourself a flag.
Okay.
Yeah.
We're going to have a rabbit hole here.
Let's proceed to our next question.
Speaking of arm retrieval.
Oh no.
Tadpo in the patreon lounge.
Who on this week's PCP hasn't supported or shared arm retrieval con three go fund me.
I am.
I did share it.
Because Homestuck is gay.
Munchy, but I am also, like I shared it right before the show and I said, okay, well, I got
to do the show.
I got all the land on the paper.
I am going to fucking, I am going to donate.
That was always, that was the plan.
Thank you.
And so should you viewers.
Yeah.
So should you go to gofundme.com slash arm retrieval con II and in between all those
words are dashes.
Please go there.
That's where I'll be.
Give us some money.
So arm retrieval con three can be a massive success.
This will be the only crowdsourcing, you know, event for any particular meetup or, you know,
convention of any sort for the foreseeable future for as long as the fucking may breathe.
This will be the only one that you will see for possibly the rest of the PCP systems.
And there you go.
Good.
I've donated.
I gave in eight bucks.
Oh, so that was not bad.
Eight, it was a lorries.
There you go.
Listen, new, new real question.
Please listen, I would give money to, to this arm retrieval illicit fun happening here.
It's just okay.
I got to think about where my money is actually going.
Do I really want to send money to the, the, the disgraceful illicit Ethan and Steve.
Is that something I can look myself in the morning and say I did a good thing today.
I'll donate on the condition that they are banned from walking through here.
Oh, perfect.
Steam, famed remover of Syldex, he's the one who went back and edited all the old panels
so they were removed from the comic.
Is that true?
Did he do that?
No.
Oh.
I was thinking.
He said he doesn't have access to MSBAInvention.com, dude.
I thought he meant for a personal archive.
Okay, well anyway, yes, everyone give money, all the money.
Yeah, please do.
Empty your wallet.
For arm retrieval, because there will be nothing else besides.
So okay, next question, what else have we got?
Let me look over here.
I have from Mecoolman in the Patreon lounge, when did you wake up today?
As of this recording, 24 hours ago, 24 hours ago is when I woke up in real life.
When you gulp woke.
Yeah, I got woke.
Okay, go back to sleep.
Is this like a matrix question?
Basically.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
When did you wake up?
Is this like asking when we got fucking redpilled, is that what we're?
Yeah, when did you take the red pill?
I told you, when I was 14 in the shower.
Yeah, yeah.
Basically.
I'll figure out when I was fucking redpilled, hold on one second.
Okay, yeah, let me go on to the question.
I found the exact date, August 10, 2011, the date Know Your Me My Little Pony was released
and thus the day I first started watching My Little Pony, that's the day when I got
woke.
All right, not bad.
August 10, 2011.
That's good, that's good.
All right, here's another question from Haid in the Patreon lounge again, favorite kind
of meat, are you team chicken, cow, fish, ham boy, or other sort of meat?
Does seafood count?
Like, like does duchel fish count?
You did say fish.
Absolutely.
Yeah, I would probably go, I think scallop might be my favorite meat of all.
Where's cock meat?
I'm gay.
We're talking about tariff, I go with beef.
Yeah.
Oh, what a New Englander, this lobster boy, how disgraceful.
Tier one cow, tier two pig, slash, selfish, what are shrimp?
Shrimp would also be beautiful.
Shrimp or shellfish?
Yeah, very.
Tier three chicken and the rest, and then tier four is all the shit that does not matter.
The answer is for sure, number one is fish.
I love fish, they got omega threes, they're killer, I fucking love fish intensely.
I think I like fish about as much as I like chicken, like fish itself.
I'm happy to admit.
Although I really like sushi and I guess you couldn't have that without fish, so.
There is the novelty factor at play in fish for me, because I never had a lot growing
up and I kind of made it seem cool in my own head, but I still love it and it's good for
you.
Yeah, it seems you just thought fish were just so cool.
Eating fish was delicious and I didn't do it enough, and it is super low fat.
We never eat fish and when we did it was like, whoa, we're having fish, whoa.
Yeah, exactly.
And it's super locale and it's got lots of great unsaturated fats.
It's super local.
I like fish is not very flavorful.
You need to put a lot of oil and stuff on it before it tastes like anything, except
prawns.
Prawns are good.
Okay, fair enough.
Or shrimp, what do you call them?
I don't know.
Yeah.
There's loads of different types of that little guy.
You're right.
Yeah, you're not wrong, but I would put chicken is like the main staple, chicken is best.
Do you guys, has anyone like eaten prawns where you have to rip the shell off by hand and
put your hands in the bowl?
Yeah, that's the worst.
I love that.
You love it?
For some reason.
I don't mind that, but I have, okay, the biggest fucking pet peeve is when you get like, you
get, I don't know, like shrimp scampi or something.
You get some like pasta dish that has shrimp in it, but the tails are still on them.
Like what the, like you have to reach into your fucking pasta and pull the, why wouldn't
the chef take it off?
He took the rest of the shell off.
What the fuck?
Exactly.
And like, all the butter and the garlic is like on the shell, now in the trash.
Like, what the fuck was the point of this?
What a waste.
No, no, no, no.
All right.
Here's the point.
Here's the point of keeping the shell on, because when you're boiling them, the flavor
of like the meat, the flesh gets diminished if it doesn't have the shell on, like the
shell cooks it somewhat.
So when you serve it, you have the shell and then you take it off and it's like the
freshest prawn of all time.
Keep them in the shell, but like they, these are not shell shrimp, well, they are shell
shrimp.
Not in pasta.
The shell is removed.
It's just the tail is on, but you can't fucking eat it.
Yeah, I don't know what that is.
Which is like, the way you're supposed to have it is...
Yeah, I get that, but I don't think that applies here.
I like shrimp cocktails.
You just eat the shrimp and you dip it in the marinara sauce or whatever it's called.
Yeah, like in that case, it's fine because you hold it by the tail and you like, you
kind of bite it out, but in like a pasta, oh my God.
I'm so fucking excited.
I'm actually a very big shrimp enthusiast.
I have not tasted shrimp until I went to Denver, where I live on a coastal city, but I had
never tried shrimp until I went to fucking Denver, Colorado, and I realized I liked it.
Are you familiar?
Hashtag fried shrimp is literally the best shrimp.
Fried shrimp tempura is delicious.
Are you familiar with the beaver boys by any chance, Munchy?
What?
Okay.
The beaver boys are an elite group of young heroes living in America and living the high
life that love two things and two things only, shrimp and white wine.
These two things comprise the entirety of their being.
Shrimp and white wine, the beaver boys, they are from Tim and Eric, and you should go check
them out as soon as we're done.
No, you mean beaver boys.
They're from several Tim and Eric episodes you should check them out.
They're excellent.
Other questions?
What else we got?
A lot of bullshit.
How about this right here?
I don't know.
Kaidera in the Patreon Lounge asks, if you could pass along any of your own skills slash
talent to someone of the PCP, what skill would that be and who would you give it to?
This is basically why I'm better than X person.
I would give Ben my financial responsibility if I could, if only I could or that.
If we give it, if we give someone the power, do we lose it or is we just clone it?
I'm going to say it's copied in this case.
You've got a one-time pass to give someone a skill you have.
Because if I have to lose it, I ain't giving anybody shit because I'm already barely getting
bought out of this.
Let's say it's collapsing, I need another handicap.
Well, Nate, I would give you my caring about my brother's feelings.
My body would reject it like a bad friend's feeling without a doubt, without a fucking
doubt.
Indeed.
I would give Digi my crippling aids.
I would give Hippo my lung capacity.
Oh, that's a good one.
That would be good.
I would love that.
Imagine give puffing up like a puffer fish and you know, preparing to unleash a torrent
of, I would give, I would give Munchy, I would give Munchy my heterosexuality.
No, no, no, get that away from me.
I would give that asexual flag as fast as you can.
I would give Hippo my 3D skills because I want to see him make animations.
I'm sick of give being 2D in real life.
It's a real disgrace.
He needs to get with the times.
It's time to, it's time to fatten up.
Time to get thick.
That's what the people want.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
I'd give Hippo my incredibly disgusting eating habits when I just engorge on junk food so
he can get some meat on his bones.
Indeed.
Though for you it just keeps you skinny for some reason, but you just got the fastest
metabolism in the world, I guess.
I just wear baggy clothes.
You don't know.
Oh, fair enough.
Fair enough.
I would give Nate my mussel-less body.
Oh, no.
It would be crippled instantly.
No.
How cruel.
How vicious.
Hey, here's a question for Gib.
I'm just curious about this.
EricBiden asks, Hippo, do you still play Fire Emblem Heroes?
What is your favorite Fire Emblem game?
This is a terrible question.
No, I was just, I was curious if you still play in this game because it was like a thing.
I had to take it off my phone because I wanted to play Pokemon Go and it kept updating and
I didn't have space.
It was all right and I might play it again, but eh.
Okay, okay.
I'm just curious about the continuity of all these kinds of mobile games because me and
Kingdom Hearts have fallen out of ways with the mobile game.
I just can't keep up with the fucking missions that are shit.
It's not fun.
Eh, what's your favorite Fire Emblem that you're a hero?
Oh, eh, fucking Fire Emblem 7 or 8.
It depends on my mood, but either of those games are the best game I've ever made.
Hippo is a capricious creature.
Indeed.
I see a pretty good question here.
Let's make it the last one because I feel like we're wrapping up here.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm just going to ask, this question is based on the assumption that there was a point in
life when you were a wee lad when you weren't actively pursuing art.
How has your view of art and artists changed since actively pursuing it as a career?
And my answer for that is just that I don't respect them as much.
Reasonable.
I don't think, because I'm kind of doing the same thing and now I don't think what
they do is special anymore.
That makes sense.
I don't know whether I'm, like I can't remember a time where I wasn't thinking about doing
art because I was always like, people praise my drawings when I was a little kid.
So I don't really know whether I was ever thinking about doing something else.
But I also at the same time feel more connected to them and almost like they're my friends.
We have commonality.
Sometimes I think about Andrew Hussie just grinding out pages of Homestuck for days on
end and I just think like, yeah man, I feel you.
Sometimes I think about Andrew Hussie losing all the money from his Kickstarter and sitting
around for a fucking year not updating.
Sometimes I think about Andrew Hussie dating some fan artist and then when she breaks up
with him, she stays the PR manager of his company.
I still don't know what's on my thinking about that.
The ultimate cockledry.
Okay.
I mean, how sad, how unfortunate.
My perception of artists has not changed at all, basically, basically.
Oh, actually, actually, my perception of this band of artists, the PCP, has changed dramatically,
actually.
I now feel the same way Ben does.
I don't feel like it's that special anymore.
Yeah.
That certainly makes sense.
It's great.
It's the best.
I don't know.
Yeah.
I generally agree.
I feel myself a little more jaded in a sense like, okay, a lot of people, I've been thinking
about this lately.
I've seen a lot of people talking about, I think I watched, maybe it was like Philip
DeFranco or something.
It was something about the new changes to the monetization stuff on YouTube.
We're now like, if you have less than 1,000 subs or you haven't gotten 4,000 hours of
watch time in the last year or something, then you're not eligible for monetization.
I'm not commenting on that, but people were bringing up the point that, okay, it's really
hard to make it as an artist on YouTube, and it's obviously just getting harder.
Maybe I'll make it, but they've really been, a lot of people have been saying, you shouldn't
make this your main thing unless you're super successful.
You should keep working your job and just make this a hobby to keep it pure.
I've really been rebelling against that in my own mind, but I don't know.
I'm kind of split on the issue.
I personally am dedicated to making it happen, but if you look at something like Weagawa,
Weagawa is a reaction to my evolving understanding of how to make it in this world.
I would rather be working on bigger projects that I could, like when I started on my channel,
spending months and years preparing really big things.
I am still doing that, but they're taking longer because of this other shit.
I'm wondering, and in fact, if I am able to go full-time content creator, I might be
able to then make a Weagawa and get my bigger projects out faster because I'm getting paid
for doing art in general and don't have to go to a wage slave job.
It might work out that I make more and better art in that way, but also, it's possible
it might not work out that way.
I don't know.
I feel a little more jaded.
I feel like someone with your disposition would increase their workflow dramatically
because you're not somebody who's just going to be like, well, I don't have to go to work
anymore.
I guess I'm just going to eat Doritos and watch anime.
You know, I sort of feel that.
I sort of feel that, but go ahead and give it to them.
I think Jesse said this a long time ago on the podcast is that Mr. Plinkett, like Red
Letter Media, the Mr. Plinkett's were great when they were around, but a lot of the half
in the bags and just the silly videos with Mike and Rich just talking about something
have just as many views and are also just as funny with so much less effort put into
them.
They've realized that not everything has to be a Plinkett review and not everything
has to be like a big project that you spend a lot of time on to make it really good because
at the end of the day, the effect is the same.
At this point, you're totally right, and at this point, I have enjoyed half in the bag
possibly at this point as a collective more than I have enjoyed the Plinkett reviews.
Those are legendary.
Nothing that's ever happened on half in the bag has had anywhere near the kind of impact
on it.
Well, there are some exceptions to this.
The one video they did on Jack and Jill as a half in the bag is legendary and I think
is makes just as good a point and artistically so as was done in the Plinkett reviews.
I'm not going to say that artistically was quite on the same level as everything that
happened in Plinkett, but the point and the meaning behind it is a really good one and
very interesting and presented in a great way.
When I was doing We Agua, just because I forced myself to grind out a bunch of videos, I ended
up making stuff that was like some of them were really great.
People really liked the one where I talked about working out.
I was just scrolling on the 4chan looking for something to talk about that day and I saw
the chart about the increase in people signing up for the volleyball clubs in high school
in Japan after the release of, I forget, the manga about or the anime.
What was it?
Was it Haikyuu?
Yes, that's right.
Haikyuu, the volleyball manga shown in jump slash anime and then I just grabbed me spiraling
off thinking about all this stuff and I ended up making what I consider a really great video
about that and non-kiromote or whatever it's called.
So great things can emerge when you put yourself on the grind and it's less likely that a We
Agua will be as good as you're growing like in video, but it's not impossible, which is
the point.
It's true.
And you know what, I only slightly disagree there.
I think even the newest plinket I think is better aesthetically or artistically, it is
better than even the best half in the bag, which is the Jack and Jill one.
It's like you have to ask what the point of the art is because when you think about it,
the difference between a plinket review and half in the bag and the difference between
a We Agua and Gurren Lagan is really mostly window dressing, right?
Because it's like attracting people from the visual presentation and things like that.
But if you made a We Agua about Gurren Lagan, you would have hit on the same points.
It's just the presentation would have been very true static.
I actually challenged this.
I feel like this group in particular has been consciously moving away for not, you know,
immoral reasons for a lot of, for I think mostly for, you know, economic reasons and
shit.
Yeah, economic and just, you know, not wanting to be stagnant.
They've been moving away from long, like, like a big, big law, not long form necessarily,
but big, concise, bombastic, huge, say everything you possibly can be, it can say about a topic
in one video, highly structured and edited to a fine, mere shine, to just spewing out
shit all the time.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
Honestly, because that works, at least for me, that's what We Agua was, so that I could
keep myself engaged in YouTube and keep people coming back.
I've tried very hard to not let my videos become like that, but I still try enough.
But like, I feel like I also can't reach the heights, like I've tried, like the closest
I got was my Rayman video, which everybody loves and it's a big old thing, but I don't
even know whether that's like, on the same level, like proportionally, like in a ratio
sense, to like a plinker review to what a half in the bag is.
Like, I don't know whether I've reached like a big project yet.
Well, I don't know.
I don't know.
It's all, all I want to say, I don't think there's like, like, you know, I, I, I love
We Agua, and I watch it as soon as it comes out.
I, I, that's, I just recently on the new one, I like, I got a letter from Psy who says
that he like loves my old work, but he said he's gotten so much more out of We Agua than
he did for like the, the like, like, look, there's like five best anime ever's because
they each took six months to make more or less.
So, you know,
I, I, I will say like, sure, if we're going to look at it from like, like, like Lynn's
like, like eagle eye point of view, what series have it gotten more out of?
Sure, maybe due to the fact that it just is so much longer, I've gotten more out of
me and Maffa slash We Agua than best anime ever.
But here's the thing, I rewatch best anime ever during the gone like, pretty fucking
frequently.
I do that all the time.
And whenever I do it, I still am amazed by how well structured and fucking edited to
a mere fucking shine it is, and how incredible it is on every fucking level.
Whereas Oh, we Agua, I would never rewatch it.
I would never do that.
You know, I think it's good to put on and, you know, I can draw the background of it.
I mean, I just have the same weight to me.
You know, that's right.
That's right.
To remember is that the reason why like this pivot is happening, it's, I don't know.
Yeah, it's an economic.
It's not a creative decision.
Like if all things, if all things were equal and like Nate, you could have the exact same
impact and make the exact same amount of money, just slaving away over the next best anime
ever as opposed to doing we Agua, I'm pretty sure you would just do best anime ever.
I don't quite agree.
I think now that I've tried out we Agua, I do actually like staying sort of in constant
communication with my audience, with like regular updates.
So I think you like that because of the economics that I mean, what I like it because it keeps
people interested in me, which is part of what I need to do.
Right.
That's my practical.
There's always a practical component like we could dream that in a perfect world, like
that was what I was proposing.
I was proposing the reason this is it's an economic choice, not a creative.
It's not just economic, though, it's it's it's like if I don't make just just practically
if I put out a best anime ever every six months, people will just forget about me, regardless
of like how much money I'm making.
And I don't want that.
I want to stay active and I want to stay involved, but I'm not I'm trying to, you know, counter
your anything.
Please go on.
What's wrong with being like, what's wrong with being like a reclusive artist who just
puts out a big bomb every now and then that's not a that's not at all.
That's just not what I want to do.
That's all.
Okay.
People people succeed on that model.
Yeah.
Well, not as much anymore, not on YouTube is exactly how it's way harder to Mr. Beetong
is not succeeding on YouTube because he's not making any money.
I didn't you were talking about succeeding as I was saying, Mr. Beetong as an example,
like he's not an example of that.
But like people love Mr. Beetong.
You love Mr. Beetong so much.
He's so niche and he's he doesn't overload you with stuff that is not interesting as
interesting.
Well, what are we talking about?
Or like a good channel?
Um, I'm I don't know.
You were talking about the way you want to be perceived, like you want people to remember
you.
I want to stay a constant force in people's lives.
That's that's true.
I want them to reflect and say, Ah, yes, let's see what you say that your goals have
changed as in a response to doing me a map of a and we go as a result.
I well, let's not forget the reason I did me a map of a was because I was sick of people
saying that they're that they only hear from me like every once every six months because
that was never my intention.
I wanted to get things out faster.
I just, you know, have to work and don't have time.
I don't really care at all how much people hear from me.
I just want to leave them with a good impression and I just want to leave them.
I just want to give them something cool whenever I got it.
You know, perfectly reasonable.
That's that's what I care about.
Not not even one iota of my original statement was to disparage we wag or short form
frequent content.
That's true.
I know I want I'm I'm a little afraid that people will just only do short form stuff.
But even though that is more economic, you know, and that's the reason they're going to do it things.
You know, I would just like art to be what I like.
I totally hear what you're saying.
But for someone like me, I would ask for people to be charitable.
Anyone who makes this point.
And unfortunately, this is asking kind of a lot, but do not judge someone like me on
what I'm producing moment to moment.
I would say in a few years, look back at what I created and then say, well, look, I didn't
get the content I wanted.
Therefore, this this time period, I would consider a failure because you didn't make a single best
anime ever.
You were too busy on the we Agua and I'm not, you know, it goes in the the the trashmen of history.
I think that was a perfectly reasonable thing to say.
Was that Tom?
I think it's just well, it might be a failure to you as an audience member.
Right.
Just for your personal, yeah, you know, you can make a case, which is totally fine.
Like I would argue that like the last year, for example, Twin Perfect is an interesting
example to me where those guys actually it was very interesting.
Recently, they've been doing this entire year.
They've been doing a monthly recap.
They called like the perfect monthly recap.
And at the end of every month, they would review things that happened the previous month.
The problem was by the time they were doing this recap, the entire news cycle for every
story they talked about was completely over and nobody gave a shit anymore.
So like these videos, they have like 55,000 subs or something.
They would get like 4000 views.
And then at the end of this experiment, that honestly, I kind of think is them reframing
like what they were doing.
They were like, Oh, that was just an experiment.
And the whole like this was just in addition to our actual content that we actually care
about.
We didn't want this to be popular anyway of of like our big analytical videos that they
did of like the new Alien movie, like Prometheus, something, something, the new one or whatever
and other stuff.
And those videos do indeed get like generally hundreds of thousands of views.
People give a shit about those and they weren't into their review stuff.
So like those are that's an example of guys trying something and like not not it's not
working out very well in terms of like trying to do regular content because they didn't
give the market what it needed.
They weren't snappy enough.
They weren't fast enough and they just like weren't engaged enough with the community,
even though they were trying to.
So that's the sort of thing you need to avoid if you're trying to make this kind of regular
content, I would say.
But they're they're a very interesting case, but whatever, I don't know.
Yeah, I I agree with everything said here.
I just I just want like like I was going to say, did you please make another good video?
There it is.
Please.
You didn't like you didn't like his like hour long Makoto Shinkai or whatever.
No, that was fine.
I don't like any of the other things that are constantly happening.
OK, OK.
The. Oh, God, I don't want to talk about this.
Who does who does I am?
Shout out to DigiBroni MLP.
Shout out. What would you guys consider my like greatest project that I've made?
Top 10 hippos.
Top 10 fucking hippos is the greatest video of all time.
Top 10 hippos is like probably the funniest.
I am like, oh, no.
I really love the G.R.P.J. is a lot.
Mine is there's a fish at the door.
Yeah, I really. Oh, that's true.
I forgot about those.
But yeah, yeah, your animations are really great.
Hippo, I'm just going to tell you right fucking now.
Here's the here's the munchy, munchy opinion.
Here's just here.
I want to lay it on the table.
Game reviews stop.
Stop it.
Animate, draw that stuff.
Here's here's what you're here's what you're going to do in my brain
when I fantasize about it.
Here's what I hope.
And when you don't do it, I'll be disappointed as the fear of mind.
Munchy predicts.
Yeah, exactly.
You should become the literally new control of the lead and just make
what are like weekly comics, not about video games, just like short comics.
Just turn all of your puns on Twitter into short comics.
You would be a billionaire.
It would be great.
I want to see you draw these.
Your drawings are good and it would be funny and games.
Fuck video games.
Done.
There's no more you can do.
Reviews are dead.
Analogical content is over by by by wiped off the map.
Do new things, create actual art, real art that isn't fake, like analysis.
Interesting idea.
That's me.
You're a butthole hippo.
Oh, no, don't worry.
I don't know.
OK.
I like the Bugs Life review.
I like all of the videos.
I just don't want them to be made.
Don't backpile now.
Well, now that we've slayed Gibb, that was a thorough examination of that last
question, but it was good.
Good stuff there.
All right, well, I guess that's it, everybody.
That was our last question.
Thank you, everybody.
Go into patreon.com slash the procrastinators pledging one dollar.
And then you're in the chat in there.
You can fucking give us questions that will answer on Saturdays when we fucking
record, so watch out on Saturdays if you're in their fucking place.
And five dollars or more.
Get access to all our bonus episodes.
There will be a new one coming out when this comes out in about a week.
I think something around there.
Delicious.
That one, that one is fucking scrumptious.
You better.
It's the best.
It's I think it's my favorite one.
It's it's incredible.
It is the Alpha and Omega bonus episodes.
Could it be our best work?
I think it's probably could it could it be the PCP's first masterpiece?
It's the new PCP's and you PCP's masterpieces for sure.
Yes, for sure.
It's incredible.
It's signed the fuck up.
And be on that PCP.
It's it's the act six masterpiece.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's no doubt.
And other than that, it's all a bunch of bullshit.
Give us all your money and thank you.
We got some some merch.
Redbubble link in the description.
Hashtag ask PCP for the pity questions.
If you don't want to give us any money, we might read one or two if we fucking feel
if we don't come down from our pedestal on Mount Olympus, we might read one or two.
What else we got?
We got the podcast is up on iTunes and Google Play courtesy of Mr.
Tom Oliver.
Thank you as always for that.
And I think that's everything.
I think we've done it once again, everybody.
Thank you for listening.
Damn, we came.
We saw we said religion forever.
We answered the questions and we made it.
I think I think the point.
The point of this episode is that we're the only gods you need.
That's exactly right.
The only God is man and I am a real man.
Just think of just think about what you've done for the past two hours
and think about how much happiness we've given you.
This is proof that short form
content frequently is the best form of content.
I think no, much more importantly, this was twice as long as church
and like ten times entertaining.
This is heaven here on.
Oh, this is a city.
Do do do the shining scene is PCPHQ.
That's where all we're all.
Yeah.
That's right.
Patreon.com slash the procrastinators.
Make it real.
Donate to your church and God's.
What was it?
The church of equal the church's equal pay.
I think is what we sell because the wage gap, I believe, is what we sell.
Exemption is exemptionism, exemptionism and grind.
Jealousism, grind.
Jealousism.
All right, sign up, everybody.
Thanks for listening, everybody.
And we will see you next time.
Bye.
I am a stupid I've got a deadline don't want to do it.