It's extra credits, right?
It's that song, it's the beginning of extra credits.
This is The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Wasn't that just like a Mario song?
Oh yeah.
Wait, it's a remix.
It's a...
When I was...
Yeah, I was thinking of, hmm, how does some other show start?
Oh yeah, that one song.
Who are you?
I'm Ben Saint.
The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
The show has begun.
I'm Digi and we have special guest, Gamer's Tavern with us.
Gamer's Tavern.
Say what you like about pedophiles.
At least they drive slowly through school zones.
Oh my god.
Oh, that's fucking hilarious.
That's a good one.
Yeah, that's great.
The first time I ever experienced being...
I think I've heard you say that.
I think...
I was in this...
I was writing home...
This guy, a senior at my school who could drive.
When I was a junior, I think, lived in my neighborhood.
It was like, yo, I'll drive you home, dog.
And I was like, sick.
And he fucking...
When you say a senior, do you mean a senior citizen?
No, a student.
A student at my school who was a senior
and showed off how cool he was and had a car
but could not...
Like, obviously too nervous to talk to any girls
except for this one who was secretly a girl
all along a sleeper agent.
But he wouldn't have known that at the time.
So he was driving me home,
listening to Kobe to Cambria,
trying to drive fast through a fucking school zone
and gets pulled over.
And we had to sit there for like half an hour.
And that's when I learned that when you get pulled over,
it takes fucking forever.
Getting all your shit run up.
I've experienced it many times myself
from speeding in the highway.
I think they make you wait on purpose.
I think so too.
I think they deliberately take their time to fuck with you.
I always drive like a couple of miles below the speed limit
because I'm terrified of being pulled over.
Well, you will never get pulled over then.
So you won't have to waste half an hour
and owe the government a bunch of money like I do.
You can get pulled over for driving too slow.
Well, two miles under is not too slow.
Two miles under is not too slow.
They'll think...
Just like five miles over is not too fast.
That's true.
I'm a leadfoot.
I am prone to creeping up
in the speed to be...
Honestly, it's probably a good thing that I don't drive
because I'm not very good at it.
I've gotten really good at driving,
but the better you get at driving,
the more insane your driving feels under observation.
As you get more comfortable with it,
so then you start to be like,
oh, well, I know I can do this.
Then you're like, Jesus Christ, did I just do that?
I'm not very good at it either, but I do it.
That sounds like hubris.
My mom drives like a psycho.
She's never been in an accident.
She's been driving for like 45 years,
and whenever I'm riding with her,
I'm just like, I mean, it feels wrong,
but it looks like a movie.
It looks like baby driver or something, you know?
My dad is a pretty good driver.
He does a thing.
He is pretty annoying because he really likes cars.
He's into them.
So he will flip the clutch
and rotate the shaft
and open all flaps and drag fins
and put the pedal to the metal
and go like...
And it's uncomfortable,
and everyone else in the car is uncomfortable.
Why is this happening?
And my dad is just smugly satisfied.
I have a car that can do this.
It sucks.
You can only drive that fast
if you know what you're doing
and you're really good at it.
That's why I drive kind of slow.
He can parallel park like nobody I've ever been.
I'm assuming this is not the van
that was later purchased by Nate for a dollar.
No, not so much.
That Nate still to this day drives
and has no air conditioning,
no music.
It's funny.
I forget.
The old gold Honda Odyssey.
It's a minivan.
That brings back so many memories.
That was the car of my childhood.
That was the car of Nate's adulthood.
What was this story about again?
Well, it's just a Nate...
My parents had this gold minivan
and like sold it to my brother
when he moved or something.
Or maybe gave it to him, I don't know.
Well, he sold it to him for a dollar.
Your dad sold it to Nate for one dollar.
That's right. He sold it for one dollar.
Bullshit.
Was it literally one dollar?
I don't know. It worked some kind of deal.
Yes, for one dollar.
Well, it's just like Nate didn't want to get it for free.
So he was like, okay, well, then give me a dollar.
So stupid.
That's what happens when you live your life
That does sound like I understand.
I just always picture it as this moment in my mind
where he hands over the dollar
and they're both looking at each other
and that like, ah, you know, like anime,
like dramatic scene, you know, like big panel,
like half page spread both of them
as the dollar goes from one hand to the other.
I learned the word for that thing in anime
where like it frees frames
and it becomes like a painting.
It's called a harmony.
I heard another word for it
that was named after like the guy who invented it,
but I don't remember what the name was.
His name is Shichiro Kobayashi.
No, it started with a U.
I don't know, whatever.
Maybe it was named after the director,
Osamu Dazaki,
because he's like the director who was known for doing it.
I don't know, I saw a tweet.
I know Osamu,
but he's not the one that did 9-11.
Oh my god.
Please, please spare me.
Brett.
Gamers Tavern, you're a fucking cad.
You're a ham.
You ever tell you that?
No, that's the first time I heard that.
Well, it's true.
Oh god, what were you talking about?
The minivan.
Digi was talking about something,
but then you went on a tangent about cars.
We pretty much did the intro
and then like just seven minutes of just it went.
And now we're in heaven.
That's what happened.
Did either of you have a topic
you wanted to bring at the top of the show today?
No.
Well, I kind of wanted to talk about something.
I don't know if you would find it interesting
or your audience would find it interesting,
but wanted to talk about how I came to know the PCP.
Okay.
Yeah, please.
Everyone's got a different story about this.
Well, I'll be interested hearing your side
and I can present my side of it.
Sure.
So who should go first?
I'll say, I think the way that I...
Man, I always forget how I found out about you.
How I found out about you, Gamers Tavern.
Was it Jesse?
I just remembered Jesse.
Or was it someone else?
Yeah, Jesse just stumbled upon the channel
and like posted it and was just like,
this is the funniest thing I've ever seen.
And then Hippo was like,
this is also the funniest thing I've ever seen.
And then they both like contacted him
relatively soon after that, I think, right?
Gamers Tavern, you are...
I'm surprised it wasn't Hippo.
Your stuff seems like so, so much up Hippo's...
I mean, I keep calling you Hippo.
I don't know why I've fallen back to calling Gibb Hippo.
You see so much Gibb's alley.
Yeah.
I always do it too.
I think you have a similar sense of humor.
Sometimes.
Yep, so that's what happened.
I guess it was Jesse.
I think I make the mistake because
I just really loved the Hippo Crit channel.
And like, I always...
I was so insistent on trying to call her Hippo Crit
to promote the Hippo Crit channel.
But now that's dead, so there's no reason to do that anymore.
But it still lives on in my brain.
Well, I...
That's how I originally knew Hippo as Hippo.
But then I found out later that
she goes by Gibbentech, right?
That was the original name.
That was her name as a pony reviewer.
Yeah, I saw some comments on some of my stuff under that name
and it took me a while to realize it was the same person.
And those comments go real far back.
I think they go all the way back to 2013.
So I guess Hippo knew about me for quite a while or given.
I just remember the two, like Jesse and Gibbentech,
talking about your channel all the time
because they would just quote the puns and stuff.
But that's very flattering.
Yeah, it's infectious.
It's infectious.
You start thinking that way after a while.
I try to do a gamer's tavern impression sometimes,
but I'm always embarrassed because I can't do it.
It's the voice.
He's got that thick, full voice that really
draws out the most in the monotone of the joke delivery,
which makes it great.
Well, it's kind of harder to do it live
because I can't cut out any laughter like I can in the videos.
I thought you were going to say silences.
Yeah, I can't do that either.
I love that you literally are laughing at your own puns
as you record those things.
That is really great.
That's funny.
That's a lot actually.
That tends to happen when you try to do comedy.
Sometimes you have the line in your head
and you laugh at it before you say it.
Oh yeah, that's fair.
And it can be difficult sometimes to get through it.
I guess that's why stand-ups have to,
they have to thoroughly practice their set
to make sure that they are over the jokes
before they go on stage.
Do you guys hear that?
Do you keep hearing that beep sound?
A few moments later.
Okay, mystery solved.
That's going to be in the recording?
No, Eleazar, put that in the bonus.
Put this on the bonus episode.
Put it in the secret blooper reel.
Gonna have a pretty big bonus.
But keep me saying, put it in the blooper reel
so that they know that they've got a patreon.com
slash procrastinator.
That's like a bonus in your paycheck, right?
Yeah, actually.
The more we cut, the more we make.
It's one-to-one.
Who's fucking crunching?
Who is that?
Who's fucking crunching, dude?
I'm crunching a trisket right now, dude.
I'm crunching so fucking hard.
I'm masticating, dude.
I'm making a fine paste out of the breadstuffs
of this wheat snack.
I had a craving for triscuits yesterday.
It's reduced fat triscuits.
You know why? Because they taste exactly the same.
Yeah, reduced fat.
Reduced fat triscuits.
They already have like four.
They have like two grams of fat in them anyway.
So it's just down to one.
Same shit.
Remember Ben said he wanted to do that once?
Who did?
You did.
He said he wanted to crunch.
To reduce fat?
No, you wanted to open an episode by crunching.
We had a whole bonus episode that was nothing but crunching.
Oh, what a nightmare.
Were you on that one?
No, I would have probably killed myself if I had been.
It was the whole gimmick.
I think we went for like an hour and it was just,
you couldn't talk unless you had food.
It was so bad.
It sounds like a good time.
All of our episodes are like that.
All of our bonus episodes are a fucking blur.
Do you know about them?
Do you know the latest one we did?
And I'll tell you this, not to advertise it,
but because I think you would find it funny.
Our last bonus episode was a commentary track for our first episode,
where it's us like listening to the first episode
and commentating on it as we go.
And you're supposed to play it and the first PCP episode at the same time.
So you have them synced up and you can hear our live reaction to it as it goes.
I think I saw you tweet that, but I wasn't sure what you were commentating.
Maybe I did.
I saw it that it was a commentary track.
We actually have to do another one of those.
Yeah, I was just thinking like, is that the most recent one?
That felt like it was a while ago.
No, we recorded that just over a month ago.
So we just have to do another one before the end of this month.
It's just that I went across America and back in that time,
so it feels like a long time passed.
Have you talked about that on the show?
I have not really talked about it on the PCP, no.
You want to talk about your fucking cross-country trip?
Yeah, I'm editing the documentary of it right now,
and it'll probably be out probably before this.
But I'll advertise it and explain it,
because it's a very gonzo documentary.
Basically, the three people who have come to live in my house,
named Ari, Riley, and Mint,
basically we were initially all just going to do a tour similar to this one.
Crack in a gridlock.
Crack in a summit gridlock for this one.
Basically, these three people came to stay at my house temporarily
with the ambition of all of us doing a tour together.
And then after my previous relationship ended,
I basically was like, hey, you guys just stay here
and we'll do stuff together until we can do tours,
and just get a fucking...
until we can afford to get an RV or something
and go on adventures all the time.
There was already a plan for this festival
that Dick Masterson of The Dick Show was...
He wanted to do his own version of Burning Man,
which got canceled this year because of COVID,
called Burning Dick, out in the middle of the desert in a dry lake bed.
Across the lake bed from a rave, we had our own...
It was not a...
Wait, like a different rave?
Yeah, there was just a rave going on on the other side of the lake bed,
but we were...
I don't even think it ended up happening
because everything got dusted out.
When we went to this thing, it pretty much lasted a day.
And then the next day, there was so much dusted,
everybody's tents was getting destroyed,
so everybody packed it up and left.
My party had left early anyways
because we were just on a fucking manic adventure
and lots of drugs.
Our Gonzo adventure took us from Virginia
down through Arkansas, which is where Riley's from,
to stay with his grandma.
And then we went to Dallas
and hung out with a mysterious organization known as The Bucket,
which...
Whoa, okay, tell me about that.
I can't tell you much about The Bucket.
You can tell me a little bit.
All right.
Well, The Bucket is some really cool people,
really nice, really helpful,
supplied us with a lot of drugs.
And so...
Okay.
We...
They're unironically extremely cool people,
but some of the nicest drug people I've ever met in my entire life...
Are they like...
Okay, are they like...
Are they gonna have a bucket list?
Like, imagine if Robin Hood gave you drugs.
Are they a cult?
I mean, they can be, I guess.
I don't think so.
I don't know.
All right.
No, I'm gonna go with them.
I was hoping they were.
Damn, okay, fuck.
But The Bucket can be whatever you want it to be, I guess.
So they try to have plenty of fun before they kick The Bucket, right?
Exactly.
Well, they're aiming to get...
That's a good way of putting it, yeah.
They're aiming to kick The Bucket.
They're aiming for that.
Aiming to kick The Bucket in the most fun way possible.
Let's put it that way.
Right on.
So we hung around The Bucket for a couple days,
and then we got some footage of Riley walking around with a cape
being the super spreader in Dallas.
Yeah.
So we then went to California into the desert,
hung out with Dick Masterson and a bunch of guys who had a lot of guns,
and we shot a lot of guns at a mountain.
I saw you shooting guns on Twitter.
Yeah, I was guided into the guns.
That was scary.
I am afraid of weapons.
The bigger guns are so fucking heavy, I could not...
I basically fired two or three times and was like,
I can't even hold this thing anymore.
It's fucking killing my arms.
If anyone comes at you with a gun, you need to gun it.
That's true.
I've fired a gun one time.
I think I fired at a pistol range with the Boy Scouts or whatever.
I think depending on how far away the person is in most circumstances,
gunning it's probably a better response than trying to return fire.
You got a better chance of getting away.
You got to be...
It's about the spacing.
Make sure you juke.
It's about the spacing, right?
If you're within five feet, the bad guy will get you before you pull the gun.
But if you're like 15, it's like 50-50, and if 30, it's like...
If you're five feet, you got to go straight for the nads with your leg.
Just kick to the balls.
Bam.
Easy.
No thought.
Pure instinct.
Yeah, exactly.
So we shot some guns in the desert and then we pretty much were like,
all right, well that's all we came here to do really.
So then we went to Vegas for a stop.
Vegas sucks.
Riley loves Vegas because he's like,
oh, this is the last best deal of America or whatever.
That sucks so bad.
Everything's overpriced.
I mean, it's just that everything is a trap there.
Yeah, exactly.
It all starts cheap and then quickly, steeply escalates,
and it's all built around trying to trap you in that.
Vegas is cool to walk through.
Don't go any building.
That's really all we did because we basically just dropped acid
and walked around on Fremont Street,
which was, it was just like too overwhelming for me.
Is that the one with all the lights over it?
Yeah, the big sky thing.
And yeah, I got too spooked too quick.
We basically just wandered around for a couple hours
and went back to the hotel room, then did Molly,
and that cured my anxiety for like two days.
That was pretty cool.
Did I tell you about the time I did Molly?
No, you did not.
I talked about it on here, but I'll say it again.
Someone just offered it to me, and I was kind of drunk,
and I was like, yeah, sure, whatever.
Yeah, fuck it.
I don't know what this is.
Great mentality.
What ended up happening was...
No, no, it was funny.
The guy gave it to me.
I think he gave me like a half-tablet because he was like,
I was like, yeah, I've never taken Molly before,
and he was like, I'll just give you a half-tablet then.
And I was like, cool.
And one of the other guys, he made like a joke about like
how it can kill you or something,
and the guy who gave it to me got real serious with that guy.
He like scolded him.
He was like, dude, no.
Dude, do not tell a guy that.
He's getting high right now, and if you tell that,
it's gonna suck for him.
He was like real serious about like,
do not give this guy a bad time on my drugs,
which I respected.
I appreciated it.
But all that happened was I walked home,
like babbling to my friend about some shit I don't remember.
And then when I got home, I thought like,
man, people don't connect anymore.
People don't love each other enough.
Molly is a very emotionally open drug.
So I walked to my neighbor's house at like four in the morning
and started knocking on the door,
because I was like, I want to say hi.
I want to make friends with these people.
Oh yeah, that's right.
You did tell me about that.
I think I remember hearing this.
And then the next day they came over and they were like,
someone was knocking on our door.
Now that I've done the drug,
I understand how that happened.
I totally get it now.
Yeah.
It's a very...
I don't remember where you told this story,
but I have heard it.
I must have listened to some previous episode, I guess.
It was of all the bad things that could happen
when you take a drug that was pretty mild,
and I think it's funny.
Yeah, it is pretty funny.
So anyway.
So we went through Vegas,
and then from there we went to Idaho
because they had all come to my house from Twin Falls, Idaho,
from a different house they had been staying in,
and all their stuff was there.
But because we already had a lot of stuff with us for the trip,
we were not able to take that much of their stuff back,
which was pretty tragic.
But pretty much from there,
we just made a straight beam from...
We slept the night in Kansas,
stayed in Arkansas for another night,
and then went back up to Virginia.
So it was like pretty breakneck.
It was like two weeks of mostly nonstop driving
literally across the entire fucking country
in all directions.
I saw every biome of America.
It was pretty entertaining, honestly,
even just being in the car,
and just looking at how different...
That sounds fun.
The desert, very different vibe from the east coast,
very different vibe from the north part.
I won't say that it wouldn't get old
if you took the same routes over and over again,
but I do think taking different routes
for a while would be interesting.
I think people would be shocked
at how close you can probably get
to literally seeing all of America.
You say all of America,
but America is a huge place.
It's fucking unbelievably massive,
but so much of it you can see...
When you're in Nevada,
you see for fucking miles in all directions.
It's extremely open.
It's mostly fucking desert.
A long time ago, I went to Vegas,
and I didn't like it much,
but the one thing I really disliked about it
that kind of depressed me is that
whenever I would wake up in the morning
and looked out of the window of my hotel,
all I see around me is desert.
You can see where the city ends
and the desert begins,
and you're basically in a city
in the middle of a giant desert.
It kind of felt bleak.
I had the best Korean barbecue
of my life in Vegas,
so it's got that going for it.
Wish I had gone to Korean barbecue.
We went to a place called the Heart Attack Grill,
where they have...
They will give you up to a 10-patty,
giant fucking burger
that's literally designed to kill you.
There have been two deaths at this restaurant,
and if you are over 350 pounds,
they will give you your food for free.
You have to get up on a big scale
in front of everybody and be weighed.
What I did not understand about this place,
from the outside, it's like,
big food, Heart Attack, whatever.
When you get inside,
first of all, all the waitresses are dressed as nurses.
Everything is themed around a hospital,
and it's all shame play.
If you finish your food,
then they spank you in front of everyone,
like with a paddle.
The whole place is some weird fetish thing.
It was bizarre.
Based.
I was not into it.
I was like, okay.
It was fun to experience for one time,
but I was like...
If they advertise that they want you to die,
and you die, can't you sue them?
No, you literally are signing your life away.
They did not make a sign of waiver,
but I think it says on the door,
if you step into this restaurant,
you understand that...
I don't know how legally binding it is.
I don't want people to die in my name,
and then sue me after they're dead.
There literally have been multiple deaths.
I would assume the family could sue
after somebody dies there.
Remember Dick's last resort?
Do you eat there with us at Christmas the other day?
A couple years ago?
Yeah, the dirty dicks.
The place where they insult you?
Yeah, they make fun of you the whole time.
That place is comparably more innocent
in vibe compared to this one.
I was not impressed.
They didn't hurt my feelings even a little bit,
to be perfectly honest.
They took it easy on me.
That reminds me of, I think,
a sketch that I think the widest kids did.
I think it was them.
It was a restaurant, and they would insult you.
It was a real restaurant.
I actually didn't know that was a real restaurant.
I thought that was just a skit.
It's called Dick's Last Resort.
I think it's a chain, but the one that I know
is at Faniel Hall in Boston.
Oh, I haven't seen the skit, though.
I love the widest kids you know.
I used to like the widest kids you know.
I don't know if I would still like them.
I'm a pretty big fan of them myself.
I'm sure.
Do they still exist?
Do they still do stuff?
Yeah.
I know they did something or other recently.
I don't know what it is.
They still exist, but I don't think they do the skits anymore.
No, they don't do that show.
A big part of why I campaigned so hard
for this show to be called the PCP
was because of the gallon of PCP sketch
from the widest kids.
Yeah, I remember that sketch.
It's one of my favorites.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I forgot about that.
Go on.
Go on, please.
No, you.
No, no, no, by all means you insist.
I insist.
Oh, but no, no, I'm not sipping.
I wasn't done sipping my red stripe
at, you know, I'm not done.
Well, I'm not done with my summit gridlock.
You know, it's funny.
I think most people would be surprised to know that I'm a big
fan of edgy humor, you know, widest kids, you know, and stuff
like that.
Yeah, I would be shocked to find out that you
opened the open the show with a pedophile.
Yeah.
Um, I think I like to.
Sorry, I went to the stream, the election stream that
Ben did.
That's right.
You were in there and towards the election night.
It was around towards the end, I think.
And you mentioned something strange, at least strange to me.
I told, yes.
I told I told an anecdote.
Hey, you told me somebody told you that the PCP ruined the
gamers tavern brand by making it more edgy.
Yeah, that's true.
Somebody somebody did tell me that.
That's not that.
I've watched the old gamers like the oldest gamers taverns
videos.
I remember them all having edgy jokes in them like you
would bounce between like these really wholesome jokes and
then these really edgy jokes sometimes like.
Yeah.
I think I think you're right.
This was not, I mean, this was not.
Yeah.
Somebody told me and the reason I remembered it because I was
I was kind of like, wait, what?
I don't know.
I didn't agree with it, but I thought it was, I thought it was
pretty wild actually.
I thought it was funny because it's like somebody came up with
a narrative in their head and running with it.
So, I mean, it's not true, but it's funny.
It's cool that it was true actually because it's more
interesting than the truth.
I would like to say that I ruined the gamers.
But I don't think I can.
I don't think I can claim that in good conscience.
Unfortunately.
Hey Ben.
It's kind of a dramatic.
Yeah.
I mean, there's not much of a brand to ruin.
I think everybody go fucking subscribe.
I immediately recognize the brown and brown of the gamers
Tavern logo.
So I would say the brand is strong.
I can't.
I will say though, at least based on your discord avatar,
I cannot actually read the text on it.
Yeah, I just, I just noticed that.
You know, I do everything myself.
So I don't have any graphic designers or artists.
So I'm not exactly very good at that kind of thing.
I'm sure we can get you a hookup because there happens
to be fuckloads of artists in this community and podcast.
So if you are interested in having new artwork,
just let us know.
I got it.
Okay.
It's pretty unfortunate.
I tried to, I tried to, I'm not logged into my YouTube.
So I tried to get to your show and I Google,
Gamers Tavern two words and there's a different channel
called Gamers Tavern.
So then I was like, oh, no, no, it's all one word.
So then I searched it with, without the space.
And then two came up.
There's the Gamers Tavern, which is a different, different show.
And then there's yours, which is Gamers Tavern show.
There's a lot of Gamers Tavern out there.
Mine is Gamers Tavern show.
Gamers Tavern show.
I came up with Gamers Tavern back in 2003.
It was a website, right?
Before it was a YouTube.
Yeah.
The website is GamersTavern.com.
And back then there was only one other person using Gamers Tavern,
but now there's like 10 or 15 or 20.
And for some reason, all the other Gamers Taverns that exist now
are way more popular than I am, even though I'm the original.
I mean, I think there's probably, it makes sense to me.
It feels natural because I think there's a pretty natural
and broad cross-section of like, you know, aging people
like my age, your age, who are like late millennials
who are reaching the age where they're starting to like craft beer.
He said he started using the name in 2003.
Oh yeah, but he said he's proliferating now.
I don't know, I just, the appeals, there's a certain brand,
there's a certain brand of nerd, right, who's like into craft beer,
and they're basically just Tycho from Penny Arcade is what I'm saying.
I was a big Penny Arcade fan back then.
That kind of name would appeal to, I think.
It appeals to me.
I inherently hear Tavern, I think.
The ironic thing is...
Yeah, exactly.
I'm saying it's an appealing aesthetic.
Like, what about just a Tavern, but for gamers?
Yeah, it was an aesthetic choice, but ironically, I don't drink.
Is that true?
Yeah.
You're the only one not drinking right now, I think, on the show, right?
Ben?
Well, I'm drinking, I'm getting high on caffeine and taurine
and branch chain amino acids.
I was hoping you were drinking, because I was thinking that if we were both...
No, not right now.
If we were both day drinking and being incessantly catty,
this show would just be the new Kathy Lee and Hoda.
Have you ever watched Kathy Lee and Hoda on the Today Show?
Are you familiar with this?
No.
God, no.
I don't know why.
I feel like I'm the only person in my entire generation
or something who's actually seen this show.
Maybe I'm just...
Well...
I mean, I know of the Today Show.
There's like an hour of every morning.
I mean, they don't do it anymore, I think.
But it was Kathy Lee, Gifford, and Hoda Catby.
These two ladies in their late 40s.
Hoda Catby?
Catby.
And they would just sit in chairs and get drunk
and talk over each other for an hour.
And sometimes it would just like...
If I passed out on the couch, I'd wake up and this show would be on.
Oh, God, she looks like a bronze Nancy Pelosi.
Sounds like top quality entertainment.
I enjoyed it.
I mean, it's definitely a show that most of the people
who I've ever known would not watch, but I enjoyed it.
Is this a new discovery?
No, I used to...
The show's not even on anymore.
It's just like I would wake up in the middle of the day
and be like, oh, Kathy Lee and Hoda.
It's like having a couple funny aunts who just...
A couple of funny wine aunts just babbling about nothing.
The show would be literally incoherent sometimes.
The level of just talking over each other and being drunk
couldn't even tell what the fuck they were saying.
And I was just like, this is better than regular television for me.
I don't particularly care to hear what anybody is saying.
This is much funnier.
You should have started a YouTube channel analyzing Kathy Lee and Hoda.
That's a good idea.
I don't think anybody on YouTube has ever seen it.
You should have started with that.
I've never brought this show up to anyone I've known
and them have any idea what I'm talking about,
even though it's like a show that I assume is watched by millions of people every day.
It's part of the today's show.
That doesn't sound like a TV show.
It sounds more like something you'd see on YouTube.
It was basically a podcast.
They literally just sat in elevated chairs at a bar table,
a little round table with drinks at 10 in the morning
and just obviously already have been drinking before the show
and continue drinking through the show,
sometimes getting just utterly plastered
and just having guests on who are like, I don't know,
celebrities from whatever show,
they just flirt with them and then fucking talk over them.
That's it.
It's a bit early to start drinking.
That's what's so great about it.
It's 4.18 right now, almost 4.20.
It doesn't seem early for me to be drinking,
but I only woke up like three hours ago,
so it is early for me to be drinking.
I am not drinking now,
but I have been drinking a lot more lately during COVID times.
I've been drinking a lot of sparkling wine.
I don't know why,
but I've started my routine on a day that I decided to say fuck it
as I go down to my local spirit shop
and I buy the two cheapest bottles
of barefoot bubbly, brute cuve that I can find.
See now, this definitely sounds like something
that they would be drinking on Kathie Lee at home.
Yeah, it does, now that you mention it.
I'm drinking Red Stripe, which is not the most daytime TV.
I can't see Kathie Lee down here on Red Stripe.
Isn't it Red Stripe?
Did they have the ads with like that Jamaican guy?
The Jamaican beer.
Yeah, okay.
Jamaican me crazy, man.
And I'll just do two bottles in a day.
Two bottles in a day is enough that I'm pretty blasted
and don't remember going to sleep.
And that's what it's like.
I'm curious about this Ben,
because you are somebody who gets blackout drunk.
Sometimes.
Enough times.
More than once a year, we'll say.
Oh.
Oh yeah.
Not even close, yeah.
More than once a month?
Probably not that much though.
Okay, okay.
So like 10 times a year.
Maybe once a month.
10 to 15, all right.
5 to 10.
I've only ever been blackout drunk one time
on my 21st birthday.
And like just like having it had happened
was so terrifying to me
that I've never been willing to let it happen again.
Why?
Was it scary to wake up and be like,
I don't remember what happened?
Yeah, I get that.
Just to have realized that like my fate
was completely in the hands of the people around me
and that they were like fairly non-committal
and taking care of me.
You know what I mean?
It was like, even though it was my mom,
her friend Victor and our friend Marcus,
and like Marcus is just like,
I don't want to be the one who gets stuck
getting cried on tonight.
Victor is just like,
oh, this is annoying
and I want nothing to do with any of it.
And my mom and her friend are getting high
and they're drunk as shit and they don't care.
So you know, and Marcus is like showing me footage
on his phone of me like crying and stuff
and my mom's telling me like,
oh yeah, we were talking about like buying you a hooker and shit.
And I was like, I'm going to go like never do this again.
It's fucked up, man.
It's fucked up.
I'm like, you know, I mean, it is scary.
When I wake up, when I wake up and I'm like,
I don't remember what happened.
Yes, it's scary.
It's terrifying.
It's the nightmare.
I hate it.
Yeah.
But you know, the night before,
you know, I'm like, you know,
if I drink slowly enough,
if I drink slowly, you know,
it's not like I can,
it's not like I can feel the transition
from normal to blackout.
It feels like a smooth transition
and I feel normal at the time.
Have you had any like,
a cliff night wake-ups yet?
Cliff night wake-ups.
Yeah, like the video,
cliff night, like where he's waking up.
Oh, like when he wakes up next to that hell cat and angel
or maybe a demon wearing a human suit.
Just as outrageous as what transpires therein.
I had a night.
This was like years ago,
but I do remember I went to some party
and some guy had like,
some fucking guy in a tweed suit or whatever,
had like some whiskey that he said was like,
oh, this is like such value.
This is like, oh, everyone like try a shot of this.
Like this is like,
he's just like half a shot
because this is like a fucking billion dollar bottle
or whatever.
Like this is like a million years old,
aged in like ancient China or something.
And I don't know,
they're taking shots of that.
And I was probably like sneaking shots of it
behind his back or something.
Cause like whatever, fuck it,
it's a bottle of whiskey.
And I remember,
I remember like a,
which is like a fire in someone's backyard.
And I remember writhing around.
He's like, this is like a super rare whiskey
and you're like, well,
that means I'm going to drink as much of it
as I possibly fucking can.
Oh, I should, I should get,
I should get as much as I can then.
Yeah.
I remember, I was,
I did end up on the ground in like the woods
next to their backyard,
just like vomiting.
That was bad.
That was really bad.
That's like the worst.
That's pretty romantic.
That was probably the worst,
like the worst a night of getting drunk I ever had.
I'm trying to remember any other fucking flip.
How, how much does a bee need to drink to get a buzz?
I think, okay,
does Jerry Seinfeld drink in the B movie?
I don't know.
I never watched the B movie.
Me either.
I've only seen big Joel's B movie video
and I've never seen the B movie,
but that video is a masterpiece.
Embarrassing.
No, it's good.
It's good.
I promise.
Wait, fuck.
I forgot.
I think I was going to say something
about the previous topic.
My favorite,
my favorite B movie is B movie.
Yeah, now I remember what I was going to say.
I need another drink.
I'm going to go get another drink.
You know, it's,
I wish I had some brute cuve.
I would, I would,
if I had a bottle of brute cuve,
did you, I would,
I would pop it right now.
Because we got to celebrate
that Joe Biden is the next president
of the United States, everybody.
We exorcised, we did it.
We restored the soul of the nation.
Nobody's clapping.
What?
Why is nobody clapping?
Get hype, guys.
Well, um...
That was the longest fucking pause.
I was waiting for somebody to say something.
No, nobody's going to say anything.
But...
Nobody else is riding with Biden like me.
Yeah, I guess you're the only one.
I guess it's just me.
That's bummer.
But uh...
It's bummer.
We have to restore the soul.
We have to restore the soul of the nation.
Actually,
my favorite thing about Joe Biden
is something that Trump tweeted about him.
I think,
I don't remember what he was talking about,
but at one point,
Joe Biden wasn't making many public appearances.
And then,
Trump tweeted,
Joe Biden, more like Joe Hayden.
That is a good one.
So...
I don't remember that one.
I feel like I would remember that one, but I don't.
You know, as the pun appreciator,
I had to give him
a thumbs up on that one.
Yeah.
Hey, Gamers Tavern.
You like video games,
obviously.
Do you like fighting games?
A little bit.
I like
Smash Bros.
and
sometimes I play Street Fighter.
Okay.
And Guilty Gear.
Guilty Gear is another one I really like.
Yes.
Good.
That's the answer I needed,
because
Steam just is having a big fucking fighting game sale
for some reason.
And it just so happened,
so there's a producer
who I've been working with,
who I know from Twitter,
called
David or Effie Gyros,
who came to visit
the house last weekend
to do a lecture
on Russell Greer,
who is a guy who sues celebrities
and is
he's a fun lolcow.
It's a pretty good lecture,
but...
Sounds like a stand-up.
Indeed.
And he
was playing Guilty Gear
Xurred.
And as I was playing,
I was realizing I wanted to switch my main
from Slayer
to Melia Rage,
who had been my backup
up until this point.
Mostly out of a desire to cosplay as her.
And then,
it just so happened,
as I was facing the dilemma of
I don't know if I want to hook up my PS4
to play
Guilty Gear Xurred Sign
when I don't even own Revelator
or X2.
And then, bam,
fighting games sale on Steam.
So what did I do?
I bought all the Guilty Gears,
all the Blazblues,
Melty Blood, finally.
They're sitting on my wish list for, like,
six years
and
and fucking
the Nitro Plus fighting game
where you can play a Saiyan or Uta.
No one knows what I'm talking about anymore.
No clue.
Absolutely no clue.
Well, in 2018,
I built myself a new computer
and around that time,
I got Steam and I bought
Guilty Gear Xurred.
And I played it and beat all the
you know, beat all the scenarios and stuff.
It's pretty good.
I agree.
I was a big fan of Guilty Gear back on the PS2.
My favorite was Guilty Gear X2
or XX or whatever.
But then I didn't
keep up with the series at all until Xurred came out.
I mean, that basically is the next game
because it was just remakes of X2
but with, like, more shit.
Yeah.
Actually, the last one I played before
I stopped playing Guilty Gear for so long
was Guilty Gear
Esuka on the PS2.
Yeah, that's the weird one that people don't like.
Yeah, and it sucked.
Is that like the MOBA one?
No, it was on the PS2.
It's kind of like,
they tried to make it more like Smash Brothers
because they had, like, four players.
You can play as four players
and you can turn left and right.
It was very weird and I didn't like it
and I think everybody hated it.
Nice.
I don't know if that killed the series for a while.
It's got mixed reviews on Steam
even though it's only $2.
I didn't bother with it.
Yeah, I remember it being pretty bad.
But Xurred is pretty good.
Xurred and X2 are both fucking gods here fighting games
and the Melee of Rage storyline in Xurred
made me have some feels.
So I was like, cool.
I'm really bad at fighting games.
I'm not amazing at them,
but I'm finally getting to a level where I kind of
understand the theory behind what I'm doing.
I learned throughout my youth how to,
I know what kind of character I can play well
and how to play that type of character,
but I don't really understand what I'm doing.
I wouldn't be able to explain to somebody.
I do a lot of jumping and going in and out.
Jumping around, going back and forth, in and out.
That doesn't make any sense,
but I'm starting to understand theoretically
what button presses I'm actually doing.
I'm not good at fighting games either,
but I've been playing them for a long time
and I feel like only just now
I understand the fundamentals enough
and I'm starting to get slightly better.
Good.
I played, oh man,
I fucking loved Street Fighter 2 Turbo
on the Super Nintendo.
That was like a childhood staple.
Who was your main in Street Fighter 2?
Jeez.
I don't know.
I guess I liked...
I played Cammie.
I didn't really have a main.
I liked spamming the fist with E Honda.
I liked spamming the fire spin with M Bison.
My strategy to spam the Hadoken was real.
No, I could never do the Hadoken.
I was like, I was so bad,
I could never do the Hadoken.
That's supposed to be the easiest move to do.
Well, not for me.
I did Throws.
No, I did the Sonic Boom with Gile
because I knew how to do that one.
I guess that's slightly easier,
but it takes more time.
Yeah, so I did...
It's really embarrassing to admit, actually.
I couldn't do the Hadoken.
I did not understand how to do...
I wasn't good enough to play Ryu.
I didn't understand how to do
semi-circle moves and all that kind of shit
until I was in my late teens.
Every time I played fighting games,
I was just mystified by the directional inputs
because they were usually based on a joystick movement.
Well, I guess I was playing N64 games on a joystick,
so I don't know.
Also, it would usually say punch-kick instead of A-B
and shit like that,
and I just didn't understand
how the buttons correlated to what I was doing.
It would just always be confusing enough
that I would look at the command list
and just be like, I don't get it
until finally it's over, and I was like...
In Guilty Gear.
In Guilty Gear,
because I was in high school when I was playing Guilty Gear,
and they had the quarter-circle moves,
which I understood with that man.
But then there were some other moves that had like...
It wasn't a quarter-circle,
it was sort of like a zigzag.
And that one, which to me was like,
oh, okay, so that just means like spaz out
on those two directions and hope that it works.
That's the Z motion,
which is I think known as a dragon punch motion.
It's like when you do the dragon punch
or the shoryuken with Ryu.
The shoryuken is like,
I would consider if you can teach someone
how to perform the shoryuken,
then you can teach them how to play fighting games.
It's like just knowing exactly how to do that motion
makes you understand...
When I was playing Guilty Gear,
I literally think,
even though I'd been playing this game for like 10 years,
and I'm fairly decent at it,
I'm not sure I had ever really understood
that if you press A while standing still
versus holding forward, it does two different moves.
Each one has a different distinct purpose,
but to me, my instinct is always to be moving,
to hold the character in a direction
that is corresponding to the enemy,
not to stand still and press a button
because I happen to know that the move
will be appropriate for this moment.
Instinctively, I guide my character towards the enemy.
I don't even know if I had fully comprehended
that I was doing two different moves,
but those are the kinds of things you need to know
to play fighting games,
that I think a lot of people have to fight their instincts
to figure out.
When I was a kid,
I didn't understand how to do any of this stuff,
so what I used to do was
I would put my fingers on the D-pad
and my thumbs on the D-pad and buttons,
and I would just rotate clockwise and counterclockwise,
and the moves would just come out randomly.
Like you were massaging it with your thumbs,
like going in circles.
Yeah, basically.
Sometimes I'd win that role.
It's not the worst strategy,
so a lot of students just activate supers all day.
Because they never know what's coming.
They never know what's coming.
Yeah, nobody knows what's coming, not even I do.
Yeah, exactly.
In terms of like...
I wouldn't say I'm good at games,
but I can beat games that just require patience.
Like something like Super Meat Boy,
that is basically just like do it over and over again
until you learn it.
I'm good at that kind of thing.
And I'm good at strategy games
and turn-based stuff.
I'm pretty good at Pokemon,
and I'm pretty good at chess.
For a noob who doesn't actually know
the theory of the game or anything.
But I'm really bad at fighting games.
I'm terrible.
I can't fucking do it.
When you say shooters, you mean them?
Obviously, I'm a champion at Slime Tassen.
Well, obviously.
Obviously, everybody knows that.
That's just the thing about me.
I just got a message on Twitter from someone.
It says,
I don't know who this person is at all.
Why are they telling me this?
I guess that's what happens when...
Twitter be wildin'.
I guess that's what happens when you're pretty popular.
Their name is Adam Jensen,
which is just the name of the main character from Deus Ex.
This is what a parasocial relationship is all about.
I guess so.
Tell you about like...
Oh man, trouble at my job.
I just thought it was very strange
that they were messaging me
and not like their mom or something.
Maybe they don't have any.
Did you see the thing on Twitter?
It was a new thing going around.
The Asian girl saying that Poggers is racist.
I have not.
What is this about?
Well, it's just what it sounds like.
Is it Poggers British?
Isn't it British Slime?
You don't...
Do you not know what Poggers is?
Well, I actually do not know what Poggers is.
I guess I'm about to find out.
I have no idea what it is.
You...
Poggers.
When your wife's boyfriend lets you sleep past 8 p.m.
That's the top definition.
Wife's boyfriend.
You have five more minutes.
Me.
Poggers.
Poggers, a Twitch emote that may only be seen
if you have better TTV installed.
I thought it was maybe a reference to Pogs.
Remember Pogs?
It is a reference to Pogs.
I didn't know this.
Yeah, it's the face.
It's the face of that guy going,
Oh!
I see.
I guess it's from...
He said...
I guess he was playing Pogs or something
and he said he was the Pogchamp
and he called himself the Pogchamp.
So Poggers and Pogchamp are basically the same thing.
I see.
But anyway, he's an Asian guy
so this thread is this girl saying like
actually, non-POC people using Poggers
in moments of non-POC joy or enthusiasm
has a deep racial connotations
and is extremely racist and problematic.
And obviously, this attracts a huge amount of like
oh my god, I can't believe this is the discourse now.
I literally just thought that Poggers
was like common British slang.
No, no, it's Twitch slang.
What British phrase am I confusing this with?
Like, don't they have a word that's just like
oh, Poggers!
That's how I've been reading it the entire time.
I had no idea it was like a new meme.
I mean, it's not super new.
It's only British if you have a top hat and a monocle.
That's so fucking funny.
Anyway, the post turned out to be fucking bait.
It wasn't even real so I got fucking baited.
I got had.
Would you say you're a master baiter?
No, I was masterly baited though, which is better
by a cute Asian girl on Twitter.
And I say she's cute because she had a little cartoon avatar
and that's cute.
That's good enough for me.
And her pronouns were she, her, and she's bisexual
so that's pretty hot as well.
So I guess it was originally there was PogChamp
which is the Asian dude and he's the older emote
and then recently there's a Pepe the Frog version of his face
which is Poggers.
I think Poggers is just like the colloquial version of PogChamp.
Well, I'm just going by what nobody or me is telling me.
I'm sure there's a Pepe Poggers.
Well, when it comes to all the new internet lingo
I'm kind of a boomer in that regard.
I don't keep up with all this stuff.
When your wife's boyfriend lets you sleep at 8 p.m.
That's a pretty good joke.
It's Poggers, Poggers know you only see this fucking,
let me see this rare Pepe.
Rare Pepe.
No, I don't know.
There's a Pepe for everything.
I love that boy.
Love that boy.
He's back.
We've taken him back.
We've reclaimed him.
He's wholesome again.
Did you see the fucking shit?
Listen, I'll keep talking about fucking Twitter drama
until someone stops me.
Did you see the thing about Movie Bob and Lindsay Ellis?
No, but I might be interested.
I know Lindsay Ellis, but I don't know Movie Bob.
Gamers Tavern, Movie Bob.
Oh God, I fucking...
He's a big fat dude who talks about movies and video games.
As a movie critic, I don't think he's terrible.
Yeah, that's fine.
I used to be a big fan of The Big Picture.
There's so much more to him.
There's so much more to Movie Bob than just that.
The way he presents his whole personality
on the outside of his videos is just arrogant
and cunt-y about being a liberal and stuff.
It's that...
Yeah, he's a certain brand of smug liberal.
He is self-described.
He's salty about being bullied as a kid.
He hates the people that remind him
of the people that bullied him in high school.
He's the big part of his fucking brand.
He's very much like...
Not in these words, but he's very much like
fuck-poor people, they vote Trump or whatever.
He's that kind of lib.
He is very...
I mean, didn't DeVoo used to say
that he was thinking of doing a lecture on the lore of...
What was that fucking...
Was it The Big Picture that had the skits?
On which show?
I know who DeVoo is now, but I don't know what you're talking about.
Movie Bob skits were on his Game Overthinker show.
Yeah, Game Overthinker.
I don't know.
The Game Overthinker skits were like...
Fucking terrible.
Next level embarrassing.
Unbelievably fucking bad.
It was so bad.
And he did them for years.
There's like hundreds and hundreds of them.
And he just kept doing it.
And I remember people telling him,
like, hey, you know, I like your movie criticism,
but these fucking skits are cringe and embarrassing
and I hate them.
And he was just like, listen,
they make the...
Stop telling me, they make the show better.
I'm not going to take them, even if everyone hates them.
I'm going to keep doing them, because I like them
and I think they make the show good.
And it's like an even worse version
of a guy with a glass of stuff.
How like he'll have himself in like various costumes
that all play like different roles.
And it's like the version of him
who is like a nostalgic 90s gamer
and the version of him that is like an 80s,
like Grimdark edgy comic character.
Yeah, I think I know.
I know what you're talking about.
Yeah.
Okay, okay.
Anyway, enough.
The point is, there was something,
it was this backstory.
Peter Coffin, who I assume you guys don't know,
but Peter Coffin is a lefty YouTuber.
He's a big fucking communist.
And he's kind of, people criticize and people say
he's like too much of a class reductionist
and he's like, no, I'm not that stupid, blah, blah, blah.
So he's...
So there's tension there.
There's tension between him and so-called bread tube, right?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
And he...
Peter Coffin?
Okay.
Does he live in a coffin?
Yeah.
He lives in...
Sorry, go on.
So he...
So, and one day, he fucking snaps.
He becomes the joker.
He gets joker-fied.
He can't take it anymore.
And he's like, I'm sick and tired of these bougie libs
telling people to vote for Biden.
And he blocks all of what he perceives as bread tube, right?
He blocks Big Joel, and he blocks Jack Sane,
and he blocks Sean, and he blocks H-Bomber Guy,
and he blocks Lindsay Ellis,
and he blocks Jenny Nicholson,
and he blocks Thought Slime.
Thought Slime of all people.
Unbelievable.
So he does this, and everyone's like, hmm,
what a fucking nerd.
Everyone's like...
Like, no one's like...
Everyone's like, that's pretty dumb.
That's pretty dumb move, like, stupid.
And Lindsay Ellis makes a comment in it somewhere
about how, like, he seems to think that it's a big cabal
when actually it's just people that are friends with each other
to talk, right?
It's like...
And Bob replies.
Movie Bob replies like, hmm, I know, right?
We're all just pals.
And he posts a picture of him and Lindsay,
and they're like, he's got her arm around her,
and he's giving her thumbs up, and they're smiling.
And Lindsay replies like, dude,
this is really inappropriate and creepy.
Don't post this.
The fact that we took a picture together at a con years ago
doesn't mean we're friends.
I've soft-blocked you, like, six times,
and you haven't got the hint.
Please leave me alone.
And Bob is utterly destroyed.
It's like...
It's like the greatest...
It's like the most horrendous,
like a second-hand embarrassment moment
of the...
So far of the millennium, I would say.
Bob's reality shatters.
He, too, like Peter Coffin before him,
now must go full Joker mode
and simply watch the world burn.
There's nothing left for him.
I don't know. This was all over the place.
You guys are listening totally non-plus.
This doesn't mean anything to you,
but to me, this was Earth Shattering.
I'm glad you had a good time.
I had a great fucking time.
Fucking Movie Bob.
Fucking Movie Bob, man.
That was a huge supporter.
Also, Lindsay Ellis isn't Bread Tube. She's a fucking lib.
But that's a discussion for another day.
Mo was a huge supporter of enjoying
the suffering and misery of others.
Yeah.
I think there's a word for that.
I heard Bread Tube, then I started reading other comments
and lost track of what was being said.
It wasn't even about that.
The point was about Bob is a fucking loser who got owned.
I'm not surprised by that.
I don't think that would happen.
Bob is a loser who gets owned.
I mean, it's just like, he's a big YouTuber.
Like, he is.
As much as people find him, he's a big YouTuber.
Lindsay is a big YouTuber.
And generally, these people try to maintain
a sort of professional courtesy to each other.
So it's like, imagine what it must take
to make one of them just straight up tell the other one,
like, don't even reply to my fucking posts, weirdo.
Imagine how much it must have been building to come to that.
I mean, I really do think the stereotype
of anyone who's a guy who's way too much of an ally
is probably because they just can't make friends
or manage connections.
They have to...
It's like the overexertion
to constantly insist upon how righteous you are.
It's like, all right.
Are you assuming that everyone else isn't accepting
or feeling this way?
I don't know.
It feels like movie Bob is somebody who thinks
that almost everyone in the world is evil and out to get him.
And that's only the case because of the fact
that he treats everybody that way.
He's very...
There's a tweet of his that says,
like, oh, I think it was after Trump got elected.
He tweeted, like, don't you ever tell me that I'm wrong
to look down my nose at the rest of humanity or something.
She's a race.
It sounds like school shooter talks, bro.
It is.
For real, it is.
Saying that sort of thing is cool when it's ironic.
It would be funny if it was ironic.
But unfortunately, it's movie Bob.
You know that he can't do that.
You know, I was surprised.
I checked Lindsey's channel recently
because I haven't seen anything from her for a while.
And I was really astonished.
She has, I think, over a million subscribers now.
Did she cross a million?
I think, I'm not sure.
That's a lot of fucking subscribers.
Wait, let me...
Because I first found out...
Back when I first found out about her,
she was much, much smaller.
Well, I mean, she was the fucking nostalgia chick, right?
Yeah, that's when I first learned of her.
Ben, why don't we have a million subscribers?
You and I.
Um...
I don't...
Well, I can...
I mean, I can answer that question in several ways,
but I do find it...
I do find it interesting to see, like,
who blows up and why.
And, like...
It seems like it's always people who...
I don't know, it sounds stupid.
Talk about current things when they come out.
I was gonna say, it's always people who, like, you've been hearing about.
I don't know, it's people that you've heard about before
and you've heard about them for a long time, right?
And you've heard about them over and over again.
And then you finally get around to checking them out
and you're like, oh, yeah, okay.
They have a million...
And I don't know, I feel like it happens through a combination...
A combination of, like, successful algorithm usage,
as well as...
I mean, connections are definitely a part of it, right?
Like, Lindsay is, like, a well-connected person.
Yeah, but the thing is,
not everybody who's been doing it for a long time
gets that super popular because...
Obviously.
Before the Game Grumps, there used to be a ton of let's players
that were kind of slightly popular,
but many of them now are, like, nobodies.
They have...
You know, they barely have any subscribers anymore.
And...
I got?
You know, like...
I got into it.
Yeah, yeah.
I think one of the only old pre-Game Grumps let's players
that actually managed to get over a million subscribers
is Shaga Konroy.
I don't know if you're familiar with him.
I know of him.
But most of his friends who know him and work with him,
they still don't even have, like, 500,000 subscribers.
And they're, like, struggling now.
I mean...
Is it struggling to have 500,000 subscribers?
Well, some of them are as low as 200,000.
I mean, you say that, but that's a lot of subscribers.
Well, the view count matters more.
Like, I saw...
Oh, yeah.
There was one let's player.
I think his name is Josh Jepsen.
You know, way back in 2006.
He still does stuff now.
His channel has 200,000 subscribers,
but I think he only gets, like, 2,000 views per video.
Sometimes less.
It's...
Yeah, it's...
You know what it is?
It's like a centralization thing.
Like, the big people attract all the attention,
and people gravitate towards the biggest people.
And, yeah, it sucks up attention.
I'm sure that's part of it.
But it does seem a little unfair to see an old YouTuber
who's been doing it for, like, 10 years,
and they just never really...
They never blow up.
I was arguing on Twitter about this.
I think it was, like, two weeks ago.
Most people agreed with me, but a couple people didn't.
And I said that, like...
Basically, it was, like, PewDiePie.
Like, in my opinion, there's almost nothing special
about PewDiePie.
PewDiePie is proof that, like, success is basically random.
Like, yeah, he did do all the right things to succeed.
He's very good-looking.
Okay, okay, okay.
Well, okay, when I say that it's random,
it's not that I mean that, like,
he has nothing going for him but succeeded anyway, no.
He has things going for him.
They're just pretty common things
that you would think that lots of people could do.
Yeah, he's pretty good-looking, he's fairly charismatic,
and he, you know, posted the right way.
He did the things the algorithm demanded of him, right?
He did all the right things.
But so do tons of people.
Tons of other people have all those things
that have done it the right way,
but they're not PewDiePie,
and there's basically no reason for it except, like,
just complete random chance.
I think people underestimate how important it is
to just, like, have big hits and multiples of them
because your real hit videos are so much more important
than any other ones.
Like, if you have a video that gets 10 million views,
10 videos that get 1 million views, you know?
Like, but not only that,
it is more likely to continue getting views
in those other ones because, like,
there is kind of a snowballing effect with YouTube
where, like, my biggest video,
the one that has, like, 3.5 million views,
continues to this day to be my best performing video
month after month, like...
I mean, same with me in the Sonichi lecture.
Yeah, it's just the way the algorithm works.
It just says, like, people already liked this,
or people will like this.
That's kind of the trouble of the algorithm.
It just promotes what's already popular.
Right.
So I think with PewDiePie,
like, I remember distinctly
that when he was first blowing up,
I remember, like, certain thumbnails
that would continually be in my sidebar.
So it wasn't, like, every PewDiePie video blew up.
It's like, he probably had, like, 10 or so videos
during his big upswing period
that were, like, huge tentpole,
you know, tens of millions of view videos
that were, like, every subscriber he earned
was from those.
And any other video he has
is being watched by people who are already subscribed.
But, like, if the video doesn't escape your audience,
then it just isn't adding to your subscribers.
So, like, any time a channel blows up in sub-count,
it's always because they're writing off of some video
that, like, really took off,
and usually, in the modern cold environment,
if that video is not, like, at least 20 minutes long,
it's not gonna leave enough of an impression on people
to, like, subscribe, you know?
Like...
Yeah.
There's always most...
Yeah, most YouTubers will have, like,
they'll have, like, one video that does really well,
and that's, like, the start of their career,
pretty much.
More or less.
Like, I remember, I remember Jack...
Jack Saints was, um,
he did the video about how, like, Sky...
The, like...
The, like, straight-to-video Disney movie Sky High
is, like, fascist propaganda,
and that one went pretty viral,
and I think that was, like, he went from, like,
in the 10Ks to, like, 100K or something for that,
and that was, like, okay, now we're doing it.
Um, and I, you know...
Uh, you know, I got the...
The only reason anyone watches my channel at all
is because of the Sonichu lecture,
which, just for whatever reason,
cracked a million, which is, like...
Yeah.
Uh, good job.
Uh...
Yeah, you're totally right about that.
You were talking about, like, uh,
people who, like, fall off,
and, uh, have you heard of the YouTuber Danny Mullen?
Uh...
No.
Uh, so he's a pretty funny and good, uh,
like, man on the street,
like, basically him and his team
will just, like, bomb into a town
and just start messing with people
and, like, seeing what happens,
but he is a very good way of making people like him.
Like, even though he fucks with people,
he will turn it around so that he's the good guy,
or, like, just make people enjoy the experience.
It's a, it's pretty fun to watch,
but, um, he did a video about a YouTuber
who had been, like, an early influence on him,
this guy who was called, uh...
Oh, let's see here, what was it?
It's...
This reminds me of, uh, I think Kassim G,
have you heard of him?
Over...
No.
Sorry, Overboard Humor was the name of the guy who he goes
to hang out with this dude who was, like,
an early prank star on YouTube
who had, like, a millions of subs,
made a shitload of money,
spent it all, uh,
you know, fucked up his life, got into drugs,
and now he lives in a tent in the woods,
and, uh, just, like...
Jesus.
Basically goes around asking people for drugs
so he can sell the drugs,
because people are more likely to give you drugs than money.
And, uh, yeah.
So, Danny Mullen, who is currently successful,
and obviously, like, fascinated with this guy,
like, goes out to spend 24 hours with him
and, like, uh, try to, you know, help him out.
Like, he goes into it, like,
I don't know if I'm gonna hate this guy or like this guy
or, like, want to help him out by the end,
and in the end, he does kind of find him to be, like,
kind of pathetic and try to give him a little bit of help, but, uh...
Wait, how long is this video? Is it, like, a documentary?
Yeah, it's, like, 45 minutes long.
I might check that out. That sounds pretty cool.
Yeah, I think you'll like that one,
and Danny Mullen's pretty fun in general,
but that video in particular...
You know, uh, success in all walks of life
has a combination of what you do
and also luck being in the right place and right time,
and how much luck and how much skill
depends on what the market is
and what you're doing exactly.
Mm-hmm.
And I think on YouTube, uh, there's a lot of...
There's probably more luck involved than in other, uh, fields,
but it's not all luck, obviously.
Yeah.
Oh, and YouTube and I think so.
Like, in some fields, like, it's like if you...
If you put the work in, you'll eventually get something.
On the Internet, you might...
You might never get anywhere,
and it might not even be your fault.
Yeah, that's true.
But there are some fields that are almost 100%
based on your abilities.
Like, if you become a professional fighting game player,
like a professional Smash player,
then how much money you make...
Well, to a certain extent, yes.
I would argue that, like,
it's not like just anyone could become,
like, a top-level fighting game player,
no matter how much they practiced.
I think you do kind of have to just have, like,
the natural ability to be, like, a top-level player at that.
So I think, to a certain extent,
you have to be lucky for that, too.
Yeah.
But, I mean, you do have to, like, perform.
I think, um...
But what I mean is how much money you make in that field
is directly influenced by how you perform,
your performance.
There's no, like...
Sure, yeah, it's true.
Outside of your genetics, there's no luck element to that.
It's not like you can, like, win tons of tournaments,
but, like, get screwed over by the algorithm or whatever.
Yeah, exactly.
Well, the thing about it with doing creative work
is that, like, quality is irrelevant to success.
It's about what people want.
And what people want, like, they often don't know that.
Like, you can't just ask people what they want
and then give them that.
You have to create something that they will then realize
that they want.
But, like, that can be...
Like, there's a...
On one level, you have to be able to identify...
It sounds so easy.
Well, there's identifying what people want,
which I don't find to be that difficult.
Like, I think that if you just observe, like,
what people are already enjoying
and then just iterate on that in, like, a, you know, logical way,
it's not terribly difficult to come up with something people will want.
It's, do you actually want to do that?
Like...
Yeah.
Most of the time, when people are doing creative work,
it's more out of personal fulfillment
and, like, trying to bridge the gap between, like,
how can I make this fulfilling for me and the audience?
That's the difficult part.
Like, making something that just fulfills the audience,
like, I think that a lot of the most successful directors
who make, like, really big pop media,
the reason they're able to do it
is that they just sincerely want to entertain the audience.
Like, they're like, I want to make the thing
that's gonna make people go, whoa, the most!
And, like, if that's the way you feel,
then, like, you're perfect to do that kind of thing.
Whereas if you're somebody who's like,
I have to get this thing off of my chest
and everybody needs to hear it,
then it's like you're in a very difficult position.
I think if you want to be, like, mainstream successful,
you have to...
Or it probably helps a lot to be someone who just, like,
really, really enjoys, like, unironically,
like, the kind of, like, you know...
The kind of thing you're making.
I mean, everybody kind of tries to make something
that is close to what they themselves like, you know?
Yeah, I think if you love, like, you know,
really broad, kind of, like, not basic shit, I guess,
you know, like, really, like, mass appeal shit,
and you're like, oh, fuck yeah, this is cool.
Even if I've seen it a hundred times before,
but this is like a cool thing, too.
I want to make something that's like this thing
that everybody already likes because it's what I like.
I mean, that's probably pretty good.
Like, that's probably not going to hurt you.
If what appeals to you is also what appeals to the masses.
Yeah, that's a great decision.
But if what appeals to you doesn't appeal to anyone else,
then you're kind of out of luck.
Totally boned. Totally fucking boned.
That's the position I've been in, unfortunately,
is everything that I want to copy is already not popular, so...
I'm like...
Every time I think... I don't know, I can't...
I'm going to funk. I'm going to funk lately,
because I'm like, everything that I might think...
I can't even imagine, like, finding an idea interesting.
Do you know what I mean?
Yeah, I can't even imagine, like, thinking of something.
Like, say I thought and being like,
man, I should, like, make a project.
I should, like, see this idea through to fulfillment,
because it would be like, it would add something to the world,
or to culture, or people would be interested in it.
Everything that I think of, it's like,
okay, well, I thought of it. It's old.
Like, if I thought of it, everybody must know it already.
Everybody must be familiar with it.
Um, it's boring.
This is a problem of the lockdown,
making it so you're not out there talking to people,
finding out what they want from you.
I think it's true to...
I think it's true that lockdown and me not social...
I think socializing with people is a big source of, like,
is a big source of inspiration that I don't have anymore,
and it's making me depressed.
Um, and I...
I think when you're talking and you're bouncing ideas off people,
like new people, meeting people and stuff,
then you're like, you have a flow of ideas that is, like, stimulating,
and you might have a fucking...
Your fucking neurons might occasionally fire and have a brain blast
because of all the random stimulation you're providing with them.
Not so for me now.
Now, my neurons are fucking dead.
They're all fucking dead. They're asleep.
And I killed them.
They went to sleep, and then I killed them in their sleep
by drinking too much fucking barefoot bubbly...
Yeah, I was gonna say, you probably shouldn't have gotten blackout drunk so many times.
Well, it's too late. I fucking did.
But, uh, that's why, uh, a lot of sitcoms...
A lot of sitcoms, they have, like, writer's rooms,
and, uh, there's a lot of writers in there,
and they bounce ideas off of each other.
It helps you talk to other people when you're trying to come up with stuff.
Yeah, Ben, write a sitcom.
Okay.
You know, that's actually...
I kind of wish I could do that.
You would be an amazing sitcom character,
so I think you would write a good sitcom also.
I bet I could write for a sitcom pretty well.
But, like, I say that.
But imagine, imagining, like, okay, I have that idea,
and I'm like, yeah, I bet, yeah, I could probably be a sitcom writer.
But then I'm like, what if I, like, how stupid would it be
if I were to, like, what would I even do?
Like, I go, and I'm like, hmm, I know.
I'll sit down at my computer, and I'll open up fucking Microsoft Word,
and I will, like, type, like, uh, uh, you know, script,
and go down and start, like, writing,
and start, like, coming up with, like, dialogue
to just, like, hmm, what's this, what's this,
like, I can't fucking do that.
That's so cringe. That's so stupid.
I would never do such a thing.
I don't think it's that bad. That's what I do for, uh, my stuff.
That sounds horrible. I would die.
I would die of shame if I even...
Well, then just draw it as a storyboard
and then take the pictures out.
That also makes me want to die of shame.
Drawing a comic? Imagine.
No, a storyboard. Do it, like, originally.
That's just a comic. It's just the same thing.
Yeah, but, like, layout. Do it with the storyboard layout.
No, no, no. I would have to have ideas.
I would have to have ideas to that,
and having ideas is fucking embarrassing.
It's stupid. It's a stupid waste of time.
You should kill yourself if you even consider it.
I am going to kill myself right now.
Do we have anything else we want to talk about,
or should we go to voicemail?
I don't know. How long have we been going?
An hour and a half?
An hour and a half, yeah.
Okay.
Well, um, yeah, we can go to voicemail.
Gamer, Gamer Statham, do you want to listen to voicemails with us?
Or is there anything else you wanted to talk about
before we move on?
Uh, yeah, we can go to voicemails if you want.
I mean, it's, uh, your show.
That's true.
It's, it's, it's, uh, okay.
Okay, okay, let me, let me get them.
I got them here.
Uh, I will post them in the general.
Uh, we will go in order.
This first one, here we go.
This first one is called Bob misses the samurai.
Uh, let's start it in three, two, one, go.
Okay.
I'm sure this will be horribly irrelevant.
Yeah.
By the time this goes in, but I just want to say that I fucking hate
all of the conversations about circumcision.
It's super boring.
Yeah, I agree.
That's why every single episode I say it's over.
Stop asking me about it.
It's super boring to know that I might be missing out on
extra cool feelings as a bisexual man.
It's so much easier to suck circumcised dick.
It's just, it's just, it's just easier as.
Huh.
Hey man.
Don't see why or how.
As.
Maybe he looks like.
My ex has a kid and his circumcision was botched
and that fucking sucks.
Yeah.
His dick looks super weird.
I guess my point is doctors learn how to do circumcisions
and just do it to everyone.
Fuck this whole conversation.
Wait, so this guy's pro circumcision.
I think so.
He just seemed to think it was easier to suck a circumcised
dick, which I don't understand how or why that would be the case.
I don't really get it.
I was hoping he'd elaborate, but he didn't.
What is.
I don't need another Colin, buddy.
I'm a little curious.
He says it was a botched circumcision.
Now the dick looks weird.
I kind of want to know why, like what exactly is weird about it?
Well, I'm pretty, pretty against this myself.
This circumcision.
Yeah.
And I think it's, unless you have a really good reason to do it,
it's better not to do it.
People have, people have gotten frustrated with me for being
like ambivalent about it.
But sometimes you got to pick a side, Ben.
I guess I do.
All right.
Because we can't talk about circumcision anymore.
We had to draw a hard line in the same.
You're right.
I made the rules and I got to stick to them.
Okay.
This one is called on your recording and release schedule.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey.
So last episode, two episodes ago actually at this point,
there were like two, maybe three voicemails that were all like based
on like story of like running storylines and people's characters
who fucked up and weren't up to date on the lore because of how
far apart the podcast is recorded and then released between
like, like that gap to miss out.
I don't know.
Which is a weird thing.
I feel like if you release the podcast a lot sooner,
like maybe like two or three days instead of like five days after.
No.
Okay.
Yeah.
That's all right.
Oh, if you just, if you just worked harder, if you just worked your editor
harder, the problem would be solved.
So the podcast was shorter and had less parts moving parts and had fewer
things to edit it.
I don't know.
I don't understand.
It takes days.
Looks like you're getting some.
We don't pay our editor a living wage.
In a, in a, in a perfect world.
Yeah.
The podcast would come out immediately, but it's not going to.
So, you know, you're just going to have to deal with it.
Listen, I would advise, I would advise people that want to make PCP
Canon just sent, just wait until the episode comes out on Friday.
Just send your, just send your voicemail over the weekend.
I don't understand anybody who thinks that their problem with the show
will be solved through a voicemail rather than through sending us money.
Like sending us money is the only way to say you want these to come out
faster, more money.
It's the only way that's going to happen.
You have to agree with that.
If we were making enough money to release this like, remember back in
the pony days when we used to fucking get our videos out within like two
hours of the show airing, we have like a fully edited analysis video,
like two or three hours after the show aired.
Why? Because it made a lot of money.
Because it made the money.
Just put your request on the money itself, write it down on the dollars.
Yes, put the money in the hand and all your dreams will come true.
If enough patrons, if enough patrons unionize and say we will,
we demand, we demand certain things of the show.
I mean, you have power.
You just need to have solidarity.
You just need to have solidarity and wield it against us.
Okay.
The next one is called the Irish samurai.
And there it is.
And three, two, one, go.
Konnichiwa.
This is the Irish samurai.
Oh my God.
I heard from agent E.
A very, very scary, very scary, but very professional lady.
That Benos sent Osan might know something about my fallen brother,
the Kawasaki samurai.
Samurai, Samma.
I heard that he died and that it's your fault that you refused a birthday cake.
And then he killed himself.
This can't be forgiven, Benosan.
I say, if you want to make men's, you should give agent E. your brain.
Yes, I know about that.
She told me that too.
You see, the new podcast ain't out yet, but I heard she told me.
And that's what she wants from you.
She wants your brain.
I know.
I would say give her your brain.
It's the only way to make amends at this point.
You're a fucking idiot if you don't give her your brain.
I'm sorry if this is a little disjointed.
I usually write a script.
Okay, that's it.
Yeah.
No, no, no.
This time.
Good try.
I didn't understand any of that.
I mean, you know, that's just an opinion.
It's just an opinion.
But what's your case?
But what's your actual case?
You have no argument.
That's not an argument.
Not an argument.
Where are the facts and logic?
They're nowhere.
Okay.
Next one is called cross.
Wait, hold on.
Here it is.
It's called cross.
My two cents on no nut November.
Three, two, one, go.
I do know that November partially for the memes, but also because I find that it really helps
my creative motivation.
Like I did it two years ago.
And during those 30 days, my skill at drawing anatomy got noticeably better because my thought
process was like, I'm not going to jack off to porn.
So I guess I'll just draw it.
And then I drew just endless number of tits.
By the way, team mommy milkers for the win.
And then last year, a similar thing happened with my writing ability because I started
writing smut instead of reading it.
And then again, like I noticeably improved.
Plus it's just like a unique experience to have, like to see how you'd react, not masturbating
for the entire month.
And then like if you're successful, it's nice to know that you could like just not like
stop masturbating just like right now.
If you wanted to, not that like masturbating is bad at all though.
I don't know.
Hopefully that makes sense.
I'm really tired.
Sure.
I mean, okay.
I totally get that like if you don't, if you're not masturbating, you might be more productive.
That makes perfect sense to me.
What's weird about it is that like.
Why would you then, why would you draw like porn?
Why would you write porn?
Wouldn't, to me like not masturbating would just make me do like, I would do anything but
that.
Yeah, that is pretty weird.
Yeah.
I would think the same.
That would make it worse.
That would make no November worse.
It would make it way worse.
I agree.
Yeah.
I don't, that's, I'm like 80% with you, but that last 20% is fucking.
Although at the same time, the hardest part about drawing porn is that you, you know,
get too horny and have to go jack off.
So maybe if you can't, then it makes it easier.
I don't, I don't draw porn.
So I don't really know.
But like most of like the porn artists that I like follow on the internet, I, most of
them seem to say that they don't, they don't jack off to their own shit, which is like.
Self control.
Which is weird to me.
Self control, I guess.
Because it's hot.
And I, because it's stuff I think is hot.
And I'm like, man, I bet they're fucking jacking it because I sure am.
But they're like, nah, they're like, nah.
I mean, maybe you have to have that.
This is, this is just a paycheck for me.
Maybe you have to have that to be able to draw porn.
Maybe you do.
All right.
Okay.
The next one is, wait, did we just listen to this one?
I'm lost.
Okay.
This one is called fraud is real.
Three, two, one, go.
Wikipedia changed the definition of president elect.
Yeah.
They changed it.
Before it said something like, oh, the president select elect isn't selected.
If it's disputed, you know, they're not like considered the president elect, but they
changed it.
They removed that line.
Weird.
A lot of voter fraud stuff.
I mean, I don't care what we're doing.
We don't care anymore.
Can we move on to the next one?
Yeah, this guy, honestly, this guy sucks.
Boring.
This guy, this guy used to be funny, but now he just like makes these like, unironic,
like, he's like, unironic.
What's the word?
Political.
Like, yeah, like, like right wing, like political diatribe voicemails and like, it's pretty,
it's pretty tedious, honestly.
Next.
Next one is, it all comes full circle.
There.
Three, two, one, go.
I used to watch TVP that stopped because I lost interest in ponies.
I then independently discovered best guy over in Ben St.
And only after getting into the PCP did I realize that they were TVP.
Pretty wild.
That'd be like if I didn't know give and take and hypocrite were the same person.
That's happened.
That's what happened to me initially.
Yeah.
I mean, that's like talking about that.
Wait, wait, that's not, wait, sorry.
Did I miss it?
Did you say that you felt that you watched TVP?
No, he did not know that hippo and given were the same person.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Did you watch TVP?
That would be fucking crazy.
That's funny.
That's a weird comparison.
If I was going to say, I would make the comparison.
I would be like, that would be like if I was watching Game Grumps and I didn't realize that
Aaron was the, was the sequelitis guy or something.
I don't know.
It's, it's funny to use, it's funny to use like hippo for that.
I did it again.
To use Gib for that.
Cause like, I don't know.
Gib is, Gib is as small and insignificant as the rest of us.
Well, on a small side note, I didn't actually mention this last time, but the early Game
Grumps with John are huge inspiration to my channel actually.
I mean, same to this whole podcast for sure.
I liked, I liked, yeah, I liked, I liked the John episodes.
I liked the, I liked the, I liked the early Danny episodes.
I don't listen to them anymore.
I don't like John anymore.
I think John Tron is a fucking asshole.
I haven't listened to them in a while either, but I think the John episodes are still pretty good.
I actually still go back to them for inspiration.
I believe that.
I believe it.
I haven't watched, I don't know.
I like, I like try, I had a, I had a period where I binged Game Grumps for a while.
It was, I was pretty, it was a time I was pretty depressed.
Probably, probably the second most depressed I've ever been in my life.
Second only two right now.
And it was, it was a dark time.
So I think it kind of makes me like not want to revisit that.
Are you the most depressed you've ever been in your life right now, Ben?
Yeah, probably.
Yeah, probably getting there.
You don't seem, you don't seem the most depressed I've ever seen you.
Is, is, have you, have you seen, have you seen me more depressed?
Like visibly, like noticeably?
Well, I don't see you lately.
So maybe that's, maybe that's part of the problem.
I don't know what you physically look like.
I don't know, I thought every year, doesn't it make sense every year would be the most
depressing year of your life because you're older?
I don't.
It wasn't working that way for me.
My adulthood has been better than my teen years.
So for a long time, I felt like every year was getting better.
I mean, I actually, I mean, I look, I look fine.
I look, I look fantastic.
I posted a selfie on Twitter today and there's everybody, everybody loves me.
I'm lifting again.
That's pretty good.
But on the inside, I'm crying.
2020 is definitely worse in every conceivable way than 2019 for me, which is probably true
for almost everybody on planet Earth.
But I feel like I did not get it as bad as most people did.
Like for, for most of the coronavirus going on, I was feeling like, wow, I feel like this
has had less of an effect on me than almost anybody else.
Eventually the effects, you know, the, just the long-term effects of the entire world
being shit for like months started to finally take its toll.
But, you know, I'm hopeful for the future.
I feel like, I don't feel like I got, I do.
I feel similarly in that coronavirus directly affected me less than most people.
So, but it, but I feel worse in a way because I feel like I personally failed to use the
coronavirus time effectively.
I feel like I fucking fucked it up and squandered it.
I don't think there was anything you could do.
I think, I think we were all fucked.
I could, okay.
I just think I could have done a lot more with the time.
I feel like I could have, I could have gotten my shit done a lot faster and I could have
been doing other stuff.
I could have, it makes, I feel like I could have been streaming these past several months
and it probably would have been a good time to do so.
I just, nobody has any money to give you.
Like everybody's fucking broke.
The world is fucking broke.
Like we're, people aren't even working.
Well, it's not much longer.
This is going to last.
So you might still have plenty of time.
Yeah.
I guess you're right.
I guess like, you know, it's true.
I could, I could, I could try and turn it around at any time, but like, I mean, I probably
just should try to do that.
Yeah.
Well, let's listen to the next voice mail.
Move on with our own lives.
Next one is Agent E. Three, two, one, go.
Konnichiwa.
Oh no.
Benosento san.
Sorry.
It's more lore.
This is Agent E. I heard that you were contacted by my, we'll say colleagues.
Irish Samurai, yes.
The Irish Samurai.
True.
As you can no doubt tell, there are many moving pieces in this story.
There's too many, Frank.
And it is your story, Ben.
And so you must decide, are you what's protagonist or it's antagonist?
Will you do what is right?
No.
Give us your unique brain.
I will never do what is right.
We must be used force to acquire it.
Stop asking for my brain.
You play, you play Last of Us.
You may be wondering.
Don't give them the brain.
The memories of the Samurai are false?
Then who was calling for two and a half months?
Why does he seem to remember you?
And who's dead body do we have?
And to be honest, those are all fair questions.
Doesn't make any fucking sense come to think of it.
The Samurai both exist and not exist.
You got to just pull the trigger.
Oh my God.
No.
What?
But how?
The Samurai is.
Konnichiwa.
Oh.
Okay.
Yes.
The Necronomicon.
Of course.
Fuck you.
The red herring.
It was Chekov's Necronomicon has come back in full effect.
You are next.
Until next time.
Sayonara.
He said it.
He's back, everyone.
He's back.
Feels good.
Fantastic.
All right.
Next voice.
The wheels keep on turning.
The cogs of time.
Wheel of fate is turning.
Duel one.
Endlessly.
Is that guilty gear?
Yeah.
Nice.
Probably.
Next one is.
Actually guilty gear is heaven or hell.
Duel one.
Blazblue is the wheel.
Blazblue.
Okay.
I knew it was something.
It was one of those.
One of those weeb games.
Next one is called.
The end.
Three.
Two.
One.
Go.
Konnichiwa.
Samurai-sama.
Get a rustle.
On way to Benno.
At Begiru shop.
With a logo.
Look like Gochi.
Not know where go from.
Goldilocks.
You go forward.
Who are you?
You go forward and take a ride.
Steady.
Agent E told me to wait outside.
And from outside I heard everything.
And.
Well you get where this is going right?
No.
Anyway.
Look.
I don't.
We wrapping it up right here.
Phase two had grander.
Grander design.
We was going to team up.
Samurai was going to jump through realities.
Agent E would be the villain.
All of that.
But.
Cassidy.
She got more important things to be worried about riding it.
So.
We cutting it right here.
Alright.
I'm going to go kill that Irish guy.
Then I will be the only loose end.
And then I will have to die.
Like.
You ever seen Terminator 2?
What a shame.
You know what I'm talking about.
It's not a rule.
We'll miss you Mr. T.
So.
Anyway.
Look.
I've already.
I've always wanted to see this.
It's you.
Nick's.
Sayonara.
Tab.
Wait.
I fucked it up.
And I haven't got enough time to crack myself.
God damn it.
No.
The curtain closes on a grand drama.
Wait a minute.
You've seen play out.
I forgot to mention this before.
Before our very eyes.
I forgot to mention this but the last guy said he was Irish.
But he didn't have an Irish accent.
No.
The other guy.
It was the other guy.
The first guy was the Irish guy.
Yeah.
The Irish and Japanese I guess.
He had like a double accent.
It was fucked up.
That's weird.
Fuck.
It was fucked up.
Next.
Next one.
The greatest utility known to man.
Three.
Two.
One.
Go.
So you're jacking off.
Yeah.
And you come.
And you're like oh I have to clean up all this cum.
But.
So much right.
You can do.
Is you can.
If you have a foreskin you can pinch it closed and it contains the cum.
Then you can just drop it off.
The nearest.
The nearest safe deposit box.
And then rinse off your day.
The nearest jar with a rarity.
Yeah.
There you go.
It's useful.
Then you know there's utility to it.
Everyone should have one.
Die.
Even women.
Just die.
Just fucking die.
That's useful advice.
It's not.
Not if you're a fucking.
Not if you're a fucking goi.
Wait.
No.
Gois are uncircumcised.
Not if you're a fucking.
Not if you're one of God's chosen.
Yeah.
There you go.
Next.
Next one is Liam From Bad to Worse.
Three.
Two.
One.
Go.
Okay.
Keep it up.
Okay, keeps going.
Okay.
Thanks for the voicemail, Liam.
Love you.
Love you, baby.
See you later.
Bye.
I love you.
Thanks for the voicemail, Liam. Love you. Love you, baby
I would sample that and maybe in another context. It might be
I fucking dare you I dare you to do it
Next one is called how to delete bad voice call and I and a lot a lot of us could could stand
One go
Oh
Okay, thanks for your thanks for your call Jesus Christ
Next one ran. Oh wait, I got a fucking posted here. Next one is called random PCP prisoner
Oh, God, I'm one of them three two one go
Hey, just have a simple question of any of you ever write a book called the intergame of tennis
It's about how to approve of things and it's pretty good cause you touched on some of the ideas
I highly recommend it if you have read it, and if you have what are your takes after reading it?
I literally got better at everything I did and it's literally great
I'm a missionary in Africa building churches instead of giving you food
Die anyway. Oh God, I just I'm the one leaving the city voice mouth now
So my only choice is to wrap a sheet around my neck with Jeffrey Epstein myself looking lean forward at produce 500 pounds of pressure
Just by leaning forward really fast and ending my life. So I'm gonna do that now
That's the that's that's the trick. Um, I feel like there's two types of PCP voice mailers
There's like the the ones who like do like the three types
There's the ones who do a character the ones who sound like they're drunk and the ones who sound like munchie
Was which one was that was a munchie one just like the non
They're trying to cram everything into one complete sentence 136 second burst of words and energy
She she she she she really tries to keep hers concise and it's and I appreciate it as well
I mean the munchie like ones are the best ones because they talk fast
You know what that value that thanks for valuing. Thanks for valuing our time
But I have not read the inner art of tennis. Is that what it was called?
But I'm glad that it made you have a rather other
African missionary thanks. Thanks for valuing our time, but we don't value your time
No, good get fucked
Next one is called imagine being gay three two one go
Those sweet heads still crying cause the dead left
Baby come back
You can
I
Baby come back
Imagines just imagine being gay that gay. I can't do it. I can't either next one
Next one is called yet another voicemail about four of skin. God
Have to play it. I do three. I have to at least hear them out three two one go
The upsides are negligible the downsides are negligible. It's not really doesn't matter
I don't understand like so many people have such strong feelings about this. Okay. Yes. I agree
Wait, what do you mean? It's not now for me the downsides are negligible if they fuck it up
I probably want to get my kids circumcised. Oh
Yeah, if they bought this procedure and like it's just a weird cultural thing that owned by states in like a handful of
That being said, okay, yeah, yeah, we've been over no long time
Um, I don't understand why people feel the need to throw in their two cents and then say the same thing that everyone else already said
I
I agree like like the first couple weeks. I attributed it to like
To it's the same as the last guy
The first couple the first couple weeks
I attributed it to people not having heard the latest episode because they hadn't come out
But now it's been like five fucking weeks and like you should know better
You should really know better than to send another voicemail about circumcision
Speaking of which the next one is called
The next one is called cross not an argument for or against circumcision three two one go
There is a medical condition called fimosis, which is
We've talked about it. I've mentioned fimosis in discussing circumcision you fucking moron cross
You're in the fucking voice jail. You're in fucking voice jail. I'm saying it. You're done. You're dead. You're out
You lose you get nothing good day, sir
Okay
Next one is called Biden COVID shoplifting Digi trans now
All right three two one go
Wait a second
if Nate is gone and
Mesh is gone and Monty is gone and
Ben is a cock
Then who's driving the PCT?
Also, it is scientifically proven that it only comes as a circumcision
if the ball such
Well, I'm convinced
All right
Next one is called mother's basement
three two one go
Hi, I'm Mozilla Fennigan and I
This is my application for the replacement to be
Goofy or whatever the fuck his name is
So I yeah, I hear you're looking for a replacement. So let me tell you why I'm the guy for the job
All right, so I annula I analyzed anime openings on my YouTube channel
No, don't look for it
Don't look for my channel don't go there and find out that I don't have like two videos about anime
I think that I don't make videos anymore. That's what I love
I just like talking about
And just like just like mr. G off I also come from reddit in fact
I'm currently part of a podcast called the our anime podcast. I know the base name
Although now he's talking like three times faster than Jeff's game
But whatever fuck crunch roll we're sponsored by hide-eye and we shove it in our audience's faces at every opportunity
She's awesome to know that they can get a 30-day free trial at hide-eye.com
So LPs are actually like you watch cool anime like Tomica market and they did the best to complete the identical anime and
I mean my own basement
I mean some my mother's basement, but like he doesn't even live in the basement anymore. So fuck him
I win this argument and
There are a couple things I don't have you know
I don't have an ethot gf with fake boobs, but you know, maybe some day
Next one is called also mother's basement. I can't wait three two one go. I wasn't fucking done. I wasn't
Mentioned the best part which is that
Just like
I don't even got you up to the podcast, you know like I don't even have to be on the fucking podcast
You can just be like hey remember remember that guy who was on the podcast one time, which I have but on the podcast
Fucking you fucking got me fucking got me Mozilla. Fuck fuck off. Fuck you
But well well played
Don't ever fucking talk to me or my son
Next one is called I got COVID
I think this might be someone in the comments of the last episode said they had COVID
Which is they said they can't tell it's mate smell or taste anything pretty fucked up
Well, let's let's hear three two one go
So just to give you guys some background. I am a college freshman. I take a COVID test every week
I wear a mask. I do what I got to do
So to start the story, I'm hanging out with some friends playing some super smash bros as you do
Once suddenly this kid gets a phone call
Saying that he tested positive for COVID. I'm just sitting here thinking fuck. This means I have COVID too
Like I had just ripped his bond 30 minutes ago. Yeah, I'm gonna have a sip of my water
So I probably have COVID like this is wild. I'm gonna have to buy the shirt, right?
So I'm an artist I've recently decided to
drop out of college and
Maybe go to art school
It's a good idea bad idea, you don't have to be taught you just
Anyway, love the show. Love you guys
This voicemail wasn't even about COVID
No voicemail was just should I drop out of school? I don't fucking know
First of all, I have an idea for you guys do drop out of school, but don't go to art school. I have an idea for your shirt
Uh, what about what about the shirt? You should modify the shirt the COVID shirt you have to say
I have COVID and then under it say I'm the reason people are dying
You mean combined combined the two yeah into a into a single
Into a single more powerful. It's a high power. Yeah, exactly
Just buy both shirts
Cut them in half and then like and stitch them onto each other and stitch them together
So it's one on the front one will be more artful that way
It'll be you put your own little you get more pranks little twist
People ask wow, where'd you get that shirt? You can say I didn't make this is a one-of-a-kind. Yeah, nobody has a shirt like this
Next next one is called for Batman love joker jelly beaner three wait. Yeah, three two one go I
Did it because I crave to be in your bat suit
Rachel is the sweetest and kindest girl in Gotham. I
Imagine she smells like oil drums and gunpowder
Your mansion your girlfriend
Your life I
Want to be you I
Crave to be you
And for that brief instant I
Was inside your back cave with your but
In that moment I
I was the bat man
And it was beautiful
Wow, okay
You know that sounded awfully familiar
Yeah, it sounded like Dan Harmon. I
can't quite place it
That was jelly beaner. I I think he was in jail. I don't remember. I don't know
Fuck you jelly beaner. Good. Good production on that voicemail. Oh, I'll prove this
Next one anarchy 2002 music video, but mp3 three two one go
Three two one go, that's me three two one go stop
Three two one, go
Three two one
Three two one go
I don't know what that means three two one go
What a banger that was great
What a what a What a what a what a what a what a what a trip?
Uhh...
What uh...
Next one.
That's what I've been hearing the whole, all this time.
Is that what I sound like?
Just kidding, I know that's what I sound like.
Next one is called, Why You Shouldn't Fap 3, 2, 1 go.
Bang.
Don't like was that do we just get
skeeded on like yeah, they'll
almost sounded like a they're
almost sounded like a jesse
bit. I wouldn't. I didn't
consent. I didn't consent no.
but unfortunately I've already
filled my jail quota for the
day so you're you're free to
go Mr. censorship.
Okay, oh god, last voicemail is called,
I win the circumcision debate, so everyone shut the fuck up.
We'll see about that, three, two, one, go.
Long ago, I gave birth to a baby boy of my own.
I didn't think about getting him circumcised,
but the psychotic doctors insisted
that they cut up his little peewee hermon.
I wasn't comfortable with it, but the doctor said,
he must lose his force gate.
It's the only way he survives.
It's true.
My precious baby boy stopped sucking
on my fat, milky, motherly titties,
looked the doctor straight in the eye and said,
doctor, I don't want to be circumcised.
Studies have shown that there is little no improvement
in a boy's health due to circumcision.
This is practically child mutilation and nothing more.
Please doctor, don't take my foreskin away.
All the doctors in the room clapped
and I was moved to tears.
My son was not circumcised
and then he lived a happy, healthy life.
And that boy's name was Joe Biden.
No!
USA.
I thought it was a wholesome story that it turned out
to be a story about a child rapist.
And it was hot too,
because it had mommy milkers in it.
That story had something for everyone.
It was pretty good.
I feel good now.
You know what, I was depressed,
but now I can face the day again.
It's turned it all around for me.
I got a new lease on life.
We made it, we made it to the end.
We listened to every fucking voicemail.
Again.
We did it again.
You know, I used to think you screamed these
before you listened to them first.
Someone used to.
We used to, back when a fascist was in charge,
but now it's anarchy, baby.
Now the people decide.
They see.
Anyway, how are we feeling?
Vibe check, vibe check.
I'm feeling pretty good.
Make it die.
I'm hungry.
Gamers Tavern.
Yeah.
You wanna say anything before we log off forever
for this episode?
Yeah.
Go to youtube.com slash gamers tavern show
and subscribe and.
We didn't plug you enough.
I will say it the last minute.
We talked about your channel more the last time
you were on, when you were a guest before.
If you want, just to hear.
If you want to hear basically all the jokes
that Gamers Tavern was making throughout this show,
except it was just those jokes,
wall to wall while you watch and play video games.
Wall to wall those jokes while he plays
like Sonic the Hedgehog or.
Kirby.
Possum, possum or whatever.
I think you mean Rockin' Night Adventures.
Yes, I mean, I do mean Rockin' Night Adventures.
Yes, that's what he's got.
You can also go to gamers tavern.com
to read reviews and articles.
Right, yes.
I've written over 500 reviews.
That's a lot of copy and reviews.
What was the one, you posted one recently
that had a slime in it?
Yeah.
Or no, you posted a picture of a slime
and I was like, what the fuck is this?
And you linked to the article,
your review of the game.
What was that game?
It's called Smart Ball for the Super Nintendo.
Smart Ball.
I'd never, never heard of it.
Oh, now you have.
I like slime.
You can also follow me on Twitter
at Gamertavern without the S.
Gamertavern.
All one word, no underscore?
Yeah.
Based, based, based.
Okay, and you know.
Patreon.com slash the procrastinators
to get bonus episodes.
That's right, to hear all the fucking,
all the cut content.
You've heard it, you've heard it.
We cut out the content.
We're gonna pay wall.
It's the only way.
Okay, buy a shirt.
Subscribe, ring the bell.
Bye.