Hello everybody and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm your
host for today, Tom Oliver, and with us we have a bunch of scoundrels starting with the
digital boy himself. Staring deep into my favorite haunted photograph.
Uh, hooray. Hippo is here.
It's a bitch's shed one.
Amazing. Uh, Lethal Laura Mage.
Hello, Digi. Is that is that image you're staring at? Is it of a figurine of that cursed life sized doll thing?
No, it's a picture of me and Gigic drunk as shit with a representative from Bandai Namco in a sort of online
bordered image that we didn't know we were taking until we did.
That's even worse. Nate is here.
The amount of joy I get from staring at my Radcon 3 Arena pin sitting next to my workstation every day is immeasurable.
I'm wearing the Radcon 3 Arena shirt right now. It's a great shirt.
It's right next to my Poobop.
Yeah, I feel that way every time I see the Poobopin that's still in the little plastic little thing because I don't know what to do with
the pins, but it just it somehow it appears in different rooms throughout the house.
Well, it's alive.
Nice. It's definitely traveling.
We have we have we have the DeVoo with us to lightly paraphrase Frederick Nietzsche suicide is in my blood.
It always was, but it doesn't evaporate in the light anymore.
I know that feel and munchy.
Hey guys, did you know that actual real Shakespearean actor Jason Alexander known for his role as George Alexander is now going to be typecasted in all of his roles now because he played one character in Seinfeld and and because of that in a Disney movie,
Hunter Beck of Notre Dame, he was cast as a completely gargoyle in a real ass horror drama movie and he says lines in the middle of Quasimodo singing about how he wants to be perceived as real human.
He says, cut the wine and pour the cheese and makes fart noises.
God, this is the worst part of that movie.
What a modern treasure.
He played an insane murderer in an episode of CSI once.
He played shallow.
Just to clarify, we are talking about I think he played a straight man hotel clerk in Dunks and checks in.
So he's not always on the offensive of Goof.
You know, these days I hear he's been like making 45 minute video game analysis videos on YouTube.
That's exciting.
What?
Yeah, Joseph Alexander, right?
Oh, hey, hey, this is a restaurant.
I didn't fuck it up.
No, it's Joseph Anderson.
Oh, God, damn it.
It's Jason Alexander.
It's Alexander the Great.
No, no, it's fucking Joseph Anderson.
You fuck none of the words.
It sounds similar enough that it made sense as a joke in my head.
Well, never mind.
I've already told the terrible story about how I thought Jay Alexander's restaurant was made by Jason Alexander.
Turns out it's not.
And my disappointment is made from Jay from Red Letter Media.
This is what you do with pins is you got to get a good fucking satchel.
All right, here's the thing now.
I've talked about the show how I want a purse and I do want a purse, but I can't get a purse or else my mom will kill me.
So what I have to do is I have to get a satchel and I've been searching.
I've been searching and all satchels are shit.
I love the idea of a satchel, but they fucking suck.
You just got to go to Kendall and Hyde and get that real leather.
You know, in college.
Write that down.
But I've only seen shitty trying too hard.
This is what we call nutsack.
It's like, oh, this isn't a fucking purse.
This is a satchel.
Trust me, I'm not gay.
Here's what you do with that.
You play up the girliness of it, but you also accentuate your arm hair.
So your arm hair is always on display and you're clutching your purse.
But it's like, oh, you're clutching your girly purse.
But you're always clutching it like it's hard to put it in your hand.
And to show you a male power, you're barely visible.
Your finger power to crush it as hard as you can just to show you you're a strong man.
Oh, oh, but in fucking Italy, which we'll get into later, but this is a quick aside.
I met this fucking guy who was my tour guide for a thing.
And he had this fucking sick ass satchel that was like black and looked super gender
neutral, but wasn't trying too hard to be manly.
And it also just was really cool and small and looked convenient.
So any rocket, super fucking hard.
And also his arm hair was a fun fact.
All European men are gay, bisexual, at least.
So, you know, just keep that in mind.
You're using fashion tips after him.
I did, I did, I did.
And he said, oh, I did, and I looked and then I looked really hard.
Like I stopped him in place and I said, you can't leave yet.
And then I looked really hard and satchel and it had the words bond, bond on it.
I've tried to search bond, bond, satchel, like the little Italian leather work,
you know, like marketplace, like the be like, hey, look at the bags.
See, that's not how they speak.
Oh, oh, oh, OK.
Well, I have a lot to say about that, but I don't want to get it myself.
Me and Hippo have both gone on trips.
We've both gone on a worldwide adventure.
But a summer of trips.
But say all the shit that no one cares about first.
Good idea.
We don't need to do that now.
This is the formless version of the show.
We just do.
Yeah, I mean, you know, I've got it.
Well, I don't want to immediately run over the show with a info dump
and also then head over to Hippo, who will also info dump.
And then the rest of you fucking pigeons.
I mean, last time we literally just let Ben talk about keto for like an hour and a half.
So like, yeah, it was all good, great.
That this is the muchy.
This is the spirit of the formless cast.
This is the topic of the day.
We want to hear about your trip and this is like this is like I'm like a fucking liberal.
I'm a liberal noble who was just overthrown.
And now the windows is expedient.
So far that now that now that even though I was on like the far end of the spectrum,
now, now I'm just a conservative and reactionary conservative, counter-revolutionary
and Nate and Nate Maximilliam.
Yeah, yeah, it's going to fucking shot my head off before I can even get a word in.
I was telling you to go on about it though.
It's the opposite of what I was trying to say.
All right, whatever.
OK, OK, OK, OK, I assume that we don't want to go blow by blow because that's kind of
all you didn't know about the shit that you can get is the I've gone.
I've gone to the fucking I've gone to all the places where you got to go.
Gone to the Coliseum, gone to the Vatican, I spin the Pope's fucking face
and I saw him on some right then and then everyone watching cheered me on.
I went to all the places that you need to.
And here, OK, I'm about to like pull up the shit because this is no longer
the procrastiners podcast.
This is no longer longer in audio entertainment.
This is a post on my personal tumbler.
Call out post for the lead.
Your faith is problematic.
The Leaning Tower of Peace.
What a duty. OK, here's the real shit.
Here's the fucking shit that you need to fucking know about the Leaning Tower of
Peace and all its ilk, all the tourist traps and the fucking black people trying
to sell you purses, all the black people near the Coliseum, right up to like high
five me modern, you know, get away from me and then they grab on to you.
They're like, no, high five me.
And then you say, no, and you run away and they say, I'm happy for you, man.
And then, you know, they're trying to get some lonely other cock to fucking
high five them and then the end then you're trapped.
All right, here's the deal.
Here's the fucking deal.
You go to Italy, you go to Italy, you look up Italy on the map and you say,
oh, I'm going to go to fucking Italy.
And you know why you go there?
Number one reason, because it's authentic, because it's rustic and you go
and you go and you go to Olive Garden and you think, what if Olive Garden was
really big and that's what you think it's going to be?
So you go there because you want handmade shit.
You want handmade pasta.
You want to roll your own dough.
You want to cook your own dough, Jerry.
It's a make your own pizza pie restaurant.
We're thinking to make the fucking stove.
You have the make your own pizza pie concept from Italy.
This is some bullshit.
All right.
It's fucking crazy.
So you go there and you want to be a rustic and authentic and then you go
there and because you're a fucking sheep, because you're my mom, because you're
a fucking 40 year old and by 40 year old, I mean, 50 year old baby boomer who just
wants to be told what to do.
They don't want to experience the real shit, even though that's what you came
here, so you can be authentic.
You want to come here and you want to be like, oh, what do I have to do?
What do people say to do?
And now I have to do it because I'm a fucking sheep and like, oh,
you know, why do I want to go to the Coliseum?
It's not because I care about history.
It's because I have to do it.
It's because it's because what it's what you do.
The Lean Tower of Pisa.
Here's the thing about the Lean Tower of Pisa.
It's a tower that leans.
You can't go inside the Lean Tower of Pisa.
I mean, I think you can, but you have to like a special pass and I was not
able to do that and most people do not do it.
So it's not really a main attraction of it.
So Lean Tower of Pisa is a tower that leans that you look at from the outside
kind of far away.
That's where the road is.
You know how else you could intake that information?
It's looking at a picture of Lean Tower of Pisa.
What has everyone done for fucking a million years?
As long as they've been alive, look at pictures of the Lean Tower of Pisa.
So you've intake and all the information that you possibly could.
Now, I liked going to the Coliseum.
I liked doing that kind of stuff because you could intake more information.
You know, I've not really seen a lot of pictures of the inside of the Coliseum.
It was nice to be able to see the be there and have a tour guide be like, oh,
this is where the people were son of I just don't know.
Wow, I wish that would happen to me sometime soon, please.
And it was great.
It was new information, but the Lean Tower of Pisa, here's the fucking thing.
When you're around shit, you get shit.
So you go to Lean Tower of Pisa because it's what you have to do.
It's what, oh, you can type on Facebook, you know, checked in Lean Tower of Pisa
and you're fucking Aunt Sally can be like, oh, my God, the Lean Tower of Pisa
is like my fucking dead husband's dick.
And then she can like it and retweet it.
And that's the shit that you want because that's what you care about.
It's fucking legs because you're 40 years old and your baby more.
You make Italy sound like the Anor Londo of Europe, where it's like
everywhere is supposed to go there is the coolest place and it is cool.
But I kind of wish you could wander around a lot more and you weren't
kind of strung through a little bit.
Well, the problem there, I'll give you real quick.
I'm just noticing I don't I don't need to rehash or anything.
But your description of what to do in Italy reminds me of my recent trip to
Hawaii and I think the reason I had such a wonderful magnificent time
the whole time was because I got to go wherever I wanted to go
because I am an adult unlike you and I paid for it myself unlike you.
So I think this is the distinction here.
Yeah, I was empowered to do whatever I wanted.
That's like what she said.
And for what it's worth, 50 year olds are Gen Xers.
But for that generation, they very much are like they go to the place
to go see the thing they've already heard of.
And to me, like what she said, yeah, it's like if I'm going there,
show me the part of Italy that I will not get in a brochure, you know,
show me the part that looks like crazy and real.
This story perfectly encapsulates what I'm talking about.
It's just one day we were driving and we saw a little beach.
It was a crazy cliffside.
I took videos of it.
They're on my Instagram and stuff.
But like that day, we couldn't go there because we were rushing off somewhere else.
I'm like, I don't care about anything else on this island.
I want to go there.
And then the day we were leaving when we had spare time, I'm like, fuck everything else.
We're going to that one place and we went there and it was the best time there.
I got to go there.
I fulfilled my personal little, whatever, self determination dreams.
It was awesome.
And I felt great about it.
And I didn't have to miss that on anything.
Yeah, you know, that's the good.
I went to a county fair just yesterday and after having an.
Oh, my God, DeVu County fairs are like a glimpse into like, like, like all the
media from other countries talking about how Americans are retarded, easily
dissuaded and how commercials brainwash you.
You don't believe it.
And then you go to a county fair and you recognize that your culture is fucking
funny poison.
American culture is poison.
I can.
I've only been.
I've only noticed that.
What is a county fair?
It's just a bunch of fucking country shit.
Right.
So this one had, you know, food.
Nothing wrong with.
Like, like, like really on like, like it's that kind of like really greasy
food where you can, you can taste the flavor of all the unhygienic cooking
conditions, which really give it that flavor similar to catching.
No, like, what?
So like, what?
Similar to how you catch a fish that was that was that swam around
deep in the dirtiest parts of the ocean.
You can just taste every single microfiber of that six pack plastic container
that it ate in its lifetime.
It's the same kind of thing.
It's like, wow, this corn dog, you know, this corn dog was like like a dollar
fifty or two dollars, but it was cooked on a fryer that has like more
crufty gunk than it has meat.
So clearly that's personality.
Clearly that's where all the flavors coming from, right?
So it's also got a bunch of animals.
You mostly just look at their butts because all the cows are turned away from
you, but the animals are mostly they are not to be gawked at by the passersby,
but mostly to be evaluated for which cow is the best, like professionals
come in and give it a ranking and shit, that kind of thing.
Like who grew the best fucking cow, who grew the best goat?
But the regular civilians can check it out, too, and be like, oh, cool.
Oh, so it's like that those things in cartoons, where it's always like the
biggest comequat contest or whatever.
Like, yeah, I kind of like that.
But, you know, not not come.
It's a lot less engaged.
And then they have some rides, some real shitty rickety, you know,
fairgrounds type rides that they installed in like three hours.
It's stuff like Disneyland or like Nautsbury Farm
and you have that your pussy fur that's like, I don't want to ride the roller coaster.
It's always easy to be like, listen,
it's way more expensive for these people to have you live.
That's how I convince people to go on roller coaster.
It's because they're going to have to do a ton of paperwork if you die.
So they're going to make this ride way safe.
They're going to make this ride as safe as possible so that you don't die.
But it fares, I really don't feel like that.
I feel like they don't care and they just feel like they die.
He was laying down on part of the steel of the ferris wheel with I shit,
you know, like all the mechanisms and gears and like bending and like
prolapsing steel that was like moving in a circle for fucking inches away
from his head and his shoulder.
He found the exact leaning position with which to not be immediately
instantly mutilated by the machine so that he could be as depression as possible.
I OK, I need to fully illustrate.
Davoo, Davoo, does your county fair look like this?
This picture that I'm up on right now and I'm up in the show notes.
It's it's fucking upland right now because my my pretty similar.
Although this one is way more populated and yeah.
OK, although yours is a little bit less white is.
Oh, yeah, there's a lot of Asians in the Diego.
Anyway, my country fair is shit food,
like unbelievably terrible food for 10 or $11 each.
You should get a little corn dog over there.
That corn dog probably costs like six.
That's why I never go to these things.
It's like like vomit.
There's everything is so expensive and none of it's worth anything.
Exactly.
Look at the graphic design.
Wall to fucking wall.
You have the most fucking disgusting,
horrible, unappetizing nightmare fucking Photoshop
of nightmares on either fucking side of you.
And they all cost a thousand dollars.
You there's terrible rights.
But here's the thing.
If it was just that, I would think, haha, like, you know, like shit food.
This is really entertaining.
But here's the thing.
Here's the most insidious thing about the county fairs is like,
I guess I'm going to call them the exhibition halls.
You guys have been like, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, yeah, yeah.
We had one of those, too.
Imagine if that.
But instead of like, you know, like, like, like grassroots fucking,
you know, furry porn artists who you want to commission, you want to support going on.
It's like weird, bum, fucking conspiracy theory.
Like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, get this sleeve for your wallet.
So when you go through the airports, you know, your soul.
That's the kind of shit.
It's stuff like that.
And like hot tubs and just a bunch of scammy, old fucking white people.
Shit that they all have greeters for and they're all they're all like, you walk by.
OK, here's a real fucking thing that was literally said to me in real life.
Not not fucking VR chat, not second life.
This is in real life.
I got dipping dots because I'm fat and I wanted to be better because I wanted to be brainwashed.
And so I got dipping dots and I walked by a greeter who who who was like,
just like he had just some fucking broom and he wanted to pedal it like it was the super broom.
And he and he and he and I walked by and he said, all right, you got the dipping dots.
Oh, you got to get the broom.
What's the segue there?
What are you trying to accomplish?
I'm not going to get your room.
I have no reason to what was called a commercial center or whatever.
It was in a chilled out building.
It was in a building with air conditioning.
So went there and it's just a bunch of booths of people peddling their their their city wide wares.
So there was like the there was like a little booth for like the hearing center
where you can go in and get a test for how good your hearing is to see if you need hearing aids.
There was a someone running for some Democrat office in the city,
someone running for some Republican office in the city.
There was a gaming booth for like magic and shit.
It seems like they're opening up a gaming booth, but didn't look like it would be that good.
And there was there was like a power and light building or just booth.
But then there was also a pro life booth.
So we checked that one out, right?
It has a little CG like movie playing on the screen of like of a fetus growing over time.
No.
And it had three like like other models of fetuses at different stages of development.
Like here's the 12 weeks, here's the 15 weeks, right?
It had pamphlets being like abortion, a lifetime of regret, that kind of thing.
And that's cool.
Show me a fully grown baby that I can slam dunk into the trash can.
There was there was also we actually took this little flyer showing the number of sexual
partners you have in a 10 year span.
And then it's like it has a little algorithm to calculate the number of people all with
potential STDs on their junks that you have now exposed yourself to.
And based on its own algorithm, if you have had 10 distinct sexual partners in the last
decade, then you have exposed yourself to 65,143 people or something like that.
I don't know how the fucking numbers work.
They did some math there for like, I don't know, number of sex people have probably.
I mean, we all have to assume that everyone who you fucked has fucked as many people as
you have before you fucked them.
I don't I don't get it.
It there might be some logic to it.
We also took a pencil.
It said life is precious.
So I figure any time I'm going to like tell someone to not get an abortion, I'll write
it in that pencil.
And of course, and so my fiance, she she does a very smart thing of like making her point
but getting an abortion, she says.
So how what kind of efforts are you guys taking to like, you know, support women who
like don't get the abortion and now don't have any like safety networks and like old
ass motherfucking woman, right, who probably who who presumably based on those algorithms
must have like joined the fucking faith after being in an orgy of 20 people and is now how
she forever perceives all sexual activity to be, you know, like 40 years ago or something.
Anyway, she's like, oh, well, you know, a little bit helping helping some women with
with single moms, you know, but we do it a bit depends on the town.
Why do they why do they act so cowardly?
Why don't they say we don't fuck them?
But that's what I would say if I were them.
I mean, stick to your principles.
Just take every CG artist you are fucking hiring to animate all the fallopian tubes and then
spend that money on some fucking like, you know, like driving them to the booth.
Fuck that.
I need work.
I really want to know.
I want to know who ever is going to stand in front of that fucking movie and be like,
oh, my God, you're right.
You know, it was like really like retro style 3D animation.
It reminded me of 3D pipes, like watching the fallopian tubes like grow and shit.
It was just like 3D pipes on Windows 95.
Whoa, that one convinced me.
OK, guys, here's a question for you.
Is it abortion or go a lifetime of eternal damnation?
If you crush a fruit before it's right, oh, shit.
Is it? I mean, it's at that point, it wouldn't be just killing a child.
Well, if you if you eat a seed, you're aborting of a potential fruit.
In this metaphor, the tree would be like the child.
A fruit is like an an egg or like a seed or whatever.
Well, yeah, fruits are not a lot.
Fruits are not like the actual product.
They're they're the containers.
They don't have fruit.
We deliver the seeds.
Are they not plants?
Fruits are there to like provide nutrients for the seed when they go in the
satisfaction to humans.
Yeah, or like when animals eat.
It's the same reason why semen taste so good.
It's so that they'll spread it around and, you know, try it out, ladies.
Hey, man, that's sigh of defeat.
There's there's semen cookbooks out there and shit.
There sure are. There sure are.
I did not want to know that.
Oh, oh, shit.
I didn't I didn't finish my fucking call that post.
I saw that the first part of it is don't go to shit.
And yeah, I have an actual reason to go like another thing just to quickly
illustrate that again, there's a building.
There's a cathedral in Florence called the Duomo.
And I have no fucking clue what's inside this building.
It looks pretty from the outside.
I sketched my sketchbook.
It was nice.
But my mom for a while was like, we got to go inside the Duomo.
And then I finally just asked her like five or six times
like of her saying that we got to.
I said, what's inside that you want to see?
And she was like, uh, it's called the Duomo, dude.
I really think and I know I've said this a couple of years.
Building it's it's you want to go inside the Duomo
to relive Assassin's Creed, too, because it's the same building
that you can go inside and is like, oh, I remember jumping up that painting.
Yeah, dude, no, I really anyway,
that the second the second part of of why your favorite
problematic lean tower of pizza is because around all the shit around
the fucking Duomo around, well, actually, the Duomo was pretty good,
but around like the Colosseum around the Vatican, all that kind of shit.
They know that if you're coming here, you're obviously brain dead.
You obviously have no fucking wits about you
and you can easily be persuaded to do whatever these people want you to do.
So around around the fucking lean tower of pizza,
there's not that authentic Italian food that you came to fucking Italy for.
There's none of that shit.
There's fucking menus in English.
That's how you fucking know.
Here's how you know if a fucking restaurant would be bad in Italy,
is if it's one in English or if it has like pictures of it
or any stuff like that, like you can just tell.
You can tell something's going to be if it has like pictures
of the food that it has, because they know people have time to read.
So they say, oh, he's just spaghetti looks like this.
As soon as you were going to Italy, it reminded me of an NPR story.
I heard there's this guy who just he's like the food reporter for NPR.
And he said on Italy specifically, he said, the way you know
that you're going to a good, real, real Nibba place in Italy is to
you only want to go to places that use catch of the day,
that have like a catch of the day and have a handwritten menu on the door.
It's like a family place, because that's the fresh shit.
And that's the real shit.
And our stereo.
Oh, yeah, that's like family restaurant.
So you got terrible fucking Disneyland to your food.
Side note, by the way, Disneyland has the worst food imaginable.
I've been there recently.
All of their food is it's like country fair food.
It's like terrible and like ten dollars.
Anyway, it has like Disneyland to your food.
Absolutely terrible.
And it's not like, you know, oh, just the food's bad.
Everything around is so fucking fake and sterile.
None of it is authentic Italian shit.
It's all fucking tourist trap bullshit.
You go to lean tower pizza because you want to experience, you know,
assumably, you want to experience Italian architecture.
You want to experience romantic architecture.
And then you look to the sideline tower pizza and you see a fucking guy
wrangling a horse and a guy in a fucking sandwich.
Penini outfit next to him.
You see them fucking dance like they're in some very
weird, you hear them screaming Italian words to try and get to donut.
Got it. Look at this.
This is like a lean tower pizza with the sandwich man.
Oh, God, I see this.
It's like that at pretty much all of the like major tourist attractions around the world.
Like if you go to Egypt or something, you know, right next to the right outside
the the like range of the photograph of the like if you literally turned your
camera like 30 degrees to the side and just be like bam stalls, you know, right.
I remember there was a whole cracked article about that.
They like showed you all the famous landmarks that people go to.
And they showed you, you know, the typical tourist attraction
pamphlet photographs, and then they showed you the photos like right next to it.
And it's just it's crowded with fucking people, you know, what's really funny
about that to me is that like people then go there and they take their own
pictures of the thing and they try to they try to excise all the extra shit.
And I'm like, to me, that's the most interesting and funny part.
Like if I was going to take a picture of the pyramid, I would want to capture
all of that in it because that is fucking hilarious.
I remember first becoming really cognizant of how repulsive
smartphone culture has turned the human genome into when there was this
like light news story going around about this flight attendant lady
who lost her shit mid-flight and like probably had like only like two hours
of sleep over the course of two days and she just like started screaming
fucking 9000 feet up in the air, right?
And the news, you know, the news broadcasts this phone recording
that someone took and it's just her screaming, right?
But what was more interesting to me about the true nature of the human condition
is that this wasn't the only person filming in between the like the frame
of this camera and the woman in the middle screaming.
There are at least 12, probably 20 other fucking stupid
cockney hands jutting out, holding their phone and also recording.
So everyone has decided to elect this poor woman, a fucking paparazzi
rape in the eyes of human society to turn her into a celebrity,
but only with the negative gossipy elements without any of the fame or respect.
That is what and then every single person thought fame or respect
does she deserve as a flight attendant freaking out on a plane?
Like having a mental breakdown, maybe she needs help wrong here.
Exactly. Maybe she doesn't need to be filmed by 20 fucking people
and every single person who decided to put up their fucking camera.
You only saw one person's phones.
Like, what's the difference?
Like only one is all it took, right?
But like everyone now knows, well, everyone else here is recording it.
I would my own recording that way.
Sometimes when I'm looking back to me about it, like I'll go to a concert
and there'll be like 30 people with their phones out recording the concert.
And I'm like, you're at the concert.
Like, what are you going to do with this recording with shitty audio and shitty visuals?
Like, are you going to post this on social media?
You see that 30 other people are recording it.
So like let the guy with the good angle do the recording
and let him post it on YouTube and the rest of you fucking enjoy the show.
I want to prove that you went there.
I want to prove to my friends on Facebook that I'm cool.
If you were to pull out your camera and take one little picture
and be like, there you go. I was at the show. Fine.
I see people who will sit there and be recording the whole fucking time.
Like, or like whichever song they like, they have to record that song.
And it's like, it's going to sound like dick and you know it.
Just just experience it.
You're here at the show watching every time I've done it myself.
I look back and think, well, I'm never going to go back and watch it.
And, you know, and but it's not even just that you won't go back and watch it.
It's that if you spend the whole time that you could be watching it, filming it.
That means at no point did you watch the show.
You have watched your camera and then you've watched your camera again in the future.
So the only version you've ever taken in is a shit version
and as opposed to the actual real show.
And this is what I was getting to with talking about the fare that I went to
yesterday, because every once in a while, when I get out of the house to do a thing,
you know, to do an activity, I'm reminded of how not so different it is on the internet.
You know, right now I'm looking at my screen and I see a thumbnail and a title.
107 facts about Nintendo's Princess Peach by the super coin crew.
1.3 million views and the re and it's not actually all that weird
that people waste their lives on YouTube so much because all you can do is go
outside and waste your life while also spending money.
It's the only other alternative.
All the fucking non millennials who go places and quote unquote do things
don't have fucking anything to do.
No one on this goddamn earth has a sense of purpose in life and we're all faking it.
90 percent of all economic transactions are bullshit in which the consumer is
trying to kid themselves into there being a point at the fucking fair.
There was a stall.
My fiance says, oh, we got to buy at least one thing at the fair.
So there's a stall that I used to have that.
Oh, that's a fucking economic equivalent.
If we got to go, yeah, I used to I used to have that.
Like every time we would go to like a zoo or like anything that had a gift shop.
I was like, well, I got to have a souvenir.
I got to have like something and I look around and I or even though I don't buy
anything from any gift shop anymore, I still look around to see just just in
case that there is something cool.
The stall.
They never.
I learned my lesson.
I personally just would want to find that this stall consisted.
50 percent of this stall was like a bunch of like $15 like pocket watches
that they probably like whoever ran this stall probably like has some sort of
warehouse or something.
They're just trying to get rid of some shit.
Right.
And then the other 50 percent is stuff that you would literally trade in at a
Chuck E cheese for 10 tickets that you've won like socks or two stint rings
made of plastic.
And I looked at this and I thought this is the biggest.
We have Amazon.com, you know, we can buy random things.
We don't need like this.
All this shitty tat has no bearing on the actual fare.
It doesn't have the dignity of being homemade and full of fucking bacteria like
the corn dogs do, where it at least makes sense.
You're not going to be able to get that at fucking at Sonic, right?
But but this is just shit that you got out of a fucking box.
Well, my family, I want to say what my family does, they buy like little
magnets of pictures of the place they went to as it's like, oh yeah, I went there
sort of thing.
Well, you know what, guys, I like I just brought up how much I love my
Radcon three pin at the beginning of this.
It's not that the pin is valuable.
It's the memories and what like if I didn't have this pin, I would think
about how much I loved Radcon three a lot less.
This is actually a very beneficial thing in my life.
That's that's one thing.
But like, I think that the difference is with Radcon three, you only got one
of those pins, if you actually helped to make it even fucking possible.
True, like so when you go to random, random place A and you just buy
some insanely overpriced thing that is just, you know, that's that literally
anyone who's been there could have had.
It's like, I understand that maybe looking at it will make you remember
that experience, but I feel like instead of doing that, you should just go
have another experience.
It's not it's not that you don't need to buy anything.
Like I for the last, I think like eight years or something, I've had this
journal that I bring to every holiday event and radcons.
And I write down like at the end of every day, something that happened.
And the purpose of that is to jog my memory when I read it back like, oh,
yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, I love Redcon.
And like that is my version of like whatever like souvenir I may have had
from from any holiday.
It's so much more effective as well, because it's my own handwriting.
It's my own thing.
Sure. But some people just want to save time by just buying some of it.
It'll do that.
I know. But like, I think it's it's worse.
I think it's not as effective.
Here's the thing.
The difference between the Redcon pin and some shitty fucking little
figurine that you could get some shitty, Florence and pink.
Michelangelo's David, you could buy at the lean to her piece, even though
it's not even the same fucking city.
The difference between that is that with the Redcon three pin,
it's that you were given that you were given that because again, like
did you said you're a part of it, but you were given that and that symbolizes
a thing that just happened naturally in the sense that like you are at Redcon
three, you have this pin to signify it when you go in and specifically buy
something for the purpose of remembering, you're not going to remember
the entirety of the trip that you've just been on.
You're going to remember the memory of you buying that pin.
The best souvenir of you having like a memory, like a memory jogging item is
the stuff that just will naturally have like, for instance, I want this legendary
food tour that I will explain in great detail later that changed my life.
And the souvenir I have to remember that is not some little fucking, you know,
a little figurine that I got along the way.
It's the business card of the of the of the guy of my food tour guide.
That's not something that I bought.
It's just something that naturally occurred and that's far more impactful
to me than making a conscious decision.
Oh, I will remember this.
I feel like that's not something that you can actually you can actually
hear. I hear your point.
I hear your point. But like, for example, there is this photograph that's
I think it's sitting in my bedroom right now of of me and Michelle.
When we did, we went to just a Korean restaurant and it was and we just had
like delayed. She had a Polaroid camera and just like offered to take a picture
of us and she did. And so we just got that picture and like, that's great.
If she'd given us like, I don't know, just like a little knickknack to remember
it, that'd be fine. But like, it's the same kind of thing.
It's like the same. I think I think there's I feel like that still fits into
what I'm saying. I don't understand the distinction.
Like you're talking about how like your your experience of going to Leading
Tower of Pisa is like inauthentic.
But you really did go and you really did have some experience.
No, that's not what I'm saying at all.
What's your point? That's not even trying to say that if you buy,
if you go out of your way to purchase a trinket,
then that is it's it's like you force that into the memory.
You feel like going there.
Exactly. Exactly. Oh, that's perfect.
I got to go on about my parents because my parents travel all the time
and they always show something.
They they do they do like all of it.
They do every possible thing because not only do they go and they get a tattoo
everywhere they go, so they'll get matching tattoos that sort of in some way
represent where they've been. How much available skin do they have?
Then they also buy a bunch of like bullshit.
But the weirdest part is that they buy a bunch of shit for us.
Like they'll buy they'll go to a souvenir shop and they'll buy things for me
and Victor and Shade and then they'll give them to us and I'll be like,
this means literally nothing to me because I did not go to this place.
And this thing you bought like what does this commemorate that you went somewhere?
Like, yeah, I'll be sure to look at this and remember that you went to Mexico,
you know, and all of those things go straight into my closet
because they're all fucking useless and they mean nothing to me.
Well, they buy those for themselves to give as a gift because the people like giving
right. And I was just like, I don't know why you do this because they spend a lot
of money buying like random fucking trinkets that are again mean nothing.
I want to check. They want to be there is like it's in the thing,
at least with my family.
There is a custom to sort of like bring back gifts or souvenirs from wherever
you go and travel, even if like, you know, all you did was travel to like,
I don't know, a different town, not necessarily for any sort of leisurely
reason, just, you know, for business or whatever.
It's sort of like a bit of a custom and it's just kind of like tradition.
It's to be nice and like not doing it.
I hate the tradition. I think that tradition is evil and propagated by this business.
But it doesn't do it. You'll be considered rude.
That's a problem. That is a huge problem because like they brought me home one time,
like like a hard rock cafe, like like wooden miniature guitar that like sits on a little
stand. And I'm like, you paid $20 for this thing that must have costed them 30 cents to produce.
And it means nothing to me. So like, why have you done this?
In Italy, there are hard rock cafe stores and no restaurant. There are just the,
there are just hard rock cafe is the worst thing that exists because it's literally,
it is just its own hype. There is nothing it symbolizes or represents except for itself.
It is a place that you go to buy things that say hard rock cafe on them and then say,
I went to a hard rock cafe in wherever and it's like, who cares? They're literally everywhere.
It's not special. We've all been to one.
What's a hard rock cafe? It's a it's a cafe that's like
in most major cities have one and it'll be like a place. It's just a fucking restaurant that like
because it exists everywhere, they play rock and roll music and I guess at some point in the 50s,
rock and roll bands had eaten at them and therefore they like have posters of everyone
who's ever been famous and eaten there. So yeah, famous for being famous is essentially what it is
at this point. Yeah, like, yeah. Well, like Munchie said, there's they have stores for it without even
the cafe. So like at that point, it's just a it's just a fucking it's just like this weird
meta meme that just hacks people's brains about what is a famous. I know there's people in my
family who will be like, oh, I've gone to the hard rock in every city and I've got like a thing from
every hard rock cafe. And I'm just like, why? Like why have if you went to a if I went to a foreign
country, why would I go to an American store and their installation within that foreign country?
Oh, oh my god, that's such a big thing. There are so many people that go to like, oh, you know, I
asked one of you like a McDonald's, you know, because it's familiar when I'm in Italy. Are you
fucking literally like, is there a note? Yeah, are you not alive? This is yeah, like, like, how could
you be that stupid as to want to get something that's familiar when you're specifically in a
place for the purpose of being in. Yeah, it's, it's, it's, I mean, I assume American tourists are
worse than than other places. I guess I guess English tourists are also bad. But like, like,
no, but like, um, yeah, I don't the the the idea of like going to a place, just to say that you
went there to your friends, like, you know, your baby boomer friends, your Gen X, your friends,
you know, everyone has kids. And finally, the kids are grown up enough so that you can go on
holidays or you drag your kids on holidays that they don't want to go on to really, you know,
just just to see the sights and to do all these things. And they do them because they're advertised
as a thing to do. And they don't have the time in their lives to really think about whether or
not it's a good idea. They're just like, ah, I'm getting old, I've got kids, I haven't had a chance
to live my life. I want to go to all these places that I've known so much about lack of proper
reflection on what actually makes you enjoy your life better. You know, when I realize the more
adult I get and the more prices I observe, like the actual like things that will actually make
your life significantly better are often a lot cheaper than very expensive things that have
nothing but hype behind them. I've observed that like people going on trips is like such a huge
time and money sink. And it's like you have to take time away from work. So that's already a
bunch of money that you're potentially losing unless you're on vacation. Then you've got to spend
all the money for the trip, like just getting there, staying there, everything around wherever
you're staying is more expensive than it would be normally. Every like just everything is so much
money. But then also nobody thinks about the fact that, hey, you're going to a foreign country.
Guess what? You don't have immunities to all the viruses that are naturally in the air there. So
you always get sick and then like someone gets pissed off because they're just not in a good mood.
Maybe the weather is not exactly what you expected it to be there. So like your family ends up fighting
about where they're going to go while they're in the town. Oh yeah. Oh my god. It's just nobody like
I don't understand how people can experience that and then be like now we're going to go to the next
one. None of these were a problem on my recent vacation because I am an adult and I kind of learned
that from when I went to the Philippines because it was funny. When I went there, I stayed for a
month with ghost lighting in the middle of Manila, which is the capital city and it's not where white
people go. There were no white people. Generally people don't speak English. There is not tourist
attractions. There's nothing there for that type of person and people kept asking him like why the
hell are you showing him around Manila? Like why don't you take him to like the beaches and stuff
where people go and it's like because I come from Virginia Beach. The whole city is a tourist trap.
I already know. I already know what the game is. If you go to the beach in Virginia Beach,
it's just an endless series of super expensive hotels. The price at every restaurant, even though
it's the same restaurants that they have all throughout the city, everything's jacked up $1.50
there. You have to pay for parking. The Atlantic Ocean is a disgusting cesspool that there's no
reason to go see it. The only people who come to Virginia Beach are people from the Midwest or New
York who just want warm weather and the ocean and they don't realize that if you went to Miami or if
you went to Hawaii, it would be like a zillion times nicer. It's just a shit tourist trap,
but people come there constantly and the city's whole fucking economy is based on that. It's like
I have nothing but cynicism for tourist places, but going to Manila, nothing there was like
anything I'd seen before. First of all, there is no green anywhere in the fucking city. It was like,
whoa, this is a fucking concrete jungle. There's billboards everywhere, every square inch of
cities. It's literally a fucking cyberpunk dystopia. All the food is something I've never had before.
There's all these weird little stalls all over the place of people just selling shit they made in
their fucking backyard that makes you sick and it costs $0.50 and you're like, hell yeah, this is
the life you're supposed to be living. Yeah, Italy is famous not because they built giant
shit out of marble, but because they killed everyone in the world, stole all of their marble,
and turned it into cool ass buildings. In other words, it's not the opulence or the fancieness,
it's the fucking violence and the death. It's the fucking, it's the goddamn plagues that make some
of these European landmarks interesting. You gotta go to that statue of the rape of the
Savian woman or whatever. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I saw it in Gunslinger Girl.
Oh God. It's the same way that you would get. We probably got more.
Ostensibly to experience an event, but then they just block it with their phone because they
only ever understand how to experience an event by proxy. You can only go to an ancient town that
was famous for a big war a thousand years ago by proxy, but you can right now experience the
mythology being crafted right now, which is to say, go to McDonald's and watch all the depressed
fat people. This is the culture as it is. There's like these, there's like this group of like 40
something super autist guys who go to this McDonald's and like, like, you know, they're like
upper, mid functioning and like that's, this is the American mythology being crafted right now.
I'm really glad you brought up McDonald's because I, you might have heard me talk about this way
back in the day on like Digibro never shuts up or something that I used to, this thing Munchy's
describing, I used to rant about all the time as the experience of going behind a McDonald's,
because when I was like 16, one time I was just like hanging out behind a McDonald's and I realized
that I was in this weird parking lot that is in the middle of town, like where I always am,
but I just never like stopped and looked at it and thought about it and I did and I was like,
this is super interesting that like this spot exists and no one thinks about it and it's just
here. What's really cool is that me and, me and Nikki, me and Cole are the only people in this
town who don't have a car, uh, fucking people at the checkout ladies are starting to comment on the
fact that we walk around everywhere. See, my mentality was, well, we're within walking distance
of like two different grocery stores and two different restaurants so, and a general department
store, so we're basically fine, we don't need a car, but then as you notice the distinct lack of
anyone else on the sidewalk, it's like, oh right, everyone else either has friends or has to drive
to their job, right? So we're like the only fucking people who are like walking around with fucking
grocery bags, right? So we're being urbanized in a suburban town. The point is, we've gotten a really
close-up look at every single like fragment of dilapidated concrete, right? Uh, and like, like
all cool, right? Yeah, so like, they're like, I just don't understand people's priorities that,
sorry for cutting you off, but I don't understand the priority of like, oh, the leaning tower of
pizza, we got to see that, and I'm like, why is that building more interesting than this building
down the block, you know, that is also cool. Okay, one path we can take to get to a certain
coffee shop is, you know, I've seen a lot of leading buildings that weren't famous, they were just
concerning, and people live in those ones, so they're way more exciting. So like,
they're about to topple over, but they never do. Maybe because it's all so big.
Yeah, that's pretty big. You know, I've seen some big buildings. One cool path that we have is,
we go out to McDonald's, out the back door, and there's a little parking lot there, but then
you sort of go to the left, and then you walk, you cut through the drive-thru lane, you get on a
little platform of concrete, and you jump into this little space between two bushes, and now you're
in the drive-thru area of a bank, and so you just sort of keep sneaking on through, assuming it's a
slow day, no one's there to like, gawk at you, and then boom, you've like taken a weird shortcut,
like through two different establishments, right? Pretty cool. If not for the fact that being mugged
was a possibility and a health risk, I would just go out in the middle of the night fucking behind
strip malls all the time. Like me, you, Nino, and Econ did that one time in Atlanta.
We did that because that's something I do. I tend to, if I'm near a big building, I always want
to see the back of it. And that time I felt safe, because as we said at the time, we have two white
people, one black guy, and one Asian guy, so I think we're pretty much safe from any discrimination.
No one will know what to do with this. You've got all the classes. You've got all the classes that
you can possibly have. Oh, properly structured like RPG party, yeah. Random interjection quickly.
I just, I want to say one of my favorite things I never get to do is take walks during the night
time, especially here where I'm in Lafayette, and it's just so quiet and empty, and I love it,
but I'm scared of walking alone. There's a reason why your fucking story inspired highly
background oriented fan art, because that's the real mythology that fucking Bethesda makes
a million dollars from a day. By the way, I want, I want to give you a red pill to the quick,
if you'll have me, brainwashed sheep. The long entire piece, I don't have to know this. It's
not just a tower, it's a bell tower. You know what it's a bell tower for? This right next to it
immediately way more interesting, detailed, and beautiful building that I'm seeing you right now.
This is right next to the entire piece, and no one gives a shit about it, even though it looks
really fucking pretty. Why, why does no one care about that? Everybody has to do the picture,
they have to do the thing with like, yeah, yeah, you can see them in this. I've seen like, I've seen
so many pictures of people doing like, like in large groups, like all over that bit of grass,
doing the, oh, I'm pushing it over, oh, I'm leaning on the leaning, oh, please take a picture of me.
Oh, I laugh every time. Dude, I, I, okay, one more thing about like random details are everywhere
in this fucking world, and I think I may have actually talked about this in the previous episode,
I don't know. Wait, before you say this, I just want to say we should start up a meme where we
all just go and take pictures of us doing the leaning tower thing next to random fucking buildings
and just like, flood the internet with it. Dogs all over locations. Oh, oh, dude, dude, my friend,
my friend Kyle, a notorious furry, and I've talked about multiple times on this show,
he does that, he went to Lincoln Monument and did that, and he wasn't even like,
Did he do the famous pose of freeing the slaves at the Lincoln Monument?
I remember he did that. So he, it looked like he was just like at Lincoln's foot and pushing
at the middle of the wall. Dude, for some reason that reminded me, one of the things that happened
at the fair is that there was a rodeo going on, probably should have mentioned that, that would
really help set the tone for what kind of place it was. We didn't go to the rodeo, none of us wanted
to go, we didn't even see it, it was way off in the stadium, but you get one of those women singing
the fucking national anthem, and one of those renditions of it where you add three times as
many notes as are actually in the composition. They make it like eight fucking minutes. Anyway,
I sort of snickered at that, I just like politely, I just like jitly like muttered to, you know,
to Colvin, like, oh man, one of those versions where they add in like way more fucking notes,
right? And she's like, she doesn't want to like offend all the fucking conservative fags hanging
out there, right? When it's like, I'm not like shouting, I'm just minding my own business,
right? What's really funny is that even though we're way far away from the stadium, you can only
just hear it in the distance, all the fucking conservative fags are like, oh, oh, I guess we're
supposed to stand right here and hold our hand to our hearts because it's within earshot, right?
So they're all standing and they're all facing towards the fucking stadium. Like, yeah, this is
just how it works. I guess it's like, yeah. And I'm just like, whatever, I wanted to back away
from this area. So I just start walking away like the opposite direction, right? Intimidate.
She she's not putting her fucking hand to her heart, but she's like standing still because she
feels like she doesn't want to like stand out too much, even though it's like, you know, it's like
four different people here, like I'm up against the side. I'm not like walking right through them,
like pushing them aside. I'm just like walking over to the side. And she's like all upset at me.
She's like, no, don't don't draw attention to yourself. I'm like freaking out about it's causing
drawing more attention. Just fuck, let me fucking not respect America in peace. God damn it. So
anyway, okay, last thing about the Lapitation, right? So there is this park that I used to live near
and had like a river. This is like a real small park, probably only an average of 15 people go
here a day. It's not very big. But if you go out into like the distance, you kind of go off the
beaten path a bit. There was like a river, a small little small little stream. And on the stream,
there is one part where there used to be some sort of concrete sidewalk bridge to get you from
one side to the other. This sidewalk has now crumbled apart. It's now in several pieces. And
the pieces are just sort of sitting there at various slightly tilted angles, as the water rushes like
beside them and on top of them. And it is the most aesthetic thing ever. There was one piece of
concrete in particular that you could just sit down and lean against and you're sort of leaning
at this 15 degree angle. And it's just big enough for you to sort of just sit there and be perfectly
dry as a stream surrounds and engulfs you and then you can whip out a book and be literally the
greatest intellectual in America. And it's like this was free. This was not planned. This was all
this is emergent gameplay and vastly better. You know, something that's always a huge pleasant
surprise. Wait, am I still there? Yeah. Okay. Sorry. The way everyone just went quiet at once and I
wasn't ready for it. Oh yeah. Like sometimes you walk into a KFC and they'll just have like a bench
with a fucking Colonel Sanders statue arm going across it. And that is just as important as Rome.
Every time I see one of those, I'm just like how are there not like 70 people lined up to
sit on this bench because this is the most exciting thing I've ever seen. It's redefining the meaning
of the word seduction every time I see one. I mean, there's there's lots of there's lots of just
crazy interesting weird shit that's just around cities that because it doesn't have the longevity
or the like the history behind it isn't paid attention to. But like when we used to go to
Baltimore for Brony Khan and Otacon like that the whole strip the there's there's like a sort of
touristy road that's just like the one road of Baltimore that's nice becomes a total shit fuck
you can walk down from the convention to this little like Harbor area you can walk down there
and you turn like left and immediately you are raped. It's like a TSA line. Guys.
And yeah, do you remember that black guy who came up to us?
I can remember like 70 black guys who've come up to be in Baltimore.
The one who was like upset that someone called them the n-word. Is that what you're referring to?
Yeah. Yeah. And then we all stood in a group around him and I think I filmed some of it where I
met up with you guys before we were friends and then and then and then you'd be part ways after
like 10 minutes and Ben was like oh well we should like drop him off at his hotel guys and you guys
were like okay and then I got it and I forgot to make a wrong turn so I had to do a U turn and
everyone was like a munchie get out of the car. Yeah, I remember that. Did you? I really like
when you brought up the Colonel Sanders thing. I don't think they have those around where I've
seen KFCs for a while. They're not common but I've seen a couple. They're probably fucking germ
magnets and considering it's KFC they're probably grease magnets but like think about this. Hold on
let me finish about Baltimore. Just that like right by the convention center there's this area
where there's like this this this very bizarre structure that's just got like a couple of water
falls and a bunch of just like walkways. Yeah. And because it's it's not quite on the sidewalk
and so it's just like no one even looks at it. Like it's a cool ass thing that you're meant to
walk through and like I because I found out about it I told all you guys about it and we checked it
out but like I you know you go there and you'll just see like hundreds of congoers passing by
and like no one's even checking this thing out and I'm like this thing is super cool and interesting
it's right here in the past. There's a there's footage of that thing in a t-bap takes brony
car as I recall yeah. I do think that video games that Dark Souls and other video games as the medium
is now called uh is it teaching people to do this or at least it's giving us the opportunity to learn.
It was in fact Fallout 3 playing that at 14 and made me realize oh yeah the lap dated
concrete actually looks just as cool as like a painting on average all things being equal right.
Every time that's wrong but to go back to McDonald's being uh like our culture and we we we we
fret so much about Rome right and every single painting that's been burned every single McDonald's
play a place all unique in the eyes of the Lord that gets demolished for health and safety reasons
is the fucking rape of our culture. It is a it is a destruction of the memories of what
the sort of Gen X to millennial transition represented and they're most they're largely
gone now and that is a travesty. Did I ever tell you people speaking of weird restaurants
of this one catfish restaurant I had an Obama room?
What was it?
Sounds good. Yeah please please tell us.
Happy birthday by the way for Obama. He turned 57 yesterday. Yeah.
Hashtag Obama day. Uh so when you say catfish restaurant.
By the time this comes out it I will have just turned 27 so happy birthday to you.
Oh yes. Happy birthday. It's my birthday.
I'm an old fuck. It's on Wednesday. Yeah so so okay so it's a catfish restaurant family owned
black family they have a fucking Obama room so one of their room one of the rooms in this building
it's just it's got a bunch of placards of things Obama did like a photo of him at his
like election. Remember when Obama freed the slaves? I heard about that. That was good.
And then like some other placard or you know like I don't I want to say oh yeah proof of
his birth certificate but I think I'm just making that up. They've got the birth certificate room
and the best part is they have a life-size cardboard cutout of him like standing in the middle
next to like a little tree. I can relate to that. So it's a 6 foot 2 Obama there and so I went up
and like my dad took a picture of me like with my hand over his shoulder and it is to this day
the best photo of me with the most sincere smile I've ever had on camera. It was my Facebook
profile for years I'll see if I could find it at some point. That's just what Obama does
he just inspires us. Even in death. Even in death, yeah.
All right I want to dredge up old topics because I didn't get to say my piece about them and I've
written them down. If I can souvenirs right the whole we're talking about like souvenirs for
getting it for the point of like you buy something because you think you're supposed to have a
souvenir of a thing and a lot of the time I mean my mom does do that sometimes. She went to
Barcelona or some other place with some of her girlfriends or whatever she asked me do you want
anything from there and I'm like I don't know anything about Barcelona. I don't know what you
can even get there. Bring me a pirate sword please. Bring me the people's election declaring
independence from Spain that was overturned by the federal government. Yeah bring me the original
document of that. Bring me back something from the point of Gibraltar. Oh wait. Wait what happened
there? It's not Spanish it's British. Oh right. We stole it it's English forever.
Anyway yeah she does that and you know I don't really care but you know sometimes she does come
back for something nice because she's got like she's got an eye for trinkets but my dad likes
souvenirs mostly I mean both of them do mostly just to be house decorations like they don't buy
things as souvenirs to like say oh look we went we got a keychain on a fridge magnet from this place
no they go and they go into the tiny little shops that are off the beaten path and and you know my
dad likes quiet places and those tiny streets you know away from the main like big like hey look at
all this stuff we all as like a family agree that it's much nicer to snake away to like a smaller
alleyway where there's less people and more locals and if you see enough locals at a bar you're like
okay that's a good place so we go there when we go to the markets there and we get like souvenirs
that just are good just like are like artistic nice little decorations for the house because they
have a house slash anime you know they are slash anime and they are like because they have a house
they are house they are homeowners they have a reason to buy things like that I don't I would
but now this is coming into another point I had which I was really interested in the way
DeVu was talking about like people go to all these places and there's no reason to do it they just
there's they don't have a purpose in life yeah I want to I want to take that opportunity to take
that info at that that idea that point and turn this podcast back into a Pokemon go
I got a ton of Mr. Mime in Italy and I'm gonna give it to you before Hippo can give it to you so
I know yeah I've got I've got authentic French Mr. Mime I've got a couple of those
how do you bust a Mime?
all right um Pokemon go is the way to have a souvenir um well it's it's a way to have a souvenir for
like a gamer that you know doesn't need things from actual real places you can take a picture
yes gamer yeah the only proper way to say it and it's like it's not just going to get a Pokemon
from a country because you know there's like the the region exclusive there's a few of those
and yeah this is the thing I had this idea the gym badges they've like I don't know when they
implemented them but there's this map that you can look uh that has a map of the world
like really low resolution but like you can see every gym you've like been to uh on the map
find that is that in the app yeah you go yeah you go to you you click on yourself you go to
your uh you scroll down to see all your um like medals and stuff and then there's your gyms and you
go to the the list of gyms and then there's like a thing on the bottom left and that's the map of
the world and all the gyms you've been to and I have like there's a there's a site called Pokemon
go map or something that just lists every poker stop and every gym in the world you go it's like
uses google maps and you just go scroll around you find where everything is and I had this idea
there it is I just found it that's fucking sick that I want I really want to like conquer the world
and be like the ideal world traveled well traveled man but because of Pokemon go because I
wouldn't actually actually I wouldn't actually go for any other reason so I want to I want to max
out like my gym badges I want to have every gym badge in the world which will take like a long time
but like it's it's just actually a reason for me to go to a real place other than to say oh I've
seen the lean tower pizza no I've seen I've seen all the the gym the poker gyms in that city actually
are you saying this whole thing all I can think is dude if you go to Italy and and use your EV
with authentic pizza it revolves into a Sicilian very nice by the way I can tell you right now I
didn't give a fuck about taking pictures lean tower pizza but you know what I did care about
yeah that's right I was getting the gym badge lean tower pizza check out this shit motherfucker
oh he did it it's great in this picture for some reason that's way cool and seen it in real life
oh yeah and it's in Italian it's in Italian that's that's authentic
the bees oh you know in you know why it's because it was something that took some
marginal amount of effort beyond the strength required to lift your phone and hit picture photo
button right I remember you know there there was actually one like hallmark level idea of a thing
you're supposed to do to be a real person that I think is pretty genuine it's a very specific one
it's climbing up a fucking hill or a mountain and then being up it and then looking out at the sky
right that is a real thing if you climb up a thing you actually actually did something if someone
took a picture of them having just climbed the leaning tower of pizza I would be far more impressed
why do you keep calling it pizza is it not the leaning tower of pizza it's pizza
for the next pisa are you kidding me right now no no this is a joke in like a wasn't there like a
whole cartoon about this probably it feels like a dexter's lab episode the leaning tower of a
spaghetti I just want to make sure we're all clear by the way going back to what we were saying
before about souvenirs I don't want to imply at all by by my railing against and and you know
agreeing with everyone else that I am against the idea of souvenirs I in fact love mementos and I
love having little trinkets and knickknacks that I can look at and and I have like a
gym and neutron brain blast and it's it's always earned as opposed to like just gain it for the
sake of gain it when it's an obligation actually jogs my memory there's something that I have
just come across like like that business card or something else like that to that effect
then it's far more impactful than actually I feel the memory more so than I would if I were
yeah by it's not a matter of me not wanting to have it's just a matter of me having the experience
and memory better from having something like I actually just yeah when it when it when it becomes
an obligation that's when it's it it feels inauthentic it feels like you remember thinking you had
to get something and you forgot what you were doing there and forgot the fun times you know what
what I like doing is I like yeah when I have like a receipt from a thing I put it in my pocket
sometimes I throw it away but sometimes I keep it I have a couple from radcon one and two and
three and I just I keep them in a drawer and eventually I might like make a scrapbook of
like all these receipts and like airplane tickets and stuff and concert things and be like oh yeah I
went to that at that date like is all the information I need yeah and I'll be like oh yeah you know what I
have I hold on the plane tickets no my turn damn it I haven't got to talk here's what I have to say
small point uh what I went to Hawaii I had no plans to buy anyone anything as I never do
but then Michelle was like hey why don't you buy your family gifts and I'm like
bitch what the fuck did you just say to me uh and then I was like that seems like a reason
so so I did uh and I have not yet to send I'm glad Ben's not here he's not getting spoiled
but uh I gotta send those bad boys out oh and while I was there the most important thing of all
is I bought myself a hoodie uh from the Polynesian Culture Center that says it on the thing it is
the most comfortable hoodie of all time that Polynesian Culture Center is run by the Mormons uh
and uh there's your fact of the day Mormons make good hood money back into the Dr. Wolf community
going back hard making a hard left turn that's right I want to quickly say it's it's not very like
super related that I I've been trying to tell us to say this that I haven't found a place to
interject necessarily like uh you're all talking about like urban stuff and and towns and cities
and whatnot but my my personal favorite place to go like vacation if I never do I never do but
if I were to go it would be like a forest and probably like a picnic in a forest or a field
and something I really really want to do before I leave this planet is like go stargazing like at
night be burn a forest in a forest or so like somewhere where there's not no any buildings
and no pollution there so you can see the stars bright because I keep seeing all these pictures
of so many stars in the sky and then I look up at the sky at night I was like where the hell are
I want to see them yeah you got city lights yeah yeah I don't know where you live in Lithuania but
I'm I'm I'm certain that there are places nearby that like you could get to relatively easily I guess
if you had a car like countryside but the thing is I'm alone and I'm scared to go dude get an
electric skateboard and Casey Neistat out there hell yeah that's the way I don't mind I don't mind
the idea of being alone and doing something like that I was on like again Pokemon go like haha but
like uh I was looking on Pokemon go map and I was looking at poker stops in London and following
the river Thames out towards the sea and then I was like curious like what does it look like when
you walk there how how when is the threshold of like because if you look at a map of of England
and you see the Thames go out to the ocean it it very slowly funnels out into the sea but there's
a lot of land left and right for a very long time so I'm like what what would it look like to go
there so I did the little google maps thing you drop the guy down you you walk along you know
move along with the on the path and I was just like what if I just walked all the way from London
down the river until I found us town and then I you know got a bus it could be a while it could be
like a day or two or like um or something but like it was just I just like the idea of doing
doing like like walking in one direction for a very long time and dying but like but without the
dying part you know hopefully yeah I'm too big of a we need to go alone I would like to go with
someone that is my boyfriend it's I mean going out at night and stuff is scary sometimes but like
I don't know you got a torch you just got to be strong I mean what the hell is one time like I
was I was in the countryside I was in the countryside and it was dark and it was like the
kind of countryside where you could see the stars a lot and I didn't bring a torch and I went for a
walk outside and I heard a horse in a nearby field I thought the gate was open and it was going to
kill me I couldn't see anything and I I peed my pants and ran home but like um yeah it is scary
to to go into places alone I guess but it's it's doable I also like about night time and walking
around in night time the air just smells different at night and I really like that sort of night
time smell of the night time because there's less cars night time is oh absolutely 110
percent better than the day you can't convince me otherwise it's perfect I'm a day boy and you
night fags need to check your shitty oh you think you're so special I'm a night owl it's not about
being special it's just about admitting get a nine to five you sacks of shit and it is about being
special because I'm special needs and I need that moonlight I need I need that isolation I can't
deal with all you fucking extroverted fucks with your jobs and your confidence and your money and
your success trajectory I can't deal with that the absolute best thing is when it's been like a
really hot day like it has been recently and like the the ground is like fucking scorching hot has
been boiled by the sun so like when night time comes around and it starts to cool off there's
like a lot of wind breezing around like the the temperature is changing rapidly and things are
like swooshing around you just walk in as a warm cool breeze it just it's just the perfect you can
go outside and shorts in the middle of the night I gotta say being up during the day for the last
month has been a huge problem because like yeah uh we we got onto a a great lifestyle regiment here
at the at the gecko estate where we've been waking up and every other day going straight to the gym
right after waking up and it's a great way to do things because we both have like problems with
insomnia and this cures that because if you just start the day like hitting the ground running and
you work all day you're fucking exhausted by night time the problem is yeah that when we started this
we were waking up at like six in the morning and neither of us wants to be up like neither of us likes
the day because first of all it's the middle of summer and it's a fucking 90 degrees out every day
and it's super fucking humid so it's it's too hot and when you wake up that early nothing's even
open that early like except for the gym so it's like you know you go to the gym and you're like
all right let's go get some food oh nowhere's open yet you know and just generally yeah going out at
night is way nicer because you can just walk and it's nice and cool and you don't even care if you
have to walk like an extra mile to get somewhere open because it's nice to walk a mile at night
during the day you're like let's go to the closest fucking place so i'm not sweating
you know 10 pounds by the time i haven't really been having to deal with this
fucking whole temperature thing ever since i moved to a desert where there is no fucking humidity
i know i've talked about this with all of you have i talked about it in an episode yet
i think you might okay well fucking humidity it's where all the actual discomfort from heat comes
from yes place where it's not it's like 98 degrees don't feel like shit yeah today's like the first
day that it's been hot and not that humid and it was pretty okay but like for the most part it's
been shit especially in veneziaans this was a fucking oh my god the weather in veneziaans was
terrible i mean the i mean that makes sense because it's a fucking waterlogged city yeah i've
literally not yet this whole time i've been living here had a single day where i walk out and i'm like
i don't want to go out it hasn't been yet and i went i just bared the entire brunt of july so
i think it's pretty cool i've been suffering for the last month i guess now i know why because
the humidity because like this the first month when i got here like um what's after me the month
june yeah june there you go yeah sorry i was thanking lefina for a moment okay so yeah june
was was fine and then like i guess the humidity hit and like i've been suffering and if it wasn't
for this little fan i have in my room right now i'd be suffocating right now and it's just like
i couldn't even sleep for a few days until i realized i have the fan and it was like terrible
awful and like for the last few days i haven't even turned on my pc because it was just so bad
and the pc added to the sheets i just i just i just couldn't do anything
you know i think i think i'm quite a tough little cookie because because because we don't have ac in
this house and it is humid and it is like really hot and well it's not just it's just not a thing
it's not a san diego or anything in london no no no it's it's like uh some sort of degrees
you can look it up yeah um but like it's humid and it's high heat wavy and it's like you don't
want to be on a train in with a crowded people you don't want to go to that london 79 degrees right
now he's that's pretty warm that's pretty warm yeah so but like um i i'm right now i'm in my room
i close the window obviously because to stop uh sound coming in and it's a sweltering in here
it's gonna be like sweaty i'm sweating up a storm but i feel okay because i'm used to this because
i'm i'm you know i'm uh i i don't complain a lot a lot of times pain happens to me and i'm like
okay all right i'll do it i'll i'll i'll i'll settle for this and if and later i'll i'll be like
i'll i'll be like i'm now i'm stronger for having dealt with it instead of
doing anything about it which is stupid really the warmth and i prefer heat over coldness like if
i had to choose between this weather and freezing cold i would choose this weather anytime of the day
but sure i mean i would do the same uh my car uh does not have ac and just yesterday i got the
oil change and attempted to get them to like repair the ac stuff uh they said it could not be done
without like major like it was the thing of like they refill the antifreeze or whatever
they they can't do it requires like a serious upgrade my car is very old um so i'm just not
going to do it and that's fine uh but i just i've been able to drive for years now with this car
with no ac and that's been fine uh but and so like in that way yes i i'm over caring about being
comfortable while driving but and i just roll the windows down whatever but in my house so i i just
moved into my new place has central air and it is incredible it is unbelievable it is a huge
massive life upgrade uh it's also like sunnier it's just such a quality of life improvement and
all these new rooms and stuff the eight months i spent the eight months i spent living in digi's
house was the only eight months since childhood i had adequate central air conditioning for both
heat and cold um i i'm just over here like so suddenly fuming with rage thinking about the
fact that like all of the best built cities are in places with shit weather and the only place in
the whole world that i've ever heard of having consistently good weather is the west coast of
the united states not and i i mean hawaii is quite nice but you know hawaii as well and like
certain places like near the equator i guess but like sure the west coast like la is like known for
its good weather and and i'm just sitting here wondering like why is it that la has to be the
shittiest fucking city imaginable i believe i've heard some people theorize that nice weather
the good one went there right well yeah i've heard i think i've heard some theories talk about how
the lack of bad weather means that like that the human innovation and hard work gumption gene
like deactivates and then everyone becomes shitty because it's so easy to live that's what hawaii is
100% like that everyone's just like hey man it's the island time relax man we're also jamaica don't
worry about it i don't know who's fucking deceive you do they don't they don't care about anything
so much they don't even care that they also just are jamaica that's how little they say yeah as a
local who who goes to la very regularly and has been to la very recently in an expo i can
guarantee you that the weather there is fucking terrible and it's absolutely a bit that's like
what they're what what they're known for is having good weather i've never heard that before in my life
it's always so hot it might be a little more as a local when i was in anime expo it was a hundred
and like seventeen on ironically it was way too hot like when we were at an expo it was insanely hot
yeah all right defined good defined good weather because when something is like
rather hot i don't like it i prefer cloudy weather i prefer uh you know a potential rain
good weather in no humidity and 70 to 75 degrees like yeah like the literal ideal for humans like
nice breeze rolling in clear blue skies it's about 70 or so degrees there's no
like bad to be oh i'm grumpy i don't know right now here's here's no no clear blue skies are nice
but that they that to me as an english man they feel like a holiday thing when i see a clear blue
sky i'm like i don't need to work it's really funny you say that like when i was watching doctor who
i like every time they show london i was like god that is the most depressing city in the
fucking world it's all right i agree sometimes like overcast skies can feel depressing and a
lot of americans who come to to england they see all the the clouds and they're like oh
fuck but like there's so much it's so it's it's hard to explain i think it's like you think of like
the sky is like a canvas it's like a clear canvas it's blue it's nice um clouds are like the the
painting stuff like you see like old paintings of clouds and they're always like puffy and cool
and the lights bouncing off them in interesting ways and then i look up sometimes and i'm like
that's a painting i'm looking at the most beautiful thing i've ever seen and the only reason i can see
that is because clouds are there to like um to make interesting shapes i'm like i would
always prefer clouds over clear blue 75 percent pictures of cool looking clouds so i do understand
that but uh i'm telling you i think you're i think you're a little bit of uh of um what's it called
when someone kidnaps you and like and you like it Stockholm syndrome yeah Stockholm syndrome like
because it seems to still i don't i don't believe that that can even happen i'm just used to it it's
not it's not that i like bad weather i just don't think it is bad weather when the when the sky is
completely white when you know no but you just have a different definition of bad weather i live in
in this that's what i'm saying you know what i'm trying to say is that as a human being there is a
type of climate that should be like like that should be just optimal for everybody don't we all
have stockholders syndrome then not quite i mean the reason why for example white people are white
is because they exist in europe where there was more cloud cover so they didn't need the kind of
people are a mistake okay like well aren't whiteness whiteness is Stockholm syndrome via evolution
like evolution via Stockholm syndrome it's like we we went okay white people made the
leaning tower of pizza you motherfucker yeah that should lead to that it's fucking leaning
is it me or is the leaning tower of pizza like us just literally a gist a big celebration of failure
like i mean maybe i mean let's look at the i think it's just very funny those egyptian
kangs those pyramids are not deviating one millimeter they are dead centers straight
up except i need to i need to say my piece about like the weather don't talk about the pyramids we
didn't make them that's all aliens i refuse to believe otherwise and i saw from all right the
islands are super white they're like the whitest possible yeah the ultimate the ultimate ubermensch
is fucking the ultimate uber driver the aliens the great ones they can drive for thousands of
monchi what's the big what is the uh the big disc called that's supposed to make the pyramid
turn into the spaceship oh it's just the love battleship it's just the love battleship it's
the love battleship that's what it is all right fucking i i i have to say my piece because you
can't like i don't right cloudy weather is not always like good obviously i'm not saying that i
like it when it's fucking wet and cold and miserable i'm saying that clouds are good and when
the cloud is when the sky is like completely white it sort of feels like a blanket and i like it
because there's no harsh rays there's no burning but it's not cold either it's just sort of i agree
it's peaceful you can just sort of you can just sort of live and it's just nice i hate cloudy weather
i don't think it's stockholm syndrome that's all i'm saying i don't like rain either okay the reason i
was calling it that and it's not about you specifically but i wanted i was going to breach
that out to the english attitude in general like the way that englishmen sort of major cox the way
the englishmen sort of portray themselves in the way that they're perceived stereotypically
is something that seems like people from a place where it's overcast all the time all right that
would explain the classic english phrase she caught a gun i which can't be helped well i mean
and granted a lot of my english stereotypes come from yatsi and how he portrays england and himself
and the cloudy weather as all kind of the it's a maelstrom of this attitude and and i and i love
england i think it's great yeah stockholm syndrome i mean yatsi is the guy who left england i don't
i don't get what you're oh yeah what's gonna do i'm saying that the human race here's what i'm
trying to say is that when we when we left africa and expanded outwards we had to play a lot of
mental gymnastics we had to play a lot of mental gymnastics as we went around the world to try to
convince ourselves that it was okay to live in shitty places like america we came here and almost
everyone died instantly like the diseases were so fucked this the the land was just not good for
living on in the way we wanted to so basically everyone died why are you trying to say that the
united states is not full of bountiful fertile land is that what you're trying to say to me right
i i think what did he's trying to say is that he wishes he was black well that's there are some
scientists they're starting to die like but specifically in african tribesmen and and have
never left africa and everyone who isn't african has stockholm syndrome since everyone's talking
about uh since everyone's talking about fucking going on vacations to famous places we went to
the most hilarious tourist attraction in the world recently because we live in boston which is near
plymouth rock have any of you been to plymouth rock nate you've been there sure have it's
fucking hilarious isn't it because there's nothing there i mean it's just the first of all it's just
a rock it's just like a regular sized boulder with a with a big stamp on it that says like uh 1687
or whatever um but the funniest part is that the like plaques and stuff next to it all say that it
is supposedly the rock they don't know that the pilgrims landed at so like no one even knows what
the fuck it is and there's all these like stupid souvenir shops and you're by it it's it's it's
very transparently corny and dumb out in the uh since it's out in the elements wouldn't have
been decayed by now no they've got it up on well they've got it up on a platform like it's elevated
above the water like they've got it like they still be rained on and winded on and no it's
it's in a it's in a building it's only been like 400 years that's not that long there's like a
gazebo over it it's like i'm looking at pictures and it just it still seems like it'd be still too
exposed to not be corroded eventually but okay well they've got it under a gazebo and like on a
lifted platform and like there's a guy there who every 15 minutes gives like a little speech about
the rock and he talks about how apparently it once was like a huge tourist attraction and like
presidential candidates would like take pictures of themselves next to the rock and shit and like
yeah but like it actually has because of the fact that it is so lame it has totally lost that
reputation and now nobody cares about it anymore that's a tiny baby rock i thought there was like
a massive monument like there's just a regular ass rock that has a fucking number on it but um
they the guy was telling us a story about how like when when they got there that first winter
they dwindled down to like yeah like 10 women were left alive so like they had to repopulate
everything from like 10 women that they had maybe it was less than that it was something like eight
eight or eight to 10 women that were still alive like they came to america and everyone fucking
died instantly and they like barely hung on like half of them died this is an unironically
problematic worldview that you're disposing right now i feel unironically twigger it's not well
here's the thing here way before that no virginia was colonized long before the pilgrims got here
okay it was colonized or was it just people lived here well they those are kind of the same thing
but i mean they had set up you know camps and villages and in virginia which was the first like
massachusetts not like i know this name i'm from virginia i had to learn virginia history eight
different times but those people did not all die i mean i'm sure some of them came over on a
land bridge from fucking from russia it went back when it was connected way back in ancient times
they adapted to live here over time and they slowly expanded because the only reason we expanded
across the earth was either because there were too many people for the amount of resources or
ideological differences like the reason we came to america like the pilgrims the uh the the ones
who came to plimoth they were running from religious persecution like they were okay with
putting up with living in a shit place that they were not meant to live because it meant that they
got to have a different type of lifestyle but and they were just brave enough to fucking deal
with the amount of death i just have i just have an issue with like the idea that i'm like the people
who live here have stockholm syndrome when we have lived here for so long that we have acclimatized to
this thing and every time i go to a hot country i am sick and i feel terrible all the time yeah
adaptations just evolutionary stockholm syndrome that's what i'm trying to say that's literally
okay it just the stockholm syndrome has a very like like persecuti connotation like you have a
fucking mental disability i don't think of it that way i don't think you can get a stockholm syndrome
by just being home like are you being that's so silly that's a silly thing i mean they're just
being a larger point okay you're just trashing english in general first of all let's define
stockholm syndrome is just when you are when you convince yourself that something is good so that
you can deal with it no it's like when you're being held against your will in a thing let's say
yeah a situation against your will but then like to make it okay in your head to be born on earth
is to be in a situation that was against your will nobody decided to be born that's changing that's
change it that's that's i wish i was trying to just be born that's where you want to live in the
world so that is a very high cost to like move i move yes i understand that you grow up in the
culture you're born into and you will immediately develop a deep saw stockholm syndrome for the
entire culture you live in like people are constantly reinforcing the values of the system you were born
into i think the only problem i have with what you're saying is that there's there's this implication
there's this implication that um the grass like quantifiably like absolutely is always greener
and you will never actually have like any good like you will never live in a good place ever
it's only stockholm syndrome the reason that you like the place i gotta say between this always
should be a better place which i kind of agree with it's just a weird way of saying it that's
what makes it funny in what made why i said it yeah that's okay let's see i'm remembering the last
like month or so like things you've been on about you've had finding the code of the universe
you have like all arts about finding the expression and now it's like every like the optimal human
condition i feel like you're sort of at step one of becoming a hitler because you're like defining
human experience right anti hitler and then i'm trying one step two i thought well step two would
be writing a book all about your worldview oh shit all right hold on we have to understand here
i'm not saying stockholm syndrome is a bad thing or a problem i have stockholm syndrome for america
like i'm just saying that to be raised in a society is to be programmed you are not making a conscious
decision to be the person you are you were created to be this person you were developed to be this
person you you learned all the pure thing you've ever brought onto the show as far as i've heard
yeah which is why i agree with it yeah it's pretty obvious i think i think i'm just saying like
obvious normal shit about how psychology works but you you just said it in an abrasive way that may
give uh you know not on board i mean i i don't i there's no way i can disagree with the idea that
we the only reason we do anything is because of outside influence and there is no real self kind
of sort of but like i just don't see the point of ever bringing that up because it doesn't have any
bearing on anything the idea is what are you supposed to do about it essentially is that let's
say like people came to london and they went oh the weather here is kind of shit but we can build
our own city here and it's good enough and then eventually people adapted to where they're like
like okay with that but like that's that just means that that is like a it's a new breed of human
this this human that's adapted to live in london and their personalities kind of reflect that
it's like the english attitude is a product of having moved to england like having moved humanity
there and like so it's a sort of it's a sort of several generations there's way more to it than
just like where we decided to settle down because there was like hundreds of years of war and like
people took over england and yeah and i'm just i'm oversimplifying this for the sake of explaining
why i would use the phrase stockholm syndrome just simply that like tom said earlier i'm just saying
adaptation to an environment is like when human race came to be in the fertile crescent it was
because this is a place that would spawn humans like this is a place that hey you know like this
is this is the natural result of being in this area and then we went oh let's go other places
and those places were shit but we got used to it you know and why do you think that it's not
so inconvenient or shit that it is cloudy a lot like i don't think that i don't think that's so
i'm just saying it's it's it's not that it's super unnatural it's just slightly different but like i
don't like that you're mixing people adapting to stuff with stockholm syndrome it's just why i don't
know it doesn't sound right it sounds right to me it feels like there's a different word that you
could be using yes sort of makes sense but you can't it's really funny yeah i'm surprised it's got
everybody's laugh and i'm human i'm raging here it's funny especially because i use the phrase
stockholm syndrome all the time it's just like one of my favorite phrases to accuse things it's my
favorite new song i didn't know that was a new song i take offense because i'm fat and i hate hot
weather and i want to be in england because it's really cold all the time it's not cold i thought
you're about to say i'm fat and i hate hot women no it's not it could be raining here according to
my boyfriend but can we get back to traveling traveling's way more funny i want to say i want
to say that i hate cloudy weather because i'm very uh i'm very affected by the weather for some reason
cloudiness makes me moody you're an evolutionary stockholm syndrome it all makes sense indigo
and also child and wait she's not in the same way mage does actually i i get headaches when it rains
and when the when there's like i don't have pressure from i do think of cloudiness and raininess as
just a thing like the atmospheric climatologic kick uh embodiment of depression and the more
depression you have the more rain uh matches your mood and even when you're not depressed you have
depressive moments you know moments where things feel low and down and if that happens to synchronize
with uh some some overcast i think that actually fits pretty nicely i remember just it just makes
sense it makes sense to me because pink floyd told me that living on in quiet desperation was the
english way and that's all i know about them but no i distinctly remember there was actually a day
the the very specific day i kicked depression and like became like marginally functional on that
particular axis which was a day in which it had been overcast and i was like um yeah overcast i
always feel better when it's overcast and then i just sort of like had a moment at like two o'clock
where i my depression was broken and then the sun came out and i'm like the sun's out i feel good
about this wait hold on guns out my divu says i've never i've never been happy that the sun
came out before i'm free i'm cured i don't get it but cool yeah teach me teach me how it's uh all
you gotta do is you gotta go into the clouds you gotta you gotta you gotta look at the clouds
right you gotta see a cloud that looks like a mountain and you gotta get your hiking gear and
you gotta climb that mountain and then when you get to the top of the cloud you realize that it's
not physical and you gotta fall and die and that's what actually what happened with me was that i
listened to i for like the 79th time that week the fucking version of you're gonna go far kid
that sped up to sound like rainbow dash and that gave me oh my god forever what whoa that sounds
like an experience uh all right i gotta go dig up that youtube video and put it on repeat for
like a week hashtag join yeah i may be cured and so for the last six years now i've been cured and
i have now only 12 other metaphysical fucking disorders i can see now divu how did you cure
depression rainbow dash um all right that's a true story for a lot of people we're the only person
would not i was gonna say i know true story for me i didn't fucking make that shit up story for
amazing yep ten out of ten i have i have a thing to say regarding to weather but also travel
and that i have also gone uh on a on a week long thing um i won't get into what i was doing we
could save that for another episode because this one how long has this been going on it got a bit
well i'll get we'll get into that next time maybe um but um it was a camp and it was rainy like
extremely rainy like i got off the coach i was like okay it looks a bit cloudy looks like it might
rain i'd better set up my tent immediately and as soon as i got like the tent poles out
fucking torrent of rain wind almost blew everything away i just had to lie on my tent to stop it from
blow you know blowing away i got drenched all my clothes got drenched i'm like okay i'm fucking
you your favorite fiddler cunt weather cunt of a weather and i was like and i was like okay i'm
putting it up and it's like fine oh shit this week's gonna suck it's so fucking rainy and windy and
cold and bad and i don't like it and then uh day two less rainy uh like uh it was like a mist of rain
constantly falling throughout the day but it was just all like you walk out and there's not you can't
really feel the raindrops unless you hold your hand at your palm up and it's like oh yeah there is
rain but it's just sort of a mist and that was okay but it's still cold and i don't like it but then
third day it comes back like the the sunny weather comes back that was like heat waving london the
whole time uh and and was like okay yeah it's now now we've had the rain and we got the sun
the the camp feels way better than if it had been sunny the entire time because the sun was like quite
powerful throughout the last few weeks before leading up to this and i was like if this is gonna
be like a scorching hot camp i'm gonna die there's only so much you can do you could put the sunscreen
maybe have an umbrella with you to to block the sun rays but like it's just you're gonna die but
the the fact that we had like terrible weather the first couple days and then like kind of great
weather for the for the rest it was just sort of everyone's spirit was lifted and it was just it
was just really nice and i i just i love variety in weather i love changing weather and i love england
for having fucking wild mood swings in weather variety it always has like either you know we
have snow here we have heat waves here we have torrents and hurricanes and and but like really
lovely summers sometimes it's just like and sometimes winter is hot it's like it doesn't make any sense
but i enjoy i enjoy the variety that it provides that's what virginia is like as well who's side
right now by the way on on the very small subject of sunscreen did you know you fucking white pigs
that ethnics are immune to sunburn i didn't know where i've never even like realized that like oh
that's a real thing that can happen it's not just in cartoons uh until someone was like why aren't
you putting on sunscreen i'm like you have to put on sunscreen like that's a real thing that's not
just a joke that people say you have to do because you can just walk outside when you're an ethnic
like me and it doesn't even matter you just don't it doesn't even like the sun does not affect you
whatsoever all i have to say about that is case in point law case in i have a oh oh by the way
hippo i want to visit england really bad we should have like a like a like a jimmy you try like jimmy
timmy power hour all right if i was thinking this if there's like ever a london pokemon go event
uh that's a very easy excuse for me to go and excuse for you to go to have like a thing i want
to i want there to be a jimmy we could we could explore specifically event a jimmy balka con
oh there are anime cons in london that would be nice i i've always wanted the three
funnily enough idly is not is not one of the european countries that i really wanted to visit
the most i've wanted to visit germany paris and england a lot but i'm really afraid that if i go
to england everyone will aggressively hate me why why okay okay because people aggressively hated me
and in italy i can only imagine it'll be more significant in england because i will be american
and they'll fucking like want to jeer at me like no like no matter what i do i don't think that that
is some validity to the idea that english people are cucks um like like we're just downtrodden
we're down and we're like uh everything sucks no no i'm just saying like like it's not it's not
completely unfounded i don't mind it because it doesn't really matter um because we just you know
you do what you do and you don't have to be the life of the product you know you just you just dab
on the head keep calm and dab on the head and like like seeing a big big funny fluffy mexican man
like you coming in and being low like ooh like like ooh uh they're gonna be like they're gonna
give you some funny looks but they're not gonna do anything especially in london people in london
are like the most anti-social people of all time they're always doing anything but looking at anyone
when they see me in orange color coming to their world of gray colors they'll be like oh who's this
and then it'll be like a disney movie they'll have a lot of good color design yeah yeah you'll you'll
touch the the river tens and it'll turn into sand it'll be like ratty fucking scorpi blue and i'll
like breathe i'll be bringing the color back to england and i'll have to touch everyone like that
like that fern golly movie yeah exactly with the green thumb makes everything green yeah it's
actually a perfect segue into something a big speech i want to say so give me the room get the
get off the stage i'm pushing you off the stage right now hippo you're in a wheelchair and i've
dumped you out you're now fucking gonna be there oh no i've fallen and i'm i'm okay with it i've been
such immense satisfaction from coming off as the one tourist who cares whenever i have the
opportunity to like speak italian like like broken italian that i've rehearsed from google translate
or like frequently peacock my cursory understanding of italian history to my tour guys i feel like
it's something akin to like the god orgasm like lsd like you know 12 pounds something like that uh
like like people okay okay people say you should learn history because like oh those who don't
learn from history are doomed to repeat it or a lot of your reason like that that's pussy shit
that doesn't even matter it's not even true here's what i think you should learn about history when
you're in venice and you're on some fucking fish or price baby's first guided tour and which has
some desensitized native venetian fuck who clearly hates you and all of your cultural
colonizing ilk is going through these state mandated motions as quickly as possible because the
tourist population outnumbers the native population 60 to one that's not a joke that's actually real
60 to one that's the actual uh uh tourist population to name a population of venice it's
fucked up uh and he's just trying to pump out these walking tours like a fucking brood mare
and well and and you know offhandly while going through the motions you know saying history like
oh here's where someone died oh here's where a prostitute had sex you know stuff like that
and you know you offhandedly mentions italian unification and all of your fat disgusting
slob american pigs slightly think uh uh what do you mean it says at idly wasn't always idly there
were other things before idly and you can swoop in and go ah yes good sir you mean the process of
resurgimento and then his fucking jaw his fucking jaw his jaw dropped so far that smashes into a
rocketing skyward erection with such awesome power precision that surfaces a miniature parkour
collider and right then and there the atom is split the entire city is enveloped in a radiative
and you'll remember this one and say thanks munchie people like me now and i'm also dead
all you gotta do is mention that dude seriously aren't i fucking wrongly after that tour the guy
i went to him was like hey where's the good restaurant around here and for fucking kid
men it's straight unironically not in second life not new pets not webkins in real life this guy
for ten minutes was like no one knows what a surgeon meant to us no every italian knows i
you know walk up to them and say what's a surgeon meant to and they say oh yes it's like this but
no american this is the first time in 10 years everyone's ever said that word to me you are an
american you know the the fucking school you know the sky is blue the grass is green you understand
i will suck out the great now two dollars two dollars three dollars once at the north for free for
free for free yes i come to london it's just a relation but i don't get on youtube but now i have
all the knowledge power exactly right it's that simple it's it's actually true it's real it's
fucking and also you get like a better like especially in idly like if you know shit about
time history like you can understand what the monuments are there's a giant fucking like like
unbelievably big mine like like like it's i mean i guess it's the same size as like the
link in mind or something but instead of like having like the outside building just be like
columns and stuff that just is you know you can go inside and see the actual monument the entire
building is one big statue would have to like the centerpiece of like the link in mind but for like
the first uh king of idly but on the outside there's just a ton of like you know marble statues
engraved into it if you like know what that is it's way more impressive like like you know you
can just be like you just walk by it's just oh it's just some big fucking marble but if you
know the history the guy victor amen well and you and you know what the fuck you did you know about
the process of resurgimento then you can fuck you have more appreciation for things around you
and it's impressive and you were you were tapping into what i what i was thinking of when we were
going on and on about this this stupid like slap dash get the cred that you went to x y and z
important monuments and then just get the fuck back yeah yeah you yeah you just you just touched
all your bases is that to take in to really appreciate the advanced fucking detailed architecture
you don't just you shouldn't just go there be there take a selfie eat some fucking dip in dots
ice cream of the future and then go back to americaville like what you should do is just stay
there for a month and then just sit on a bench looking at all the architecture and then pull out
a book and learn all the context behind these buildings and when they were built and actually
do something productive and and like have a fun time that way and then just spend like a total of
like 35 man hours staring at that building off in the distance as you read your book and and really
soaking it in and feeling the dark souls within you you know what was the best thing i could have
feasibly done at well in idly and it improved my trip tremendously it was not only good for
like just like memory jogging and like being able to appreciate the details but it was so good for
my art is i sketched all of the monuments are things that i liked a lot so i so when i thought
something you know i want to get a picture of this i didn't take a picture of it i pulled out my
sketchbook and i started to draw as well as i could and then that way i get a more like it like
intimate understanding of the details of it because you know i gotta draw oh yeah you know i'm practicing
dry yeah the the last time well the the only time i went to Florence was on like an art trip thing
it was like a college thing it was like uh part of the tuition fee was uh we'll take you to Florence
and you can see the art galleries and all that cool shit and i was like uh fucking sick cool so i
went there and it was like i it you know i brought my journal with me i think it was the first time
i used it and i had like a lot of time to sketch buildings and and architecture and
paintings in galleries and i'm like i i drawing stuff from life i know people say if you want
to get better drawing you need to draw from life you need to do it but like people don't say that
it is really cool and makes you appreciate things like people never say that they say if you want
to be able to draw anime boobies you have to draw from life that's what is that's the end goal anime
boobies all the time like it i would rather learn how to draw buildings really well yeah there's just
so much better i drew so many fucking buildings it was it absolute blast it was incredible i loved it
yeah dude like and for the two of you listening to this podcast who aren't wannabe artists you
can take any profession by taking inspiration from life you can bring an artistic mindset into
anything i remember watching the fucking vox video about uh like the newer generation of japanese
bullet trains which like take their aerodynamic design inspiration from like the wingspan of
owls and like the smooth floppy belly of penguins and like there's a certain kind of bird that's
really good at diving into the into the water and they like they took inspiration from its beak
to like design their bullet train to sift through the air faster that's fucking engineering oh yeah
i love i love robots based on the classic scene in any action like sci-fi movie where like the
character is like thinking how do i solve the mystery and then like something happens in his
house or like he sees a thing outside that makes him think exactly that's what i need to do to
solve the problem in an abstract way in which i creatively thought of that's codes uh you ever
seen those like those those robots uh that are like um like centipedes like each segment can move
on its own but when you connect them they can move like a centipede yeah once or twice i think i i
love and then there's like um uh like dragonfly robots that like they just they take things from
nature and they try to turn them into robots so that basically you can just have a pet dragonfly
and you can have it drop out in bombs if only if you want if you want to do that remember in uh
laputa how like the the weird flyers that they use flew like dragonflies as opposed to like uh
you know guys i've got an idea for radcon six and it will call it whoa is that what we're doing
we'll call it well i mean you know when we get to number six uh it'll be radcon 60 it'll be radcon
666 and the joke will be that we were gonna call it radcon 66 because the premise is that we would
be driving down route 66 except we won't do it on route 66 instead we'll follow a random train
a random a random abandoned uh railroad through all of uh some part of western america because
all along the railroad tracks we're so sick like that all along the railroad tracks in in the west
are ghost towns everywhere because back back when they built the railroads they built all these
towns around the railroads like thinking oh railroads are fucking the center of commerce
and then as soon as we invented cars railroads were completely fucking worthless and a lot of
those towns were abandoned and so there is no tourist shit there it's just super fucking
interesting history everywhere of crazy ass abandoned towns where you can go and just do
anything are you saying that that we should get one of those like like you push one side you pull
the other like one of those like squeaky things get the whole crew on that now that's a good idea
but i just want to point out if we skip out on the calling it radcon 66 we can't do an epic joke
where you put uh execute radcon 66 you know when you enunciate that you made the audio sound different
because you knew that yeah because it would be my voice dubbing over it is what it would be
like that's the only joke you could do with 66 whereas you could do a million jokes with 666
like it's an enormous wellspring of digi i thought that joke you were going to do was yeah radcon
6 known as radcon 3 in america that's a good dude i totally think that would be the one where we
go to japan where we don't stay anywhere it's just a travel log and that's how we get all of the
content and that's sort of what i was that's what i was imagining with that it would be like a it
would be a big road trip through the american heartland because the main the main reason why i
would have uh like trepidations about go of doing the true american dream fallout irl is that it is
kind of dangerous and i can't respawn in real life and so the only reason that i'd be trepidation i
have trepidation about nuking america and starting a post apocalyptic world because you know i mean
there's some downsides but if it's in a group and there's nine strong severely autistic men
binding their powers no and they'll be afraid of us we got that season strength that's true
we would be the gang of super mutants wandering the land i just want to if we do if we do get one
of those train things where you push and pull will be jacked by the end that's true i think we're
probably about to wrap up right now before or really you know the the talking about this section
i just want to mention that it i don't want to hear fucking a single word out of any of you
foreigner pieces and shit being like oh americans are so fucking patriotic i can't stand it and then
you have a nervous breakdown when you go to fucking idly and there's this in the center of town it's
called the altar of patriotism and no matter where you fucking stand there's always a tricolor within
your fucking prayer for you vision tongues are so fucking like like it's just that building is bad
i know it's that what a tourist try do you want to hear about being patriotic but not that much
you want to hear about being patriotic though what's that again i want to hear about being patriotic
and the thing that you can literally get fined if you don't raise your flag during special holidays
well it's not a problem by the way i don't have a problem with people i i don't have a problem
seeing the italian tricolor because it's fucking history and it's important and i like it but i don't
want to hear anyone be like oh america and then fucking shitting themselves that the reason the
reason well i think the reason american patriotism is made fun of is because it feels tacky like look
at that building that is fucking sick look america doesn't have buildings like that if you go to dc
no it's fake it's just a it's just cardboard cutouts it's a bro bro bro bro bro bro bro bro
bonas all the way down to a lady gaga concert in washington dc we were just ran like literally
wandering random sidewalks and it looked like anor londo like what the fuck is going on everything
is taller than life and bigger than god it's it's just it's a it's an underdog mentality 100% like
the reason why americans being proud of america isn't like it's because we're too good it's because
we're too powerful and the same reason why nobody wants to hear white people going on about being
proud about being white it's because like all right guys we get it uh please stop you know this
is embarrassing uh you know it would not a good look no i'm not making anybody real comfortable
here with with this talk here uh even though it is in fact fine to be white and to think that it's
yeah 75 years from now when we're living neck deep in the china apocalypse uh everyone every
fucking person around the world is going to be able to go uh yeah remember the american era you know
and shit like everyone eventually probably yeah you know in in that sense um thinking that black
pride is okay is kind of racist because you're belittling the people who you know in a way it is
in a way black people are lesser so they can have their pride dude i recently watched it's sort of
that bigotry of low expectations it's that it's in that ballpark it's not ballpark i recently
watched a video called how africa is becoming china's china which is that now that china is
becoming less poor it's now more difficult for them to be the sweatshop zone so they're turning
africa into the sweatshop zone in exchange for votes and that sounds like that sounds like progress
to me i know right the whole world's leveling up we're all going one i know right so that's
capitalism for you baby there it goes there it goes and then eventually every country will be rich
enough and now who's going to make our fucking like plastic toys and things that like you press
these little pimples and you put them on the floor and they pop back up the mole man those inferior
mole man below the surface of the earth oh i was thinking child labor but before i well i mean
ideally we'll get to a point where the people at the top have enough money that they don't need to
rely on this as the only way to make money you know something like that but who knows but i
want to talk about still i think we should probably i mean i mean what else are we gonna
say here do you want to say you want to save a bunch of the shit like hippo you want to save
your camping trip stories for next time um i mean i do because i feel like it will spiral into a
long conversation about stuff okay next time did you hear we gotta fucking talk about city playing
because i have a lot of thoughts about going to roam i'm gladly hey i have a quick aside uh i just
wanted to give everybody an update from something that we talked about in the last episode this is
technically the post main topic review period i did canonically uh uh there this so i let me
huel everybody i did in fact get huel i've been drinking it for like a week now one meal a day
as as is recommended and then after a week you can go up to two meals a day uh so this morning
i just went for a run uh did some pokemon going came home got my huel on and it was a lovely
experience isn't it fucking dope it's it is it's great i really like it it doesn't even taste bad
right i read a bit about huel and they yeah to put it in nicer words you can't have your regular
bowel movements oh what that is mage is when you make a hard turn and you you massively adjust your
diet to start doing huel immediately yeah like you're because your gut bacteria has adjusted the
kind of diet you've been eating up to that point it can cause an issue just like you're a vegetarian
for a long time and then you eat me to follow up on uh since the whole reason we pushed the show
back was to address comments and we've like never done it uh someone from canada was saying that
they really want to be a post food boy and drink huel but apparently because of the fact that canada
considers it a meal replacement in their laws and and and not as a supplement or whatever
there's like it needs to have a certain minimum amount of vitamin d that it doesn't reach and so
it's it's to tariffs are too high or something so they don't send it to can i remember one
advertise itself as a meal replacement right that's the problem i mean it absolutely does but i mean
these are just legal technicalities as to what it's classified as i want to put out a hit list
for anyone who drinks huel they are anti-culture anti-american anti-human what is it i am i am
across the board anti-culture 100% i want to be closer to huel is a drink that is a meal like
it's like just a meal and a drink basically and it's like everything you need
yep yeah and it's great it's literally living off of it for most of his meals
ever since ever since i first i know i mentioned this a long time ago but ever since i first saw
the matrix and there was that that clip in the matrix where they have their food and the the
like the the the the handsome black fellow just squirts out a little bit of juice for neo and
he's just like there you go everything your body needs and they were all like ew gross i don't
want that and i was like everything my body needs yes please sign me up that's all i want
fuck food fuck cooking i hate it here's the one thing i do have stock home syndrome okay
is food right yeah you all do you all do release i find that disgusting mostly because i i i have
like lived my life thinking man i really better get good at good at cooking i see people who make
good food my dad makes good food i like good food i like fools i watch cooking shows i want to do
that and then to suddenly be you know there's an option like now you don't need food i'm like
you're the same people who like who you know as soon as like i learned how to do a skill it's now
like defunct like now i have to have have done a computer science degree and now my other degrees
are useless like fuck off i'll just keep doing it i don't care there was another comment on the
last video that uh that that was funny where he was basically criticizing everyone for just like
so out of hand being like fuck cooking because he was like cooking's fun and it's cool and it's a
thing to do and i like it and uh and i but i thought he was specifically talking about
Nate and how like Nate just seems to like want to replace everything and i responded to him
with Nate everything is such a process that i'm not surprised he would want to cut some of them out
like right i feel like it would take you longer to do cooking than it would normally take someone
to do cooking i've noticed it it's about getting in the right headspace it like takes me longer to
like edit a random thing for like gib can edit a potty cast episode way faster than me for some
reason that i just don't understand everything you do just has more steps i think like i think
see it now i can see i am an autistic young man i can see me getting all the ingredients putting
them all together getting everything like in the oven and then taking the oven and put it in sony
vegas and have all these fucking transitions yeah whatever i'm whatever i'm doing anything
i have to break it down into the component steps so that i know exactly what i'm doing if i'm like
making progress etc i'm sure people who are just like better at getting things done right out of
the box true yeah like here's i say the cooking is fun here's my cooking process first i think
yeah do i want it to be something that's fried i say yes what pans are not currently dirty well
here's a pan that is kind of dirty but like you know if it's if it gets to boiling then all the
germs are cleaned right so okay i'll just use the oil that's already on it some actual restaurants
just keep using the same grease for like decades i've had donuts that were cooked that way so i'll
just use that nice i turned it on and as it's heating up i then look in the freezer to see
which meats i want to cook and then i just put them on there and i just keep putting ingredients
until it's done yeah for me it's like i open the freezer and there's like five different varieties
of asian steamed buns and i decide if i want the okay i can confirm this is true do i want the
octopus uh shumai or do i want the crab rangoon thing or do i want the pork steamed bun or do i
want the you know i've just got like one of each meat one being octopus which is the best one
and then i just steam that shit for 10 minutes and it's done and i eat it and it's delicious
it's like hill but it has flavor it's it is not to be overstated how good the food in idly is
aside from obviously all the tourist traps that are shit and try and be like hamburger you'll get
your hamburger with the spaghetti on it and they try and trick you into hamburgers when you're idly
aside from all that shit food in idly is unbelievable uh there is a fucking it the reason
wait wait the reason pro food the reason pro food no munchie i need i need to clarify this
uh because because we have history idly versus idly go okay ironically the best taggateli i've
had has been at idly because whoa because because okay because everything in okay okay here's the
difference between the the ragu in idly versus uh the ragu in idly uh because the idly is almost
like a shred beef sort of like beef stew-esque uh uh what do you call it meat and it goes really well
with the sauce because it's really hot and stuff and you know it's almost like a like a soupy little
mess of pasta but the ragu the beef ragu in idly is more like a ground beef and i don't i really
dislike the the texture having the the ground beef-esque uh uh in the sauce and i just like it
but aside from all that here's a fucking here's a new dish i haven't even heard of before that
is fucking delicious what what is it Nate what do you want i i've got okay can i take a huge
tangent here no i just remembered a great story is what you're talking about interesting at all
because this is better yeah no i yeah it is okay i was gonna say it real quick okay there's a new
fucking dish and it's fucking delicious it's what i've always wanted you may you may call me queer
you may call me fucking insane but i've always wanted this a condiment yeah i want to add something
to the pantheon of condiments you got your Zeus ketchup you've got your fucking Poseidon ketchup
i want to add pantheon of gods right there you may call me queer and insane i want to add
egg yolk to that i want egg yolk to be a common condiment that you did before your french fries
or you know steak and whenever you have steak and eggs we have steak and eggs you fucking cut open
the the yolk and you dip your steak in it and it's fucking delicious and what they have in idly
they have a pasta that's instead of sauce it's egg yolk they have egg yolk pasta and it's okay it's
egg yolks it's a little bit of cheese it's a lot of pasta and then it's bacon and black pepper
and it's called carbonara and it's delicious and it's fucking good it's so good it's so good
there's a lot of times where i make a hamburger i make a hamburger and i fry an egg to put on the
hamburger right that's the way and and if i cook the egg just ever so perfectly the first bite will
release the yolk and it will soak the meat and it'll get down to the bun which if it the if the
bun has been sufficiently mayonnaiseed which creates a seal it will not soak through the bun
entirely and you have created a fucking immaculate orgasmic food product i never even considered
that you could seal the fucking bun with mayonnaise that's what out in brown on good eats said that's
why you put the mayonnaise on the bun oh man i'm so fucking hungry i gotta get some food after this
all right strap in for the story of a fucking lifetime everybody all right here it comes here
it comes okay so so uh my girlfriend was just at her job the other day this is the story through
her but you'll you'll trust me this is worth it it relates to me so it's still good uh so she's
she's just she's at work or whatever doing her thing and then like because she's an attractive
young lady uh like a guy just comes up to her it's like hey what's up starts chatting her up
um uh eventually uh he asked like oh so like oh you moved here from hawaii that's crazy why'd you
move here and she says well i moved here like for a guy uh and and he's just like oh wow pretty
that's pretty cool and then that just like passes for a while eventually because this guy
obviously is way into her he brings it up a few more times just like what is this guy like how
did he how do you pull this off like what exactly is the deal here and uh she's just like well you
know like whatever i like how did he win you object what do i have to win you now basically
basically and so uh it culminates with um she's just like well you know i moved for a guy like
he's a youtuber i like him a lot he's really cool and he's like uh he's a youtuber but uh
does he even play fortnite literally what and she says uh no and he goes yeah or some guy
and struts off and struts off disgusting this actually happened this actually happened wow you
was slain that night i was doing him in fortnite or else you're gonna lose michelle i know i have
to my honor jesus i like to imagine you're like coming home in a huff and like throwing something
you at you like come on i'm like what's what night like is that what you're not even a real
man nate what are you doing you're wasting your fucking life here uh yeah that was why would you
play fortnite when you look at me anyway that was it i thought you'd all enjoy that is it fortnite
is it fortnite like the like the shitty free version of another even more it's actually
it's the better free version uh you could call it it's it's legitimately a good game but it is very
like kitty i could not everybody love we have interested it it's it's the natural progression
of minecraft x overwatch no i i know that because i saw my uh my um maize like autistic cousin who's
like 12 playing it and everyone has an autistic cousin because our families are
i don't know if you've noticed but we are a cabal of autists on the internet and everyone in our
family is probably closer on the spectrum to that side you know i have a plan to think about
everyone in your family and slowly realize oh shit all autistic oh fuck it all makes sense i'm from a
i'm from a family of mega normies and uh me and ben stand out like gigantic sore thumbs from like
the rest of our family wait hold on nate your dad studies psychology and hippo your dad is like a
multi instrumentalist who's like like a musical expert like these are both like highly autistic
hobbies you know what my dad my dad is by far the most educated of like our family so he does
stand out as like i you know i'm not to be mean to them but like the smartest one of the bunch
so i guess that trickled down into like into me who is the smartest of this bunch the intellectual
guys that are me and ben if autistic if autistic just means like good then yes i mean by our standards
it probably does like i would think that what we value is things that are more on the like i mean
look at einstein like if einstein's work was helped by having autism as opposed to not having autism
it was a good isn't the way that autism works is that like a lot of parts of your brain don't
work right or don't get enough like fucking attention and therefore you over develop other
parts it's sort of like being blind will make you hear better and vice versa yeah that's how it works
right i don't know i feel like this is another this is another situation where digi is just using
a word in a way that it doesn't actually mean you know what it is it's um language is all broken
and wrong and i'm the only one yeah i agree digi i just want to say i am so sad digi that you were
not here for the episode on language where these fucking bullies were just laying into me for for
having objections with the concept of language and you come in here later arguing the exact same
point sorry i wanted to be on that one i wish i had been i hate language it's an authoritative
practice of bullshit and and lies and it all it does is cause problems for humanity it also
causes all the solutions but it also causes all the problems there are right now right now like
another like like right now uh another two hours i don't know the podcast language to
all right let's let's make language to oh oh italyans are really funny because of language
because a lot of their food is just foreign words but spoken in italyan so so you have a
spaghetti you you you have a florist is called bestaica and you know what it is it's beef steak
but it's bestaica that's like a high that's how japanese is too with all the like yeah
young tea steaky um beautiful that's all we need to fucking oh yeah we gotta move along here
whatever let's go let's go let's go all right all right because i have a lot of fucking shit to
say still yeah are we on questions now or do we still have like songs to do or now there that's
a good good question there is so there was one final opportunity for people because the deadline was
the 31st of july which we are now past so the contest entries are over there's no more but
we gave people a small window now i hate to say it but one person submitted their entry on august
first after the deadline there was one final entry here's what i thought we could do we can't
accept it as the winner but i thought we might just play it on the show just because he made it
i don't have a problem with that it won't be formally in the running to win but i thought that
might be nice let's go for it okay uh what if it's the best one now let me see this is by i know i
hope it's not literally the best one it's by at moss spheres moss spheres yeah whatever and it's
called um pc it's like a pc ph e me so something about that name you should write me that i'm slave
to the knight's government and there's nothing i can do something about i don't i don't know what
but i just remember uh sounds good all right here we go uh listen to pc theme here we go
this will have to be the menu screen music for the pc prpg it's a good one oh oh it's building
no this is the kingdom house trailer for pc basically oh this is three minutes long
it's got the slow start i don't know how this in any way reflects the pcp not to be rude but i think
this might be a repurposed song it sounds like it was made for a video game it sounds like it's
like steven universe sort of it does actually uh pc and pirachu it would be like an actual piano
though why is there not a political compass for the pcp instead of like like you know left right
it's gay and dead and then you can have the there oh my god what would well you have to have four
things right gay dead what what's the other axis well i mean brony and gay and dead would have been
we but gay and dead couldn't be on two opposite ends of the axis because just because like the idea is
that you're both at once so like yeah so you know edgy that could be alive and they would be alive
and straight did you yeah didn't i i literally made a four-quadrant alignment of us of edginess and oh
yeah i remember when you put me as way more edgy and like right wing than monkey which is yes i did
you know fair enough fair enough um i thought this was gonna like ramp up but it's just yeah
it's changing it's just a fucking regular ass song man it's it's like it's just it's okay you know
what it's like a hollow night background yeah yeah i hate to cut you off a first heron a k whatever
but i think we've heard enough and it will be killed you and you will be destroyed you know uh i'm
kind of glad that it wasn't something that would really want to seriously consider as oh you have
to say that you don't have to say it like that no well all right all right let's get to some cool
ass questions all right chip wise men who asked if kirby sucked you up and devoured your soul
what a thousand times before i don't know why people upload that would you say that a thousand
well i that's that's that's like the what what is your favorite anime question paradox
crocs ask what's the next big thing you're saving up for uh like that's what you're saying or like
artistically like what you're what you're going to be making i think that's really funny that's
what yeah uh a computer i already bought a laptop uh and i'm gonna buy a desktop soon good nice uh
probably having money and then after that uh going to the dentist because i'm getting a lot of i'm
getting a lot of dark spots and it's starting to look it's probably still not cavity it's probably
just standing because i drink fucking coffee constantly but don't get braces if you get braces
you're literally cuck and it will destroy you no braces i already had braces for years i already
had braces for years and then i stopped wearing the retainer and they're getting a little bit
crowded again i still haven't had my fucking wisdom teeth taken out so my mouth is still kind of a
fucking mess yeah i should probably go to the dentist or not right now having some gum pain
it's a it's a scam well it's well did you unlike you i actually brushed my teeth and floss and
mouthwash i don't know why so that's good that's good the next thing i'm saving up for is uh tom
taught me that there are now like 16 core processors that you can get for 800 bucks and uh so i mean
that's not the next big thing is the next big thing is my taxes but after that 16 core processors
all that's on my mind yeah i remember you telling me it's like i'll do you can like fucking render
three times as fast if you use these and it's like yeah or you could have like just use adobe
premiere which renders three times faster than vegas the cpu that you recognize that even true was
that a 16 core was yeah it kind of is like anytime ben used i initially recommended you a 16 core
date and you were like that's too expensive i don't need that oh yeah i think i took like the one
below that because that was like i mean the one you pointed was like 1500 bucks or something i think
like whatever time that was like this the super intro one there's there's an amd one that's like
a little bit less expensive but still yeah so yeah yeah there's things there's things i mean i know
what i'm the i the main thing i'm saving up for is i have already decided a certain threshold of money
that i need to save before i'm comfortable going full-time youtubeing uh so once i reach that that
'll be pretty good did you read even that read from your speeds uh it will it can render like
one and a half minutes of pretty advanced video per minute which vegas is a lot slower than but
did you see is really invested in this idea of vegas being the really the really easy and convenient
editing program i know it's really the same as premiere don't frame it that i am actually invested
in that that is just a thing i tell people so that they will start making videos like i don't
actually believe that vegas is in any way superior to premiere it's just the one i know i think it's
a little easier to use um that's something it's just it's just so immediate like you can literally
look at vegas and understand how to edit like in my opinion yeah but maybe it's just the way my brain
works but like i agree i i do think that i would encourage people to if you you know want to make
the next step to level up to the more advanced programs but like when people are on twitter
being like uh i don't know how to edit i'm like download vegas and look at it and you'll know
how to edit it i just don't respond to that i'm like i'm like the old uh uh uh the the ancient
martial arts master living on the top of the mountain if you're not willing to climb the
mountain to get to me to you know prove that you're really committed to it already uh you know
fuck it just give literally google it you know figure it out so sony vegas is it it can do most
things pretty well and it is like pretty understandable to use like to move a thing
across the screen you'd go into i hate you and you can drag it around it sucks they're in another
yeah it's oh it's terrible okay it's i'm speaking i'm speaking right now um but so uh uh at some
point in sony vegas you will come up to a wall uh if you you know if you get used to it and you're
like okay i want to do this sort of effect i've seen it done before how does it get done and it
doesn't exist and that is when you have to make the program to premiere and after that you'll think
oh i want to do this a thing uh but it doesn't happen in there so how do i do that you go to
after effects and that's just like those the two pretty much figured that out because of
nate doing that effect where he makes the screen like balloon open and then pop like oh yeah and
when i first saw him do that i was just like sasuga premiere like this must be what the next stage is
you know everyone just needs to use hitfilm express it's like it's like after effects and premiere
but free arm achieve the entirety of arm and she was made into fucking hitfilm besides the last
few episodes which ethan made in vegas but like the majority okay what what what what was the question
i don't think it was what are you saving up money for i don't think tom answered yet oh yeah or an
apartment that's a good one that's a good one uh i'm i'm not really saving up for any like
money thing like of course it would be nice to have money so that i could get an apartment but
i'm not like i don't see like more than you know getting the money i'm i'm worrying about like
having a way to get the money like creatively like doing the thing i'm i'm i'm in a creative like uh
you know not a rut but like i'm i'm figuring things out and i'm getting getting going on that
real stuff creatively go to like monster dot com and just search for like jobs i can do with them
i have all right i'm kidding dude i'm kidding i have all right i have a right is about monster
dot com eat shit and suck a penis i have a job it's just um i'm not really thinking about
like saving up i'm just i'm just thinking about like day taking one day at a time like figuring
freaking out things but i guess i guess what the like a thing i kind of want recently i i had this
idea that you know fruity loops uh makes me cry um so i i want uh well i fell studio as it's now
called i mean that's what it's like yeah and um i wanted to get one of those like
musician keyboards the ones that they have on their desk instead of on a keyboard stand that is
that doesn't have weighted keys and it you plug it into the computer you can make midi songs with
it or you can just use it in programs like that instead of having to click you definitely do that
you you play it on something i wanted for a really long time and tom had one and was gonna
sell it to me but i didn't end up buying it this was like five years ago though uh they're cool i want
if any music men are in the audience and i know there are um please give me your your your your
your recommendations of like how how to get into that sort of thing because i have no idea what
here's a super fucking circle jerky question by me manifest what is a character trait you wish
you could inherit from the other members oh character trait
hmm i wish i had sighs good news i think we all get it what was the question
what is a character trait you wish you could inherit from the other members
um nates diligence i want jeff's height oh yeah you know what i think i probably the most would
be nates relentlessness yes relentlessness that's it what what to do things and doing them
it's it's the best yeah i guess if you could if you could take a piece from a person but not their
entire personality then it's great you just take all the best bits and leave all the bad bits
oh it's a lot oh yeah i would love that i would love i would love instead of me if if you were to
like try and take my mind like lay would be like lost in translation like if you tried to like
reach inside my mind take it out by force like the moment you like relinquish it from the inner
like like from me in my skull it will like instantly deteriorate and like turn to dust
i believe that i i would really like digi's lack of inhibitions uh like to do the sort of like
videos where you're you're you're being like yeah i'm a cringy who cares i'm doing all this stuff
and it's and it's like it the confidence is the funny thing about that is that i i feel as though i
have only very recently like actually had no inhibitions like like i've started being shirtless
in videos and i was terrified to ever be shirtless in a video until recently and but it was it it
always fucked with me because tons of people are shirtless in videos all the time like lots of
youtubers i follow they do it for comedy or just because like no one gives a fuck like victor's
shirtless in every video he's in so i like it's just that i have body image problems so i didn't
want to be shirtless you know and then at some point i just went out fuck it like i don't give a
shit anymore um so i'd like a lot of tom's uh just like savviness mustache of like just a lot of
information that tom has uh would be very useful and i always find myself going to tom to ask like
business or technical questions same i feel like that would be very very useful i don't want that
stuff though because i like having a guy who knows that stuff like i just like to be able to consult
the guy so that i because to me that's that stuff becomes very time consuming if you actually
keep track of it like tech is replaced so often that it's like i just don't want to have to know
any of it until the moment that it's like i need to start charging all of you for this because
i'm wasting my time i need to take your money did you i see that you're stuck in the same like
paradox that i am i keep running through every attractive attribute of each of these members
and then i i can't decouple the attribute from the life path required to obtain it and so then i
have to keep rewriting my own life and i'm like well i don't want to be that different of a person
and so i'm kind of stuck i can't make any decisions yeah i would i i would also like davoo's um ability
to use language effectively in small videos where he explains points because i i stumble across i
stumble upon words oh i do and i don't make points i just i start them like 12 times until
eventually it comes out right yeah so every vlog you've ever seen at short it's like the 20th take
not even exaggerating yeah and also you edit the shit out of the audio like i know when you do just
audio there's like hours cut from them sometimes this might lead to some uncertain unforeseen
consequences but i would like ben's pacifism to the like like he can just be in any scenario and
not care like actually yeah happen to him pacifism isn't the word i would use but like his his
his apathy apathy i just wish i had his ability to um like live on the lowest like he legit doesn't
care about if he yeah the edge i guess it's the word i'm looking looking for like he he's just not
afraid of having no safety net under him because he's like well what's the worst that can happen
and it's like pretty much and the answer is always like the the answer is yeah the worst
like it happens not that bad like it's it's not hard to climb back up from a low point if you know
how and i guess just because he is he just has that intellect that he could like i mean he's
worked as a fucking scientist before so it's like i know i can go back there if i really want to but
like that's so what's the worst that could ever happen you know it other than losing a limb or
something like that but it's hard to like convince yourself that you know to actually like make
decisions on that basis oh Nate Nate's uh i want Nate's um meme library in that he has in his
brain that is a very helpful thing it helps a lot because because whenever i want to like have like
a funny image on screen i i never know what to do i i don't i don't go to 4chan i don't i don't
i save i even like when i was young i did it even more but i still possibly even more than ever
now i make an effort to save every funny meme images image that i think might even be useful
potentially it's a real habit that i'm glad i did you know what i want to note Nate how do you
organize your computer files because right now i'm getting your computer so i want to transfer
all my files and i and i want to make these my computer to mess right now how do you organize
you know images uh well specifically with the so i some people go are are really meticulous about
like grouping like okay pepe images go in the pepe reaction image folder okay my my transparent
pngs that i can use for the particulars like effect on 4chan those go in like this folder
i gave up on that and instead i gave myself the freedom just i literally put them all in one
folder and what i do is i go there i scroll to a random section and i just look for something
so i get a lot of spontaneity with like the stuff that i end up using or like i had a feeling that
was how you did it from the way that you tend to send images because there's no like consistent
formula it's like it's all over the place it's all over the place i'm not like those like some
people are like currently is i just have a 4chan folder and the inside that there's a different
folder for each board and then i separate by board and then i just put all the images that i
get that makes sense that one folder that makes sense i just i pretty much everything is like
from v i'm on v way more than like every other board all right i wish i had everything i have
from like a decade ago back when i actually i've made never to say i can be bothered to make me
folder i tried i really tried but then just like i can be bothered oh hey i just wanted to say on
the 71 ben was relevant i did want to say one thing about ben um well i am a very i consider
myself a very diplomatic person and i really don't try to burn bridges uh just like just
paradoxically i very much admire ben's willingness to burn bridges and his brutal honesty i like those
a lot yeah i like their admirable quality i i've i've like whatever whenever there's something
going on here or elsewhere i just wait for ben to roll up and say the thing that i don't want to
have to be the guy right it's pretty great ben he he is not willing to make any concessions whatsoever
on being himself and like granted he's a reasonable person with like he will he will listen to you
and try to like say okay well if i agree with what you're saying i will acquiesce but if he
doesn't agree he will in no way budge on anything and that's it's definitely something to be
admired in that way all right i would rather just run away from conflict and just stop talking
i decided how i would answer the question uh i want jesse's video game catalog and playing
experiences and probably if i have to have it packaged his taste in video games as well
so yeah because he's got he's got at least in the top three best taste in video games of people
who i know who are the other two uh i think jim sterling's taste in video games is fascinating
because of how much he likes convenience and doesn't like hard things convenience he's he worships curbie
i know that and uh oh i don't know i kind of rank good taste based on interesting taste so maybe
some sort of like amalgamation of razor fist and examined life of gaming as like the ultimate
gray brown boredom simulator oh i'm just gonna use the word amalgamation now i'll seem like a copy
what were you gonna use it for mage i said i was i wanted to say that my personality is just
amalgamation of bad choices so no one wants anything from me you know what i want i want
hippo's dad give me your dad
myself you can try maybe you can try but it's not gonna be easy for sure that'd be good you know
what i want i want munchies youth i want i want 12 oh yeah you know i will say about mage though i
do like mage's air of mystique i do that is pretty sick that is cool that is cool who is i don't
know i don't even do it i would love well it's just natural i would love mage's past of being like
a rough and rough and tumble knife wielding freak i want that i wish i wish i had like a weird
past i want mage's super hero persona i just want to modify what you said like i do think that it would
be nice to have mage's lack of having completely fucking docked myself on the internet and and
everyone like knows what i look like and uh yeah that comes with costs it comes with costs
i like hippo's like ability to make like these odd jokes but they're funny it's just it's the way
they come come out of your mouth it's just the zingers yeah hippo's zingers are like the best
in the world and his mind for puns is i love puns i love puns so much is so good i wish i was a
circle jerk now uh yeah i like it we're two and a half hours in we want to have any other good
questions let me just real quick find a pity question here uh what do we got what do we got um
i like a shitty question at sis white scum 69 asks uh evo is going on as you speak y'all
gonna tune in does anyone care about evo no guys i don't uh i i care about fighting games
i'm not gonna fuck cares about video games what a what a joke electronic it's it's fucking
bodily that you nate can like play kingdom hearts and like play rpgs and then say leave
legends a waste of time when like these super fucking long single player rpgs where you have no
outside connection to the world is like a useful wasted time okay saying that like a long rpg is a
waste of time is is in my mind is the same as saying and this might be true but it's like
saying reading a long fantasy novel is a waste of time like you know it kind of is it kind of is
well i i don't think either i mean there's there is no rpg that lasts nearly as long as what league
of legends will take of your life like that's a reasonable point the absolute most time you ever
when people talk about like super in-depth super long rpg so like dude 300 hours like that's the
standard like i did absolutely everything i hundred percent of dysgaea i hundred percent of skyrim
like 300 hours league of legends you can play 300 hours in like two weeks and then be playing it
for 10 fucking years and something like that yeah i mean i played three years i played a whole
disclosure i do speak as a person who's played team fortress two for 2700 hours
shit on my ass and that's how it is for all those any of those games that people play as a
lifestyle like that's the difference is like kingdom hearts you consume as a work of art with
the message that that is just like watching an anime or or watching a movie you know it's just
and like i went back i went back to esport and it's gay i went back to kingdom hearts like no
they're just i've been i've been i've been trying not to speak much this whole plot has but i want
to say before i forget the point yeah go for it uh with the with the needs comparison with with uh
with uh you know the whole long novel book thing like it's like you make a choice and like i think
you don't really regret it's not a waste of time if you make a choice and you do it because you
really want to but with like mmo's and stuff like that there's this sort of like a psychological
need to sort of log in every day and do a thing because you kind of need to you have to you
you already invested so much why can't you why can't you you know you just kind of kind of have to
keep going and that's like that's why i hate multiplayer games because i feel like i have
to keep playing all the time to stay competitive so i can actually enjoy playing the game if i
take a break from a multiplayer game and i get shitty then i'm just gonna get tooled on and then
it's not fun anymore incidentally that's why i've never gotten into a multiplayer game because
like i will the way i play video games is in one go like if it's a single player game i'm gonna
play it in a day or two and be done with it and never look at it again so like with a with a game
like say splatoon everyone loves it and everything and like i played it for like an hour one night
and like an hour the next night and i went all right well i feel like i've played splatoon so
that's done i play video games is the social aspect and specifically right that's the difference
the appeal of dominating another human being to make another sure sure i just do that in my wraps
dog i play video games i play video games yeah i was thinking you know i i used to play a lot of
mmo rpgs like a lot of mmo rpgs i used to hop from mmo rpgs to another one like within months
sometimes we could depending on how interesting it was the thing of i managed to sort of like
train myself like um to ask myself am i still having fun with this game or am i doing this
because it feels like a chore and i have to do it as soon as the game starts feeling like a chore
and like i'm logging in just for the sake of logging in i stop playing the game and i move on
and i i still get caught up in this stupid psychological need to log in into some games
but i really try to like i recently cut out a game out of my life and i still have like this
sort of itching needs to go back to but it was an app on my phone and i i uninstall it and i
don't want to look back at it ever again because it lured money out of me and i read read deeply
ever spending money on it the multiplayer time crunch time sink singularity has has just reached
closer and closer to a singularity over the last like 20 goddamn years and this is part of why
i'm entering into game design with such confidence because i know even if it takes a couple of games
a couple of years but they're part of a decade anyone who has their head firmly attached to their
fucking neck is going to be able to figure out how to make a game that people are going to actually
play because most development resources are constantly being diverted to the newest variation
of multiplayer mmo hybrid cash grab trend right now it's fucking battle royale before that was
mobs before that was mmo's and like everyone's wasting their time trying to run for all the
money there's no way games would be so multiplayer centric if not for the fact that they have the
most open monetization strategies when what most people really want is like a certain amount of
gameplay with a certain experience to be felt and it's just a giant shit show farce that it's so
multiplayer centric out there i okay i don't think okay there's a distinction here i don't think you
have to play multiplayer games the way that i or the people play them there's nothing like set in
stone like you have to play them for thousands of hours well they are designed to psychologically
manipulate you to do much i did not play no one's fault but your own if you get much i agree i agree
but like as soon as i feel like the game stops being fun and i just do it just because it's a chore
then i stop playing it but that i have spent yeah i have spent a lot of time playing those games
because i did generally enjoy playing those games it's just and then you gotta appreciate
munchie that like you can say it's just you can say it's your own fault but i mean you get into
these games young for the most part or when you're in a time of social unrest or you don't have enough
in your life and they they prey on you you know just the same way advertising does like it's and
whenever you ever bought something that was advertised to you you don't because you know
better you do two weeks later when you're thinking about what to buy you know i will
literally like see a commercial for a tasty like burger king burger and go buy it immediately
i can relate like in me a biter just watch something and like we're watching anime or
something and they like in the anime they like eat some sort of food like let's see a burger or a
creep crepe and and i was like i want that now and later laughs with me because i always do it
all the time see the food i want because usually when i when i'm hungry and i want to go get food
it's a 10 minute conversation of well what do you want to eat well i don't know what do you want
to eat well i don't know and like if a commercial just comes on right then it's like bam done like
let's fucking go to hardy's like but hey to respond to munchie's point munchie i totally
sympathize with your love of the social aspect and of dominating noobs in in mmo or tf2 whatever
because like i played league of legends like all my friends who i played with for years for many
years were much better than me because they worked much harder and like researched meta changes and
like researched like the best guys i'm not even saying they were like yeah of course it's fine of
course it's fine but like but here's the thing but oh fun you're right it absolutely is fun but
here's the thing right now some of my friends are going through a period of like oh well we don't
we don't play those anymore uh you know uh has that time really like i there the reason i started
youtube was the time i stopped playing league of legends my entire youtube career could have just
been me playing leg of legends instead i it was basically a one for one trade of one for the other
and i could not be more glad that i made that trade but some of my friends didn't and looking back i
think they regret it and and that is what i want to enhance people for people from if people want
to play a game with their friends as i did socially just like to connect with them to talk to to get
together and have fun i could not be more okay with that but what i fear is that later on they'll
get they'll get kind of sucked into the world and they'll end up wasting something of their lives
that i don't care if people waste their lives they're okay with it but they will regret it later
that's what i don't want yeah the thing is that's why i'm saying that multiplayer games are an
unmitigated like blessing upon the world but i feel like they get an unfair rap for things
which is just our human nature to want to sink at our human nature is extremely flawed and we have
to engineer around it because it is a problem we have to be smarter than human nature so that's
why i object to things like like like i don't like the ban on like gigantic soft drinks in like
new york city but like i really understand why they would do something like that because humans
are not smart enough to know not to drink stuff like that so i do not have a huge amount of faith
in just human intuition human decision making any of those things you mean all those mobas are like
the 32 ounce coke of video games and the thing is the thing with those mega uh ips those things
that like it's this one entity that can suck out all your time is that pretty much the same amount
of time and the same type of effort the same like variety of skills and focuses can you can
instead just engage in the hobby of an entire medium like the 2000 hours you can spend playing
league of legends can be spent on all the different kind of games that you hear about and i know
you're all interested in playing i know everyone has a giant list of video games all those like
10 to 20 hour ps2 single player games that everyone's heard of and no one gets around to playing
and you spend the same amount of time you could spend playing those playing one game and it's
almost always going to be more fulfilling getting into a medium actually feels like a kind of an
actual accomplishment it's just as useless but it is genuinely more fulfilling to the soul
well okay and that's it for this episode of the procrastinator spot wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait last question last
question for russell asks will you guys go to the final brony con next year oh hell yeah okay
yeah we are i don't care what the other guys are doing i don't care what anyone else is doing
i don't hey i think that might be when radcon whatever is because i'm going to go to boston
and i'm just going to keep you down to baltimore when that happens so if like four of us already
there we should just do it then i think before before radcon four we got to do radcon horse
that's what that's that's true radcon horse radcon four radcon horse just so people are aware
the final brony con ever is next to your august whatever uh so considering that first first of
your ass to brony con friends to meet the horseshoe crew
right we're gonna have to languish as being a horseshoe crew yeah your sub horseshoe crew yeah
yep that's right that's right would you say davoo me and you aren't a horseshoe crew
grabbed to be the horseshoe yeah c m c oh and it's adorable but we have to get a pass analysis back
yeah who else would would have been a c m c
horseshoe crew uh c m c member that's a real title that he had that's true hey can i get a
yay or nay real quick guys i think that next brony con will be the appropriate time to conduct
into the horseshoe crew officially to uncritic white yeah i think that's the time we are going to
get out of the water we're going to and everything that has been alleged against him we are going to
you know reverse we're going to make everyone forget what's happening yeah ductum i have no
desire to go to brony con next year that's it we'll see how you feel yeah we'll see we have a gun
to your fucking head did you we'll see how you feel about that everybody patreon.com slash the
procrastinators five dollars for the bonus episodes including the new bonus episode out right now
monsters two listen all the way for a little surprise at the end but uh enjoy that uh one dollar
get into the fucking patron lounge get the questions that we answered
at tpcrastinators on twitter follow us for updates and shit subscribe like comment and die piece of
trash thank you for listening to this episode if this episode gets a hundred likes for to add
doge to the pcp let's add doge let's get let's get the 10th member doge we'll be here see you then
everybody
you