Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Ready Phantom? Oh my god!
We did it ladies and gentlemen. Hey it's not a T-Bap show, everybody watch Come On Let's Go Pro Crastinators.
We actually made a fucking podcast. Welcome ladies and gentlemen.
And today we've got me, the best guy ever, in addition to some lower life forms including Munchy.
Do these count as a map of us? I mean technically you did like release a video.
Absolutely not. It's got to be on my channel.
Well it's got to be on my platform.
Well I guess you guys are going to be watching this episode on a different channel.
Yeah when Nate finally stages a violent coup it's just going to be like the channel will just vanish overnight
and then he will have hundreds of pieces of content to just re-release on his channel and we'll all be powerless to stop him.
It's the big brain play honestly.
We should definitely talk about that because that's crazy shit. I think this is the first episode.
Yeah it definitely is since that happened so we'll get to that later but there are more people.
Tom, Tom is here of course.
I need more soul.
Where are you going to get him?
From the shoemaker.
That sounds like a man bereft of soul poops.
You're going to kill all of you fucker.
No not me.
Oh there it is.
I am a weak boy. I am a mere hollow sir.
What do they call a shoemaker? Not a haberdasher.
A cobbler.
A clogmeister.
Dude I straight up got my feet measured by a cobbler once.
Dude that's straight up.
Dude you get your fucking boots blacked?
Yeah I got them fucking shine dude.
I got them shine all the way to the ideal.
You engage in some boot blacking as featured in my favorite webcomic Ojoi sax toy.
I fell apart immediately upon standing up and walking outside and you didn't give me my money back.
And of course we also have the furtive hippocrite.
The furtile hippocrite.
Oh yeah.
Listen I don't want to make the pockets weird or anything but like I'm just imagining my children being bred by hippo and I'm just trying to get a little bit weird right now.
Being bred? Like putting the fucking pizza oven and cooked?
Yes.
I'm like fully breaded dude.
Hey you forgot me but that's okay I'll introduce myself.
I slipped it in. You had said some words.
What's up guys? Best guy ever here.
No wanted sex criminal.
I don't know about wanted.
Back at it again from the Pizza Hut where I'm laying low from the feds.
I'm obligated to inform you that I am a sex offender.
If I'm to be on this podcast.
I have a zero rating on the social credit score.
Hey speak of that Pizza Hut Nate.
Do you want me to tell us what that really strange thing you said before we started recording?
Child sucks cult underneath your pizza?
Do you want to explain that on the show?
I think we better save that for the bonus episode.
I think we better keep quiet about that and let the fans speculate.
Before we do anything I have a bone to pick with Nate.
Oh don't we all.
I gotta air my grievances because before this podcast started.
This guy thinks he's got the only bone with Nate to pick.
I'm just gonna be just trying to repeat it.
I was awake all night playing Dark Souls 3 because I have no light.
I listened to all of Matthew Muteau's Dark Souls 1 commentary.
It was pretty cool and then I needed something else to have his noise while I was playing it.
Oh no not the lowly Mia Mathifa.
Mia Mathifa came out and I was like I'll just start listening to that.
I got like 15 minutes into the Devil May Cry 5 Mia Mathifa.
I'm like this is the most retarded take I've ever heard.
It's not even a take.
It's a deliberately incomplete take as a man struggling with the reality
that he has not found himself attached to the way that other people do to Devil May Cry.
I had to roll my eyes.
I audibly rolled my eyes.
I'll let you figure out what that means but I audibly rolled my eyes
when you were just like Devil May Cry 3 man I don't even understand.
What's the Temina Gru? I don't even fucking get it.
I haven't seen this video.
I'm thinking this man, the man who sat us down for three hours
and had to explain the difference between the Keyblade and the Keyblade
is complaining about the Temina Gru.
You don't have any ground to stand on sir.
It's just a matter of personal commitment to like how much have I investigated one verse.
It's the fucking tower. The tower is the Temina Gru.
There you go.
I haven't watched this video but I have seen multiple people in multiple discords
complain about your takes on Devil May Cry.
I'm glad I can air that publicly now.
I know you haven't played many of the games or you're not like that into it.
I actually have played all of them as a matter of fact.
He's just an idiot. I don't know what to tell you.
It reminds me of the backlash I got for being like
for the Heroes of Might of Magic videos I made
where like I had no idea, I mean, you know, big mistake
to make a video where I wasn't like super fan of the games
and I talked about them and people ripped me to shreds in the comments constantly
about my lack of knowledge on this cult classic that everybody knew about.
That's kind of sad though because like the interesting thing about those videos
was like you were someone coming into them not having that background
backlash take. Here's how someone would experience them today.
And like that's cool.
It's just that I didn't expect backlash because I didn't know about it
and if I knew that there was like a big fan thing
I probably wouldn't have put my opinion out there
because I don't like getting told I'm an idiot.
So I probably would have waited until I had more of an understanding
of what I was talking about.
Frankly, like that video was designed to be kind of a parallel
to the Hollow Knight one I made for me a mouthful one.
And like, I mean, again, it's not like a genius take or anything.
It's just like basically my first exposure to this particular game
and looking back on that like Hollow Knight video,
I'm sure people, if they watched it now,
look, no one's a bigger Hollow Knight fan than me
and I like barely understand what's going on in that game
and I'm fumbling around and I'm quite critical of Hollow Knight
and now it's like my favorite game of the...
I mean, before Sekiro, it's definitely my favorite game
of the last like five, six, seven years or something.
So that's what I was kind of hoping people would take away.
We'd be able to look back at it as like a landmark
in Nate's journey of trying to finally understand
what people love so much about Devil May Cry.
You know what would work about a video like that?
If it was a video where you start the video, not getting it
and then you...
And then I get it at the end?
Well, yeah, because like there was this...
It only played two hours.
James Rolfe did this thing where he was like,
I've never got into Power Rangers before.
I want to know what it's all about.
And then he basically...
It's just sort of an explanation of him beginning,
like not knowing anything, being an idiot,
and then he marathons the whole thing
and then he comes back at the end.
A lot of that kind of time.
I mean, it was James Rolfe. He's crazy.
So he marathons the whole thing and he gets it
and then he has like a big like, oh, this is so great.
And the people who would otherwise have been annoyed at him
loved it because it is living proof
that you can get into this thing.
And then they could share that to their friends like,
see, Power Rangers is good.
This is why you should try and get into it.
So Power Rangers, American Power Rangers
was actually thought to be good by James.
Is that accurate?
Because he's always pretty childish to me.
I mean, I watch it when I'm a little kid.
Well, it's super childish.
But like, that's its charm.
Its charm is just funny, goofy.
Like, I think that's also kind of the reason
why Devil May Cry is great.
It's because it's just like fucking stupid,
but like in a cool way.
You know, I wanted to clarify.
I just didn't have time to say everything I wanted to.
Like, I wanted to say how much I love the ending
of Devil May Cry 3.
Like, it is so good.
And I absolutely love it.
And like, the intro, like, I don't feel as much
of an attachment to.
So I feel like if things skewed a little more negative
than I wanted to in the video anyway
about like the whole series.
But I mean, yeah.
Just just to be clear, just to clarify
before I like jump down and throw it.
I've only watched the first 15 minutes of the video
because then I had to come up here.
It does get more positive.
And I don't even care that you think it's that
that like you don't understand it because I'm not
going to sit here and say I understand everything either.
I just thought it was hilarious that like
you're the three hour Kingdom Hearts lecture man is like
the story confuses me.
I just thought that was like saying that I because
I did a three hour lecture on Kingdom Hearts
or whatever that I that I can't be critical
or have any concerns about any story
that's overly complex.
I'm the first one to admit Kingdom Hearts is overly
complicated and doesn't need to be this way.
It's just that it hooked me early.
So I just got dragged along for the whole ride.
But I see your point.
I certainly see the.
I will say and I agree that I think the Devil May Cry one
is still, I mean, I've said it before.
It's still my favorite.
I think it's so good.
I love it so much.
Great.
And I actually mentioned this in the I Am Games video
I did with DG when we were talking about our favorite
games is that because that one's by Hideki Kamiya,
it has a tone that's different from the rest.
And I kind of miss that.
For sure.
It's a little bit more grounded, but just like,
I don't know, just the subduedness of it is kind of cool.
But at the same time, like it soon as like crazy over the top
insanity is also cool in its own way.
I mean, yeah, they're two different flavors.
And I definitely feel like there could absolutely be a divide
about like, depending on what kind of person you are,
like I always like the gaming Brit.
He, he's a guy in my eye.
It seems like like the Itsuno Devil May Cry games,
like that's, he's the guy for those for sure.
Whereas I feel like I'm more of a DMC one kind of guy,
but, but I want to learn about this world
because I do not understand it.
Now, I mean, that's what I talk about in the video.
So people can go listen to that for more.
But by the way, you were saying about James Rolfe.
I was just curious about his Power Rangers video.
Has Linkara filed litigation?
Yes, because he's coaching on his turf.
And is he shutting down this operation?
Because as far as I know, Linkara is the only man on the world
who's talked about Power Rangers in any capacity.
You shouldn't actually be telling all of it.
You could tell you all about the, about recording
and the production.
Mr. Green.
Yeah, yeah.
It was a pretty, pretty, pretty intense on set, you know,
having to just stand around and do nothing
because we got all the Asian actors already from five years ago
to do all the action scenes.
Right.
You know, I had to like put the helmet on sometimes
and stand there and shake my head a little bit
to make it look like I was talking in the dubbed dialogue,
whatever it was.
Ah, yes, classic.
It was great.
10 out of 10 experience would do again.
You know, this might be an embarrassing truth.
This might be like a thing like,
uh-oh, why did you say that?
But I have actually watched all of those
Linkara reviews of Power Rangers.
Uh-oh.
You watched a YouTube video
that might not be considered quality.
Guys, time to call out the firing squad.
They're going to fucking tell the me that I like bad things
and then they're going to think I'm stupid.
All right, tickle them to death, please.
No.
That's gay.
Get out of there.
Are they good though?
Are they enjoyable?
Uh, I mean, I've marathoned a lot of
that guy with the glasses stuff just because
and I used to like nostalgia critic.
I guess I used to like Linkara as well.
They were just sort of like, ah, yeah, I guess.
I mean, you know.
The comic stuff was like,
I don't care about comics and the way he does them
is always terrible,
but like a video review of something
is inherently a little more interesting
because I'm looking at the thing
and it's like moving around.
That's certainly true.
Certainly true.
When you're a kid and all you want to do is feed,
then watching nostalgia critic
isn't at all a strange thing to do.
I used to watch it all the time.
I don't even know whether I was that young.
It was like five years ago or something.
Whatever.
Munchy, can you run that by me again?
What do we need to do?
Oh, just when you need it.
Feed.
Okay, okay.
All right.
You just need to feed.
You need to consume.
Oh, all right.
This is a new concept to me,
so it's blowing my mind.
Well, yeah, I know you're post content and post food.
I actually, you know, looking back on it,
my internet search history
and my internet history in general,
like I was not a YouTube kind of guy
who was like watching nostalgia critic
and like I totally missed fucking
the angry video game nerd completely
and I'm still looking to go back to that.
That shit was like old hat
by the time I even like was aware.
I mean, like I had probably heard of it before.
How is that possible?
Because I was watching AVG.
Well, I mean, I don't know.
But it's due to Ben that I got into it
when Ben turned me on to like the pony stuff.
That's when I really dived into it.
Whoa, holy shit.
Yeah.
Like when did, um,
angry video game nerd probably started first, right?
Before the nostalgia critic.
Yeah.
He started before YouTube was a thing.
He used to make home videos of that for his friends.
Sure.
But I'm sure no one was watching it at that point.
Well, yeah.
No, you couldn't.
Yeah.
I think it was like pretty soon after YouTube got started.
So it had been like around 2006
because it was originally the angry Nintendo nerd
and then you'd be branded for copyright.
Well, like I watched,
so I was in college until like 2010 or something.
And I was watching YouTube around them,
but I definitely was not watching, uh,
uh, yeah, it wasn't,
it wasn't until like pony stuff.
Weirdly.
I mean, I had in college, in college,
me and my friends,
okay, this, this,
we did delete this,
but we made a video game review,
um, in like a group,
attempt to be relatively comedic.
Whoa.
It was, uh, we made one on,
it was, it was, I believe it was Ratchet and Clank,
uh, like it was the first one of the new PS3 games.
I forget which one it is.
But it was one that everybody loves.
Tools of destruction.
Oh, that's not a good one.
No, it wasn't Tools of Destruction.
I'll destroy that game.
Wait, was it not?
You know what?
I'll, I'll, I'll Google it while I look this up.
That game, that game was a miserable experience.
I played that in 2015.
I, I, I can't believe,
I can't believe Nate showed up hippo
before hippo was even born.
I know.
I, I, which one was it?
Was it, I guess it was,
no, it was a cracking time.
I'm like 99% sure it was a cracking time,
which I think,
Cracking my ass.
The crack, cracking time wasn't too bad.
The point is though that, uh, like,
so obviously I was aware.
The idea was to release this on YouTube.
Uh, so clearly I knew about YouTube stuff.
But all the production fees and just the publishing,
you know, just,
Oh my God.
I wish that still existed,
but like we finished this product.
Okay.
And then we looked it over.
I think I edited it.
We filmed it on like my old parents' camera or something.
Uh, and then we all sat around like in a dark room
with like the glowing neon light illuminating us.
We all stood and watched this like 15 minute
ratchet and client game review.
We all, it finished.
We looked at each other and we said,
We have to destroy this.
It has to be removed from existence.
And that's exactly what I did.
Were there dude,
what the freak moment?
Basically.
I can only imagine.
That would be, that would be such a cursed,
that would be such a cursed artifact
if it still existed.
That would be so.
It doesn't though.
I'm pretty sure we completely explained it.
It would be so incredible to post now.
I wish I hadn't.
I wish I had kept it.
Oh my God.
It was so fucked up.
Dude, what if it's on the camera?
What if, what if the raw footage exists?
You know,
You're gonna react that down.
Gonna get the VHS out of the archives.
The RCA.
Whatever it's called.
The little tapes.
I mean, I'd have to like call my parents.
Okay.
Tell you what.
I will, I will do a cursory investigation
to see if I could possibly unearth this thing.
But, uh, but we'll see.
We'll see.
There's nothing more intense
than a cursory investigation by Nate.
Yeah.
Honestly though,
I don't want to get people's hopes up
because like 99.9.
Like even that feels like,
but there's like a 0.1% chance.
Like it's not, it's basically zero.
It's pretty much just zero.
Yeah.
It would be a miracle.
I remember deleting it.
Barring an act of God.
Yeah, we'll see.
And I mean,
although God is real,
so hopefully that this is real.
No, I just,
I just tweeted before we started
that I'm an atheist
that God isn't real.
What?
Dude, dude.
I actually,
It's true.
Represent.
Tom, proud of you.
I'm proud of someone's out there
willing to say it.
Someone has the courage.
I mean, to be fair,
I was making a Dark Souls 3 joke,
but it stands for God.
Guys, hot, hot take on God,
hot take on God,
fake.
Hot, not real.
I think he's just
a little bit fake.
Hey, speaking of me
making videos though,
I'm currently doing that.
Uh, and other things,
me and Mafia 2 is on,
ladies and gentlemen,
and you're probably watching it,
hopefully.
Uh, so that's cool.
But really,
me and Mafia 2 is,
is simply kind of just a hype engine
in order to propel
the excitement for my channel
that is going full time.
I have tendered my resignation
at my job.
I kept it a secret
until I announced me a Mafia.
And, uh, yeah, I quit.
I, I, I knew about it.
I knew about it.
Oh, did I tell you ahead of time?
I couldn't remember who I told.
Uh, you, you did not tell me.
There have been murmurings in chat.
Oh, did the parents spill the beans?
My dad, you're dead.
Your own dad.
Spill the beans.
Be solo in pregnancy with dad.
Wait, hold on.
Why did your dad know
that you were making me a Mafia?
Why did you tell your father?
Because he has to tell him everything.
He has him under his iron foot.
No, you fucking nerd.
He knew, he knew that he was
tendering his, he knew that he was,
he knew that he was
tendering his resignation.
Yeah.
In fact, my dad didn't spill.
He, my dad didn't call me up
and say, dude, Ben,
do you hear about this new me a Mafia
that's about to happen?
Yeah.
That's where I was gonna add to it.
You know, okay.
As, as a matter of fact,
I, uh, did not tell my dad,
like about me a Mafia, frankly,
cause I, you know, like he's not
really up with the lore.
Yeah, I wouldn't imagine that you would.
But, but what I did do was
I called him,
when I was thinking about
leaving my job,
I called my dad and my parents
and wanted their sage advice,
which is exactly what I got.
And, uh, so, you know,
it was all part of my,
my process of moving my way out.
I had to talk to my parents
so I wouldn't be scared and alone.
Um, but yeah.
Yeah.
So, so I guess the good news is
they seem pretty positive
about how things are going,
so that's nice.
So to be clear, this isn't
me a Mafia's building up
and then like you're going to
quit on me a Mafia.
Like the wheels are in motion.
This shit is happening.
I had, I had titted my resignation
over a month ago at my job.
It's just, it's like,
because of my job,
it's like a team I'm a member of
and we got a lot of stuff
on the wheels.
Uh, they, they asked me to stay on.
In fact, I was hoping to be gone
by the beginning of May,
a little bit unhappy
that that's not the case.
But I mean, hey,
they asked me to stay.
I agreed.
And frankly,
this is laying the foundation
as people take, take my advice.
I think this is wise.
Don't burn bridges.
Like I'm going out of my way
to do extra work for these guys
so that I have a safety net.
So they already say like,
hey, Nate, if things don't work
out, give us a call.
Yeah, we could probably fit you
back in here.
Um, like if things don't work
out, I will be fine.
Cause frankly, my job is great.
Uh, it's just that you,
does that, does that mean
you're staying,
you're staying in the area
or not moving anywhere.
You're not,
you're not PCPH queuing it up.
Well, okay.
See that that's the,
so plans have not yet been made
as to exactly where to move,
but I still think that
to exactly where to move,
but I certainly plan to move
somewhere because there's
nothing tying me here anymore.
And frankly,
me and Michelle are both
looking forward to,
uh, I mean,
among other things,
seeing the ocean on a regular
basis.
I just,
I just crave that ocean for you
over here.
That's true.
And I mean,
okay, now to get a little bit
dark with it,
I wonder if me,
my,
my, my nature to keep things
secret,
uh, is so strong,
my comp,
my compulsion to not spill the
beans and to surprise everyone
in a favorable way was so strong
that I couldn't bring myself to like
discuss any future possible plans
with like any of you guys
or Digi or anything,
even though that probably would
have been a wise idea,
uh,
to see what happens.
But,
uh, I mean,
so we all know Digi's
in Virginia Beach now.
Right.
So, uh,
he seems pretty dead set there.
I mean,
that's the negative side
of your natural showmanship.
Everything has to be,
has to have the,
the wow factor.
So we can't ever know,
but I,
but I was,
I was,
I was privy for at least like a month.
Oh, of course.
Because Munchy had to do
the fucking logo, of course.
Uh, as,
as I,
I'm the logo Smith
for your entire channel.
Have you,
have you seen,
there's a lot of positive feedback
about the logo.
Is there,
is there,
absolutely,
people are way into it.
They fucking better be.
And,
and the fucking,
yeah,
we were,
we slaved on this logo.
Uh,
I forced you to be my slave.
We,
we slaved,
we slaved smash cut to you
You know,
it really hurts cracking
that whip after so long.
Oh,
it's not,
it's more than zero effort
to work with Munchy on it.
That's true.
You were very involved with
I got,
I got fallen arches
from crushing Munchy
under my boot heel.
Indeed.
It turned out great though.
It turned out great.
As always,
as always,
oh,
it did.
And as always,
I stand up for employers
who are the real heroes.
You know,
they're,
you should,
you should fucking,
you should move to London
take the dogs to the park
and they can play
in the park.
Oh,
Sonny and Sessho
hanging out.
That would be great.
I'd love to do that.
Maybe I'll fucking walk
the dog daily.
Maybe,
probably not though.
Yeah.
You should,
you should,
you could unironically
make a vlog of you
with your phone out
like walking the dog every day
on a show.
Oh dude,
straight up.
Okay.
All right.
Here's a video idea for you.
You get your GoPro
and put it on your dog's ass.
Record a vlog
from the dog's ass
Oh my God.
So you're walking down the street
and you're just like,
like the,
like the leash is going down
to the video,
like,
like from the angle
which the dog's ass is at
and you talk down to it.
That's the,
that's the vlog.
You strap an iPad
to the back of the dog's
you can see.
Yeah.
Oh dude,
that's next level boomer shit.
Like you put farms
on your iPad
and put it on your dog's
ass while you're walking
your dog.
I have several
good ideas for videos
that I've been cooking up
for a long time.
And that's
doing things with the GoPro.
Doing things with the GoPro.
I have not really thought about it.
We all have.
I mean,
the great thing about it
is the list is totally changing
every single day.
I start basically at zero
and just have to come up
with something.
So,
I've got a few questions.
So I'm going to ask these
and then if they're two,
if they're two,
you know,
next level
then feel free to deny answer.
How much of this?
Okay.
Cause this was the same thing
for the last minute and a half.
So obviously you had time
to prepare
and you had thought about this
because you know,
you quit your job
and I'm sure for many a few months
beforehand,
how many of these videos
were pre-made?
Zero.
Zero videos
have been pre-made.
Really?
That's correct.
Every single one
was made on that day.
That wasn't even
the case for the first one,
was it?
Yeah.
Actually,
okay.
Frankly,
I was just kind of
fucking around
and not getting my,
my,
the end of April
when I was announcing it
and I was like, well,
I guess this is how much time I have.
I'm kind of hoping to
currently
make,
like manage to make two in a day
so I can get a little bit
of a buffer back
so that I have a little more
time to relax.
Cause this is a,
that's crazy.
I'm getting very little sleep.
That is insane.
Very, very little sleep.
I mean,
I can imagine you're still going
into your job.
So all of these are just coming in.
Okay.
So you got your,
you got your working hours,
of course.
What are your working hours?
You know,
capital W,
like real work,
okay.
You know what?
So,
so,
I don't want to give anybody too
much of a false impression.
The thing is we worked
out a deal.
I'm working a few hours
less than full time now
for the remainder
until I'm out at work.
So that gives me about
like two extra hours
in a day to work on stuff,
which is not a ton,
but it is something.
So things are a little bit
easier than they were
for,
for me a math of a one.
Thank God.
But basically I,
I've committed about
six hours every
work day
to my
job,
job.
And I got to,
you know,
do me a math of a stuff
and do everything
else I got to do in the day.
So,
frankly,
it's been,
I've just,
just like,
I'm just in my office,
like all day.
Can't,
I want to watch the new
Game of Thrones,
but I don't have time.
God damn it.
You're missing nothing.
It's fucking shit.
But that,
well,
the last episode
sounded like it was a big,
a big deal,
but I haven't seen it.
So I wouldn't know.
It was a spoil.
Don't spoil me Tom.
Don't you do it.
You're in for a surprise.
I'm going to say the Game of Thrones
word.
I'm going to say it.
Well,
you see,
in Game of Thrones,
Game of Thrones,
James,
James Game,
the main character,
found that there were six rocks
across the
world of
Thronia,
and that he had
to drag them down
in order to,
you know,
become more powerful.
Sorry,
well,
that's pretty sick.
I was enrolled.
Yes.
The last words,
the final,
the ending,
you know,
shambles his broke ass in
and he sees John Snow
sitting on the throne
and John Snow
suddenly looks down
and says,
huh,
chaos control.
Cut to credits.
That's the end.
We don't even see that.
We don't see what happens,
but we know,
we know what happens.
Chaos has been controlled.
Nate.
He goes,
he goes super,
John.
Are you in
the work doghouse
right now
and just fully devoting
your time
to making things?
Do you have any time
or anything else?
Um,
well,
I'm trying to kind of
carve out time
to do other things,
not really,
although even,
even in the depths of
uh,
Miamavva,
I still find myself
like wasting time
when I need to get to
the video
and still,
you know,
in what way,
in what way?
Well,
I mean,
just for example,
the,
the one I did on Sekiro,
the Sekiro video,
like I had everything
I needed to get started
on that video,
I can't remember exactly
what I was doing that day.
It's all kind of blurring together,
but like,
I know that I only started
recording that
at like 10,
no,
okay,
I recorded like the intro stuff,
which was way too much,
probably,
and I shouldn't have done it.
Uh,
but then I only started like
the main video
recording the actual
like discussion of the game
at like 10 p.m.
And
like that was like,
that was like three hours later
than I could have been
if I'd just been peak
efficiency.
So I don't know why
that happened,
but I ended up releasing
that video, you know,
because I just took that long
to get it done.
And, you know,
that's just,
that's just what I have to do.
I,
now I have,
to my credit,
I have founded myself
the absolute iron will.
I will not stop
until the video is done that day.
And it's nice to feel that again.
It feels good.
So that's cool.
I like that Sekiro video.
It's very,
very informative and fun
and epic with the sword.
Yeah.
I like it too.
It's good.
So you've been doing these
for how many days?
Five,
five days.
We're on day six today?
No,
day five today.
Although there was also day zero,
so.
Have there been any,
like,
you just thought that you couldn't
get the video out?
Or is that iron will
just so prevalent
that you just
could not even imagine it?
There have been issues.
Okay.
So one of the things that
happened with,
I believe it was the
Sekiro video.
Oh, no.
Okay.
I was going to say,
there was another technique
club.
Oh, there was another thing
with the stream.
There was so much stress.
Like I,
because the aforementioned iron
will,
a video must come out that day
when it seems like things are
going horribly awry
and the video may not come out.
Like it can't not come out.
It has to come out.
What,
if I need to scrap what I've
done and re-record just a new
video,
that's what will be done.
But like,
okay,
so I discovered a wonderful
feature of Sony Vegas,
ladies and gentlemen.
And so my camera happens to
record MOV files.
And in the past,
I've noticed sometimes,
just when I put too many videos,
just the whole project breaks.
And this actually happened with
the Kingdom Hearts video.
The way that I finished my
Kingdom Hearts,
we Agua,
was I actually broke that file
into several different
Vegas files and then rendered
the pieces together once they were
all rendered individually.
So that shouldn't be
necessary.
Why did that have to happen, Nate?
Well, I found the answer while
working on the Sekiro video.
At least I believe it was that one.
And it was that,
did you know that Sony Vegas,
which uses QuickTime to support
MOV files,
can only handle
up to a certain amount of
MOV files.
And when you go over that
number,
it doesn't give you an error.
The files simply stop
working in Sony Vegas.
So picture me,
it's already like 1 a.m.
I've been struggling for two
hours to figure out
why the fuck these perfectly
good video files will just
not be visible in the
Sony Vegas.
And then I,
you know, I'm spending hours
searching to try to find the
answer.
And then someone in a random
YouTube tutorial says,
oh, by the way,
just so you know,
Sony Vegas breaks if you have
too many fucking MOV files,
so make sure you don't have
too many.
And I'm like,
well, why the fuck didn't you
say so?
And so that's,
now I know.
Like, now that I knew that,
I could-
That should have just been one
year,
you're a mere math of a video.
It's just public service
video.
That's like the story of making
a mere math of a-
The way-
Detail like all the issues I
had so far.
Oh, you could set like a
making of video,
like a making of episode.
Yeah, yeah.
Something like that.
You go to a mere math of a
factor and just start cranking
out the same shit over and
over and just like,
like just teams and teams.
Yeah, you do a making of the
video and then the next day
you do a making of the
making of.
Yeah, yeah.
Forever.
And that's the rest of the
month for you right there.
That's the rest of the month.
Yeah.
We've got the formula down.
The way it usually goes is
that when you learn a
program to, you know,
use it for whatever creative
job, you know, you learn
Photoshop or you learn,
you know, I don't know,
Dasty or something, you know,
FL Studio or something.
Then you, there's a hump
where you're getting a lot of
errors because you don't know
how to use the program.
Right.
And you're using it in ways
that it doesn't intend.
It seems that Vegas,
that initial hump is forever.
Like you never get out of
getting errors in Vegas.
It seems like no matter what,
even people who have been
aiming for years seem to always
just have problems in that
program.
So I decided to learn it
myself.
I would bet that there are
peculiarities of most types of,
of any kind of software.
You know, as a software
developer myself,
formally full-time, now
part-ish time and soon to be
not at all.
There's always stuff that you
discover as you're like doing
more robust testing.
If you're doing the same,
like we, at my job, we have a,
we have a software that we give
to customers and like things
can absolutely break.
If you just do things in like,
on the edge cases of like what
you're currently working on
or whatever.
But the thing is our customers,
they do the same thing over
and over and over again with
the software.
So like really for them,
they don't need to worry about
like these, these edge case
issues.
But we do.
Like when customers are,
you know, they're going to want
to use it for something
slightly different than,
you know, what we've prepared
for.
So, you know,
always happens.
I feel like this will not be
answered.
I'm not going to ask for
specifics.
Like, you know, names,
but can you tell us what your
software is?
So I think I'll just forever
not say.
Nuclear launch codes.
Because of the possibility
that I will one day go back.
I don't want anyone to know
where I actually work.
So, so, but I'll tell you,
the software basically what it
does is it's,
it's a file transfer protocol
specifically for CAD 3D model
files that people use for
engineering.
3D printing nuclear bonds.
Indeed.
Well, like that pizza, you know,
there's some kids down there,
and they need to be
taught some lessons
from your home channel.
Fucking.
That's fair.
Fair.
But one of the things that
our software can do is like,
it can change the file type
as it, as it is being sent
through the pipeline.
As it's thrown midair to
the next office over.
Indeed.
So if you're like an
engineering firm and you use
like, let me see,
what do we got?
Use like,
UGNX 10 files.
Like that's,
that's a file type.
And you want,
you want to get into a person
who uses step files.
And you're trying to collaborate
on like development of some
engineering project.
Like you could use our,
our software to like,
you put in your file type,
it gets piped over to them.
And on the way,
it translates the file to the
step type or something.
So yeah, that's,
that's what it does.
And that's what I work on.
Just hand break it, bro.
Just hand break it pretty much.
I mean, unironically,
I mean, that's the interesting
thing.
Everything about what our
software does is,
and we have huge clients.
You know, like government agencies
and whatnot use the program for
various reasons.
Oh God, the 3D models of the
nuclear launch codes are being
transcoded.
It all comes back to it.
The 3D models all the codes.
It's like numbers.
They're just numbers.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No one ever looked at a 3D model
for it.
It's so ingenious.
Encrypted.
I mean, being on the development
end, like everything we do,
like you could replicate,
you could just like do it on
your own, like for every file.
But the problem is when you're
sending like thousands of
gigantic files, like you want
someone to streamline the
files.
Really, if you think about it,
everything in life that we buy
is kind of just a streamlining
so that you can save your time
and not have to, you know,
grow your own food and produce
your own shit.
You have to buy the seeds and
buy the stuff.
Well, that's what they say.
You spend, when you're a kid,
you spend time to save money.
And when you're an adult,
you spend money to save time,
something, something.
I learned that from Hippo, I
think.
Oh yeah, that's something I
It's true.
Yeah, I'd never heard that
before.
But it's true.
I always think about that
mostly when it comes to video
game piracy and the insane
high-level hacking I would do
to like my PSP to be able to
get free games.
And it was dope as shit.
And I'd do it again in a hard
beat.
It was super fucking dope.
I keep thinking like,
is this going to be the day that
I finally eBay a PSP
and jump back into that?
Dude.
I'm going to play the Japanese
version of the Bleach fighting
game a year before it came out
again.
Man, I got some of that shit on
my fucking DS.
There was like a DS fighting
game.
But like, the world was my
oyster.
Back when I first got into like
ace cards for my DS.
Dude, this stuff is the shit.
I still stand by it.
The DS, I think, is the
greatest, at least
handheld device of all time.
And probably my favorite console
literally of all time
because of the ace card.
There was so much good shit for
it.
Being able to play Quake 1,
the PC game,
ported onto the DS,
it was fucking the best.
It sounds like such a Wild West.
It was amazing.
I played Mother 3,
you know, whatever it was.
Really?
Like translated?
On my PSP, actually.
It was on my PSP.
Yeah.
Damn.
There's a fan made dub
of Western.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And it was dope.
It was like, it was fantastic.
It was fantastic.
I actually played it on a GBA
emulator on my PSP.
I played Mother 3
and it was one of the best
experiences on that thing.
You know what?
The entire time we're playing
Mother 3 on my PSP,
I was like, man, this just
isn't the same.
I wish I could play this.
Hold it in your hands with your
PSP, dude.
I can do it.
Have you ever considered?
All right.
So you know, you remember back
in the day with the PSP,
you got a memory stick
or I didn't use an SD card.
I had a memory stick.
Because Sony is all about
making proprietary formats
so they can get more money.
And those things are
super fucking expensive.
Nowadays, they have
micro SD
to memory stick adapters.
So imagine just getting like
128 gig fucking micro SD
slotting into your PSP
and putting like every game
ever on your PSP.
Yeah.
That's the dream.
Times have changed.
We didn't have that shit back then.
That's why I'm like, oh fuck.
Because like I'd have like
an eight gig card
and feel like a god.
Like I can have three games
on here.
I know, right?
God.
PSP.
It was too early.
The technology now.
We can fucking crush it.
Yeah.
That's true.
Oh.
What warm times.
We're going to get a cubic ninja
port to switch.
That's what I want to know.
Speaking of Sony PlayStation,
recently, the other day,
I replayed Ratchet and Clank 2
because I just feel like,
I just feel like nostalgic
playing the same five video
games I've played my entire life
and I will never play anything new.
And I've realized that
a lot of that game is dog shit,
actually.
Oh no.
Like the game is fun
and it's really nice
and all that.
But like I was paying attention
to the story
and when you're a kid
you don't really understand
anything that's going on.
You see the jokes
and you go,
but that's it.
There's a lot of
dead ends
and nothing character-wise.
And I was thinking back
to the first game.
Well, like the whole thing
is about Ratchet and Clank.
They are characters they have.
They start off,
like not really,
they're unsure about each other.
They have a falling out
and the story is about them
as characters having a character arc
and by the end of the game
they're best friends
and that's that.
And they're pretty much wrapped up
at the end of the first game.
Yeah.
And in the second game
there's like themes hinted at
but nothing happens.
And it's just,
it was just sad to think.
Like they get transported
to another galaxy
and Ratchet is like,
ah man, I'm not a hero.
It's boring being,
having nothing to do.
And he goes to another planet,
another galaxy
and he gets a hero task
and he's like, oh sick.
And then
he does stuff,
he gets clank,
there's cutscenes
with funny bits in them.
Indeed.
And there's like,
there's like a,
there's a female
longbacks lady
who's got,
who's really hot.
Hell yeah.
Before going somehow.
But, and there's like
very, very, very slight hints
that Ratchet may like her
or like he does like her.
And it doesn't go anywhere
and Angela never like
reciprocates that at all
and then it ends
and that's the end.
It's just like,
it's such a shit story.
It's like,
this is the reason
why Ratchet and Clank
is not really considered
a classic.
Yeah.
It's like,
it's just a,
it's just a fun game
from, from back in the day.
And it sucks to,
to realize that,
oh, I guess,
I guess it actually
wasn't that good.
I guess this is the reason
why this is not like
a Metal Gear Solid 2
or anything.
This is,
this Ratchet and Clank.
I've always felt,
yeah,
I definitely,
I love Ratchet and Clank 1.
I played 1 through 3
and really enjoyed them,
but I felt a big,
I never felt the kind of
attachment to the game.
Like he,
you know what he feels like?
This is the best way I can describe it.
He really feels
like a PlayStation All-Stars character
as opposed to like a Smash Bros.
character.
That's a,
that really sums it up right there.
Say with like Kratos and,
well, no, no,
Kratos has like
loads of character
and story and stuff.
I mean, I suppose,
but I,
Like, have you seen,
have you seen Jesse's video about it?
I haven't even played him,
but like,
Jesse's explanations.
Kratos is pretty cool.
In that video he did.
But I have played them.
So here's my expert opinion.
Kratos,
well, that's the thing.
Kratos, just like in,
just like Ratchet and Clank,
for their first game,
like narrative,
I'll say masterpiece.
Like it's just,
it's great.
It's like solid and fantastic.
We get everything we need
out of the character.
Like everything after that
is basically wasting my time
with the character.
Like, oh,
he's still sad about killing his family.
He really wants revenge on the cops now.
You have the same problem
with the rest of the God War games
you have with the Don't May Cry games
because David Jaffe
was only involved in God of War One.
You know, honestly,
that's, I think that's part of it.
Although, I mean, to be fair,
like Devil May Cry,
when it changed,
like it changed into a thing
that a lot of people liked
even more than the first one.
So, you know, some people are,
I really want to spend some time
like getting deep into Devil May Cry
technical shit.
Cause I mean,
I feel like that's
well-loved.
You'll be a better player than me
cause I never fucking went down
that rabbit hole.
I have other things to do.
That's so surprising to me
that you're such a big fan
and yet you're not like,
I don't know, like,
isn't that the main draw of the game?
Um, I guess.
But I mean,
Other things, I guess.
I mean, my whole thing with games
that says I've never,
I've never played a hard video.
I've never played a video game
and felt accomplished doing it
because deep down I know
it's a waste of time.
So, I play them to have fun
not to get any sense
of accomplishment from it.
Maybe someone like me
is just better at like
ignoring that reality.
I guess.
It's very possible.
It could be.
Have you considered that
playing video games
is useful for making video games?
It is.
That's why I'm playing them
way more now
than I have been
for the last couple of years.
I was watching,
I was compulsively re-watching
all of Matthew Matosis's videos
ever made.
Of course.
Naturally, the other day.
And I was on the Mario,
the first Mario 64 video.
And I was just scrolling
through the comments
and someone was like,
I wonder, someone said,
and I don't know,
tell me what you think about this,
I wonder how much of Miyamoto's
ingenuity comes from
how much he doesn't play games.
How much is the fact that
Mario 64 was such a
groundbreaking title
that basically defined
a new way for characters
to move in 3D?
I wonder how much of that
came from him not being my...
I definitely feel...
I guess in that case
there was no template
he could have even looked at.
But it wasn't the only time
that he did that,
that he pretty much
just sort of came up with
a whole new fucking game type
out of whole cloth.
And show me the game
with more developed
movement controls
than Mario 64.
Show me the game
with better, more fleshed out,
interesting movement mechanics.
Mario 65.
I forgot, of course.
I definitely feel like
there's that aspect of game developers
who didn't play games
when they were younger
because they didn't really exist.
Maybe there was Pong
or whatever, Atari stuff.
And they have an idea
and they get into programming
and they make it.
He's gonna be crazy.
Just throw this out there.
My mom was alive
when Pong, the first video game ever,
was released when she was young.
First video game ever.
Well, actually, the first video game ever
was Tennis for Two on the Oscilloscope.
Okay, well, close.
Get fucking destroyed.
It's crazy.
But nowadays,
there's a lot of people in the gaming industry
who lose stoner idiots
who played video games
and now they're in the gaming industry
doing a job
in a huge company
that is overblown and bloated
and nobody has any artistic vision
because they're stupid.
You know what's a great comparison to this?
Like Hideo Miyazaki.
Is that right?
Ghibli guy?
Did I say his name right?
Whatever his fucking name is.
Hidetaka Miyazaki.
Okay, right.
I mean, he's very much a...
Did he actually say anime was a mistake?
Is that like an actual quote?
Is that like a joke?
No.
Well, so that's Ghibli man.
Okay, pretty sure he did actually say that.
I mean, it was in a larger context.
Right, right.
Well, I mean, I'm trying to get to his larger context.
Okay, Miyazaki, whatever his fucking first name is,
from Ghibli,
he's very much a critic
of Otaku culture in anime.
It's Hideo Miyazaki.
Hideo Miyazaki.
Yes, thank you.
I'm a fucking idiot.
Me as a...
Right, from soft game.
That's the Hidetaka.
Okay, anyway,
like he's very much a critic of the sort of incestuous slurry
that is like modern anime development.
And obviously not everything's that way.
Like Maiden Abyss was a real breath of fresh air and whatever.
All this cool stuff.
But like the kind of incestuous slurry
that is like modern anime...
Say it one more time.
Incestuous slurry.
Yeah.
It's excellent.
Homestuck.
And like this really reminds me of
this kind of game development approach.
Because fucking Miyamoto seems to have a very similar approach.
I think I've heard him say,
like, you know, he makes games from a life well lived
and like experiences had.
Whereas like, I don't know,
what do modern game makers do?
They grew up playing video games
and they want to make, you know...
Want to make more...
An iteration of...
Like another video game.
It's...
What am I trying to say?
There's this sense that if you only...
If you don't broaden your like the input,
like the output could only be a lesser quality of the input.
Right.
If you know what I mean.
Like if you don't live a life in the real world,
when you make fiction,
it's only going to be worse than the fiction you have consumed.
And to give him a little credit,
I get that games are more like technical
than like a movie, for example.
Like you have to, you know,
there's a lot of just beats and bites.
You've got to crunch to get that shit all
working the right way so it can be tough.
But I mean, I think we all,
we're all hungry for innovation and whatnot.
Like I think that the Securo sword play,
I know it wasn't the first to do it,
but like it was the first game that I've ever played.
I'm sure there's others that really made me feel like
this is like how a sword duel like would kind of work.
And again, I know it's not a one for one perfect.
I'm just saying it feels like a much further step forward.
There was some...
There was like the PvP sword play game.
Oh, you're talking about For Honor?
For Honor, I think it's a game.
Yeah.
Where they have all those,
sort of, that was pretty cool from what I know.
My only defense to that is that I didn't play it
so I can't speak on it,
but I, if that's like better than great.
However, Securo is like the most aesthetic game of all time.
It's the same, it's the same idea.
Like the idea of blocking in a specific direction.
Like back in the day,
you couldn't account for such precision with your animations
and stuff in 3D.
You just, if you swing nearby an enemy,
then you hit it.
That's that.
In other words, you can get the model clanging
with another model very accurately.
Hey, here's a transition story.
All that new stuff is all possible.
Don't.
Because we've entered a new era of indie games that...
That's true.
Just are...
That's the real innovation there.
Trying to correct dark magic and evil.
So you've got games like being developed by indie creators.
Like, rolled out.
And rolled out.
You want to Google it.
It is a Super Monkey Ball game
made by fans of Super Monkey Ball
and Rom had creators of Super Monkey Ball.
So basically,
Monkey Ball stopped making good Monkey Ball.
So the fan said,
we'll take care of this.
We will.
Exactly.
So they're making a new IP,
but it is exactly the same as a Monkey Ball.
Right.
I mean, that's the same with like the...
Ega made his own like Castlevania.
Because Konami just stopped making
2D Castlevania people.
Something, something.
Mighty number nine.
And that story is not uncommon anymore.
In fact, it's sort of almost common in a way.
So you've got stuff like rolled out.
You've got stuff like what you just said, Nate.
You've got stuff like that Pokemon game
that's going to be coming out.
And you've got less direct,
but still highly influenced games.
Stuff like Shovel Knight and Herdew Valley,
where there's no one game that it brought us up from.
But still, you know,
heavily derivative from games that's come before.
And you know, that's obviously been the case.
It's been the case and will be the case forever.
But a lot of indie games,
well, many games are extremely large,
you know, subset of games.
So I will say, I would say,
I am seeing a lot of indie games
that are simply,
the video game companies have
betrayed our trust.
They've betrayed what we like about certain IPs
and certain game genres.
And so we are just going to do it better.
So to be fair to the companies,
it might just be that the market shifted around them
and that they're just fucked
because the model they used to use doesn't work anymore.
And they're slowly, you know.
What do you mean? Explain.
Well, I mean, like,
what I think about like Square Enix, for example,
like, I don't think they do it on purpose
to release a Final Fantasy like every like 10 years.
And that they're like thrilled about that or anything.
But I think that they feel pressured,
you know, rightly or wrongly,
that like we have to make it be like the most beautiful game.
Like we have to make it be like a big,
gigantic, you know, world-expanding 3D action.
I think that they feel, they don't have to.
I think they feel they have to.
Yeah, I definitely think there's
there's like a fucking AAA game development.
You can't say that way. You have to say AAA.
You got to be Jim Stirling about it.
It's the only way to say it.
Yeah, big games, whatever.
There used to be different types of games
and now those types of games aren't AAA big games
like platforms, like Wretched and Clank
was a AAA game of its time.
But you can't make a Wretched and Clank game nowadays
because it'd be very niche because
that's true, the market has shifted.
So people, they want to fill as niches
because they like those games.
They just don't get made.
Oh, look at this.
Look at this rolled out fucking mouse and a ball.
Yeah, it's a mouse and a ball or a hamster.
It's fucking great.
It's even called a love letter to Super Monkey Ball.
Yeah, there you go.
It's so fucking cool.
That's like, you know, like isn't it fucking sick
that like technology's gotten to the point
where just like people with a dream can make
exactly what took like millions of dollars
like 10 years ago?
Indeed it is, Tom. Indeed it is.
It's pretty sick.
The barrier to entry is so much lower.
I mean, in a sense.
Yeah, you're totally right.
Go play Run Away from Snakes.
That would have cost millions of dollars
to make 20 years ago.
Yeah, I ironically want to make like
not like a giant game,
but like a wretched and clank-esque
like run around with punk in a three year old platform.
Oh, give her like a costume change
where like you can be like Indiana Jones cosplaying
and you're like, oh, these fucking snakes, bro.
I'm running from the fucking snakes.
Hell yes.
Give her a hand.
Yes.
For some reason it sounds like there was like an echo
on the run away from the snakes.
And if I didn't please a villain fall.
A little bit of oblivion.
Oh, yeah.
How you doing, oblivion?
This is my quick call out.
Man, fuck you.
Congrats again on winning oblivion fall.
I'm calling you out oblivion.
Man, I'm calling you out.
Fuck you.
Man, fuck you.
Man.
What are we talking about?
Roll out?
Kill yourself.
Hey, I'm not oblivion fall.
I'm your only friend.
You gotta stick with me, buddy.
Delete everyone else's audio except for Ben.
We gotta stage a coup.
We gotta stage a PCP coup.
I've got a hot transition ready
and it's that, you know, modern games development
reminds me similarly to like,
again tied back to the whole Hideo Miyazaki thing.
It reminds me of like the big fucking Marvel movies.
Like those like the big appeal to everybody,
but we've lost like, like why do we watch the Marvel movies?
Like, because I watched the last Marvel movie
and I gotta know what fucking happens.
I broke the cycle.
I'm free.
You're not watching Endgame?
You're breaking out?
Well, I didn't watch any Marvel movies forever.
Basically.
Well, okay.
So there wasn't even a cycle to break.
I watched the Avengers assemble.
Yeah, pretty much.
Not for a long time.
I watched Avengers assemble
and that's basically it.
Yeah.
I didn't watch any of them
except for fucking, you know,
Infinity War and now Endgame.
Wait, wait, wait.
You skipped right to Infinity War?
That damn right I did, Ben.
What?
Damn right I did.
Because Infinity War is just the best one.
Although, to be fair,
I want to go watch Guardians of the Galaxy
because here those are actually good.
Guardians of the Galaxy is sick.
Civil War is fucking, not Civil War.
Winter Soldier is fucking sick.
I don't believe you.
Okay, that might be fair.
My friends are big fans of a,
not Thor Dark World.
Ragnarok?
Ragnarok, Ragnarok.
Is that the, maybe.
I think it might be Ragnarok.
That's the third one where he gets short hair
and it's like,
I mean, Ben doesn't know.
I don't know.
I just, they say that it's like really weird
and like not very weird.
It's the generally consensus good one.
Yeah.
Like they embrace the humorous aspect
of Chris whatever the fuck
his name's worth.
Chris Hemsworth.
Yeah, yeah.
And incidentally,
okay, let's, I guess let's get into
a little bit of spoilers for Endgame
if anybody cares.
Now you know.
I sure loved Fat Thor.
I thought it was, you know what,
love way too, way too strong a word
of how I felt about Fat Thor.
I enjoyed and got some chuckles
out of Fat Thor.
Yeah.
That seems fair.
And I was surprised.
So that was cool.
The forces of nature have conspired
to make this for sure
the last Marvel movie I will ever watch.
Now this may be,
I think a lot of people probably feel that way.
I know that they do for a lot of reasons.
Like everybody's retiring.
Come on, man.
There's two more Spider-Man movies after this.
You gotta go see Spider-Man.
Whatever, Spider-Man.
I don't even know who that is.
That's probably good.
I like Spider-Man.
Spider-Man, the only good Spider-Man
is the first one.
You mean with the
Sam Raimi.
That's the first one.
I'm planning my flag in the sand here.
I unironically love the MCU
and I watched all of them.
Yeah.
This may surprise some people.
I've actually like
kept up with Marvel pretty.
I wouldn't say,
I've not seen every single movie.
I wouldn't say I've even seen half the movies.
But from like,
basically since the first Avengers,
I've seen the big ones.
So like, you know,
I've seen all the Avengers.
I've seen all the group ones.
And I've seen a few,
you know,
a lot of the standalone ones.
Here's my thing.
I've been watching the Marvel movies
since X-Men in 2000
before it was full.
Because I've loved comics
since I could read.
So this isn't like me getting on the hype train
of like, oh man, this is the new thing.
There's just the thing I've always loved
since the womb just happens to be
in the public spotlight right now.
Well, that's great.
When everybody's shuffled away
and they don't give a shit about Marvel anymore,
I'm still going to be there with three other people
as they ruin everything
and drive it onto the ground.
I'm going to make an angry rant about it on YouTube.
I'll still be there.
I look forward to that.
I think about there is a store in Boston
that I always walk past and it always makes me think.
There's a Harry Potter store
on Newberry Street
that is just taking you to Harry Potter
as an IP.
It is the wizard store.
And I always walk by it and I think,
how glorious must it be
to have the thing that you like
have an entire store
dedicated to it.
That it's such a large force
in culture that you're able
to just go to a full store.
That's why every day on the Harvard Square
in that curious George store.
Yeah.
There's a curious George store.
There is one curious George store in the world.
The one and only world famous.
And I brought Munchie to it.
Holy shit.
How curious.
I think we've gone to it like basically every single time
we've gone to Harvard Square.
Well, where else is there even to go?
What else is there to see?
Literally nothing.
I start typing in Boston curious
and it auto-completes Boston curious George store.
That's what I want to say.
Here's the meme bin
hanging out in Boston Experience.
I go to Harvard Square.
We meet in the tea station.
We walk out.
I'm always scoping out for soccer guy.
I'm always looking out
praying to God that we'll see him.
We never do.
Soccer guy has yet to re-emerge.
He fucking devalues.
We walk and get Mexican food
and then we go to the curious George store.
Then we go back to his house.
That's the way it goes.
Is curious George like a Boston thing?
Like a product of Boston?
Like they made it from there or something?
I think it's British, isn't it?
I thought so too.
Yeah.
Well, it was from continental Europe.
I think it was from some fucking Belgian, I think, or something like that.
Okay, I was just wondering.
Why is there a store in Boston?
What's the store behind the store, Monchi?
Give me the lowdown.
Wait, why are you asking him?
I read a plaque.
This is probably a butcher.
I'm sorry about all the curious George fans.
All the curious heads
who are just going to fucking put their fingers for it.
The huge contingent of curious heads in our audience.
Not just because it was the George heads,
aka the last king of England.
All the George heads out there,
where I'm not talking about you guys, stop.
The American colonists were not a George, let me tell you.
But anyway, from what I understand, they fled.
By the way, curious George was created by two German-born Americans.
Okay, exactly.
So there were some people fleeing the Nazis in Europe, two Germans,
and then they fled to America.
And I believe they landed in Boston in the Harvard area
and distributed curious George there.
If I recall correctly, they had ridden curious George,
or at least a prototype beta version of curious George.
And then one of the few possessions they brought to America
were those huns.
It was curious huns.
It didn't catch up.
They didn't get in touch with the youth.
Curious Hitler did not.
Curious, curious Adolf.
Oh, that Adolf was pretty curious, let me tell you.
He had some big ideas.
He was really curious about some questions.
Which questions?
You want to try a few ideas out.
Let me read you some curious George facts.
When the first story, Cecily G. and the Nine Monkeys,
was published in France in 1939, George was named Fifi.
In the United Kingdom, George was originally called Zozo in 1941,
apparently to avoid using the name of then-king George VI.
No way!
Okay.
He came out in America, I think, so they changed the name.
Okay, yeah, no, no.
I think in America he was originally George, from the very start.
Okay, okay, cool.
Oh my God.
It all comes back around like a mobious strip.
Curious George, fucks curious George,
and they come to make a new curious George over and over again.
You know those bugs in the East Coast?
They have brooding seasons.
Their entire lives are to live and fuck for like three seconds.
So you go to a gas station in Virginia,
and then you just covered your car,
and everything is littered with bug corpses and bugs fucking.
That's what curious George is like in all aspects
that could possibly be considered.
What are we talking about?
Marvel movies, man.
We're talking about movies.
She's so mean.
Hey, movies, right?
Marvel?
Sure.
I haven't been keeping up with them,
but I realized that, you know, I liked the first Captain America.
You know, it's not like I think that they suck,
or that I'm avoiding them deliberately.
I also like the first Captain America.
I think the reason I'm not even trying to get into it
is because there's just not enough female representation
in these movies.
Oh, that's true.
There's this push to get more females in movies or in media,
but there's not enough push to get females in good media,
and Marvel movies would have been-
Dude, not enough push to get more female CEOs.
Hip-hop, you're way off base right now,
and you don't know what the hell you're talking about.
Did you go see Captain Marvel?
Did you go see the Avengers Endgame
where they had an all-lady scene?
I basically said that as a meme.
The point is that there's just all big,
mostly guys doing cool things, and that's fine.
And I'm gay, and that works for me.
The Avengers is good.
I had my fill.
I've seen Thor and Iron Man 1 and 3,
and it's like, yeah, this is good stuff.
Captain America, that was cool.
But I don't need too much extra more of that.
If there were more female superheroes that were cool
and not just supermodels with a sword,
like actually cool, designed characters and stuff,
imagine Gun Girl as a superhero.
Imagine Kit Kars, but with Gun Girl.
I'd watch that.
I mean, that's cool.
Isn't that like Kit Girl?
It does sound like Hit Girl a little bit.
Hit Girl from Kit Kars?
Yeah, I'll watch that video game.
I mean, I guess.
I suppose my only pushback to this in any way
is just like, okay, people go write great stories
about female characters that I can't wait to know.
I just, ironically, would like more movies
that feature female characters that are just written good
because I don't see enough of those.
They always seem to get panicked.
The bottleneck is just that there aren't enough
beloved female superheroes from the classic era
to mine for modern content.
I'd recommend watching Jessica Jones
the first season on Netflix if it's still on there
and Disney hasn't pulled it.
That was a good Marvel show.
It was about a female private investigator
who has superpowers.
What's a superpower?
Just out of curiosity.
She's just like strong and shit.
Okay.
Sick.
Strong female, you say.
Sounds like token representation to me.
Strong female characters, yes.
Wonderful.
That was a really hilarious feminist joke the other day
that actually made me laugh.
Feminist joke pick one, am I right?
Indeed.
Yo, listen to this feminist joke.
Or is it a tautology?
Well, that'll be for you to judge.
Okay, here it is.
It was just like a tweet from a feminist.
And it was simply this.
It was like, man says to doctor as he hands him
his newly born daughter.
He says, you know, I kind of feel like this is just
over pushing the whole female thing.
Why did we need to go with like a daughter in this?
It just feels forced and uncomfortable.
I mean, like why do we need, and I was like,
okay, this is actually funny.
Yeah.
I laughed.
Insert any social minority or any group of any kind.
I mean, Nate with his non-black wife
is handed a black child and Nate says in response,
yeah, I just kind of feel like this is like forced,
you know, black, like, you know, this just,
why do we have to go with this direction?
Believe me.
It was very easy.
It's really like it's really easy to joke about all that.
Like fucking token female stuff.
And I heard that Wonder Woman was a good movie.
I might watch that.
It was.
It's basically just that I like powerful female characters
as in like good characters that are cool
and have risk and all that.
There's just none of those in like things outside of
Undertale at the moment.
What the fuck somewhere?
Wait, stop.
You're saying there are no strong women female characters
outside of Delta Rune and Undertale specifically.
You got the monopoly.
We got to break it up.
You know what I mean?
Like in the sphere of like big budget stuff,
like Hollywood.
I mean, I guess there's fucking Cat Marvel.
I mean, I suppose.
I've heard that that's not a very good movie.
It wasn't great.
Wonder Woman apparently is a good movie.
Jessica Jones on Netflix is fucking lit.
You got all those like Charlize Theron movies
where she kicks people's asses.
Fortunately Vapors 3 is almost done.
Oh my God.
That's a female character.
Yeah.
Only a few more pages to go on that.
Now hang on.
And I've been cranking them out.
If only someone would make a film adaptation of The Champion.
Well, that's great.
Then is it fair to describe Magda as a strong female character?
Because she seems to have some pretty serious anxiety.
She's strong.
I mean, what do we mean by strength here?
You know what it means.
You know that it doesn't mean that.
Stop.
I don't mean like powerful.
Well-realized, well-defined.
Well, okay.
Wait.
Is a character.
Not written to be merely a sex thing.
Okay.
Wait, wait, wait.
So is the question here.
Is the quandary.
Can a character be a strong female character
if she is written to be weak?
Like emotionally and in terms of like will and stuff.
Yeah.
I mean, I would think so.
I mean, no, right?
Yes.
Maybe you just don't understand what strong means.
Of course.
I'm shocked.
Nate, I'm shocked and appalled.
Strong female character.
This is like a whole thing that like I thought we were,
I thought we as society had understood.
Okay.
That a strong female character doesn't mean someone
who is a badass.
It means someone who just.
Well, yeah, yeah.
Like to me, it literally just means a well-written
female character.
Okay.
Well, so if you've got like, for example, like a mom
in some show who's, I don't know, whatever,
she's like a mom and she's like really competent
and good at stuff.
And maybe she has an interesting backstory
and whatever.
Okay.
Sure.
Strong female character.
But like, what if we just have like a biopic
about like a, like a depressed, sad,
I don't know, like disempowered girl
and like, sure, we get way into her backstory
and we learn all about her,
but like everybody walks all over her
and let's just say this is a sad movie where she has
no arc where she gets over it.
It's just kind of a portrait into her sad life.
And she is.
That would be a tragedy.
We will describe her as like weak-willed and whatnot.
Is that a strong female character?
I think it, well, I mean, I guess it depends
how people want to use the phrase.
To me, the answer is yes.
Well, okay.
I guess good female character would be a better way.
I mean, I'd probably go with that.
But I mean, whatever.
I get the idea.
Well, you know, I don't know.
Maybe when people say strong female character,
they do mean like a fucking badass superhero
that they can look up to.
Look, isn't the idea that otherwise,
why wouldn't they just say good?
I think there is a contingent of people who do that
because like, if you look at like female characters
that have been introduced in like comic books
and like popular media as of recently,
they're always like borderline Mary Sewish
that like they just are invincible
and conquer everything and don't face challenges.
Isn't that just what superheroes are like?
I mean, not all.
Well, I mean, not true.
Lots.
Like most superheroes are Mary Sewish.
I think a great example of this in comic books
was Riri Williams as the female Iron Man.
Everybody just instantly loved her.
She was smarter than Tony Stark,
even though she was like a little kid.
Everyone just like saying her praises.
Nobody mistrusted her.
And it was just like, it felt very artificial
because like she's a black girl.
So she cannot, if we say anything bad about her,
we're racist.
So we can't do that.
So she's definitely strong in that sense, right?
Right.
But this is like not a well-developed character.
I mean, that's what I would consider
like a misunderstanding of the desire
for more strong female characters.
Your character is only as strong as the adversity
they overcome.
And if they...
Oh yeah, that's true.
Like the reason I like characters like...
I mean, nobody knows what gun girl's personality is like.
She shoots people and she's really angry all the time.
And she's a total badass, you know, all that stuff.
But she's like really like emotionally distraught
and fucked up and that's what is cool about her.
Okay.
Like she has a lot of mental problems
and she doesn't know how to love people.
She shoots them, you know, she kills them.
She's an RFCK character, you know?
So like a lot of superheroes that are good
are people who are, you know, they're super powerful
but they can't deal with their real life
or like they have, you know, Tony Stark is a good example
because he's such an asshole all the time.
Is he really that?
Well, he's snarky, I suppose.
He's a snarky piece of shit and he's like...
He finds it difficult to be genuine or to, you know...
He gets so worked up in his work
that he doesn't have time for social stuff
and he feels depressed at certain times.
Like it's just more interesting, the more human.
Spider-Man is the classic example of a superhero
who is like...
The strong female character.
Yeah.
Who's like got all the power but his real life
is all fucked up because of it.
Or he can't fix his real life because even the spider...
Is there any...
Spider powers.
In the term, strong female character
isn't part of the kind of idea behind that
like an inspirational figure?
Yeah, I guess.
I think so.
I guess.
A lot of time.
There's aspiration there.
Isn't the idea that we wanted to depict
like strong women on screen so that little girls
would be like, I can do that too.
Well, yeah, it's not to show...
It's not like literally...
I mean, in my...
I'm aware it's not so direct.
It's not like they have to be physically strong
or mentally strong.
Yeah.
They have to have a flaw and overcome it.
That's like a normal hero character or thing.
Let me tell you, you show me...
You show me a quote-unquote strong female character.
I'll show you a woman I can choke out real fucking quick.
Just fucking choke her out.
Like if there was like a female character
who was a superhero,
she's like Captain Marvel or whatever.
And she has like a crippling social...
Oh my god, you're talking about Jessica Jones.
Just go watch Jessica Jones.
I'll go watch it.
I mean, I don't have Netflix and I never will
and just pirate it.
Since there's ambiguity,
I guess I'm gonna keep using it just to mean
like a strong female character
is just a well-written relatable character.
I think that's what it should be.
Okay, but that may introduce confusion.
Give, another thing you should definitely check out.
Well, I'm not introducing confusion.
There's already confusion.
I mean, that's true.
People are already using the word multiple different ways.
That's true.
Tom, yeah.
Hey, oh god.
Tom was gonna say something to me.
Before we wrap up on this topic,
I don't know if you've played it yet,
but something that would probably hit all these notes
and also be your fucking aesthetic
beyond good and evil for PS2,
you should play it.
Oh, I've heard of that.
She's got green lipstick.
Yeah, her name's Jade.
I almost keep saying Jade Empire,
but her name is Jade.
It's fucking sick.
It's got like this hand-painted,
low-poly, PS2, gorgeous aesthetic,
and the main character is a chick,
and she's cool,
and she's like a journalist-photographer kind of thing,
but she also has this cool staff.
You beat the shit out of stuff.
You try to unlock undercover, conspiracy shit.
It's fucking lit.
You should play it.
You play as Anita Sarkeesian.
Yeah.
That's correct, Ben.
That's correct.
Right.
I should make clear that this is not because
I have high moral standards.
It's literally just because I see a lot of characters,
and sometimes I also like to see a sexy one also.
Right.
I like girls.
Women are just sex objects to hypocrite.
You heard it here, folks.
That's all he wants.
I'd like to see boobs on the screen,
as well as a relatable character.
You know, is that so much to us?
It's great when you can have both, I suppose.
It's the standard meme.
It's like if you're going to be staring at someone's ass
for like 10 plus hours,
and I also would be one you like to have.
I reject that framing.
No, this is a nightmare.
This is a fucking...
This is a patriarch we've done.
Hey, I'm just being real.
We were doing so well,
and then we became a patriarchal nightmare
in the snap of the finger.
Look, I'm a proud member of the patriarch,
a card carrying to my grave.
Patriarch?
Hey.
I feel like it would be disingenuous of me
to not mention that that is part of it.
Sure.
That's fair.
Thanos is so dumb now.
He's like so mean.
Dumb and thick is what he is, my dude.
Support our regressive politics.
Dude, straight up when Thanos was farming
in his fucking white t-shirt and ripped jeans,
I straight up got hard and pre-compromise.
I'm just going to say, I orgasm to the theater.
I'm not joking.
Support our regressive politics at patreon.com
slash the pro-crastinators patriarch.
The pro-women-crastinators?
That's what I have to say.
The pro-LGBTQ-crastinators?
That was a good cap to the ad.
Was me coming to Thanos.
Dude, okay.
It's not weird.
He just was in like relatable clothing.
You mean like when he was at his farm?
Yeah.
He was wearing his fucking...
He was wearing his pure cotton,
like, you know, marbled, gray and white t-shirt.
His ripped jeans.
Always his heather gray, heather gray.
He was old and greasy.
He just, he was eating.
Listen, it's not weird.
He wasn't wearing his space farmers.
Wait, was Thanos in jeans and a t-shirt?
Yes.
That's what we're saying, yes.
It was not jeans, goddammit.
Yes, it was.
It totally fucking was.
It was skinny jeans.
Nice.
I don't think he could wear skinny jeans.
He's too dummy.
Oh, he made it work.
Oh, yeah.
Thick jeans.
Well, this has been thoroughly unpleasant.
Hey, guys.
Let's, let me just fuck it.
I'm gonna fuck it right up.
Okay.
Let's just fucking, let's fucking go.
Hey, trans athletes, trans women in female athletics, acceptable?
Probably not, no.
Discuss.
Okay, considering the fact that we have, in terms of our leagues, we've made a distinction
between men and women's, like, leagues, that having people who, let's just, I mean, they're
somewhere on the border between, in some capacity.
I'm just saying it adds complexity, and I don't know.
I've heard some people suggest a trans league, because it just, I mean, I don't know.
That seems kind of, you know, shitty as well.
I mean, that would just end up being a trans woman league.
And the other option, considering that men outperform women in base, in almost every
athletic capacity.
There's no solution that makes everybody happy, because like, if you just say, oh, let's have
everybody compete together, then I'm sorry, but women are just gonna lose.
You know, okay, here's what I find, here's what I find interesting about this.
I watched a YouTube video about it the other day, and I was like, hmm.
What I find interesting about this question is, one of the arguments for it, right, some
of the people that are like, no, we should let them compete, is like, well, people already
have natural advantage, right?
Like, some people have longer legs than others, and those people are just natural.
Like, should we say, oh, well, people whose legs are too long shouldn't be able to compete?
Why, then we say, oh, well, if you were born a man, then you shouldn't be allowed to play,
just because that gives you, like, you know, a statistical advantage.
More testosterone, bigger hands, whatever the fuck.
Imagine me competing in basketball versus, like, Michael Jordan, like, you know, if that's
quote-unquote unfair, you know?
I have a solution in my head.
I don't agree with that line of thought that leads to, therefore, we should allow trans
women to dominate the, wait, let me finish, to dominate the female, like, sports leagues,
but I do think that it kind of highlights just the inherent unfairness of the entire,
you know, just the entire enterprise.
There's something of a naturalistic, I guess, fallacy when it comes to this stuff, but yeah.
Maybe this is like, it couldn't be put into practice for most things.
But, like, surely if there are, like, you know, some people are naturally more gifted than
others, and it's like, gender is becoming less of a thing.
Men and females, like, if you're a man or a woman, go here or there.
Really, what separates the top from, you know, the women from the men, generally, is that
the men are usually stronger, more athletic.
What if, instead of separating them at the start by male or female, you separate them
by their performance?
So, like, there's, like, a bracket, like, a heavyweight or a, you know, whatever.
Well, it's then, like, in, like, 99% of cases, then the top bracket will just be men, and
maybe trans women.
Yeah, like, that's, that would be how it would usually go.
But that would make it so that trans people could just go to wherever they, like, physically
are capable, regardless of what gender they, you know, ascribe themselves.
They can just be in, like, somewhere on the list.
The problem with that is that then, you know, the category to watch is the top category
of performance, and that's men.
I'm not sure it is.
Isn't that already a problem, though?
Like, men's sports already supremely outperform women's sports across the board.
And I mean, you know, that's no, that's no grand conspiracy.
It's just that, you know, the men just do better.
Nobody said it was a grand conspiracy, Nate.
Yeah, okay.
Okay, okay.
Well, you know, it's a biological difference.
Like, I know that it would be basically the same thing, except the...
Oh, wait, to be fair to my point, women might be, like, promoted less.
So, perhaps there is something to be said for that.
I get it.
Go on.
I just feel like if the gender thing is the problem, and it's, like, kind of controversial
and, like, maybe unfair in certain situations or maybe all situations to, you know, say
to a trans person that you're not literally allowed because we don't, you know, society
doesn't believe that you are the gender that you think you are or, you know, you've decided.
If the difference is in physicalness and not gender, and gender is just usually, you
know, it's a safe bet that a man would be stronger than a woman, therefore, separate them.
I think separating on something other than gender will solve at least the controversial
nature of it, if you know what I mean.
Well, you know what I've heard?
I've heard a thought.
Basically, yeah, like, we could either get broader and, like, you got two ways to go.
You can get broader and just say, like, everybody competes.
But the thing is that, yeah, I mean, it's going to make it harder for some people.
Women athletes will have a fucking tough time with that.
The reason we have men and women's leagues is because there is a significant performance
gap that would basically mean that women can't compete.
So the only thing you can do is you have to atomize, and currently we atomize basically
on men and women, but, like, I've heard proposals that, like, let's atomize on specifically,
like, we measure your testosterone and we use your, or, like, you have to be within a
certain range of testosterone.
You know, it's interesting you bring that up.
But there's so many more things than just testosterone that do it.
Yeah, yeah.
Testosterone alone does not account for all the differences.
Of course.
Of course not.
Well, Nate, it's interesting that you bring that up because I was about to bring it up
because I saw a news story and I didn't read it because I didn't care.
I didn't know this was going to be coming up on the PCV.
But there was a story of, like, some athlete who was a natural born woman and she just
happened to have extremely high levels of testosterone.
Right.
See, that's the thing.
I saw that on Twitter.
She got disqualified.
Yeah.
That's fucked up.
Like, that's straight up doing the thing, like, oh, well, people whose legs are too long
can't compete in basketball because they're too naturally abandoned.
That throws a whole other fucking fan of worms into this.
See, there is no good answer here.
There is no good solution.
I mean, I think my answer is the goodest because it, you know, ultimately, not much will change,
but for the people that it doesn't, like, the normal male-female gap doesn't necessarily
apply to, like a woman who's got a lot of testosterone is really strong, who can compete
with men, can, like, fight their way up to the top of that bracket or whatever.
No, no, no, you're pretty much just proposing that we eliminate the gender divide in the
inathletic league.
I mean, which is how, well, I mean, yeah, I guess you could argue that, but, like, we
all, we have women's leagues for a reason and it's because they would be, they would
generally, in most events, they just, they just wouldn't play.
Sure.
And I think on the one hand, that is a problem, obviously.
But on the other hand, I think if all you really care about purely is merit and, like,
there's only, like, two or three percent, you know, women participation, that means those
two or three percent are good enough to compete and then you have as close to an equal playing
field as you can get.
I mean, the thing is, it's a nice idea in theory that it should be entirely a meritocracy.
Yeah.
But I understand the rationale for dividing the league to give, you know, more people
the chance to.
It's a very damned if you do, damned if you don't, because right now you have, you have
the women's league being pissed off because they get paid less than, like, nobody cares
as much, but if you did the meritocracy thing, they'd be pissed off at, like, nobody could
make the cut.
They would be out of the league.
You know, I ever hear the story about the universal tennis ranking or whatever, and Serena Williams
once said, like, you know, I'll beat any man.
But, like, in the universal tennis ranking, she's, like, below, like, the top hundred,
because, you know, it's all fucking guys and some, like, I don't know, she was offered
a chance to, like, fight some, like, college senior, like, like, not a pro, but like a guy.
And I think she returned it down.
She's like, no, I can't beat this guy.
Or, you know what?
I might be misrepresenting her point, but the point is, like, they're different.
Men are different.
It's just, yeah, it's unfortunate, but it's the sad reality.
And I, like, I'm being, I don't know, I guess I'm being feminist to hear, like, I don't
want to fuck over women in that way.
And I have great empathy for trans people, too.
But it's just, but how do we make a fair system?
And I have no idea.
I have no idea.
But then, yeah, I don't know.
Like, I've heard, I don't know.
This video that I watched about it was, like, a couple of trans women, like, placed really
highly in, like, oh, fuck, it was like an Olympic qualifier, I think, for, like, a sprinting
contest.
And they pushed out that girl, right?
Yeah, yeah, they pushed, they pushed out, like, this other girl.
And it's like, I don't know, doesn't seem right, you know?
Well, Nate, it's interesting you bring up that example with, like, the, what's your name,
is, like, a hundred places below on the universal tennis thing.
Because if the gap is that wide, and we let trans athletes participate, like, over time,
that'll just mean, like, all the benchmarks for women's athletics will just be out of
reach for naturally born women.
Bro, bro, just the other day, a, a, what, I can't determine, sorry, it's like a male trans,
like, okay, biologically one, whatever.
No, no, wait, the other way, sorry, a biological male trans woman competed in, like, a weight
lifting competition.
I don't forget the deals.
But, like, shattered, like, every fucking record they have, because pure weight lifting is,
like, one of the biggest ways men have a huge advantage over women, and just, like, like,
what's going on?
I figured it out.
You rename the, the brackets, cis male, cis female.
But that's, that's, that's, I guess, just, like, outwardly, quote, unquote, discriminatory?
Well, that, well, that would, that would basically mean you'd have to then have a trans
league.
I don't want trans people to not be able to compete, it's just, but there's...
No, no, no, no, no, the, the, the, you can, you, cis male plus trans...
So, you'd have, you'd have a trans female participate with cis male, because biologically
they were male to start?
I mean, like, like, if, if, like, I didn't care about, like, people's feelings, that's
one of the ways.
Now you're speaking my language.
Well, like, I guess it makes sense.
That's the way it has to be done.
Like, okay, okay, I, I guess it would make sense, right?
If, if, like, the, the metrics or whatever say that, like, biological men prefer better
men in a sport, and therefore, if you, you know, you got this one league, and you, maybe
you call it the men's league, but you, like, it's, like, women can compete in it, right,
including trans women.
Yeah.
And then you got the female league, and, like, but, like, only, well, no, that's...
I don't see any solution here.
That's exactly...
I think the thing that's, that's interesting is...
Well, I guess the solution is that, well, I guess that is allow trans women to compete
in the men's league at, I mean, that's, you know, that's basically just saying, well,
for all intents and purposes, biar sports, you are men.
Which, I mean, maybe for the, maybe for the sake of, of competition, that's just something
you gotta do.
Yeah.
And if, like, there's any, because, like, the trans women that perform and break all
the records, they're quite strong, obviously.
Of course.
Because, like, the most, the strongest female people, they could, they could rip me in half
in any sport.
Any sportswoman could, could, like, fold me in, like, origami, you know?
Indeed.
So, like, what if a, a, like, a scrawny man like me, a small person would to, to, to,
male to female transition, they would be more female, like, biologically, like, musculature,
like, maybe they have more potential to, to grow based on, on, I don't fucking know,
chemicals or whatever.
But, like, it seems to be the only ones I ever hear about are male to female people
who break super records.
There's never, like, any trans women who go into the sport who are sort of, like, middle
of the range or low, you know, tier, like, bronze medal winners.
We probably just don't hear about them.
They're, they're disadvantaged.
Well, they wouldn't be breaking records if they were, if they were switching the other
way.
The sort of people who, like, if they performed in a men's tournament, they would do terribly
and if they performed in a female tournament, they would still not do perfectly.
Yeah.
Like, we don't see any of that.
And there's this, there's this, there's this, like, idea in the back of people's heads that,
like, what if you're, you're transitioning, you've always wanted to be a sports person
and this is just, like, a good opportunity to win some medals.
That's, like, that's, that's, like, really, like, a mean thing to think.
Yeah.
It's, it's just, I don't know.
There's no solution, bro.
We're not getting anything.
Everything we've thought has been a complete dead end.
What's, what's interesting, yeah, what's interesting to me, though, is, is, it's that argument
about, like, well, it's not fair to begin with.
So I, whatever, fuck it.
And it's like, well, yeah, you're right.
It's not fair.
It's not fair that some people are taller.
Some people got more tea.
Some people got whatever.
But if you just follow that logic to its conclusion, then you have to question the entire institution
of male and female leagues.
You absolutely do.
So, like, yeah.
You have to question the entire idea of sports in general.
That's true, that's true.
Like, at the end of the day, isn't, isn't sporting, isn't athletics in the end just like,
just sort of a big institutionalized litmus test for who is the tallest and who is,
has the most muscular endurance and who has, like-
And frankly, take it to its extreme.
This really goes to all inequality of any kind.
None of us are our own designers.
None of us, I don't believe in free will.
I don't believe any of us have earned anything by, like, you know, any, whatever, like anything
we've done.
We're just programmed this way.
We didn't choose to be born with the genetics or the parents or the environment or the brain
state that we have at this very moment.
And so I guess this is where it kind of gets into, like, you know, more socialist stuff
of, like, nobody deserves anything.
So we need to equalize the experience because that's only fair.
And, like, there is logic there.
There is logic.
I mean, you say go to the logical extreme, but I don't think people generally do that
except in conversations like this.
Well, that'll be my counter to every time they bring it up.
Like, in any implementation of the things we've been talking about, nobody would ever
go to the logical extreme of anything.
They would always try to find some sort of compromise.
I don't know what idea you're putting forward, Nate.
Well, I'm saying that, like, the point of inequality there, it's like, I'm just saying
that on a larger level of, like, our entire lives, everything we do, basically, in life,
is a competition.
So, you know, I'm extrapoling beyond the sport thing.
I'm just saying.
Well, it doesn't have to be.
We kind of made it.
We kind of designed it that way, you know, capitalism.
Well, oh, right.
There was no competition before capitalism was invented.
It's not like people competed for resources or land control.
Oh, sure, sure.
Yeah, yeah.
I know lobsters have higher.
Good.
The point is, not everything has to be a competition, but I understand that, you know,
this natural, yeah, sports are naturally unequal as are many arenas in life.
What were we talking about?
I'm trying to understand.
I have one more point.
One more point about this, right, is that the reason that it would be unfair or, like,
it would suck to have everybody compete on an equal playing field, men and women in the
same sport league would be that men would win all the trophies and they would get the
champagne balls and, like, be happy and smiling.
Yes.
And women would never feel the success of having a gold medal around their neck and it would
suck.
I'm sure in some cases, but very rarely, yeah.
But, like, the argument there is that...
Neither will you or I.
Why would you do a sport if you don't win?
That is the argument.
Like, there's no reason to do the sport if you're not going to be the best of all time
in a world.
I mean, the goal is to win.
Hey, did you know that the NFL has no rule against female players and occasionally people
do try?
It's just that they never make it anywhere because, you know, they got disadvantages.
When are we going to...
Do we have any trans-female NFL players?
Oh, shit.
Would be my immediate question there.
Yeah, I mean, that could happen.
It's only a matter of time then, right?
I'm sure it could.
Probably could.
Yeah.
Seems inevitable.
By the way, I just want to shout out real quick.
In I Shield 21, the quarterback of the final guys that the devil bats fight against, their
quarterback is like the best quarterback in the world and she is a woman and she's like
the only woman on the team but she's just so good at quarterbacking and like, I think
this is the ideal we all want.
Is she just like so smart and tactical?
Is that her thing?
You know, I forget her specific like a football-based superpower which everyone has in I Shield 21.
God, I Shield 21 is the best.
I never got that far.
No, you should finish it.
It was so incredible.
Yeah, I want to reread it all the time.
It's so good and I love the art.
The art by One Punch Man, everybody.
Morata, who's doing the updated manga, just so everybody knows.
Because it's so weird to me that One Punch Man is like the thing everybody knows about,
not I Shield 21 now.
Okay, but anyway.
It never made it to the West due to its weird racial shit.
Well, maybe that's not the only reason.
I mean, frankly.
Well, sure it got scan-leaded, but that's not like a commercial release.
You're right.
I meant to say actually released.
Well, the racial shit in there is there, but in no way is it disparaging.
It's pretty similar to what we're saying here.
Can you explain to me the weird racial shit, please?
It's a little gauche.
Oh, Munchie, I'll tell you.
There is discussion.
They go into the inherent advantages of black people.
Being black.
Yeah, basically racist white coach just has to learn that, you know, in the end of the
day, black people are superior athletes and you gotta make people.
It is really funny.
I'm not kidding.
That's pretty much true.
It's pretty much true.
Oh, okay.
But it was like, I liked that because people shy away from that.
I mean, it is, you know, it does seem to be losing Kenyan, you know, I don't know.
Fucking look at football players in general.
You know, it's, you know, fact, fact, I heard this on the Internet.
The thing about Kenyans running, it's not just Kenyans.
It is a like the marathon runners.
It's a specific tribe from Kenya that is like disproportionately like good at marathon running.
Maybe that's a bad example.
But like, if you look at like, that's fine.
I just wanted to point that out as an interesting fact to it.
Yeah.
Okay.
I thought that was neat.
Well, all right.
That was relatively pleasant.
Yeah, I'll fucking, oh, just wait till after the show.
I'll fucking rip you apart.
Fucking.
Hey, I want to point out there is a, there are a couple of good videos.
There's a series of videos from SB, you guys know SB Nation?
I don't think so.
Well, it's the company that John Boyce, the guy who did 17776.
Right.
It's that company.
These videos are not by him, but there's a series called Beef History that goes into
like, oh, there's one about, there's one about A-Rod and God, what's fuck?
I forget who the guy that he had a long beef with.
That one's really good.
And there's another one about Serena Williams versus.
Jeter perhaps?
Yes.
Jeter and A-Rod.
I thought you were talking about like the history of roast beef.
No.
I wish.
It's the, it's the, each video is like the history of a particular beef between two
like professional athletes.
Yeah, that's cool.
There's a good one about A-Rod and Jeter.
And there's another really good one about Serena Williams and Maria Sharapova.
I'm not even a sports guy, but I like some of these, some of these, you know, because
these videos are about like the narrative.
Right.
It's about that human drama.
It is about that human drama.
Absolutely.
John Boyce just put, John Boyce put out a video maybe a week ago.
Oh God, I forget the title of it, but it is an examination of Bob's in sports as in just
like, he just tracks the prevalence of people named Bob in professional sports.
And it's weird because like you can see he tracks like in, like he tracks them like by
sport and like overall, and like there's a huge spike in Bob's and it's suddenly, like
there's only at its peak, there were like 600, there were like 600 Bob's in professional
sports.
Today, nine.
Bob's are dying out.
Oh my God.
It's a genocide.
It is.
It's a Bob.
This is the kind of Tism we need more of in the world.
And he goes through a couple of noteworthy Bob's like Bob's Cyclone who lost like four
15 professional boxing rounds and then retired having never won a single match.
Rest in peace, Bob.
But he kept showing up night after night.
That's, I respect that.
I respect that.
He put, he put the time in.
Too much Bob in, not enough weave in.
He was a Bob.
That's true.
He was a note in this symphony.
He mattered.
Fair.
True.
Valor.
What do you say we move on to the voicemails, lads?
Anybody, anything else?
Are we good?
I've been dying to move on to voicemails because it is a voicemail that I've listened to before
the show that I know you have picked.
Oh, you think so?
Okay.
I just guarantee it.
And I'm going to have a lot to say about it.
Oh, okay.
All right.
We shall see.
By the way, just so everyone knows, I basically just picked them and generally nobody listens
to them or like, you know, goes and checks on them beforehand.
As far as I know.
I, okay.
Well, I actually listened to a few of them beforehand.
What I'll do is I have notifications for the email for the procrastinators on my phone.
So I'll always get notifications when someone uploads a voicemail.
So if there's ever, listen, guys, if you want me to listen to your thing beforehand, if
you really care, then get a really catchy, like, munchy, please read, please listen to
this and then I will listen to it.
So there you go.
There's how you do it.
Although it's still, if you're not here for the episode, we probably still won't play it.
So it's, you're still kind of up in the air, but do your best, everybody.
Okay.
Let's move on.
Oh, before we get to the proper voicemails, we have a man on the case, a man on the hunt
for the pizza party podcast.
We've got some wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, Nate, please before, before, before you say
that, I just want to say that before like yesterday night, I was driving around with my friend
who was in town again, and he turned to me and he said, said, munchy, so I've listened
to the PCP and my heart, my heart dropped.
To pity your stomach, yeah.
And he says, what is this, like, where's the podcast meme?
I don't know.
Where is it?
I started to sweat bullets and I'm like, I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know what you mean.
I don't understand what you're saying.
Denied, denied.
And then we're speeding down the highway and I get out of the car as fast as I can.
Yeah, that's better.
I start bromeling.
You know, ducking around.
Yeah, they roll down the incline.
Oh, well, maybe we'll be able to have some answers for him after we listen to this voicemail.
Okay, this is from Detective Kleiner Hut.
Let's see what he's got.
Go.
Greetings.
This is Detective Kleiner Hut.
I'm a detective for the Bureau of Foreign Investigation.
All right, so I've been getting a lot of foreign mail from an anonymous sender telling me about
the case of a lost podcast, the pizza party podcast.
Sounds interesting, but the hair up don't think it's important.
So I've decided to take the party case into my own two hands.
Problem is, I'm foreign and a tourist visa ain't gonna be enough to solve this case.
It's a looseness.
You guys just accepted gay marriage, so I beg of you.
I might have to give a swap or two.
I will become a homosexual for the case.
Detective Kleiner Hut, I'm going to the US for the pizza party case.
Tata for now, gentlemen.
Oh, and Pia.
Tata.
The moment God told me to bring my tiniest hat or bad things are gonna happen.
Huh.
What's that I want, huh?
Okay, so this guy, he's going gay so we can get a green card so we can come to the United
States and search for the podcast.
That's dedication.
That's, yeah.
He's willing to go full gay.
Yeah, he's going all the way full gay.
Maybe that's why I could never find the podcast because I wasn't willing to commit to that
level.
Yeah, that well.
You know, the problem with gays is just they're marketing.
The guy that adapted slogan, I've got one for you, go all the way, go full gay, TM, trademarked
and whatever.
Yeah, that's pretty good.
I think we'll get a lot of converts as a result of that one.
Just put that on the trans flag, like Times New Roman font up old.
Yeah, good idea.
Let's put that on a t-shirt.
Impact font.
White impact font.
Black border.
Dude, it's like a line structured like a meme.
So at the top it's go all the way and then at the bottom it's go full gay.
Exactly.
With an awkward penguin in the middle.
Yeah, you're able to stick an awkward penguin in there just for good measure.
Just throw that in there.
Just pick a poker dad.
Like a Mr. Mayhem.
You know what?
You've got to put a different poker dad on each stripe.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
Because they're different colors.
I prefer the slogan I came up for the gays with on I Am Games, I believe it was gay
the prey away and I stand by it.
That's excellent.
Yeah.
Now that opens up many deep avenues of philosophical inquiry.
And some atheist power move.
Okay, let's move on here.
We've got, speaking of this, we've got the real homosexual is calling in.
So let's see what you have to say.
This is the same guy calling in later after the last.
It might be.
It could be.
Let's see.
Go.
I'm going to be seeking some advice.
You see, I would like nothing more than to start a simple, modest, well speaking family.
But I can't reconcile this with the additional fact that I just fucking love the cock.
I crave it.
And I won't be fucking slammed by a massive hook with a massive knob.
Oh yeah.
If you have any advice regarding this matter, it would be greatly appreciated.
Thank you in advance.
You're so cute.
You're just hipping.
I got two.
The first advice, wait, it's that you're doing the right thing.
The first advice is let the Welsh race die.
It's the right thing to do.
Okay.
It's the only thing you can do for a just future.
Yeah, please.
But okay, Ben.
What do you got?
Oh, that's way better than mine.
I was going to say two.
I was going to say two words.
Trans husband.
But no, I like yours better.
Welsh genocide now.
Win.
Literally win.
We've been waiting for 10 years.
Just release it already, please.
This seems like, I don't know how real this struggle is.
I mean, it probably is fairly rough.
Like, I don't know.
I have a strong paternal instinct, I think.
If I just so happen to be gay, that'd really throw a wrench in the works.
Wait, wait.
I mean, can't you?
No, you get a donor.
You get a donor.
You get an egg donor.
You adopt.
Yeah.
You have to get them.
You have to get them pretty young so that you can inject your accent onto them so that
they can't help but be Welsh all the time.
Indeed.
That's true.
Everything just plays Xenoblade Chronicles 2, where there's willed characters left,
right, and center.
Like, you have a kid and you want them to have the Welsh accent, so you lock them up
and the only media you allow them to consume is Xenoblade Chronicles 2.
Yeah, that's right.
And then you come back in a few months of them being in the pit and uh-oh, they're
Japanese.
Oh, shit.
We went too far.
Damn it, we switched on the Jap dub.
God damn it.
We made a mistake.
We forgot to disable it.
Yeah, we had to turn it off.
Yeah, another one bites the dust.
Well, uh-uh-uh, you know, I don't know, look into adoption, yeah, I'm sure there's, you
know, I don't know, there's fucking gay dudes out there, you've got big old families.
Just get ahead of me.
Be the best dad you can be.
The proud gay dad.
You know, we have two gay dads around here.
The proud, proud tradition of two gay dads.
Indeed, indeed.
One day.
Welcome back to best dad ever.
Who you are with.
Maybe I'll have another child monthly.
Well, we'll have you go with Barry's broods.
I mean, it's only utilitarian.
I have to have at least nine wives, I think, that's the math how it works out in order
to, you know, be keeping the train running at any one moment.
Maybe I'll actually make a fucking family.
Okay, let's move on.
We got a call from God.
God is calling in.
Oh, God, this asshole.
Tom's had some harsh words for him recently, but, you know, maybe, uh, some harsh words
right now.
Okay, let's see what he has to say.
Go.
Hello.
It is me, God.
My question to the DCD is, if you were to meet me, God, what would you ask me?
Yes.
God.
Can't you handle the reverb assholes?
Turn down the reverb is the first thing I'd ask.
Is that, that's it?
That's it?
I'd ask you from where you hail.
I'd ask for a fucking, I'd ask to fucking leave me alone, please.
Don't, don't, don't ever talk to me or my gate, my two gay sons ever again.
I'd say, I'd say put dispenser here and I'd point nine.
Tom, Tom, you've had some, some back and forth with God recently.
What would you say if he appeared before you?
Uh, fuck you, buddy.
Yeah.
I mean, okay.
I hate God.
What's the deal with this capitalism thing?
What's with all this inequality?
God damn it, God.
I'm about to ruin the next, the voice down for the next two months.
God, can you please put a wah-wah on your next, uh, your next recording, please?
Oh wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I take my answer back.
I have, I have the perfect thing to ask God.
Okay.
Where's the podcast?
Yes!
Oh my God, I couldn't, I had abandoned hope.
I had abandoned hope.
I didn't even think of it.
No.
That's true.
You're right.
You got to keep hope alive.
That's, that's the litmus test.
If he can't give you an answer, clearly not actually God.
That was right online.
Oh, that's so true.
Atheism for the win.
You got him coming and going, Tom.
That's finesse right there.
Uh, I would repeat the entire final cut scene of the Simpsons game for Xbox 360, the Simpsons
Finland confronts God.
And then I would challenge him to a DDR match and I would win using the Xbox 360's terrible
D-pad.
But I would still overcome any challenge in front of me.
And I would destroy the Prey station.
I would destroy it.
Oh yes.
Please do.
Um, okay.
Let's move on.
Uh, the Japanese man, Yuta, uh, is calling it.
Let's, uh, let's hear you say, go.
Okay.
So here's a D-D, a D-D bro impression.
Uh-huh.
So Japanese is in the middle of hell here.
Stop.
Stop this.
Let's shut up fucking down, I hope.
Nate, Nate, we trust you to get things for quality and experience at the best quality.
There he goes.
All right.
Is that it?
Is this the first inductee into the voice jail as we were discussing before?
Get this guy on the teen CP.
Oh yeah.
We announced, we announced a new concept on the PCP.
You've heard of the Hall of Fame.
You've heard of the voice grail.
The Gary for the voice jail, for when you're a shitty voice girl that we fucking hate,
we're putting you in the voice jail.
And you Japanese man, you're going straight to the fucking voice jail.
If you get put in the voice jail, you have to double your patronage.
You have to.
That's how you get out.
It's the only way to get out.
You gotta buy your way out.
That's right.
The joke's on us because anyone in the voice jail is pledging nothing.
There's already a zero dollar patron, so doubling it is still zero.
Dammit.
Nah.
Plus 10.
That looks amazing.
We gotta define exactly how many PC pennies it takes to buy your way out.
You know what?
I mean, we can adjudicate on a case by case basis.
We can levy fines.
This guy's like a twenty dollar monthly.
We're clearly on a first name basis with God now, so we can offer indulgences to anybody
who's in the voice jail.
We can offer them an affordable payment plan to mortgage their way out of voice jail.
Okay.
All right.
Let's move along.
We've got one from hashtag where's the megafauna?
Let's find out.
Go.
I love megafaunas so much.
Hey, everybody.
Last week or so, y'all were talking about the domestication of the avocado, and I gotta
say I love that shit.
Let me tell you how it all went down.
You know how fruits and shit have seeds, and sometimes we swallow on an accident?
These were designed that way, so we could shit them out elsewhere and give them some
fertilizer.
Well, avocados were the same way.
Central America used to be home to all sorts of megafauna, like giant sloths and shit,
who could one-shot an avocado and crap out the pit.
But then they all went extinct because of climate change and rise of man and shit, and avocados
were like, fuck what now?
But then people showed up and were like, I like this, and started farming them, and
that's like the only reason avocados are still around today.
Natural history gets me rock hard.
Hell yeah.
Were we talking about the domestication of the avocado?
I don't remember what we were saying about it.
I have no recollection of anything before.
It was the most important day of your life.
To us, it was Sunday.
Yeah.
Oh, it's so true.
It's harsh but fair.
By the way.
I love hearing stories about things that should not be, but humans have prolonged its extinction
just for our own benefit.
There are so many instances of plants or animals, or just things that we have just kept in the
world to make ourselves happy.
I bet that a natural avocado doesn't look anything like the thing we buy at a supermarket.
You ever seen wild bananas?
Yes.
Like what bananas used to look for, like before we fucking...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, no, no, no.
There are some crazy bananas that are like spheres.
They're like all seed, and they look fucking nasty.
Did I want a sphere banana?
How would you pull that?
You don't.
Fuck it.
Here, let me find a picture.
I don't want to eat it.
I know exactly what you're talking about, and they look like fuck.
They're from Papua New Guinea.
Yeah, oh god.
They're really gross.
They're really, really gross.
Copy image, post in this in the...
I had heard this somewhere, and I don't know if it's true, but the reason that banana-flavored
candy doesn't taste like bananas, because it's a different kind of banana that doesn't
exist anymore when they made the flavor, is that real?
Yeah, yeah, there was another strain.
This is bizarre.
I know what you're talking about.
This is always...
Dude, okay, okay.
Apples used to taste like raw potatoes when you ate them, but they used to bread them.
We bread them to be how apples are now.
That's fucked up, man.
But also gross.
That's not fucked up.
That's delicious.
Yeah.
True.
Hey, also, I've taken the liberty of...
I just made a document.
Oh, Cavendish.
Wait, no.
Cavendish banana was...
Yeah.
Well, I don't remember if Cavendish is the kind that survived or the kind that died out.
No, no, no.
Okay, okay, okay.
So, Cavendish is right now.
Yeah.
Cavendish are modern-day bananas.
Before modern-day bananas, it wasn't like...
Was it Gross Michael?
Yeah, exactly.
Gross Michael.
It didn't go from what you just posted, Ben, to our modern-day banana.
There's been various iterations.
And Gross Michael, fun fact, which I learned from my favorite YouTube channel, Laffy Pursuits.
So when you taste banana candy, right?
And you think, okay, I'm ready to taste some banana, but it doesn't really taste like
banana, like modern banana.
It has a very...
It has a different taste.
And you may think to yourself, that's just because, you know, it's artificial flavoring.
It's different candy.
No.
Wrong.
You are actually tasting the past, because the banana candy flavoring that everyone
uses is based off the Gross Michael, the past iteration of bananas, and it was flavored
to be like the Gross Michael instead of our modern Cavendish's.
How crazy is that shit?
Fuck you, bananas.
Why don't they update it?
Whoa.
Because that's what everyone is used to having candy taste like, you know?
It would be like, oh, why is banana case different now?
Is there any way to get the old banana back?
I want to try it.
Yes.
But there are a few, you know, they are not widely distributed because of a disease that
ripped through and destroyed like a lot of the banana population a while ago.
So now, Gross Michael is like an oddity and a rarity.
Banana Hitler didn't fuck around.
No.
I just made a document that's going to be in the show notes, people.
It's the official PCP Hall of Fame slash shame slash voice jail, whatever.
It got them snakes riddle my ass Batman, grail, sure, whatever.
In the Hall of Shame, we've got the Japanese man, Yuda, and I'm sure there's others I'm
forgetting.
I'm sure there's got to be more.
Okay.
They didn't know they were committing a crime now.
You guys know now that there will be repercussions.
There will be repercussions.
Yes.
Okay.
They've been made aware.
Well, I don't know.
This is really repercussions if we're going to be remembering them.
Hey, what about one?
Remember?
Well, no.
I don't want to comment.
Talk about how terrible Yuda is.
Talk about how he's a nightmare.
Doc's Yuda.
Everybody docs Yuda in chat right now.
Okay.
I think OneSpar should be on the Hall of Fame.
I agree.
He had a saga.
Remember the OneSpar saga?
Yeah.
OneSpar Weekly.
Fagely.
Oh, yeah.
He briefly became Wolfspar.
Oh, okay.
You know what?
I do remember that now.
Yeah, fuck it.
All right.
He's in.
Okay, but no more reaction.
You have to be current.
You've got to be up-to-date next time.
Yeah, okay.
That's fair.
Okay.
All right.
But let's move along here, people.
We've got lots to get through.
Next one, we've got a voicemail from the humble John.
Okay, let's see what John has for us.
Big Bird?
A one.
Malina.
Two.
A one.
Three.
This one's for Nate.
You've said an expectation long ago, expressing your hate.
I can relate.
And I've been looking forward to this thing you mentioned on a podcast.
You did with Diggy Bro.
Yeah.
About a terrible show.
But the one I want to hear from you.
One is the one that has this song.
Yeah.
So when are you going to make a video that destroys your favorite little sister show?
They say be the change that you want to see, but you really don't want to hear from me.
That was so good.
That was incredible.
I think that's the Auremo theme song.
I was going to say that's got to be the Auremo.
It's got to be.
Holy shit.
That was so...
Is that a voice grail right off the bat?
I think that he does that.
That's a voice grail.
That is for sure a voice grail.
I'm going to put John Auremo.
John Auremo.
That's his name.
Well, you've got to do it now.
You've got to do it now, Nate.
You know what?
You spelled it wrong.
The I goes before the M.
Or a emo.
Man, I fucking hate that show.
As you should, man.
As you should.
You know, there actually happened to be another voicemail about this as well, asking me about
it.
And so, people, I just want to remind everyone, you know, maybe I didn't say this with enough
force before.
I'm going full-time YouTubing, ladies and gentlemen, and what do you think I'm doing
that for?
What do you think I'm trying to do, but finally get this bugbear off my back?
It's all about that Auremo, baby.
So that's not my first project, but as everyone knows, it's in the works.
So you will be seeing a lot more of best anime ever's from me in the future.
So get ready to slurp them down deliciously.
Everyone or emo, best anime ever, as everyone knows.
So we'll, I'm excited to see more of that.
One Spark, you could add some backing instrumental to that.
If you can do that, buddy.
That'd be great.
Just see what you can do.
See what you can do.
Oblivionfall, you mean?
Oblivionfall, what did I say?
You said One Spark.
One Spark.
Congratulations.
Congratulations, dude.
Yeah, sorry about Oblivion.
Okay.
Moving on.
That was so good.
He clearly wrote out lyrics.
It was fantastic.
That was really nice.
That was a really nice job with the lyrics there.
Oh my God.
That was so sick.
Okay.
Parody songs are like sort of a difficult art where if you make them lame, they can
just be really, really stupid.
Absolutely.
If you don't make the lyrics fit, if you don't make the lyrics funny and fit the tone of
the song or the syllables, then you've made a shit product.
For sure.
We hate you.
But if you make them good, oh.
If you're doing a cover and you fall even a little short of nailing it with the lyrics,
you just eat shit way harder, you know what I mean?
I can say to this kind of my area of expertise is I've written quite a few of these over
the years and hope to do more in the coming months and years, a lot.
It's a very fine balance.
I don't know.
I do this a lot in my content in general.
Maybe it stems from this.
I did this first, I don't know, whatever.
When you're doing a parody, you can't be too overly sincere and overly saccharine about
it.
You've got to have a playful element to it.
Then you've got to earn your sincerity if you're going to hit some at the end.
I would say that the artistry of a parody song is in how you re-cajigger the lyrics.
You've got to make the way you do that funny and clever and sound great.
Remember?
Remember the opening of keg reviews or the song at the end, blah blah blah.
Let me see.
I fear I told the little Fib about my being cool but now I'm 8 on the line so don't think
I'm a fool.
I wasn't quite the super alpha pony like I claim.
The fact is that I was a nerd who everyone called gay.
Now see, that's a classic line.
Everybody love that.
Is this R.A.E.M.O? I posted the thing.
Oh, let me see.
I saw this.
Yeah.
That's her.
The people know.
Okay.
First of all, no.
That's Umaru-chan.
My little Umaru-chan.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Possibly.
Hey, I don't know.
They call Orange-chan.
This is a similar little system.
I hate Umaru.
Oh, maybe even more.
I don't know.
As a person, Umaru is a significantly worse person than Kirino.
Oh.
I hate the program.
I mean, I hate them both, too.
I hate the entire endeavor.
Yes.
It's bankrupt.
By the way, shout out to atstingercropes on Twitter who drew this funny picture that
you should be looking at.
A little link in the description.
They're cool.
I like them.
It's got missed opportunity.
It should say doomaru.
You know, that's true.
Because it's doom, right?
Alas, get a better luck next time.
That's it for your life.
Better luck on the next Wheel of Reincarnation turn, my dude.
Okay.
Doctor Wolf II has left us a message, ladies and gentlemen.
Oh my God, five on one.
One was enough.
Okay.
I hope we see him at BaronyCon.
I hope to God.
Oh, he'll be there.
But let's hear what he has to say.
You know, be there.
Well, this is his big brother, Doctor Wolf II.
Okay, let's go.
Oh, it'll be Doctor Wolf I.
Two episodes from when yesterday's playing.
Another listener called in about a situation I'd like to coin in no offensive way as light
cooking.
Oh, yes.
I mean, with everything y'all had to say, just about not being personally comfortable
with a situation like that, but I'd like to get specific with my question.
Let's say one of us, one of us is dating a model.
It's in the realm of possibilities, so hear me out, humor me.
Try to imagine that world where that's happening.
How would that person cope with his girl receiving unsolicited messages that contain
explicit materials on the reg?
Thanks.
So he's talking about me, obviously.
My girlfriend is a model.
That's pretty simple.
Yeah.
I mean, it's nothing to do, you know, they're unsolicited, what are you going to do about
it?
Indeed.
What's to say?
This is almost, so you know what, I actually, I did kind of want to respond, because frankly,
I was thinking to myself that, I mean, I forget what we were talking about, like dating
a porn star, dating like a, there was a voicemail about like companionship.
Was this the same guy who was on the, God, what was that website called?
Oh, Seeking Arrangements, I think?
Seeking?
Yes.
This is not the same.
This is way less of an interesting question, honestly.
It is.
There's nothing to discuss here.
I mean, I thought it was, you know what, I'll say this though, okay, like on the spectrum
of cuckolding, because that's really what we're talking about, and like, so this is a
wide spectrum.
And okay, like, I'll just say that frankly, the people who are like, involved with a woman
who are being the least cucked, I'm not endorsing this, but I'm just saying that I think the
truth is that it's basically like, like those like Islamic extremist people who like, force
their women to cover themselves head to toe, so that no other man can see their woman.
I think those are the least cucked men on the planet, because you know, they're obviously
going over the top, and they're-
No, that has nothing, no.
That's dumb.
Well, let me finish my point.
Okay.
Well, I object to your premise here, because that is something that the man is doing.
Whether you're being cucked is not up to you, it is up to your partner, you know what I
mean?
I mean, I mean-
It's entirely about their decisions.
Theoretically, one way to avoid getting cucked is to like, you know, you could like, intimidate
or imprison your significant other.
I mean, in an amoral sense, one could do that.
Yeah.
But I mean-
But that doesn't make them any less cucked than a man who doesn't do that, and whose
woman isn't cucking him.
I think if you're the sort of person who has to imprison people in order to make sure
that nobody steals them away, or that they don't leave, then you are the biggest cuck
of all, because you can't hold onto them with your own like, qualities.
Well, I mean, I mean, in a sense, that's true.
I think-
I feel like that's so far down like the ridiculous angle that it's like, I don't know, what
does he mean?
I mean, I'm trying to get to the root of his point here, but like, I just re- I think
that nothing, nothing you do can make you any less cucked.
If you're cucked, you're cucked, and if you're not, you're not.
Well, I don't know if I agree with that, because like-
Well, I mean, I think like the inaction of like letting it happen and not like putting
your foot down.
If you're just like a shitty BF, and your girlfriend is like, fuck him, I'm gonna fuck
Chad, then I mean, you know, you're involved in the process somewhat.
Well, okay, then you've been cucked, but then it is, it is your, you know, then the question
is, well, how do I respond to this?
And the answer is with a fucking atom bomb, you got to turn that key, you got to put that
key in the lock and hit that big red button.
I mean, I'll follow my example, though, to the extreme.
So first of all, on the whole like receiving unsolicited dick pics and whatnot, like there's
no control.
I mean, obviously that's, there's nothing she could do.
And I mean, you could say-
That's something, that's probably something that most girls-
I was going to say, to once again put on my, well, to just go full feminist as I do every
moment of my waking life, the, you know, women just have to deal with that in general.
And like, what's the solution?
Stop being an attractive woman who's on social media, is that the proposal?
So again, I'm not trying to moralize, I'm just saying-
I like this completely, like modest, like normal opinions are going full feminist, guys.
Like deep down the rabbit hole.
You know, maybe-
Well, I did just endorse to Sharia Law, so, you know-
There's some disbandages, maybe there are some, no, full feminist, full feminist, full
feminist.
But my only point is, okay, you know what, maybe, I will say it, I think that as a man
who has a girlfriend who does, in fact, produce and distribute images of her looking, you
know, relatively sexy, she's a sexy girl, obviously, but you know, in bathing suits
and whatnot, do I think that that's slightly more on the cuckolding spectrum than someone
whose girlfriend does not do that?
Yes, yes I do, but that being said, like, let's not, you know, obviously this is a very
slight degree, this is a very modest amount here.
Alright, everyone start writing your think pieces titled, Nate Bestman admits to being
cucked.
To be cucked.
I don't know, honestly I feel bad even saying it, obviously it's not actually the case,
but I just gotta be honest, gotta be intellectually consistent here, and one who has like a modest
at home wife who just like wears her big Victorian dresses that cover her 102%.
Her hoop skirts.
Yep, yep, and you know, dressed super modestly and all that.
It just, it strikes me as funny to like come at it from a very intellectually like consistent
perspective when this is very much an emotional thing.
I mean, that depends on what she's writing to.
What does it matter, what does it matter one way or the other whether you are technically
cucked like a certain percent or not?
I mean, I'm approaching it more in the technical sense than the emotional one, because I do
not feel cucked, but like technically analyzing it, I think that there is, you know.
Why would you even go to the effort of making sure that you are being honest with that when
it, you don't feel it?
Well, I just try to be intellectually consistent, and like maybe I'm wrong, but like this is
just my thought process on the subject.
Like, like, how do you know people like add up the numbers the same way you do?
I don't.
Here's my, here's my counter example.
Okay.
Say you got a couple that are in an open relationship and one of them fucks another person, that's
not cucking.
But again, unlike my technical analysis here, the whole relationship is kind of dual way
cucking.
Dual way cucking?
No.
That doesn't make sense.
You know, my worldview about this cucking spectrum is actually pretty flawed.
I'm noticing.
So, you know.
It's a little, it's a little weird.
It's maybe.
Backpedal.
Maybe there's some mistakes here.
Undig that hole.
Undig that hole quick.
It invites certain lines of inquiry.
Cucking is such a vague thing that everyone means it in a different way, and it's hard
to actually have a conversation about it because no one actually, you could mean actual cucking
as a real thing that exists that has a proper name, cucking, you know what I'm saying about?
Like more far removed, like the general sense of just cheating, if you just make it like
a personality trait where dude, that guy is such a cuck.
Fuck that guy.
But people do use it that way now.
So, it's hard to say that that's totally wrong, I guess.
Well, I'm not saying that it is wrong.
I'm just saying it's another definition that they're just playing out.
That's a figurative cuck without being a literal cuck.
I guess that's true.
I was watching Joe Rogan the other day, and he had like a debate with the Adam Ruins Everything
guy, and basically this was a discussion on like whether-
Ah, yes, Adam.
Well, Adam, I can't remember his name.
Adam Conover.
Yeah, I don't know his last name, but I know-
He, um-
It's Adam Conover.
I confused him with Alton Brown all the time.
Oh, yeah.
Let's kill yourself.
Well, okay.
Only Alton Brown likes you.
They had a debate about whether or not alphas and betas like exist in human beings.
And basically, I mean, it immediately seemed like Adam was using the like, like the biological,
like inherent like wolves, like they have alphas and betas, like, you know, like a naturalistic
sort of setup.
And he's like, no, no, no, that doesn't exist in humans.
Like we don't operate on that level.
We're like far more complex.
I have something to say about this.
My only point is just that like Joe Rogan, like he was definitely saying like, no, no,
like alphas and betas, like you got like a strong alpha dude and you got like a little,
you know, intimate, timid guy, like that alpha beta dynamic is right there.
But like, obviously he's just using kind of a different definition from what Adam's
using.
So like-
Yeah, if you define alpha and beta to mean confident guy versus shy guy, then yeah, obviously
they exist.
So, um, think about, think about alphas.
Did you know that that like wolf research was discredited and like that alpha, that
actually doesn't exist in like wolf packs in nature?
Okay.
Don't like gorillas have it too though or something?
Well, they have a, they do have a, I think they have like a, fuck, they have the-
A big leader guy?
Is it called the alpha?
I think so.
I think there's, I don't know if it's the alpha or if it's not, yeah, yeah, I think
like a gorilla has a, has something like that.
But like that, that research where the word came out of that like this happens in wolves,
like that same researcher did more research that like invalidated his old hypothesis was
like, yeah, all that stuff I said about alpha wolves doesn't happen.
Just to be clear, I mean, what did he claim?
Like there was like one dominant leader that would like get all the girls basically and
that-
It's something like that.
Okay.
Yeah.
I mean, I've, I feel like wolves, they're very much more of a collaborative group effort
sort of thing.
I mean, I mean, all groups of animals that, you know, successful, they group together,
but like-
Even us.
I've seen nature documentaries and it seems like they just work as like a team rather
than one guy is big and the others are small.
Um, yeah.
Though, I mean, I mean, they're like, it's not, you know, not every naturalistic system
is like, you know, even or whatever.
So there's like, there's only so many like females to breed with or whatever.
So it would make sense for there to be some-
I mean, yeah, there's always the ones, there's the ones that are the most good for the thing.
Like, I think alpha and beta, it means something a little different than just, uh, I'm talking
out of my butt.
I mean, even, even from the beginning, like as soon as people started using that like
alpha dog, like wolf research and like mapping it onto humans, we were already like being
figurative.
Yeah.
I mean, that's true.
Like, do I believe that there are confident and less confident humans and that this impacts
their like social graces and skill and achievement?
I mean, yeah, but you know, if that's not what it biologically means that they, fair enough.
By the way, are you guys aware of how hyenas are like structured socially, especially
like men and women?
Yes.
It's fucked up.
The men are repressed.
Those poor repressed gamer hyenas need to rise up and overthrow the cruel matriarchy because
the women are bigger and stronger and bully them and it's mean and I don't like it.
Male hyenas are fucked.
Dude, have you heard of spiders?
Uh, a little bit.
Is it just that-
Male spiders are tiny and the females kill them and eat them after they impregnate, are
impregnated by them.
That's fucked up.
Oh, wait, so, so the just like female hyenas are the bigger like more dominant ones?
Yeah, they're bigger, stronger and dominate like the whole social hierarchy.
I mean, really, what is it like?
There's nothing inherently like more-
Guys, we gotta stop all these trans male hyenas from competing in the male hyena arena.
In the hyena arena.
It's not fair to those poor, you know, natural-
I'm a turf for hyenas for sure, coming down a hard stance.
We gotta have the male hyena leagues.
Hyena.
They can't compete.
I'm a trans exclusionary radical hyenaist.
A turf.
Lion King 4 hyena arena.
Guys, you aren't using the right term.
Yeah.
We all know that saying hyena is just so 1990s, we have our new term.
The phrase that comes up with it.
You gotta say yin.
Guys, I just love being a yin.
Is this the furry equivalent?
Is this like how they slang?
Or is this just like the new, is this what zoomers call hyenas?
This is slang for hyena.
Yo.
You guys just love saying yin.
Yo, me and my boys, we're chillin' in the safari.
Say it right now.
Say it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yin.
I'm yinin.
I'm a big fan.
So, like, so when you're on Twitter and you're retweeting your cute hyena pics and you're
like, oh, look at that yin.
Like, like, yin is to hyena as doggo is to dog.
Exactly.
I hate doggo.
Doggy is better than doggo.
Well, doggo is like the Reddit version.
Well, yin tops it all.
Doggo is like the mage version, which is good in some situations, but not all.
All right.
I'm thoroughly enamored with hyena arena.
Yeah, hyena arena.
Like hyena arena, hyena arena, hyena arena, hyena arena, or yin arena, yin arena for short.
Yeah, we gotta save time, because we're gonna be saying these words a lot.
In the jungle, the mighty savannah, the lion is a hyena.
All right.
Let's move on.
Please.
Yeah.
Okay.
We've got Hell No Fresh is calling in with Hell No Fresh Freestyle World Star Exclusive.
Yeah.
Okay.
Shut the fuck up during all of this.
Let's commence.
Go.
All right, Nate.
I see how it is.
I think you're a big, strong man, big, tough guy talking shit about instant ramen, huh?
Yeah.
All right, dog.
I'll remember that.
Yeah.
See how tough you are in a minute.
Throw a shade at my ramen recipe.
I'll put it simply in soliloquy.
You can rest in peace.
Fuck a tutorial.
I'm cooking up bars now.
I'll shoot you into space like Joseph did the cars now, because you're the type of
nigga that fuck with hearted bitches.
It's all engagement till the social workers get you.
Get the picture.
I'm no longer fucking with you.
Thought you could get away with shit and all my dishes, did you?
Spit bars quick, instant ramen in the booth.
How about you make like Sekiro a bunch of suicide tooth?
I rhyme for my bootleg food.
It's Hell No Fresh.
Easy to follow recipes, John Favreau flex.
You're dead.
Now, I'm the best guy ever.
You're just a ghost in the shell.
Oh, well.
Good luck in development.
Hell, kid.
Yo, shout some munchin'.
The carbonara was fire.
I think we're done here.
Peace.
Yes!
My two favorite things.
Hating Nate and loving myself.
Wow.
It's so cool.
That's lame.
Okay.
Combination.
Please allow me to have the floor, because this requires a lot of information.
So to start this out with, I would say this, this beautiful song, you know, obviously anti-night
which we can all get behind, you know, the working class and his past recipe on the last
episode.
Holy grail.
However, however, Hell No Fresh, I've got something to say that I've got some follow-up
for you.
So last episode, if you all recall, Hell No Fresh called in with a recipe for peanut butter
instant ramen.
So it was, you would make some top ramen, mix in some sesame oil, some red pepper flakes
and some scallions and put some instant top ramen and get that chicken flavoring and
the peanut butter.
It would be delicious.
Now, immediately upon hearing this, I thought to myself, sounds delicious, sign me the
fuck up.
But those of you who know, my kitchen was not working.
So I had to wait a few days.
And then the day that my kitchen became available to you, which has happened, everyone, that
soggy is over.
And I had to look.
Hooray.
Ready and willing, prepared to make this top ramen.
The kitchen arc begins.
Yeah.
The kitchen arc ends.
So I, this was going to be the first dish that I made in my new kitchen.
Hell No Fresh, you had the honor of being the inaugurable person that would make the
recipe for this brand new spanking kitchen that I had in my disposal.
So I got all my greens.
I got the scallions.
I got the peanut butter.
I got the red pepper flakes.
I got the spicy sesame oil.
I got the top ramen.
I got everything.
And I was ready to go full in all chips on the table.
And so I got all my greens.
I was chopping up the scallions.
And so I thought to myself, wait a second, wait a second, hold on.
This is, in occasion, this is a special event.
You know what I had to do that I've been putting off for a while and since I haven't had a kitchen
and I haven't been able to use it, I required, I acquired a chef grade knife from my girlfriend's
father.
He gave it to me because he took note of my cooking and so he gave me a really high quality
sharp ass knife.
Was this boards of like adamantium or something?
What's the, yeah.
Okay.
It's ultra sharp.
And so I, you know, I'm going to use it for the first time on this.
Hell no fresh.
Listen, buddy, me and you were bonded.
We're so linked.
We're going to bet to J.O.
And I'm at three seconds.
Artquist crystals sink.
Nice.
And so I got down my chef knife and just, I want to point picture.
I was so excited.
Right.
I was so eager.
I was so just ready to live the cooking lifestyle again, to be the chef that I was always meant
to be.
I had this professional grade knife.
I had this recipe that I was so just interested in and I was so happy.
I put my fingers a little bit too close to the blade.
I didn't practice proper blade safety.
I did not curl my fingers the way they're supposed to.
I did not make the block so that my, the, the, the, the, uh, the braid would hit up against
my, my midfingers and you know, knock on my finger.
So I chopped down while I'm making the scallions.
Oh God.
Wow.
What?
Yeah.
A slice of my fingers are gone and I'm not saying like, I'm saying a slice of my fingers
are gone.
And if you look at my fingers now, literally there is a deformation on my fingers.
Even now there is like a slice of it visibly off nine.
My hair now lopsided forever.
My, my, my left middle just forever deformed because of chefs in general and specifically
you hell no thresh, but I will say, and because of that, I'm putting you in the hell and in
the voice jail because of you cause, but wait, but wait, but wait, but wait, what's this?
What's this?
I've cut my finger and I'm really pissed off and it's bleeding everywhere and I have
to go to the emergency room and I have to pay $75 for them to just give me antibiotic
cream.
I'm receiving the, I'm receiving, but with rage, but, but I can't let these scallions
go to waste.
What, what am I going to do?
And so I had the bandages on the next day.
I, I'm, I'm in pain.
It's bleeding profusely, but you know what I do?
You know what I do?
I have to finish the fight.
I have to, I, I, I, I just have to in the weird, weird L's words, just eat it.
And so I go to town, I practice, I practice blade safety.
I'm a master of this katana folded 10,000 times.
I chop the scallions properly this time.
I get rid of the dead skin and flesh.
They're just residually on them.
I wash them properly.
I put in the top ramen.
I put in the sesame oil.
I put in the red pepper flakes and you know what I fucking do?
You dumb fucking slut, instead of using water, I update this shit.
I improvise on this shit.
I use homemade chicken stock instead of that water.
The chicken flavoring is off the charts.
I fucking grill some new bacon and, oh, uh, uh, peanut butter goes right with bacon.
Put that in there as well.
So I'm eating this delicious fucking meal, hell no fresh.
I'm eating this delicious meal that you have given me this recipe.
Moff it to my own specifications.
I take a bite and it is mind blowing.
It is absolutely undescribable.
The pleasure in which I am, in terror, terror taking in when I eat this peanut butter instant
ramen.
The, just the, the emulsification of the peanut butter just make this very light peanut butter
sauce inside of the top ramen is so orgasmic.
Why must, why must brothers quarrel?
Why must there be division?
Hell no fresh.
You are in the voice grail for the rest of my life.
Hit me up.
DM me.
We are brothers in arms.
And you know what?
I think we're going to have a long career together.
And then that's the end of my tale and I've been waiting all week to sell.
That's beautiful.
Hell no fresh.
Welcome to the grail.
Welcome to the hollow fame.
Yeah.
I would say that rap alone was enough to get into the grail because that was devastating.
It was Nate.
I think you might have to leave the PCP soon.
Or well you're just going to have to answer with a fire track of your own.
That's the way you get around it.
That's the only option.
That's the way you beat a rap.
Dude, me a mouth of a perfect time.
Make a rap.
Man, I wish I could rap.
Sometimes I think about maybe I should try to compose a rap.
That's too hard.
Hey man, just download a beat as you know, Jesse and did you just do from the internet.
Work on some lyrics.
Yeah.
And do it.
I just have no idea how to like, how do you like write it?
I want to figure out how to write that.
Is there like a structure you follow?
I mean I'm sure you could do it any way you want.
I've made some in the past but I felt too silly, too bad.
You know what?
In the same vein of munchy learning to cook and getting all into it or learning to code.
I want to learn to rap.
I want to figure out that shit out.
I don't know where to start.
I suppose I should just ask Digi but he's Digi.
He might not have like the teacher sort of.
Indeed.
Not an ability to pass on his knowledge.
The aspect.
Nate, I want to move away from the ashes of the Hello Fresh debate and it may come up
but I do want to move into the Forcing Nate to Cook arc which I am going to bring up every
single episode until it happens because you know it has to be done.
You know it has to be done.
I don't care about cooking frankly, I just want to cook like the calories I need in the
day properly.
I don't care about things that taste good.
That seems like a waste of effort to me.
Yeah, I agree, Nate.
I agree.
It's easy to make something that tastes good and is calorie efficient if you can do it
yourself.
If you can make healthy food that's like, you hate your macros and whatnot and you also,
taste great, that'll probably like keep the train running smoothly and you'll be like,
I can't wait to make the food.
Literally the difference between, let me give you a tip.
Cooking tip, any vegetable, any vegetable at all, olive oil or butter, salt and pepper.
Add it to that, roast it in the oven and it's delicious.
There's like no exception to it.
Indeed.
It does, yeah.
The salt just makes it good.
Yeah, that's it.
It's like all you need to do to cook like any fucking vegetable.
You know what I've been doing?
Yeah.
A friend of mine sent me a care package, it was a giant box full of nuts, various nuts.
Oh, it's so thematically appropriate.
Did it have an unsalted variant of a popular nut?
She's specifically, well, she, yes, yes it did and there were a bunch of other timelines
in there too.
Bara nuts, there were peely nuts, there were like tiger nuts, whatever the fuck those
are.
They're trying to do tiger.
But mostly there was like big ass bags of peanuts, cashews and almonds and what I have
been doing is I spent a bunch of yesterday just like roasting trays of these peanuts
because they're uncooked peanuts.
I've been roasting and salting them myself and putting them in mason jars and they're
so good.
That's incredible.
It's better when you roast them yourself than when you buy them in pre-roasted, oh, it's
so good.
It's like emotionally gratifying, making this raw material undergo this process and transmuting
it into this delicacy.
I feel like I'd be a healthier human if I cooked more, I'd just be more in tune with
the world.
Yeah.
Seems like a real thing.
Just cooking is so fucking, it makes you feel so sexy and desirable as a human being.
I agree.
It's such a great feeling to be able to go downstairs and be like, what do I got in
here?
I got this and then just, I'll make this dish.
Dude, fucking, we're making the peanut butter top ramen and I just like, I looked in the
fridge and I saw that we had the carcass of a chicken and I was like, ah, shit, you know
what I can do?
I can totally make like a quick little sock out of this and it would be really easy and
I can put some of the leftover like meat bits inside of the soup itself.
Like just being resourceful like that while cooking is the best feeling.
Munchy, walk that towards his fridge, third person over the shoulder camera, slowly walk
towards it, looking at his ingredients, going, ah, shit, here we go again.
There's the meme.
Yeah.
There's the one.
With the chicken carcass.
Oh, yep.
Put a chicken carcass there, ladies and gentlemen.
I mean, for me, more than feeling cool and sexy, cooking made me feel efficient because
when I had, you know, when I had my, you know, Instacart all set up, I had my pipeline, like
I knew my ingredients and stuff and I'm just like, okay, well, you know, time to, you know,
I've got all my ingredients that I get and I know where to get them to get them for the
best price.
So they're all really cheap.
So I'm eating for relatively cheap, but I'm still eating well because I'm, you know,
I know what I'm putting into my body or whatever because I'm getting in myself and I'm, you
know, just throwing that cauliflower and shit in a pan and roasting it up and putting it
in a bowl and eating it.
And I'm like, this is exactly what I want to be eating and it's all, it's all like sorted.
Right?
Yeah.
So I've just cleaned out that, that pipeline, the, the nutrition pipeline has been, has
been cleaned and efficient eyes and maximize to deliver nutrition unto me at a minimum
expense.
I do want that.
Well, well, I do love, you know, I'm just into cooking and like as, as like an artistry
and like a passion and like a hobby.
I completely agree that a lot of the joy of cooking is like finding like optimal strats
to saved frames because, you know, I don't always want to like cook like a big ass fucking
I just want to be able to, you know, throw something together really fast and, you know,
get some something that's scrumptious and walk back upstairs.
It's not, it has to always be a federal issue.
Now I'm thinking of like you getting your, you know, meal and then doing the Mario 64
like back, like long jump back.
Yeah.
You know what this reminds me of?
Totally.
Incidentally, I was happy to, I was in a thread about Oolulilia on V the other day and like
in his description, I think this is not like his LinkedIn page or like some, no, it was
his Facebook, I think, and he was like updating like his current work status and like he works
at Walmart, I think, and he said something like, like, you know, he'd been a cashier
for many years and he said something that was along the lines of like, yeah, like my
skill level at like, you know, these like stocking shelves, like blah, blah, blah.
Like these are all like, like, these are all high level, you know, achieved close to mastery,
but when it comes to cashiering, I've maxed out my stats at cashiering.
This is on like a Facebook post, like to his family and friends, he's a good man.
He's a good man.
I've, you know, you know, I started this, this adventure, you know, I became a cashier,
but I think I've done all I can do with the medium and it's time for me to move on to
bigger and better things.
Yeah, pretty much.
Pretty much.
It just like, just like, uh, Watterson retiring from Calvin and Hobbes because he'd done everything
he could do with it.
He's like, I'm going to go out at my peak, I'm going to go out at the peak of my cashiering
career.
Okay.
On top, baby.
That's fantastic.
Okay.
Uh, uh, uh, uh, next call is from, uh, Patreon, serious questions, how to get bonus episode.
So this one is just, I'll take any excuse to talk about the bonus episode.
So let's, uh, let's listen to it.
Okay.
I have a serious question about the, like the Patreon and when you buy, like the bonus
episodes, how do you get them?
Is it like a private YouTube set of videos and then you get the links to them?
Or is it like MP3 shits you have to download?
It's like, I just want to know how you, what ways you get the episodes so I can know how
to like be able to do them because like, what if I buy the thing on mobile and then it's
like a fucking file that I can't download or some shit, you know, like, let me know
how to, what happens once you buy the bonus episodes.
Like what happens, you know, what, what do I, what happens, you know, what the fuck.
Okay.
We need to convert this potential customer to a full real customer.
And here's how we do it.
We want to change those players into payers.
That's exactly right.
We, uh, uh, okay.
Here's what you do.
So all you got to do on Patreon, you got an account or whatever you sign up and you click
on us wherever you say you want to support us.
You got to say, uh, like the $5 tiers, the one to get the bonus episodes.
And once, once you are there, once like Patreon says like, ah, here's a user who was logged
in as a $5 member or whatever, uh, what the bonus episodes are, they are YouTube videos
that are hidden and only people with the link can get there.
And like, if you, if you are a person, you're a $5 patron, like the bonus episodes are just,
they're on Patreon.
You can click them and play them there on the website, I think, but there's also just
links from there to the YouTube.
And once you're on YouTube, there's a playlist of all the bonus episodes.
And really that's the thing.
A lot of people keep track of it because that's easiest for them, but you can just do it all
through Patreon when there's a new episode released.
So, so there's your answer.
That's how you do it.
Be a patron mostly.
We release the episodes there, you know, the end of the month or whatever.
Uh, so that's it.
Now, give us your money, please.
Uh, uh, I, I have something to say.
Sure.
I have something to say.
Now, it is probably, it is probably possible with the right connections to, uh, this is
like one of those things, Ben, that's like, uh, this is like jury nullification, like
it exists, but if you speak it, you are disqualified from existence.
Well, I just want to, well, I just want to say, I just want to say that, uh, you know,
I know that is a thing that people would probably do and I don't blame them for that,
but consider the fact that we're only asking $5 for like 40 fucking bonus episodes.
There's 25 out now, 25.
So if you, so if you engage in that kind of activity, no judgment, but if you enjoy the
content and you want to, and you want to say thanks, I will like, I will pull you up little
bench.
I've been known to go to Napster.com and download a hot M peg or an MP3 once in a while.
So, so I, I get it kids, I get it, but, uh, yeah, I mean, you know, certainly appreciate
this.
Maybe, maybe I shouldn't, maybe I shouldn't even said anything.
Oh, no, it's fine.
It is what, and, and you know what, uh, bleep that'll allow bleep, bleep everything Ben
said.
Don't cut it, but just bleep it.
I put some safety measures into place and here's what it is guys, even if those leak,
I've taken the sneaky move of, so normally with PCB episodes, we have, uh, uh, an ad
every half an hour, I decided as a compromise in case people decided they wanted to leak
the bonus episodes.
What I've done is I've placed ads at the very beginning and the very end, but not throughout
the episode.
So even if like people want to pass around bonus episodes and they, you know, whatever,
like just the guy that got a ton of views or whatever, we would still get some money.
So it's not like a total loss or anything.
Oh, that's, that's not going to, I mean, it's not going to make a difference, but it's
going to make, that's going to make, I mean, we got like, we got like, I mean, how many
patrons we have a couple hundred or so something like that.
Yeah.
So like, I get it.
So if that number gets, if that number gets boosted up to a solid 500, we're going to
make, we're going to make a cool 20 cents a piece on each of those.
Okay.
You know what?
You might be making a fair point, but the other thing is just that, uh, we can also
see just like the view counts on the bonus episodes.
So like if it goes more than a couple hundred, we know that like, okay, some shenanigans
are up here, but, uh, but that's like never happened.
So I've, uh, I've been pretty, feel pretty confident that most people are, uh, not stealing
it.
Although there was that one episode.
And I'm just saying, I'm just saying pledge to the Patreon for the bonus episodes, sure,
but also just if you like what we do and if you want to support us.
My Patreon, my personal one is just to support my work.
So that model is, it does, it's not, not terrible.
Uh, okay.
Let's move on.
Next one.
We've got a call from, should I make a move on her?
Uh, let's see.
No.
Strong no.
Next question.
I'm going to see detective Pikachu with a girl.
Should I make a move on her like holding hands?
Hmm.
Let me know.
No.
Well, Detective Pikachu, it's nice that you're bringing, you know, fucking like Clefairy to
the premiere of your, your movie, but I don't know, man.
I mean, the thing she resists is you, you know, type.
Yeah.
What are you going to, what are you going to tell your grandkids 50 years down the line
and tell you to, oh, I met your grandma at Detective Pikachu.
No.
You're right.
Are you going to tell your fucking dog next year that you snogged your girlfriend while
watching Pikachu snogged Ronald Reynolds?
You know, you know, these men speak wisdom instead of all that.
What you should do is tell no one as you're alone on your deathbed about all the times
you didn't go talk to the girl that you wanted to talk to.
That's a much better solution.
That's right.
Yeah.
I think that's right.
You, you only you and God will know how pure you are.
Holding hands would be all right.
I would say you should try holding hands.
If she's like, get a, get away, get away from me.
I hate you.
Then it's probably something up.
Look, obviously any, any approach or like anything that you do to any girl, like, like
it could be like a great date thing that you're totally into, like, or it could be some kind
of sexual assault.
I'm just saying like, like if you just walk up to a random girl, say nothing and grab
her hand.
That's like technically assault.
Well, no, the city is already going to the thing with a girl.
I mean, even if you're going to a girl that you like know and your friends with, like,
if she's not thinking of you romantically in any way and you just like make a move, then
like you're just setting yourself up for failure.
So you got to, uh, I mean, yeah, like, like, okay, I'll just, here's the little crash course.
You can test the waters here.
And a lot of this is just sensing how she's vibing and if she's into it.
All you got to do is like, like it's little things like, uh, like if she's comfortable,
okay, what do you want to do?
You want to establish physical connection.
I'm just going to let, ask you to let you, let her read your palm, read her palm.
Oh yeah.
Okay.
That's the classic one.
That one's a little corny, a little corny, but like things like read that palm, read
that.
Here's a weird thing.
Okay.
If anybody's ever gone out and like try to hit on girls and stuff, you may sense like
a weird wall appear and it's the wall of like the mutual recognition that neither of
you have ever physically touched the other person.
And as long as that like is there, like there's going to be like a weird kind of aura going
on if you're like trying to get to know this person.
So what you want, you want to smash through that quickly and a lot of guys who are friend
zoned or not necessarily friend zone, but haven't made a move or anything, they don't,
they don't know about this.
And I'm not saying like, grope up girls.
What I'm saying is like, there's nothing wrong with like, when you're hanging out with
a friend, like, you know, whatever, like touching them on the shoulder briefly or like something
like that.
Give her a fucking, give her a high five or whatever.
Yeah.
You know, there's any number of ways to break that, that, that initial like touch barrier.
I'm guessing you are at that place.
But even if you're beyond that, maybe you're, maybe you've hugged or whatever.
It's not weird between you or anything.
But I mean, yeah, just, you know, you got to vibe it out, like have fun, get her laughing.
And then I don't know, I, at some point you got to make the commitment, I guess to try
for the smooch or something.
Just go straight for it.
Okay.
Don't even make it a big like anime Disney like kiss moment.
Like be silly and playful.
And like when you're having fun, when you're goofing around, you've established physical
connection and you're having fun and laughing like, go for like a cheap kiss, like be silly
about it.
Like call it a joke.
But you know,
you're the kiss until Mr. Mime appears on screen and that's your moment, that's your
signal.
I don't know.
Also in general, here's a movie going power move.
You stand on top of the seats in front of you and you just, you like with your arms
crossed.
Oh no.
Yeah.
You T-pose while watching the movie.
In front of your, of your, so she's so that she's looking through your legs at the movie.
You don't, you do not move.
Embracing your sexuality passively.
The entire time.
Yeah.
That's the way to do it.
Give some of that a try.
Well, let us know how it goes.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Let us know how this advice works out for you.
Please do let us know.
Cause I'm curious.
You got, you got to take the, take the leap at some point though.
You know, you can't, you can't, uh, you can't get a girl unless you risk losing her.
I mean, that's absolutely true.
And like, you know, it's not like pin her down and make out with her and not that, not
that kind of risk, my dude, uh, you know, it's not, not unless she signs a waiver.
There's going to be a point.
In triplicate.
Yeah.
And like, I don't know.
I remember struggling with this a lot.
We're like, you know, you're not like letting a girl know you're into her, but at some
point she has to be made aware that you're actually into her.
Um, and I say playfully approaching that like in a humorous way, uh, while, you know, doing
a little physical contact, I think is the way to go.
I would recommend a red nose, white makeup, rainbow wig.
And one of those flowers that you squeeze and the water comes out.
Yep.
Just get her nice and moist.
Say it on a unicycle.
You know, that's the new, that's the new shirt.
If you wouldn't say it on a unicycle, why say it at all?
You know, have the car.
Haha.
I like you, honk.
New, new, new shirt on the, on the teespring.
Say it on a unicycle.
I get a custard pie through her in her face the first moment you see her.
Hey, that's contact, right?
Break.
Well, not really.
Okay.
Whatever.
All right.
Hopefully that's enough.
And just be cool.
And that's honestly 90% of it.
Just be yourself.
Lol.
Okay.
Let's move on.
Haha.
That'll, that'll fuck him up.
Sure will.
We've got a call from Nate is a hypocrite spelled with kooky capitalization one.
Okay.
H H I P P O C R I T.
That's correct.
Let's see what we've got.
Let's go at the risk of reopening a can of worms.
Uh, I would like for Nate to clarify his stance in regards to the whole, uh, subscribe
to PewDiePie meme shut down topic from last week's episode.
Um, cause I hear some, uh, some contradictions with Nate's philosophy.
And I just want to give him more credit for more credit than that and, uh, let him defend
his position.
Steelman me, Nate has been a staunch defender of the capitalist market and the capitalist
system.
And this is a perfect example of that, uh, people in the market decided that something
was not profitable anymore.
You know, the, the image of subscribed to PewDiePie and all the baggage that comes with
that, they made the decision to outwardly not support it.
And then the market changed, uh, and this became completely untenable.
So PewDiePie made the capitalist financial decision to change his mind to, uh, respond
to the market so that he could make more money and continue to be a viable brand.
Um, I don't really see the issue here because in a capitalist mindset, this is how social
ideas are, are propagated through, through the whims of the market and through the market
forcing good ideas through.
Um, so I don't know, I'd like you to clarify, Nate.
Okay.
Quick, quick response.
This will be very simple.
Um, you, in your question there, you are embedding the fact that like PewDiePie had to do this
because there was a giant, you know, whatever, like, like his brand was suffering.
Like, okay, like, I get it.
I understand your point there.
Like, I, I don't quite agree with all those points.
And just, just in short, uh, all I want to say is that like, what you're doing is you
are, you're criticizing or you're, you're coming back to me on like the economic level
of, you know, this is the way the social landscape was.
And PewDiePie reacted to it in a way that made sense logically in, you know, don't you
endorse capitalism?
Don't you endorse the free market?
My criticism has nothing to do with people choosing to do what they want in response
to market, market forces or anything.
My criticism is solely having to do with the social framework that led up to that decision.
And it is simply that like, I don't feel that things needed to go this way.
And so, so that is the focus of my criticism.
Obviously people can do whatever they want.
And yeah.
So you are not, so you do not think, so you're not criticizing PewDiePie for saying, for
backing off from the, for saying, don't say subscribe to PewDiePie.
No, I kind of am, but only in the facet of like, I feel that he is validating this point
by like acquiescing to, you know, this, this is something I realized after the discussion
and I left a comment on the, the episode explaining why I think there was so much arguing during
that.
It's because there is two sort of angles to take this from there's the viewer's perspective
and then the content creators perspective, like this guy's talking about, it's more logical
and capitalist to do this stuff, which is what I was arguing at the time.
But Nate is more arguing about the fact that socially he wishes that this just wouldn't
happen this way.
Yeah, that's true.
My comment is more in depth.
If you go back to the episode, you'll see it.
Okay.
Well, I mean, that's all I got to say on this.
So I mean, frankly, we can just move on.
Well, I don't wait, wait, no, I'm going to prod you because I don't think you've answered
this guy's question.
No, I think I did.
No, because like, well, you said, well, you said that, yeah, you still think PewDiePie
shouldn't have done it.
Yeah.
But, but not for like, not because I'm actually being counter to myself and being anti-capitalist.
I understand you have to do with the market dictates.
My criticism is of the social like reality.
I'm like, I like, basically my point is I wish people would not let these things, you
know, let the influence them.
So you're, so you're not criticizing PewDiePie's decision.
Ben, no, in part I am for one reason.
On the other hand, I understand why he made it.
That's my point.
Well, if you understand why he made it and it was the right thing to do for capital
God damn it.
Why would you criticize it?
You must understand nuance, right?
There are things to be discussed.
It's not just one topic.
I understand that you're, I understand that you're trying to have it both ways here.
Ben, what the fuck?
I don't want to talk to you for a minute.
No, no, no, no, no.
This is exactly why we sent the conversation last time.
This is one different answer.
Why won't you fucking answer my question?
I answered you three times, Ben.
But no, you haven't.
The answer is clear.
We can all understand what Nate's saying.
We can all understand.
No, I can't.
But everyone else understands except you.
You're the problem.
You haven't, you haven't.
No, you're trying to draw in the ways that are trying to make him look bad all the time.
No, you've just given a, you've just given a non-answer.
The answer is that he doesn't have an issue with that side of the debate.
He does not have a problem with the fact that PewDiePie made it for an economic reasons.
He has issue with the fact that he was forced to make this decision not because of the market
problem, but he just upset that the social, that's what the social plane is like right
now.
Ben, I'll give you your answer.
So what's to criticize about PewDiePie's decision then?
It's about the social aspect of it.
That's not what he said.
No, for fuck's sake, there is two aspects to PewDiePie's decision.
There is both the capitalist, good money management thing and the social thing.
It's not one or the other.
So I'm sorry, but my answer is I'm conflicted on it.
That's my, I'm so sorry that I don't have a clear yes or no, and it's not about that
I just actually hate fucking capitalism.
It's actually wrong.
Gotcha, gotcha, Nate, gotcha.
This is retarded.
Let's move on.
Okay, whatever.
Because it's, it's, it's that it has both aspects.
One, the capitalist, Nate agrees with the other, he doesn't agree with, therefore conflicted.
Yeah, but-
I mean, I get it.
But then, but you, okay, I'm just confused because when I say that, you, like, it seems
like your criticism of PewDiePie is something that other people did.
No, no, no, no, okay, because I said before, my criticism is that I feel he acquiesced
and I think that strengthens their argument.
And I, I mean, again, I might have done the exact same thing because I'm not like an invincible
super god of, you know, I wouldn't even say morals, like, of whatever, standing up for
myself or, you know, fighting on my own behalf or whatever.
But like, but I, to me, I, what I see is, you know, a little bit of giving in and I,
you know, I'm just, just, they say in my piece, I don't, I wish he hadn't, but that's, that's
how it seems to me.
That's it.
Is that more reasonable?
But that, well, no, but let's continue.
Okay.
Gangster's PCP Paradise.
Please save us.
Oh no.
Bro, have you guys seen the Sonic Movie Trailer?
It looks so fucking radical, dude, like, radical, tactical.
Oh my God.
Holy shit.
I love it.
It's Gangster's Paradise.
That's the song.
Hey, all right, you did save us, Gangster's PCP Paradise.
Let's talk about how mad I am that people are happy that they're fixing Sonic's character
design.
Well, okay, so there's the artistic, like, okay, you could say like, hey man, respect
the artist's vision.
So you know, just let them do what they want, but on the other hand, I mean, I never thought
this one looked very good.
So I guess I don't think it, I, well, it's not that I think that you need to respect
this artist's vision.
It's not that I think this is sacred, it shouldn't be changed.
It's that, like, it's like, why would you be happy about anything related to this?
If it's changing, it might improve, I guess.
The design could get better, but I think the problem is the entire thing.
Oh, I get it.
I get it.
It's just seems so doomed to begin with.
If I had seen this trailer and Sonic had looked like Sonic, would I have been like, oh, looks
good.
Well, yeah, I guess not.
I know it's not.
I've heard, like, like, probably baseless rumors, but it was interesting as a thought
that Christian came out in the movie.
Yeah.
No, that this initial trailer was made as deliberately really bad and they had like
a backup better looking Sonic.
And this was all to build hype for the movie, to get people talking about it.
You know, these are the kind of nimbus who would do that shit, the Sonic 2.
I don't think that corporation, like, that seems like a really risky move that I don't
see a big company taking.
It's risky, but it's also risky to, like, remake the whole of the animation as well.
That's a lot of money that I'll have to spend to do that.
It's, yeah, true.
It seems that way, though.
I don't know.
I don't think companies are competent enough.
I would probably say that this was not a scheme, but, like, it worked out so well.
Like, people are so hyped to hear that, like, they're changing the character design.
It seems like it was planned.
It's like the new Coke thing.
Like people that the Coke introduced new Coke just so they could bring back a classic Coke,
which I don't know, it's possible.
If so, it was an incredibly risky move.
These are very large brain moves that I cannot follow, but I mean, maybe.
I think the reason people are excited in the first place, is it even because, like, oh,
the movie's gonna be great now.
I think it's just the fucking amazing fact that, like, oh, this big Hollywood machine
that just shits out bullshit is actually listening to constructive criticism, instead of just
calling out everyone for being fake fans and being gay and yelling at everyone for complaining
about something.
I mean, if I had to guess.
That is shocking.
That is actually happening.
I think that's where the kind of rejoicing is coming from.
It's like, wow, there's actually a dialogue happening on this platform designed for dialogue.
What company is making this?
Paramount.
They're all owned by Coke, anyway.
I want to say a small thought that has come up with the Sonic movie.
Okay, so this is gonna get a tiny little bit philosophical, but when you are a person
with ideas and an ideology, and then you reach a point in your life when you want to reject
those ideas that you've had before in your life, and you think to yourself, no, this
is not how I should be anymore.
I have to stop some of the vices which I have been displaying.
I have to make some changes in my life.
Then it's easy to look at the way you act and the way that you feel and say, time to
do the opposite.
This is not working out for me.
I need to pull back, and pulling back can be a gradient.
It doesn't have to be, you know, you completely turn heel and then whip the other way.
The reason I say this is because I agree with the people who say there's too much cynicism
in the online space.
There's too many people who are too willing to just shit down movies or art in general
or online creations.
People are too cynical and mean and write things off too easily.
But that doesn't mean that everything needs to be happy.
That doesn't mean that you have to always try and just, you know, steal a man or look
on the bright side of some issues.
Sometimes, knee-jerk reactions are valid.
You don't have to just pretend the SOG movie is going to be good for the sake of being
positive.
That's true.
Stop it, please.
I don't know, maybe you'll surprise us.
It will be glorious.
It will be glorious when it's a tough dumpster fire.
The thing is, I've never liked Sonic.
Like ever.
Yeah, in any way.
We can't encourage people, we can't encourage people to go see the movie.
Just morbid curiosity, just to see how bad it is.
Yeah, we should pull a little more money into the pockets of this company because it's
going to be so funny to laugh at them as they laugh all the way to the bank.
Yeah, that's true.
On my dollar.
What I'm trying to say is that, like, I've seen people, I've talked to people who are
like, um, but you know, it won't be, you know, there's some problems, but you know, like
look on the bright side, like no, no, I won't, we don't have to do that for everything.
I agree that there could be more of that in general, but it's the Sonic movie.
Look on the bright side, I could spend money, I could spend money to a big corporation,
I let the bright side.
Somebody's going to buy a yacht.
Isn't that, isn't that beautiful?
Isn't that lovely?
Yeah.
I contribute to some guy's yacht.
Some guy, some guy deserved it, you know, for making the Sonic movie.
He took the initiative, he made it happen, and God bless him.
I'm sure whoever stole my bicycle is having a better time with it than I would in the
industry.
Oh, that's so true.
Yeah, yeah.
He's going to have happiness.
That's not like an Alturid comic.
Those big-wig fat cats are going to enjoy my money more than I would have.
What was that Alturid comic?
I believe you're talking about bike-cuck, based.
He's enjoying my bike more than I would have enjoyed still having it.
By the way, slide it into my Sonic stance.
I just want to go on the record.
I played Sonic Advance 1, 2, and 3, and those were great games, so I don't hate Sonic entirely.
I just think that he's kind of lame.
That was fucking amazing.
But okay.
Sonic was shit because I played it on my flip-flop, and it was the best time of my life.
All right, that's sick.
Okay, but check this out.
Next voicemail is from Elmo recommends a sword game.
So let's see what he's about.
Go.
Yes, please.
Hello, everybody.
I have heard that you all love sword games.
The best one Elmo has played is the owner.
It has directional combat.
Hey, we were talking about that.
It's like Dark Souls if it was actually good.
Yay.
I know what the best looks like with a controller.
So the swords to release are easier to point.
Elmo hopes you all have so much fun.
Goodbye.
Bitches.
Bye.
Bye, Arlo.
Hello.
Here's some canon lore.
That is Red Man's cousin.
Elmo.
Yeah, that sounds right.
That sounds right.
I think Arlo was blood this whole time.
We're going to Arlo to call in, guys, I just watched the last episode of the PCP, and I
just wanted to comment on Ben St's keto recipes.
That's what I want.
He's a keto man as well.
You don't know the half of it.
I don't.
Look at his physique.
Ben second.
Oh, my God.
Look at those blue feathers.
He's not a hardcore keto, but didn't I tell you about me getting that recipe for keto
pizza crust?
Yeah, I just didn't know if that could have been kind of a coincidence if he was doing
keto something.
I mean, he's not full keto.
He just wanted to lower his carb intake.
Arlo is what happens when you go full keto.
So he's a coward, basically.
What is the deal with Elmo?
Why do kids like Elmo?
I mean, because they're babies and he's nice.
Because he's got a high voice and they pushed it really hard, I guess.
I know.
I've met babies who just fucking are apeshit for Elmo, and I'm like, dude, what's the
deal?
And I'm like, what's even the disarmed kutzwerk at work here?
I don't even fucking get it.
You go down to your local vape shop and all the babies are in there.
Vape it away.
You start up a little conversation with them.
They're talking about Elmo again.
Oh, these guys suck.
It's like, hey, explain it to me.
Explain Elmo.
I want to get it.
I want to understand.
Like, tell me what it is.
Like, what am I missing here?
They go Google GaGa and they take a hit of that vape.
All right.
Let's get the hell out of here.
She's a cookie monster on the whole plane.
Wait, cookie monster, total killer.
Yeah, that's true.
That's true.
No, no.
Cookie monster's a big rowdy.
He eats baked goods.
Therefore, he can't be a killer because he's not keto.
I think Big Bird's a killer, though.
Big Bird's a juvie.
Kermit, Kermit the Frog's a killer.
Kermit?
Yeah.
I don't know.
He seemed like a real juvie to me.
He's like a neutral arbiter of wisdom.
Oh, yeah.
I don't know.
Oh, God.
You know, the thing about, the best thing about living in Slime City is that you can change.
You can betray your faction.
That's true.
You can contain multitudes.
You can be whatever you want to be in New Los Angeles City.
One can be many.
You can watch the slime economy crumble in Neo-Milwaukee.
You can hear this juvie stomach's rumble.
Well, on that note.
Quotes.
Oh, fucking quickly.
Animal, Red Man's uncle.
Oh, animal.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
They're all canon.
There's a full Sesame Street lore tied in with Red Man.
Don't even get him started.
Yeah.
Okay.
Here we go.
I should try and find out how to buy a Muppet of Red Man.
Unsee Arlo as the chief Muppet man on YouTube.
Okay.
Here we go.
She-Pollution role-playing as a PCP member.
Let's commence.
How many more voicemails do we have to listen to?
I don't know what these fuckers are doing, but I got deadline.
I got people waiting for me for my next big project.
It will be great.
It will be the best thing they'll ever see.
But I can't finish it as long as these fucking voicemails keep coming up.
And they all suck.
All the voicemails suck.
Oh, I hate them.
I wish they all died in a shit.
A shitty poopy shit.
Yes.
So my question is, how accurate does this describe you?
Not necessarily right now, but just in general, when you're recording an episode and you're
nearing the end, how much do you want it to end so you can continue working on your project?
Ironically, 100% this is the most related I've ever been to personally.
Yeah, yeah.
Right now.
Very specifically right now.
Well, I spend the voicemails waiting for real my ass back.
Well, you're in luck there, Ben, because we've got one coming up next right here, baby.
All right.
Yeah.
Let's get into it immediately.
Here we go.
Riddle my ass, Batman.
The song continues right now.
Wait, what?
Okay.
It didn't work.
Wait, sorry.
Hang on.
I don't know what that was about.
Okay.
Copy.
Riddle my ass, Batman is canceled.
And okay, let's try again.
Go.
Is your eye better, Batman?
Yes, Riddle.
Good.
Because I want you to see the next poor soul you failed to save.
You, Riddle, let's go ahead with the riddles.
I have four legs on which to stand.
It's my eyes skimmed by, watching on the slide.
When I'm hungry, it's grass I eat, soaking in Africa's heat.
Big and fierce, but cute as well.
It's well known that I yell, yawn and toot.
Who am I, Batman?
It's the first riddle you give me that doesn't suck, Riddle.
The answer is hippo.
Very well.
Riddle at least a minute.
Thank you, Batman.
Hippo.
I just want you to know that when a dating sim comes out, I'm choosing you as my lover.
Wow.
Whoa.
Thank you, Batman.
Crash.
Holy heartwarming, heartwarming hippos, Batman.
I never paid you as a hippo fan.
Why not?
He's the funniest.
By the way, did you bring the stuff?
Yes, Batman.
Yeah.
Robin finally arrived in the battlefield.
Well, the supplies he brought me enough to save the merinimias of the PCP to the next
time I find out.
Same PCP time.
Same PCP channel.
Whoo.
Oh, the glorious.
That's why you're the chief of the Hall of Fame.
Yeah.
Goddamn.
Once again.
Every time.
What was that about taking you as his lover?
In the PCP dating sim.
Oh, yes.
He's a fan.
He's following at PCP dating daily.
Wow.
Incredible.
That was great.
As always.
I'm flattered.
What a...
And I'm safe.
Yes, you are.
Most of us are safe now.
For now.
Who's still there?
I'm sure this is all part of Riddle My Ass' plan.
It could be.
So it's all part of his grand plan.
I think so.
I think he's building to something incredible.
But let me see.
I think Jesse and Digi are still up there.
Anybody else?
I can't think of anybody else.
I don't know.
The Davoo.
No, Davoo's been saved.
Davoo saved.
When have we got Davoo?
Oh, did we?
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
I think that was last episode.
Davoo saved.
I think everybody else is saved.
I think there's only those two left.
Unless I'm forgetting something.
But the sagas nearing its conclusion, ladies and gentlemen.
Will Batman be able to continue to puzzle out these epic reasoning games?
We'll see.
It seems like Riddle My Ass Batman's riddles are getting better.
They are improving.
He's growing more powerful.
Yeah.
The problem is with only two people left to choose, it really narrows down the focus
of who's going to be the answer.
He's going to have a tough time with that last one.
There's only one person left.
Well, it'll be Digi, and Digi will have not been on an episode in months, and so he'll
forget that he's a member.
He'll be like, uh, uh, Jeff, no, no, gone.
Well, we'll see.
We'll see what happens.
But anyway, I guess that's it, ladies and gentlemen.
If you're interested in watching this, please like, share, and subscribe to our channel.
And if you're interested in watching this, please like, share, and subscribe to our
channel.