Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemail for the Minecraft stream. I really want to have Radcon funded by you. We can be procrastinators.
Hey, Lodagos Kickstarter should be live right now.
We can talk about that a little bit later, but go check.
Yes, and I also made the website, which is the most important thing.
Oh, obviously I've seen your lecture. That's how I found out about you.
Yeah, okay. That doesn't surprise me.
Good. Great.
So, I guess I'm, thank you. Thank you.
So you've been like bouncing around in some Discord servers that I'm in here and there.
You gave me the heads up when some shit went down in the TGT community, or whatever, behind the scenes.
You have the inside scoop into all the goings on.
Would you maybe want to give just a brief summary of how you became TGT's envoy, liaison, ambassador, whatever?
How did you get where you are today?
Well, I was born in...
No, please.
I'll just skip that part.
Basically, I've been a fan of Tails Gets Told since about like 2012, which is basically when it got popular or when it was discovered.
So weird to think that it was on TV not for months.
Did people like find it on 4chan and that's how it got popular? Is that the story of it?
Oh, it was found by someone on something awful.
Okay, that makes sense.
Yeah, and my friend was like a something awful goon, so he showed it to me and I just thought it was hilarious.
That's right. So you found it in 2012. How old were you? How old were you in 2012?
I was 21.
Okay, so we're okay. So you're not that much younger than me, so that's fine.
Yeah, I'm 30 now.
Okay, good. Few.
I can't have any more grooming allegations.
That's a joke. That's a joke. I'm clean. I have zero.
Yeah, unfortunately, the average Tails Gets Told fan is a bit younger, unfortunately.
Sad but true. Sad but true.
Yeah, I have to deal with all these zoomers and shit.
Yeah.
But anyway, so yeah, I've been following the series ever since then and through all the events that happened.
One notable event was after his DVNAR account got hacked. That was a whole situation.
When was that?
It was actually early in TGT's life compared to how long it's been going. It was also in 2012, but later in the year.
Right, right. Okay. Who hacked it again? I used to know this, but refresh me. What happened with the hack?
It's really weird. It was like this weird Greek brony guy who wanted to get revenge on something awful.
So he like fished Laserbot's password with like a fake DVNAR site.
Okay, yeah. You know what I mean?
Makes sense, I guess. Okay, so anyway, continue.
Yeah, so Laserbot's password was Donkey Balls, which he used for every site.
Oh no.
So yeah, the hacker got into all his shit and including his YouTube, which thankfully he didn't delete any of the videos.
So it's still up, but like nobody has access to it.
Is that the channel that Micorat is posted on?
Yes.
Okay, maybe we can talk about Micorat later. All right, continue.
Yeah, so, oh yeah, that was the whole thing. And so that was part of the reason why Laserbot had to get a new DVNAR account,
which also relates to like why I made the site, but I'll get to that later.
Basically, and the weird thing is like I told Laserbot like, oh, if you just email DVNAR, they'll like get you your account back.
But I guess he didn't.
So you were talking to him like even back in the day?
Well, I wasn't talking to him personally. I was just leaving comments on his DVNAR page.
So I just left a comment that was like, you know, if you just like email DVNAR and tell them your account got hacked, they'll like get it back for you.
But I guess either he like didn't understand or like he didn't trust anyone, he didn't trust anyone because he just got hacked.
So he thought I might have been like trying to hack him again or something.
I guess that's a good time to mention that I have asked Laserbot a couple of times if he'd like to come on the show.
And he always kind of says like, yeah, I would, but I don't have a microphone or I'm just like, I don't feel like it or something.
He always is like, maybe, but I'm not actually going to do it. I can't do it for whatever reason.
He's like a little, I don't know. I found him a little bit hard to get.
I don't know. How hard is it to get a microphone? I'd buy him one.
I'd buy him one if that's what it's, but I don't think it's it. I think he's just like not very communicative.
Yeah, it's also that and he's bad with like technology stuff.
And I don't mean that as an insult or anything because like not everyone can be good at everything.
But like, I remember I was reading through the DMs that the hacker sent to people when he had laser.
Oh, yeah, that's another thing. But I don't know if it's like out of order if I don't want to get into it right now.
But I eventually did get his DeviantArt account back like years later.
What I just, I just pretended to be him and I emailed DeviantArt.
I said, oh, someone hacked my account. Can I have it back? And they're like, sure, here's the password.
It wasn't too hard.
So is that is that how you all right. So so anyway, let's get back on track.
How did you get involved with managing the the brand or whatever?
Yeah, so the thing I mentioned about how he moved accounts, like he did that like a bunch of times and you even mentioned it in your lecture.
Like there is like some there is like he had a bunch. He had like a bunch of different DeviantArt accounts and yeah.
It made it used to be very difficult to like read the whole comic.
You had to go to multiple different accounts and websites to like find the parts because they weren't all in one place.
Yeah. And I always saw people like commenting saying, oh, where can I read the rest of the comic?
Because either like they only knew about his first DeviantArt account and they thought it ended there or they only saw like some other stuff.
And it's like, like, I guess I can't blame them because you have to do like a lot of research to like try to find all the parts.
And a lot of people aren't going to go through that like that much effort to try to find stuff.
True.
So as and and like people have made other sites like it's something awful.
Goon made tales gets trolled dot com a while ago, but they stopped updating it.
And now it's like taken over by like advertiser bots and shit.
So I was just like, I'm tired of this shit.
People don't know where to read the comic.
I'm so like pissed off that nobody can read this masterpiece easily.
So one day I was just like, fuck it, I'm going to make a new website so people can read it.
And that's what I did basically.
And and when the website started out, it was just like a basic like HTML.
Like you probably remember it.
It was like just like a white page with black text like you would find in like 1992 on the on the web.
It was just like links to all the pages and shit.
Sure.
And actually the real hardcore, you know, tales gets trolled fans before that.
The main the main way to like read it was like people passed around like zip files of like the comics and shit, which is kind of cool in its own way.
It's like it was like an underground like people swapping like zip files and shit.
Yeah.
But that's a good old the good old days.
Yeah, but that's what I that's what I based before TGT went mainstream man before it sold out.
Yeah.
Like I actually I on ironically sold out because I'm selling merchant shit.
But yeah.
Do you make money off that?
Yeah.
Hmm.
Okay.
I just put it into running the website and I give half of it to laser bot.
Makes sense.
Yeah.
So I used that zip file.
There's also like a zip file and ZBZ file and shit.
I just use those to like make the website and yeah, I made the website and I guess I wanted to talk to other people about it.
So I also made the discord and I guess I guess that's basically when it started.
When was that?
2018.
Did like.
Did you like ask laser bot like hey do you want me to manage your social media and he was like yes or did you it sounds like you just kind of did it.
Well the the website was before the social media really.
I just I just made the website and I told laser bought it out.
The way I got in contact with him like personally was through Facebook.
Yeah.
Actually when he had when he had the DeviantArt account he like posted on DeviantArt it was like oh everyone add me on Facebook.
So that's that's how most people got in contact.
That's actually how the hacker hacked is a DeviantArt because the hacker.
This is a totally unrelated tangent but I just so happened to be talking to um.
Oh Lillia the other day.
Yeah.
I just I just I just like messaged him back because I had like not responded to his last message to me which was a while ago and he told me that he is making a game and I told him no way I'm making a video game too.
And he was like yeah it's going to look like a Super Nintendo graphic style and I was like no way my game is going to look like a Super Nintendo graphic style.
Oh Pog Pog.
I'm going to I'm going to I'm going to spoil it.
I'm going to spoil it.
I don't know.
I don't know if he would mind if I say it but I'm going to say his he told me that the name of the game he's making is Barakana.
I don't know what that means.
I have no idea what the significance of that is but that's a little that's a little bit of future.
If you see that's that's a I know you heard it here first.
You heard it here first.
Yeah.
You heard it here first Barakana by Nick Smith.
Okay.
Anyway that's off topic.
Let's get back to a PC a PCP exclusive a PCP exclusive scoop.
Yeah.
What happened to what happened to platform master is I think he just kind of like he just dropped it.
I think he like made it work.
I mean this is like my my speculation.
It seems like he made it exactly as he envisioned it and it worked but he just like didn't.
I think he must have been like well it works but I don't really have any desire to like actually like polish it into a finished game.
Right.
I think maybe like his proof of concept was enough for him and then he lost interest after it was done.
That's what I suspect because it seemed like if a game was like made and working and there were demos of it and then it just disappeared and like the final release just never happened for no for no clear reason.
Oh yeah tragic.
Oh damn I should play the demos and because I don't think there was playable demos there were video demos though.
There were like there were.
Yeah he posted videos of it like playing.
Well I'm showing off all the parallax scrolling in the background.
I hope I hope he at least releases like something from it but I know he's a perfectionist so.
No he didn't he didn't give me hardly any details about Barakana other than that it will have a SNES inspired visual style.
And that that's its name and I he literally didn't tell me anything else about it.
But that's that's all I got.
OK.
And so you made the oh yeah go on.
I was just going to say I am checking out the website.
It's quite nice because it's like really like simple basic you know no bullshit everything's nice and easy to find.
What's the URL.
It's told.org which is in my username on the server.
Let me see.
Oh sure.
I noticed.
Whoa.
Whoa the sprites.
The little sparkles on the sides.
Whoa.
They look great.
Yeah.
Actually.
This looks so cool.
It's awesome.
Actually a Tails gets trolled fan came to me and just like hey I made a new layout for the website.
Here you go.
And he just he just gave it to me like before it was like the HTML should I was talking about.
It was like really simple.
I like tails in the top bottom left.
I was I was just going to say I really like the logo is just those iconic tails eyes.
Actually the if you refresh like the logo is random every time a bunch of fans like you
have like a contest for it right.
Yeah.
And a bunch of people made logos a bunch of people made logos so I just put like every
time you go to the page like a random logo comes up.
I see.
Yeah.
And then Ben is in the on the website as the TGT thanks on the credits page.
Am I.
Yeah you are.
No.
Yeah.
Hold on.
They're giving you thanks Ben.
Control F Ben.
TGT thanks jazz flight Ben St. to win and newness.
I don't know if I oh I don't know if I did anything to deserve that but I'll take it.
You brought attention to the series.
I did I I mean your lecture has like four four hundred thousand views.
Do you do you think that like I made it like I brought any significant attention to it that
it didn't already have though.
It did because I've seen people on in the community say oh I found out about tails get
stroked through like Ben St. lecture.
That's so fucking cool.
Yeah.
So fucking rad.
Oh my god.
Beautiful.
Though I do make a difference.
Yeah.
That's another thing I'll get to later but I agree with the other thing though is I agree
with Cybershell is that you shouldn't like watch the whole lecture if you haven't read
it because it spoils a lot.
Yeah.
I agree.
It's sad but true because I know that watching the lecture I'm sure is not as interesting
after you've read the series and you already know it all but it's true.
It spoils the whole thing.
It spoils the whole thing and it's worth reading unspoiled.
No it's the opposite.
You shouldn't read it.
You shouldn't watch it before you read it but after you read it it's really interesting
to see.
You think you act to see like people's reactions to it and stuff.
Yeah I guess.
I mean I mean I I would watch you know what I am totally the kind of person who would
watch a lecture about a thing I already know just to hear someone talk about it.
Just to hear is the funny people go.
Whoa.
In the crowd.
Neutrals are cool actually like whoa.
Yeah.
That's why I enjoyed it personally.
It's fair.
The big thing that bothers me though is that you never mentioned that Sonic died.
That's a huge yeah I really fucked up.
I really fucked that up and like I just skipped over that it just what I just forgot to write
it in my notes that there's like a whole big thing about how Sonic the Hedgehog dies
and it's like a huge thing and I just forgot to mention it so like I'm like an hour into
the thing and I'm like yeah so then the ghost of Sonic oh by the way he's dead oh yeah he
died a while ago.
Whoops I forgot to mention I was like really important I think.
Yeah.
I fucked it up.
But what can you do.
Well I didn't know about.
Tails gets gay.
No he mentions.
I think I mentioned Tails gets.
I never read it I guess.
But I mean it's one thing it's one thing quite easy to find.
It's one thing for me to say like oh yeah there's a part called Tails gets gay where he just
changes his art style and makes it all like goofy looking and sparkly and there's another
thing to actually like see it.
To see it with your own eyes.
Yeah.
It's something to behold.
So okay so you got you made the website you got in contact with laser bot and I assume
you were just like hey let me manage all your social media and he was just like yes and
now you like run the the website and the Twitter account and probably like the Facebook group
and stuff like that.
Oh I don't run the Facebook actually Facebook sucks and only boomers use it anymore.
And I mean yeah literally the only thing I do with it is occasionally message.
Oh yeah like once every six months.
Yeah and for those who are those for those who are wondering since you didn't mention
it that's why you brought him up because.
Fuck.
Yeah Nick.
Nick.
Nick also.
Porky pig.
Nick.
Yeah yeah I get it.
Rest in peace.
That's spoilers by the way.
Anyway yeah he Ben brought him up because he also only uses Facebook.
Yeah.
Nick.
Nick used to have a YouTube but like you know YouTube sucks so.
He told me that he told me that he like installed some kind of blocker on his computer that
blocks any website that's associated with Google.
Including yeah including YouTube so he'll use Facebook because it's not Google affiliated
but he won't use YouTube because it's owned by Google.
That's awesome.
That's what he told me.
It's something.
It's something for sure.
Yeah.
So alright so yeah you did the website and you run the account and you started like the
Patreon for them right like you.
I remember I would see you tweeting.
No.
No you didn't but you were promoting it because you like you would see you tweet a bunch that's
like guys Tails gets trolled doesn't make enough money guys it's a travesty it only makes
$150 a month.
Yeah it was $100 yeah.
You mentioned in the lecture they actually had a Patreon before.
Yeah okay so that was before you were involved.
Yes.
And but it was also when they were making Tails gets trolled polished which nobody liked.
That was a disaster.
Like I don't like to say anything bad about it but it was like the one time one of the
only times where I questioned like why I was a fan of Tails gets told reading that.
I mean yeah I didn't I didn't I was just kind of confused by it.
I think a lot of people were why is can you can you explain to me why the Patreon.
Okay so the Tails gets trolled Patreon is patreon.com slash Zegars underscore lab Z A Y G A R S underscore
L A B can you explain why that's its name.
I'll just I'll tell you what I think this isn't official or anything since I didn't make it
sure but I get the impression that Laserbot and his brother Ember Graham aka Zegar they've
they've always they've always wanted to like make projects together and that's also part
of the reason why they made like a bunch of different accounts like they made one account
like one was called upside down and they're like this is going to be our group where we
make projects and then they made another one that was like all this no this group is where
we're going to make the projects and then the last one they made was Zegars lab and
they're like no this is our new account this is where we're going to make the new projects
and that's that's like part of the reason why they moved accounts so much and they got Zegars lab
upside down was the account that he he commented on my lecture on an account on YouTube called
upside upside Annie down yeah yeah what's up with him I know that like Laserbot and his
brother who I guess is Zegar aka was Ember Graham yes Zegar Ember I know that like they
worked on Tales gets trolled together but like everyone still knows Laserbot as the Tales
gets trolled guy what is like what is like their deal like what is their like working
relationship like does one write and the other draw or do they both kind of just come up
together but then Laserbot like would actually finalize it like like what was Zegar's role
in everything I've always wondered about him yeah well they're they're broken up now they
had a falling out but I want to talk about that eventually yeah yeah but before that
for like a large majority of Tales get troll production from what I understand basically
at first Laserbot was just making the comic by himself and his he would show it to his
brother and his brother would like give him some ideas and like some suggestions for dialogue
like one example that they brought up is like during the fight where Sonic dies and like the
characters are fighting and Alex the emo troll like kicks or kicks I think it's emerald the
robot from Sonic Alex the emo troll kicks him and like he flies in the air and like
kicks him and then in the next panel he says I just Peter Pan kick his ass apparently apparently
that was a suggestion from his brother so Zegar wouldn't like do anything he would just
kind of be like oh wouldn't it be cool if this happens yeah that's how it was at first
but then later in the comic they both like started co-writing it they both started doing
like half and half like a lot of the stuff with like the weed the weed party and stuff
I think that was like Zegar oh yeah the weed party with um you mean with with Cheeto man
yes yeah the classic yeah um there was I mean there was the extended hiatus and then
there were many hiatuses yes yeah I'm talking about the one though where it came back like
well being drawn by new people yes that was because of me actually explain uh well for
uh this is like sort of off topic but did you read the um interview laser bot did with
know your meme no I have not I didn't know that he did an interview it was like the only
interviews he's ever done and that of course I had to get them in contact with each other
because like I said he's not really good with like technology or like getting in contact
with people and stuff sure but I mean like since we're doing the podcast now you can read
her but he I'm just gonna say he divulges like a lot of interesting information in it
but any I mean what are what are some highlights oh just basically what I mentioned about how
like him and his brother were involved and like what what they did what they did okay um
anyway um and like how and like how yeah yeah yeah go on and like how he came up with the
idea for tails gets told and stuff um okay I should read that I didn't even know that
was a that was out um so what were you asking I was I was just um I mean well I want to
know how you were involved in getting the you know tails gets told to come back because
it my understanding of the timeline is that you know it was going for a while and then
it sort of petered out and then it he did the um the what was it called the perfect tails
gets told perfect polished polished yeah he tried to bring it back it's like the polished
form and it nobody liked it and it didn't work and he stopped doing that after a while
yes and then and then then it kind of just went away and then it came back with like
new artists yeah that's right so how did how did that happen um basically and by the way
I mentioned I have not read the like post uh hiatus stuff I've sort of been waiting for
to be finished I don't care about spoilers though but I don't know like any of the post
uh yeah the post skip uh plot points unfortunately I'm stupid well you can you can read like
we've already completed one chapter so you can read the chapter and then just wait for
the next chapter to finish I probably should okay but anyway tell me about what happened um so basically
um after he quit uh doing tails gets told I was still like I was still friends with him on facebook
and seeing what he was up to and stuff and he was post he was posting some concept art for a new series
he was working on called gods heroes gods heroes yeah which is basically he says is like a spiritual
successor to uh to um tails gets told can you I I'm sorry to interrupt but I want to know more about
gods heroes please um please tell me what what the deal with that was he actually posted on his dvn art to um
uh his ultimate I need to find some I need to find some art of it to show on screen I want to see it
I'm going to his dvn art right now to look for it yes yes he because he posted all the concept art there
too uh I haven't even heard of this yeah he didn't he didn't talk about it much uh is it okay if like
I link it in the um sure yeah it should be in there uh it starts with the guy who says don't
mess with me I can't sleep I will fuck you up this this fucking batman looking guy yeah and all the
all the characters starting with him after that until the guy with the moon are all gods heroes
characters is this so the are these the titular gods heroes um I really don't know okay so this is
like so this looks like this this basically looks like tails gets trolled as you know
like an action shonen kind of thing but with in the style of tails gets trolled but with
original characters yeah basically basically it's the still it's the classic the classic
laserbot trope of like a character just on in grass just just grass and sky yeah that's actually
that's actually one thing that I liked about tails gets trolled um that's one thing that
drew it drew me to it because it reminded me of like when I was like 10 years old uh I made like
shitty sprite comics and they were just like video game characters on a blue sky with like
green grass on a blank background made in Emma's paint sure sure and it reminded it reminded me of
those days the good old days oh it's got one of um wait no not save I want this this one this image
of a stereos coconut right here uh looking looking good making making a cameo lamal uh I mean was
was that well the guy who was on the dick show or am I thinking of something else yeah kind of
yeah like that that you got the right guy it's whatever I'm making a joke because it looks like
him um so very yeah I know I'm I'm really funny uh all right so God's did he tell you what was the
do you know anything about the plot of God's heroes or what the I don't know was it like a
was it like a christian thing I don't think so it was more like the okay than the neutral thing
because laser bot laser bot says he like grew up in a rich of religious household which made him
hate like christianity and shit I so that makes that fits very well with what I know about him so
okay but he uh he still uses it in his works as like a theme which I think is interesting um yeah
but oh shit what was I gonna say um what did you ask about again oh the plot the plot yeah yeah he
told me he told me uh he told me some aspects about the plot but he told me not to spoil it
so I might tell you what about what about can you tell like the premise or anything
or I mean if he told you not to say anything then I guess don't say anything um well I guess I'll
just say like a bait like uh like one aspect of it is that it takes place in the same universe
as tales gets trolled oh fascinating but that's and some characters might appear that were in
tales gets trolled but um I'm not gonna say who specifically that's very interesting okay so he
was so he was working on God's heroes during the like well he was away from tales gets trolled and
then and then what happened sorry I got the coronavirus not really I got vaccinated get
vaccinated everybody yeah I got Pfizer to vaccination gang are you Pfizer are you Moderna uh Pfizer yeah
Pfizer gang okay cool I got there uh I live in Arizona and they set up like a free vaccination
places where you can just drive up and get the back I we have I'll just this is totally up
if we're talking about vaccinations we have they set up the the Heinz convention center which is
like the place where like they do anime Boston it's the place where they do all the big like
nerd conventions in Boston the whole thing has been like stripped down the whole interior of it
like the vendors hall literally the room that they would have the vendors hall in at a convention
has been cubicalized and turned into like a big like navy uh navy reserve run like clinic there's
like hundreds and hundreds of these people in the navy reserves like medically trained navy officers
like sitting in cubicles given given vaccines 24 hours a day seven days a week uh uh it was it
was beautiful honestly honestly it was a little moving I was a little bit like wow look what society
can accomplish when we all work together when we all when we all uh pitch in we put our heads
together we put our differences aside for the common good I was a little bit I was a little bit moved
by it yeah also it was cool to go to the Heinz convention center because I haven't been there
in a long time because I'm not a freaking nerd we go to say anime conventions anymore although
nobody does maybe I should be um I will you know what if they do it again they're probably not
going to do it this year but if they do if they do coronavirus again if they do coronavirus again
no if they do anime Boston I'll do my usual thing or I'll do my old thing that I used to do
of just go I won't buy a ticket I won't buy a ticket because I don't want to go to any panels
or anything because I'm not a loser but I'll go and I'll just like sneak past the security guards
and wander around in the halls and just look at people because that's the fun of going to a con
oh you know looking at weird weirdos you know you don't have to buy a ticket for that you know um
this is like really off topic but um the most amazing thing I ever saw is when I went to um
odacon in 2017 and I was I was basically doing the same thing I was walking around looking at stuff
and I saw this guy and it was like the most amazing sight I've ever seen in my life although I'm
showing you the picture right now oh the kick-a-stand flick
bass I odacon odacon's in Baltimore right yeah but the year I went it was in Washington
I see um I god when I I think I might have told the story before but when I was in college
I was in I think it was Baltimore and it was a decent I think it was Baltimore and um um
I just happened to be in the town where odacon was I wasn't there for odacon I just was visiting
the town and it happened to be the same weekend and I was with a bunch of friends and we went out
for brunch at this place that offered free mimosas with brunch and somehow I drank somehow I got
wasted on mimosas which is like I don't even know how I you do that I don't think I could do it today
if I tried but I got blasted on on brunch mimosas and then we and then we were walking home from
the restaurant or back to the place the friend I was staying with and we walked by the convention
center where odacon was happening and I was blacked out drawing I don't remember but I have just
like a flash of memory of the walk home of being in front of the odacon convention center and some
like some girls in like gothic lolita with parasols and like tiny top hats pinned to their their
their hair or whatever and I and I just remember puking like in for like on the sidewalk like with
them looking at me uh uh and then I don't remember anything after that um it's good breakfast mimosa
puking brunch mimosa you ever had a mimosa nope I don't think so it's it's not a it's not a strong
drink it's just it's like champagne and orange juice it's not a strong I remember it from the
Incredibles movie oh yeah you actually actually actually I may have had that before
it was it was good from what I remember yeah it's it's it's great it's delightful but it's pretty
I must have drank a lot it must have been a real lightweight back in the day I don't know
pretty interesting that you got blackout drunk in the morning well it was a celebration
for what it was it was on vacation it was a really nice brunch
really it was it was very it's good uh okay what we're what are we talking about I've got
god heroes god's heroes right god's heroes okay right so he was doing god's heroes and then he
was posting stuff about god's heroes and then what happened yeah so um I was like I thought
I thought like god's heroes looked good and I like sure I guess he didn't uh he didn't actually
start making it or at least he didn't post anything from like what he was making so I I just assumed
he was working on it so I was like hey uh god's heroes looks cool and all but like I think it would
be really cool like if tails gets cold came back but I I understand if you're like busy working on it
so I and actually a few years a few years before like laser bot like actually posted on
his dvn said you know I want to keep making tails gets trolled but it's too hard so if like
there are any like artists who want to help me draw it's too hard yeah sure yeah well he I mean
I laugh but I get it because like I'm sure it it's a comics take a long time comics take a lot
of time and effort he didn't literally he didn't literally say was too hard I'm paraphrasing but
yeah sure yeah but uh um he actually posted that a few years ago so I'm like you know that
idea you had about other artists like drawing it for you like how about uh how about I try to find
some artists like draw the script that he already written because the um the next part of the script
after uh coyote gets sucked into uh the thing which is the last part yeah which is yeah I don't
think I'm there yet no that's the last part you read apparently what do you mean no I remember
the last part I read was in the middle of the fight between coyote and demara yeah that that's it
oh demaro like wait what he gets demaro had demaro had like a portal on his head and like
coyote got sucked into it oh no yeah yeah you're right yeah you're right I remember now okay yeah
so yeah that's where it left off yeah so after that laser bot and and uh his brother actually wrote
a script that says what happens when he goes inside the portal but like he never drew a
comic for it so I was just like you know people could like draw out like that script and laser
bot and laser bot was just like sure go ahead so I posted on the website saying like I'm looking
like we're looking for artists to help draw like the um the next chapter of tales gets told and
like people offer to do it so that's when it started makes sense uh yeah so that's been going on for
what like a year now a year and a half a year and a half it's it started in uh November 2019
is is the story like getting close to being finished or like how how much left is there
uh laser bot and uh his brother said that they actually like have planned the whole story out
they just haven't and they've written like notes on it and shit they just haven't like scripted it out yet
so and like how much how much it has left to be made um this I'm just going off of what
Embergram said so take this with a grain of salt but he said that there are four arcs and we're
nearing the end of the first arc I don't know how after that first arc I don't know how I don't
know how I don't know how accurate that is but uh that's what he said okay meaning like arcs that
take place after coyote gets sucked into the portal no he said uh the one we're in right now about how
the um the characters are invading troll fortress which is like the overall the overall plot like
when silver you're telling me that Embergram told you that tails gets trolled is nearing the end of
its first of four arcs yeah well he he said it he said it he said it he said it in the discord
that's insane that's that's impossible I know that can't be true I know like that's why I said
take it with a grain of salt because I don't I don't really okay I don't I don't believe it myself
like I don't know I don't know if they actually have written that much I get it like like having
such a huge idea like oh what if I just did so much with it and then you actually have to work
and it's like oh maybe four is too many but like exactly the pages post post like hiatus the pages
have not been coming out very fast like they've been like a steady trickle yeah that's that's another
thing I got I'm trying to get him to uh like um do do it faster but uh he's busy with like
like they have like a really by he by he do you mean Embergram yeah well both of them but
especially him now since laser bot left uh they have a really they have a really weird
living situation where they move like every six months so that makes it hard as well okay I want
why why is it like that why are they why are they okay like all the like stuff that happens
behind the scenes like like you said they've had like a they've had like a falling out like they
don't work together anymore laser bot left the project and it always seems like laser bot like
he doesn't have a computer set up or he doesn't have internet access for a while or he doesn't have
of this or that or he's away like what what's the deal what's what's the deal with it like
the what's their living situation like that it's all it seems really chaotic I don't really have
any idea except that they're like they're like low I don't mean this as an insult but they're like
low lower like they don't have much money I mean that's I mean look at look at me look look who
you're talking to it's it's fine no judgments yeah uh okay that's that's okay well hmm all right
gotcha gotcha and I know they also had like a bunch of people living in their last house
like they had they had Embergram his wife their daughter their kid that they just had
they're married and have a he's married and has a kid yeah I didn't know that did they live
did Embergram and and laser bot live like in the same house yes and also and also
Micah was there too I think maybe Micah must be like the third friend that they made Micah
Rat with right oh Micah is their brother oh right okay there's three brothers yes and yeah
and the three of them the three of them together must have made Micah Rat which for anyone that
doesn't know is like an old like YouTube series yeah it's like a cartoon series about the three of
them as like animals just being wacky and being being weird uh I think I made a I think my YouTube
channel the Ben the Ben St. YouTube channel has a playlist of all the Micah Rat videos that I made
just because it would be convenient yeah yeah uh so if you can check that out if you're curious
Micah Rat is very dumb and I say that with love it's very like very silly and and random
yeah yeah so okay so the three okay so they all live in a house I I got you I got you so well
well they well they did now um laser bot moved in with Micah and their friends and they have their
own place and laser bot and his wife and their hit their two kids moved to a different place and
they're like looking wait laser bot is also married and has two kids no embergram's kids okay okay
and there was like a whole family situation like laser bot said he didn't want to talk about like
the falling out publicly but it just had to do like their like living situation basically
and I mean I messed up it was my next question was going to be so yeah laser bot left the project
can you explain like why that happens and like I I'm sure that like some details of it probably
like we don't need to get too deep into like family drama or whatever but if there is anything like
I don't know that he said about like why that happened or like what the problem was like is
there any chance that he'll get back on it or is it like what's the deal what's the deal with that
please explain yeah well the falling out is like one part of it the other part of it is that
basically he told me that well I mean you could probably tell just from being like a someone who
was like like following tale sketch told it seems like he didn't have like much interest in continuing
in the first place I mean it seems like he's been trying to start other things for a while
yes exactly yeah um like he's want he's wanted to move on for it for a while and like apparently
ember gan was like basically the one who convinced him to continue after the last hiatus
I mean on the one hand I get wanting to I get wanting to start other things but also I mean
tales gets trolled is what people know laser butt force so I think if I were ember I don't
kind of make sense in my head I don't really know these people but just my my gut feeling is like
embergram is like married and has kids probably he's being pragmatic being like
if anything is gonna like make money from this from this venture if anything is like gonna
be commercial or profitable from this whole comic thing we got going it's gonna be tales
gets trolled we should like we should make it we should work on it because this is our this is
our hit right yeah that's just my guess my wild speculation yeah um I talked to them but I don't
really like know them personally either yeah so I don't really know what's going on inside their
head all I can do is speculate but so okay so he all right so I guess they they had a falling
out or they had a fight or something and also just he laser butt's not super invested or he
wants to do other things and so he's not on the project anymore and ember is like so ember is
basically managing the like guest artists basically how is it working how is the project
working right now for for getting the rest of it made well actually the thing is I'm actually
managing the guest artists and I have been so what's so what's ember doing he has like the
script that him and laser bot wrote yes okay all right but you're in charge of like delegating
pages and stuff yeah basically mm-hmm how's that going um we're just waiting for a
embergram to provide more scripts to uh so we can make pages out of it
oh because he has like notes but he needs to actually like write out the full script yes
I see and he's going he's like has a lot of stuff going on with his uh like with his job
and like his new apartment that he's moving into like it had moles so he had to go to another
apartment and like all this other stuff yeah like the animals oh you cut off for a second
moles like the like the burrowing mammal no mold uh oh molds like the like the like it was infested
with digging moles they were digging a big tunnel underneath it okay that would be a lot that would
be a lot funnier I know it's disappointing um I see well I mean I guess that I don't know is there
I mean what if I just give you the floor to like say anything you want to say about
tales get strolled and like how it's been working on it or like the current state of it
yeah yeah what's up um well I do want to say that this is like probably going to sound like
really pathetic but I'm really I'm really proud that I made a difference in the world by making
the website for tales gets trolled and making it like more accessible to people I mean when you
when you tell me that people found tales gets trolled through my lecture I swell with pride
and feel like I made a difference in the world so I I get you I get you that makes me feel really
good it's a I mean it's a cool it's a great thing to I'm a big fan so you know yeah and the fact that
I made the website and I was partly responsible for the comment coming back and um yeah it's
it's something that I've been focusing uh a lot of my time on which is like one reason I was like
really like almost heartbroken that like laser bot left the project because like nobody knew like
what was actually going to happen like if it was going to continue continue or not and it's like
I spent so much like time and money like uh promoting tales gets trolled and stuff like
it would have it would have been like really sad if it ended without like finishing
like it like I know that cancelled yeah I know that like laser bots art it is sad because laser
bots art is such like a an integral part of the tales gets trolled comic um but I mean if
yeah so like when I heard that he left the project I was I thought that was a bummer and oh no the
comic's dead but I mean if if they had the story if he knew the story if he knew like where it's
going to go from here I even even though losing his art is a shame I still feel like uh you know
the project can be complete I still feel like we're getting the real tales gets trolled if it's
if it's what he intended to happen him and him and Zagar yeah so like I'm glad that it's continuing
yeah I'm I feel kind of bad like I haven't done a good job like um oh what's the word uh
like describing or relaying like what is actually going to happen with the comic
because the tweet I made the tweet I made about um laser bot leaving got like it got like the most
like likes and retweets of any tweet I've ever ever made and then the fall and then the follow-up
tweet where it's big news and the follow-up tweet where I said uh actually guys it's not ending
that only got like like 50 retweets oh so you think that maybe some people think that it is over
yeah well I've actually seen that like unfortunate people are like oh you guys think tales gets
told is continuing while it's canceled so yeah well I mean what can you do people are gonna
people are gonna talk yeah especially people on 4chan apparently don't go on any other website
besides 4chan so they don't know about anything um I guess where okay do you I mean do you need
do you still like need people to help with the comic are you still looking for like guest artists
or anything um I'm not sure because uh we don't have anything to do right now so it's not like
I'm not sure if like we would if we were making stuff right now we wouldn't have enough people or not
I'm not really I'm not really sure like I can't I can't I can't tell until we go back into production
I see um how long have you been waiting for Zagar's scripts um since the last page released
uh when was that um it was at the end of May I don't remember the exact date oh so it's been well
it's been a couple weeks I mean I guess that's not a huge amount of time yeah that guy needs to get
cracking though yeah May 27th yeah um well where should people go to find tales gets trolled or to
get in contact with you what where where can people contact you about any of this I mean assuming
people are welcome to ask you questions about it on their own time if you want that uh tales
gets trolled.org there's a section on the main page that says contact site admin and there's a
and you're on twitter too right yes uh there's email on twitter that's linked what's your what's
the twitter at tales got trolled tales got trolled very good um tales get tales tales gets trolled
wouldn't fit so if you if you uh well if you're if you're if that's unless you have anything else
you want to add I have a couple of non-tgt related things that I was going to that I have on my
little notepad document here just just to talk about just shoot the shit you want to shoot the
shit for a while uh if there's if there's if there's anything else you want to talk about
tales gets trolled like if there's nothing else you want to mention then sure I can't think of
anything off the top of my head but if I think of anything else what whatever I'll ask it okay uh
I don't know get well how's your week been cc how's how are you doing how's your life
uh I've just been working pretty much yeah cringe cringe lame what about uh you give
oh uh the past few days I've been like catatonic I've been like nice like not moving and it sucks
are you still sick but a little bit I don't know it's like it's hard to say I'm the same as I was
like I'm not I actually vomiting or anything so it's just fine but it's not that great
that's how I felt like since the whole pandemic started I barely I barely go outside anymore
don't don't feel like doing anything well actually later today apparently I'm gonna go out for
father's day with my sister and my dad I have to call my dad later today yeah um I have been I have
become incredibly powerful actually why is that it's uh because I've started lifting again I've
been lifting I've been listening and it's a double-edged sword though because my lifts have been
going up my lifts have been shooting up in in one month I am back I was lifting for a while two
summers ago me and me and Kazi would lift weights in my basement two summers ago and this one I've
been lifting again for one month and I'm already stronger now than I was back then I'm already
up to like higher than I than I got on any of my lifts back in the day um but um part of the
reason why that's the case and I've made so rapid progress is because I've been eating a lot uh so
I'm also getting fat so I'm just going bare mode um and I don't like that but I really like seeing
numbers go up but the problem is you have to do both you can't I can't I have to make my my the
number on the scale go up at the same time that I make the number of plates on the bar go up it's
it's a faustian bargain you mean go down um I don't want number to go down number go down bad
number go down bad you don't want to lose weight I I do want to lose weight no I'm too fat I'm too
I'm too fat but I'm not strong enough it's such a it's such a conundrum no strong enough to bear
the burden of being fat that's right that's right uh it's just you lift you lift more when you're
fat it's just kind of true so I mean I should I should I I should try that I'm fatter more now
than I've ever been in my life I've I've put on I've put on a bunch of weight recently only some
of which is muscle I'm sure so you know it's a double-edged sword there um yeah but but I don't
know feels good feels good to be strong feels good to be powerful so you know that's pretty cool
yeah I had yeah go on I was working out before the pandemic but then after I was just like well
time to stay inside and get fat there's well yeah same well I didn't know I I quit working out
before the pandemic started and then during the pandemic I still didn't do it I have no good reason
because I have my weight my weight set is in my basement I didn't have to leave my house to work
out I could have been doing it the whole time I just didn't because I'm an idiot yeah well it's
well you live you live in a house right yeah well that's easier for you because I still live in
an apartment unfortunately yeah I mean I have no excuse but they have they have gymson like my complex
so I don't have to walk very far um yeah was the basement you were in the same basement where the
lecture took place no that was the tails gets trolled lecture it's oh maybe you don't know the
radcon lore but do you know about radcon uh that doesn't mean that mean anything the radcon was
this was to be funny it's really funny I just assumed there was when all the pcp people got
together basically basically yes basically but we would rent a house for it um so that was in a
that was in a rented house that we all stayed in for a week in Sharon Massachusetts uh so that's
that's not a house that I actually lived in um so yeah different my current basement is a fucking
bare concrete exposed insulation spiders everywhere uh piles of garbage not garbage garbage but like
you know junk that's in storage that's not just kind of yeah that sounds like the house
Ember Graham was trying to move into I mean it's a night I look my house is pretty nice
which is why it's a shame that I have to move out of it in uh six weeks uh I better get house
hunting why is that well because my roommate a couple of my roommates have decided that they
want to move out and the rest of us can't afford the place without them so we've all got to move
out because we've all got to find a more affordable situation yeah yeah I've I've I've a roommate too
he's my dad nice but I actually I actually make more money than him and neither of us can
afford a place by ourselves so oh you make more money than your dad and neither of you can afford
a place yeah damn do you live somewhere expensive or do you just have shitty jobs uh shitty jobs
that's fine yeah well I mean it's not fine I mean it sucks but understood understood
yeah which is which is one one way I can relate to laser bot because we're both what it's one way
I can relate to laser bot because we're both poor sure yeah I I get it I mean yeah you know I laugh
I laugh but like yeah imagine imagine being like on the constantly moving not having like a steady
place to live not having just like a place to have your shit set up in your microphone and your
computer and stable internet yeah I must blow it was pretty hard it meant I can't I can't possibly
but if I could I'm sure it would be a big problem yeah that's lame well what one thing I I forgot to
mention is that they could uh they could probably talk on their phones on discord like they wouldn't
need a mic but that's I mean that's how that's how um we we did um the episode with Mallory
which everyone hated because they're all a bunch of weird fucking bootlickers who got offended by
shoplifting fuck you cowards is is is uh what's her pronoun or their pronoun what's her pronoun
yeah that's her yeah that's her um the purple hair sweet beans sweet beans new guy I just I just
didn't want to refer to them the wrong way no you got it she's a lady okay what's her
pronoun yeah that's funny but is she the one who she was the one who made like the the the furry
comic where like they steal from like the um yeah and they're like bkduke and the new and the new guy
and the new guy one about the the new guy you remember new guy no I don't know he was a new guy
a job he's that guy who's new I can't even remember what it was about but people were really mad
about it it's her her self-insert is laughing about PewDiePie they don't say PewDiePie but it's
she's laughing about PewDiePie getting robbed or Bray's house getting broken oh yeah I remember
that well actually that's and the new guy's like how'd you like it if someone broke into your house
and she's like you're a stupid jerk Baldi well she doesn't say that I'm paraphrasing um yeah that
that's actually kind of based not gonna lie it's kind of based I'm so glad you know what this is
this is not even joking this is like my litmus test if you're fucking if you if you get upset
if you get upset about the sweet beans comics if you get upset about Mallory's comics I
literally don't want to be your friend I literally just don't want to be your friend I
don't want to know you fuck you well this goes for you too viewers I'm not I'm not I'm not upset
by it but the the shoplifting one I mean I don't have a problem with stealing from corporations
it's just the comic was just kind of uh no I don't know I'll kill you what's wrong with the comic
uh I don't fight me I don't really remember I mean there's nothing there's literally nothing to
it it's just like a character it's literally just the character goes in and shoplifts and pens and
then walks out they're like like yeah generic understanding of like huh stealing I guess that's
bad and then if they don't think about I guess I don't think about it they might like just join
the crowd of like hey this comic sucks it I mean it's it's one this is this will be like the eighth
time I've gone in the same rate it's one thing to see that and think hmm I don't think shoplifting is
good but it's another thing entirely to read that comic and be like upset that someone drew it
upset that someone drew a character stealing got I will can you if you can believe it actually
some of the most some of the most popular works of cinema in in the pre in the last century have
involved theft have depicted scenes of theft murder sexual assault uh many many such illegal
activities have been depicted by character you know you get what I'm saying did you know the
crystal meth from Breaking Bad is not legal to eat dude it's logging into my logging into my
YouTube account to post angry comments on every screen on every upload of a scene from Breaking
Bad like I can't believe they made a show about making drugs don't they know that drugs are illegal
this is a bad influence that's literally doing that's literally what they're doing it's like that
a lot of people think like Walter is based though even though like he's a fucked up criminal
I know so this fucking this fucking little fucking orange cat that stole pens is also base I don't
get it oh yeah oh nothing literally nothing makes me angrier than fucking new guy discourse
yeah okay whatever it's totally off topic yeah we didn't really have a topic but I got something
you're right I got my please my lord of ghosts speaking of comics speaking of
incredible works of art like like tales gets trolled would you say that lord of ghosts is
better or worse than tales gets trolled oh it's far worse yeah agreed I can all agree probably
everything is worse than tales gets trolled it's just so it's so fun to watch that to read that
but yeah the lord of ghosts is my comic and I'm kick starting it right now I mentioned at the
beginning of the show link in the description link in the description I've got I got a video for it
it's uh everyone everyone put money in his Kickstarter yeah I've seen yeah that would be a
really good idea I've seen the I've seen the video it has not released as of right as of recording
the video is not public but I've seen it and I think it's funny so this has been from the past
predicting again a PCP scoop a PCP uh a exclusive scoop I predict that in the future you viewer
will watch a funny video and laugh uh and click the link in the description and be proven correct
it's a it's a comic about a ghost who is trying to become lord of that's not actually true
it's not actually what it's about but it's about this this guy who's a little blob of weirdo
he's stupid he's stupid and he goes around in this slime in his mud and there's killing
and there's blood as well dude how could you draw a comic where somebody kills another person
like that's such a bad influence on our society why didn't notably no but notably none of them
said that crime should be illegal did you see that Ben Shapiro tweet oh oh yeah yeah oh god none of
the what should what should you think should be banned hmm none of them said crime hmm says a lot
about our society yeah and the and the thing that he was uh tweeting or responding to they were
giving answers about like what food they would ban or something and it would I would ban crime personally
but crime from my restaurant all these these route these route co-left democrats won't ban crime
what the fuck is wrong this country that's true that's true sad yeah I mean lord of ghost is the
ultimate crime lord because his goal is basically to just build an army and then like attack another
city and he's the protagonist he's a good guy you like that you like that he wants to kill everyone
I can't believe this comic depicts an act of colonization lord of ghost wants to colonize
those those slime people and it's wrong yeah it's evil yeah anyway whatever what enough of this joke
enough uh or what kind of comic is it is it like a physical comic yeah it's it's a kick
started for the physical release of what I've done so far which is like a 90 something 100 pages
of what would be like a comic sized comic like smaller than a 4 bigger than a 5 I don't know
like the the normal size um speaking of which I've been I've been interested in looking into
a physical release of tails gets trolled oh all these I'll have to I mean I'll buy I'm gonna buy
a copy of lord of ghosts I will I'll buy an official release of tail gets trolled if that's
I'll have to I have to it would be really funny to have that on the show so yeah yeah yeah but the
thing is I have no idea how to make books or anything I it's not so difficult I I use this
well it might be a UK based um or maybe they have an American version as well but like it's
it's quite simple mix and what did you use mix and okay I used a company called cub lamb
yeah so mix and like that you go to them and you you say okay I want page thickness of this
grayscale full color um how many pages then you upload a pdf and it gives you like
like a little there's a little onsite on the website like you put the information in
even before the the images and stuff you see like how many pages and and like the size of it and
how many copies and then they tell you how much it's going to cost and it's really doesn't seem
that expensive the most expense I think for me is going to be the postage sending it out to people
once it's been made that's that's the hardest part because like
especially especially yeah especially for you because you live in a country that
sucks well I mean most most most of most of our audience is is in the US yeah predominantly so
like most stuff is going to have to go across the pond which is I have accounted for that in
in the the pricing there's a lot of like number crunching and and potentials because I don't know
exactly how many people are going to be from the US I have to like yeah figure it out make sure it's
not too expensive oh it's it's a whole thing but I've got it all set up and it's hopefully there's
going to be the lot of ghosts comic then there's the little ghost pin which I can take a picture of
because they exist now I got some samples and you showed me then there's like oh yeah I did show you
uh there's um there's a fucking stretch goals for guest art Ben of of whom will
potentially be drawing a little ghost story oh god that's right I agreed to do that oh no
I'm fucked now you just gotta hope you just gotta hope that uh the fucking thing doesn't
reach that goal um I'm gonna sabotage it yeah it's the only thing there's like a
then there's like a red man stretch goal like at the red man comic print which might be fun oh you
mean red you mean red noir no no no the little like little twitter comics in a little tiny square
book oh right right right right I forgot about those you haven't made one in a while I haven't I
should well I would but the final big stretch goal I have to mention to tease is the possibility of a
lot of ghosts plush which is it's really far up out there but I have like the plush company
making a sample of the thing and I might have a picture to show at some point I don't have it yet
but it's it's a whole big thing and I'm really excited I'm really excited to see how far I can
go with this because as soon as you have a sample you should post you should update the kick starter
with a with a picture of that as the stretch goal yeah definitely because I want to see that I want
to see that yeah so yeah it's uh for for tales comic news for tales gets told characters the only one
I would want to see a plush of is Rob the dragon born yeah yes yeah we're less dragonborn well the
other characters wouldn't work for obvious reasons I mean I mean I would like I think Alex is iconic
enough oh yeah he could he could have he could have a plush yeah I just meant the copyrighted
characters you wouldn't be sure yeah because you can get official plushes of them too if it works
so well because his head is always drawn like a thumb shape like it's so smooth like an egg
that's Rob is a strong choice I think I think Alex or the troll king would make pretty good plushes
yeah and Alex anyone else Alex could Alex could have his own back uh his cigarette
tomorrow yeah tomorrow and Alex could have his own cigarette which he smokes backwards
or removable you could remove it you can take it out yeah yeah and you could smoke it you could
smoke it yourself he it's an actual cigarette that you can just smoke it comes with one's real
cigarette yeah for fun yeah yeah uh yeah hell yeah did you ever so you can put it you can just get
a little hole in his mouth you can light a cigarette put it in his mouth and let it burn down until
it lights him on fire yeah okay that reminds me of a great idea Ben you know those under uh they
made like official undertale plushes and like if you destroy the plush there's like a heart inside
no no I never heard of that that was that's a pretty cool that's official that's official yeah
amazing it's like it's like supposed to represent how when you kill monsters like you get their soul
and shit sure yeah you would have to destroy the plush to get it oh that's great yeah it's so
that's pretty good yeah that's pretty on brand that's pretty good yeah um impressed did you
ever listen to those um the tales gets told album
no the the one uh j-flight made or just I haven't heard about it no you have it you
haven't oh my god you know what tell me tell me about it you didn't hear the tales gets told songs
I didn't please wait I saw that on the side there was a there was a bit about yeah um yeah there
jazz flight was a something awful goon and like he made a soundtrack for the first
10 chapters of the song of of the comic based yeah and the first is it is it good is it quality
yes it like they get stuck in my head all the time like the first one is like tales gets
trolled tales gets trolled yeah there it is and he he basically gets trolled the album
he basically he basically takes the dialogue from each chapter and like makes the song out of it
I see you have to I'm really surprised you haven't listened to that because that's like a famous
thing among the tales gets called community I I know I'm guess I'm a little surprised too
because I hadn't even heard about it fascinating I I do want to talk about I I know that I've
I know that I've come down with a pretty strong anti-dream stance famously oh my god but I did
I did have a dream and I want to talk about it I want to tell you about this funny dream oh
I thought you meant the fucking Minecraft guy no not the Minecraft guy fuck that guy I'm so I've
never I've literally never like seen him I don't know what he sounds like I don't know what he looks
like I just see his logo and I just hate him instinctually the only thing I know about him is
that he keeps trending on Twitter I'm just like shut the fuck up I don't care about this shit it's
I've heard that like someone who works at Twitter is just a dream stan and they like promote his
bullshit not just in like in like the trending tab just because they like him not just dream it's
like a bunch of Minecraft fucking people like like yeah and their and their fans are all like 16 year
old dumb younger younger than that you gotta change your Twitter location to like yeah country
I did I changed it a little bit on my main account which is a chaff and hammer
um I changed it to like the country with like the least population I don't remember what it was called
but I just looked your your chaff and hammer yeah oh okay I know okay I've seen you I didn't know you
and the tails okay got it got it anyway yeah I I used to link the I used to link the accounts
to each other but I don't anymore but my my bio still says I'm the admin of tails gets full
but anyway um yeah I just looked on Wikipedia and said what is the least populated country and
then I put that as my put that as my trending and now nothing comes up so I'm pretty happy
about that all right that's all great but it's a distraction from the important thing which is
my cool dream that I had okay I'm gonna and I'm gonna tell you guys about I'm gonna tell you you
about my dream okay so in my dream I went to a big Christmas party at a hotel and the thing
was that I was meeting Joe Rogan because he was my uncle Joe wrote oh yeah Joe didn't you
talk about that on Twitter I know I might have mentioned it in my discord oh yeah you did yeah
um yes okay I'll I I like woke up after this dream was over in a in a sort of disturbed emotional
state and I was like I I'll forget the details I have to go write it down so I went and I wrote
down all these notes about everything I could remember about it so I'm looking at this big
paragraph I'm not going to read the whole thing I'm just going to give you the highlights
so as a hotel big Christmas party Joe Rogan is my uncle I'm meeting him for the first time
I'm really excited I'm like I'm going around the hotel I'm exploring the hotel and for some
reason I decide to call Joe Rogan on the phone and tell and pretend to be a little girl I pretend
to be like a little girl cousin and and be like I want to talk to grandpa uncle I'm a little girl
uncle Joe Rogan please unlock the basement so I can go down to the basement to talk to grandpa
and he knows that it's me impersonating this some little girl and he's like not impressed he thinks
that's really lame and he's like uh this is bad impression why are you doing this this is annoying
and I'm like uh no it's not Ben it's the little it's your little niece uh uh Samantha uh okay bye
uncle Joe and I hang up and I'm like oh fuck this is my first time meeting Joe Rogan and I just
made an idiot of myself he hates me oh fuck what have I done so uh uh um anyway so I'm walking
around and I'm getting and I get into an elevator and Joe with a bunch of people and Joe Rogan is
also there um and he asks if I need to get into the elevator and I do but I pretend that I don't
and so I'm just shuffled down the hallway as he like watches me leave down the hallway and I'm
like muttering to myself like oh you know you gotta you gotta do what you gotta do sometimes
just don't get into an elevator and I go down to the hotel lobby and someone offers me an alcoholic
coke zero and I know I shouldn't drink because I really want to make a good impression on Joe Rogan
yeah that sounds good but I take it I drink it anyway and I get a little buzz on my ha ha
now I'm gonna look like a fool in front okay I'm gonna skip a little bit I'm gonna skip a little
bit of this this is all you've like not wanting to fuck up your meeting with Joe Rogan I just
because he's got so much clout because he's got yes this is just ways all right late he's there was
like a big magic statue it was like a big like mobile art piece that like whatever there was
like a magical statue this is dumb this is boring I'm gonna skip that part the first part is is
relatable in a way not the doing the girl voice but like fucking like thinking for some strange
reason that what you're doing is like oh this this could work and then of course as soon as you do
it you wait you realize that's the stupidest thing I could have possibly done why did I do that I've
ruined it why did I why did I want to talk to grandpa so bad why did I need my uncle Joe Rogan's
permission to go into the basement in order to do so and why did I think that pretending to be
a small girl on the phone would convince him to make that possible for me um anyway who who's
your uh grandpa in this situation I don't know nobody in particular just a hypothetical grandpa
of this family that includes me and Joe Rogan I would have assumed it was another celebrity
no but okay so skip oh one thing I want to say is that I've been laughing this whole time but my
mic hasn't been picking it up okay just laughing on the inside yeah okay skipping through a bunch
of weird shit um I get to the end and um I finally even though I've already met Joe Rogan like in the
elevator it's like okay oh I'm meeting it's time for me to finally meet my famous uncle Joe Rogan
for the first time I hope I make a good impression even though he knows that I impersonated a small
child on the phone earlier but it's okay so he and some other uncle are walking up I mean he's like
hey oh Ben so yeah different uncle is it your uncle is he just a person who is an uncle no
another of my uncle so his brother or something so we really oh Joe Rogan it's great it's me
hey Ben it's me Joe Rogan your uncle oh it's great to meet you oh that's not what he sounds like
so we hug and I'm like wow uncle Joe Rogan I'm honored I'm honored to make your acquaintance sir
but he's like but he's like kind of sweating and he's like huge I know Joe Rogan is literally
five foot three everybody knows this well in the dream he's like he's really tall and he's like a bear
of a man and we hug but he's like a little off and he seems like a little bit like out of it and
distressed and he's telling the other uncle like uh it's fine it's fine it'll be fine you know I'll
just do a little drunk drive and you know it'll be fine it's gonna be fine and then and some other
guy some other family member we're in like a garage and some other guy is changing his tire or he's
packing up his trunk and Joe Rogan pulls out a huge silver gun and shoots that guy and his head
comes off and just plops onto the ground on on like behind where his car was and Joe like walks
over to him and soccer kicks the head and like kicks it like across the garage like kicks it
through a window or something and I'm like looking at this and I'm thinking like this is like a bit
right this is like some kind of joke like I'm being fucked with but I look at the ground and there's
like gore and blood from like the the gun decapitation and I'm like this is a bit this is a bit right
you're joshing me right now and so and so he Joe Rogan is like he's waving the gun around but he
looks back at me is like anyway where were we it's great to meet you Ben and I'm like uh yeah it's
great to meet you too uncle Joe um it's gonna be like drunk driving I'm just gonna do a little
drunk driving it'll be okay I'll be okay we do a little jump driving it's cuz we do a little jump
driving so that's that's where I woke up I woke up feeling like boy I gotta pretend like it's cool
that Joe Rogan just shot this guy's head off I gotta pretend like it's cool or else he might do the
same to me because he he seems disgruntled he seems he seems emotionally disturbed but he's got the
gun and he's huge he's huge Joe Rogan he's so powerful he's got so much so much clouds yes
exactly oh the cloud allows you to do so much you think he was gonna go to jail for shooting that
other uncle's head off no no he doesn't give a fuck that's he's got he's connected I just so
anyway that was my Joe Rogan is my uncle dream I just like how it's a unspecified other uncle
yeah well you know how in dreams there are people who you you don't know who they are they're just
there and you understand like they're like peripheral uh details you know what they are but
you could not possibly describe them yeah I was there I wanted to talk to some grandpa I impersonated
some cousin the guy he was with some uncle no one no one in particular you know yeah I have dreams
like that where I have family members but they look nothing like my family but I just they just
think they're my family in my head in the middle of talking to me he just pulls out this gun shoots
this guy's head off the head sits on the ground he walks over to it soccer kicks it out the window
it turns back to me still waving the gun like hey great to meet you oh boy it kind of it kind of
jealous that's a good dream it kind of reminds me of something from like a neil brain movie
it wasn't that good oh yeah
um anyway that was the most interesting thing that happened to me this week was a dream
it was all make believe that oh wait there is there is one other thing this week I decided okay
so you know like I said me and Oolulilia talked about our games how we're both making s and the
s looking video games a little bit uh so I've been working on that I've been programming I've
been coding I've been like tech tech tech like hacker typing like all the code into my game right
what engine what engine are you making it in a game maker studio two okay yeah game game maker
studio um so anyway I decided this week that like okay the game has a bunch of enemies and I'm not
going to say what the enemies are but the enemies are all a particular kind of thing so I had all
these dummy sprites that were the enemy and I was like you know since I have like a template
sort of made for the enemy sprites what if I just made you know like 30 or 40 slight variation like
I decided to do a lisa where every enemy in the game is like a little bit different looks a little
bit different has its own name just because I thought it would be cool because I love I love
that lisa did that I think that's so awesome so I decided to do that so this week I was like
I was grinding out all these unique sprites for each individual enemy and then I was like you know
I've got I've got like 30 done and I need like 40 something so I decided to make it like a
patron thing so I got in I got on patreon and I made an announcement I went into my server my
discord server and I made an announcement in the patron channel was like patrons if you want to design
an enemy as long as it more or less matches the template that I have like everyone can make one
and put it in the game and I think I've I've I've put like 10 in so far um people have made some
really funny ones I won't say what they are it would be spoilers but there's it's been it's been
funny and I've been it's kind of what I've been working on a lot this week is a lot of enemy
sprite stuff and adding those in and just having a just having a good old freaking time patreon.com
slash ben saint if you want to suggest an enemy design to be in phantom's revenge when that comes
out in the not too distant future um there's some funny there's some funny someone someone
suggested someone uh a brunswick reference there's now a brunswick references there there's an among
us there's an among us reference in there uh you know all the cool shit all the cool
shit that you have the two cool things that's right that's right uh yes speaking of speaking
of patreon uh apparently zegar aka embergram is gonna put me in charge of the tgt patreon soon so
might get some good rewards up there maybe oh you're not you're not already in charge of it no
hmm it's it's uh yeah it doesn't it's it's under I mean just do they give rewards now I haven't
read through it in detail what's the deal with the patreon right now uh zegar was the one managing
that stuff uh before I came around as as we've said as we've said before like they're really bad with
like um promotion and shit so yeah he's like he's the one um he was the one doing that stuff before
I came along but he's still in charge of the patreon but he hasn't he hasn't had time to like do anything
the only rewards right now is that you get a title on the uh discord I mean okay fair enough
are you you're gonna add some more rewards you think yeah the one I'm thinking of right now is
the original like hd versions of the comic nobody nobody has them besides me and
embergram so that would be cool to upload them for them that's that's good that's a good that's a
perfectly reasonable thing that I could see people pledging for yeah hi res yeah um and maybe like
like you said about the other one like suggestions for characters and shit I don't know well I mean he
did the um was it Lorenzen Jared Lorenzen and uh the the bird yeah like they've already had there
have already been like fan suggested like characters in the comic yeah yeah yeah Jared why not yeah
Jared Jared every every so often I get comments on my lecture that are like actually Jared Lorenzen
was a real life football player and I'm like okay thanks for letting me know thanks for telling me
again yeah I've heard tech well technically the character in tales gets told is only based on Jared
Lorenzen and it's not actually him hmm his his yes he did not literally become a two-dimensional
character yeah yeah it's a it's actually only a picture of him it's like this is not a pipe
it's like you have the picture you have the picture of Jared Lorenzen from the tales gets
told common it's this is not Jared Lorenzen underneath it yeah yeah all right yeah in the
comic so far they just revert for oh sorry referred to him as football player and football with two
words of course foot oh they don't actually say his name no they just call him football player
two words oh okay football player yeah and he plays football not football yeah and this is uh
got it uh and for anyone else who wants to know all about the tales gets told characters and the
tales gets told universe there's a tales gets told wiki which is linked on the front page of the
website and you can find all about football player and everyone all the other characters
football player yeah he plays ball and he and he likes feet I don't know he's apparently friends
friends with hulk
uh should we go should we start voicemails uh cc do you do you want to listen to voicemails
with us sure sure you don't have to we won't okay well if you if last week zero dipped in
he he crashed the podcast and then we got like halfway through voicemails and he was like I've
had enough and he left and you know what I can't I can't blame him who's zero um oh he's he's one
of the two guys from the kato um uh anthology kickstart we had he was a guest uh like last month
I think uh okay not not zero from mega man oh I thought it was no I apologize I'm sorry
who have misled you okay in the in the general chat I have posted the first voicemail this
is called hilarious jpe are we ready yeah yes okay on the counter three three two one go and tifa
be tifa I don't know all I know is that when I see tifa I fucking come
yeah true I don't know if it rises to the level of hilarious but I smiled I smile uh next one is
called let me put it in general chat next one is called guilty three two one go
welcome to the pre podcast rape why are these rapes this guy hello and welcome to another episode
of the procrastinators podcast too late you were selected let us begin I thrust my penis towards him
I remember that I don't remember where it's from is is this you that's me why it was just
I don't know just so like some one of my videos maybe why would you why would you sexually assault
best guy ever and admit to it uh well you see I didn't think the candles were rolling I can't
believe you would make depict you would depict sexual assault in a piece of media that's so
unacceptable and it's such a bad influence on our society you know people actually say that about
tales gets trolled they say like oh people say bad words and tales gets trolled it's like it should
be shut down they sure do yeah they sure do they made me they made me say the n-word they forced me
to they forced me to mention the bad words they don't mention that the bloody gore and death yeah
they they don't care about that we love that they just care about trolls saying like bad discriminatory
words the words of power yeah words of power words of death words of death that's right I'm
thinking of Dungeons and Dragons there's actually the words of death and the words of words of life
but they haven't gotten to the words of life yet oh pcp exclusive a pcp exclusive scoop you heard
it here for oh my god there's so many scoops there's so many big scoops this is like this is like an
ice cream shop this is like raisin brand this is but there's three scoops uh sorry to disappoint
you but that's actually like been publicly revealed fuck we're back down to two scoops
unscoop we're back down to two scoops we're equal to raisin brand yeah unfortunately okay cool uh
next voicemail is called idea oh oh quick quick quick uh where do you leave voicemails what's up
oh uh where do you leave voicemail why are you gonna go leave one are you gonna leave a stealth
one while we're not paying attention yeah okay well all you have to do viewers and all you have to
do is go to www.speakpipe.com slash pcp voicemail okay i'm just gonna i'm gonna go pee so you can
do that while i go pee okay i need a pee break too okay pee break okay break ellie is i need to get
i need to get water too a few moments later in this brief moment i just want to remind people
that you can read the lord of ghosts on gibb and take dot site if you haven't read it already
read what um if you don't know whether you want to get the kick started version if you if you want
before you buy yeah yeah on her website you know she has a website give and take
give and take dot site give and take that site the home of all bet you got bail bail jpe uh lord
of ghosts lord of ghosts red war red noir right pocket boys uh the very short live not nuzzle
attempt i didn't even i didn't even die i just didn't i just didn't play the game
i i've never done when i was like when i was like 20 or something i also
no i think it must have been like maybe 23 or something i also started a what was supposed
to be a nuzzle comic and i i was drawing like stick figures and i did like one page of it and
then i just didn't keep doing it yeah everybody everybody gets one everybody gets one it's it's
hard to keep up with that stuff um especially since like if i did nuzzle like i wouldn't even draw it
too lazy yeah and also i'm not a good artist the last thing i drew was for that um the
fuck the the top 10 tales get strolled characters from the contest tops okay did you submit uh
no like weren't you the judge no each each member of the art uh each member of the art team
drew one character like we had we had a pop we had a popularity contest for what the most popular
characters were and each each of us drew one character who like the characters who got the
most votes and i drew mario so you can you can tell that i'm not a very good artist wait you drew
mario yeah on that picture yeah that just looks exactly like how he appears in the tales get
strolled comic yeah it looks like it looks like it looks like it was traced out of the comic it
wasn't traced nice it wasn't traced but i i i closely based it on it i'm i'm gonna bet coyote
won right it says on the picture oh it's right there it does it literally says okay i mean it's a
it's a great i mean look at him he's ripped yeah that's that's uh the main artist for the main
artist for chapter 23 uh he drew coyote like really sexy and people complained about it
they were like why why did they keep showing coyotes ass you know yeah
i get it i get it uh okay let's go to that last voicemail i posted the 3 3 2 2 is called uh
idea 3 2 1 go okay then mom he doesn't want the pcp because he doesn't want to talk about
okay get on fucking sigh the original arch digi head like arch digi like simp at least in the past
who i believe would have a lot to say on the subject if if uh discussing this whole debacle
is what you're really after um yeah get scion but why would scion know as much as monkey right up there
with the pcp so it could happen so yeah i wouldn't i don't so i wouldn't know anything in particular
about it honestly a bunch of people have suggested like get sigh on and like who's sigh i mean i i don't
care sigh is sigh is the gang themselves i have open condom sigh is a youtuber who we know who wasn't
it honestly if sigh wants to be i would let i would let sigh be i would let sigh be a guest like it's
fine i don't care sure why not he's just a youtuber yeah he's a he's i think he's an x i don't think
he does youtube anymore oh yeah i'm something about that um i'm not really looking to like
i mean i thought it would be interesting to talk to mumke about i'm not looking for like
oh we gotta get anyone we can find to talk about the trixie drama like it's not that serious
if sigh wanted to it would be fine i don't know whatever someone tell tell sigh to ask you to be
on the show i will if you're like any kind of if you're any kind of like if you have any kind of
like social media presence if you're any kind of like known creator on the internet and you
ask me if you want to be on the show i will usually say yes so if sigh just asked me like hey can i
be on the show i'd be like yes sure come on on sunday didn't and that's true for a lot of people
didn't mumke make those uh elliot roger videos he did okay he was the elliot roger the guy the uh
the guy who drew coyote in that picture also made a mumke fan art i think it was like a i mean it
was like a picture of him and elliot roger like shooting guns i drew i drew some mumke fan art one
time i drew um in at the end of one of his nuzlocs when he beat the elite four i drew a picture of
his grand bull punching a hole through lance's charizard bad ass with mumke in the background
drunk because he was doing a drinking challenge uh there's right there's two things i want to bring
up the first one is that speaking of youtube uh i've been on youtube since 2006 and i just got
1000 subscribers so i'm pretty proud you have a channel yeah what do you do on your channel uh i
i just basically upload like random like shitpost videos what random shitpost videos what's it what's
it called uh it's the same as my twitter which is chaffenheimer himmer whatever chaffenheimer
chaffenheimer whatever based yeah next congrats on one k yeah you just get you just need 99 more
and you get that silver plaque you mean 999 000 more i mean 99 i mean 99 000 more yeah or yeah 99
more k's yeah yeah you get the you get the silver at 100 k you get the gold at a million right that's
how it works right yeah i was thinking of uh i was thinking of making one for myself just drawing
like a a play button on a piece of paper and writing 1000 subscribers the the the paper plaque
for one k yeah honestly the first they should be the first thousand is the hardest paper should be
the one subscriber plaque yeah yeah true yeah you can you can upgrade to cardboard when you when you
get the more budget uh yeah yeah when the production budget increases okay okay speaking of speaking of
production okay oh sorry yeah go on no no it's fine what is it what's up uh just um you guys will have
to like show me how to like make books and shit so i can make uh physical tales get shown
i mean there there's not much to it um there's yeah the the sites they they they make it quite easy
for you they at least this one does that i'm using you just you need to put it into a pdf format for
this and it you upload it and it just puts all the pages there okay yeah kablam kablam has like
you know you can you can choose like what page layout you want and they'll give you a template
that's like okay lay it out so that like the image fits into this area you know this is the margin
where you know you might get partially cut off so make sure there's nothing important there okay and
it's like okay just arrange arrange your files into like tiff files or into like a pdf and then
you submit them and then they'll they'll quote you a price based on like page count whether
you want color or not and stuff like that yeah i think the the the most difficult part would be
making because all the uh all the um uh pages are not the same size are they elf tails gets
trolled some of them are bigger or longer oh yeah you're right you have to cut them up so that so
that everything would fit on a page at a time yeah yeah yeah it's just can be a little tricky
yeah we'll figure it out you guys can send me the websites later yeah next voicemail is called
bradley garlic home three two one go i have never seen winier winer babies or poopier
pants poopers in the comment section for that brad lecture yep i want things to go back to the way
they were shut up just shut up shut up please please if a hundred other comments were left
saying the exact same thing maybe don't comment it i had a hemorrhage reading through that
it's i i i get i get it can i get it if you're nostalgic for like pre-pandemic old pcp whatever
i get it but like can i uh i don't know can i life is changed can i inquire can i inquire about
what the brad lecture entails well you can see it on our honestly the story i had the story all
right i i know this is imagine explain imagine explaining the context of the brad lecture just
someone who doesn't know where i got it so so the the channel right it got hacked one day because
um uh nate made a made an oopsie and he downloaded a program and he has access to the to the to the
channel his account his youtube channel and the pcp they all got hacked and what uh the content that
was uploaded instead was this uh this live feed of like cryptocurrency brad cryptocurrency like
ceo boy brad garling house with his his coin it was like live it was live streams yeah live
streams about this cryptocurrency called ripple which is owned by no the cryptocurrency is xrp
the company that owns this ripple and the ceo of ripple is this guy called brad garling house so so
we were trying to get our channel back um it was really annoying and brad garling house was like a
funny name for the villain uh he didn't do it himself it was obviously just some guy who found
you know hacked you don't you don't know that you don't know that we you know we don't know that
uh it could have been him personally but yeah then later we got the channel back we had radcon
very soon after we got the channel back because we had been planning that we met up and we thought
wouldn't it be fun to have brad garling house um appear at radcon he's the villain he's the guy
he's like a character in our universe now so uh nate dressed up as brad garling house and he did
a no nate wasn't there nate what nate was taking a shit nate nate missed it all night nate was
mysteriously absent when brad garling house showed up that's true that's the party that's true and
and brad garling house did a lecture uh in the style of the lectures we do at radcon like the one
the tails gets full lecture kind kind is a little different is brad brad's new um yeah and yeah and
that that's that was what that was so and so it's a yeah and the reason people are so nostalgic
is because we took a really long time getting that out and so much is the the whole pandemic
happened in the time in the time since yeah the whole pandemic happened and also we had like
five members quit since then so like most of the people in that video are like not even around
anymore or like maybe half i don't know that's that's that's another thing i wanted to ask you about uh
before i found the tails gets trolled video the only member that i knew about was uh tricksy
i hate you so um i yeah because because she did like anime shit i love anime obviously um
and manga and gaming uh yeah uh so yeah go on so like what happened what what a what a
i'm not i'm that's too that's too much to fucking get into yeah i'm not gonna ask you to get into it
that's that yeah you watch all just all you have to do is just watch all like 280 episodes of the
podcast and then you will know and then you will know yeah i so i i sort of have an idea of what
happened so i'm not gonna ask you to get into it but it's pretty it's pretty sad yeah pretty sad
what happened uh no it's good it's good that she's gone and i think it's funny and i think that her
i think that what she's doing to her do her career is funny and it makes me smile so you know
yeah so we can agree to disagree about that self sabotage lamel anyway okay the next voicemail
oh which i haven't even uploaded because i'm stupid uh i'm uploading now the next voicemail
is called king bradley the fourth there it is three two one go also this concept of like we
gotta go back like not that much has changed like tricksy is not on good terms with the podcast
and munchie doesn't want to do internet stuff yeah that's about the only changes we've seen
nate still is on good terms with the pcp yeah and jessey i don't know if you noticed but he
wasn't super involved before radcon four yeah so that's true that status quo hasn't changed too much
he had already been basically gone for like a year but then he just showed up for radcon because we
asked him if he wanted to and he said sure um yeah this guy's right i really i wish more people had
this guy's attitude yeah yeah things some things change yeah i don't want to i don't i don't want
to be too hard on the people in the comic because i know that a lot of people are like uh i you know
this was this was fun and like i'm it was a good old day i don't i don't begrudge anyone for feeling
like ah the good old days it just was funny to read all those comments and see that like swelling of
like tears it's like jesus yeah come on guys i come on you know i have to um we did that stream
where we um we workshopped the final chapter of road to radcon i have i have not gotten around to
writing it uh but maybe this week i will um because i'm getting a little i've been really
cranking on the game and i'm getting a little burnt and maybe i'll take a break and just do a
little do a little creative writing with road to radcon chapter five um anyway next voicemail
is called uh mar it's margar okay three two one go what up it's your boy margar what up so
we are approaching one year of nate not showing up to the podcast so everybody maybe stop asking
about it because it's pretty clear he's not gonna show up and if he does that's been has been posting
no nate no watch see you next week for a year so maybe don't be so fucking annoying and constantly
bringing it up all right that's pretty much it i might start sending voicemails in again remember
when margar was the thing of course yeah how could i later i i mean i think no no nate no watch is a
meme now like when people post no nate no watch i mean is it a bit of a tired meme perhaps but
they're not seriously complaining like nate's not here and it makes me upset it's a it's a it's a meme
yeah so it doesn't bug me that much no but it is this is pretty tired it's a little i mean it's
it has been an entire year uh okay the next voicemail is called an indecent proposal there it is
three two one go hi pcb it's a minute sorry you know jane nicleson yes have you considered
inviting her on for one episode she's kind of a big inspiration for the whole group right
kind of i know it's not funny how there's so much drama around specifically the brain lecture
when a year ago jenny released a video about the brunny fandom and it's almost identical
in format to the pcp university lectures i find it kind of funny if she was on maybe some other
crew members could come on for a one-off sin who knows uh and a final question for you
are there any other characters in media that are like brisker that you enjoy and uh do you
like them for the same reasons that you like brisker anyway thanks for the cast love and kisses
uh return to strong toton it will never die and peace what character did he say very brisker have
you read homestuck cc nope it boo it just it just looks it just looks like a worse version of
chales gets trolled you wait explain justify yourself i'm joking i i've never read it okay
you fucking better be so that was a real comment he made i i don't i don't know some some people
well some some people have actually some people have actually said that i can't understand i can't
i can't understand the minds of people who haven't read home i'm like that that episode of regular
show where they get too smart and they can't understand regular people anymore like that's
me but it's with people who haven't read homestuck so like if someone says they haven't read it
like i'll i'll believe any dumb shit they say because like of course they would um yeah no i i try i
tried i tried reading it but uh i stopped reading it when he was in his room that's the first panel
that's the first page yeah basically okay there that's fine that's that's fine um but optimistic
of this guy to think that we could just get jenny nicholson to be on the show like i've talked to
i've talked to her before but like it doesn't i don't think she just like oh she i mean she's
a big name yeah she's a very big youtuber right now yeah she's famous she makes like a billion
fucking dollars for like two videos a year she's really big lol uh hold on how much does she make
on patreon jenny nicholson page yeah it might be fun to see it like if if we're doing like an episode
about like the new generation of my little pony effect when that comes out and we want to talk about
it get jenny nicholson just give her a ring hey you want to come on the just just get up we're gonna
talk about ponies oh yeah you know we should get um you know who i you know who i hear is big on
youtube uh pewdiepie we should get him on the show like that would be pretty good right like that would
be a good idea no just a lot of people would watch that one he's cringe though just keep him away from
bridges and we'll be fine um because he's gonna burn them because he's a troll who lives under a
bridge he said he said he said a bad word when he was playing a game oh yeah i know the clip
oh i don't i don't know it's it's the adpocalypse clip he he he said he he says one of the words of
death oh oh no okay i got you yeah i got you um to answer the question uh about vreska
other characters there are some characters that that get that sort of character of like of like
oh i i i know who that is yeah yeah the really fucked up um mean girl who secretly uh or is
repressing like the desire to be nice um and it's really tragic there's not that many good of that
but like the the general like trope uh like the the the the sort of stereotype of that character
appears a lot uh pacifical northwest from gravity falls is kind of that and i like i like that when
i see it i think i think um riska's riska is king i think i think i think i i think i know who
you're talking about now is she's like one of the trolls right from uh not tales gets told from
homestuck that's the thing about oh that's why because they both have trolls in them that's why
you thought they were the same well i i i just laser laser but red homestuck and put trolls from
homestuck like you put cart like you put carcat in just like saw that would be so good that would be
so funny uh that would get me to pledge on patreon.com slash zegars underscore lab well uh i'll i'll
tell them to put one i don't know but yes make tell them to read homestuck tell them to read the
whole thing make them do it actually the only thing i know about only you the only thing i know
about homestuck is when i met a homestuck cosplayer in 2012 oh well that's not special there's a million
of those yeah especially especially back then uh which which good old days which which character
is this let me send it is that uh that is that's feffery yes feffery feffery no no it's minna
it's minna how can you tell because it's the short hair and she's got the stuff oh no i think you're
right it is minna wow yeah yeah everybody yeah everybody's favorite character minna from a homestuck
oh my god she's all right yeah i don't know anything about her she's like she's like a like a like a
rare like shining beacon of something in axis yeah i guess i mean to me she she's mostly just
emblematic of like briska's like dumb x6 nonsense i didn't i didn't like the briska minna thing i
thought it was annoying uh yeah in the late stuff no oh god and then like the tooth like minna is
involved with with carcats arc in x6 and and um and briska and they're both bad they both have
no no i hate minna i hate minna all there but their fish puns are kind of cute that's all i
think about it there was already another troll that did that and she was bad too and minna's just
worse why i got oh i'm mad i got you guys i got you guys on a tangent no yeah yeah well we're
second picture has as terezi and gamsy in it wait are you are wait who are you are you in these
pictures yeah i'm the one on the left in the first picture and the one on the right in the second
picture you're the white guy yeah nice okay cool uh gamsy's good terezi is good yeah terezi's
gamsy's better than terezi until x6 x6 doesn't count x is in canon uh one one thing one thing
one thing i found annoying is trying to read their dialogue oh yeah oh it's so hard at first
like oh my god i can't imagine reading this but then there's she uses wait she you wait she uses
threes for ease and and fours for a's and ones for eyes i don't i i can't oh it's so confusing
like i can't figure it out what is it what does it mean some of them are more confusing than
how do you read that i know i know you're being sarcastic but yeah you're a fucking dope you're
a fucking dope in a fool and i hate you yeah no that's that's that's a that's a complaint that
some people have and i i don't get it i i never found it hard i can i can i mean there are a few
characters that have really obnoxious typing quirks but like they're all like minor characters
that you just don't have a lot of dialogue yeah i get i get the ones i can i can read it it's just
annoying you probably didn't get to the one character whose dialogue is all in white so you
literally have to like highlight the text in the thing or you literally can't read it oh that that
sounds cool it is cool unironically it is it's awesome homestuck rules i did i did like that
yeah you know i think it's changed to a very very very light gray
remember uh there was actually uh tales control did a homestuck ex esk thing
in the early days there was a page that was no it didn't yeah there was a page that was actually
animated that oh oh that's not anything oh i watched the new oh did you see uh the new uh
episode of that time i was reincarnated as a slime it was very homestuck esk the way that it was
animated yeah the way that the images moved yeah exactly you've got you've you've struck a nerve
my friend you've made me testy you've made me testy yeah exactly with your bad homestuck takes
i'm sorry i'm not a homestuck uh expert i'm very defensive i'm very defensive about my faves
homestuck is my fate is my my fave i'll how long do you think it would i'll fight anyone
how long does it take to read yeah um 20 minutes probably more maybe two weeks
mm two two weeks if you really like buckle down and read it like a lot it's very long uh i'm very
it really it gave me the Stockholm syndrome because i had to come to devote so much time
to reading it that once i was done i was like well i better have liked it or else i just wasted
all that time yeah that that's the trick yeah that's how i feel about tales gets trolled as well
it's the fuck what is i mean tales gets trolled is not as long
if you could probably read tales gets trolled in a couple days yeah at the most yeah um it's
it's the sunk time fouls yes yes the sunk cost effect yeah 100 percent it's true it's true like
if you finish reading anything the longer it is like the more i mean there's like
there's like a there's like a funnel effect where like if you don't like something that much
you just won't like the longer it is the less likely do you are to finish it but also there's
the like if you do like it that much to spend that much time reading it then by the end you're
going to like it even more because of the sunk cost effect you're like you've invested now you're
emotionally invested yeah it's true it's true it's true for anything homestuck is just particularly
long so it's especially true um anyway the the next voicemail is called tarp we already listened
to an indecent proposal right i think so the the the jenny nickelson brony video i mean
it's not it's not really similar to a lecture i mean it it's similar in that it's a person talking
about a casual of like um i guess i like going going through the history of my little pony and
jenny nickelson's video is about the brony fandom in general yeah trixie's lecture was i mean it was
a little bit about that but it was more about it focused more on like the things she was specifically
involved in which you know including like the pcp and the horseshoe crew and also like being a an
editor for uh you know being the daily yeah the equestria daily like content editor oh yeah her
position and stuff like her name used to be ditchy brony right yes okay back in the day
yeah um she was digi brony mlp in fact her channel is still that's still her url i think
yeah are you are you gonna are you gonna hate me for saying that i've never watched my little pony
as well that's way no that's fine that doesn't that doesn't bother me okay i'm way less defensive
in my mlp than about homestuck my little pony is just like a you need to to have been there at the
time and it's still an okay show but like it's not like a as it's as big as brony dum was i wouldn't
i wouldn't like overblows the like the goodness of the show i wouldn't i wouldn't recommend that
anyone like go back and watch mlp now no i don't i i have no interest whatsoever but i was there
because you couldn't really escape it back then but yeah i didn't sure yeah i wasn't uh yeah but
the next the next voicemail is called tarbuck transom finance god oh god it's a minute long
three two one go fast talking crashmen and indestructible super god tarbuck transom here
and i've been catching up on every pcp episode since january while i work on overdue furniture
commissions instead of the digi archive that i'm in charge of and through all of those episodes
one issue has burned brightest in my very keen mind the federal reserve does print money but that
is not where most of the money actually comes from you fools it comes from double account banking
uh which doubles the lent money supply by trading the debt as currency every time that it gets lent
out but unlike anti-matter it doesn't annihilate when money is repaid and it also comes from
fractional reserve banking depositing money and then loaning out a multiple of that amount
such as 10 times because money is just numbers in a spreadsheet the fed technically controls
the money supply because they set the multiplier bonus for fractional reserve banking but printing
bills only accounts for 10 percent of the money generated every year and that's about to get a
whole lot worse because in the middle of trump's administration they pass a loss to set the fraction
to zero if you aren't clocking this it means that the banks can now print infinite nominee
with no consequences ah that's stupid i gotta admit i like i'm sure this is in response to
something that we said about money that was dumb when we were talking about it at some point in
the past but i'm like totally not in the headspace to think about fractional reserve banking i don't
i don't have anything to say about this at fractional reverse banking where they give me money
that's like yes please that's like a really good idea i heard about reverse internships
where instead of working there for free you actually pay them to work there
i saw a post i saw i don't believe it i don't believe that that's a widespread thing but i
didn't see one listing i thought it was a i thought it was a joke like people were making fun i i saw
a post that claimed to be a real listing of like you pay us to work here but i don't know how much
i i actually isn't that like school but like with work attached no yeah like for the for the
owner it's basically slavery well so is capitalism so is capital yeah exactly when you get right down
crack capitalism more like what no it's not like that at all it's it's totally wrong that's totally
an act if you made a fool of yourself next voicemail is called uh taru buku turan somu
three two one go the arches fast talking craftsman and left is jordan peterson the one and only
tarot transom coming to you from what was supposed to be my dining room but is now my workshop
positively buried in sawdust and rethinking my life i just had a pretty bad day making things
for reasons not exclusive to the quarter inch splinter that i just pulled from underneath my
fingernail and it was made all the harder because as i have said for thousands of years
furniture is a scam you should just make it yourself it is so much cheaper and i find myself
part of that industry taking advantage of people who don't know any better than to pay me to do
something so fucking easy and i wonder if this is how i really want to support myself or if it was
better off as just a hobby and something that i did to me needs a mind so they came up i'm a long
time proponent of the ben saint lifestyle of just accept a lower standard of living so that you can
do whatever it is that you want does anyone who can hear the sound of my very fuckable voice want
to share a time when something prompted them to take a step back and reconsider their relationship
to their art or craft um what uh that's a lot that was a lot um did were they saying like building
furniture is easy he's he said building furniture is easy and he doesn't understand why everyone
doesn't just make their own for i mean i for me to make i mean i would have to go out and buy a
bunch of like lumber and power tools in order to craft my own chairs to sit on so i'll just buy a
chair i feel like you like you if you have a hobby that requires you need a bunch of tools
then you don't have to put money into getting the tools that you already have i'm happy i'm happy
that you're able to make a profit crafting furniture like good for you that's that's a win-win for
everybody other people get furniture they don't have to make it themselves that's that's that's
ethical uh mercantilism right there that's a human corporation people doing things and division of labor
division of labor yes i would much rather spend the time not doing that and doing something else
yeah was there a time that made me step back and reconsider my relationship with my art um
every fucking day because i hate art and it sucks and it's a waste of time
what does it mean to have a relationship with art do you mean does it mean like a skill
specifically or just like the act of creating i think it could mean a lot of things uh i think
i don't know like you draw what's your relationship with drawing did it ever change probably i
i don't know i like it sometimes it's hard yeah true true um i don't know i feel like
too stupid to answer such a question bedhead bernie made a really good tweet yesterday and
i retweeted it and it went on to get out like a couple hundred likes and i thought it was really
good it was um i'll read it it was uh scroll scroll scroll guy who chose to make their hobby a job
this is worse than manual labor and i and i read that and i said so true king so true this really
annoys me like when people like when youtubers talk about like oh how much work they put into their
their stuff it's like yeah well that's fine and i guess i if i like your stuff i appreciate it
but i don't feel bad for you and i never will because at the end of the day you could have just
worked at target like anyone else you could just dig in holes you could have just had a regular job
like like most people do and you chose this every every youtuber chose this right yeah it's it's
funny because it's like every person who has a job that is like stressful sometimes they would like
to go to a huge audience and get sympathy but only the youtubers get it only the big social media
people are allowed the the audience to cry for them that's true it's like yeah yeah yeah
every everybody everyone hates their job sometimes but you know if you it's you only hear about it
if you have the kind of job where you have an audience and like any any any creative job or
anything that you do that's just based on like people giving you money because they like your
stuff i don't know like any any kind of like donation based or like patron based or like sales
based like selling your own original content it's like if you're making a living doing that stuff
you did you did it you know you you chose you chose to do this and it worked out for you
and the worst that can happen is that it stops working out for you and you just have to go get
a regular job like everybody else right so like it's really i very rarely feel sympathy
for anyone but especially but especially content creators uh somebody in my discord
i said i really like shawn i really like the youtuber shawn and someone said oh
shawn made fun of linsey ellis shawn made fun of linsey ellis when she
left twitter of her own volition okay i don't fucking care i don't fucking care i don't feel
bad for that for that to matter i would have to feel bad for linsey ellis and i'll never feel
bad for linsey ellis she makes so much money she's so famous i don't give a fuck that anyone made
fun of her for any reason even even if it wasn't valid and probably if shawn made fun of her it
probably was valid um so like good yeah i don't know i kind of i kind of like fuck content creators
is what i'm saying they're all there's not a not a good one not a good one among them among the bunch
the uh we're all criminals the movie bob linsey ellis thing was so like cringe embarrassed thing uh
i don't think anyone i don't think anyone looked good in that situation yeah i don't know everyone
everyone i've created some times all that stuff is just sort of like i feel like i i was standing
in the doorway and i saw something i shouldn't have yes and i'm just sort of leave yeah yeah
yeah like the quen the quentin thing yeah the quentin thing is like uh okay yeah yeah this
is uncomfortable but what else can i even say about it it's just like oh that's an awkward
interaction that occurred yeah oh well anyway we got to be here all day i keep going off on these
tangents i'm sorry i'm wasting everyone's precious time the next voicemail you've got we've got a few
to get through the next voicemail is called uh it's janez janez three two one go ben you talked about
depth the first five thousand years by david graber a few times on the pcp really good so i was wondering
well how do you remember such important information from a book where nowadays
you hardly read but except on twitter i just really liked the parts about the lele tribe i just
thought that was so interesting i don't know just some some i i couldn't tell you the whole book
just certain parts of it were really really interesting and because i found them interesting
i thought about them a lot and so they stuck in my memory there are boring parts too that i
don't remember at all uh that's it that's my whole answer okay next one is called i don't
i don't understand transgender i think this should be good uh wait no this is sorry no
actually this one is called this one is called maki's back sorry i post the mount of order
this is maki's back three two one go hey it's me maki's back uh you might remember me like four
years ago i did a cool skateboard grind and a voicemail and you guys liked it um if you know
that's cool but uh i haven't i kind of stopped listening like 2018 thought i'd pop back over
if you ask us to update you on what the fuck happened i'll kill you are you idiot i can't say
i'm not surprised i just like your grind was not cool like huge lore events have happened that i
should know about listen to the podcast this is a lot listen to the last 280 episodes and then you'll
know listen to the last 280 episodes then you know you rube you fool what do you think we make content
for if you can just make a voicemail be like oh just tell me what happened no shortcuts no spoilers
you gotta put the work in you gotta earn it you gotta pull we gotta pull a home you gotta put in
all that time and emotional investment and get sunk cost fallacy on our asses do you think do you
think it would take longer to read homestucker watch 250 episodes of the pcp oh 280 probably the
pcp although you can speed it up on youtube you times to it let's see okay if we assume that
that the the pcp episodes are on average two hours each which is maybe a little conservative
but whatever then it would be about 540 hours and i think let's see i read i originally read
homestuck in a in about a week or no i mean it was nine days and i read for about eight hours a day
sounds like a job but now it's but it's longer now it's probably at least twice as long as it was
yeah i think you would take longer to listen to all the pcp actually i think reading homestuck
would probably only take maybe 200 hours tops to read all of maybe but i think listening to all
the pcp would be like closer to 300 maybe you should make a pcp lecture about the pcp about
what happened you're not suggested that you're not the first person to suggest it i don't think
it's a crazy idea i don't think it's a crazy idea at all um but we'd have to get a whole
audience of like non-pcp people that don't know what it is i'll join yeah because i i don't
i don't really know either yeah all the guests all the guests that like don't even know who we are
like we get to aria de mezzo and uh and uh and uh jim storm dancer and people that don't even like
know what this show is that just we're on at one time and just get make them sit down and be like
ran until you the whole history of our podcast well i'd be interested yeah it'd be funny yeah
i think it'd be funny okay the next the next voicemail is called i don't understand transgender
i think this should be good three two one go hi uh let me preface this by saying i don't want to
offend anyone i just don't know any better what get a different answer depending on who i ask
so yeah um why would you need to be a certain gender or sex in the first place that's something
i don't really get because i feel like your actions and desires is what should shape your
identity and others perception thereof yeah so like the concept of man and woman it's a bit like
it's simplifying your identity instead of asking what you'd want to be in the first place
so yeah um feel free to discuss i'm sorry this wasn't and i'm hoping this wasn't offensive
anything i i thanks i sort i sort of agree i sort of agree well in the sense that like okay
it's really different takes on the up my i don't i don't really think that being a man or a woman
means much of anything so i guess in that sense i agree but then like the caveat from that is that
okay because it i don't think it means much there's like there's no there's no grounds for me to say
that like someone else is or isn't and so if someone else says i am this i can't say no you're
not because like yeah what does it mean to not be that nothing like it's it's it's it's difficult to
explain because um it sounds logical to say it like that but i feel like
when i realized i was trans it was it was like things that have i've felt about um you know
myself and what i am what i perceive myself as and what society perceives you know my gender
to be like um it it affected me in ways that i wasn't aware of until i learned about
what being trans was so like it feel it means nothing for like cis people because they feel
okay but for trans people there's just this element of not feeling okay all the time it means
it means basically nothing to me so yeah but that's just me yeah and once i realized that the
it's like you know i was questioning i was like could this be could this be part of what i'm what
happened you know it's part of my feelings i i looked and then i tried some stuff out i changed
you know my pronouns i said call me she her and i i you know doing all this stuff and i realized that
i had been like blanket level depressed about that my entire life and acting a different way
and doing certain different things in you know in the framework of like what society
accepts and and thinks of as female because that's the only framework i have and you know
as it's a you know gender is a social construct men have uh short hair women have long hair you
know it's all made up it's all arbitrary but the things that were assigned to be like this is a male
or a male gender thing to do i didn't like all of them and i wanted to do all of the other ones
and i just didn't feel like i could i was like it wasn't i didn't feel like it was acceptable
to just do all of those so it's it's really just it's really just realizing that it's okay to try
all of those things and just to do all of those things that make you happy um would you say
but you i mean i would say uh i don't mean to disagree but i mean i would i would say that
like if you wanted to do all of those girl things you could do all the girl things but
still call yourself a guy if you want it but if i wanted you or you could do none of the girl
things and call yourself a girl and that would be fine too because i mean the part of it part of
my take on it is literally it's literally just about what you call yourself like that's the
question it's the thing about pronouns what your gender is it's literally just a question of what
do you want to be called yeah and like it it's basically like a con there's like no content
a little bit of that there's no descriptive con i don't know i don't i don't see it as being very
descriptive it's it's um it's based on what society is and the one you grew up in if you know
we grew up in a society where all of the things that made me feel comfortable um were things
that i was expected to do already then i don't know whether i would transition exactly i don't
know whether i'd want something different but i can't know because that's like a hypothetical
alternate reality so it's difficult to like explain it in a way that is perfectly understandable
and i'm not like a psycho analyst person i mean i've just i've just like watched youtube videos
that have tried to explain it better than i could i mean if it's at the end of the day
it's literally just about like how do you feel and what do you want what do you prefer yeah so
it's basically it's it's it's the way i like to think about it it's just like transitioning is not
like um anything in particular it is just changing yeah it is transitioning from something you didn't
like and if and if it just so happens that um being perceived as male and and that like societal
pressure to be masculine is something i really didn't like and i wanted to move away from then
that's the the the decisions i make affect that um you know it's just i just want to feel okay i
just want to feel better and it did work it like as soon as i was doing those things that you know
i it was really confusing for a while like i tried the pronoun stuff out for joke no well it
was i guess it was a joke as a prank bro it was just a joke to myself that's the way i uh justified
it like who who would just do that lol um but like it actually made me feel a lot better and it was
really weird and i couldn't wrap my head around why and uh yeah it's hard to explain seems seems
seems pretty wacky to me but like that's cool yeah it's it's it's based entirely on my own
perception of what society uh is so if like if i have wacky ideas of of like um well yeah it's
it's it's kind of in my head and that's but the yeah i don't know that's fine yeah sounds sounds
sounds rational to me makes makes sense uh fuck what number what number were we on uh
uh cc are you gonna are you gonna get pinkpilled you've you've been on the show now and about in
about half of the people that that um associate with the pcp become trans so i would talk to
your i would quarantine yourself for at least two weeks afterwards and talk to your doctor if you
feel any sensations i think i think you can't explain i think it's too late for me oh yeah
yeah i'm too old you toast yeah you're too old i knew a too old i knew a woman i knew a
a trans woman when i worked at astro camp in the town near the camp there was a bar
that i went to like once or twice and the bartender there was this woman who was trans and who had
i don't know who told i think one of my other like counselors knew this person and like told
me about her and she had been like 50 she had been like like 40 plus and married and then was like
you know what i'm a woman i'm gonna leave i'm gonna go become a bartender on some mountain town
population of like 200 uh and become a bartender in this little bar and serve weird kids who teach
at the space camp up up the hill sounds pretty cool and you know what and you know what she passed
pretty good so you know that's that was neat one of one of the things that pops into my head or popped
into my head a lot was like i know but i'd be ugly if i was a girl that was that's a dumb idea i
shouldn't even try yeah that's that's that's that's that's that's how i feel too yeah it's is it but
is that how you feel if i if i was a girl i would be ugly yes okay it's it's i don't know whether
it's like a classic case of like um dysphoria or not um i wouldn't i wouldn't judge me uh but i
definitely felt that before and i've come to the realization that yeah i'm never gonna be like
as attractive as if i had been born a woman um but it's not really about being attractive
necessarily society does say women are valuable based on how attractive they are and as they age
they become less valuable and they should be uh shunned and true and it's like it's like i don't
no old bitties allowed and that's like that's you know whatever but like christmas christmas
cakes no christmas cakes please when i think of like the the the like alternative of like living
life as a man i was like you know what anything is preferable to that i just i mean like like
being like an ugly old woman that's cool i would i'd rather be that than an ugly old man
i mean nobody or a slightly more attractive old man you know nobody's as hot as they want to be
right no matter gender aside uh you know i uh i i wish i was i wish i was a sexier man
unfortunately that's just never that's never gonna happen it's this never you know what it's
okay at the peak i'm already at the peak i'm so fucking strong and i'm so fucking fat
and that peak male performance yeah you might not like it but this is what peak male performance
looks like yes oh my bench is up my bench is good my bench is like um 145 no i benched 140
yesterday grams grant yes no pounds no pounds like currency no that's quite expensive not not
silver not pound not sterling uh a regular pounds i'm a good old american pounds um my my bench is
bad my bench has always been my worst lift but it's going up and i feel good about that and uh
uh i like being powerful okay next voicemail let me just get it loaded up in here it is
electro dome three two one go
someone just recorded themselves playing mario part i was gonna say
yeah i feel like i'm there yeah it's it's like i'm there yeah it's like i'm watching a it's like
i'm watching a summoning salt world record progression about mario kart yeah oh wow pog
next voicemail here we go it is called ps a for those that haven't heard
sad face uh updates in coming three two one go welcome to grand central station
now time for public service announcement by concerned citizen oh dear
whether in real life or even online please beware of crocodiles these nosy slimy evil reptiles
are extremely versatile they're stalking the forums and the lakesides too crocodiles waiting
to jump at you if you feel the opposite they'll steal your information and publish it so when
you see a crocodile please stay back that's what's in style call the army to put them on trial and
hope he's gone for a long long while i mean the intro was a little different the intro sounded
different i know i like it i like the concept of of crocodiles that's like docks you they chomp
you and then they docks you yeah yeah it's funny i don't know i said last week that they all kind
of sound the same this one kind of sounds the same yeah it's a new it's a new poem kind of
sounds similar i don't know i don't know i spoiled on these ben you think i'm getting spoiled on these
you think so they're they're crazy maybe so they're crazy but we've heard like we've heard like a hundred
of them that's not true i don't know maybe i'm spoiled maybe i'm spoiled uh uh uh i know i know
the person that makes them and she's a lovely she's a lovely individual
i'm hmm hmm uh uh just jester uh amuse me oh no not no this this oh i've seen i've
heard this before something novel oh cover me in cover me in raspberry pudding
um
yep yep uh next next voicemail is called you have a voicemail archive it came free with your
i know i said this last week i found that i have an archive okay three two one go
if you're curious of how people are getting a hold of raw voicemails for the fucking shitty
wrapping all over it um metal pig edits you literally have a voicemail archive it is just
your soundcloud i i understand that it's like been over a year since it was updated because
i don't think anybody's been fucking with it since mate left but it's literally just right there
god damn why do we have a why do we have that oh oh it's because the way nate
did it was he wanted to play it through rhythm and rhythm can't it can't do it through speak pipe
so it has to do it through youtube or soundcloud so he would take the he would listen to the
voicemails download them upload them to soundcloud and then play them through rhythm but
what i yeah you're you're right i forgot he used to do it like that but i don't do it like that
okay well mystery solved next voicemail is called a quick question three two one go what is one
youtube ad that you keep seeing over and over again that you just despise good i have turned off
and i haven't and i haven't seen one in a while yeah same i only i only get uh ads on my phone in
my work computer i mean i see the i see here the like like the the paid sponsored like plugs in videos
for stuff that's like i don't know what what do i rate rate rate shadow legends
i feel like that's kind of old at this point i haven't heard that one in a what's what's the
one there's there's uh it's radon earbud fucks it's yeah the earbud space and then there's um
skill share there's another one skill share is the one that i always i don't like discussing brands
they're winning by me saying those names yeah even even it's like oh i hate these ads i see them
everywhere it's like well that's their thing that's that's one thing i feel bad like i can't say the
same for all all boomers but at least my parents they keep watching tv they keep watching tv and
it's like you know tv is like 90 percent commercials i mean i i i mean i watch a lot of youtube and
youtube is full of ads too so i i can't like i can't judge anyone for watching tv yeah but at
least you have ad blocker i mean i guess i mean i i try my best um i mean i don't watch shows i mean
it's not just boomers like i have i have friends that watch like well it means they watch like
streaming services and stuff now not like broadcast television or cable or whatever yeah i was that's
not for me i was talking about broadcast fair fair uh i just i don't know uh yeah skill share skill
share is the one that pisses me off because it's the one that i hear the most often next voicemail
is called uh tim rogers translated moon remix rpg no voicemail okay three two one go
all right is that zero seconds there's no voicemail it's just there is no there is no voicemail
it's just tim rogers translated moon remix rpg i don't know what this means were you talking about it
on the stream i was i was talking about i've talked about tim rogers the last couple episodes
i don't know what the moon remix it's uh it's a it's a it was a game for the playstation one
that only came out in japan and they recently released a switch version in english it's called
moon remix moon remix rpg uh oh or just or i've never heard of it or just moon for short
it's one of the game but i guess it's one of the games that inspired undertale
i'm fine okay i've never heard of it but i guess tim rogers translated it and good for him
uh next voicemail is called uh let me find it it is called ben saint question mark three two one go
ben saint yes more like
worst guy ever thanks for the voicemail buddy next next voicemail is called uh minor
cycloneal spoilers that's okay well we already we already me and cheezy talked a little bit about
cycloneals last episode so i don't know skip ahead a little bit if you don't want to hear spoilers
three two one go lim saint you're so wrong about cycloneals the origin of the story is not the
ideology bet is that trying to create a socialist world through unsocialist means always results
in authoritarianism and a provision of socialism um i don't know how seriously to take this when it's
a delivered as a donald trump voice coder i don't think that's the point of cycloneals i really don't
i don't know what that is so i'm good with spoilers how do you how do you make socialism
without like stopping what's happening already last socially get socialism how do you non-violently
get it last week give me and cheezy talked about it and we both agree that it's a little disappointing
how like the the oh god the jubilite movement is like nominally like a socialist revolution
but this story is not really about that at all and it kind of doesn't really have any bearing on the
actual story it's just like an aesthetic thing in the end it's just like any other like revolution
that has kind of its own sort of hierarchy associate and we both found that pretty disappointing
the manifesto itself is not available to read we just hear about it being socialist yeah but in
in practice all it really is is just like a militant uprising like its politics are sort of
irrelevant it's kind of kind of no it's kind of a bummer um this is this is why i was like
the other day i was reinvigorated to to do my re-listen and so we could do a cycloneals cast
which i will do soon i swear uh sooner every day i don't know do you have any thoughts about that
uh no i i i kind of want to replay re-read that as well cc cycloneals by the way is a
is a newer thing that the homestuck guy made oh it is a visual it is a visual novel it's not
it's not a homestuck related okay except for a couple little Easter eggs yeah it's a new thing
is it like being constantly released or is it like finished
no it's finished it was released it was released episodically but it's it's finished now it's
fully out okay i think it was 10 chapters yeah um next voicemail is called message to
eleazar there it is three two one go please make ben sound like a chipmunk for the next
two voicemails and this one thank you eleazar you better not you better not do that if you
do that i'm gonna be real mad and you're gonna hear it from me that's the editor right you
that's the editor okay that's the editor who i'm sure has enough respect and professionalism
not to not to not to obey the whims of some some random voicemailer uh i am your i am your god
eleazar you must obey me i guess we'll see i come i i command you i command you uh uh normal voice
please okay next one is called do you not like the beach there it is not like what oh beach okay
beach the beach yeah uh like princess beach yes three two one go wait ben i'm gonna read villain
verse i didn't understand what he said i think he said i'm gonna read villain verse which is fine
and cool i'm sure cheesy will be happy villain versus pretty good uh cheesy really cheesy really
puts the work in he really grinds it really cranks it out it's a fun it's a fun read you
should read it i endorse it what do i read it do i gotta have it do i gotta get it uh
i think shit yeah i i think so i think you have to buy the book i don't think you can
oh fuck am i stupid i i think you can't it's not posted online actually that reminds me i gotta
actually buy the third book because i didn't actually do it yet but i will um buy jesus
comic read villain verse it's good next voicemail is called there it is it is called you can wear
diapers at the beach no three two three two one go also i thought it was super funny that nobody
did take noises last week oh god i hope nobody does it just scare you this week i thought it was
coming i really thought i really thought he was coming it's it's it's the perfect horror um skill
is is to build tension and just not not deliver yeah it's the scariest thing ever this i don't know
if he intended to do that but he did it he he had me he had me on edge there and he didn't have to do
anything uh next voicemail and now i'm gonna be on edge for all the rest of the voicemails of which
there are only like eight no there's like 10 left i think so the next one is called uh hoomst
will screen the voicemails there it is three two one go we all know Nate he's a money hungry
lib fucking and cap a reddit so um if you want the voicemail screened just pay him to do it from
the episode like like how he gets a cut for the the uh accounting bullshit or whatever just pet
just pay him and he'll do it i'm sure i'm sure he will right yeah of course he would but i don't
want him to do that he used to screen the voicemails and the result was that he would pick like three
and it was dumb he would pick bad ones that weren't funny no i don't want them screened
you fool you absolute rude um thanks for the voicemail next one is called
uh the pcp bad comment award show episode 266 oh this is this sounds funny three two one go
ladies and gentlemen boys and girls those with terminal daddy issues welcome to the pcp bad comment
award show yeah there's a word for the worst comment on episode 266 goes to
axel stars and now we present a dramatic reading well that's just starting to get a burnt
shard that's all folks for the next week same pcb time same pcb channel
it but where's the lie huh um that's that's no i mean i mean yeah that's why it's such a
bad comment because obviously obviously this is just this is just sad at this point like you
don't have to tell us why do you where we're doing it's a bit this is just a bit like the last like
hundred and fifty episodes of the pcb have just been a bit uh it's all it's all a build up to a
punchline that may or may not ever come uh and if you can't see that then i honestly don't know
what to tell you i honestly i don't think you know you then you just don't get it you just don't get
it bro you just you just you just know we're just not on the same wavelength uh next voicemail is called
a glimpse wait it's called a glimpse into the future signs and saints three two one go the year is 20
xx weeks after the fire of megatucid ben now ascended would make his divinity known
first ben appeared to gib offering her a great boon as a show of his power gib was enjoying life
at this point Clarissa was now a series she could now afford to have not one but two hot plates in
her apartment but something was still missing ben's boon for gib was the gift of a pair of the biggest
boobies the most voluptuous mommy melcos you're welcome to tom ben also thank you already immortal
tom had little to gain from ben that is except the gift of healing tom could finally walk again
ben in becoming a god gave up his sainthood but upon tom and gib he bestowed to each a new sainthood
ben remembered also his trusted allies that is all the contributors to patreon.com slash ben saint
they too receive miracles and boos just like in real life this is the future before you
even now the hands of fate move ever closer to this eventuality this the relief based future
uh uh you know i like the idea that your patreon has like a tear or is it you literally get a
miracle bestowed upon you miracles and i mean already you get to put a fucking enemy into my
video game so like what greater boon could there even be true it's true i it's it's with it's
entirely with with no bias at all that i say that i like this story about how i become a god
and obtain ultimate power and then rule the world uh and crush my enemies and and imboon
in my my allies it's it's it's pretty good it's it's it's it's it's a it's a good read yeah
next one is called uh wait oh uh pcp bad comment award show number 266 justification
i don't know if it needs any justification i was already on board but okay three two one go
i'm gonna make this segment just to sort of like justify which comment i choose because um i get it
because i don't know it might be necessary sometimes i'll just go ahead and do it for
each of them so you can skip these voicemails if the if it's obvious but uh so the reason
i chose this one is because you know over the the recent pcp something very good and happy
has been happening which is that uh gib has been you know transitioning and based on her twitter
it seems to be going really well so you know i don't think the pcp is particularly sad right now
like ben seems not in a particularly good mood but he never has been so that doesn't really matter
gib is happy ben is the same as always so therefore it's a happy show now
fuck you honestly i think that's a bad justification because i mean it's what what he meant is not oh
the tone of the show is sad oh it's not that like oh this is it's it's that he thinks that like oh
fewer people means that it's like desolate oh it's it's pathetic it's a shadow of its former self
so honestly this justification has made me think less of the initial appraisal so
you really shot yourself in the foot on that one sir
next voicemail is called mensa is for dweebs uh here we go yep there it is three two one go
if you go to mensa meetings and you don't have a phd you are a fucking dweeb like yeah they do
fucking research sometimes or something i think i don't fucking know they sent me a bunch of dumb
newsletters that i don't care about but leading into i joined mensa once just to fucking take the
test and prove that i could so that i could put it on a resume and be like hey look at this guys
i proved it by taking a fucking test that i'm a smart boy but no i never fucking did mensa
shit because it's all dumb they sent me all these fucking newsletters and they all look so fucking
boring i'd rather just play video games i don't know fuck you exactly what they do i'm using your
name for clout and i'm not giving you anything anymore fuck you i don't know exactly what they do
they're the high iq society i gotta imagine that it's just a thing you do to fucking jerk yourself
off about how smart you are yeah i get that impression too oh my god look at these oh my god
look at these millennials look at these hip young millennials slash older zoomers who are
having just a great time being mensa members this this could be you if only your iq were high enough
was that Thanksgiving dinner what are they doing they're just having a just having a fucking ball
they're just having a fucking ball uh that's the iq dinner okay let's see uh reasons to join
mensa um how can i join mensa why should i join what are the benefits of membership um
would you want to smile and clap your hands at dinner it is an honor to be a member of
oh my god oh my god this is great i'm gonna read this i'm gonna fucking read this this is
fucking awesome okay from the mensa.org website here's what some members say about being part of
the mensa community i will screenshot i will screenshot this this is good it is an honor
to be a member of mensa from the very first moment my eyes have been sparkling finally
i arrived in a place where people share similar thoughts say similar puns have similar associations
like i have naturally i also see the differences different characters at two dudes it's misspelled
attitudes and views some of these some of these i embrace others i reject but this makes the world
complete we cannot be different in the same way okay okay george george 44 that's pretty good i can
see how he got in because he said use the word naturally you're only smart people is 44 his age
or his iq okay uh let's hear another originally i just wanted to have my iq tested i guess i was
looking for some external reinforcement i thought i would never have the time to attend programs
as i had two young children out of curiosity i finally joined mensa and i have been a member for
14 years now i found a great community interesting activities lots of love and eventually a husband
as well okay that one's not as embarrassing well why did you read it before you knew it was funny
well the i saw the first one was funny i assume the second would be funny okay that one's fine
attitudes attitude that first one is so like is so like enlightened by its intelligence
that's so like wait a minute it's just missing like an indeed this reminds me um
you maybe you don't remember but i was on i guessed it on a podcast called shreddit and
on the episode of shreddit that i was in we were going over posts by people on the r slash
cheating uh subreddit which is like people who are like cheating on their spouses and it's like
it's like their hobby they're like into it as a thing they post about like how good they are at
cheating how exciting cheating is how fulfilled they are now that they're cheating what they
didn't used to be and like they're like i'm so grateful to have found a community of people
that understand you know what why cheating is so great and you know most people don't get it but
like we here on the r slash cheating subreddit we understand each other you know we have different
we have the same attitudes towards the whole thing and this that's the vibe that i get from this
from george honestly i think he sounds exactly like one of those guys who telling a story about
like i got a call from my mistress who understood i made a pun about i my wife called me and said honey
don't forget to pick up the eggplant and i said uh eggplant like my dick and she didn't laugh at
my dick joke but then my mistress called i called my mistress and said uh my wife didn't get my dick
joke and she laughed at it and that's why i know that cheating is great and i'm so grateful for this
community i don't know the cheating community the cheating um um whatever anyway whatever this
looks like just a place to jerk your dick off just like every fucking thing on the internet
fuck mensa yeah uh uh lame next voicemail is called um why isn't it wait there there we go
there we go okay next voicemail is called um trixie sexuality studies 401 advanced topics
okay three two one go trixie sexuality is 100 based around filling a role and that's why
she was uh straight before and is also i don't know i don't know i don't know what word to use
she liked women before and likes guys straight so the reason is that before you can listen to all
these dumb solo podcasts trixie did i listen to all of them and love them which i miss now but
whatever that's off track trixie would always say oh i want to be a dad now i want to be the
internet's dad so that's why she was into may is because it was like you know being a paternal
character because i guess it's like a dysphoria coping mechanism or something i don't know but
that if you don't know why you like is that that's the role she wanted to do and that seeped into
everything including romance but now now she's a fucking woman and um i know right friends um what
does a woman do a woman is with a guy according to society so that's what trixie wants to do
to fill in with the role to be the role of the woman who lets other people punch drunk angry
people punch her so that's why it happened maybe i don't know i mean maybe who knows
it's one of those annoying things because it's like transitioning like being a woman doesn't mean
i have now a new set of values that i must i forcibly ascribe myself to like there are things
that i know like i know my voice is still sort of masculine i need to like if i want to appear as
though i were female i would need to work on that and that would be like a conscious choice
to to like change that voice but i don't feel dysphoria about it so like my transition
doesn't need to include that necessarily yeah i feel fine with the voice i have but like if i
wanted to be like quote unquote more feminine i would need to do something about it yeah but you
don't it's not like part of transitioning for everyone it's it's always going to be like the
individual's choice i i do i do i do think it's curious that Trixie liked women before her transition
and i guess likes men afterwards but i say curious with like complete neutrality like i just mean
like huh that's curious that's interesting i mean yeah i mean it's not even that i i don't
know what i think about it because i i i don't know if i'm like hmm there's no like like weird i
guess i don't think there's like a hard and first rule for like a or a term for like changing
the gender preference or sexual preference like um it's it's not really i don't know i don't care
it's not really my place to like speculate on something like that i mean another person i was
a little surprised to find that she has a boyfriend just because she had been so like i mean she
used to when she talked about like i mean she always talked about thinking about girls
whether it was like being one or being interested in them it seemed like that was well it seemed
like she thought about that in both well i mean that's just what she said or that was the impression
i got from what she used to say about it so i was just i was surprised but i mean like deep down
like it had not occurred to her maybe that um being with a man would be fun or good
right i just trying it out and she likes it so like cool at the end of the day i mean i don't
know i don't know what's i don't know what's in her head um yeah who knows yeah next what you
don't have a sexual preference from birth it'll all the change depending on stuff that happens
that's the thing i mean you can does anyone have a sexual preference at birth you can you can always
change your mind you can always develop new preferences like you can i mean if you i don't
know you can like not to say you can genuinely go for you could like theoretically you could like
be gay and then like stop being gay if you decide you don't like man anymore or whatever or you or
the other way or whatever you could be asexual at one point in your life and then later be like
you know what i think i have developed an interest in sex and then you're not anymore and like
that's fine you can have it you can you can have be something and then just like change your you
can develop a new preference if you want that i'm not a cop i can't stop you i can't stop you from
doing that nobody can um it just is what it is man i don't know um next voicemail is what number
are we on we are close to the end finally okay uh this is called uh discord please accept my file
there it is max revive tarantino casts okay three two one go so i know nate doesn't want to be on the
the pcp the actual pro crass tornadoes podcast i don't know but we got this fucking tarantino cast
over here that only ever got two episodes i think everybody liked it and now it's fucking dead
why are you telling me i don't know nate and tom and gib are all still affiliated with the show
in maybe maybe wishing upon a star jesse could be coerced into participating just for this one
fucking thing you know i don't know i don't feel like jesse likes doing youtube i mean he's never
like doing youtube content the prospect of coming back to do a podcast is like i could imagine
inherently disgusting going back going back to that bernie tweet talk about someone who is like
oh i made my i made my hobby into a job and now oh this is worse than manual labor jesse is that
like embodied nobody ever complained about having a cushy youtube job as hard as jesse did
that's my fucking that's my thing i'm sorry if i'm coming off a little rude but that always rude
that's i don't want to feel like i've maybe been a little hard on jesse at times i don't want to
come off like i hate him or anything but boy that was one thing about him that would bug the heck out
of me at times i i suppose so i've i've always felt like it was he was playing it up but i
yeah he did do it all the time so i don't know yeah um uh i don't know thoughts on getting the
tarantino cast back together gib um the tarantino cast we just watched the i mean it's a good excuse
to watch the movies because i haven't watched all of them um i think was it spearheaded by Trixie
and Nate i don't know maybe i think it was was it started at radcon no sure no i think we had an
episode and then we decided to do a live one at radcon for i remember doing the logo before all that
um i like that logo that was a good logo i don't even know what the logo was and i don't
know if i've seen it i've probably i've probably seen it on the channel somewhere
if i just google it maybe it'll come up um no like the cast of the film tarantino cast
now is never gonna come up okay next voicemail so that's so that's probably a no on reviving
the tarantino cast i mean if you wanted to do a tarantino cast so tom like it wouldn't be everyone
but i i wouldn't be uh i wouldn't mind i mean if you're talking about a film if you wanted to
make i'm not i mean i'm not super in i'm not super excited about tarantino a tarantino movie rewatch
i guess i could do it which movie oh which movie we were going through all of them in order of
release and we did pulp fiction last so i don't know which one's next okay brown so that's a big
may that's a big maybe next voicemail is called uh mike oclon three two one go hey ben i hope i
still made it in time for the show um just wanted to say you're no breathing manually
uh fuck you man
fuck shit fuck you uh no i didn't i i i had one manual breath but like i'm already over it
you did i didn't even stumble damn that yeah that never really trips me up as much as i expected
it always gets me the one that really gets me is noticing that i'm blinking and god damn it
oh yeah i'm get yep oh when am i gonna blink when is it gonna happen
that one yeah that one actually got me worse next this is the last voicemail i think is called
mike awk short three two one go got to say you're also blinking man i did it first amazing
amazing we well we've made it to the end of the voicemails and we are now breathing and
blinking manually and it's a nightmare uh what else i don't know anything else to there's nothing
else i'll i just want to reiterate go to the laura ghost kickstarter page watch the video
yes and and be hype for pledging money for a comic that will be shipped to you physically you
there's also a pdf if you're if you don't want i don't know why you would have the pdf but just
in case in case people want that you showed me the video early after you finished making it
and i told you this and it was absolutely true that the song from the video was genuinely like
two days later i was like humming it unconsciously i won't i won't hum it now i won't hum it right now
but it's it really is an airworm where does it come from it's from tim and eric or some
show great job i see i you know i didn't recognize it i'm really now i'm manually
stopping myself from humming it because i'm like i want to but i oh you're mad yeah you're
manually not humming manually not humming i must restrain myself uh cc any any final any closing
thoughts for the podcast um go to www.talesgetstroll.org give money to yes give money to uh
patreon.com slash sci-car's uh underscore lab yep um based based based based buy buy some merch
so i can get money and laser bot yeah uh i uh go ahead anything else well okay what were you gonna
i want to say thank you for coming on uh uh i don't know um if anyone wants to contact you about
the ongoing effort to finish tales gets trolled or the first the first of four acts of tales gets
trolled if that's a real thing yeah whatever uh they can contact you we'll have your info in the
description your your twitter uh yeah the tales gets trolled twitter account and you're obviously
they can contact you through tales gets trolled.org uh oh yeah Tarantino casts it's it's good looking
it's good i'm looking at the logo right now um okay yep get in anyone can get in touch with you uh
that way yes um patreon.com slash the procrastinators do have that right is it the procrastinators
yes okay patreon.com is about how many times have you said it every fucking week for five years um
patreon.com slash the procrastinators for bonus episodes someone sent me a discord message the
other day yelling at me about not understanding uh minesweeper and i told that person you know
you would be interested to see the minesweeper pick cross bonus episode where we all learn a little
something uh along the way uh and that goes for all of you as well uh bonus millions of bonus
episodes literally millions of bonus episodes uh at the top at your fingertips for only five
dollars uh get it get it while it's hot and um i think that's gonna do it oh and also access to the
pcp minecraft server did you oh yes i didn't mention it but it's true yes also that's now
rolled into the five dollars you get the minecraft as well we should do a minecraft this week
yeah it's been like three it's been like two weeks i think yeah we should do one this week
okay um yeah okay that's the episode everyone thanks for listening and thanks zizi for coming on
the show and goodbye goodbye goodbye bye goodbye