Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of the Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I am the best guy ever and I am here today with Hippocrit.
I haven't seen you with a tiny hat in a while, I'm getting disillusioned and also Digibro.
I'm still alive, somehow, despite all that drug and alcohol content.
Our topic for today is the elusive, mysterious concept of a convention, specifically a nerd,
geek, stupid, retard convention for babies who poop in their diapers.
Which you, as I understand, are a huge fan of.
I love more than pooping my own diaper, I love to poop in other people's diapers, and
smear it all over my manhood.
Right, so we're talking about conventions.
So I know that Digi and I and Munchy have been to conventions, Gibb, what's your experience
with conventions?
Well, I've been to three conventions ever, the first one was London Expo, I don't know
what it was called, I think it was just called the London Expo and it's this huge big thing
in London, near the river, and it was just nerd stuff, there was games, there was anime,
it was all sorts of stuff, I got a Phoenix Wright book and some badges for Hitman Reborn
and I don't know, I was going there with friends and it was really my first experience
of seeing cosplayers in real life and it was actually a lot cooler than I thought it would
be.
That was that.
Then there was...
Well, those good cosplayers, yeah.
Yeah, and then the second one was the Bronycon, which is slightly documented on my channel
on Gibb and Tay, and that was the first time I met you guys, in fact all of you in school
is the first time I met you in real life.
And after that is Radcon 1 and 2 and that's it.
Oh, I know those.
That's a conference though, it's not a convention.
That's close enough.
It was certainly a con, I feel ripped off.
Yeah, I got'em.
It's gay.
Well, okay, I don't know about you guys, but I have not been, I mean yes, I went to
Bronycon with you guys, but that was like for a good reason.
When I was young, I used to go to anime conventions very frequently and would cosplay and would
be really excited for them, even though I always had a shitty time, but now I realized
it's kind of like my experience with D&D, when I was young I got really excited for it,
but now I realize that they're terrible and I don't enjoy them at all, but it's possible
that there's new ways for me to experience them, and in the future I'll figure out ways
to make them fun.
And looking forward to that one day, for example, doing a panel and being praised by the public
for my genius and my creative abilities, that would be cool.
I kind of feel like I missed out on the con experience, because the second con I went
to, I was already on a panel, and the first con I went to, I wasn't really doing anything,
I was just walking around overwhelmed by it, but I kind of liked, you know, I saw somebody
in a Luffy, like they cosplayed as when Luffy was wearing wax on his hands and feet.
Yeah, Champion Luffy, I remember that.
Yeah, and I was just like, whoa, this is like things I know and like, and people are making
good costumes, and there's like a fucking metric ton of key blades, I didn't really know
how that was.
Yeah, I kind of wish I was going to cons earlier, because they seemed like fun for a kid, or
a young teenager, and I missed out.
Oh, and which I am, and greatly enjoy.
Allegedly.
I think you're an undercover adult.
I think you're trying, I think what you are, are a plant by the FBI to convict us all of
pedophilia.
That's what I suspect you are.
You're trying to bait us into it, but I'm not going to crack.
In Andrew Hussie's webcomic, whistles the clown, there's a species of plants that only
eat clowns, and that's what I am.
I'm a plant that only eats clowns.
I've been to a few conventions in my day, but which ones did you go to?
I've mostly been to Otacon a bunch of times, and it's sort of similar to Unate.
The first time I ever went to Otacon was in 2008, and it was the greatest experience
of my life.
It was mind-blowing, and life-changing, it was the coolest thing ever, and every single
year since, it has been worse.
Like progressively, it's less and less interesting, less and less fun, and there was one time
that I went to NecoCon, which is a local anime convention, and that was enough.
I went to one local convention, and my conclusion was local conventions aren't worth it.
You go to the big ones.
That's definitely true.
Because there's nothing at a local convention.
It's just an excuse for a bunch of nerds to stand around together.
There are a few functions that are served by a convention.
Mostly my experience is with anime conventions, and to me, they serve as A, a gathering place
for like-minded people.
That one is already horrible, because I've never met a person at a convention I liked.
It's always been terrible.
Yeah, that's fair.
I mean, it is a huge gathering place for autism.
It simply is, and I don't like hanging out with autistic people.
They make me uncomfortable.
More so than autism, just nerds.
I mean, I would say we're all on the spectrum there when it comes to nerds, but it's not
even that most of them are weird.
They're just kind of awkward, or have a different sense of humor.
I feel like the problem that I have with nerds in general of hanging out with them is that
nerds are a class of people who think that having a shared knowledge is the same thing
as having a personality, or a joke is simply stating a reference to a thing, and at conventions,
that's really amplified to the upteeth degree, where you could have a panel going on and
someone makes reference to, and not all shows are good, and then someone in the crowd is
going to go, like, guards is wing, and then people go, I also know what that is, and that
kind of shit, that's the element of conventions that always makes me want to not be there
anymore.
I don't blame people for wanting to share that kind of relationship with each other.
It's just that that, with the absence of a decent person behind it, or just a personality
behind it, that's where it's a problem.
I agree.
I hate conventions.
Don't go.
I think people who are awkward are awkward, and fuck them, but I do appreciate the nerdy
convention area for allowing real human beings like us to convene, because like, BronyCon
was like, I mean, at the time everyone was kind of tired of the pony stuff, but it was
just really cool to just go to a place and generally know people that know you.
I need some huge scare quotes on real people when it comes to us.
I'm real, I think.
That's true.
But really, I wanted to talk about what is the function that a convention serves that
draws people to it, because you've talked about this before, Digi, and how, like, the
only thing that you can get out them.
I think it's precisely because it's mostly nerds, because nerds don't go out and have
friends.
This is their only chance to get together and make their stupid jokes and not be ridiculed
for it.
They just want an internet forum, but in IRL, you know, IRL, internet forum.
But see, okay, you know, that's true, that's true, but all right, it's just a much bigger
deal for everyone, so which is why it keeps getting funded all over the place in different
forms.
Yeah.
And I mean, maybe people have figured this out better than me, all right, but I've got
an axe to grind here, because I kind of had this idea when I was young, and I started
going to conventions.
Me and my brother went to anime Boston every year for, like, eight years, and...
Your brother being Ben St.
Ben St.
That's right.
Not up on the times here.
That's true.
And Connecticut, which is a smaller one, and was less worth our time, but still went occasionally,
and I've been to a few here and there.
The highlight of my entire congoing experience was when I found out that, and this is like
one of the things that cons are useful for, actually, Yoshitaka Amano, illustrator of
Final Fantasy, was at, like, New York, not Comic-Con, but like some New York comic convention,
and me and a friend from my anime club and college found out, and she wanted to go.
I can't remember why.
Um, actually, this was funny.
This was when Gurren Logan had just taken off in a big way, and I had not seen it yet,
so we went to the convention, everything was Gurren Logan, and I had no idea what any of
it was.
It was...
It's funny to think it back to that.
Crazy.
But anyway, I met Amano there and got to shake his hand and have his autograph that I have
to this day, and that was like the best thing Akon has ever provided for me.
But when I was a little kid, what I wanted out of an anime convention was nerd friends,
and I would go there, I got dressed up like fucking Monkey D. Luffy, I sewed my costume
with my mom for weeks, if not months, worked really hard on it, got together, you know,
all my money so I could afford to buy things and have a fun time there, and I went there,
and I stood in halls, and I walked around, and I looked at things, and no friends appeared
to me.
No friends magically sprung up for me, and I will never forgive conventions for hyping
me up for making friends and then not delivering.
I'll never forget the disappointment I had when I was coming home, and I had just spent
a bunch of money on anime bullshit I didn't need or want, and was still a sad child.
That was cruel of you, fucking anime Boston, that was very cruel of you.
How cruel and unusual to present merchandise, and then have the option to buy it.
That is, resist capitalism, baby!
I kind of like that whole like, I mean, not like being sad, I mean like making a costume
and being a bit of a loser faggot idiot, making a costume, wearing a costume.
I kind of want to do that still, like even though I know there's nothing to really be
gained from it.
I kind of want to make like a really terrible home stuff come play of some kind.
Well that's the thing though, it's fun, it's fun in and of itself.
And then to go with friends though, it's totally different.
I never went with friends, I went with my brother who it wasn't cool to hang out with
and my mom.
So, like I was just there hoping things would happen for me, and they didn't.
Nate, we have to understand this, the reason I like cons, because I exclusively go to cons
with friends, and it's always a fucking blast.
Because really like the difference between going to Disneyland by yourself and with friends.
Exactly.
Like there's stuff to do, but it doesn't feel the same.
I'll say that I do think part of what has made cons that are like Otacon weaker for
me year after year, is that like I do go with my friends, but we don't stay together.
We all split up and go do different things, and we don't really hang out during, like
Victor always, my brother Victor, he always goes with his girlfriend Hope, you know,
and so they, like he immediately fucks off to hang out with her the whole time, you know,
even if we, I mean last year he drove up with her, but it used to be he'd come with us,
and she would just happen to also, you know, be going.
But then like, you know, my other friends, we all have kind of different, you know, anime
we're interested in, or different things we want to see, so we all just split up and
we rarely end up encountering each other, and it can be weird, like going around to
this stuff alone, and then just kind of feeling like, is this, like does this mean that much
to me, that I'm like, that I'm willing to, you know, drive four and a half hours and
spend all this money just to like be in this place, so I can sit alone and, you know, and
just see this thing that I've seen some variation of eight times already, you know, no matter
what it is.
Yeah.
To me, it feels really like 2006, in the sense of like, I don't know, like it reminds
me of a time when like full metal alchemist, the first one had come out, and everyone was
getting really excited about and watching things on the fucking adult swim and to Nami,
and like there was an emergence of this culture, but now, I don't know, I feel like it's gotten
a little stale.
I mean, there was a time where-
I'm over it.
Yeah, there was a time where you could go to a convention, and like every con, every
anime convention has like screenings of different shows, and you know, there was a time when
they would be screening something that you legitimately couldn't find, you know, like
you did not know where to buy the DVD or the VHS, you didn't know where to stream it or
download it.
Like you could go to a convention and see something that, that like, you know, just
sitting and watching anime could actually be valuable.
And now it's like, there's no, like when you go to those screenings now, they literally
stream them off Crunchyroll, like it's just them playing Crunchyroll on a screen, you
know.
Just thinking about that is hilarious.
Yeah.
Like, even if you were going with your friends, it's like, I could sit with my friends and
watch this at home, and instead I'm watching it in a giant group, and like, there are times
where that can be fun to see an audience react to something, but then there's the other times
where the audience is laughing at the wrong moments, and it like, I get, I'm a fucking
pretentious elitist faggot when it comes to this shit, but I really can't stand being
in a crowd that seems to be getting something very different out of something than what
I'm getting.
Like-
Dude, I totally agree.
I can't stand consuming media with one other person there in the, in the fear that, like
not even that they do it, but in the fear that they'll get it wrong or not be in sync
with me.
Can't stand, if I'm taking it seriously, can't stand it.
Like it was so great when we all watched Mad Bull together at Radcon too, which is like
nine guys screaming the whole time at Mad Bull, and that's very much like what the convention
experience should be at its height, but could you imagine watching that, like watching Mad
Bull with like different people, and you don't know who they are, and they could be, you
know, like, that's a show that a lot of people say is, quote, awesomely bad, or is like a,
a really terrible show, and like imagine if you're in that crowd, the, you know, this
is a, oh, like the title of the panel is, So Bad It's Good, shitty anime that you should
check out, you know, Mad Bull 34.
I promise that's it, like that has happened, Mad Bull has been in those panels, I've seen
it, you know, so like, yeah, that's, that's how I feel in those crowd situations is like,
on the one hand, I love, like my favorite thing, well, one of my favorite things about
conventions is the, like the feeling of these are my people, you know, these are the people
who are watching anime, who I'm talking to online, this is, this is the crowd who gets
what I'm about on some level, but at the same time, they're totally not my people, because
they're, they're walking around dressed as Kirito, you know, and being like, anime is
great, and I'm like, I'm like, Japanese
Japanese
you guys are completely off base, off color, and this is based totally in the fact that
you guys are losers, if you guys, if you guys weren't losers, then you would realize that
cons are great, I can still imagine myself enjoying a con, definitely, well, I would,
I would never call him a loser, I'm, I'm, I'm talking about the other two numbskull
knuckleheads, of course, of course, exhibit, I'm hoping, I'm hoping this year to fly out
to stay with Munchie for anime X though, yeah, yeah, oh, oh, but believe me, I have like
a whole like, like fucking history of every con I've been to, and the ups and downs of
each con, I heard the crinkling of a piece of paper, you said that, you actually wrote
this down, I actually have, anyway, cons are great, because they offer three things, and
by three things, I mean, I'm thinking of one in my head, and once I'm done with that one,
I'll probably have more ideas in my head. Okay, when you, when you get, when you get
your bros, when you get your beefcakes, when you get your, your manly fucking men that
you surround yourself with on a daily basis, you know, the fucking, the, your people, your
stash, your handboys, your handboys, your handboys, when you get them all in the car,
and you go up to some like shitty, like anime, like, like, you all hate anime, not you, but
as in like, like, you and your friends all hate anime, and you go up to an anime convention,
it's fucking great, because you just get to be, be little, ridicule, and antagonize all
of the goers of the con, go to panels, ruin them, you know what you are, Munchy? You're
a fucking Chad, that's who you are, you're a disgusting fucking Chad, I'm just a little
boy trying to make friends, and here you come, with you, we're a bully squad, trying to embarrass
you, one of the things that I love, go fuck yourself, Munchy.
Munchy, have you been to a furry convention, and done that?
Oh my god, no, but that's been, that's been a fucking top billing, dude. Well, I guess
you could, well, I have been to various Brony conventions, so, you know, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Is, is, is that why you were at BronyCon? Just to laugh at us?
No, no, no, that was, that was, that was a fucking joke, that was a charade, that was,
that was, that was a meme, that was a jest. I like to go with my friends to conventions,
A, we, we, we, like, like, me and my friends are both in sync, and we know what we would
like, and we'd go to the same panels together, because, you know, we both have an appreciation
for whoever the fuck Japanese retard bitch, whoever's talking, you know, you want to-
I like how this has gone from me and my friends to we, the two of us, have this connection.
You're, it's, it's one totally different feeling from this description mask.
Well, see, well, yes, well, it's, it's one guy, but he changes masks, more often than
you. He plays many roles in the munchy, like, in munch's life.
Cosplayers. You know?
No, no, he, as in, like, one, like, one to two people come, but it's always, like, different
people.
As in he finds victims and he skins them and wears their skin.
As in I kill Native Americans.
What was they fucking, oh yeah, we go there and we all-
Talk about how you like conventions.
Yes, and we all, we appreciate the panels together, and then we go buy merch where
we couldn't buy it anywhere else, or at least I don't know how to. I don't want to use a fucking
computer, it's hard.
I see the one one is a big thing. That's like the one good thing about convinced one time
I literally ask did you how to buy anime because I didn't know how to and then he taught me and then I still didn't know
Did I did I did did you ask me that and then I immediately made that entire 40 minute buyers?
No, no, I asked you like a year after that and then like like while you were teaching me
I Google search like how to buy anime merch then I saw that thumbnail and then I remember that I
Linked you the thumbnail with fire around your eyes and like you glowing like a fucking golden crisp God
Anyway, so you can buy the merchant with you with your meaty your meaty your meaty sockets
And you just have a fucking good time you get to hang out and you get to spend time in an exotic city with exotic sluts
Doing gay shit, and you get to fucking you just look at lots and it's sick
Tell me about the sluts and if I go to a convention are there exotic sluts there? What's what's happening here?
Oh my god, it's Jesse. Oh shit. Okay. I've been here the whole
Jesse did join like ten minutes ago. I wasn't sure if he was like you sound like you're underwater. Yeah, I was gonna say
Yeah, you're like you were just drowned you were drowning in water. Do I are you mouth deep and pussy again, Jesse?
That is a possibility there are many possibilities
The other possibility could be that my microphone is broken from the flood nobody knows everything. Oh my god
Oh god the fucking three hundred dollar one broke. I don't know as you guys are saying I sound underwater. I haven't heard it yet
I don't fucking know nothing. Oh, yeah, it broke in the underwater boy
Either a broker you're just recording through the wrong microphone, which I am an underwater boy
And I have aids and no one can stop me
from having a
right now Jesse yeah
Yes, all right, that's cool. Jesse. You want to talk about your convention actually much you motherfucker. I'm not done
I'm fucking you alive. Wrap it up. You're taking the whole fucking
I'm saying is damn at
At an expo. I'm munchy. Oh my god. Listen buddy. I deserve time. Okay. Hey, it's his catchphrase listen buddy
It's my favorite
Get on the ground you fucking nigger
An expo I got a girl gone. I imagine a sitcom about munchy like he's the Kramer he comes in the door
I and like whatever something weird happens. He looks at the camera and goes get on the ground you
Hired out like a clown to children's parties. Hey kids get on the ground you fucking niggers
Imagine you're watching like like a normal sign-of-the-lip episode and like Jerry's in his apartment
He's talking to George about how he can't get late or something and then like like I burst through the door like Kramer
Like like in my piece of jumpsuit and never just wetter. I'm just get on the ground you fucking diggers
And George would be like I'm getting frustrated by all these racial slurs. I'm not even black
To wrap this up. I like her in the gun. I got a girl in the gun book
I couldn't have got that anywhere else other than a so and it made me happy and I really like it and um, yes, okay
Okay, bye merchandise is cool. That's that's one fun thing
I never would have ever gotten Kingdom Hearts 2 final mix plus if I hadn't seen it well that fateful day
A good like convention piece of merchandise yet. It's about the fucking experience
I guess I've probably spent you by your diamond tiara fucking plushie yet. Yeah, but that was a piece of shit
It was like the one that the cheapest made plushie. She's she's sure I'm a chair is crying right now
She's diamond tiara is so rich. She deserves to be made out of fucking gold
I got the cheapest one because I'm a bitch
I should I couldn't find a better one and that was I've probably lifetime spent like at least five grand on
Merchant conventions
Like that's that's one of the big reasons I go there is to drop a lot of money
I spent more money there than anywhere else, but I was never that big of a spender on that kind of stuff anyway
I go to conventions to spend money and kill people. Yeah a huge part of
Why I went to Otacon so many times is that it happens to almost always fall directly on my birthday
Which is August 8th and so my dad would usually like you know like he'd he'd you know
Buy me the trip to Otacon and give me a bunch of spending money, and I just blow through it all there
Oh, yeah, so so it's like a big birthday thing for me
That's where I got a lot of my figures a lot of my posters a lot of my art books and just a bunch of other shit
All of which I regret none of this none of that money should ever have been spent
With me is at the moment is like I don't have any like huge
Like desire to own things about a thing like even though my little pony wasn't that great
I have a lunar plushie, but that was like a gift
So you know that's great, but like I wouldn't buy a lot of brony stuff
The only thing I would buy is like home stuck but home sucks dead and no one will make any home
Suck art not an animax bro. Not an animax, bro X bro
There's so much home stuck shit there. I was in my boggles my mind. Oh shit. Well, I gotta go there then
I gotta go. There's this one risk. There's this one brisket cosplayer that was just like
Oh
Is that
Attraction is that what that's I like it
Yeah, you know when you start to foam at the mouth and also foam at your penis
Yes, yes, I do you've all you've all kind of covered my my main reasons for going to conventions
But I want to summarize them like that that there's pretty much three big ones and then a fourth one that applies to me and you guys to some extent
Well, to the same extent really but anyways
The first big reason is you know being around your people to whatever whatever
Ills or games that may entail and for me the best like the ultimate being around my people thing
Cuz like, you know out in the convention halls. I don't care man. It's just a bunch of fucking, you know
People I don't want to talk to you know in the panels. I don't care
But there's one place I go at Otsa Khan every year and I spend hours there
Which is Otsa karaoke?
I hang out in the karaoke room all day and just listen to people
Attempt to sing anime songs and that's when I truly feel at home because you have to have a certain level of
Like passion to want to do it. It's to an audience of nobody. There's only like ten people who hang out in there
There's a bunch of regulars who every year. It's the same few people singing there
You know singing the songs
You're getting up every year and I recognize all of them though. I don't talk to them. We communicate only through song
That's not entirely true. I do I I trade a few words, but I you know
I don't like fucking buddy up with them or anything
They're they're often cosplaying and stuff
I mean you're gonna hear the fucking every song from Inuyasha a thousand times and you're gonna hear a bunch of the same songs every year
What it's always interesting to hear
God bless
You know that Haruhi one not a lot of that not a lot of not a lot of God knows
I would be the one probably to go up and sing that
I do that one. That's a classic, but
But it's always interesting to see which song is the big one that year like this past year. It was all JoJo, you know
JoJo so big is that a JoJo reference?
What indeed
Anyways, yeah, I always hang out there. That's my best like connecting with the nerds place. Then there's the merchandise which
Was a lot more impressive when I was younger because Otakan has a merch room
that's the size of a fucking aircraft hangar and
And and you know, it's it the first year I went there
I legitimately got lost for like an hour and just was exploring this wonderland of anime crap
I have returned. I left the call
Welcome back bloody dead man
Oh, no bloody dead man's gonna bloody kill us. I left to increase my age. That's Babadook spook
This is just me. This is just my voice now
I'm just a broken man
Bloody dead man has like a British accent. That's true. What he dead man is the father of under Taylor
I thought I told you that I disowned you you're not my family anymore
Oh
You're a disgrace to the dead man family name because you're you're weird and just slightly a different way than me
This it makes total sense like the bloody dead man disowned his son because he liked undertale too much and now
Sansa is a surrogate father. He's like he's perverted in just slightly the wrong way, and I don't want him anymore
And I never had a father figure. That's why I want to suck your weirest of my own fathers
They're sending you little and great. I've tried to suck mini a lemon pipe in my day
And when I do it I bite him because I'm kind of a vampire maybe or something. I don't know
Dad it's not my fault the bot flies choose me. They chose me. I didn't choose the bot fly lifestyle
Listen the last bot fly that I was in a committed relationship with was your mother and she was a vampire bot fly
Oh my god, his mother was a bot fly
You think bot flies had
After these vampire bot flies they get inside your lemon pipe and they turn it into a kool-aid pipe
They turn you into a bloody dead man
They turn you into a fucking ruddy leaky bloody dead man cock is what I've done for god damn dead boy
No
Does anyone else fuck you son?
No dad you're gay. Do you stop?
Some have called me that. Many have called me that in my 5000 years on this earth gay
But it's only one of the many things I am
Bitch, I'm on a crest to save sense and told me to kill all the gay people and I'll have to kill you
That's what I've talked to you. I haven't talked to in 16 years, but now I'm finished if I
Years is but a blink of an eye to me. I've been here since before the dawn of time
I only went down to the store to get a pack of cigarettes
I was going to come back one of these centuries. I swear
Lend me strength so I can kill my bitch dad. There's no such thing as sense and I hate my son. Fuck you
You're just gay
Oh, no, they left. Where'd they go? Oh, they're gone
Oh, it's
What lore what adventures we have here in the procrastinator's podcast
You know what? You know what we could the amount of characters that we have in the pcp
We could we could all cosplay them and go to a convention. Oh my god. I mean this there's even yeah
I'm gonna cosplay the undertaler my son. You should. Oh, does that mean I'm the bloody dead man? Oh, shit
Yes, I'm like the young years. You know like the once learn that like the laurax movie
I'm like that version of the bloody dead man. Oh, like the young like that makes sense. That makes sense
Yeah, one she the twink
But she's a fucking six foot one
230 pound twink well well compared to the bloody dead man who is like the like like the the opposite of a twink
Like the polar opposite that makes sense. What are we talking? What's the plot? Oh, oh, oh, this is this is the pcp lore podcast, right?
Hey, uh, here's the thing that I wanted to mention
Uh
One thing that I like about convention or rather okay, so now I don't care about this at all
But when I was young this was something that I was very interested in so I talked before about you know
How you should talk almano was going to convention that was cool
But before that when I was even younger I got excited because I still cared about uh voice actors
And uh, I used to go that that's my number my number three. Oh, yeah, yeah, okay. Well here take it away
Go ahead. Oh, well, I'll just finish my number two point first. Yeah about the merch
Because the merch was such an such an ocean of of possibilities when I was young
Um, and then I realized by like the second or third year that they all sell the same shit
Every fucking booth is the same shit and it's only like the most popular shows that have any merch
Um, and they just they never have anything I want
So I'll wander around for like hours in this fucking endless sea of merch and walk away with one thing
That was like, you know what the thing is, you know, what the thing is
Uh, a con is inversely proportional as in the more
It's your the what you will get out of going to a con is inversely proportional to how much you already know about like anime culture
That's the more you learn the less you get out of it. I just absolutely agree with that
that because
Another part of the appeal when we talk about panels
Is that uh, you learn a lot like for me in the early days one of the coolest things about conventions was I would go to a panel
About something I'd never heard of and then learn like all this interesting amazing shit about it
Uh, and now I know everything like there has not been a panel in the last few years that the ones I started going to
Uh
Instead of going to like ones about anime now
I go to all the like weird japanese culture like like a panel about noodles or something
Just so I can have something new that I don't know about because any anime panel you've reached
You've reached weeb bedrock at this point and it's just there are directly diagonal to bedroom bed. Yeah, it's actually the same place
but uh
There's been like a ton of panels that I go to and not only do I feel like I could give the panel
But I feel like I could give it better like half the time. Oh, you know calling you out con panel holders
And I mean I've run on the universe. That's right
but
But um, but yeah, so with the with the the shit like last this past otacon
I literally went there with the intention of sparing no expense
I was like i'm going to spend as much money as I can
And I will buy anything that interests me and I still there was nothing like I came away with like a few posters
And that was about it. Um, so yeah, it's
That aspect is kind of dead to me now and then again with the panels, you know, there's too much stuff
I already know. Um, and it used to be that one of the coolest things that you can meet
Japanese guests because yeah, wait, wait, wait before we get into that just about that topic
I wanted to share one just small anecdote about this whole things you can learn when you go to convention
I have to admit my first visit to a convention was definitely
I want to say almost definitely worth
Going because I remember this was when I had gotten into one piece in a big way off of the four kids dub
And so I was there in my full luffy costume with my big captain's coat
That I still wear my my gur and login one is I I don't know if I've ever mentioned this
But like the gur and login coat I wear is a is just my one piece coat
I made way back in the day just with the gur and login thing sewn onto the back. There's there's some lore for you
but um
When I was there, uh, uh, like I happened upon another cosplayer a zoro cosplayer
And this exchange would come to define my life for decades to come
Because what he told me what he said to me
He walked up to me or we were taking a picture and like we he got into it with us or something
Because it was me ben and like a friend. We were all cosplaying one piece. This guy joined his zoro
And so he uh, after we took the picture a ben was sanju sanju
He's a big sanju fan or at least was um
But uh, so this guy like I
You know, I had watched the whole show up to that point that was aired and I thought it was great
And this guy just looks at me and he's like, hey dude, nice costume. Like yeah, you too
Of course at this time I was young and timid and was just like, yeah, thanks. And um, he uh, he just said so like what's
So, uh, what's your favorite part and I'm like, oh, I don't know
I liked when they fought like captain coro like something like that and he just says yeah, that's pretty cool. Uh, how'd you like skypea?
and
Skypea had not been aired. Skypea would never air. I don't think at this point
Yeah, like basically what happened here was that he introduced the concept of manga to me
And I was I had no idea that one piece was even based on a manga or that I was behind
And the shame the deep shame that blossomed in me at that moment of not knowing
I thought I knew everything there was to know at this point
And then I learned there was a whole universe beyond my reach and on that day
I vowed to never allow someone else to have more knowledge of something I like than me
What I would what I would give to have been that man
Yeah
He he would man. Oh, because I found out about one piece through the manga before the anime even debuted in America
Um, I'm a true fucking patrician. Yes, you are. You know, anyway, uh
Yeah, I'll never forget you zero cosplayer. You're a legend like wherever you are out there, buddy
If uh, if you're uh, unless you're gonna like talk with like number three or number four
I don't know what you're gonna say to you, but
Well, yeah, I'm gonna go into number three
Unless you want to continue or whatever you want. Well, I was gonna I was gonna sort of change gears, but I'll do it after
Let's finish these examples that will yeah. Um, well
So to to to broach the subject of number three
I just want to talk about that first con I went to the first ozakan and why it was so magical that day
Because it happened the first day of the con was on my birthday. I was turning. I think 17 and uh, you know, it was
Everything about it was the craziest shit I'd ever seen. There's more people than I'd ever seen in one place
I'd never seen cosplay, you know, so that was
Magical and now it means nothing to me. I've seen every cosplay
The only thing I get out of cosplay now is seeing what is the most popular show to cosplay that year is always interesting
Um, like, you know, recently was like tokyo ghoul is like the big one. Anyway
Um, I'm seeing all this fucking cosplay all this stuff and everything all these people
But the thing that truly made this concert this uh, this con experience was that they were having a concert
Um with jam project whom all of you have probably heard at least one jam project song
They did the one punch man opening most famously recently. Um, is that what they're most famous for? Okay. Well, yeah
Everyone knows the one punch man opening so I can easily give that as an example
Um, oh and you know members of it did the one piece opening and the dragon ball z opening
So, you know, they performed those at this show
um, but
The japanese ones of course not the fucking yoyo yoyo, but
jam project
Is a five person it's like five singers who are all famous for anime music
And they have a super group and they mostly do like robot shows
But anyways, they were they were doing a show
On my birthday at otsukan, you know and I went to this show and they fucking, you know, they they sing all these incredible songs
And for their encore they sang the op to the soul taker
Which is my favorite anime opening of all time that I'd you know that I'd sang like
The the opening the opening lines of the soul taker is this woman singing like
It's like this like epic rise up and me and my brother would like sing that when we were like
Unboxing like it's like a new piece of equipment or something like, you know real autism shit
So I they they played that song. It was the the greatest thing I'd ever seen in my life
You know cool band my favorite anime op on my birthday at this convention. Everything was magical
I spent all this money and I saw all these japanese guests, you know, I met like
Well, I didn't go to any meet and greets. I didn't actually do that till this past year, but like
Um, you know, I got to see these people talk about the anime industry and I learned all this stuff and over time
All of that like has gotten lesser
There's like, you know, ozakan has fewer and fewer japanese guests because they all go to anime expo now because anime expo is way bigger
Um, you know, there there hasn't been these magical panels where I learned things there hasn't been these epic encounters
There hasn't been you know a beautiful moment on my birthday
It's like every year I get more jaded and more cynical and more and more like why am I even
Going to this anymore and like last year was the last year they were doing it in baltimore. They're moving it to dc
I was almost I wasn't gonna go to ozakan this year, but now they've announced they're actually bringing back jam project
So now I totally want to go um, but man, that's great
Yeah, but like it was definitely like this downward spiral and now I want to go to anime expo to see if
See if it can reignite the spark because it's it's now like twice the size ozakan ever was
And has all these great japanese guests and shit and uh, I could hang out with munchie though
We'll probably just split up because of her ways because he won't know anything I want to go to
Uh, no, I I mean I hate anime so no matter what I do
I wouldn't be happy like actually paying attention to it. So I might as well just make myself like miserable
Because it'll be funny
Oh, and I hinted earlier there was a fourth reason to go to conventions that only applies to me and and us
Which is to run panels to to be a part of the convention whole different world
It's like a whole different flip side of the coin where it's it's really about
This epic moment of showmanship because it's it's one thing to like, you know run a youtube show and you could see
Oh, I have 250,000 subscribers. I have comments and stuff like that
But when you actually see like a thousand people sitting in front of you listening to you laughing at your stupid jokes
Then it's like that's when you really realize like I am a wizard god like I control people, you know
I wasn't I I don't know whether I liked it when I was up there with the brony con stuff
I mean for one thing I embarrassed myself by swearing too much when I shouldn't
That was hilarious. It's fine. I guess it was funny, but I felt like oh no
Oh, no, I'm doing wrong things. I was hey at least you weren't the one who when we did the concert where we
For anyone fucking punched celestia in the goddamn face you fucking drunk
No, I wasn't even gonna bring up that. I don't think I actually like hit her dude
You watched if you were close to her face, dude, you were real
It's my birthday
If you if you watch the footage that hippo has of otacon, you'll see that we we got to we
They were having a big concert and we for whatever reason were like the djs who went up in between songs and like and or in between sets
And announced it and I believe that the very first thing I did was like to run on stage and be like what the fuck's up
The lady running it was immediately like I've made a huge mistake
Because I was yet she kept us going for the whole two hours or whatever the fuck it was
Well, they eventually took the mic away from me. They wouldn't let me uh like everyone else went on and did like the dj thing
And I went up there with a roll of toilet paper. It was just throwing it in the background
She gave me the mic and it was like you're the responsible one hold on to this mic and make sure they don't do anything crazy
From my perspective that was it was it was terrible at the time because I wasn't drunk and I was like, oh no
Yeah, everyone's having a good time and I'm just sitting here being gay
But watching the footage it was great, you know, even though when I went up on stage
I didn't know what to do. I was just standing in the middle of the stage for like five seconds
Not really doing anything. I didn't have a mic. I didn't know what to do. So I was like, uh, here I am
I'm definitely a little embarrassed. I'm pretty sure I had the most fun I've ever had in my life at that
concert
Yeah, I mean looking back on it like remember when uh, there was that one part where like everyone backstage like all went out and
Started dancing all together. Yeah, and we were just it was we were all fucking going nuts. It was it was crazy and uh,
I don't know that that was awesome. I definitely
Was embarrassing myself and looking at it now actually not now, but when I first watched it back
I was like, oh god, I will never be okay with this
But at this point now, I'm totally comfortable with it and it just is just a music
Digi the image of you being completely like like drunk like not even be able to like recognize your surroundings
Being sang to by nicole oliver. You are my sunshine
It was tearing at like nothing. It was the weirdest
Fucking thing because no one warned me. No one gave me stage directions or told me what was going on
I just all of a sudden have like a you know a I don't know if she's a famous voice actress per se, but you know
She is for in the context of this convention essentially a literal goddess, you know, that's true
Um putting here and I remember
Having this moment where I felt really bad because of the fact that I didn't care about my little pony anymore
Like oh, yeah, like I felt it was like if this had happened two years prior
I would be like crying, you know, like this would be so meaningful to me and instead i'm up here
obliterated shit
With like I don't care about anyone in this place at all
I have like, you know, I'm out here because it's fun for me to be a drunken idiot not because I actually care about this crowd
um
And like their goddess is singing to me for my birthday and I was just like this is wrong
I am a bad man your god to me is just another slut and it's my birthday
What's that what is that clip I said that somewhere right? I don't know
It's it's it's when we're all walking to the thing and victor or maybe I was holding no it was victor holding the camera
Watching you be drunk and punching natin and stuff and then yeah, yeah
Uh victor comments that I wish I was as drunk as you is like it's my birthday, bitch, and I just
onto the part where you almost
When you were pretending to fight jesse
That was one of the funniest edits i've ever seen in my life
That was the funniest the best part about that was her fucking face like she real like I just sang to this person
I just sang like you're my sunshine to this person and now they're like fighting
You changed her whole view of the human race and what to expect when you know like good things are always
When I watched that footage I got the impression that she realized what was like like that she you know
She was scared to try to get out of the way, but she realized that this was a drunken insane party and that
Like oh, yeah, you know these are I actually remember seeing her backstage just thinking oh, what's going on up there?
Is like is is someone getting a birthday like I was backstage looking at I was like that
Is that who I don't know who that is, but I think it's someone
I mean let's she went and did that. It's just so weird. Let's be real the brony community
There's a lot of infantilization in there right like the idea of the character princess celestia singing to you
Is like oh, you're like you're my child, you know, you're all my children kind of thing
It's like but in that moment. I think she remembered. Oh, yeah, this is like a drunken 23 year old man
When you started swinging. Yes, I think this is a grown bearded fat dangerous man
And dangerous
That should be the name of your biography fat and dangerous
Gayer than god is the name of my biography. Okay. All right. Fine. Fine. But fat and dangerous would be the sequel
It goes it goes dead and gay and then
Dead and gay right and then gay and god. I think it will be the finale
I was already planning to make a gayer than god song for the gay and dead album
But I I think I'll also make fat and dangerous a song
It'll be like a big fat like fucking
Atlanta style heavy beat like killer mic song. It's gonna be one of the samples is it's my birthday
Yeah, that should definitely be one of all I should definitely be one
Oh my god. Yes
So, okay, so I think it's fair to say that if you're on the side of
Like of of making or being you know the one up on stage doing things at cons that changes the game and it's pretty fun
Most of the time it's pretty fun if you're if you're used to it
I was so overwhelmed like in the panel and on the thing that I kind of hated it at the end
Well, you know like that was only your like second convention though
So like you were probably still acclimating in general and then going up on stage is just like another big change, you know
So also, I think I think personally you should give us more tracks. We all had
The group
I did to shit through that whole panel. I forgot about the group shit. Oh my god
Literally all of us. Yeah, we we we ate wendy's on our way to the convention and we were like fucking late
Like we almost missed our own panel which had all of us on it because we like woke up late
And then we went to wendy's and they took forever and we ate and it was like totally all of us felt shit
And uh, so we second we got to the convention
We went to the bathrooms like right by the you know right by where the the panel was gonna be and we like all
Simultaneously took a shit. I forgot about the group shit
Oh my god. Yes. That was the best thing that ever happened. I was so I was so conscious of my point
I didn't want to poop my pants on stage as well as
Well, yeah, I mean munchy that by that point by by this brony con I went to three of them
And by that one literally the only reason any of us was there was to hang out with one another
Yeah, yeah, which is why rad rad con happened because it was like after
You know after going to brony con it's like we're really here to hang out with each other and to try to get laid
Um, I think
Yeah, the main reason we went to brony con that that year that I was there is because I hadn't been to one yet
And I wanted yeah to go. Oh, yeah, that's that was a big thing before it was totally over
Yeah, and while you were still like someone with like clout in the community who could enjoy being famous kp
kp is like the top billing guests. I really want to see here. Oh, yeah, dog. Oh, yeah
Uh, that's what conventions are. They're just locations for play dates
And that's why they're incredible. They are incredible play date material
They're like theme parks, but I but wouldn't you say munchy that it was even better at rad con than like
Them brony con. I would say it was better
However, I don't like like just the fact that it was better doesn't mean that I wouldn't I wouldn't also cherish going to a convention
It's not it's I'm not saying that hanging out with your friends is inherently like
Like better or worse with the convention, but do you think it's an interesting location and it breeds a lot of discussion
And uh, like like it's easy to ridicule people and therefore very funny
Yeah, it is a definite like different because like in digi's house
Some people have rooms that they go to when they're not, you know doing something with the rest of us
And so like in a convention, you know, you're you're always having to do something other just sitting around talking or
Or like going to a panel or just eating, you know, it's just everyone's doing something at the same time
Panels are the fucking worst thing but like what I mean is everyone's doing something at the same time
It's a different sort of feeling than just being in a house together
Yeah, because you know people wake up at different times and sleeping arrangements are kind of rough. Yeah. Well, I mean for sure
It's the the thing about conventions and the reason that I wanted like well aside from the fact that I just want to hang out with
You guys and make stuff. Um, the other thing I don't like about conventions is
Uh, it's hard enough living in one house with everybody. It's even worse when you're all in one room
And it's like yeah, like for me. I have terrible insomnia and I
And I also can't stand silence. So I'm used to you know going to bed playing music
You know having like a certain certain way
Jacking off you can't jack off and you're all in the same hotel room big problem. That's what you think amateur
Well, you know, you can take a long shower, but uh
It's harder to get we'll say it's hard to get away with jacking off
When you're all sharing a room, but um, you know for me every convention I've ever been to
By four in the morning
I'm going to be stepping over everybody to get out of the room and then just wandering the hotel for like hours
And then I'll probably sleep for 30 minutes and then go to the con, you know
And and be like miserable and sick all day. So, you know, that's that's like as many like there's
All the cons are worth having gone to
Like it's worth it to be able to tell these great stories and to be able to say have all these fond memories
But the actual experience of living it is often hellish because it's always like no sleep
Very difficult to remain uh to keep up your hygiene at all, you know
Which is is actually a problem when you're in baltimore in the summer and it's fucking 95 degrees and you're walking all day
you know, so like
Usually by the end of a convention, I am physically broken like my voice doesn't work anymore. I can't see
I'm like sleeping. I usually sleep for like almost a whole 24 hours the day after a con
Um, so yeah, it like there's a lot of nightmarish elements that make it that that are like why I wouldn't just like like
Even if otacon wasn't that great, you know, um, it would it would still be worth going to right because why not?
It's something to do for a weekend
Except that it's something that involves like a four-hour car car drive, which isn't that bad
But then they're sharing a hotel with a bunch of other people not getting any sleep physically exhausting yourself, you know
And then the existential ennui of realizing that you've put yourself through all of this and for what, you know
That's what gets me the most. I always end up like by sunday. I feel like I hate the world at most conventions
So, yeah, it's fun. I've had that at the end of radcon. Well, that was physically
I felt like that through all of radcon
But radcon 2 was for totally different reasons. Um that I felt that way I understand what you mean and I appreciate it
However, uh, I think it's wrong and I think you're gay. Uh
I I I
One way to put it is that radcon 2 was like if we went to a convention and we ran every panel
That's that's how I describe radcon 2
Uh, I mean, uh, it is exhausting. However, like I I don't feel pain in the sense that like
Like you don't feel pain at all pain is like really funny to me and like like whenever I get hit by it
I just like dude like dude
And and uh, like like I like I'm literally here is a like like
This is like a like a part of my life that you need to understand to get me
Uh, and I I will I will title this chapter of my life. Seinfeld was like a mindbreak dosion for real life
Yeah, I'm I'm always thinking about my life as if I was a character on Seinfeld
And so every bad thing that humanly happens to me. I just think that's really fucking funny. That's sick
That's that's that's amazing because victor does the exact same thing but with curb your enthusiasm as opposed to side
You know, that that's the ironic age relivering. We're living in now where our own suffering is merely an amusing fact of uh, you know
I think again, it's easy for me to see it that way in retrospect, but in the moment. It's just like I do in the moment
Yeah, um
But you just got a faster processor for this shit
Because I got a mindbreak dosioned
I wanted to talk about this for a while
Uh, you've been talking about anime cons and and brony con. I don't know whether any of you've gone to like a video game
Convention like just for video games. No, I have not I would say this
But I kind of wish jeff was here because he has gone to all of those
Oh
You know, uh, and he could we could talk about that because like I don't think they're that different though that he wants us to go
To to magfest. I kind of would like to go like to magfest or packs or something because like from what I've learned
From watching like
You know youtube content people who are video game ish
Like total biscuit and jontron or whatever game gross
They it's a different sort of feeling because it's not like I don't know
I feel like I I would have more fun at one of those perhaps
But maybe not I'm just not I'm skeptical that there's much difference really
Yeah, I don't know because I haven't been to a game. There's there's someone who's been to like a shitload of uh otakans
Like there's off. There is a huge contingent of gaming there
Like otakans is really an everything convention. It's not really about anime per se if you go there as just a gamer
There there's a huge arcade room
There's people who just hang out in there and play street fighter the whole convention
You know they have gaming tournaments
Even brony con had like smash tournaments and shit. Um, yeah, that's what i'm saying
It's I remember there was a guy who was like wider than he was tall playing smash. That's all I remember
And uh, it was in there just sort of yeah, I think victor competed in that actually and um, yes
There's a pretty big there's a pretty big arcade room
I personally I I never have the patience to like wait to be able to play one of the games
The only time I the only time I was excited enough about a video game
They had because they they they don't have like a lot of really cool interesting arcade cabinets at otakon
Unfortunately, and that's I would like to go to a gaming convention if they had like an like a legit arcade
Like if they had games that I really had, you know heard of and spoken in soft whispers and always wanted to see
The only time I got really excited was when they had dengeki bunko fighting climax
Which had not come out yet in the us
Which is the game where you fight like novel characters and get to beat up kirito and shit
Except that there was this fucking guy at the like, you know, they had two cabinets
So everyone was fighting each other and there was this dude there who was playing kirito and had obviously played the game
Like he had it
He must have had the japanese version on vita and was just destroying everyone
But he would never
Move like, you know, he was just like taking each new challenger and kicking their asses and everyone was dead silent
Because like the the atmosphere this guy gave off was like a total douchebag asshole
Who was like here to beat people to prove that he's so good at this game that none of us have ever played
Because it's not out in america specifically. Yeah, just at this
And so there's probably like six people and we're all we're each like moving through the line
And each person will like get up fight him lose and then just silently walk away and the next person goes up
Why don't anyone make this guy fucking move?
Just because you know
You lose the match and you walk away and it was like it was new people coming up
You know like nobody was like hanging out around the machine. It was just like people were you know, all right
that's fine lining up to play and
Realizing this guy
But I was there long enough to see that he had you know beaten down all these people and of course
I tried and I got my ass kicked because he knew the like the auto combo
You know, he wasn't even like great at the game
It's just he had played the fucking thing and I was so mad at that guy. I literally wanted him dead
I was like I will train at this game for the rest of my life just so I could beat this guy and rub it in his face
You know, um
I'd like to see your uh oreimo against his uh, I assume he was a kirito player. I just yeah, he was playing kirito
How did I know how did I know I said it but uh, well, that's how I knew
but
I was at the time I I had tried playing shana because I shana was gonna be my main
I wanted her to be like the one I would play in the game, uh, but I ended up being good with uh, what's kirino?
anyways, um
Yeah, like so I haven't hung out in the gaming room much
But I I I do kind of want to go to magfest not so much for the gaming
But because it's specifically a gaming and music convention
Like there's it's more about like nerdcore bands and shit playing. I'm sure uh Tupperware remix parties probably played there
Protoman plays there. Yeah, they have and I want to see them there one time. Yeah, I just got back
Yeah, like
I don't know. I wouldn't have been like unwilling to go to magfest
But jeff wanted us to go to that and radcon and I was like we can't
Radcon's an event for making things and there's like a schedule for it
And we cannot afford to go to that and magfest, you know, I kind of would like to go
At some point with jeff and all
Just as a big old procrastinators magfest
Yeah, it would be fun. That could be cool. It's just affording it
Maybe he could he could be the guy to introduce us to I don't know fucking
Everybody's super buddy hop. I hate all of those
I don't I don't dislike them. I would be I'd be happy to just see. Oh, yeah
I mean, it's just that it's just not my crowd right now. You know, I mean, maybe it could be
I mean, I just didn't know anything about it. I'd certainly like to meet buddy hop. He's cool. But anyway, uh
Yeah, but
Oh, yeah, so I do I do agree though that
Gaming conventions seem different going by because there's a lot more gaming like there's more hands on
There it is it's it's more of like, you know, you're going there more to do something as opposed like with an anime convention
You know, if you go to all these panels that are like the informative ones again
Like if you already know the stuff, it's completely useless, you know
Like you might get to meet some cool industry people but at a video game convention
There's often actually a game there that you could not play elsewhere that and that's interesting
You know, that's probably what I'd want to go for the most
But I doubt they're that different from anime cons, you know, I'm ready to make a sweeping proclamation about
The function of conventions and and what they should be used for and what purpose they serve
Conventions are something that children should go to
Yeah, they are they are best for for young adults like, you know, 12 13 that that sort of range
And they're just gonna you're gonna get less out of them as you get older
And I'll tell you why and if you go with friends and you just tool around then that you can go at any age
That that'll be fine
But the usefulness of the actual thing is best for the young and I'll tell you why
It's because I mean there's this thing I said before of just the more you know about the subject matter
The less you get out of it and and that really applies in a lot of ways
Like when I was when I was young one of the first panels
I went to at some convention and this blew my mind
This is like one of the first sort of analytical lectures I ever heard about
Anime or in this case a video game
It was a lecture that some dude was giving on how like teetus from final fantasy 10 represented the
The like the human ideal of the ubermensch and like his role in final fantasy 10 was like a representation of like the ideal man in a
Like a fantasy world or like some bullshit like that
But I had never heard any talk like that before which is now a format that's kind of you know people talk about that show on youtube now
But at the time I'd never heard anything like that
Um, but other than that there are the there's like so there's that little bit of information you can gain
But then there's the distinct like magical moment factor like when me and ben were young
Um, and I think this was even more important for ben or more enjoyable for ben than was for me
When we were young at anime boston the pillows played and it was one of the most
Awesome things we'd ever seen our lives and and in addition to just hearing all the songs and being completely blown away
And the place just going insane and just loving every second of it
There was also this moment where up on up on the rafters
We were down on the ground floor watching them play
But up in the rafters there was a couple of people standing and watching the band from up above
There was a mamimi cosplayer just dancing by herself
And just watching her dance while listening to
Fucking crazy sunshine and and you know all the shit from the show
Uh, fuck. What's that one? I think I can all that shit
Watching her dance by herself was just such a magical moment
And I'll always regret not going up and joining her that's stuck with me my whole life
My relationship with women
I mean, I would still lose my shit for a pillows concert
But I can't even imagine like me at 17 at the same age I saw jam project
If I if I had heard fucking hybrid rainbow live when I was 17, I would have cried a river
I would have been losing my fucking mind to that
So yeah, I can definitely appreciate what you're saying there
So that was great, but then also at the time I still gave a shit about voice actors
And I don't think I'd really care about these things as much now
But there were two incidents that were that are very memorable to me
One was when I met Steve Blum. He was doing something. I think it was it was this was the gurren login thing
He was signing autographs. I think for his role as learon
And um, I went up to him and and and said hi and shook his hand and I told him
I'll never forget this. I I said hey, dude
I know that you get this all the time, but I just loved you as spike and I was like
I know he's doing some other character, but that's what I remember before
I'm sure he's gonna hate me for it. He's just like dude. It never gets old. I love it every time
And he smiled at me and I went on my way and I just felt so great about my life
I I think it was incredible. Yeah, I might hate dubs more than anybody in the world
But I could still probably mark out for Steve Blum like
He's a fucking legend. He's he's a legend been in everything. Um, and then there was this other moment
Here, this is my last thing. I even have to say
When I was at some like fma would gotten really big and I was at a convention
I think this was anime boston and it was a panel
Uh, like the voice actors or something and I didn't give a shit about anyone except vik manjana was there. He was cool
Tell me a case of vik manjana story. I know and this this is classic vik manjana
Like just being weirdly obsessed with the character of ed, but he did this thing. He's like, hey guys, um
I was like taking questions or whatever and somebody asked him to like do a line from the show
I mean, of course, right and so he's like, okay. All right guys, but I've gotten good at this
So let we're all going to go through an exercise because this is the best way for you to experience this
I don't want you to see me god
This is this this is this tells me so much about him as a man right now
But he's like, okay. I don't want you to see me as like this old like 30 something, you know, slightly balding
That motherfucker is 15 now. So he was probably in his 40s
Yeah, okay, maybe he even said 30s and was lying. I don't know. I can't remember but uh, that that'd be hilarious
That was true
But he said like I don't want you to see me as this old man
Everyone close your eyes and just listen to my voice and he did like I think he did the monologue from
After the barry the butcher fight, you know what I'm talking about where he's like crying about like he realized how vulnerable
He is how much he cares about that's the scene that that
Made his whole career oscar bait scene from fma. It's the reason that he won every fucking
Voice actor award for dubbing ever and that's why he's so fucking famous is for that one scene pretty much
And he did it and at the time I was definitely an fma fan
And he did it with such passion and just clearly
Loved doing what he did so much and loved the character so much regardless of the reasons why
Yeah, it was just that was just a great experience that really made me get into anime in a big way
If this was like 2006, I probably would have felt exactly the same
I I loved that performance when I was young. Um, he killed it on that one how I hate it
I did get to just that that's the just that's the end of my case for how
These things I think like now like like you were saying
I don't think these would really make as much of an impact on me because I've had all these experiences
But when I was a kid first getting into the stuff not knowing much to see the world
That's out there and the passion these people are putting in I can see why
Like I get this stuff and I understand why it's valuable
Seeing the stuff and and seeing the things people can do with it and like why my parents just don't
They haven't had any of these experiences. They don't get shit about this. They just think it's goofy cartoons
You know just two or three years ago at ozakan. I also met ed's voice actor, but the real one talk to rome
Uh, the japanese voice actress who's one of my favorite voice actresses and she was so fucking
She was the
You know sometimes you see someone there's there's certain celebrities that I have that that like
That waifu or idol like crush on she's one of those she's just so perfect and hilarious and
And adorable and I absolutely love her and I would
Sacrifice my life to for her
No, she's she was great
Yeah, I want to throw in a bit
Uh, I'll probably have more to say about this possibly in the future if I take up any of these because I've run
I've run a few uh panels at conventions
The first one I did was at necocon, which is why I went to necocon that year because
Me and this guy named uh, what who? Oh, sorry. I just said that makes sense as to why you went to this one
Yeah, yeah, um, it was like 2010. I think and it was me and this guy named pats who is another anime blogger
And uh, we ran a panel called
Released and relinquished shows that had been licensed and dubbed in english, but no one paid attention to them
So yeah, it was just like a you know, it was just a recommendation panel
Which that's another thing that like at the time kind of made sense
But now it's like why would you ever want recommendations?
There's there's the internet has entire websites dedicated to anime recommendations
You don't need a panel not that it would still be a successful panel, but um
The internet's definitely made these things even more obsolete obviously. Yeah, uh, but it was a pretty good turnout for it and
Um, and then of course I've done three panels at brony con
One with tom one with the you know with you guys and and then another one with with just the pcp members
uh
I think that was actually called the horseshoe crew or something that time. It was called the horse cast live dog
Do you guys remember my ancient lumarian questions?
I I remember I I know I've blocked them out
Smurfs too, right? No, no, no, no something far more sinister
He he had like a long question about ancient lumarians that are at uh
That of course I I I basically just relayed to you the history of spirit sign
Science at a horseshoe panel that went on for easily seven minutes
And by the end there's no way it was seven minutes long. I don't believe you and no the entire crowd
Hated me. You know like like is he reading this off his phone?
Why why is it taking so long?
And I just kept going on and on about how like the ancient lumarians are like
Fucking building bunchy like the animal you are
Are fucking behind all my little pony and and how trial at sparkle was like like like an agent of the fucking devil
And it was uh, it was great. I remember your I think it was I think it was you specifically Nate
Uh, you said something along the lines of I don't know. I don't care
Stop good. Oh, thank god
I had enough to do something about it. All right. I remember wanting to kill you
You're so fucking good. I loved there is a video of that of that. Um panel on my channel
I haven't looked it in a long time. So far. I remember anything
I started a lot if I if I had given that one today
I would have been a lot more confident in my assertion of luminary that would have there have been more niggers in
Oh, there would be oh, there would be so oh, yeah
He's really come into his own with the whole
Yeah, uh
I would say I've never liked panels
And then like like I've I've been to maybe five panels and all my like seven cons I've gone to
Uh, they all fucking suck
I've had some of my like
A lot of my best con experiences have been panels like the one uh, charles dunbar gave on kill lock hill that totally changed my opinion of the show
Um, and like I've seen a bunch of wish I could see that panel. I'd like to see that panel
Yeah, I wish it existed somewhere. He was supposedly writing a book of that panel and I don't think it ever came out. Okay. Yeah, but um
So
Yeah, I've been to some that like really changed my opinion of shows or just educated me on stuff
Some are just fun and interesting like uh, there's one dude who always does like a japanese noise panel
Like literally about noise music, which is such a weird fucking obscure thing to do at a con
But he was like this really knowledgeable dude like being in a room with like 40 other guys
And listening to fucking noise music is a surreal and hilarious experience
Um that I highly recommend you know why I fear every panel I go to it's because I I've mentioned this before
I don't trust congoers to not embarrass themselves
And I am such a wonderful sensitive human being that when other people humiliate themselves
I feel humiliated so I can't I can't abide cringes. Thankfully. I've gotten I guess so I've gotten really good at both
I mean, there's certain people who do panels like charles dunbar the guy who did that kill out kill panel
He goes to like he gets invited to like 13 cons a year and does like five panels per con
So like he it's practically a job for him
So for someone like that like you know, they're gonna put on a good panel. It's good. You know, I'm not talking about him
I mean when well, I mean that's always a possibility
But I just specifically meant when they get questions from the crowd
Those people like the good ones the good panels usually don't do that. Like yeah, thank god
You know the really good the people who know what they're doing will probably have a fully stacked 90 minutes
I mean, there's a lot of panels that are an absolute garbage fire
Even at like ozacon because it'll be people who don't know what they're doing
And they'll get up there and just like either not know their subject or not be prepared or someone doesn't show up
Or something breaks
But i'm pretty good at figuring out which ones those are gonna be because like every year at ozacon
One of my friends will tell me like yeah, we went to that one because you know
It had a hilarious title and it sounded like it would be great
But it turned out they had no idea what they were doing and I was like you could tell that by the description
You know like if it's just a hilarious title, but it does but there's no like indication of who's running the panel or like
You know, uh
Like something something in the description that catches your eye. It's probably not good
God I had something like that at brone con it was like like there was this one panel
But I went to and I could have found out that was bad by the description
It was it like I read the description and it was something like thoroughly analyzing my little pony live or something
Fucking awful like that. I wouldn't anyway see that one coming
Press one if that was the shittiest joke you've ever heard your entire fucking life
I actually didn't see it coming
really
But but you know our panels were like awful. I mean people loved them, but
Literally had no plan for any panel
I tried to put together a plan, but you guys were just like let's just say questions
Let's just say question which frankly was a better idea
So just because the the crowd just wants to hear us talk
They don't give a fuck and we're all funny and we can just riff off of whatever they say, you know
um, yeah, and I think I mean for me personally, I think that
My sense of humor nowhere shines better than in answering questions at a at a convention panel like that
I think that's if when I make videos, they're not funny
On this podcast I hit or miss, but I think I can actually be funny in that situation
Well, whatever I see my favorite panel that I've um, I've ever like seen in a video
setting has always been like ego raptors like
Solo panel where he's just talking about stuff to a crowd. He's he's standing around with a mic
He is good at that. He's good at that. That was just it's just such a night
It made me like the idea of panels and want to be on a panel by myself just say yeah, yeah
I'm just chatting with it. I mean, I knew it would be like I gotta admit
He handled that panel like a pro the way that ego raptor runs favorite videos of his the way that he runs his panels
Is exactly how I tried to do so like I mean with the with the two that we did as a group
Then there was a lot more like spread out as a group. It's kind of difficult
Yeah, because everyone wants to say something but the one that was just me and tom
I mean, you know
At all the panels. I usually am the one who does the most talking but the one with me and tom in particular was like
It was pretty much me in the crowd and then tom offering thoughts sometimes about you know, like when I asked him
Tom, what do you think about this?
But it was great fun to do that and I'd love to do yeah
Doing solo panels is super fun and I'd love to do it all the time
Just imagine how important you feel as the only guy up there, you know, yeah, I'm interested in it mostly for the power trip
That's what I want. That's what I want the power trips a lot of fun and just the feeling well
Because like what what I think makes it what what makes it fun for me is that it's an opportunity to simultaneously
Like
Say to the crowd, you know
Hey, you guys are all great and I really appreciate all of you while also just ragging on them incessantly
Because that's what I like when people ask me a dumb question. I will I will make them
I'll I'll answer it in such a way that's like you're a dumb
But thankfully you've given me the tools for me to use my genius to make this interesting, you know
That's the right way to do it. Yeah, it's uh, it's fun
Great
Uh, and and I've I've been um
Recently I've been invited to some conventions
There's one in particular in new jersey and they want me to come up. It's in like
I don't know
April or may or june, maybe june
Then they're like they want me to come up and they they they said we want you to do like two or three panels
and I was like, uh
Is anyone else presenting at this convention?
Um, but yeah, they were they're offering to like, you know pay for my trip and everything to to do that
It might be worth and I'm considering it. I haven't decided yet because I don't know what I'm gonna be doing in june
Like I might not even live in virginia by june. Um, that that's true
So, you know what though, can I just say on that point?
There's one thing I didn't mention that is actually by far the most important thing to me about conventions
Uh, and so I would definitely go to that and any other ones that were offered to me
Because of my dream I've had since I was a very young man
And it's not it's not a lofty dream
But it is a dream
I've had consistently for most of my life and it's to fuck a cosplayer girl at an anime convention
I will do whatever it takes to make that happen at some point in my life if you want to get into fucking
stories of fleeting but very deep and real love
Uh that I've had with women at conventions who I did not speak to my god
Like I have I have a lot of like vivid memories of women
I immediately fell in love with
Here's one that we all shared uh, at least most of us who are in our remember our spot at brony con
We all looked down to get collectively
I know jesse was there and I think most of the people here were we looked down and there was just a raven
From teentines cosplayer sitting there alone with a book open just reading a book on the side of the open convention hall
But not bothering anybody just quietly being there perfectly cosplaying raven
Just being by yourself reading a fucking book and we all instantly fell in love with there
All of us together in the same way nate that you were like always wondering
Uh, I should have gone on dance with that girl that I I was always like remember that and I'm like
I should have just gone up and said that's a really it's really cool that you're reading like that
Why didn't we damn nothing nothing is cooler to me than method cosplayers. They are truly the best
There's this one dude um who
One year at the karaoke. There's this guy who was dressed as kamina and he had like the perfect build for it
He was like an he was a you know a perfect kamina cosplayer and he was like dancing and raving
He's saying the masinger opening
Yeah, which is awesome and he was like totally down for everyone else's stuff
He was like being this hype guy right then the next year. He shows up as uh, dr. Frankenstein from soul leader
Again a perfect spot on cosplay and he even had the he had the giant
I don't know if you know Frankenstein, but he has like a screw coming out of his head that he twists
Yeah, it's got the big bolt. He actually had that and was able to turn it and make clicking sounds when he turned it
He put a hole in his fucking brain
Goddamn, okay, additionally he he had he was insisting insistently sitting in chairs backwards because that's how stein sits
Yeah, and I was just like the fucking dedication like in this guy's mind
He just is dr. Stein and it was so legend like it because it made me realize that like him acting so hype the year before
Was because he was Kamina like you know because this year he wasn't being hype
He was just like sitting on the chair, you know being that man's name was dustin hoffman
What a legend of cosplay
That's the first method actor who came to mind that was the first one I could think of that's right
Also could have gone with christian bale or whoever the fuck you want. Uh, why not uh the guy from
The guy with the mustache from there will be the guy who killed himself
Uh, uh, heath ledger heath ledger. Yeah, there you go. And that man's name was yon renkowski the actor jace w commons
Yes, it was him all along austin
Uh, that is the the the whole method acted thing
Like that the fact that people can do that is the reason i'm i'm always apprehensive of being a cosplayer because nobody likes
You know somebody putting the costume together and it being yeah, it's pretty good pretty good
And then you go up to them and they're just some fucking actually actually
There's an entire uh giant legion of of people who dress up as a they dress up really well
But don't act the part at all and it's called fucking women every fucking time
They can't act a for shit. They just they're just
Talking about slots. What what what about the raven cosplayer we were just talking about she's completely
I don't respect her or women. No, it's uh, she she's a hero. She's a hero
I don't respect sexy cosplay girls outside of wanting to fuck them
And that is what I will use them for throughout my life. So, you know, I appreciate that on that basis
How much of okay, I feel like I might be the ultimate convention creeper, but it's all on the download
It doesn't hurt anybody so it's okay. That's fine because because you know
You always hear these stories about women who like have guys like all over them and stuff and like
Predator tactics and they're always taking now at a convention
Everyone takes pictures of cosplayers and I've always been super duper shy
About like asking to take someone's picture. I don't know why I just feel really like I know that everyone expects it
And yet I feel like I can't do it
And usually I'll just jump in when someone else is taking the picture
But there's particularly been cases where I saw a girl in a cosplay and I was so in love with her that I felt
It would be wrong of me to take a picture because I secretly am doing so because I'm nefariously in love with them
So I won't I get even more afraid
But man, I'm just I'm running through the like rolodex of images of like I remember that girl's cosplay
I'm just curious. Well the very first girl
I remember just being absolutely in love with based on their cosplay
Was the first year at otacon because we were in the line going into the building
And this girl just like kind of like fastly walked past
And it was a really small asian girl in a boogie pop costume
And I was I at the time boogie pop was my favorite thing in the universe and no one knew about it or talked about it
Most people didn't even know that boogie pop is actually a you know, a little girl who or a young teenage girl
You know a small one so conventions are a place where you go to fall in love as a young man
It's really true and as an old man
Every year every year at karaoke broken man as well
Every single year at karaoke some girl will get up and do a performance with so much heart that i'm like
Why am I not I actually do like this with with the younger ones when it was just cosplay
That was more of like this fleeting sense of brilliance of like
Oh my god, if if only but when it comes to the karaoke
I actually legitimately feel like i'm an idiot for not talking to those girls
I had this woman tied up in the back of my car driving away right now
Yeah, if only I was reenacting the stan music video with this girl right now
But but like with like last like for instance last year at otakon
There was this girl who did like a cosplay performance and it wasn't that she was like
Unbelievably cute or anything. She just did a really great karaoke performance and I was like I can't imagine a more perfect
Like like legitimately a more perfect match for me than a girl who does passionate anime karaoke
Like this is literally the kind of person I should be seeking out to date and of course I didn't say anything
Uh, and I I regret it weak man. It's a different kind of regret
There's that there's that that that hopeless romantic regret of I saw like the you're beautiful
And I saw your face in a crowded place
And I don't know what you know, and he kills himself at the end of the song
That is more like the early cosplay stuff. This is more like. Yep. Wow. I'm a fucking idiot. Why didn't I talk to this girl?
um the feeling I think that's sort of the uh, the the the digivolved form of this emotion, you know, it's leveled up
To use the term that you people will understand
I I know what you're this has only happened once to me before and just as that zoro whoever
Cosplay changed Nate's life
There's one cosplayer that changed my life and and jumpstarted me into the era of my life
I like to refer to as the overly sentimental gay asshole not seinfeld era
Okay, okay, I wish I will not go into detail about uh, just hope it had happened
Could you tell us what the cosplay was? Uh, no
Okay
I have um, I think I know I've seen a few
Digi digi, dude, if you talk, I'm gonna I'm not I'm gonna act. I'm gonna actually pee my pants
Don't do it. Did you don't do it? I won't
Yeah, okay. Yeah, I've uh, yeah, I haven't really um
Like had a an amazing experience with a cosplayer
I mean, I really like a lot of them and it's been like cool to see that some people are actually really good
But the moment I see a risk of cosplayer, I will not waste a second. I will go up to her and I will say
Uh, uh, you're you're cool or something
Because good that'll that'll be my my ultimate pickup line. You're all
Becky, you're cool. You are cool with just the letters. You are cool
I'll say it like that and then they'll she'll hug me. Oh, what a what a dream
What a fantasy that is, you know, cosplayers are real hugs sluts, you know, they're past that shit out easy
Oh, oh, they they can't wait for that. Let's go to anime for right now
You know, it's kind of a shame because it used to be back in the day that cons were a lot more like physical
Like yeah, glomp me people used to go glomp me sign. Yeah, they used to be glomping
They used to be the yaoi paddles where they were hitting girls just walk around hitting people with paddles and I don't know
And now there's all these cosplay is not consent. Well, which it totally is so that's bullshit
Boy, is that actually a thing? That is exactly a thing. Yeah, that's that's that unfortunately is a very real thing
Well, I wonder if it's actually real that this was a problem like did people assume cosplay was consent
That's news to me. There there is a lot of harassment of of a of female cosplayers at conventions
I get that but I and male actually
Okay, I I don't mean to to go over the top here
But aren't they I mean I'm talking about harassment in the sense of like calling to them in like reasonable ways
No, I'm talking about harassment kind of asking for it
I'm talking about like actual physical harassment does happen a lot of conventions. Well, that's not okay. Yeah, that's yeah
But unless they're dressed like a slut in which case
I mean
Unless they're brisket. Yeah, and in my very complex and not useful
Notes that I jotted down that don't bode well or don't don't translate well into this type of podcast
And therefore I wasted about 30 minutes. I wrote down the words uh slut in all caps at least five times
Yeah, is there anything else at your notes you want to read off? I think we're kind of winding down here
Well, see my my my notes were just ever kind I've gone to and how I felt at each con and the interesting parts of it
Hmm
So that sounds a little detailed, but we get the gist of how positive of why you enjoyed them
And how it's a little bit different than our experience in general. I mean, there's some weird themes
Yeah, you reminded me. I wanted to talk about uh a way that cons
Um have started evolving for me. I'm trying to make them evolve
And it didn't work out as well as I wanted it to at this last note to con
But um, so I know a lot of older congoers and eventers like there's this one
This one anime blogger called omoe kane who's like probably in his late 30s now and he's like a he's a lifetime eventer
He goes he like flies to japan just to go to events and stuff got a lot of money, right?
Goes to lots of shit and um those guys always talk about how like when you go to a convention
It's not really about just going to the convention. It's about going to that city and doing stuff there, you know
and baltimore
You know where the convention center is is right in the middle of like a big strip
That's like famous for its restaurants and stuff and and bars
So like at this past otacon
I really went there with the intention of like i'm not going to hang out at the convention center most of the time
I want to go
And uh, you know go go out and eat go to all these fancy places because I'd been going to this con since 2008
You know, it's always in the same place and I never really been to all the places around that are like all the tourist attractions
Like all that stuff is advertised on the website for otacon
You know, they really push the idea that like hey, you're in baltimore try the crab
We're famous for our crab, you know go to go to all these different places
I tried the crab and then you were betrayed by that restaurant
Well, not only was I betrayed by yeah, we tear in a dog was one of the worst restaurant experiences ever
That was a brony con wasn't it or yeah, I like that place. I don't know. Yeah, we went there brony con
They were fine when we went at otacon. It was absolutely garbage
But then like
Aside from that there were two major issues that I didn't account for and that made it not worth it to go to all these places
Because I didn't care about the money. I had money. I had saved up a bunch
I was like i'm gonna go and spare no expense go to all the interesting stuff the two big miscalculations were one
I was the only person with money
So I had no one. Oh, that's the word. I just went to all these places alone
You know like yeah, and number two is that it was like the hottest day in recorded history
For like one of the days of the con so like
And and also just that baltimore stretch is it's not a great it's it's honestly
It's too spread out
There's too much space in between all the all the restaurants and stuff and none of them are that great
It's it's overhyped, you know
I remember one point. I like walked a mile in the fucking
Unbelievable heat, you know sweating fucking balls and I went to some crab place and
It was I don't even really like crab like I I was I was hoping that by eating like such a high class crab
That it would be different. But no, it's just crab, you know, so
I was like well
Fuck fuck these restaurants. Fuck this town. Fuck baltimore. I'll go somewhere else
But I do think that's a very interesting way to explore conventions is to not just worry about the convention
And I kind of learned more of that from brony con where each year at brony con
I only spent like probably half of it in the con spent a lot of time in hotel rooms with other people, you know
Unfortunately not having sex like no fucking panels didn't even yeah
No, we literally other than the panel we ran we did not attend a single thing at the last brony con right to
We just sat around
And it was a much better time for it. Yeah
Uh
Although that year their fucking was no seating anywhere like we spent the whole first day just looking for where to sit
Our spot too, which was fucking bullshit. Yeah, it was retarded
That was that was a huge part of why I didn't want to go back because I was like, you know
It'd be one thing if we were all going to go and sit, but there wasn't even anywhere to sit
We were like fucking roaming around looking for where we could fucking hang out
That's that was fucking garbage
But yeah, I hang out in a lot of hotel rooms hang out with people, you know
Stuff like like what what bunny hop just did at magfest where he made that video about the sony playstation
Where it's like, you know, he got to go like into this very exclusive room where they endo playstation. Yeah, that's what I meant
the nintendo playstation and
You know and there's video of like him doing vr with jeff and shut shit like that
Like that's that's fun stuff at conventions that people don't take into account when they think about it
And that that's the element. I'd like to explore more
Um going to conventions in the future, especially the money spending part
Like it's a great way to just treat it as a vacation and go to a bunch of places
Unfortunately, if all your friends are fucking poor then uh, you're gonna do all that stuff alone
Which is you know, when you when you go to an expensive restaurant by yourself
All you're thinking about is how much money you're spending on the food
Like there's no like that's that's all it is. It's like I sit down and I go
This is a 16 dollar crab cake. I'm about to spend 16 dollars
So all I'm thinking while I'm eating it is is this worth 16 dollars? This probably isn't worth 16 dollars, you know
Yep, um
Yeah, dude, uh
Conventions are great
All this talk about how you don't like conventions just convinced me even more that I love conventions
I mean, I wasn't trying to present the idea that I don't like conventions just that as I've gotten older
My what I get out of them has changed and I definitely think I will enjoy them again
If I go about them differently going with the the crowd
I've been going with where we all just kind of split up and go our own ways is not fun
Uh, you know, that's why we're gonna stick together bro. I'm gonna be on your ass like your dick is fucking gay
Which is very
Both of the both of those can be preceded with the adjective very and and also, uh, I don't I don't know
Where your hotel is muchy and relative in relative to the convention right next to it
Yeah, I highly advise
Everyone if you're going to a con plan ahead get a fucking room near the convention. It's so much vastly superior
It's like a whole different world when you're close enough
And this this past otacon we tried to do that think think about how you're gonna get girls back to your room guys
Plan your route plan out how you're gonna do that shit
I mean even beyond that just like like every year at these conventions
We would always get a a hotel that's like 10 minutes out of town and like you can't hang out and drink all night because like
Some if you're especially for sharing a room if even one person gets tired
You know, then it's like the rest of us are holding that person like forcing them to be at the con while we do our shit
You know and then
You know, we all have to leave at a certain time
There's sort of like a curfew and you can't just hang out and enjoy it at your own pace or anything
And then like this past year we got a place that was like close enough to the convention that it could be walked
But it was it was a fucking
40 minute walk. So it was not fun
Um, especially in that heat like we ended up, you know, my friends mostly ended up taking like lift uh to and from the convention
It was like, oh, yeah, that's what I would you know, it wasn't even worth it
um
To walk that distance so like by all means get a place nearby
It makes it so much easier to hang out and enjoy the uh atmosphere
So, okay, uh, Gabe, do you have any closing thoughts on your uh, convention?
We're only an hour and 36 minutes into this
All right, but I want to go to questions because I feel like we've explored this pretty thoroughly by this
Yeah, I want to talk about fucking brony con
You already talked about brony con. Go ahead. I like brony con. If you have anything worth saying, then go ahead and say it
Brony con 2013
boring digi-bur
crazy
uh next note brony con
horror uh
I love ben sainte. Yep actual activities. I told you met him, right? No
Yep, that's where I met him the first thing that ben's ever said to me
Uh, uh, I was I like I shook hands with digi
I was like, hey and then like like he moves out of the way like out of out of like the camera like view
Like the eye camera and then I like pan over to this fucking retard and his name is ben sainte
And he shakes my hand that time he was named phantom horn. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, and and he just says hey
I've heard a lot about you
And I haven't heard anything about him, but then I found out brony con 2015
Hey, you know when I uh you this might amuse you to know munchie at that time when ben told me about you
I thought you were way over hyped. I thought you
That's right, buddy. What does that mean exactly? What what?
How is he hyped exactly?
This is my art that I'm presenting to you for you to interpret however you wish
So you were over hyped. There you go. Like like like over hyped
I don't remember ever
I'll explain the joke I guess because ben was really excited about munchie and thought he was really cool and I was like
Oh, yeah, ben was definitely ben ben was in love with munchie from a from an early point. It's been a big cheerleader of yours
It mutual mutual brony con 2015 end of rome. I hate romans
Second note. I hate mlp number note number three. I love victor slash ben
All right, that's the end of my notes
Is that really all of them? That's all the notes you had that you well, I had more but I I cut out the other ones
Okay, I only did the ones probably shitty anyway. I'm gonna I'm gonna piss on the pcp
Okay, anyway, we interrupted gibb. He was gonna say some some bullshit. I mean
No, no this this is not real
This is fake
All the things that could interrupt me. No
No
He's pouring water. He's pouring water
I'm honestly not
Nate you brought this upon your fucking self. I don't believe you. There's no way that we've devolved to this level on my fucking show
Munchie, I won't have it still going. What could you possibly that's too long? Yeah, you blew it buddy
You went too long now. I know that you're pouring shit. Do you want me to send you a picture, Nate?
Do you really? Yeah, send me a goddamn picture of you pissing on your computer. Okay?
Yeah, snapchat me bro snapchat
I really hope that was into a bottle or something. Oh my god. We we have hit rock bottom folks
I can't decide if I believe that was real piss
No, I don't believe it for so long
All right. Well, he's a big boy. He is a big boy. I'm gonna send it to you, bro
Oh, send me send me bottle that piss and email that to me so I can see you're all over my phone. Hold on
Okay, anyway, we were supposed to be listening to fucking gibb talk about something
Take it away, buddy. I don't think I can top that
Anything could top that that was rock bottom
Okay, all right
I'm gonna go to
I don't know. What was the anime expo where there's homestuck stuff? Yeah
I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm gonna find and talk to a human being called brisket and I'm gonna say you're cool and I'm gonna
She's not a human being hopefully
Oh, oh, yeah. Well, I'm gonna troll an alien girl alien girl
And uh, I'm gonna buy a homestuck thing and that's gonna be my future for cons
And or going with jeff to magfest to meet real cool guys
The good news is there's lots of risk of cosplayers at least there were
How how long is hippo? Do you think like what what's the timetable on this plan?
Like could you actually afford to do any of this in the next year?
um in the I mean I
Technically I can but it would be eating into stuff that I kind of want to save up for like
In case I you know die. Yeah, because I'm probably going to anime expo with munchie this year
So there is a room out there. You can join
In july
Yeah, some of plain journeys are really yeah, you could room with us. There'd be no problem
I could just have to hear me piss a lot. Munchie has just apple juice, dude
I know you're a big apple juice guy. You poured apple juice into that glass. What happened? No, no
Maybe you should have a taste Nate. It looks pretty fuck. It looks like piss, dude
I think he actually pissed although that cup looks too small for the amount of time that piss went on for
It's not there would have been less. Oh, you're actually looking at it. You gross gross
It's just apple juice, dude. Don't worry. Don't worry. He made sure to post this in the ben saint chat, by the way
Yeah, he sure did
sure did
uh anyway
Maybe I could come to anime expo. I would need to make a bit more of a patreon buck
Yeah, or something go to youtube.com slash patreon slash louis batton
I guess
Give me money for that
So I can go find briska and live my dream
Of saying hello. My briska's living her dream. My briska's living her dream. My briska's living her dream. That's an old good meme
Um, yep. Good old meme old good. Are we ready to answer the uh questions here?
I think so. Uh, by the way, I just want to reiterate my point everybody. I still think it's a good
I think that's a wise policy. It's for children conventions are for children
Take your kids somewhere if you want them to be indoctrinated into that culture and to have some crazy experiences because they're kids
And they don't know what real life is like yet. There you go. Okay. All right. Here's some questions. Um
Now actually there were some pretty good questions on here as I was looking through
Oh, where's the one I was looking at? Um, oh, okay. Here's a very specific question
But I liked it. I thought you might like this digi. This is by uh at monkey away
Uh procrastinators. Uh, what should I listen to while I play dark souls 3 now that I've run out of tpc
Podcasts in digi bro after dark content the biggest problem in the universe and then that's what I was thinking
Which is what I listen to almost exclusively while playing dark souls
There you go monkey. Perfect. Um, uh, give suggestion. No, no, it doesn't matter
Okay, there you go. I'll listen to dick show or biggest problem in the universe. Uh, okay. What have we got here?
Here's a terrible question. Uh, if you could choose any youtuber to survive the apocalypse with who would it be?
No duplicate answers. Uh, that anime snore
You would how fast would you fucking die and you would be no wait movie bug because there's plenty of
That's smart. I could survive for quite a while on that. Uh, I'm gonna choose
I'm gonna pick the only other human who's responsible that I know other than myself
So because we'll probably actually figure out what we're doing
That's true. I would choose. Um, I would choose lacy green
Oh, because she has those because she's a because she's a dirty slut and she's got wide birthing hips
So it could re could quickly
Create a new human race and that that would be a I'm going. I'm she's a breeder. She's my breeder is what I'm picking
Why did I stick? This is why I can't get a girlfriend. I I only think about my stupid guy friends
I'd ever think about women out there in the world
That I could be trapping on island with me. I couldn't think of like a I couldn't think of like a youtuber
Who is a female we're trapping in a post-apocalyptic sniper wolf? She's
It doesn't even matter like the answer should have just been any female
And if you yeah, it's just the only two of you. Yeah, that'd that'd be the thing to do. Uh, okay. Let's see. What else do we get?
I didn't get to answer you fucking. Oh, I'm sorry. You fucking whore. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Please go ahead
It would be any female. Obviously you didn't let me have my input
Okay
You could you could sex change ben saint and bring him. Oh
Um, no, that would work out. Well, no, that'd be that would be against nature. That'd be against god
Oh my god, there's so much piss in my fucking there's this one person asking these incredibly emotional questions
I can't but she went so far for that piss joke that it's like ruined like he's now
uncomfortably sitting covered in piss and like
It really is really fucking sad like how much like piss didn't go into the
Audio only piss joke that he could have faked easily
He went all out
To me like to me. I know it's real and to the listeners. I know they know it's real too. So just imagine me doing it
Hey, um, this person
Uh, okay. Well, I'm gonna answer this one real quick. Uh at ripe. Oh god, ripe
Rony pasta
Yeah, I think that's it ripe rony pasta asks opinion on the rants series. It's the best
Sengoku rants the genius game, uh, the rants like Sengoku rants, um
Gay japanese one through seven. It's all these it's these these crazy sex arrow games where you do awesome shit
It's a game about trying to rape your way through ancient japan
Yeah, but in that universe rape is like a handshake. So it's great. No one loves it. So yeah, I played, uh,
15 minutes of it
I played up until when the gameplay starts and then I looked at it and I went
I don't fucking comprehend this at all and I quit it. Yeah, it's fucking brutal
But I have one of the hardest games I've ever played. I have a hug pillow of usugi kenshin
Didn't know who she was for like years
I I got it because it was it was it was like I bought a manga magazine from japan that was it was only 30 dollars
Like after shipping and it came with the free dakimakura. So it was like the best deal in the world
I'd buy that. Um, yeah, me and my friend donson both bought it
We both bought the same same set because he just like told me about it. He was like, hey free dakimakura
And I was like, well, shit. I I just I only wanted it for weeb cred like of course
I mean most of what's in my room is not here because I like it. It's here because I
Because I wanted to have an otaku room
Uh because back in the day that was like a thing that they would people would post these images of the otaku
Room, which is like no white space anywhere. It's all anime posters and shit
And I always thought that was super cool and I wanted to have it so and you're you're carrying that toward this very day
I'm starting to work on the ceiling. I've put up a line of posters, but they look like shit and they keep falling
So and it's and I and I'm realizing that it's going to take even more posters than I thought to cover my whole ceiling
So, uh, I gotta do it before I move
To note on that poster things and it goes slightly back to the cons
Another reason why I actually like conventions is because I live in literally like minimalist like a painting
Like I there I have nothing in my room. I have no possessions
Why I'm looking up at at my at my like the only things that decorate my room
As a like like the only thing that isn't playing white walls is an american flag and like two undertale posters
I don't understand what fills the hole in your life left by not having any human companionship if you don't have stuff
How do you
Live myself and piss and
Yeah, how'd you get the piss out through all those hot flies?
Well, they joined in too. Oh, okay
Munchies as do you have less stuff than davoo in his room?
Uh, you know what? I actually have one more poster than he has
Impressive. Yeah impressive. Uh, okay. Let's move along here
Uh, here's a bunch of questions by this guy, but let's only answer one decent one by at gypsy gypsy
Who are your smash bros mains and why he said no, okay? Okay. No, no, shut the fuck up. This is my this is my question
This is my question
Okay, when I was a little baby boy when I little when I was a little baptist when I was a little baptist boy whipper
I loved curbie and so I played curbie. I got really good as curbie. This was in brawl
I I played melee a lot, but I didn't play a melee a lot
I played brawl a lot and I played brawl a lot
So in brawl, I really like to play curbie and then smash fork him out and I was like, hmm
curbie definitely is the worst character in this entire fucking game
And I'm really upset, but uh, you know, I really like curbie
So I'm gonna I'm gonna stay like a curbie curbie like a curbie curbie guy
Not like a not like the guy curbie, but as in like the greater like expanded star wars universe curbie
Uh, so I played ddd. Uh, I know how to play dd a lot. I like dd. He's a good guy. He's really slow
I'm slow and not in the mental way
I'm the fastest guy around but I'm slow as in I'm really fat and I can't move my limbs
And I also piss way too much because I'm full of piss
Anyway, and also I really like mute 2 because mute 2 is like really good in that game
And he's also fun
Um, Ganondorf is fun because he's like big and like you do like fucking has like a huge dick like huger than my like forearm
He's like a huge like horse dick and um, um, um, um, yes, I love super smash bros. Please. Um, I'm I'm honestly I can drooling
I'm drooling right now
All right, let's keep it together. Uh, Ganondorf's pretty good for I think he's fun to play but uh
Oh, he's fun to play
But if a tierless or any way to view the game then he's like he's like the worst
I I cry tears. I was gonna say I have a tear on my cheek every time I talk about tierless. You're right. You're right
You're right. I you are right. I can't even like I played smash. I know in smash one
I played Pikachu
But you know that game's ancient and grappling with the onset of menopause and uh, what?
It's a line from billion mandy, uh in in super special is melee
I think I played Pikachu briefly and then link or something. I don't know all I know is eventually I found
Samus and I've been playing samus for like eight years and she's the only character I'm any good with
And uh as as the people here can attest to am I not actually a pretty okay samus player
Yeah, it was it was funny when I played you on digi bros
I expected you to be like literally the worst player in the entire fucking world
Yeah, everyone thinks I'm just garbage at all video games
But I've been playing samus for so fucking long that I can actually do it
I still beat you. It was easy. Well, it helps that I have the way I play here is different from
I think how anybody else plays smash at all. So it's yeah, I think it's use or something
What I'm saying is I think it's just it's not that I'm great
It's that the way I play is so different that it takes getting used to and once much he probably figured out the patterns
He was able to deal with it
Smash is all like like you could go up against like one of the best players in the world
And if you just play like a retard slash differently, yeah, as as he's known to do then yeah
Because I just I just I fucking spam missiles and jump around like an asshole and that's how I uh, all right
there's acting of
Yeah, um, my my main since uh
Nintendo 64 days was always been samus and kirby because kirby could you know when he gets hit
You can fly it a lot
So that made it easy to get back to the stage and also samus because the up b was ridiculous in that first game
And also I hate link because my brother's always played link and that's why I don't like legends zelda as much as the metroid series
Yeah, I
Unironically have the exact same emotion my friend
I have like okay. My friends are divided into two types of people
The fucking assholes and the even worse fucking assholes
The first fucking assholes are the people who are like actually good at the game and they all play link
I'm serious. Literally everyone gets guess guess who my main is
Guess who my main is
Toon Link
Yes, to link to one. Yeah, I know
I know he's way worse and and and and the other assholes and people who play samus
So it's it's funny that we have two fucking degenerates in this call right now
You know
To be on to link was the guy that I've played the most over the years
I I have not played him much in smash 4 and now I almost exclusively play
Peach is my probably number one most played
Jigglypuff who I love to play so cool and now I play a lot of cloud because those are like s tier
Characters are you telling me jigglypuff is s tier wait wait wait. Yeah, hungry. Hungry box fucking
Is like the champion of the world just because
In fucking melee, not in smash 4. Smash 4 fucking jigglypuff sucks
Yeah, we're I'm talking about
I forgot to mention pacifist donkey kong is also
I was gonna I was gonna ask you to I was gonna ask you to explain that but then I remembered we do it in the smash
Let's play that I haven't uploaded yet. Yeah, which is
Funnily enough like during radcon. I actually edited and uploaded that video
But the the audio sync was like 30 seconds off
So I was gonna read you know like re-sync it and I just haven't gotten around to it yet
So that video has videos been uploaded on private for like three weeks and I just haven't fixed it
But it will be there. There is a like two hour long smash bros
Let's play with all the pcp boys in it. Yeah, it was
Uh, let's let's move along here. We don't got time to spend smash bros all day here. Um, yes, we do
What okay by on we on me once again. Hey there on we
Uh, what is one medium you want to create in but probably never will
Oh comics uh, what uh, just one just pick one. Let's not fuck around anime
Anime yeah, okay. There you go. Honestly honestly like
Uh, modern art sculpture because I've always been like really good with my hands
But the idea of just doing that is a career. Oh, baby. He's good with this
Does does architecture count as a uh art form? Yeah, sure. Why not?
I've always had like a hard on for architecture
But it's not something I have like any because it's it's all math and I hate math
So like there's no chance I will ever do anything with architecture, but I think it's super cool
Yeah, if anybody knows um anish Kapoor the guy who did that giant like mirror thing in some city and
And some other cool things. He's like uh an inspiration when I was in art
Do studying art
Is this the mirror thing that like caused fires on people as they were walking home?
It looks like a big beam that you can walk under and it's just a big mirror
Cool. Oh, I know that you must have seen. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, of course
No, he's a famous guy. Um, he does lots of really cool sculptures like that and I've always wanted to be like a
Like like low-key wanted to be a big sculpture person making really cool things like that because he's one of those those fine artists
Who like who is actually making stuff that's interesting and not just like a
Something that's really delicate and has to be inside
Behind a glass case that's boring
Like he makes huge structures that the the london 2012 olympics has a giant red tower that he built and designed cool
Yeah, that's sick. Oh
Yeah, yeah, yeah, uh, I want to get into but probably never will do anything with my voice including podcasts
You blew it mind she you blew that one
Well because blew that horn. Yeah, see the thing is I like I don't it's not that I dislike my voice
But I don't I don't think it's very versatile
And I would like to like sing. Well, no, I wouldn't want to sing. I don't want to do anything. I'm never mind
I'm looking at that red tower and it looks like a roller coaster like crumpled into a ball
Apparently there is like a slide that you can actually go down in that. That's pretty cool
Hey, um, does did the terrorist axe count as an art form because if so, oh my god, I would be so into that
That's just like that guy from Naruto the guy who thinks explosions are out and he makes things a little mouth. Oh, yeah, that guy
Deidara, Deidara, whatever that guy's name. Yeah, I don't think I made it that far into Naruto
Um, okay, I got katsuki. I got two more questions. I think here's one another one
But this is this is a good one by at gypsy gypsy. Um name one good thing to come from the pcp
I just helped me dude. I got under Taylor 587
The undertale, you know what?
You got it there, but and I think I think in general the the the royal rumble the royal rumble is pretty great
We got so much art and shit from that. It was it was great. It's the best video we've ever made
Also, also the new meme of me pissing on the pcp
Which will be a meme. I've already first seen it
That's also another great thing that's come out. It'll start a chain reaction every podcast that anyone is in somebody has to pee
I'll always be the one to do it until you pee in spite of being someone who loves peeing outdoors and in strange places
I could never pee into a bottle. It's just uh, it's a hang up. I can't do it
That was the first time I've ever done it in like six years
I've told that story about how my roommate pissed in bottles when I was in college, right? That's yeah
We don't need to go into that shit. Uh, do you think Tom my nightmare is sick?
Um, okay, you know, if you don't know a bottle just piss into your mouth. That's much more efficient
I was gonna say one more, but here's a question that I didn't see and I got to address this one by at joestar 93
Nate, how good was that one piece movie that you were tweeting about and let me tell you buddy
That one piece movie that I was watching tweeting about earlier. Um, movie six. Yeah, like baron okutsu
Omatsuri and the island of mystery or some bullshit like that movie number six
Uh, it was great. It was by far the best one piece movie
I've seen everyone was right. It is great
Uh, and to answer other questions that people were asking me
Now's as good a place as any because I kind of wanted to talk about this and thought I'd never get a chance
But here one has fallen into my lap
Uh, yes, I did watch it because I was reminded of that movie's existence by super eyepatch wolf
Um, uh, and and watching his new video about one piece today
Did not love his video and I watched that movie only because I was reminded that it exists
And do not want cucks like him to lord the fact that they've seen that movie
Literally no one can any longer
I care, right?
And uh, and by the way, he's dead wrong. That is not a great place to get in one piece
To start from chapter one of the manga. Don't listen. He's an idiot. Okay. Let's move on and last question
Now this guy actually asked a couple and they were all like full of pathos and were
Really god like I when you hear this you'll you'll know like where this guy was when he asked these questions
So this is a rato
Or uh
At intrepid feline. Okay. Here's the first question. How hard is it for you guys to meet new people?
And before we answer that let me just read his other questions
Next one. What advice do you guys give to trying to make friends?
And then the next one is how talkative are you guys outside of the podcast?
So I'm starting to get the kind of guy that this is and brother brother. I love you and I I want to legitimately
Answer these questions. So, um
Who wants to take any of those? I well I'll I will say that the reason we talk to each other
Is not because we're good at meeting new people. It's because we like the content that each other makes
Right. So that's that's one way to talk to people. It's just to be someone really good
That doing stuff. I mean if you're trying to if we're talking about on the internet
The best way to meet new people is just like hey, I love your work or uh something
You know or just like go just go to any community anywhere and find someone who has similar interest to you and talk to them
I think making friends on the internet is like a dime a dozen. You can easily do it
It's just about having literally anything to talk about
I don't think this guy needs internet friends though. I mean based on these questions. I can tell this is a lonely individual
I got the sense it was more about you know, like making real friends or human connections in which case you are barking up the
Absolute worst tree you could be barking up at this situation
I haven't met a new person to be an expert
In years
The last like the only times I meet new people are either, you know online like either we meet them through
They're them being great like the last new person I met online is monkey, you know
Right made great videos got in contact with them slowly developed a sort of like hey test the waters
This guy seemed like our kind of guy. He does seem like our kind of guy
All right, let's drag him into the crew and now I've met him in real life. He came by my house cool guy, right?
um as for offline
I only ever meet people if
For some reason someone is assimilated into my friends friends and even then I don't hang out with my own friends anymore
So I've actually not not only have I not met a new person in years
I've actively repelled almost everyone I knew before so like now I'm at probably the least a number of friends
I've ever had is right now
So I just like to say I am in a similar situation right now
Tomorrow in fact I'm going to go to a local pub
Just to see how easy it is to to talk to new people
Meet real people that I can say I mean, it's not like I'm bad at talking
The only way you get good at talking is by you know practice
But the the the act of like going up to a person is completely different from knowing how to talk
As the conversation has got I've truly realized so it's it's it's really just um
I don't know just go into places where people are and eventually something might have I've realized how awful I am at like
Even wanting to talk to people because the other day my mom
My mom's a part of a school of rock program
And they were doing a show a live show at this bar called hot tune out the street for me and like
Basically everyone my mom knows was invited. I didn't know they were all going to be there
But like it was at a bar and so I was thinking hey
I can you know have a few drinks. Maybe I'll talk to someone. Maybe there'll be a girl
I could talk to who knows um, and I wore my fucking giant fur coat because it stands out in school
Alpha's peacocking dog peacocking peacocking in my in my big coat and I had like a glass of wine before going
But it wasn't enough to get me drunk
Unfortunately because I should have just gotten like sourced before I got there
But like I showed up and of course it's mostly my parents's friends and like everyone wanted to talk to me
I got tons of people like commenting on my jacket lots of people, you know my who know me
But I don't know them because you know they all know my work and stuff from from facebook
My parents share my shit all the time especially my raps
So I was getting a lot of questions about like my rap and stuff and I was just like yeah, uh-huh
Oh hi, you know like like actively deflecting everyone and like wanting nothing to do with anybody and I was just like
What am I doing? I just I don't even like like people are actively trying to connect with me
And I am just telling them to fuck off essentially in so many words
Um, so yeah, I am the last person to come through for advice on this. Hey rato. Hey rato
I mean okay much you go ahead go ahead. I'm the best person to come and do a task about this because
Okay, here's we have to understand. I'm the saint like like there is no like real life me
There is no other me. I am like this all the time
However, there is one there is one difference
If you meet me on the side of the street
Then you will realize and you observe my actions and you observe me in my natural habitat
You will learn the meaning of fear
Actually, you will learn the meaning of friendship and charitable actions because I am the nicest person in the entire
Fucking universe. Just just not for the kikes. That's all. You know, that's the one thing
As all the people in this call are right kikes and niggers, you know
Uh, I am like like like no matter even if you're just some random fucking normie
I will I will actively try to be your best fucking friend if I meet you in real life
Like like if you just bump into me or something you're like, oh, hey, I'm I'm a tourist here and redacted
Uh, do you uh, do you know how to fucking kill people? I'll be like, do I ever bro here?
I'm gonna be your dad now. We're gonna kill people together. That's what it's like
Um, well, you have to understand. Okay. Uh, not about me you you you who asking this just act like you're crazy
And act like you are unstable and if you do that people will come in and they will have to be your friend
Or else they'll be scared. They're gonna die or else. They'll be scared. You're gonna kill them
So if you just act like you're going to kill people then people will like you
Well said munchie
Let me I want to comment on this
I feel I feel your suffering here
I know what it's like to be to be lonely and want to make friends and and not be able to communicate very well
Uh, I was like that for a long time and still am in some ways. Um, so I just want you to know
it sounds like
I mean, I feel like I know you that you're a guy if you're watching this podcast
Uh, which clearly you are then I feel like you you fit into kind of this nerdy guy on the internet group
Probably doesn't socialize a lot. Uh, you know by your own volition or by your question
I'm inferring that you're not a very talkative person
I would just highly recommend that you just change your life in such ways and it doesn't have to be drastic
But just try to make changes in your life where you're around more people more of the time
Because really what you're talking about is grinding a skill set of communication
As and like meeting new people
So like just if you can
Try to make changes in your life that put you in contact with a lot of people so that you can you know
Kind of practice grind up your talking skills as fast as possible
And put you in contact with lots of people so that you as fast as possible will meet people that you find a kinship with and like
And I wouldn't really recommend like pursuing internet friendships that much because there's just as human beings
There's just such a there's just such a great benefit to having like contact with people physically and face to face
As opposed to talking online, which can you know cause all kinds of problems
So you know just try to get out there more and and make like small changes
Like go to the library and do your homework there instead of doing it in your room or something like that because you know
There will be people there
Maybe they'll say something and try to push yourself
Little by little to to say things that maybe you don't feel comfortable saying right now
Like maybe complimenting somebody or if someone's got a shirt with something that you like
Like if someone's wearing a fucking death note shirt, dude, get in there. Let him know that it's your favorite anime
You know, it's not a joke like that. That is why I wore
You know, I wore anime shirts my entire like young life and I I just looking back at myself
I know it was that so I would get people to comment on them so I could make friends and and that's a weird thing
People didn't so be the hero who does man. They want to be talked to about that if they're wearing them be empowered
I've never like really worn shirts with like logos and stuff on them because I just generally thought
That's tacky. I'll just wear a t-shirt that is a color. Yeah, and
Nobody comes up to me
But then that one time at brony con where I was wearing the sweet bro and hella jeff shirt a guy
Was playing as dave. Oh look to me
He was also very shy and I didn't really we didn't really approach each other
We were saying hey, you're wearing my stuff and I was like, yeah
my stuff
It was cool is like I'm with you, you know, I'd never really experienced that that much before to expand
That's kind of the magic of cons, you know shared experiences can bloom into friendships, you know to expand on that point
Like don't not just that you should go up and talk to other people if they're wearing something cool
But if someone talks to you make sure you like
That's true. Be prepared for
Because for me I I actually get it's shocking how much I get talked to when I'm out and how little I say in response
Because I'm always wearing something fucking weird something that attracts attention
I go around in a bathrobe and everywhere I go people are like, oh man, you look comfortable, you know
And it's like they're being like genuinely friendly and all I ever do is go like, uh, yeah, you know like
There's very few times that I that I actually go and like
Try to make that into a conversation. It's not hard to do
I all the time when I'm out because you know, I eat out like every day and I'll hear people having
I'll hear people having like just conversations all the time, you know
The other day I was at a at a Filipino restaurant
Someone came in and they're just you know, they're waiting for their food to be cooked
So they just strike up a conversation with the cashier and the two of them are just shooting the shit about whatever
And like if if you talk to someone like that, you know, you might
Become friends with them some, you know, maybe there'll be you'll realize that they're really fun to talk to you
You know, and I went up to the counter and I was standing there and the guy had the guy at the cash register
Who I'd just been listening to have this conversation with some, you know, just some guy
I'm looking and there's a 3ds right there with the majora's mask logo on it and I
And I'm thinking to myself
Just say
What are you playing?
You know, what game are you playing? What are you playing? And I kept thinking it and I didn't say anything and then just left
so
Be in that situation and say what game are you playing because you'll probably have a conversation about video games
And maybe you guys like the same video games
Maybe he wants to you know, give you his xbox gamer tag and you guys can fucking play games together and become friends
And then remember that you live in the same town and you can actually go hang out with them, you know
That's what this is. It's constantly be kind of putting out little
Little constantly be extending little olive branches to people or little, you know friendship offerings
And because eventually someone will take it up, you know
Like I mean the the problem with me and a lot of people like me like being shy is that you think about all these things
You know, you try you go to a place where there are people but you don't end up saying anything you just think
Oh, but what if it doesn't work? It's always about like being
Being prepared to look like a complete idiot. I think is the most important thing for for people
It's just like you know that it's not going to be that bad
But you're thinking it is going to be terrible
Well, and you just got to be you got to be prepared for it to be the worst thing that could ever happen
And like listen like I recommend listening to other people's conversations because when you do so what you'll quickly realize is that
Everything everyone talks about is vapid and retarded and nothing you will say is going to sound dumb
Because everything everyone talks about is totally stupid
Like people just get you know, like that guy having the conversation at the counter. It's just like, you know
Oh, yeah, uh, you know, well this trump guy whoo-ho like yep. Yeah. Yeah. Hey, you know like not even saying words
Just like just emitting sounds from your mouth is enough. It's just about the human connection
They're not having a conversation that's meaningful or interesting
They just want to i'm sitting in a place with another human. Let's you know make it not quiet in here
Like that's all people want you don't have to come on
You don't have to be a charming cool smart funny guy
You just have to be willing to talk and you've you're in you know
Just about togetherness and and feeling like you're in the part of the same community as one another
It's so I just want to leave you with with like an action plan here
Just try to change your life a little bit so that you go out in public
There are people that you could theoretically talk to around you
Uh, and and you know try to make some effort to uh
To reach out to them in in whatever small way that that you can and this I want to emphasize this really is a skill set
So like they were saying it's not going to go perfectly at first
But don't worry about it. Just think about how you're improving and it will lead to better things later on
You gotta grind those rpg stats, bro. That's exactly the way I think about it. You know doing this shit
Uh, just try and hopefully that was helpful and be cool and exactly what already are
Good luck intrepid feeling. I'm gay
Okay, oh, oh, wait, wait. I'm sorry. I have to add on be really really really gay
That's how I that's how I got to the that's how I got to the podcast
Just be like the gayest fucking person possible
Did you you're gay, right? You like that that's worked out for you, right? I'm gay and dead as a matter of fact
It's worked out double for this
Okay, that's enough. All right. Thanks everybody for listening
Be sure to tweet us podcast suggestions or questions like this at tpcrastinators on twitter
And uh, well this will be going up. We'll answer more your questions next week
So uh, be there be square friends and just so you know whenever we're recording these generally on saturdays
We put a little note that says hey send us questions and we respond to them like we just did now
So be there and you know, you'll be available to get your questions answered. All right. Thanks for listening everybody
Thanks everybody for being here and we will see you next time a buh-bye. I piss into a bottle
Yeah
Yeah, uh
I'm supposed to be working right now. I'm supposed to be working right now
But I'm not working
I'm doing nothing
My dick i'm jerking
Myself i'm sucking
I am an asshole. I am a stupid
I've got a deadline
Don't want to do it
What the hell is wrong with me i'm supposed to be
Making money
I'm supposed to be creating funny
Things that the people
Gladly will pay for
Artistic genius. That's what they came for instead. I'm tweeting
Hashtag repeating
That's why there's no heat and holes in the ceiling
Yeah
It's quite the burden
It's a hard knock life
Being a genius