This is the theme song, this is the new theme song, this is the theme song of the show, this is the new theme song, it's the new fucking theme song and this is how it fucking goes.
This is the new fucking theme song of the podcast. The podcast has a new theme song. This is it right here.
This is the new fucking theme. Oh God.
Why am I forsaken?
There's no forgiveness. God does not exist. And if He did, we are abandoned.
He doesn't love us. In fact, He hates us. And He hates me the most.
This is the theme song. Yes, this is the theme song of the whole fucking show. This is it.
If you demanded a new fucking theme song, well here it is. Here's what you get.
Welcome back to another hilarious episode of Doug Funny.
Here we are. We're over here at that old...
That old...
All over his house. Hey, Ben, why don't you sing to us? Why don't you dance for us?
Dear journal, today Porkchop was looking real hot over in his little dog house in the backyard.
I don't know what to do with all these feelings. I can't tell my dad. He's too hot also.
Hi, I'm Doug Funny and I'll see you in hell, fuckers. Doug out.
Just so all the fans know, whenever you go to Ben's house, you know, you're looking for tips.
You're looking to where to find the secret coins for each level, where to find the hidden power-ups.
You go to him and all you can talk about is just Doug Funny. Doug Funny, Doug Funny, Doug Funny.
He's just talking about how much he remits. He laments about how he never got his big shot with Patty Wagon.
And how he never got to have sex with that cartoon character. He just limits how Doug screwed it all up for him.
Pat, the other day I legitimately, me and Crack almost, we were this close to actually putting on some Doug.
He was saying that Doug is like the biggest idiot. He's like, if you watch it again as an adult, you realize that Doug is unbelievably stupid.
I think Crack might be unbelievably stupid.
You think so? I don't know, man. I'm kind of curious. I wonder. I wonder.
Doug fucking organized a band that had like eight drummers. How could a man like that not be a genius?
So did SpongeBob and SpongeBob organize a band that had like eight thousand members.
Yeah. I thought the whole point of Doug was that he's like a severely schizophrenic artist who like hallucinates full-on scenarios around him.
Yeah. Well, I know.
Is fucking Zach from Save by the Bell also like, is he hallucinating or is that real?
Well, the moment that I always remember is that like he has this full-blown like dissociative fantasy of himself like being thrown in jail or something.
Like it shows him like he's in jail and he's holding onto the bars like let me out of jail.
But then it like goes back to reality and he's like standing behind a bike rack like holding onto it like he's like a completely crazy person.
He needs to be locked up.
This episode brought to you by this image of Doug Funney and Patty Mayonnaise on this t-shirt.
Link in the show notes below.
It's a sweatshirt. It's a comfy.
I wonder how I got myself into this situation.
Well, let me tell you, it all started in January 1985 where I bought this sweatshirt, even though Doug came out of the 90s.
Hey, let me tell you about another show, right?
I'm making a new video, right?
It's your own original content, your new show called Fun Dougie.
No, I'm...
Oh, no, no, no. It's actually, it's Fun D as in Fun Dougie.
It's trying to make season three of Doug Funney happen.
Fun to Dougie, everybody.
Hashtag fun to Dougie.
I'm starting a new series which I may abandon.
I may abandon prematurely, but we'll see where I do an episode by episode analysis of the new adventures of Winnie the Pooh.
You're committed now, Ben. You've talked about it.
Well, I'm committed to...
This is your ghost in the shell.
I'm committed to at least two episodes.
I want to at least get to episode four, which won the Humanitas Prize, which is considered the Nobel Prize of American television.
Is that the one with Piglet going crazy?
No, that's the one where Rabbit finds...
What's EO, isn't it? It's cure.
No, it's the one where Rabbit finds the baby bird in the snowstorm.
Oh, my God. Yeah, somehow I knew. Somehow I knew that was the one.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's, man, Rabbit's the best. Rabbit's the best guy who ever lived.
He's a fucking humanitarian. He deserves an award. He deserves a peace prize.
That's true. That's true.
You know, I'm not going to spoil. I'm not going to share my thoughts.
I'm not going to share my thoughts about that episode, which I rewatched the other day.
But, man, it's kind of, you know, they're all really dumb.
They're all dumb to the point of like...
What, the episodes?
No, no, no, the characters. The characters are all dumb to the point that they're not even human.
Well, they're supposed to be childish, right?
They're supposed to be... I don't know. You know, maybe I'm spoiled.
Maybe I'm spoiled on such modern-day classics as My Little Pony and SpongeBob, where the character...
Everyone, please drop PCP fan art of us as the individual Winnie the Pooh characters.
Oh, please make me Eeyore.
Obviously, Jesse is Pooh.
Hell yeah.
Obviously, Ben's Eeyore.
Yes.
I'm thinking I'm Rabbit because he's so neurotypical, but also kind of autistic.
I think I'm probably a heflon.
Who's Owl?
Owl's Tom.
The most neurotypical activity there is is just wanting to tend to your garden.
Yeah.
Like, I tend to my subscribers. You know, I'm out there hoeing my fields and sowing my weaguas and reaping the rewards.
That's me.
I'm definitely a heffalump, definitely.
I guess I'd be like Kanga Mage. She's the closest to a tribola.
You remind me of Kanga because you're motherly mage, kind of.
Oh, don't... Why?
Is that a nice thing to say?
Can we get some impreg fetish art of Kanga Mage, please?
No, no, no.
No.
I refuse. I deny. I ban.
Ben.
Who's Rue? Who's Rue?
Is Hippo Rue?
Yeah, I guess me.
Because I'm small and I jump.
I do jump.
Like a piglet, kid.
As we got on this topic, I immediately felt like I wanted to go off on a rant about Owl and how he's the worst guy ever and how I hate him.
What?
He is deceptively terrible.
He's the biggest pseudo-intellectual pretentious cock who ever lived.
He causes trouble.
He causes problems everywhere he goes.
He makes everything more complicated and more horrible.
Every situation is worsened by Owl's inclusion every time.
That whole debacle with Christopher Robin going to school and they thought he was going to skull.
That whole thing was caused by Owl. It was all his fault.
Listen, I have new adventures. I haven't watched the old theatrical shorts. It probably happens that too.
But I watched six episodes and in one out of three episodes, Owl let someone fall to their death.
What the hell?
Well, I mean, a bird can't really support that much weight despite what your enemies lead you to believe, Ben.
Owl's just being realistic about the situation.
He's got Eeyore up in the sky on balloons trying to cheer him up and then he pops all the balloons and says it's time for his solo and lets him plummet to his death.
Why would he do that?
And then in the next one, Kessie falls off the tree.
Rabbit can't hold onto him and he falls off the cliff and Owl finds him falling and he doesn't help him.
Or hair, rather.
And he's like, oh yes, oh my uncle Horatio. Oh, a double aerial gainer. What an unusual technique.
Because Kessie's doing sick gainers on the way down, bro.
I mean, he's just being a social Darwinist. This guy has to rise and fall on his own weight.
He can't be helping him out.
Well, I love every single character except Owl and I'm sure that Christopher Robin feels the same way.
Yeah.
Kessie does figure out how to fly on the way down. It's debatable whether Owl helped or not.
There you go.
I bet Owl doesn't even know how to use a 10 scale. Doesn't even know how to use a 10 scale properly. That piece of shit, Owl.
Owl is Christopher Robin's mistake that he regrets giving life to every day.
Well, are you guys, I mean, you're probably familiar with this, but the original conceit for Winnie the Pooh was that half of the cast is stuffed animals.
Like poo and I think, and fucking piglet were stuffed animals.
Actually, I don't know about piglet, but then the other half were just animals that lived around.
Pooh, Piglet, Kanga, Eeyore and Tigger were the original toys.
Yeah.
All the other ones were invented by Mill.
Was Rue real then?
No.
Like Kanga, his mother is a fake.
He probably made that one.
No, the mother was a real toy. Rue is not a toy.
Okay, there you go.
Rabbit was not a toy. Owl and Gopher were not.
So there's a real Kangaroo in the woods and he has no mother and then Christopher Robin creates one for him.
They're on display in like the New York, in some museum or library in New York.
You know, Kanga bothers me a little because Kangaroos don't live in the forest.
They live in the fucking outback.
Well, now they're just fucking tigers, but you don't believe that.
He's not a tiger, he's a Tigger, he's an idiot.
He's a Tigger, you fuck, yeah.
Don't fucking tear you.
Oh my god, remember that one episode where Tigger loses all the stripes and loses his identity and just becomes so...
Okay, whatever.
We'll spend all day talking about the deep pathos.
I haven't seen that rewatch that one yet.
When Tigger loses his stripes, he just becomes fat now.
You just called him Tiger, the shoes on the other foot now.
What are you talking about? You made me do it. I got confused.
I got you fucking muddled me all up.
You fucked up, you fucked me up, you fucked it up.
I was gonna say that when Tigger loses his stripes, he just gets fat and becomes Garfield.
But then I remembered that Garfield also has stripes.
So it doesn't make any sense.
So maybe when he loses his stripes, he becomes Tiger.
But Tigers have stripes too.
Dude, what if Garfield is also a Tigger?
Oh, he's just like a fat lazy Tigger who didn't see his potential.
He's the only other one. They need to meet, they need to be friends.
You did it, the crossover, that's the secret.
But that can't be the only one, so they will have to kill each other.
The first episode, it's like the pilot episode of New Adventures.
I totally lost Ben.
Wait, am I there? Am I here?
Yeah, we've got a weird connection.
The connection says it's not great, but the first pilot episode of New Adventures is very Garfield-esque.
You know how John fucking brings Garfield to the beach and everywhere?
He brings them on international vacations and it's weird.
The pilot episode, they all go to the movies and it's terrible.
What? That's weird.
Christopher Robin brings the whole gang, well not the whole gang, but half the gang to the movies
and they all fuck around watching a Godzilla movie and Poo is eating candy bars and stuff.
And it's gross, it's gross and it's bad.
Wait a minute, does the staff not notice that this kid's stuffed animals are sentient?
Because that would cause problems, I think.
Is this diagetic snack-eating or is it non-diagetic snack-eating by the characters?
Who knows?
Is Christopher Robin just picking up the candy and throwing it and like shit?
You know, Calvin and Hobbes, Calvin and Hobbes takes care that any other character just sees them as the stuffed animal.
But like Poo, I just think that the animals are never even on screen when like an adult is in there.
Like there's an usher that tells Christopher Robin like this is in the playground
and just the characters just aren't there when that happens.
In the new movie that came out they addressed it where it's just like
Christopher Robin was like Poo, stop moving, you have to act like a real stuffed animal
because people were seeing a movie and talking and they were like
hey that bears fucking talking, what's happening?
He's like no Poo, you gotta be normal.
Is that the one with the Baxon?
Were they afraid of the Baxon?
No, they made a live-action movie recently.
Dude, forget this whole...
This is important, I'm talking about the live-action Poo movie!
That's when he's like grown up, right?
Yeah, it's like hook.
Oh yeah, that's right.
It was great, it was wonderful.
Dude, forget the whole feminism thing of how like it's like
women have to act a certain way, the patriarch is coming down.
What about the literal like the nightmare existence of you have to move
and pretend you aren't even sentient Poo and other toys like you?
That's the real civil rights per se we need to be on these days.
It was never like that though.
That's the toy story thing.
Yeah, they gave it toy story logic.
The difference is Christopher Robin or grown up or whatever
is complicit in this evil...
He's like no, no, no, we have to do it's like
even though I educated you my black African slave
we need to pretend like you can't read.
We need to like act this way.
It wasn't even like Christopher Robin is like
oh man, maybe I'm crazy or like...
Yeah.
No, he full on knew the whole time.
He was like, oh yeah, these are my like old stuffed animal friends
who are alive and live in a magical portal in a tree.
But I'm gonna pretend not for what?
If this is civil rights issues, Christopher fucking Robin
you need to defend their sentience and defend their personhood.
And Andy on the other hand, he doesn't have that issue
because he doesn't know they're alive.
But Christopher Robin does and he's culpable.
Nate is becoming a robot for me.
Yeah.
Nate's becoming less sentient because he's so riled up
about these issues of stuffed animal sentience.
His Turing test results are going down and down and down.
Listen, the toys and toy story, their entire motive
for not wanting to be seen moving and talking about
so they can't be put inside the labor force.
They don't want to be put to work, plow in the fields.
So whenever Andy comes in they have to pretend
like they're not sentient when obviously they are.
Well, Christopher Robin, he did learn a lesson in the movie
because they did the whole scene where Christopher Robin gets mad
and he yells at him.
He's like, God damn it, Pooh, I'm 40 now.
I don't got time for your stupid bullshit, you idiot.
And Pooh was really sad and he went, oh, you hurt my feelings
Christopher Robin.
And then Pooh got lost and he fell in a hole
and he almost fucking died.
And then Christopher Robin is looking for him like, oh my god,
I've killed Pooh.
What have I done?
And so then he finds him again.
And then they come back with the real world.
They don't know how to finish this point.
This is important, yeah.
This is my non-existent point just talking about what happened
in the movie where they come back in the real world
and they all look, you know, like they look realistic,
like real stuff to animals.
That was pretty fucking cool.
But, you know, they come back into the world
and Christopher Robin has a daughter
and like he's like, he's separated from his family
because he works too much.
I mean, it's just hook.
The movie is literally just hook.
But then, you know, they go and they fight the fucking guy
Wait, they don't fight a guy?
Well, they don't fight a guy.
But like Christopher Robin has this like shitty boss
who wants him to work and stuff.
And like they're talking about like woosles and stuff
because nobody likes a fucking woosle.
And the movie comes up with this like really great metaphor
actually where it's like some humans are just woosles.
They're just like slimy, sleazy sacks of shit
who want everyone to be sad.
So Christopher Robin's boss is like the biggest woosle of all.
So they got to go and they got to tell them fuck off.
And Christopher Robin like invents some new way to make money
at the grown-up money company or some shit.
I don't even remember.
Hell yeah.
But then he becomes closer to his shitty family
and they all, and he goes, hey, by the way, daughter,
this is my stuffed bear who is alive
and my stuffed tigger who is not a tiger, but he's alive.
And he has to explain like stuffed animals are alive, daughter.
And his daughter just like pukes in her own mouth
and like her eyes start bleeding.
And she gets her pants.
She has a heart attack.
She gets like arc of the Covenant face melted in size.
She screams.
And so I guess whatever the fuck point I was trying to make
with all that shit, that's Winnie the Pooh.
That sounds good.
I like that one.
It was good.
It was great.
You know, woosles aren't so bad in new adventures.
There's actually like a giant woosle colossus
that Pooh makes friends with.
He's like a giant, he's like 50 feet tall
and he's a demon.
But Pooh befriends him through generosity.
What a woosle is is so unclear because there's one woosle
who is literally just like an animal weasel.
But there's this other one is like a giant stuffed beast,
like a giant stuffed humanoid like construct.
I don't know, man.
Also the rules of imagination.
A woosle is a state of mind.
Maybe.
I guess it is.
Yeah.
It's like going hollow.
Like you go woosle.
Yeah.
She turned evil.
If you're shitty enough you just become unto a woosle.
The rules of...
It's the default state of man as a matter of fact.
The rules of how shit works is super vague.
Like just magical shit will happen
and it's like sometimes there will be a line about imagination.
Like when Eor is on the hill watching the sky,
watching the cloud painting,
it's like all it takes is a little imagination.
But whose imagination?
Is he psychically controlling the clouds?
Wait a minute.
Or is this all in Christopher Robin's imagination?
Are you citing like the big one everyone remembers
of Eor on the hill looking up at like the Aurora Borealis type thing?
Yeah.
Don't keep her a day.
Is that actually not physically there?
Is it imagination?
It's hard to say.
Okay.
That opens up a philosophical can of worms
because if Christopher Robin has given these characters life
through his own imagination
and they all have their own imaginations,
could they also create life?
That's a good question.
And is that the origin of Kessie?
Oh my God.
It was that a rabbit needed something in his life
to give him meaning and to grow as a person.
So he imagined that which was necessary to him.
Yes.
Kessie is rabbit's poo.
Oh my God.
That's true.
And then Kessie abandons him.
Well, because you know what I mean.
It's like if poo grew up
and was like Christopher Robin,
I don't need you anymore.
I'm going south for the winter.
I'll see you, never idiot.
It finally evolves into Baron the Big Blue House.
Welcome to the Woody the Pooh Theory podcast.
It's a lot to go through.
Did you grow up with Russian poo bear?
Sorta, yeah.
I have like one of the original Winnie the Pooh books.
Yeah.
But I never read it.
Have you guys ever seen Russian poo bear?
No.
It's a little weird.
It's a little uncanny.
It is a bit.
Yeah.
You know what?
I'll link it.
I'll go find Russian poo bear.
Pooh bear was an asshole, a bit of an asshole.
What?
He's kind of an asshole in the other.
Like he's kind of a selfish idiot a lot of the time.
Yeah, he's just dumb.
Not all the time, but sometimes.
He comes off as kind of a dick.
He's not super smart.
So he just gets himself in situations where he needs help.
Like when there's one where his friends aren't home,
they're off in the land of milk and honey in the jungle,
which may or may not be imaginary.
Who knows?
Right.
And he just like breaks into their houses,
like rummages for honey.
And then when he finds none,
he assumes that like a honey napper is out
and like about, but like, yeah,
he just breaks into his house to eat their food.
I just looked up Russian poo to see what he looks like.
He looks like an actual poo.
I don't like it.
Oh, look an actual poo.
He looks like a Tanuki is what he looks like.
He's round and he's brown and he's like smeary and smudgy.
Down to clown.
He's round and he's brown and he's down to clown.
Oh, this is interesting.
Oh, Eeyore looks weird.
Eeyore looks weird.
Eeyore looks fucking weird.
Look at all this.
This is interesting.
There we go.
Anyway, also Tom is here in Mage.
This has been a great episode of the PCP,
the poo conspiracies podcast.
The poo see poo?
No, no, the PC poo.
Whatever, fuck it.
If the procrastinators poo cast.
That's the one.
Well, I mean, it was known as the poop procrastinators.
Wait, no, never mind.
I cut all of this the whole thing.
Oh, wait, no, the poop procrastinators.
I coined a great neologism in my video.
I refer to the rules of the poo universe.
Oh, yes, good.
Yeah, I want that one to really stick in the poo fandom.
Wow, this was a great warm up, guys.
Can we just start the actual show?
That was the actual show.
Voice mail's coming up.
Here we go, everybody.
So anybody, let's go.
Anybody got something they want to talk about?
All right.
I got to just mention it just so that's done,
because there's so many people here.
It's going to be hard to wrestle it in later.
I'm currently doing a thing with the 2019.
I initially was like, I'm not going to do a New Year's resolution.
That's dumb.
But then I found myself, one day,
watching a series of extremely detailed analysis videos
about a guy's video about Dark Souls 2,
which took all day to watch.
It was like 11 hours in total.
These were the ATB Armour Guy videos.
The response to them.
Yeah, the response to HB Armour Guy's video on Dark Souls 2.
And it was good, but I hated myself after I woke up.
Watched all of it and didn't do anything.
And from that day forth, I decided,
no more YouTube.
It sucks.
I hate it.
So I've started the YouTube challenge,
hashtag YouTube challenge,
where I will not watch YouTube if I can avoid it
for the entire of the year.
And so far, I've watched three videos.
And that's my story.
I'm doing a lot to increase productivity.
I got a harsh bedtime at 1 a.m. or 1 p.m.
And I've been going to bed at 1 a.m. every day.
And I'm starting to wake up earlier and it's like,
you know, I can do stuff like this.
I can live my life as a real human being.
I can make stiff.
That's fucking cool.
Yeah, I've got a bedtime and I'm limiting gaming
to two hours per day maximum.
That's the worst thing of all,
because now I can't play Minecraft with you, Mage,
for an entire day.
I got to stop after two hours and then go to bed
and get my warm milk and be fresh and ready to,
you know, do whatever I'm doing.
And it's so far, like, one week in,
one week and a few days,
because I started just before the end of the year.
It's good.
I would recommend,
I would recommend at least the YouTube challenge,
mostly because I do get cravings for videos
and it's only the ones I really want to watch
that I end up watching because there's this thing
hanging over my head of,
okay, you can't.
You baseline cannot watch YouTube,
but when I got to watch a YouTube video,
you know, the longing is like, has to be really big,
so I only watch the videos that I actually really enjoy.
They're usually ones I've already seen.
Like, I've done a video that made me very important.
Huh?
Oh, I mean, yeah.
Oh, the Delta Room, right.
Have you guys seen Liga's show notes?
Delta Room, Susie in the Well Christmas Animation,
Belly Inflation, Fetish, Lesbian, Intermingling.
Nah, dude, it's not inflation.
It's weight gain.
There's a difference.
There's a distinct difference.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Totally took two completely different ballparks.
Yeah, they gotta, they know what's up.
They know it.
But let me ask you something.
Yes.
Surely, there are websites.
There's social media places that occupy more of your time
than YouTube.
Like, for instance, Twitter.
Twitter occupies a lot of my time.
The thing is, it wouldn't be one or the other.
It would be, I would, I would wake up and I'd be like,
ah, I gotta do some work today,
but I'll just watch a video for a bit.
Yeah.
And then, once you're watching a video,
you're like, well, this one in the sidebar looks good,
or there's another, like, there's more videos
that have been uploaded since I went to bed.
New subscriber videos.
Like, I better catch up on all of these before I start.
So, you know, clear the pilot.
It never ends up being a good idea.
And I end up playing video games and listening to YouTube videos.
And it's just, it's very, very difficult to stop.
Twitter occupies a little bit of my time.
I don't follow a lot of people.
I only really go to Twitter when I want to say something.
And then I go, you know, check replies to various things
and leave.
And I guess Discord takes up a lot of my time,
but I've muted basically every chat I'm in
and I've left a few, so it's not as much as it was.
So, like, I feel like it's just, you know,
you cut what you can.
You cut what you think is the least important.
I don't like cutting out YouTube entirely,
but it is helping.
Yeah.
I've been less active on Twitter.
I've been very inactive on Discord,
which is a source of great guilt and shame for me.
I have been...
See, I don't like pop onto YouTube to be like,
oh, I'll just watch a video.
I usually go to YouTube to put something on for background noise.
And then...
Yeah.
Which is a noble goal.
I was like, oh, I'll put just a video on in the background
while I'm working.
And the problem is that then while working,
if I feel like procrastinating,
then I'll just switch mental gears to actually watching the video
instead of doing what I'm supposed to be doing.
So...
Word.
Yeah, it's bad.
It's also bad.
It has the same net effect as just not doing anything
and just watching videos in the first place.
There's like this...
Sad times.
What would you say is the main goal of this?
Is it just the obvious you want to spend more time working
or do you feel like it's negatively impacted you
and in the other way?
It's not so far negatively impacted me at all
because I found for a long time,
especially December of last year,
I would just stay up at night in bed with my phone,
watching YouTube videos,
and then go into bed really late.
And I guess the main point is just to cut it out
because a lot of the time I don't feel like the time I spent
or the minutes watched is equatable to enjoyment levels.
Like I have a lot more fun talking to people on Discord
than I do watching a video.
It's more fun to just meme about stuff
and hear about videos and like,
lol, what the fuck is this?
I like doing that too.
Two hours is enough to save me.
It's enough to save me and if you do it every day
that's still quite a lot of gaming you're doing.
Let me throw out a proposition.
I include myself in this as well.
Tell me if any of you disagree with this about yourself.
I feel that we're all way too lazy
and don't do enough work or put enough effort in our lives,
including me.
100%.
What is your response?
My goal in life is to be more lazy as lazy as possible.
I want to be a bum.
I want zero responsibilities.
I want no one depending on me.
I want nobody looking forward to anything I do.
I want nobody expecting anything of me.
I just want to, my dream in life is to exist
and be completely alone
and just fucking do nothing.
I want to do nothing.
I want to lay in bed
and fucking and watch the WWE Network
all day for the rest of my life.
We got to do a remake of Office Space
but instead of being an office cubicle worker,
he's a YouTuber.
Ooh, not a bad idea.
That's my actual life.
That's how it is.
I agree, Nate.
I also don't do enough
and I don't think I could ever do enough
because even on the days that I do accomplish a bunch,
I still go to bed being like,
oh, I didn't do enough.
I didn't get anything done.
And then on the days that I actually didn't get anything done,
it's pretty much the same.
It's slightly worse.
Well, let me rephrase that then.
I guess what I meant is that I want,
I need to, I want to work harder
at everything in life that is not this.
Like, because accomplishing anything on YouTube
feels worse than accomplishing nothing.
Well, it doesn't have to be YouTube.
That's fine. That's fine.
Like, I want to work hard on things like,
like putting a resume together
and going to the dentist
and other stuff that like actual humans do.
I do need to do that.
Totally human core.
Making a resume is very human core.
It's the most human thing I can think of.
Nate, I would completely agree with you.
And I would still pretty much agree with you currently.
However, I don't want to get too much on with this
because it could be its own tangent now.
But everything's arriving here in Boston, right?
Leave my fifth or sixth trip here.
I started up commissions and basically,
I felt like a fucking god doing these commissions.
Where I'll pretty much like,
I'll either be doing commissions while I'm home
for an extended period of time.
Yesterday, I went out for a little bit into the world,
which feels productive,
even if you're just like fucking around outside,
you're not really doing anything really.
Going outside is an activity onto itself.
You're being exercised, you're going out,
you're seeing other people.
You're riding the subway,
which increases your culture by like 20 points
every single time you buy a ticket,
which is actually true.
So I'm just doing that.
And then I came home.
I just worked on commissions all day.
And then I went out and I had dinner and it was lovely.
That's a highly productive day.
Sounds like a great day.
You know, of social interaction,
as well as like actual working,
I'm getting things done for monetary benefit
and to hide in my chi energy.
I mean, that sounds like a balanced day
of getting that social interaction,
like earning a living and stuff,
working towards your career type stuff.
And also like the meal or whatever,
like relaxing and having a good day.
Because I think it's important
that people kind of challenge themselves every day,
at least a little bit,
to feel that like good,
like, ah, I worked out mentally or otherwise today
and I am improving on this day
and not getting worse or whatever.
It's like straight cougar says, you know,
there's no need to rush through breakfast.
Breakfast is meant to be enjoyed.
It leisurely pays.
The rest of that?
Yeah, the rest of everything else,
he's turning his car into a pink magic car
and being like, ah, I fucking,
I did it in a million miles an hour last time,
but this time I did it at a million miles and one.
I've shortened the world, but only breakfast.
Straight cougar is the only memorable character from Skryad.
Mostly.
Here is a little life hack for you,
which works for me more than you would think.
Is schedule more social interactions?
This will help you work, I find.
People resist that.
They don't like having their life in a box.
But when you have, for instance,
in two days from now,
I will be meeting an RFCK fan in real life
and we have scheduled this interaction.
I know what I'm going to meet him
and I know when he will leave.
And because I know that there's no way...
And I look forward to that moment, especially.
There's no way I'll be able to be working
while I'm with him.
We're going to be out on the town.
That gives me the time, like,
okay, I'm going to be losing like four hours there.
Unacceptable.
I have to work now so that I know
I can, like, rest easy that day
knowing that I haven't wasted that time.
So that entire day up to that point
before I meet him,
I'm just going to be working really hard
or, you know, the night before or after he leaves
to make sure that I can reclaim that day.
So it's nice to be able to know ahead of time
what time you're going to be spending.
This goes to, like, work and, you know,
like scheduling podcasts or social interactions.
Anything.
Having a calendar is very important
so you can manage your time effectively.
I feel like I'm...
I mean, that doesn't really work for me.
I don't know why.
I feel like it's leading up to an event
where I have to be ready.
I don't want to be, like, in the middle of something
when I have to leave.
This is, like, if this is happening on the same day.
But, like, days before,
I would generally, like,
try not to start any big projects
or work on any big projects.
I would do smaller things,
leading up to an event that I knew was coming.
And then once the event is over,
I feel like I can start work on something big
that would require me to stay inside
and work really, really hard for a long time.
I'm kind of the same, but maybe worse.
Like, for example, I remember, like,
leading up to, you know, Christmas,
because I knew I was going to go visit the fam
for, like, two days or whatever,
like, a day and a half.
And, like, the entire...
Like, two whole days before that happened,
I wasn't getting anything done
because I was kind of just sort of milling about, like,
oh, no, I'm gonna have to...
I gotta spend, like, a day and a half away from my computer.
I won't get anything done.
And then that anxiety, like, made me
not do anything for, like,
longer than I was even away.
It was a nightmare.
It was totally wrong-headed
and pathological and bad.
What do you mean by an event, Hippo?
What would you describe an event as?
Well, I mean, I'm not a very social person.
I don't get outside much.
So an event is, like, a social interaction
usually outside the house.
Oh, okay.
If somebody comes over, then it's, like, whatever.
But, like, going to a party,
going to a thing, going to meet someone,
yeah, any other thing of that nature.
I guess it's mostly just social events.
Also, there's, like, times like this Christmas
my parents bought tickets to a comedy show.
And so that was, like, an event of the holiday.
So I had to know that that day we were going.
But that's easier because I can just easily just...
Well, I don't know why it feels different
because it's still a day out
and you're still away from work.
But it's more of, like...
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know why that feels different
because it is exactly the same thing.
I empathize with the idea.
When I'm back home, going out at all,
just, you know, to hang out with my friends
or just leaving the house to go for a walk.
That does feel like an event for me
because I very rarely do it.
But I really am thankful with the fact
that staying here in Boston,
I am staying in a place with such great city access
where the city access is I walk outside
and I'm in the city.
So that has, like, 10...
Oh, that and Pokemon Go
has tenfold increased my, like, willingness
to just, like, go outside
and interact with the world.
There are times where I'll just walk around
just to have fun,
which is something I would never do when I'm back home.
I would never even, like, thank for a second
to, instead of checking Twitter
or watching YouTube videos,
just go out and maybe walk in a park or something.
And I think, I mean, I think we can all agree
that that's a more useful, you know,
spending my time
going outside and walking, exercising.
One of the best things about, like,
the thing I'm doing is, you know,
it's not cutting out procrastination entirely.
I'm not tirelessly working every second
that I'm not watching a YouTube video.
But I am doing more things
that are, like, better things to do
when procrastinating,
such as doing the laundry, cleaning the room,
you know, doing things,
doing chores that need to be done anyway.
And then also reading books.
I'm reading books because I can't go on the Internet really.
I'm like, ah, God, I want to play a game,
but I've done my two hours gaming
and I can't watch a YouTube video
and I don't want to work on this thing.
I'll just pick up a fucking Isaac Asimov
and read that. I've wanted to read that for a while.
You should really, like, choose your own adventure books.
It's kind of like playing a game.
I do have one of those. Those are cool.
But yeah, it's like...
Any books you want to recommend?
Uh...
Do you want to link to your Audible?
Link to your Audible?
If you like, if you like, um,
adventure-y, cool shit,
the His Dark Materials trilogy,
uh, starting with, uh,
I think the Northern Lights.
It got turned into a movie called The Golden Compass.
Yeah. The movie, I don't think, was very good,
but the books are like, um, Harry Potter levels of...
Harry Potter slash Lord of the Rings levels of cool,
to me. They're like the...
like the... they're good.
Have you read the last one? Have you read the whole series?
I did. I read the whole series one summer
when I was like 12.
Yeah, I read it when I was like in high school or something.
And, uh, man, I don't know.
The end of that series gets so far up its own ass.
It is, like, so preachy and like...
Oh, maybe.
So it's like...
Like, you read that story when you're a nascent,
fedora-tipping atheist.
Because, like, in the end, they go and they kill God.
And God is fake anyway, but they kill him anyway.
Yeah, it was pretty sick.
And then they're like, man, the afterlife sucks and is stupid.
Let's open a portal to, like, end the afterlife.
So no one has to suffer through that hell that is life after death.
Yeah, actually, I haven't re-read it. Maybe it's not that good.
But, like, um...
I haven't re-read it either. I just remember being like, wow.
I guess I was younger when I read it, and I was like,
oh, my God, this is the first story I've ever read.
Yeah.
And it's cool.
Um, the...
The first... the first book, Golden Compass,
is very, like, Harry Potter kind of, like, you know, alternate world,
like, you know, adventure and magic and stuff.
And then, like, in two and three, especially three,
the scope sort of expands out to this, like, interdimensional war,
and it gets very, like, abstract and preachy and stuff.
Also, teenage romance, which, you know, I enjoy.
Yeah, we all do.
Of course, of course.
To go back to what Hippo was saying before,
before we got on Harry Potter 2,
I very, very much empathize with your wanting to limit YouTube time.
I've been on a pretty similar kick.
Not kick the messaging app to sex children.
No, stop thinking about kick the sexting app.
I'm talking about kick, like, with my leg.
Anyway, I've been on a big yearly theme kick
after listening to some great episodes of the podcast Cortex.
I don't know if you're a fan of that Hippo,
I know you're a fan of Hello Internet,
I don't know if you watch it.
I haven't listened to that.
Very good, very good.
Anyway, they are a big proponent of yearly themes as opposed to resolutions.
And I've gotten very big on this because I've always been thinking
for the past couple months about this general idea
of wanting to limit social media in the particular way that I use it.
And so this idea of the yearly theme has given me not the confidence,
but more like, it's easier to get behind ideas
when you can clearly articulate them, you know?
It's better, you're more willing to push forward a plan
if you can clearly identify the actual actions you're going to be taking
to do said plan, as opposed to just think about it in the general.
So I am not really someone who wants to outright ban YouTube,
like how you would want to, or outright ban Twitter.
But I think the problem with Twitter that I have,
and with YouTube and all other social media,
is that I use it in the exact same way every single day.
And it just gets boring and doesn't, you know, help me in any way.
Using Twitter to find what your friends are doing,
or using YouTube to watch a YouTube video that you really want to,
those are things that I feel like impact you in a positive way.
But once you just, like, watch YouTube for six hours a day,
or check Twitter when you're outside having dinner,
you should check Twitter over and over again,
there's no real reason for that.
You're not getting actually anything out of it.
It's just you become addicted to it.
So I just want to use...
If you're following some Dank meme Twitter accounts
and you just want to be on the uptake.
Yeah, that's it.
What about that?
Dank memes are bad.
Whoa!
My whole idea this year,
I'm going to be trying doing more with my life in many ways.
But in regards to this conversation,
I want to use social media
to not just solidify the connections I have
and just, you know, follow you guys and a few select others.
I don't know if you know this, but I have something like 60 people I'm following,
where everyone else I know has, like,
easily over 100 to 200.
I have a very, very small selection of people I'm talking to,
just even outside of Twitter, on Discord,
or in any social interaction.
I have 56, I win.
Just letting you know that. Okay, move on.
Okay, that's cool.
I hate Wendy's. Wendy's is fucking garbage.
No one should eat it.
That's the new topic for now.
Please go on. I'm listening.
I mean, I guess that's it. That's all I had to say.
What led you to this conclusion, at least recently?
You had a baked potato.
Alright, look.
At a certain point in my mid-20s,
like maybe 26, 27,
I don't know when exactly it happened,
but at a certain point,
my body decided that it can no longer eat the spicy chicken sandwich from Wendy's.
I just can't do it anymore.
If I eat one, I get, like, my stomach turns into, like, fire,
and I poop, but, like, the bad kind of poop.
Not the fun kind of poop.
Like, hot fire in my pants.
Like, fire ants in my stomach,
creating a colony and then shooting out of my ass with their poison,
and they're flaming, like, starship trooper bugs
that shoot the fucking fire and acid out of their faces.
That's the inside of my butthole and my tummy,
now that I'm, like, old, I guess.
That's what happens when you get older.
You just can't do, you can't eat the spicy chicken sandwich anymore.
So, like, it's the only thing that happens when you get old.
Everything else is the same.
That's second puberty.
You can't eat the spicy chicken sandwich.
I mean, I was, I wasn't, I don't know,
I was existentially horrified to realize, similarly, one day,
that just eating candy, specifically chocolate, hurts my teeth now.
Dude, dude, you two, yeah, me too, chocolate.
I don't know what the fuck that is, but it happens every time now.
There's, there's, like, one spot in my mouth
that just hurts when I eat chocolate.
It's, like, all my teeth, I don't know.
Unless I'm really careful not to get it in my teeth.
It's weird.
Well, like, I can't eat the spicy chicken sandwich anymore.
So, I, you know, it took me, like, years to come to terms with that.
I didn't want to let it go.
So, like, I kept eating it.
I ate through the pain.
I, I kept, because, you know, it's, it's my favorite sandwich in Wendy's.
It's what I eat when I go to Wendy's.
I don't want nothing else.
So, I, you know, but I finally came to terms with it and I, and I said,
you know what, I'm not getting any younger.
I'm going to have to come up with something else to order at Wendy's from now on.
So, I perused the menu and I experimented and I, you know, I said,
well, maybe I'll get fries today, or maybe I'll get nuggies,
or maybe I'll get, you know, this is a regular burger that's not made of chicken,
like it made out of burger, and, or maybe I'll get, you know, like a,
like a single burger, or a baby burger, or a double burger.
Look at that damn baked potato.
What are you talking about?
There's no baked potato at fast food?
Is there?
Yeah, Wendy's is.
Yeah, yeah, that's it.
Yeah, Wendy's, you can get a baked potato at Wendy's.
Well, that's, maybe I'll do that, but that's not part of the story.
It's pretty, it's pretty okay.
It'll give you a big nut sack full of sour cream that comes with it,
and you just squeeze that shit on there.
It's great.
It's so nice.
How's that for a visual, ladies and gentlemen?
I got, I got a nut sack full of sour cream for you.
Too obvious.
So I tried all the different foods.
I went, I went like 90% of the way to that joke.
You just did that little tiny, all right.
Yeah.
And I, and I took all the glory.
I kill, I stole your kill.
I guess that's true.
So I tried all the different foods at Wendy's only to realize,
after much experimentation,
everything at Wendy's is garbage except the spicy chicken sandwich.
Everything else on the menu is pig vomit, dog shit, asshole,
poopy food, and it's all bad.
Like Wendy's is just bad.
And the fucking, the smug Wendy's Twitter account,
who thinks it's so fucking cool,
some fucking 20 year old whose job it is to roast people
from behind the veneer of this corporate fucking mascot,
which is fucking sick and weird and creepy anyways.
But you know, they're so smug about it.
Like, oh, we're Wendy's.
We're the best fucking place.
And we can just roast everybody else.
No, you're not cool Wendy's.
You fucking suck.
All of your food is fucking dog shit.
Wendy's burgers are, the beef is pretty good,
but like they're sort of just like a loose kind of mess
of like tasteless vegetables.
I don't know.
But Wendy's burgers are not frozen and square.
They're for quality.
The episode that me and Hippo can't participate.
Unless, is there a Wendy's in the UK?
Uh, no.
Wendy was banned like Lauren Southern from the UK.
When I was in the US, I have had a Wendy.
Oh, how was it?
By far the worst burger is Burger King.
Burger King burgers are actually disgusting.
Oh yeah, Burger King is hideous.
No, no.
They have, they have like, they have some kind of weird
like smoky, like chemical mixed into the beef.
It's fucked.
It's nasty.
Yeah, I made it.
Maybe in the, maybe in the US, but in the UK,
at least the Burger Humania where I live is really good burgers
and they have like the best milkshake.
It could be different out there.
Yeah, like I know that like fast food is bad for you,
but like Burger King tastes bad for you.
Like it tastes, like you said,
it's got that weird smoky mutated taste.
It tastes like a fucking, like someone grilled up
a living Dalek on a fucking bun.
It tastes like a weird chemical soup.
Uh, that's, it's, it's, it's bizarre.
It's bizarre.
I don't know why there's not more outrage about it.
I'm pretty sensitive to those sort of things.
So I don't think the Burger King near me has that.
Fair enough.
I'm saying people shit on McDonald's,
but I think I would much rather eat a McDonald's burger
than a Burger King burger.
Yeah, like, you know, McDonald's like takes the brunt
because it's like the, the, the number one in everyone's mind
to like make fun of fast food.
But like McDonald's is like actually good.
I like McDonald's burgers.
Really?
They're not too bad.
No, they're not too bad.
I, I prefer Burger King to McDonald's as,
as disgusting as it may be to admit that publicly.
Why?
Why though?
I guess I just prefer the, the, the, the grill
instead of the fucking flat top that they do at Burger King.
But do you, do you acknowledge the weird smoky chemical taste?
I mean, to be fair, I haven't had Burger King,
you know, in a hot minute.
So perhaps, perhaps modern Burger King has infused
their, their burgers with more bullshit.
But in my youth, there was a Burger King in a,
in a McDonald's right next to each other.
And I would always want to go to Burger King
because I just found the fries to be way better.
And, and the burgers would be better too.
Well, you know, the real advantage is that Burger King
has onion rings and you know, McDonald's doesn't.
That's a good point.
That right there was the deal breaker.
Yeah.
Burger King wigs.
I like onion rings on a burger.
Me too, so you got to get your ass over to Burger King,
which I guess you do.
The only thing Burger King ever did
that was really courageous and brave
was giving the world its first video game
where you play as a rapist.
That's something that only Burger King had the balls to do.
I'm sorry.
Can you elaborate, please?
Well, sneaking is like you literally just sneak around
and you jump out of garbage cans and rape people.
I'd argue that the first video game where you played
as just any male is where you,
because all men are rapists, so you know.
Got them.
Have you ever tried like breakfast wrap at McDonald's?
Do they have that in the Americas?
Yeah, they have that.
It's my favorite.
It's okay.
I don't like the sauces they use,
so I always ask without sauce,
and then I just use their barbecue sauce,
because they don't offer that,
but their barbecue sauce is really good, so.
I always think McDonald's breakfast eggs
are kind of tasteless.
Guys, I'm so bored.
I'm so bored, and I've got something.
I've got to say, I've got to get off my chest here.
Before you do that,
I thought of an actually good book recommendation
that Munchie might like,
because it's like thoroughly researched historical fiction.
Yeah?
Wait, what?
Oh, wait, that actually doesn't make sense.
Yeah, yeah.
Bernard Cornwell's trilogy, starting with Harlequin,
it's a medieval fiction book,
but it takes place in events that happened in England.
Could you show the author name again?
Bernard Cornwell, I'll type it.
Now that's an English name, if ever I heard one.
Yeah, it is.
You know what, books are very fucking good.
I used to know Bernard.
Hey, hippo.
Shit.
When we're together in July,
I want to watch a BBC historical fiction series with you
called I, Claudius.
Would you like to do it?
Yeah, why not?
Sick.
It's six episodes.
What are you saying, Jesse?
What books do you like?
Oh, these books that I like,
that people don't talk about as much.
I mean, everyone, I think, knows about them,
but they don't get talked about,
because only the first one got a movie.
It's like all the other Hitchhikers' guide to the galaxy books
that came after the first one.
Oh, I've been...
Yeah, the whole The Five Book Trilogy?
Yeah.
I read those so much as a kid.
For years, I've been meaning to reread them.
And they just get like...
Everyone knows the story of the first one,
because they made a movie about it
and there was a series about it
in the 80s on the BBC.
We talked greatly last episode, I think,
because I mentioned Dirk Gently.
Yeah, you did.
But the ones after the first book,
where it just gets weirder and more obtuse
and more and more depressing with each book,
the fourth one is really kind of somber.
Yeah, the fourth book is kind of a bummer.
Arthur ends up on Earth again,
and everything's normal, nothing even happened,
and he meets this girl and he falls in love,
and they learn how to fly together,
and the whole book is just this romance,
this really sincere romance of him falling in love
with this girlfriend church.
And then at the end of the book,
he gets zapped back to space,
and the whole thing didn't happen.
She's gone, she's just dead,
she doesn't exist anymore.
He goes back to his own reality
where the Earth was destroyed or something.
The whole book is just this,
him falling in love just so at the end
it can all be taken away completely irreverently
with no sense of even that this is sad.
It's like, hey, you're fucked, it's over.
And then in the fifth book,
he has a daughter,
but the daughter is fucking crazy
because she thinks she doesn't fit anywhere
because she was born in space or some stupid shit.
But she's like, I don't know,
like the fifth book just ends
with everybody on Earth
and the Earth blows up again,
and everyone's just dead,
and that's how he ended the entire series.
And then they gave it to some younger guy
to finish it, a new author,
and he made a new book that wasn't good,
but the way that there...
There actually is a continuation, does it?
No, no, no, the fifth book's the last book
in the Hitchhiker's trilogy,
but there were other books in other series.
It was implied that Douglas Adams wanted to write another book
after the fifth one, but he didn't get to because he died.
Really?
Yeah, so that was the last book,
but then 20 years later,
they gave it to the guy who wrote the Artemis Foul books,
and they said,
make a new Hitchhiker's guide to the...
So they gave him an official continuation
to write a new Hitchhiker's book and wrap it up,
and the one that he wrote,
I mean, you could tell...
Is it good?
No, you could tell very clearly
that it's another writer trying to sound like Douglas Adams
on every page,
and you realize very quickly that it can't be replicated,
and I was almost happier
when the series ended with everyone dying
than them getting to come back to life,
but now it's a bad book.
I think we have to say that the fifth book is the true ending.
Let me just...
I remember when I was young,
Ben and his boys were big into it,
and as his younger brother,
I followed suit and read them all as well
and quite enjoyed them,
and I remember getting to the last book,
I definitely was too young to really appreciate it at the time,
but there's the whole metaphor...
Mom gave me that book when I was 12.
She gave me the first Hitchhiker's guidebook
when I was a little baby,
way too young for it.
Yeah, maybe it kind of helps.
Given a challenging...
It's not that hard to read,
but the themes presented are fairly adult.
The theme of the original story is
there's an interstate trying to get rid of Arthur's house,
and then I forget when this...
This might be in the first book, this happens,
but they're trying to build a space intersection
through their first chapters.
That's the very first chapter.
Right, okay.
Yeah, that's the very, very beginning.
I think that happens in the beginning,
but ultimately, it ends where...
I remember there's a time loop
or alternate dimension or whatever,
and that finally does happen.
I think Arthur gets killed in the process of that.
And I remember the last scene
just being whatever corporate fat cat it was
who instigated that to make it up,
just looking down and being proud of his work
and is like,
well, there's my interstate,
time to move on to make another one elsewhere
and destroy these other worlds.
And it's a very somber, sad ending,
but it felt like a message about...
I guess kind of corporate tyranny
or about the suppression of individuality
for the group benefit or something.
Those books, obviously, they are absurdist comedies,
and that's what they're famous for being,
but they had a very dark profundity to them
throughout the whole series.
The part that I remember the most in the third book,
I think, was they go to a planet
and they see an actual message from God,
the last message that God gave to his creation.
Damn, I don't remember that.
And the message is written in these gigantic, burning letters
on the side of a hill or something,
and the message from God, it simply says,
we apologize for the inconvenience.
It's like profound.
Like, if that were the actual real message from God,
I think it would actually make me feel better.
Yeah, that's true.
I mean, how much better do you feel when you're listening?
Like, if you're put on hold, do you prefer to hear silence?
I can't think of anything I would rather hear God tell me.
I mean, yeah, having him say, I apologize,
would at least be an acknowledgement of the many sins
of the creator of the universe.
I have such a strong sense of deja vu.
I feel like I've heard Jess say that before.
I don't know.
Maybe.
I think we've all heard Jess say that often.
No, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wasn't it like the robot Marvin was it?
And he saw the message and that made him feel better?
Yeah, and like Marvin is like dying, I think.
And they say like, does that at least make you feel better?
And he's like, yeah, I guess it kind of does a little.
That's like the last thing that Marvin sees when he's croaking
and it gives him some manner of peace.
Seeing a real message from God wouldn't be a bad last thing to see, I think.
Tying this back to Winnie the Pooh, naturally.
I must have just had a real soft spot.
I must have just really like depressed voice of reason characters
because I really loved Eor and I really loved Marvin.
They were my favorite.
Wow, then you're so like original.
I bet you go to hot topic like every day.
Yeah, like so cool.
Christopher Robin's final message to Eor.
I apologize for the inconvenience.
Comment below if you shared my proclivities, edgy teens,
listening to this podcast.
Our sea of transsexual gay audience members
are absolutely all going to come down on your side, Ben.
It's going to be a sea of, I don't know, what do they do?
Zero for Ben, you know, that kind of thing, yeah.
Maybe, probably.
They'll buy a shirt.
They'll go to the Ben Saints teespring and buy a St. Hart shirt.
Yeah, exactly.
They'll go to pray, throw crass news, I'm just being cool shirt.
Oh man, I feel like I had somewhere to go with that.
I could pick this up.
I just looked it up and like get a load of just like the depth of emotion
and the profundity of this passage.
It says, we apologize for the inconvenience.
God's final message to His creation, written in letters of fire
on the side of the, oh God, I'm too far away to read this made up bullshit word,
on the side of the quenchilis quasgar mountains.
I think Marvin murmured at last from deep within his corroding, rattling thorax,
I feel good about it.
The lights went out in his eyes for absolutely the very last time ever.
That makes me feel like, hmm, that's a good feeling right there.
I felt really sad for Marvin.
He went through so much crap and then this happened.
I mean, it's pretty funny, but also existentially horrifying
to be designed specifically to be grumpy and upset about life all the time.
He had to wait like how many years?
Millenials, I don't know.
Yeah, there's some kind of time shenanigans where he gets sent back to the ancient past
and has to just wait around for millennia for the other characters to meet up with him again.
Damn, that sucks.
I don't know if he was designed to be depressed
or if that was just a natural result of him being so smart.
Well, there were those doors, right?
The doors were designed to love opening and closing for people to hate through
and gets massive enjoyment, and I think he, on the other hand, was designed to be upset about most things.
Too bad. Too bad. That's a shame.
Hey, but to pick this up, speaking of apologizing for the inconvenience,
I just want to say a short message to people who listened to the last week's episode
because I feel like my energy levels were greatly repressed,
and I just want to explain that that was because I had just gotten back from vacation
and I had not even slept yet.
I wanted to be on the PCP so bad that I didn't take any breaks
and I feel like I didn't have my thoughts together.
So it's a mild apology from your God.
A mild apology. That's the title of your autobiography.
So really, you should be thanking him.
Yeah, that's correct. I want to turn this weakness into a you owe me thanks for doing this for you.
That's where I want to take it.
You have apologized for the inconvenience.
Exactly. Exactly.
But I did remember a hilarious story that I wanted to tell people
that I totally forgot to on that episode of my visit to Hawaii,
which was basically simply that when we were first there,
we went straight to go get some food.
It's like a Japanese-Chinese little food place.
And so we go in. I got curry.
I've decided my favorite food in the world is Japanese curry.
Put that in the books, folks. That's canon.
Put that on the prokarystopedia.
That's right. Put it in there.
And as we're sitting there, our female waitress, who was Chinese
and with her accent, you could tell she was actually from China.
Spoke some rough English.
And she comes up.
And so it's me, Michelle, and Michelle's mom.
And she says to Michelle.
She says this female waitress is to Michelle in like broken English.
So spare me. This is what she sounded like.
I'm not offending anyone here.
Well, this is what she said.
I'm not offending anyone.
You're offended. You're wrong.
You cannot be offended by this.
Here we go. She was like, oh, I want you to.
You can do it.
You're so beautiful.
We're going to get deep platforms.
She said something like, he want you to know out front.
You're so beautiful.
And we were like, what are you talking about?
And Michelle was confused.
What she was attempting to communicate
was that either the chef or the guy at the front desk
wanted to or at least had said that Michelle was beautiful.
Now, it wasn't implied.
It wasn't conveyed if she had been given this message
to pass along to Michelle,
or if this person was just privy to this information
and chose to share it, possibly against their wishes,
that we don't know.
But I'm assuming it was that latter,
because why else would you say anything?
Nate, the only reason you would want to relay this story is
so you can be, haha, I have a hot girlfriend.
Also, I can make a funny racist voice.
That's the only reason why you want to share this story.
Those are two great reasons to tell this story.
Does that matter?
Well, but here's the point.
Okay, here's the point.
And then she said, oh, me sucky sucky, big egg roll, Jackie Chan.
And then she said,
Shanghai Hong Kong egg-foo young fortune cookie always wrong.
Look, here's the point.
Here's the point.
Okay, fine.
The message was conveyed.
We all sat around just wondering what the point of this message was.
Because remember, Michelle's sitting there
and I'm sitting right next to her and her mom's across from us.
Now, Michelle is like Asian and Hispanic.
So she's obviously not related to me because I'm fucking white as snow.
And like, so I'm right there and we've got this lady coming across.
By the way, she's like, I don't know, like 25 and the dude's also 25.
We can like, we can see him passing along a message to my girlfriend
that he thinks she is beautiful.
Now, I don't know if this is like more common in China or whatever,
but it's like, what exactly is the end game of this,
of this proposition of this information being passed along?
Are we attempting some sort of cucking situation?
Is that what we're going for?
He thought you were easy pickings and he wanted to get out.
Yeah, I think so.
Yeah.
It was good.
I mean, I guess it could be.
He figured there was no way that you knew Kung Fu
and would defeat him in an honor duel.
Little does he know.
I've watched so much anime.
My power level is off the charts.
Could he see?
There's probably just a weird way to try and get tips.
It could have been that.
Except it wasn't that she said that Michelle was beautiful.
It was that this guy had said she was beautiful.
And presumably she had been, she was passing along the message.
And that was it.
All right.
Ladies and gentlemen, that was my experience.
Good story.
Thank you for delivering us from boredom.
Thank you for your welcome.
You're welcome.
I think that was good.
The podcast is saved.
We did it, everybody.
Thanks to the procrastinators girls.
And now we can move on to the...
Just for fun on that subject.
Michelle has told me that she's got Asian eyes
and when her co-workers, she said, will attempt to say something back to her
that she had said or whatever.
She's noticed they will squint at her while they're just saying the words.
And she's like, why are you doing that?
Why?
How does that help me understand?
I don't know.
It helps her empathize.
It builds your rapport.
You want to see the world the way she sees it.
I want to question.
So when she's repeating the words that Michelle said, is that...
Yeah, when they're trying to probably make fun of her or joke about something she had said.
It's like when they come up to her and they speak really slowly because she's a foreigner,
they squint their eyes and they say, do you know the...
There is this thing, I'm not saying maybe the co-worker is trying to be racist,
but sometimes when people are trying to focus, they do squint.
I mean, maybe.
I guess the implication is that this isn't done when quoting, I guess, non-Asian people.
I mean, I don't know.
I think it's hilarious and I'll laugh at Michelle either way, but you know, I'm just saying...
Racism is good.
I just want the world to understand that it's always funny no matter what.
You don't even have to have a punchline.
If you just say something racist, I swear to God, it's hilarious.
You know what they say.
Okay, listen to this, guys.
High walls build strong neighbors.
I heard a joke.
I heard a joke and I'm going to repeat it word for word.
This is a Louis C.K. joke that I heard on a podcast from 2015.
All right.
It starts with...
Oh, no.
I don't remember.
It goes like, how do you...
No, wait.
Hold on.
Let me just think.
I know what it is.
God damn it.
I'm sorry.
I'm tripping over my ums, but here it is.
So he was on a podcast with Bill Burr's black friend, Patrice O'Neill.
That was it.
And Patrice O'Neill.
Bill Burr's black friend, Patrice O'Neill.
I just forgot his name.
God damn it.
He was dead before I even found out about him.
Okay, anyway.
God.
Patrice O'Neill was saying like, hey, did you guys know where the word kike came from specifically?
They were talking about slurs.
And they said, oh, well, you see on Ellis Island, like something like the Hebrew word for circle
is kykel.
And so what the, what the fucking, the people would say is like, oh, here comes the Hebrew,
doesn't speak English.
You know, one of these kikes is coming along, you know, doing the same kykel because that
was the thing.
That doesn't explain anything.
I know the clip you're talking about.
Well, it was just like a shortened version of this word that was...
Why would they use the word circle?
Because they didn't know how to sign their name in English.
And so they would simply draw a circle and they just abbreviated that.
So yeah, I left that point out.
Sorry.
And so in response to this, Louis C.K. comes in and he says, hey guys, you know where the
word nigger comes from?
So one time there was this black guy and he was just being a real nigger.
And you know, so then they just started calling him that.
Get it?
Do you get it guys?
Why aren't you laughing?
That's really funny.
I'm picking up what you're throwing down.
Okay, good.
Best guy ever.
I'm really, I'm really feeling it.
You burst out roaring laughter at that joke because it's really funny.
I mean, that's what happens in the clip.
You really left me hanging.
They all burst out laughing hysterically.
Yeah, they do.
And it's great.
Yeah.
I get it.
You know, in a different context, maybe I would have been amused, but...
I guess so.
Let's talk about nicer words like the word smorgasbord.
Yeah, you know what?
There's not enough talk about words that are nice that everyone agrees on and feels
good when they hear.
Okay, but the word smorgasbord is just, it's just like, I just realized it sounds like
something Starfire would like use to describe like from Teen Titans is just like one of
those.
It sounds like a made-up word.
Yeah, I suppose that's true.
She'd probably be pretty excited about that word.
Although a quick question is Tameranian actually a different language than English or whatever
they speak?
Yeah, it's like she used a lot of those words and that's why I said like smorgasbord just
sounds like something from her language.
You're right.
Dude, you know what?
I like bogus.
Bogus.
I think we should say bogus individual instead of nigger.
We should make a PCP bonus episode only called the bogus episode and it's like totally wacky,
bro.
You know what I mean?
No, that's a bogus idea.
All our bogus episodes are bogus episodes.
That's true.
In fact, all of our episodes period are totally bogus.
What word I love and I always thought it was a racist word, but then I looked it up
and I realized that I found out that it's actually was not racist like I thought it was.
Is it niggardly?
It's not niggardly.
Although that is also in this category of words.
Edimologically unrelated.
Yeah, it's boofer.
I fucking, I love, I love boofer.
I love calling people boofers.
I love being called a boofer even though it's an insult.
Is that like a, is like a verb you can boof someone?
I just, no, like a boofer is like a lower class, poor, lazy person.
And so like obviously I could see why there would be racist connotations if you yourself are racist
and think that all poor, lazy people are black, but it's actually not.
It's actually totally not racist.
You can say boofer all you want to anyone you want.
It's okay people.
We can say boofer.
That would be such a good name for a boofer.
That's true.
I might adopt that one.
That's pretty good.
Yeah, like when I was, when I was, when I was working on the farm as a teenager, you know,
the person we worked for, she would yell down the stairs to us like,
you boofers get up and get out there in the field and shovel that shape shit.
What are you boofers doing playing your boofer ass video games?
Oh, boofer ass is such a good one.
I love describing things as boofer ass something.
It's great.
With, uh, uh, spout off into the boofer core subgenre.
She also called us work niggers a lot, but I,
like, like, like, like our, our job was work niggers, but our,
what we actually were as people, as human beings were boofers.
I'll just do it.
Okay, word uncanny.
Uncanny.
I, I, you know how it learned this word.
Garfield.
I learned that word from Garfield.
I, I, I was binge watching like some, uh, TV show about like paranormal activity and whatever
and every single episode there was this woman that would just like guess was like,
that's so uncanny.
And I thought that it just meant like, oh, that kind of looks like something else.
But then I learned the real.
That it doesn't look like a tin can.
What?
Yeah.
I thought the word meant like, oh, it's, it, this thing looks like another thing.
Oh, you know, it's similar looking or whatever.
Oh, it's, it has, it shares similarities because like the way she used it,
she used it wrong apparently.
And so like,
Is uncanny a racial slur?
Have I?
No, not at all.
Okay, no.
I'm just talking about a word.
Just a random word.
Okay.
Just a random, non-offensive word.
Sorry, got racial slurs in the mind.
Those exist?
Yeah.
Well, get rid of your mind.
I don't know.
Oh, these fucking tin cans walking around with their AI and shit.
Fucking, yeah, uncanny for life.
Know what I'm saying?
Maybe.
Could be something like that.
Yeah, so I learned the actual meaning of the word and I still like it.
It's a pretty useful word.
I just googled it by the way,
because I didn't actually know the real definition.
It says strange or mysterious,
especially in an unsettling way.
Yeah, like uncanny valley and stuff.
You know what I, you know what doesn't make sense to me is
whenever white people get caught saying the n-word,
I'm calling it the n-word now.
I've changed my ways.
Whenever white people get caught saying the n-word,
they give that excuse.
It was like, hey, man, you know, I'm not racist.
I have a lot of black friends.
I know black people, you know, that's like people.
That's like the quintessential stereotypical fucking white person excuse.
But really, I think it would be a better defensive yourself
to say that you have no black friends.
Like if you get caught saying it,
you should be able to say like, hey, I don't have any black friends.
I'm not hurting anyone's feelings who I care about.
I'm just saying it because I don't care.
I don't know anybody.
Dude, it's just like how my heroes, Mike Pence and Ninja,
the face of Twitch, they won't associate with women.
I do the same with black people, man.
I've got a policy where I'm just not going to, you know,
look, I know I'm not racist because I refuse to associate with blacks.
Wait, wait, they won't associate with women.
Well, it's a thing where they won't engage in like private meetings
because like if they're alone,
they don't want to like have rumors start or, you know,
I read an actual defense.
Well, it's different with Ninja versus Mike Pence.
Well, okay, I'm talking about Ninja.
Yeah.
He won't stream with female streamers because he has a point.
Femoid streamers is the term he used, I believe.
Yeah.
Because people like make you rumors and say,
ha, are they cheating?
Are they going to have sex?
Am I going to make a rule 34 of Ninja and this female streamer?
So he says he's not going to stream with any, you know,
female streamers who want to stream with him because of that.
Yeah.
That's the unfortunate curse of being popular with the kids
is that they will draw rule 34 shipping of yours.
So just what happened to the game grumps a lot of time.
I'm so fucking mad.
Whenever I say I want more PCP porn,
everyone always draws shit fucking art that's like,
oh, ha, ha, MS Paint.
No.
We need to get Shadman involved.
We need to get him involved in this situation.
I want to be in the big leagues.
I want to make it big in the world and have people draw
all the wrong porn of me and my friends.
Funny story about Shadman.
I heard second hand.
I don't know if I'm exactly supposed to relate this fact,
but I don't see who would be harmed by it.
So whatever.
Okay.
You know that comics guy, Maryweather, who I know, kind of.
Well, he was doing, he had his, like a YouTube channel where he
would interview some more or less famous internet people.
And he was apparently supposed to interview Shadman.
And he got Shadman in the call.
And I guess he and this other guy, EZK, were talking about it
beforehand and they discussed what they were going to say.
And like before the interview started, Maryweather asked him like,
Hey man, so like, are you a pedophile?
And this, I think he was asking it as a joke or something,
but Shadman took it super seriously and got really offended,
you know, as you might.
And like basically just like tank the whole interview after that
and like wouldn't give any real answers to any questions.
So the thing like ended up never happening.
Well, okay.
That doesn't like incriminate him or anything.
He could just be sensitive.
Like I would be fucking mad if someone asked me that.
And like especially cause like I know probably a lot,
like a lot of people say that about him legitimately.
So he's probably like extra sensitive.
That sounds like somebody overstepping.
True or not.
It sounds like somebody overstepping their bounds is to like,
that this person is like edgy, right?
So I can say really edgy things to them and they won't mind.
Like I don't have to be polite.
I mean, we all know that like in the modern era,
like just the accusation like is smoke and you know,
people just assume where there's smoke, there's fire and shit.
So like, you know, it's a little touchy, a little touchy there.
Sure.
Yeah.
I mean, I can kind of understand both why the question was asked
and also why it was a disaster.
I think Shadman is an interesting guy though.
So I mean, it's too bad.
It's too bad it didn't.
I'd like to hear.
I'm gonna be best friends with Shadman,
have him come on the podcast.
Why is Shadman so popular?
I'd have him on.
Exactly.
Because he makes Burger King foot lettuce porn and you know, what not.
What?
Oh, that explains it.
That explains everything.
Yeah, he makes like porn of basically every meme and shit that comes on.
I feel, yeah, it's really bad.
It's that he taps into the meme market and makes pornography
that it is, like the fact that it is a porn of a meme
is meme worthy and people share it and that's why he's well known.
That's a weird thing to be the most popular guy who does.
It's not, I don't think he's the most popular because of that.
A lot of the time it's because he like takes, like, you know,
he does normal stuff and then he does like really out there stuff
and people are like, oh my god Shadman.
His stuff makes me feel like really prudish and uncomfortable.
I don't know.
I agree.
I'd have you a Shadman call us.
Come on the show buddy.
Get in here.
Let's do it.
Get in here and defend yourself.
Defend yourself against the accusation that your porn is kind of weird looking
and sort of makes me feel dirty.
That's fair, that's fair.
Shit.
Did you guys see, now that we've thoroughly poisoned this podcast
with racial slurs and talk of pedophilia.
Oh crap, we did.
It's time to plug something.
Yeah.
Did you guys see that the guy Tectonic Improv did a PCP style lecture?
Of course.
You mentioned that, but I did not watch it.
He picked up, I watched it.
He picked up the lecture torch and he did like a full on like two hour lecture
about a top the fourth wall, the Linkara series.
Just quick aside, you're aware of this.
Not about the person.
I was just going to say you're aware he's not the first one to pick up the lecture format.
There was What's His Face.
Who did those like, what were they, I think they were like PCP lore lectures or something.
Yes.
You know what I'm talking about?
I know your friend.
No.
Wait, wait, wait.
Was it just him like sitting in front of his computer though?
No, he had friends and he was doing like a reel in front of a board.
Like the audio was shit and like the one or two that I heard though, so it didn't really
work that well.
He put the series though, I think.
I think he did.
Sorry, I can't remember your name, dude, but if somebody tells me, we'll like put a link
or something.
Anyway, go ahead.
I don't remember that, but this Tectonic Improv atop the fourth wall, it's not about Linkara
the person, it's about like the lore of the atop the fourth wall series, which I didn't
know anything about.
It's pretty funny.
It gets pretty fucking wacky after a while.
The lore that goes on with that guy with the glasses people, I could never figure out all
of it because you'd have to watch all of their reviews all the way through because things
could happen in the middle.
It's like comic books, there's like too much continuity.
I was excited when it first started back in the day, I was like prominent on the forums.
I didn't like any of them, but because I was a part of the forums, I like through osmosis,
I had a lot of exposure to the whole Vekar the glasses culture and I mean that's like
a lot of what my old videos were sort of making fun of and satirizing because of the whole
like oh here's a character and it's just me in like a new t-shirt but this version's
evil and we have to battle for the fate of the world but like with no real self-awareness
how silly it was, like they took it completely seriously and all the endless crossovers with
all the different people on the site and they were all so bad.
I don't have a point to this, they were all so bad.
Even Spoonies was like he seemed to be like pretty self-aware except when it came to the
skits he did where you go like big on the makeup and big on the serious tone.
Spoonie was like easily by far the most talented of anyone on that site but like he fell into
the trap of making his content their way and it sort of ruined his content and eventually
it fucking ruined him and he just now he's sad and it's sad to see that he's sad and
like his whole audience has turned on him and it's like it's like the worst fate that
can befall any of us.
I saw the down the rabbit hole about him, yeah he seems like he's kind of not doing so well
let's all give our hopes and prayers to Spoonie, let's all raise our hands and try to give
him our fucking power, he needs it, he needs to spirit bomb himself.
For me the saddest thing and I think about this a lot like when I'm kind of tweeting
a bunch and like haven't produced a video in a while to see him I don't know if he is
like super recent but in all those videos he's like so active on Twitter so like you
know he's like right there but just something's preventing him from like making content whatever
it is like inside him or he just I don't know maybe he's scared to repose because he'll
get all much shit and stuff.
From what he describes of himself I mean these are his own words about his own like mental
problems he's got like everything like he's bipolar he's manic depressive he's like he's
always been that but then you take all that and then you combine it with like the stress
of internet drama which we all know and just how much of a grind this can be even for something
for someone of perfect mental health.
Hey you know what I thought I saw the other day which warned my heart a little bit like
I know he's had his issues with like all the that guy with the glasses guys but like you
know that legendary moment of him and angry Joe at whatever conference that was where he
just goes be trail or whatever yeah and like they like there's a bunch of people like got
mad at them because apparently like that quote unquote lack of professionalism like cost people
like there was a I heard one guy whining about how that the interview the interview with
not the interview with not oh my god my channel would have gotten a million subs if I got this
one I know is a stepping stone whatever the point is like I was just watching a fucking
angry Joe just review which are pretty good videos that I like even in this day and like
just like what like angry Joe just says I think about Fallout 76 he's just like yeah this
game betrayed me be trail and I'm just like that you that's Spoonie you remember your
friend Spoonie yes I saw that cute I really like yeah he um yeah bring Spoonie on for
a fucking video Joe just do it you have millions of subs if I could bring him back yeah I wish
if I could like do an interview with Spoonie if he were like open to taking like anything
like that from anyone but I know that he probably wouldn't like I bet that Spoonie isn't a place
now where anyone who approaches him he assumes is a troll and like I know that feeling like
I totally get it he's just like he's he's sunk so far that like he's in like a bad place
now and it's just sad to look at man needs like when it comes to his YouTube presence
like I'm not trying to fucking psychoanalyze the guy but I like he needs like sincere people
who just want to help him and like just like give him a little bit of confidence like get
back and like he's obviously taken a lot of flack for shit that he you know is guilty
of and he is imperfect in a lot of ways and he has clearly made quite a few mistakes but
like of course there's always also shit that he takes that probably was outside of his control
and probably wasn't that a big deal but now because you know all of the shit has coalesced
into like a massive wall of hate so like even the shit that's not really that big a deal
is mixed in with the shit that he did do wrong so like I he's probably like just he feels
like you can't get out of it you can't do anything right anymore these these waves of
hatred are fairly transient though relatively speaking so like like the current though the
wave of hate at Spoonie's been in the doghouse for like years now and like and like he could
like yeah he could just totally come back and like make a good video in the style of
if he just started making the same stuff he used to make like I think a lot of people
yeah like just come right back people hate him but they want him to be able to make a
comeback like I've seen like his yeah that's ever his subreddit of like all of his former
jaded fans who just fucking hate him now and like as much as they hate him like if he found
the strength to like really go at it again I think he could make a comeback yeah I think
so yeah yeah I agree everybody I've really never watched much of his content but everybody
talks about him pretty well yeah if you've if anyone out there has like never seen Spoonie
if you if you just know him as the guy who sucks now and everybody hates him and doesn't
make any content and lines about Trump on Twitter and you don't get what the big deal
is like I his fucking Spoonie's Ultima retrospective is like one of the best things ever on the
internet it's like one of the best sort of video essay reviewer retrospective things that
I've ever seen I still think it holds up I watched it pretty recently so anyone who doesn't
know how good Spoonie was watch that or like his his ultima video I'm googling that his
ultimate retrospective or his like Highlander videos he was good he was cool yeah first
result when I when I Google Spoonie Ultima is Ultima retrospective complete no skits HD
all the yeah people went in and took the skits I get it but yeah yeah it's they're not for
everybody they're not for everybody I mean well some of those skits aren't like there's like five
second clips of him just doing a silly voice in an medieval costume and like that's okay you
can leave that in but I assume they got rid of all of them probably probably yeah I wonder if
that means they took out the live act like all the live action bits because like I can understand
not liking the skits and thinking that they drag but like part of the ultimate series like the
sort of climax of it is this one like near the end of it he goes on this one long take of just
like a live action bit of him just kind of talking about like when he was a kid and his brother would
play ultimate with him and it gets it like really emotional and that's like the climax of the whole
series and it's like really cut that part yeah like the dude is a great performer and a great actor
and it sucks that he I guess hates himself and wants to die I'm certainly we all know that
feeling indeed I do know the feel of hating yourself and wanting to die I ain't got no
iPhone my heart is racing thinking suicide I don't got no iPhone left turn left turn of a
subject matter here but Ben on your suggestion I tried Instacart Instacart yeah the delivery
service I'll tell you I signed up for the free one month trial bam in one hour I had my fucking
shampoo and deodorant I needed I had some fucking bread I had whatever the fuck else I bought a bunch
of shit and it was fantastic yeah I'm doing it maybe it maybe I should just bite the bullet and
sign up for the subscription it's $100 for a year and that's probably less if you do it a lot so
that's probably less than it yeah there's some hints back when I first started talking about
Hello Fresh you you you stated meantime before about how frequently you use Grubhub for things
yes do you have any interest in cooking food do I have any interest yes technically yes
you just turn into fucking Xavier renegade Angel for a second like want to become a
cook massive relying on Grubhub and spending copious amounts of money well do I want to rely on
Grubhub no of course I don't want to rely on Grubhub but I also don't give a shit about I just want
to not worry about it and have my nutrition that's all are you trying are you trying to push Hello
Fresh no okay however I'm ready to fucking fight I'm ready to fucking fight about however I fucking
hate you Ben and everything you ever say is fucking so stupid and make Hello Fresh is the worst
I okay what it does what a disaster Ben you are such a fucking freaking asshole maybe I could
cook maybe I could cook my own food for more than it would cost me to go out to a restaurant and buy
it hmm good good idea the whole point of Hello Fresh is just to build confidence it's not so that you
can use it for all of your cooking forever it is simply for new cooks and families who want to
have easy instructions so like Nate says they don't have to worry about just fucking google a recipe
it's the easiest thing sure I'm not saying that's unviable I'm just saying that there is a use I'm
saying it's strictly better I hate you
I'm unmount you side with this one okay it's fair yeah I can see that anyway I'm gonna be doing
that a lot it's gonna change the game um Instacart's rad say it's like it's it's not that expensive
and it saves you fucking like a several hour trip to the goddamn grocery store I'm saving gas money
too I mean it's got to make up some of the difference so you know yeah yeah um incidentally
saves me saves me like a fucking hours walk through the bitter cold yeah it's pretty great
it's pretty great yeah I have things to discuss uh uh but does anybody else have any other subjects
they want to bring up before we we talk about stuff I mean last subject I tried to bring up I was
cut halfway through when we went into a conversation about Burger King and Wendy's so I'm just gonna
resign myself to comment you know other people now I'm sorry I didn't mean to cut you off and
make you feel sad with that Wendy's bit I just I don't know Nate it was Nate's fault he said to
say talk about something else and I didn't know what to do hey hey Jesse just make sure you open
all of your packages come in the mail for the next two weeks okay I'd be sure to give him a big sniff
test open them inhale deeply before you do anything else well I'm just gonna I mean I mean just
just put just just poke out all the wires you can hey hey don't worry about the the beeping noise
just uh just just set it down and open it yep yep a bunch of ghosts for bomb I go for anthrax okay
that's good I mean we can team up really that's true what if we blow anthrax all over his house so
we can't escape uh hey wait wait hold on I'm sure there are a lot of people who want other people
to not be breathing anymore what if we kill people for money and then we take that money and spend it
on more weapons to kill people for more money oh my god we've just evolved into the people killers
with a c podcast this is it well this is it send send us a request for who you want us to kill and
we will uh dude we will split up with some people are dying directly so yeah um all right my life
and I want to die I don't got no iphone should we should we go to voicemails let's go straight to
the fucking voicemails I think uh we got we got a bunch today we got I got like 15 of these
mother fuckers but they're good they're quality ones oh wait is that Tom is Tom here I am here
Tom's been here the whole time yeah oh huh there was a bit I wanted to bring up earlier about books
but it's too late now so fuck it let's go to voicemails talk about books talk about books talk
about books talking about how like good book series and I wanted to just go out on the limb again
and say anamorph's is good everyone judged a book by their covers and fucked up I'm a hundred percent
positive I was thinking about an anamorph's retrospective I was thinking about maybe if I
wanted to do that's my next pcb lecture I'm doing it on anamorph's wait oh really confirmed
oh maybe maybe I subconsciously stole the idea okay well quick but it's so fucking long aren't they
just like uh like four children I I can I can I can believe I can believe that anamorph's is like
really good because all I know about it is that it's extremely long extremely complex and I like
homestuck so like it could be the books are written yeah incredibly simplistically the font's big the
words are just like very simple uh it's a children's book but the story if you like listening to
trump speak you're gonna love exactly it's like a trump wrote books uh but like the the whole thing
is about like an alien invasion like this like intergalactic politics and like the the effects
of war on children that's what the series is about boring what phone type they use to the use
there's like there's like straight up oh yeah there's tons of like like yeah that's true
fucking like cutting off of limbs born dying yeah it's fucking crazy there's one part been
there's I remember I remember a part where like a horc bezier like stabs his fucking hand blade
into marco as he's transformed into gorilla and he looks down and sees like a gaping a whole
yeah torso and says that he can see his gorilla inside it's fucking sick did anyone ever read um
I read a bunch of the spin-off books I was way into it I what's it called like the not the
andolite chronicles there was one of like the the whole yeah there's an antler chronicles or viscer
there it's actually not even though there's like one like god
the elements yeah yeah elements the elements yeah he's like he's like the elements the elements
book is the only thing I remember like he's like you he's like you my father is a festus I'm attending
camp half blood I have a best friend who is a gargoyle and we go on adventures together
and we and I have great Greek mythology inspired adventures together listen to this fucking zoomer
with his uh yeah Percy Jackson precious little life Percy Jackson you know I'm glad you brought up
the versus the versus the I'm glad you brought up the impudence of the younger generation because
I really have a problem with these fucking young people I'm sick of them it's not a bit it's not a
joke I hate young people I don't like them I want them to die every time there's a school shooting
I secretly am happy I don't like teenagers and I want there to be less of them one less
yeah yeah that's it that's it that's all I want that that's the only thing I ever wanted to say
and now I retire they don't look they don't like what I like and it makes me mad Percy Jackson is so
fucking cool he gets to talk about the person and they talk about the fucking they don't know
shit they don't know anything they don't know what's really real and what's truly true they don't
know what's really good they don't they only know about like whatever the fuck uh
dude I love dog funny dog trying to make it more good they mock the past they mock the foundation
that their lives are built upon they don't even know the pillars the cornerstones of our culture
that they just disregard flagrantly get some fucking culture zoomers watch dog they care about
you don't you don't know fucking Alex Mack you don't know the secret world of Alex Mack she turned
into a fucking funnel and went under these doors you don't know that shit you don't know
fucking Clarissa explaining it all for us where do you go when you need something like nowhere you
got nothing you know nothing it's okay how many how many months do you have the dog we had digimon
we had multiple months okay we can we can choose between months back in the day we can watch
Pokemon over here we can watch season 1 over there they were totally the best shows
his greek adversaries in combat his great future madden in the world with so much to them
he's a lovely character I mean who's more lovely than he is he has a power of one in the
thousand you can't even decide who's more lovable he's the son of our fucking god Ken itchy joe g
and she's a bow and he's a smart because girls are smart and she's a brunette she's just
worlds you got your pokemon over here the black digimon over there and pokemon still around
your little imputed welps are still playing pokemon game we lay the foundation for everything
that you think it's game one enough enough understood that's good percy jackson barrett
does funny race war race war race war age war age war isn't even a demigod you shouldn't even be allowed
to like pokemon if you're under 26 he has a rich in her life munchie he has a rich in her life
that all right good understood good points everybody all around um what's doug's friends
like joe it's like it's like sketer no sketer oh i thought sketer was the bad guy that's that's
roger that's roger ben you look like fucking sketer all right uh let's let's go voicemails
people it's time uh we gotta gotta go do it um uh before we get to the actual voicemails there
was a voicemail that isn't a voicemail um but listen to it and then you'll know what i mean here we go
die
yeah they'll fuck you they suck that's the intro yeah that they supplied
yay thanks dude uh that was from okay i mean they said their name was voicemail intro theme so i'm
just calling them that i don't i don't know who they were beyond that i'm for it i'm a fan i think
didn't we get one before that i completely didn't get uh shit i think that one was like way better
this one was still good it's from one spark right great oh no no we'll never know i want to hear it
oh hey we had a topic like actually like pre-written before this episode about how we're gonna argue
about the intro oh shit i forgot about that oh oh yeah the intro sucks in every one of the
one in the entire world every episode bitch oh oh the the the intro so i admit if i were a new
listener to this podcast i would never listen to it because the intro would turn me off so much
fuck you the intro sucks sasuke pro is a fucking champion and his intro is great it makes me laugh
every time as if this podcast would ever have a new listener anyway there's no such thing as a new
pcp fan we pride we pride ourselves on our high barrier to entry uh listen the pcp has a high
better for worse okay we're gonna have to do another theme contest everyone send in your suggestions
to the pcp voicemail and we'll listen to them weekly the theme contest was fucking based and you
know it okay but here's the point uh uh we we see we see this vocal minority assuming that
is okay commenting that they don't like the theme so here so here's what we're gonna do here's we're
gonna do nothing imagine imagine being such a fucking low iq pennant that every single episode
you have to see yeah just hold your you have you have to say something like man i sure am still mad
that the that the my favorite pcp theme didn't win that a different theme song is the theme song
get get over it imagine someone having criticisms of the show of the audio podcast
show imagine being so fucking useless that you that you are still talking about it that you're
still complaining different people every time everyone's just waking up to it at different
times i i don't think i don't think that's correct munchie but it doesn't matter what i think
because we're gonna just use hard data here's what we're going to do why doesn't everyone
everyone who edits just use the the theme that they like i do i do i fucking put a different song
in sometimes yeah i use the main one like half the time and i use a different one why does the
intro have to be like an important thing like a random stone it's not that question it's fucking
nuts um it's okay well anyway here's what we're gonna do uh it's gonna be a link to a fucking straw
poll vote in it for i don't know i'll probably do like uh if you if you're happy with the current one
if you want it changed and maybe i'll put some options for like specifically what do you change
okay or something no don't don't i don't have a spoiler all right all right i won't try to split
no i i just i just want to i just want to yeah okay yeah go and vote and with the full knowledge
that we're not gonna do anything about the results of the poll the poll means nothing here's the
the purpose of this poll is because i think it really is a small number who even care so if like
first of all if like 10 people vote it doesn't matter fine if like a thousand people vote or
whatever and i think very few of them will actually complain about like the main theme song
but we're gonna find out because we could argue all day about it but i don't give a
shit about even my opinion i care about the numbers so that's what we're gonna do oh my god
we're no no no i'm putting my foot down we're not changing the theme song even if everyone
says we should we can't that's i'm not saying that we need that's fucking cowardly how is that
cowardly that's addressing problems with the show and then that's lip no listen i feel strong
that's literally pathetic that would be literally pathetic and disgusting are literally pathetic
and disgusting what is going on look i hate it i hate it well then i okay i mean i don't
think anybody else feels that this is what ben is outraged by and not me talking about like
school shooting and being in favor of them and whatnot look nobody hates nobody hates the
the zoomers are the problem they're the ones that are complaining in the comments i know it
that's i know it to be true let's be real it's a bunch of munchie heads out there we know if it's
zoomers complaining then i'm on ben's side let's throw them in the garbage a munchie
complains a lot about the main heads but we all know there's a strong condition of munchie heads
out there just shitting up you can tell you can tell by the fact that they don't say you can tell
by the fact that they don't say lol when they type it's it's it's it's i don't know what you see a
lot of grown-ups or grown-ups belong on the internet zoomers belong in a pot on the stove getting cooked
in a soup and they die in the food what do you want to concentrate them all in like camps of some
kind that might be a good way to you know separate them out um okay well we'll we'll get back to you
by the way it's entirely possible that everyone likes the intro but i just choose to believe that
everyone doesn't for my own we'll find out i don't choose to believe anything i just don't like
i like it a lot personally i'm still way into it i don't understand okay well fair enough but i
like it this is height moment nate has and why did it fucking win if everyone's such a everyone's
such a fucking bitch about the intro why did it fucking win the poll why did we collectively
vote for it because you're an idiot what does that fucking mean i'm actually mad i'm actually
fucking mad that you would say that um you just got pwned we all fucking voted and it won
and now we're so stupid for liking the intro we all voted for it and not once upon a time
Ben you're making our side look unreasonable please restrain yourself i don't understand
i don't understand one single point i'd not one single point did i give that so i don't
guys it was just that there's a majority win i don't fucking get this fucking lip that i'm
receiving in your opinions but just think of poor sasuke pros ego out there just the center of
all this controversy not sasuke pro and bad feelings he doesn't deserve this he doesn't deserve this
he's a good boy um but okay let's he is a good boy we'll come back uh this ongoing discussion i guess
let's go to the next five the actual voicemail let's let's do it shall we okay all right first
voicemail this is from apparently even worst guy ever please go nate it is me worst guy ever
i am back with virgin vengeance and after hearing you talk about me on the pcp episode i shall i've
decided that the only way i could possibly possibly defeat you and the pcp and blue pill the world
is by creating my own rad con to rival yours i can't call it rad con for legal reasons the jewish
hierarchy won't allow it but what i can guarantee i can do is go over and create lame con lame con
forever oh my god shall take over the world and and then we'll get a house somewhere on a deserted
island and we'll have our own munchie and our own blackjack and pokus and we'll make you look like
a bunch of fools i feel special that he's uh uh uh you're you ain't so tough now with your loving
family and your supportive friends oh god i'm so alone there it is i'm i'm i'm kind of worried
about this i'm i'm a little concerned that he might he might make us look like we've got to watch out
for the for the nega aka the new pcp uh and their lame con uh it's gonna be a new arc coming up god
maybe i'll defect and go to lame god i love and appreciate comedy where a guy is terrible and
also hates himself it's my favorite shot it's so relatable all right uh well okay he's irrelevant
as worst gaver is in everything he does next call this is from um tar buck transom let's let's see
him mom always said that stupid is as stupid does daddy always said the capitalism is as
capitalism does what's something that's broadly hated that you think is unfairly maligned or
something that's widely beloved that gets way more credit than it deserves the theme song what
happened to his voice flash from that accent change yeah that was that was like two different
ones did anyone did anyone else get a asmr head tingles from him talking about your game don't
address it i have no idea what just happened the first half of that was like some set up for
like a racist forest gum and then it just turned into some fucking irish guy just space i think he
was was he well just asking a regular question yeah irish it sounded like a what did he even say
he asked like what do we think is unfairly maligned i think or what is overrated diet soda
over praise i was so faping faping by the change in uh an accent there that i completely didn't
even process yeah it was like a me i'm a wacky character what are your guys plans for 2019
what was the question it was like what's undervalued that's overvalued things that are unfairly
maligned or things that are overly beloved and don't deserve it like overvalued undervalued my
answer undervalued the pcp theme song diet soda vaping things that things people people shit on
all of them for no reason and they're all just they're all just stuck in their ways they're all
just afraid to embrace the future they're all good for you undervalued double decker a good
anime that no one ever talks about never heard of it exactly uh and undervalued i'm gonna fix it
radcon forever fund it now good good good job what a double double decker the anime sequel
to uh blade runner where decker meets another decker and they have to decide which one of
them is the replica that uh and then they both this is the original show these are original
show that spawned double batman the uh the breakout success that would come later
i'm trying to think of something that is unfairly maligned but i'm drawing a blank there's lots of
things that i like that are good but i don't think anybody hates them yeah i mean i don't know
like just the first thing that comes to the top of my head is a lot of people think that gun buster
is way better than die buster but i humbly disagree but like who gives a shit because they're both
good and everyone okay all right yeah everyone loves both of them here's something that that that's
more maligned than needs to be uh uh people who are affluent like rich people and i don't mean this
as in like people who are poor shouldn't get mad rich people for having money like that sort of
side of it i just mean mo like like i have had the pleasure of meeting one or two rich people
it and rich i mean just like not like rich rich but as in they can afford a good apartment in the
city which is where i'm sitting right now uh and uh and and they're really nice and they're all like
you know they all eat food and they're all just like yeah you know let's go out and let's walk around
today let's go out to dinner i'm like yeah dude i like to do i like to go out and have dinner
so that's why i like rich people yeah but yeah but they're doing every everything they're doing
they're doing on the back of hoarding resources that other people need that's fine and that they
and that they don't deserve if i'm friends with rich people then they'll give me things for free
because i was gonna say they will give me things you see oh oh yeah that i guess i guess i guess you're
right i guess you're right about all that i always felt like notch um billionaire now who sold
Minecraft was like i mean he's maligned enough but like is he well at the outset of like like
selling the company to microsoft uh he lost all his friends and he was really sad and i just felt
like that was a bit fucked up but i guess i can see it this is unfairly maligned is such a weird
like thing like unfairly in like what content like how big is it unfair i just don't like seeing
people be upset i i think rich people deserve more i agree i definitely wait wait wait hold on backup
it's me muncher from the future i i i just saw the wacky and crazy plot line that will be revealed
in two years and nine days to this exact date so check the pcb channel at that exact time for the
wacky plot that i've just established and will forget about i've just come back to make sure that
everyone knows that what i just said maybe five months ago was retarded and it was actually true
but here's the real thing that i'm about to say right now rich people are good because they're
smarter unironically they are smarter every rich person i've ever met is smarter than poor
people that's actually true that yeah that's cuz they fucking got to go to fucking college
because they didn't have to fucking take out a loan exactly i mean that's true yeah well ben it
sounds like oh my god i'm what's what's interesting about this man is that so you seem to be complaining
and not too fond of this d of like you're born into the privilege of wealth or something like that
yeah uh however we were both born into some pretty decent wealth yeah i know yeah i know
okay listen that's true and yeah i'm privileged but it's not fair sure it's not it's like the
things that i had growing up it's not fair lots of people didn't have them and you know here's the
thing if if i don't know if like the one percent of like billionaires out there you know didn't
weren't billionaires then those resource like like more people could have had what we had okay but
consider this and it's it's it's fucked up please consider this fact it's not cool it's not fucking
cool being rich is wrong and it's bad it is and i agree and i hate the fact that people who are rich
when people are when you're rich it's easier for you to be a good person so they they get away
true with just like like life is even regardless of how much money they have life is just easier if
you've had money because you don't have the fucking mental disorders and insanity that you
gain from a life of having nothing and fucking suffering at every goddamn turn i hate people
who have the privilege of being mentally sound and okay i hope that they all suffer i want to see
them all but be broken logic if you're just born with a disability you should be furious at everyone
who doesn't have you absolutely should absolutely no it doesn't do any good god damn it that's not
the point you just have to survive and do your best well it's it's it's it's different because
like if it's a genetic disability then there's nothing anyone could do about it but like if
your disability is being destitute yeah there is something we could have done about that as a society
but we we didn't it is we let that happen it's very important in my opinion to preserve the ability
to pursue wealth even at very high levels to and like and being poor desire is like a disability
that that no one cares about or even notices at a glance if you see a guy with no legs everyone
knows well his life's hard obviously he has no legs we should you know everything that he does
is better because he did it without having any legs but nobody looks at a poor person or a person
whose life is just regular and crappy and says well everything he does is better because he's
fucking poor his life sucks he had to overcome everything just to get out the fucking door
today and and get like a job just to afford a crappy apartment above a bowling alley that's
a fucking miracle anyone who has an apartment is is a god you've done something incredible and no
one fucking cares i think you i think we all accept the basic fact i think shadow the hedgehog
is unfairly like people make fun of it i know nate nate i think yeah i think you should be able
to pursue wealth but the the amount of wealth that people can aspire to is insane and horrible
and a nightmare like nobody nobody deserves a billion under but people can no nobody deserves
under appreciate is good shoes oh my god everyone who thinks like oh you know i can just get by with
some cheap shoes it's fine and you know oh yeah my feet just hurt that's just part of being human
right no not at all my friend you go and find yourself some nice fitting shoes i myself have
wide alligator snout feet they are wide and broad just like my mother and so i have to get
specialty shoes and let me tell you it's more expensive but it's way way worth it these things
are like a dream i have specialty wide art supporting flip flops and shoes which i spent like two
months allowance on to get to get uh both of them and it was totally fucking worth it and absolutely
they're great they're so fucking great muchy and i love them and i never have any pain whatsoever
they deserve to be praised they deserve to be everyone deserves to have good shoes
muchy did you say you have like a high arc on your feet uh yeah oh same high five yes hey do
you guys know why you're able to buy these wonderful uh customized you know wide foot
alligator i don't like to tell right now so i'm gonna i'm gonna take out my headphones they don't
want to hear about because capitalism and people pursuing wealth on a high no no everybody
yeah yeah we would never we would never have shoes that fit if fucking Jeff Bezos didn't have like
800 billion dollars for making a website no what you would have is like do i need to explain the
benefits of mass market capitalism i don't think i do i think you know very well that it's yeah i know
i know there i know there are benefits i know there are all the world needs to understand
obviously it works obviously it works to everyone who is poor is inherently a hero and everyone who
is rich is inherently evil and a villain and should die yeah that's all that's true i only hate
rich people on their assholes and out of touch but you know i only hate poor people on their assholes
it's easy for a rich person not to be an asshole exactly it's so easy okay then look it's so easy
and yet they still choose to be assholes shaking literally shaking literally here it goes you've
been watching too much h bomber guy ben you gotta relax there he's getting a piece of the papers
i can't harris has harris has opened my third eye and now i perceive everything wrong with the world
listen when when you're rich when you're rich you don't have to fuck anyone over to get ahead
because you're already ahead when you're poor who's being knocked over by we'd have to get
the specific i don't know it's a doggy dog world people come poor man it's a constant it's a jungle
out there it's a real war outside your front door people commit okay just let me say one last
people commit people commit crime and steal shit because they're fucking poor and that's gonna they
need something right and i agree for them every time a but maybe you're crime but rich people are so
rich people are so good and magnanimous they never steal anything they never break into my house and
steal my shit yeah no shit they don't do that then you're okay if if your solution to this ben
mean mean it's just like shoes okay we just like shoes we're not here to discuss capitalism we
just like good shoes it's in paradise i mean one phrase uh taxation is theft if i don't want to
give someone something the government comes and forces me to give it that's theft how do you
justify that oh because other people needed it uh that's not good enough yeah oh my god are you
fucking are you dead serious i am dead you're dead serious about taxation absolutely oh my god
you're a villain nate you're a fucking villain okay let's do this another time someone post the
comments how i'm wrong because honestly i've heard that capitalism has already run amuck the fact
that someone like jeff bezos can exist is proof of capitalism has run amuck that's not a complete
thought that's not a moral argument it is a fucking moral argument he has more money than anyone
should be allowed to have other people fucking need that shit and what's he doing with it i don't
running amazon it doesn't fucking take that much fucking pizos the clown
okay well only point small point it's just that i think presented with the exact same information
ben you i think understandably are concerned with how it seems unbalanced and unfair i get that
my concern goes more to okay given that this is reality what can be done to benefit people in it
and so i focus kind of more on that aspect i think you focus on the other i literally think we
i literally think we should just take but jeff bezos's money i literally think we should just
do to an extent via taxes but we should take a lot we should take i think that we should i get it
probably work on uh together as a as a culture we should all get work on uh assassinating the
royal family and redistributing their wealth oh oh here's something that i'd like i'd like to do
i prefer to do it non-violently first i talked to you was like oh i fucking hate the monarchs oh
they have so much fucking money it's so fucked up they're still kings and queens jeff green likes it
um it's cool that kings and queens exist the queen is a nice lady i saw her once on tv
she's she's fine listen they're fine it's just a it's the it's just the same shit they're just
another dynasty they just have a title that like that like other rich people don't have but it's the
same shit they just inherit their wealth i mean they're just i mean they're fucking they're obviously
you know like luciferian wealth hoarders who like sacrifice children and eat babies and satanic
rituals to prolong their lives i mean but you know they seem like nice people i mean yeah
she waves really politely on tv in a little armored car correlating wealth with just evil
yeah i am can we can we move on guys it is fucking it is fucking wrong that people have so much
what other people have so little it's fucking wrong let's move on please we're not gonna go anywhere
this is why why why you got okay why are you guys so afraid of talking about a real thing only
because i think it's boring to people that's why i'm not afraid to talk about is it not on the
podcast because we're not going anywhere i mean we've got major whining about how you know it's
you want to hear about camelism and i feel like commenters oh my god i i i we here we are having
like a genuine ideological we're having like a genuine ideological disagree and we have an
actual thing to talk about that we have strong opinions about and we're all like backing off
we're not going to have a real conversation about it it's not going to actually bear any fruit
it's just going to be people screaming at one other at the end of the podcast i guess that is my fear
as well that's the whole fucking we're not going to do anything no matter what value is the real
point so that will be entertaining people will enjoy it people fucking people fucking listen to
this shit no people people listen to people talk about real things all the time i i because they
actually have insight it's not just us or you read i just i look dialogue going on my thing is
that i try to keep it a reverent because i i'm very afraid of being seen as a person who
thinks that my opinion matters yeah okay i don't want to be seen as a creature of vanity
it's it's too it's too it's too late we're all already no i want to i want to remove all vanity
all ego from my existence i want to just exist and be i want to talk about like cheerios i think
that plain cheerios are unfairly maligned they don't need to be honey not they can just be playing
and you can put your own yeah actually i i'll agree with that a hundred percent yeah cheerios
say we can talk for hours about how much i love i mostly feel that i've basically fully articulated
my feelings on the on the subject anyway you know honey not honey not pretty excellent sometimes i
forget how much i do enjoy that honey and then i nut that's how it goes all right over on to the
next uh voicemail okay here we go we have 14 more of these this one's from real rogane let's uh go
gamifying masturbation shut this off
is it is it would it be like if if you masturbate that's like going more hollow and that's a bad thing
you just try not to forever yeah is is is do you win or lose if you know that november like a thing
is that is that content is that stupid that's kind of a game i guess that is kind of masturbation
is not a game i take it very seriously i've always heard like the one sort of game is how many times
can you do it in a day um you know that's a that's yeah probably theoretically i think there was a
boy that died from doing that too much well was that like over a span of time because he like didn't
eat and he like was only doing that or something or was it more that he literally i didn't read the
story i just saw something i would i would be i would be surprised if you could kill yourself in
one day but maybe if you were going for like weeks maybe if you're a true hero you could do it yeah
maybe one of our fair viewers right out there is gonna be that hero yeah um all right let's move on
the point is game if we game well we can't do it if we gamify it i'll i'll do it during all of that
here's a real actual topic that's not a voicemail uh we've been talking murmurs you know there's just
been some some whispers here and there about brony con 2019 um literally let's just like get a panel
i don't think it would be that hard one of my friends who isn't even a pony person just like
asked for a panel and got one let's just get a panel for the pcp and they will fly us out there
i'm not fucking joking right now yes let's just do it yes yes absolutely would they would they
fly us out there that's the main thing um they would definitely pay for like our expenses in the
sense that like you know we wouldn't have to get a badge and stuff like that we'd be able to go
yeah so that's that's not enough there's a lot of money for me to go there um well we can talk
about it we can we can we can we can email them stuff like that if this is if this is a one weekend
event that costs me no money i would absolutely do it it's just a question of if it's going to
actually be that um so yeah i mean we look into it that's cool with me all right i'm pretty sure
i could get there for not that much yeah i don't mind paying even a little bit of money um but you
know i just don't want to be like a big labor right okay okay if they pay for my hotel and my ticket
i will go uh i'm yeah i don't think they usually do that for panel uh this is really relevant
announcement my cat is on the table and he's adorable that is all excellent will he be at
brony con no well then who gives a shit there's my question oh no no he's not he's never made a
fucking youtube video you're not a real human being if you haven't made a youtube video well
he's like yeah you know don't don't it's not you making youtube videos is so human when when uh
facebook inevitably goes under because facebook is currently the repository of all human information
it's going to be youtube accounts that are the sole currency that we use and only those people
with youtube accounts it's going to be a dystopian nightmare where literal political influence is
determined by subscriber count and is it is it not already that's not even not okay i guess right
just indirectly do voicemail do voicemail do voicemail that was a joke but okay all right
next one is uh cool guy is a completionist uh here we go all right i'm i'm just being cool here
all right it's me again i will buy that fucking shirt soon yeah and yeah i have a dilemma for you
guys i have finished all of the episodes of the procrastinator's podcast i've watched every
single fucking one hundred and bonus 30 or 40 episodes on earth and i've watched all the lectures
what a mistake um the amazing content yes good and i want some more shit to watch i don't know
but to watch i don't want to watch your individual shit because it's not the group it's just one
person and individually all of your content sucks
the weaga whatever the shit it's fucking gay anime and i'm trying to watch in the the decompression
chamber and it's fucking gay all of your shit is gay okay i tried arm retrieval like what the
fuck is home stuck kill yourself i fucking hate you i was on your side and now i hate you
hen home stuck okay um like you uh i don't know give me some content to watch i hear you guys
talk about this aps adventures stop saying what the fuck is a t-bap and how do i find it all right
i was gonna yeah um t-bap is the ultimate pcp content yeah um i was i was gonna say uh i was
gonna say like i have a playlist of every video i've ever been in and digi has one too do you
guys have i know i'm not i'm not that's totally complete yes i do have one i do have one but that's
the thing this guy doesn't give a shit about yeah yeah we're one of best well but he's asking about
t-bap he's asking if he wants group like like if he wants group stuff there's the podd cast uh
there's this chibi backers there's the pony car so in code there's the old there's the old uh
horse casts yep true the horse and yeah the horse is tbbap but actually the yeah the horse cast is
a great idea uh that's a good one on uh that's on digi's channel and i think on jesse i don't know
those those horse casts are like very old like a couple years old and i'm worried about the person
that i was when i recorded them jesse i watched them all extremely recently there's nothing
that i think you would be object to i think you've said way worse things on this very
i'm terrified of anything i've said over a week ago
as we are i watched them like six months ago they're fine um okay but anything else the best
answer is endless war endless war uh i mean i made a vow to not say that or the name of the show
that which it comes from this episode i made a vow to myself well well i did make any such
i will just i assume you've listened to the bonus episodes but if not that's 21 episodes
right there available so i mean you've probably already watched them if you're a big fan but
five dollar this is pretty deep in there this is this is like deep pcp lore not a lot of people
know about about this particular genre of solo pcp content but there's this guy called mother's
basement and he makes some legit anime uh analysis video essay this guy is just you know he's so
he knows about any i don't know if i'm being sarcastic i don't even know if i'm doing a bit
right now i see yeah uh um some of his content to be quite honest though sometimes he does
waff a lot of it no i actually like jeff a lot i've i've seen like half of a mother's basement
video ever uh i mean it really depends i do like most of his content i he had a video about dug
i mean i mean archie and he had a video about persie jackson and the olympians that i really
liked oh god oh i was really appealing to the zoomers with that one all right uh let's do the
next fucking call um this is from uh callum k64 apparently dumb so this is a question mainly
for munching so i'm gonna you said you wanted to go to college so you could actually work
it's okay things that you said online like when you yell the n word out on camera
we'll ever come back to like bite you in the ass later like if someone like in the place that
you're working at like see those videos i thought that was a good topic okay all right uh uh this
guy is asking a question which yeah pardon me but i feel like i've said this all before a thousand
times however like i guess like on scattered that name that show the show that won't be named
right streams of stuff and stuff like that uh but the short answer the cliff notes version after
boiling it over a thousand times uh yeah i'm scared it's making me shake my boots but you know
you just gotta do it and you know fucking you know used to have like what am i just going to like be
like it has the potential to ruin my life so i won't do what i want to do no i mean that there's
i mean there's a chance it won't and i think there's a pretty big chance it won't so i'm just
going to have to continue doing what i want in my life and hope that people don't take too seriously
what i said was when i was 15 i mean of course in our current culture that might be unlikely
but i mean you just got a chance it's only gonna get more common for people to be to like discover
like you know raunchy stuff people said when they were younger as time goes it's going to
become less and less of a big deal i think so yeah it really especially because of like like kids
nowadays these zoomers doing like open role play on twitter like erp like all over the place just
publicly like this all like totally out there yeah and then kids and that's just gonna be with them
forever they're gonna have a whole generation of people who have nothing to they can't hide anything
so so hiding stuff will not we won't be a big deal it's all gonna swing the other way like once
the once the zoomers start becoming irrelevant and a better newer generation takes their place
then maybe we'll be we'll have we'll have some room again the groomers
the tumors on the big the big bumping babies that's gonna be the name of
them
not the baby boomers just the big bumping babies the generation that hashtag stays babies and just
stays babies their whole life it's i'm waiting babies for life that's the millennials you did
already happen i guess you're right real ones stay thank god i have something this fun is i have
something i have something i have something unrelated uh to mention it's just a side note
thinking about the the t-bar made me remember okay so i said i've said before i'm making
though that winnie the pooh video and it's probably gonna be out right now when you're
listening to this uh but i googled a little bit and the only other person i could find who like
had reviewed episodes of the new adventures of one of the poo is someone that i think we know
it was a yeah it was a pony guy called the autistic brownie remember him oh yeah yeah he did
yeah he did a cut he's the only other guy so it's me and him man it's me once again
for like that's a crowded field for sure you're playing with the big boys now
i should reach i should reach out to him why not do a collab dog that's how you do a collab
yeah do a collab what do you have a pony you'll see you can do it autistic autistic brownie what are
you doing in my interview uh uh uh i i i also i chose that uh message that munchie responded
to already uh specifically just because uh i knew he had responded to it before but i i wanted to
double down and just add my voice to the chorus people uh that i also think that uh like just
imagine the world where anything you've said as a child or in any context can be absolutely stripped
of context and used you know in the worst possible way to disparage you maybe society will end up
that way but that just sounds like it did fucking be destroyed so whatever where they're all gonna
die anyway um so i definitely even on this podcast again i made extremely off-color jokes
but they are in fact fucking jokes and i can defend everything i've ever said uh in my humble
opinion and if people just don't accept that then frankly do you even want to like have yourself
in a situation where the people that like are judging you would make that determination and be
willingly uh willing to like strip things of context and condemn you even if you can make a
case i don't i would rather not even work for those people so you know i emancipate yourself
you're gonna be like mad sad nate you're just gonna be up on the you're gonna be up on the
testimonial block and everyone's they're gonna bring out the pedophile accusations and all your
leaked chat room things you're just like no it was a joke it was a joke that was all a joke
that's gonna be me yeah it's gonna it's gonna be me all right let's um that's that's a good
that was a good millennial reference these fucking zoomers won't understand it it won't
fucking get it all right uh next one's from i like it uh from the chad ideas guy let's uh
let's see what he's got for yeah you've all talked about inviting new guests onto the pcp for just
one episode or so so why haven't you all done it already like seriously it's getting uh it's
getting pretty dry with just the same old standard cast talking about the same old bullshit so why
don't we get some interesting characters in there that aren't prerecorded uh well hold on uh we
haven't had a guest in a long time first of all we haven't talked about it a long time and last
time we did we had like two people on we were planning to have someone but they they couldn't
make it they're okay well i remember remember the whole thing about when i was trying to get
laser by yes on here and he like led me on a fucking wild goose chase only very hard to get
that guess only to reveal that actually i have no internet or microphone so i can't be on well
yeah it was very it was very hard to depend on people people are worthless yeah uh yeah agreed
agreed um i'm just gonna throw out there you know i um uh i do think we should have i'm you know
what i'll make it up not a real commitment but uh zen huckstable come on the show come on the
show zen huckstable oh yeah i think you're cool oh yeah i like you so come on the show agreed um i
don't talk about it i just think it is down to uh two days ago oh sorry would you say jesse i think
i think we're all in agreement that guests are good it's just that we're all stupid and lazy
and that's absolutely true i mean it's hard to convince people to come on a show where it's so
like they don't know what they're getting into they really especially after this episode
i mean i i've heard about this a lot i have actually i won't i mean like people who i have
talked to i've offered to come on have said no for various reasons and one of them is just
the show is overwhelming if you don't know all of us and like yeah like you can't just mesh in if
you're like a new guy um just kind of an awkward fit it just yeah i don't know if i would want to
be a guest on a coming onto a show where it's like seven people screaming at each other yeah i absolutely
wouldn't so like i totally get why people don't want to i totally we we could try and like make
a different show that is not the progress natus podcast which is about making it very like we
have the same hosts every time and there's not a lot of them and it's all about asking questions
in order in order to have a guest it has to be like no more than three people yeah it should be
something like that yeah i think like a guest is like it a guest should be like an interview situation
absolutely yeah so the structure of this show as a free form there's like seven of us right now
not great for guests but we could do something different um although somebody like zen i think
would come on and and do just fine as is or somebody like um i don't know who else have we had uh
whatever various people can be fine so yeah we'll we'll work on it people we'll try to we'll try to
get some more fucking shit going on uh all right next voicemail here we go this one's from uh our
old friend or rather our new friend kishin slayer aka sword man is calling in again yeah update us
yo it's the sword man again since the last episode was a seriously shitty episode to ask
a question of the entire pcp i'll just hope this episode works better to re-establish my goal
is to make a lark sword for all of y'all who want one digi and ben have theirs mostly on lock
but sadly i do not have the seven hearts of light and 13 shards of darkness to reforge the key blade
for nate if he wants i could make him a katana so he could become a true calming the motherfucker like
me but he would first have to man up and then maybe dm me to find any specific lens if you're
lazy like digi then i would appreciate it if you at least specify what you would like to use your
weapon for since i have to make the choice between a wall hanging sword and a whacking sword this
this is an excellent opportunity for me to stretch my limits but understand i can't make stable
curves very well you can dm me at sword man in the rfck discord or just use the email and the speak
pipe i'm gonna i have i have unread notifications on discord from sword man right now in trouble
i was talking to him the other day i was talking to him the other day about about my specs i gave
him my my design it's gonna be okay first of all i've already talked to sword man we've got my
sword sword down it's the best sort of all time and it's gonna blow all of you out of the water
even you hippo you think you're cool no give do you want to give us any details on what yours is
i specifically don't want anyone to know okay okay um i don't mind saying that it is uh i like
swords that are like historically kind of accurate so it will just look like a real sword but with
subtle iconography that sounds cool i you know what like i could just say make me the komino katana
i'm gonna think about it a little bit more and get back to you yeah i'll think about that ben i'm
i'm gonna level the keyblade though scrap it i'm gonna level with you and this is not a joke or
like any sort of podcast performance it it yeah please try just try to respond to me more
ocean please i i know i left you hanging for like for like three days this has been a ben thing as
long as i've known ben ben's always been terrible at responding and extremely slow you know in the
mind slow in the mind yeah yeah uh well i know you wanted to record an rfck thing and i after
after new years i got sick and i didn't want to do it which is why i didn't say anything about it
you could have just said i'm sick let's do it after i'm sick and i would have been okay and then
no i know you know i know i could have done that it's bullshit that just because someone messages you
you're expected to respond like it's on you now it's munchy though it's not like just some random
guy like this is a close acquaintance and co-worker and friend you know it's uh a little bit different
of a context than like you know i mean are you picking it up i can't i can't i kind of agree
jesse but i am i know i should have said something all i'm saying is that it makes me very distraught
and upset and mad all the time well whenever i want to get a hold of you i can never do it and
it makes me like you a little bit less unironically well crap that's funny because the reason i don't
respond to people is because i'm afraid that they don't like me and it's and it's a self-fulfilling
prophecy fantastic okay short man good time we'll get back to you dog um uh okay so this is from next
one's from dave dave uh go dave strider nate why do you keep letting through voicemail
people this horrible recording quality you sound like they are speaking directly onto the microphone
and even worse european accents that i do not understand they make the words and i don't understand
what they are saying and then you respond and i get confused because i don't know what they are
responding to it's terrible there's no one speak english what are the sounds they make what his life
help um okay uh good despite trying to sound terribly sounded all right and i could understand
everything you said too good at this he's too good such the undermine his own point of having
terrible audibility and uh like his recording quality was pretty great i bet he has a good microphone
um so yeah blue yeti sounded like he just he just sounded really fancy he sounded french
fucking owned yeah uh debunked atheists kill yourself all right next one uh from cheesy manfredo
cheesy manfredo uh go hey ben saint i hear you're in the market for some beef yeah well if you want
some i got some for you you see i also make my own webcomic it's called bongo and luna and it's
basically the opposite of all your comics first of all i draw it all traditionally therefore i know
how much you hate that shit it's colored and unlike your bitch ass who's always fucking late
my comic updates twice every week i also upload our webtoon which is the rival platform that
tapas so we got that shit going for us but we get personal i am a full-blooded mexican so we
could have a race war kind of thing going for us i'm also way younger than you like my early 20s
younger and that could open the way for a boomer versus boomer kind of situation that's your thing
yep i'm also a clown so i could be your joker you know you always complain about society and you
could be batman is this just a villain i'm here for you my twitter is at cheesy manfredo my webcomic
is bongo and luna and my dms are open for you man and you could fuck off with that stupid ass
endless warship it's fucking gay have a good day oh oh i fucking hate this guy
nate why did nate why did you choose this one because he's attacking you personally and that's
funny to me that's why this was just an ad but yeah this voicemail was just an ad i was aware
that it was an ad i thought the fact that he was attacking you made me laugh enough that
it justified playing it even despite that i didn't like that it was an ad but you know i'm not gonna
cut that out or whatever it's fucking annoying uh you know i started i upload maryweather keeps
pushing the uh the uh not tapas what's the other webtoon uh i haven't i like uploaded everything
there but i haven't like made it public because i don't know no how come i don't like tapas or
webtoon um but i actually have like thousands of followers on tapas and i just forget about them all
the time uh they're they're an abuse group the ben saint followers on on tapas what does it stand
for the tap the tapas followers two angry profiles are it's a thing you eat i don't think it stands
for anything it's it's food uh go to a ps adventures dot site read a real webcomic that is good only
our advertisements are allowed on the pc hold on hold on bongo and luna that sounds familiar that
sounds like a poem maybe it's good maybe it's like popular i don't know was that wait wait no no i
think that maybe uh bongo like in the how they marketed maybe one of the ads did you did was for
bongo and luna okay maybe bongo and luna no i just found it no um move on next maybe looks okay
all right it's about yeah it is about a clown okay anyway all right here we go next one i thought he
said he was a clown that was well the character and he personally bongo is also i don't know
definitely definitely okay uh uh so this is a message uh i and cheesy man freight i'm gonna
kick your ass crap you fucking mexican here's another call here's another message race war
from angry boy 45 aka patreon.com slash jack is boy uh commence oh i know that's person i did a
commission plan all right you fucking piece of shit man you're like my fucking dad i fucking
hate you you fucking piece of shit all right i fucking hate you you fucking okay number one
i recorded a bunch of these fucking voicemails every time every every time every time i record them
you know i don't remember because you know i'm probably intoxicated but uh
fuck you all right uh here's my question
when you when's when's red con for i don't know i'm still i'm still okay
that's it that was it okay i just want to go on record jack is boy is the thirstiest mother
fucker calling in to the fucking voicemails and i'll tell you why i haven't played your
fucking voicemails jack because they've been shit every single time and what am i supposed to do
just play a shit voicemail because you leave 10 of them this is a public service announcement
and an open letter to jack is boy even this one just now i used as an example it too was just
played to like i don't know get on the show or something but i'm just letting you know and
everybody else out there like i don't know okay that was actually funny because you like put music
again in the beginning that's like why i'm actually responding to it right though so but like um well
there you go i i don't know um red con for one of these days i want to give a shout out free
advertisement to at jack is boy on twitter for having the sickest icon of all time nice bro so
that was you who drew that one i'm aware of that jack is boy is a cool guy whose content i do like
but these thirsty ass voicemails need to end just stop getting drunk and doing them i mean
i'm a big uh anti-alcohol guy uh it just makes you dumb and not better at anything so i think
there's a problem right there you got to work on that dog uh just be sober when you decide to do
things that are cool and that goes for everyone in the world um i guess that's just my personal
message to jack is boy let's move on to the next fucking voice mail we're a straight edge podcast
now um you know what i'm gonna skip this one there was a fairly cool one from lane fag but
it's just some lane audio so i'm just gonna fucking skip that one um yeah all right here we go don't
do this one instead is from uh nate's hr department let's see what they have uh this is bill from hr
and we just wanted to let nate know that he doesn't have to threaten interns with death if they speak
about the pcp podcast i don't know like it's not a big deal so just just calm down you don't have
to threaten him he's really scared actually oh contraire bill uh you have to curb this before it
gets out of hand and you have to crush those who could expose your secret cool internet identity
before it leaks uh to the wider populace um okay i i guess that's it i guess that's it
glad that's sorted i like slightly related to to stuff like that um since like stopping youtube
now no longer being a youtuber as career um it's like doubly awkward now when like people who
are only just like coming to terms with the fact that i have an internet job because i've told them
once are asking me about how it's going and i have to explain to them that i've stopped and it's like
i don't know i mean you can definitely just say to someone excuse me i i get that like switching
tracks is kind of annoying for that but you could just tell someone that you're a writer
which is a pretty good i mean i do that now that's what i do but like for for everyone who i had to
like explain like uh i i do an internet thing i mean you wouldn't know like i had to do that and
now they'd know that and now i have to undo it for everyone that knows that i guess if it was me i'd
probably him and haw to like try to just say that it's going well i'm doing writing because like it
technically is you know i mean it is online in the sense you communicate via the internet
i get the point though okay fair enough all right so so our last three messages are all
somewhat related and i just want to remind everyone there was an active hot war going on between the
discourse oh and uh these last three are are various messages about that we didn't talk about this
did we talk about it would you say gib we didn't talk we didn't talk about the word oh yeah not
to this point but i'm sure we'll have plenty to say uh as we get through these let's start with
this first one this is a message from uh afy kuhn uh there's some big news people so listen up
december 30th 2018 the rfck discord invades the poti discord
they at spam everyone hitting both crew members and civilians alike
the captains don't take kindly to it they nuke those motherfuckers right out of orbit
banning them back to their terrible home we launch a counterattack hit them back with
whatever we have been in their mad rage insanity overflows and they at ping themselves over 1,000
700 times they destroyed themselves in a blaze of glory and for that i can respect them some
but in the end they lost rest in peace rfck
you will be missed god if it only for that easy we'll be back we'll be back stronger than ever
big news the poti escort isn't meeting even more servers everybody run
there it is uh they've they've actually personally launched raids on my personal
discords um i don't know what they hope to gain considering i'm already on their side um
but they in fighting in fighting has indeed they're too aggressive um well i mean i they've
invaded like my discord as well but on my discord i'm canonically someone else i'm hippo and then
like the pirate me is like fighting me so like i will shit talk myself yeah from each
i'll probably do that too and it's it's fucking funny as evaded but in our talk where people post
other people's art or their own art they posted like the flag and the fanner so it's the flag
waving that african made yeah yeah so that's not like i don't know it's not a meeting he's just
showing off art i guess it was a it was a nice little invasion uh just to leave their stamp and
move on their way um sounds like uh sounds like a rose boy civil war a little bit it's all right
things are coming down they know that their friendly fire uh needs to be corrected okay next
one this is from them snakes we've got them snakes calling in again not everyone's favorite here we go
jesus okay i've done it i killed crunchy
he had to die several weeks ago he impersonated me in a previous voicemail
and after tasting his blood i am thirsty for more i must taste the blood of the real
munchie but i still am envious of ben saint for stealing my ven snakes thunder i must destroy
one of them now i sliver through the sewers to new los angeles city can search out their blood
but who should i kill whom should be my next victim press one to vote for munchie
press zero for ben Shapiro saint
wow um man them snakes uh you'll never you'll never reach me in my ivory tower
in the in the in ben saint ben's cathedral um i think we should i think we should team up
i think we uh i think we have common interests we've been discussing actually how there's no
way if the rfck community united that any other single force would be able to stand against them
that probably is that they themselves are divided by infighting between the killers and the rowdies
at all times one day they're they're they're they're and when they do come together it's just a
curb stomp some juveniles indeed which we can all celebrate across every discord uh all right
one final message from chirpskay this is the last one and then we're done here we go go
hello this is chirpskay a representative from the best guy ever's ticket to enlightenment discord
i'd like to formally announce that we will be remaining non-interventionalists during this
discord war kill them it means they're easy that being said there have been attempts to annex
the best guy ever's ticket to enlightenment discord into the paddy escorts ranks this
shit is not gonna happen if any like anything like that ever happens again me and lee watts are
going to personally fly over in the inola gay to the ship of the poddy escort and we will
blow it out of the fucking water you have been warned um pretty gay what do you have to say about
that uh good wait what's the i was wondering that what is the inola gay i know i know that i
think it's a historical plane to drop the bombs on japan yeah okay hell yeah okay um cool we need uh
an ebola gay to drop the disease on i don't know your own survey that would be that'd be great
that's my recommendation um okay that's it that's all the voice melz where your contractual
obligations are complete everyone finally was that shit discord is a mistake it's fun god damn it
i'm having a great time telling everyone to kill everyone else um patreon.com slice the procrastinators
people bonus episodes hey the new ones out now that it's actually out we know what it is we're
playing poker and gambling your patreon money and it's great yeah watch us thoughtlessly fritter about
and and cast it to the winds uh uh just for fucking fun uh by donating five dollars per episode on the
fucking patreon so go do that and follow us on twitter at tpcrastinators for updates and what
not is anyone else yeah is anyone else emotionally exhausted after yeah absolutely are we finished
can we done i did can i stop recording a week no we have to say thanks for being here everybody
i'll go and never talk to each other again that's a great idea yeah let's let's down
make sense all right bye guys goodbye thank you and good night wave