Hello, everybody! You're listening to The Pro Crastinators Podcast! I'm Digibro, and with me is Mage.
Hello, I am Ithpresent. Yes.
And Tom Oliver.
Today's episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast really lives up to its name because almost everybody procrastinated on even fucking showing up!
It's true, although we were pretty much on time. Actually, we started much earlier.
Oh wait, did you just mean everybody else who's not here?
Yeah, no one's fucking here. It's a goddamn ghost hack.
I was punctual as fuck. I got the voicemails done 20 minutes before the show started. Nate!
I mean, it's 105 and we're recording. This show usually starts at like 115.
And actually 130 would probably be the closer time. 115 is early. That's what I casted.
That's true. We have been drifting late as of recently, which is disgusting, unprofessional, and that's why we kicked everybody out of the podcast except for us.
They had their chance, they failed, and now it's just us forever get used to it.
Fuck yeah. Yeah, I saw those motherfuckers at the BronyCon posting videos where they're like, oh Tom, we wish you were here.
Tom, I'm so sorry about your back being dead. Digi, you're a piece of shit for not coming here, you faggot.
You don't have an excuse other than your own apathy.
I was on the ground floor of BronyCon planned last year. I was like, yes, let's do it.
It was me and Munchie's brainchild of an idea. And at the fucking finish line, third and goal, I dropped the ball and everything goes down.
Is that a real football, third and goal? That's like third down. There's less than a yard or something. I think that's how football works.
Someone correct me in the comments, yell at me.
I don't feel bad because they look like a bunch of boomers trying to relive their glory days.
No, it's just you're going there, you're having a good time. There's a bunch of people there that I'm never going to be able to probably see again.
Why not? Like who? Well, it's different for you even because you have way more friends in the BronyCon community than any of them.
So I don't understand how that's even real. I don't understand how it happened. I just kind of know everybody.
So there's a bunch of people that I would have liked just like, hey, bye.
I'm just not worried about meeting like the PCP guys because I see them like relatively all the time.
I agree. I mean, it's less, I'm less worried. I'm like, as much as I would like to hang out with the PCP crew again at BronyCon being a boomer.
I just saw them like what, like four or five months ago? It's not like it's been forever.
But like everybody else that I usually see at BronyCon and I haven't gone for like three years.
Those are the people that I'm kind of bummed that I'm not going to be able to hang out with.
That's why I was saying like it's different for you because it's like we just had that meeting in January where like everybody came, even Hippo.
Except for Jesse, maybe. But like I've gone to Jesse's house directly. I've gone to Nate's house.
I had Ben live with me for like six months. You know, when I lived in Boston, you lived in my house.
Ben came by relatively often in Munchy and one time Nate and Hippo fucking flew in while we lived in Boston.
So it's like, I've seen these guys. I know I'm going to see them again because we're going to do another Radcon.
I don't want to go to BronyCon.
I mean, if you're not interested in that convention itself, then it makes sense.
But like, I don't know, part of me did want to go. It was the last one.
I see the fun that Nate is having in like taking pictures of himself with Dr. Wolfe.
And I get why he thinks that's funny, but that would not be fun for me to do.
I'm not going to go to BronyCon and take a picture with Dr. Wolfe, who I've like really talked shit about on the internet like hardcore for years, you know.
Yeah, you'd go and have a fistfight with Dr. Wolfe. It'd be great.
Right. Well, like, I think that Nate has always maintained that he tries not to burn bridges with anybody because he wants, even if he thinks of them as like kind of a meme,
he still wants to treat them with respect so that he could take pictures with them and like think about it in his mind as a fun thing, you know.
Nate is very non-confrontational in that way.
I can relate.
He will always kind of give everyone the benefit of the doubt, which is probably good in today's interconnected world where you can always kind of like connect with anybody, I suppose.
I mean, I think his mentality is always just kind of like, well, I might not like the guy's content, but I respect the guy and the fact that he's famous and in a way that I think is funny, you know, so I'm going to take pictures with him.
Nate has that basic human decency thing that is required of a Starfleet officer that not all of us have, you know.
And like him and Ben both got pictures with Chris Chan, which is awesome. Like, you know, I appreciate what they, again, I have never even read Sonichu.
I'm not like a hardcore Chris Chan follower. I just know it through Ben's lecture.
Ben and Nate have like legitimate connection to Chris Chan. I would love to have pictures with her.
I have no such desires. So, yeah, like, it's like, I see why they're all having fun at BronyCon because they still involve themselves in like that community in some way, or there are also all the slymoids who are there.
That's like a big part of it. And I don't play the game, you know, I've never played the RFCK. Yeah, the RFCK game.
Endless war.
Right. Endless war. That's the word I was looking for. I have never played Endless War. And so like, when those guys hang out with people from Endless War, that's all they talk about.
Like, when, Tom, you experienced this, because when we were doing IM games, there was one time that we had Ben and Munchy come over in, like, October to record an IM games with us.
And they came in and all they fucking talked about was Endless War, and you and I had no fucking idea what to say about it.
And so, like, the IM game stream just became a rowdy fucker's cop killer stream because they were talking about Endless War so much.
And, like, I came to realize that when enough Endless War people hang out together, I really just feel like I have no idea what's going on.
I completely agree. And I keep thinking, like, maybe I should, like, kind of understand what this is. But I mean...
It takes a lot of time. Like, it's kind of an involved project, especially when it has a lot of history by this point.
It's not as incredible as, like, an achievement in terms of just, like, what it's done, but it doesn't change the fact that at the end of the day, like, even though my friends made it, even though it has this big, like, community and, like, all these people I know are kind of tangentially involved in it, it's still a multiplayer game, and I've never liked multiplayer games.
It's also a PvP. I don't like PvP.
I don't, like, role-playing, you know?
Oh, no.
I'm bored by, like, I don't know. Like, if I role-play, I will probably be, like, the stupidest character, you know?
Like, when I did Dungeons & Dragons and with my friends, I was a nigger Rafiki, and I had 5,000 bottles of liquor that I throw at enemies, and, like, that I only would solve problems through liquor.
And, like, it doesn't really work in the game.
I feel like that would fit in with Endless War.
Maybe it would.
Everybody in Endless War is an insane character.
Like, from what it sounds with Endless War, I think I would like it just generally.
Like, I like slimes, and, like, mining slimes sounds like a cool idea.
If I could just, like, if I could just, not being bothered to just mine slimes all day, I would probably play it, but I don't want to be attacked by people.
Right. That sounds like it takes a lot of time, or at least a lot of, like, opening that browser again and again, and, like, I don't know, man, I have all my servers on hardcore mute on Discord.
Like, I'm not somebody who wants to spend a lot of time on Discord because I fucking try to work way too much, you know?
So, like, the idea of, like, a high effort Discord communication circle.
Like, I know you probably can be a fairly passive player in the game, but it's just, like, what's exciting about the game is the culture.
It's the amount of shit coming out of it.
So, if you're not really down to, like, pay that much attention to it, I don't feel like you're going to really get the appeal
that those guys are getting out of it, which I have nothing but respect for, but, like, I don't get it.
So, I have no idea what they're talking about when fucking they talk about it.
So, I just kind of feel like the odd man out, especially when I see that there's, like, that many people from the game.
Like, it's basically a meetup for RFCK at that point, you know?
Because I saw they had pictures where they're hanging out with, like, a ton of the people who have been at other meetups and shit like that.
I am glad, though, what's working out for the guys and, like, the game's popular and people seem to love it.
It seems fun.
It's just, it's...
They've definitely tapped into that cult mentality, which is what I longed to be able to cultivate with my own stuff,
because that's where the true power lies, is having a group of brainwashed young children to do your bidding for you.
Yeah.
Oh, god.
So, did you went to Otacon, right?
Yeah.
How did that go?
It was great time.
Is that still at the Baltimore Convention Center?
They moved by now?
No.
Well, a couple years ago, they moved to the DC convention and, like, convention center.
And I had heard that it wasn't as good in DC from my brother, Victor, who basically, I think he had had a hotel maybe in the wrong part of town,
and he, like, was just upset that there were no street vendors outside, like there are at the Baltimore Convention Center,
because he likes to go and eat, like, the street hot dogs and spend no money and go no distance, you know?
Right.
But, like, maybe he had other complaints, but I don't remember what he had said, because I thought the DC venue was fucking awesome.
Like, it was in the heart of, like, the best part of DC, and it's within walking distance of the White House, the Washington Monument,
the Congress building, the fucking, the Capitol building, like, you know, you're in the heart of the sightseeing part of DC.
There's even, like, a Smithsonian Museum.
This gigantic fucking park that's, like, fucking probably three times the size of the Boston Park, which is a nice park, you know?
I love parks.
So, big, beautiful park that goes on forever and has all these fucking monuments by it.
So, like, it's basically a fun trip to DC to see all the bullshit.
You know, I didn't do that much of that, but we ended up walking around for, like, an hour on Thursday night, just sightseeing DC, because why not?
And then, like, and there's also fuckloads of food all around the convention.
So, it was like, if you wanted to do things other than the convention, you'd be well-spoken for, but there was a lot going on at the convention,
so we mostly were doing that, because it was, like, tons of Japanese guests that I'm a fan of, which is, like, that's really what I turn up to cons for the most,
is, like, getting to meet the, you know, creators behind different anime that I'm a fan of.
So, like, you know, in the case of My Little Pony, there was a time when I cared more about, like, meeting the creators of the show,
though, like, none of them have really done a lot outside of MLP that I'm a fan of, you know?
Whereas with, like, an anime director, they might have done, like, ten fucking shows that I like or something, you know?
So, I've never, in the time since I haven't been keeping up with MLP, I have not followed any of the people who worked on it, you know?
Like, I'm just an anime guy now. I do not watch My Little Pony or care about it.
I was going to ask if you still keep up with the show. What about you, Tom? Do you still keep up with the show?
I've watched episodes here and there. I actually was planning on trying to get caught up before BronyCon,
but then I forgot because I was busy working on game stuff and I just totally slipped my mind, which I guess was for the best,
because it didn't even end up fucking going, because I wanted to go and, like, know what was going on.
Because the last time I went to a pony convention was, I think, 2016 or something, and I was already, like, way out of the loop at that point,
so I had no idea what was going on at the convention. There was a bunch of art and shit.
Like, what the fuck are we talking about? And the show is totally different now, apparently.
Like, there's a whole new, like, B cast and everything.
There's a lot of, yeah, new characters. I'm actually, I actually yesterday just finished catching up.
I mean, the show's also, like, ending soon, right?
Yeah, I think that's, this is the last season on episode 20, so, like, I think it's a few episodes away from ending.
It's a really weird atmosphere to me to have, like, this idea of, like, oh, it's the last brony con, like, around the last season of the show,
and, like, most of the people at the convention are still just, like, doing that shit full time, you know?
Like, Dr. Wolfe and KP are there because they still make my little pony videos regularly, like, for money, you know?
So, like, from my perspective, it's like, I fucking have not even involved myself in this in, like, five years, you know?
So this is a totally different experience for me versus people who are going here because they're sincerely still watching the show
and still interested, you know, still watching Dr. Wolfe analysis videos.
Like, I haven't even watched a new episode since halfway through season five, and I have not gone back to watch it again.
They're sort of trying to wrap up loose ends with the show from what I've noticed.
Like, how Twilight, you know, freaks out whenever she gets nervous or organized or whatever.
Man, that's still a thing.
No, no more. Like, actually, there was one episode where she freaked out, made her heart hold on.
I think I have an image that I showed by her because she was making so many stupid faces.
The animation was very weird in that episode. I'm not sure if it was just that episode or it was just noticeable in that episode.
But just, yeah, she was freaking out really hard.
Then the next episode was like, you know, I learned my lesson. I'm not going to freak out anymore.
And she didn't. And I guess that puts a pin in that thread, I guess.
Until another writer writes the next episode and forgets everything that happened.
The show usually does.
Yeah, but like, if this is the last season and then, you know, this was like almost at the end of the season.
So I think, yeah, she's going to stop freaking out.
Also, major spoilers if you haven't caught up.
Yeah, she's going to be, she's going to take over Luna's and Celestia's role now because those two are retiring.
Okay, whatever.
Fucking, I've been alive for like 10 billion years, but now the show's ending.
We got to wrap everything up in a nice pretty bow.
Yeah, the two sisters are just like, you know, we did this.
We just want to go chill.
And they actually had an episode where they went on vacation and that didn't go too well.
But yeah, the show is just going which way direction doing things.
It's kind of interesting to see. I'm not saying the show is better or worse or whatever.
It's just different.
I'm stunned it lasted as long as it did.
Yeah.
If you had told me going in like back in like 2012, it's like, yeah, the show's going to be going like through 2019.
I'd be like, no, no.
I feel like I have a different expectation just for that because I never watched a lot of long running American cartoons growing up,
like other than stuff on Cartoon Network, you know, that like stuff like Ed and Nettie or Dexter's Lab that was around for a long time.
But I did eventually watch it end.
You know, like those shows lasted maybe like five or six years, maybe even 10 years.
Like as Ed and Nettie kind of came back for a little while and had a proper conclusion.
So like I've seen shows not last this long, but like I'm mostly used to watching anime where shows literally go for like 13 to 26 episodes,
maybe 50 and that's like a huge show.
Yeah.
And for me, it's like considered a huge investment to go watch like all of Ereka 7 or all of Mobile Suit Gundam, the original, you know,
much less watching like like the amount of episodes of My Little Pony at this point.
There's got to be like what?
A lot.
There's over 100.
I mean, episode 100 was like three years ago, wasn't it?
Right.
There has to be like fucking close to 200 episodes, right?
And that's not even counting the spin-offs and stuff.
That's like watching like the whole Macross franchise or something, you know, like, like I could watch an amount of anime that would feel like an impossible amount of anime
in the time it would take to watch all of My Little Pony Friendship is Magic at this point.
And I've only seen less than half of it, which is really weird to think about because it's like I was so into the show for those four years that the idea that there would come a time where I had seen
less than half of this show would be would be, you know, like no way.
But like the show definitely did change as it went on.
And I just didn't really care about it anymore.
You know, like it felt like it was too different or too watered down or like just, you know, repetitive.
Like even if even sometimes the episodes were good, but it was just like this point's already been made before.
And like we're kind of going around in circles.
Yeah.
And I feel like we've already had enough good episodes that I feel like I got a satisfying show out of it.
You know, I don't feel like I have to wait another seven seasons.
I'd rather just end it now and remember it as good, you know.
I think I think MLP suffers from the same problem that most like Western cartoons and just like, I don't know, just like the Western model of entertainment.
Because this is a huge issue.
Just go until you fail.
And comic books as well is that they have they have properties with time.
There's too many people in the kitchen, right?
There's like what like probably there's been over 20 writers over the course of MLP.
You go to comic books and like a character is written by like five different people over the course of like, you know, a couple years.
So there's no coherent singular creative vision behind a lot of these properties.
Yeah.
You know, like you go read Spider-Man.
Like depending on which book you pick up, it's written by a different person.
So the character is completely different.
The story is different.
The tone is different.
So it's just like,
But it's a sequel to the previous guys work.
Right.
And it'll help guys like,
what they didn't like about the last guy's story.
It's just,
I don't know.
It just alters the story into something that can just continue in whatever way.
And then when you explain the story to somebody, you have to explain all those changes, you know,
you have to say like,
Oh, well, the reason this doesn't make sense is that this author completely changed everything about the character.
Yeah.
And MLP did the same thing when Lauren left and Megan McCarthy took over and there's, you know, there's like,
every season has like at least five or six different writers and there's no singular coherent plot going through it.
So it's just like,
it's the same trappings that all these kind of things do here in the West when we make stories.
It's just like a clusterfuck.
Yeah.
It was like that.
But like from what I've watched now, it could be wrong since I was drawing and watching at the same time.
So I haven't been paying too much attention, but I was, I was watching.
I think they started getting their ducks in a row with the last few seasons, like maybe the last season.
And they're like the main six, they're sort of passing on their torch to the younger generation of the students.
The Twilight has it has a school now, if you didn't know.
Yeah.
So it's just, and there sort of been, I guess a bit more consistent or at least it seems like that because the focus of the episodes are less on the main six
and more on other characters that are, they, they managed to keep in line.
It's really interesting to me that they did that because like I had said way the fuck back in like 2013.
I said, like if this show continues on, I wanted this to happen by like season four or five because I had felt like season four, like pretty much wraps up any outstanding character arcs and like most
and a lot of them just kind of repeat by that point.
Like a lot of the arcs had already wrapped up in season three and they just kind of repeated their same kind of point in season four.
So that was why I had started to feel like it was getting repetitive and I was losing interest because I felt like we had completed most of these character arcs.
But I had said what they need to do is just like establish the cutie mark crusaders as like a six person team because they had mentioned having three more of them in like main
Manhattan or whatever that there was like a second sect of the, the, the, the fucking I forgot the, the CMC.
Yeah.
So I was saying like they should be the new generation and just like, you know, move on to making them characters.
And that did not happen when I wanted it to, but it did happen later, which is really interesting, but they didn't give it to them.
It just like made six new characters.
Yeah.
They're all different species and made those like the new real characters who they could give like a new development arc to.
But, you know, like by that point, I just kind of am not interested enough in the show as a whole to have continued watching it, you know.
Yeah.
I mean, at some point, I probably will finish it just to say my own curiosity.
They finally understand that I could see doing that in like, in like 10 years, if I for some reason ran out of everything else to watch.
And I was just like, man, I really want to know what happens at the end of my little pony.
But like, well, here, here's the thing, dude, with like MLP, like the interesting thing with it is that since it's in English, you can just like listen to it while you're doing something else.
That's what I'm doing.
Yep.
I also like, I had like plans at one point to cover the Japanese dub of MLP because of the fact that it had a bunch of voice actresses from like anime that I am a fan of.
So like, I was planning to do like a cover of the OP to open the video.
Like this is when they first started jumping in Japanese like 2014, probably maybe late 2013.
And yeah, I was going to do like a whole project just to talk about the Japanese dub and how like as an anime fan, that was the one that was more fun for me to watch.
Though it was, you know, not better than the English version because the voice acting is pretty good in the show.
But like, you know, yeah, I always forget that you can watch American shows in English and it makes it much easier to just leave on in the background.
It still would take a lot though to watch all of the fucking show, you know.
It is fucking long.
Yep.
Like even watching Yu-yu Hakusho dubbed, it takes like a week of concentrated effort to do, you know.
Shit's fucking long, dude.
Tom, did you hear when I said Skoodle's parents have been revealed?
I'm not sure if you're interested in that, but.
Um, I did not know that that happened, but you telling me does not surprise me.
I feel like that's, especially if you're saying they're wrapping everything up, that's like one of the big things that they must have had to get to at some point.
So, yeah, there's just, again, like just to save my curiosity to be like, ah, yes, that thing that I was thinking about way too deeply back in 2012.
They finally gave me an answer and it was subpar, not as good as the ideas I had in my head.
God damn you show for five year olds not living up to my adult expectations.
And that's, that's another funny thing about it is that like when we, when you and I in particular, when we were in the Brony community,
like you and I read a lot more of like the fan fix and shit and saw the like really great nuanced takes that some people had on the characters that like made it more interesting to be a part of the fandom
because you kind of have the show and how you associate the characters there.
And then like a different way of thinking about them because of the fact that certain people in the fandom would write like really, you know, basically just good fiction that happens to feature some element of the show.
It's the same thing every artist does.
Like I have this great idea.
How can I get people to actually pay attention to it?
Oh, I'll just make a fan work.
Or just how do I make it like while I'm still learning how to make my own thing?
Like a lot of the times, a lot of the usefulness that came out of yours and my videos to people was that we had like a lot of people who would say like, I'm a fanfic author and like listening to you break down how the world works has helped me to like, you know, to like conceptualize how I would build a fictional world.
You know, and so like a lot of those people would then write an MLP fanfic as a way to like, like just basically deconstruct the world building for themselves and then go and try to write their own world based on that.
And like, I was shocked how many comments like that we would both get, you know, especially on shit like our weird lore videos and stuff.
I mean, I guess that is like people prime to watch that kind of content in the first place.
I had I had such a cool idea for a MLP comic that I wanted to do, but then I didn't end up did not doing it.
But it was going to be like a bit darker than usual.
It started off, I actually had a first page somewhere finished.
I started off with this one pony just like going to dig for diamonds, but then she discovers some big old evil that and she accidentally releases it and just causes like a dystopian in the pony world.
She has to travel around and find other ponies who haven't lost their spark, so to speak, to restore the world to how it used to be.
It sounds like Dark Souls.
This was before Dark Souls.
At least I never.
Hold on.
I have this.
I found the first page.
The only page I actually do.
Dig up some ancient mage art word.
It was interesting how the show really was like such fertile ground for a crazy fan work and stuff.
I even started a fan fiction of Fallout Equestria.
Somebody came up to me at Otacon and told me like I've been following you for, you know, since the Brony days and I'm like, I might have even been.
There was this dude's son of Marowak who hung out with me for a while at Otacon and said he was going to BronyCon too and he was really excited to meet like Hippo and Jesse.
Because he was like slowly, he was like currently branching out through the PCPs stuff like like investigating everybody's channels like because he's like a Brony but I guess he wasn't really around in the pony days because he's also a huge anime fan and that's how he knows about me, you know.
But like he's moving his way through watching like the horseshoe saga and shit.
So like, which is like to think that that's still happening in 2019 is really impressive, you know, that like people still are like, yeah, well, I just, you know, I am both of my little pony fan and a fan of the PCP so I'm going to go back and watch those videos and like get the full effect of them, you know.
But like, fuck, I forgot like why I brought him up.
He wanted to meet Hippo.
I remember you.
Well, just that he's going to.
That's the guy.
Which guy?
You're talking about the guy who you said he wanted to meet Hippo, right?
Yeah, what is this thing that's loading though?
That was the page.
It's just it's not loading.
If you click on it, you can see it.
It doesn't look for me.
At least when I click it, it looks good.
It looks good.
It's very it's show accurate.
Definitely a far cry from what you draw today.
Yeah, definitely.
It is very show accurate though.
Thank you.
I tried really hard back then.
Yeah, well, I guess I was I don't fucking remember why I was talking about that.
I lost track of thought.
He left a good impression on you.
Yeah, no son of Meruac was a cool guy.
I don't remember like I just wanted to bring up why he was going to both cons, but I don't
remember to what end you started saying how it's interesting how even now like our old
work like getting people like into our like videos and like seeing the horseshoe saga
and how even today people are still kind of going down that rabbit hole.
Yeah, but I don't I feel like I was there was a going to be a twist on it at some point
I forgot what the twist was that I was going for something.
Fuck.
So forget about it.
Well, the twist is you'll never know what the twist was audience.
Yeah.
Well, fuck Barone Khan.
I'm not salty that I'm not there at all.
I'm sorry, Tom.
I really do think I I totally appreciate why those guys felt so bad about you not getting
to go because it really would have meant more to you than anybody else in the PCP since
you do know people in that community.
Yeah.
Like, I know you would have hung out with like Jack's Blade and AC Race Best or something.
Like, yeah, I mean, I would have seen all those guys like apparently because I was talking
to them like leading up to this as well.
I was going to drive in with Matt and like Saber is like, oh, yeah, like we rented like
a private suite for the first night.
So we're all going to have a party up there and like you can come and I was like, oh,
sick.
Like, and it didn't happen.
Like, do any of those guys still watch MLP?
Or is it just an excuse to hang out with each other every year?
Like, they do.
They still they're still caught up.
That's amazing because I'm going to chat with a bunch of them on Discord as well.
Like they'll ping each other every now and then and be like, oh, yeah, we're going to
watch a new episode.
So like, yeah, they're up on it.
They're still involved in certain ways.
They go to all the conventions and shit.
Like they get they're still like part of that click.
So like, you know, like Barone Khan invited them over because like, I feel like there
are a lot of groups who like even as of like 2013 or 14 when I went to Barone Khan for
the first couple of times, there were people there who were like not even into it anymore.
They were just there to hang out with friends, you know, like that was already rampant at
Barone Khan.
And that was how it was for us in 2015.
We're like, none of us were talking about it anymore.
We just were still kind of auxiliary about Barone famous, I guess.
And like, yeah, we just wanted to hang out together, you know, I mean, that's why in
Barone Khan as well, like the people right there right now, the PCP boys, it's not
right, like they're all just there to hang out with each other.
But there are people there who are like still, you know, connected deeply to the show and
are meeting up because it's like, oh, yeah, we still watch it.
We're still a part of this community.
This is still, you know, part of our identity and stuff.
Like that's why it's just an interesting.
It's an interesting event from the outside to see that there's some people there who
are like still really into it.
Some people there who are just there to see friends or even have completely unrelated
meetups about like RFCK, which has nothing to do with My Little Pony in any way.
We don't like plenty of people involved with it have never watched My Little Pony.
I'm sure, you know, like, but would still go to Barone Khan to see the PCP.
So, you know, I know there are some people who are probably there just for that who
probably would have wanted to see me more, you know, like then Bronies would have wanted
to like who don't know who the fuck I am at all, you know, at this point.
But like there would have been like PCP fans, but I met a bunch of those people at Otakana
as well.
So like, you know, I met a whole lot of my like big fans because of the fact that obviously
most fans of me are huge fans of anime.
So like, you know, I hung out with a couple of people who were really cool and part of
Sara, who gave me weed.
So that was fucking cool.
Yeah, we're smoking up on the hotel in fucking Washington, D.C.
It was beautiful outside.
Fucking.
Yeah, it was it was fun to hang out with them.
And like D.C. was a great place.
It was like Otakana was a lot of fun for me.
I got like everything I could have wanted out of convention, even like the fan interaction
and like hanging out with people you know, because like I don't particularly know Paru
and I definitely didn't know Son of Marowak, but like they they seemed cool.
And like I knew of Paru from like my discord, you know, so it's not like I had no idea who
this person is.
Whereas at Bronicon, there will be a lot of people who would be following us around who
we don't really know.
And that was kind of what made me like I thought it was cool for us to have like this posse
around us of all these people who are like just kind of following us around because they
think we're the most interesting thing going on.
But I don't know most of those people and I can't really do things with them around,
you know.
And like that was kind of the motivation to do Radcon in the first place was like, hey,
we've meet up at Bronicon all the time, but we can't really record things here.
Like we can't make cool shit together.
And it's fun to be around all these people we don't know, but like we also want to just
hang out together, you know, and just do things like because we're friends, like play video
games together, you know, like we can't do that at Bronicon.
But like when we hang out at a place that's most of what we do really is like we find
every excuse to do let's plays because we all love just hanging out and playing video
games and talking, you know.
So like to me that's if it's like, oh, Bronicon versus Radcon, I would much rather do Radcon
because it's me and my bros hanging out playing video games and fucking just shooting the shit.
Bronicon is like a weird event where you're going to be like a celebrity and followed
around by people, you know, and a lot of them are going to be people who you only know through
this game that I don't play.
So I have no idea what the fuck they're talking about, you know.
So like that's kind of why I didn't want to go.
It's like, again, I appreciate why Tom wants to go so much.
But like for the rest of the PCP, it's like I understand why this is more appealing to
you because you know more of these people who you're hanging out with.
I don't know any of these people.
I'd rather just hang out with you guys.
And I think we're going to do that probably by the end of the year.
I'm sure we'll be able to organize another Radcon.
Like that was this point because we made sure you're going to go to Radcon.
I'm going to not be a quitter.
I don't know.
Like if we're doing it, we're obviously doing it by Kickstarter.
And I think that we should really like, I don't know, I think we should aim a little higher
than we had last time just because like we could afford better accommodations, you know,
or like just to be able.
I don't know.
The Airbnb worked out pretty well.
But like if we could get that like somewhere like where like if we could get that and get
everybody like make sure everybody's flight is covered and everything, which I think we
did last time, right?
Like, yeah, it was covered last time.
We had to like make some last minute concessions to balance the books like after the fact.
But that's the thing.
Like I think we need to ask for more just to have like everything cost more than you
expected to.
And like, we never really account for it because we're trying so hard to be as transparent
as possible and be like, you know, hey, the funds go up by 150 like like the stretch goal
of $150 is that another guy gets to fly down.
So you can very visibly see that that stretch goal is just to cover that flight.
But like everything ends up costing more than you think it does.
Just because you don't realize like a light bulb goes out in the house because you're
overloading the electricity or something.
You got to go buy a new light bulb or just we're hiring Vic as a cameraman.
But can we feed him?
You know, he has nowhere to go and no money like, you know, just there's reasons that
it costs more.
So we should make sure that we don't put ourselves at a deficit, which we've done each time that
we've done a Kickstarter.
Yeah, I think the best thing to do for this upcoming rad con to prevent that is to not
go so ham on the stretch goals like we did last time.
We just need to set like the stretch goals were kind of fine and that they were just
like video.
Like I feel like we accomplished everything that we had said.
It took a long time to get like everything edited, but we did record all that stuff at
rad con.
So it felt like we had at least accomplished what the goals were.
But yeah, it did just go over budget.
It's like we need to factor in the budget of anything we're planning to do, but then
also just have like a deposit of like, like how about everybody gets paid to have done
rad con?
Like not just that it covers the cost of it, but that you actually get paid to do it,
you know, because that's why nobody feels like editing the shit afterwards is because
we've we've made enough money to fund rad con, but there's no residual.
There's no like, oh, you also get a hundred dollars for the time that you're going to
be working on editing those videos.
You know, it's like for us, there's no more benefit of cost.
There's no additional payment that we get for also doing the stuff afterwards, which
is the hard part of the work because I mean you by yourself.
Right now we're doing a regular episode and we're going to get paid for it through
Patreon.
Right.
Not only did we not get paid for anything we did at rad con at all because we lost
money at the end of the day, but that following week we didn't do an actual PCP episode because
we were busy getting everything squared away from rad con.
So we lost even more money because no one made money that week either.
Right.
And like granted, we do make some extra money through like super chats and shit that we
do during the thing, but we don't get that money till much later, you know, so and it
kind of comes in.
I mean, it's just related to that stream and you don't really feel like that's additionally
contributing to you editing this video that is now going to definitely be made at a deficit
because you know it's not going to get a lot of views.
You know, it's not going to be drawing new people to the channel.
It exists to be something cool for the fans, you know, like the people who really care
about the PCP are the ones watching the rad con videos, not people who are just stopping
in to to hear a random podcast, you know.
Right.
So like I definitely think it's like, yeah, we just need to charge a little not charge,
but like set our goals a little higher.
And like maybe I mean, I still think we can offer like higher tier rewards, but like we
definitely have to factor the cost of the rewards into the total cost because did we
even do that with rad con three with all the shirts and shit?
Like, is that why we went over budget?
The biggest problem that would fuck us over going over budget was the international shipping
on those shirts.
That's something I had to factor in with.
I ran because did you know that I just sold fucking 50 shirts?
I did not know.
Did you go versus Kirito shirts?
Yeah, 50.
That's fucking great.
Dude, fucking I sold them.
Okay.
So here's how I did it.
I ran some experimental runs to figure out what it was going to cost because like I bought
basically when I overheard you telling Ben that the t-shirt press was like $200, I had
just always assumed it was expensive and that I needed to rely on the fact that you had
one to make shirts.
When I found out that I could just buy one for myself for relatively cheap, I was like,
well, well, I can just make my own shirts and I can just do it whenever the fuck I want
because I don't have to commission anybody and I can just experiment with random designs,
print them out and put them on shirts and see what happens.
Heat press isn't hard to use the heat press.
Oh my God, I fucking love.
It's like I've always wanted to have like a DIY collection of clothes.
Like I want to make a bunch of goofy shirts that just have slogans on them and shit and
wear them in videos because it would be really cool to just have like a constant array of
different shirts that are all made by me.
Yeah, I would love to have that like just t-shirts with my own designs.
It is not expensive to do this.
Get a heat press mage.
It's not hard.
Buying 50 t-shirts is like what, 100 something, 150 maybe, something like that.
It's like over $100 to buy the baseline.
Yeah, you make that bad quickly if you sell these, but like even if you just want them
for yourself, you can buy 50 blank t-shirts to fuck with for a hundred bucks, you know,
and just fuck with them.
You can go even cheaper than that.
Like if you want to sell things, like if you like what you're doing right now, did you,
like getting the heat press makes total sense, but like mage, if you want to just make custom
t-shirts, all you have to do is go to a craft store and buy iron on heat transfer paper.
So it's the same kind of paper you're using.
Oh yeah, you could just use a regular iron.
You don't even have to get a fucking shirt press.
You just print out on the special paper and just use an iron and you iron on that design
onto a white t-shirt and it's, you're done.
Wash off with several washes of the washing machine though.
It depends on the quality of the paper you get.
Sometimes the iron on stuff works okay, but not great.
Like that's why people usually get a heat press if you want to do it professionally,
because the heat press gets much hotter than an iron.
So the designs are transferred better and they last longer.
But if you're just, you know, you're just digging around.
You're just going to wear like a shirt casually around the house.
Yeah.
I mean, look up like iron on a shirt tutorial.
It is much easier than you would probably imagine, because it's just applying heat to
it for like 20 seconds, you know?
The only reason it's harder with an iron is that you have to go over the whole image
like piece by piece, whereas with a heat press, it just presses the whole thing on it once.
And it only takes 20 fucking seconds.
So like it takes way longer to print out the images.
If you have a like, in my case, I had a really detailed picture with lots of color in it.
So it took like eight minutes to print each page.
But what sort of printer do you need for it though?
Just any kind of regular printer.
In fact, the specific paper that I got on Amazon cannot use a laser printer.
So I couldn't go to any print stores to get it printed.
And my printer was acting up initially.
So this is why I was being so experimental with it, like that I was not trying to sell
anything right off the bat because it took a long time to even figure out how the fuck
to work all this stuff.
But like basically I got my printer working.
I just needed new ink in it.
And, you know, the ink was probably the most expensive part of the process because my image
used a lot of ink.
So I probably went through like five ink cartridges.
But I was buying the cheap repro car cartridges from, you know, like from Target because
they have like $30 for a refill as opposed to 50, you know.
All right.
I'm going to what you need to do.
Digi, if you're going to keep doing this, you need to go on eBay.
You're going to search for your printer model, like the cartridge that it uses, refillable
cartridges.
That's what I have for my printer here.
You just buy a bottle of ink that's like massive and it's, it's like a thousand reloads and
it's like $10 and then you just take a needle and you inject it into the cart and refill
it.
And so it's like a thousand cartridges.
Oh, you need a needle?
Yeah.
That's, it's a lot.
I mean, all you do is like, it's just you put the needle in the bottle, you fill it up
and then you inject it again in the cartridge.
It takes like as long as you need to even say that.
Sure.
But like you're not, you're not shooting yourself up with fucking printer ink.
Still though.
It's just like really technical for a layman such as me, but you know, I don't know.
It's not that technical.
It just, that's a really good thing is it saves you like infinity dollars.
Yeah.
And basically becomes a no costs.
Well, that's, I'll have to look into that if I'm going to continue this as like a serious
venture because that was like, all my experimentation was about trying to cut the cost as low as possible
without cutting too much quality.
It was like, cause I didn't want to use Gilden shirts cause we've used those for all of our
selling so far.
And I think they're not that comfortable.
I would much rather have higher quality shirts, but I didn't want to go too crazy cause I
didn't want it to be like a really expensive run.
So I bought the Haynes shirts that are like the step up from the Gildens.
So depending on who you ask, like I don't think May says she doesn't like it as much as the
Gildens.
So whatever, I guess there's a taste preference level.
Nonetheless, I sprung for the Haynes, which was like $2 a shirt as opposed to like 190
a shirt, you know, it's not a huge difference in cost from the shipping end, though when
you're buying a bulk, you know, it does, it does make a difference, but it's like you
can, you have a higher quality shirt, more people are going to buy it, you know.
Right.
So I bought the Haynes shirts and tons of papers.
I had to buy a lot of ink, but you know, I printed it all from home.
So there's no additional fee on top of paying for the ink.
The papers are not expensive at all.
And you know, the shipping, that was the hardest thing to figure out because I thought I was
going to ship them all from like the post office.
Well, no, I thought I was going to ship them all from FedEx because for my care packs that
I do every month, I was originally shipping those from the post office, but the post office
basically has like a flat rate for anything under like seven ounces or something like
that.
Or maybe, maybe it's even more than that.
It's like anything under a certain number of ounces, it's all like 350 or whatever to
mail something.
So I had initially been mailing through them and it would usually cost me like 70 bucks
to mail 40 care packs or whatever.
And then I found out that at FedEx, the weight is directly proportional to the, what?
UPS.
What did you say?
UPS?
What did I say?
FedEx.
UPS, not FedEx.
Sorry, that was a may correcting me from the sideline.
Listen to my story.
Yeah.
So yeah, not FedEx at all.
It was UPS that we went to instead of USPS and like, yeah, the weight scales by price.
So like, no matter how light your package is, it keeps getting cheaper for being lighter.
So because these were like one ounce packages, UPS would ship them for like a dollar.
So that immediately cut my cost into a third for shipping those.
So I was thinking, okay, well UPS is just better than USPS.
Not fully understanding their system yet.
So when I took the shirts there, I had done an initial round where I sold them for like,
I think, I think it was like $40 a piece.
Like I was really selling them for a lot initially for this test run that I did where
they were all printed differently.
Each one, like the printer had fucked up in a different way on every single shirt.
So either it had a weird ink running effect or it was like all blue or something like,
they looked cool and like people in my discord were like, oh, I like that it looks fucked
up and that they're like exclusive, you know, because each one looked so different.
And they were like neat and like glitchy and aesthetic.
So people were like, yeah, I'll buy those.
And this is like, you know, the most hardcore fans are offered first.
So it was just in my discord that I promoted it.
But I sold all 10 of my like initial or eight, I think of my initial round of shirts went
to UPS and they're like $10 a piece to ship because they were heavier, you know, and then
I found out that at USPS they would still be, they're still under seven ounces.
So there's still that flat 350 rate.
So I'm like, fuck, I got to do this at the post office instead of UPS.
So that was like the importance of the experiment.
So yeah, through USPS they'd be 350 to ship.
But what eventually happened is I go to USPS carrying 50 fucking shirts that I want to
ship and they all need postage and they're just like, uh, you know, we have like a machine
over there.
You can do it yourself because they have to like input all the information on every single
fucking package.
So it would take hours if they were going to do this.
So they told me to go over to this machine and the machine, if you have to enter the
information yourself, it takes like five minutes of package and it was charging more
than what that flat rate was for some reason.
So we were just like, fuck it, we'll do this at home and get a stamps.com account.
Tom, I think you have one, right?
Yeah.
So I had been resistant to getting it because it's like $19 a month and I thought I might
only do this once, you know, but like they do give you a free trial period and a bunch
of like free postage when you start.
But more importantly, they give you way cheaper rates than anything else.
It was only like a buck 15 to mail each of these fucking shirts, the postage that they
gave me.
And like granted, I don't know if all these shirts have gotten to everybody yet.
I've heard a couple of people say they got them, um, you know, I don't know if I'm going
to go to my PO box and find it flooded with returns because that would be terrible.
But uh, the postage that it printed for me was very cheap.
So I sold all these shirts for like 30 bucks a piece, 40 if you lived international.
Um, no, maybe it was 25, was it 25 that I was charging for the shirts?
It was either 25 or 30, but like you, it was an additional five if you were in Canada because
that's how much more of the postage seemed to cost, but it ended up being less than that.
And uh, you know, an extra 10 if you lived in, uh, uh, like a, you know, far away foreign
country, because I was used to paying like $10 shipping to go to there and it was cheaper
again through stamps.com.
So like I couldn't make my shirts even cheaper next time and sell even more of them now that
I know how cheap the postage is.
But like, uh, yeah, fucking, I made a shitload of money selling 50 shirts because they were
all handmade and I signed them each personally.
So it was like a very exclusive run.
It was like, this is the only time I'm printing this design.
You get, there's 50 of them for sale.
Um, here's the sizes I have available and, uh, they're all hand signed.
So you know, this is the only chance there will ever be to get this design signed by
Digi Bro.
And, um, you know, I mailed them to everybody personally and it went extremely well.
It funded my Otacon trip entirely.
I made like, so the total cost of production was probably like $500.
But the total I made was like $1,500.
So yeah, I made like over $1,000 profit.
I used it to pay for the hotel for Otacon and, uh, pay, uh, I pay May $400 a month to
be my assistant and that just went right to her paycheck.
So it was like, yeah, it was a huge fucking benefit for me, just like pocketing a thousand
grand as extra money for that month, you know, just, just here's a more money.
I have, and, uh, now I, now I still have $600 in the bank after going to Otacon, you know?
So yeah, it was fucking cool and, uh, I will definitely be selling more physical things
in the future.
But like what, you know how I've made almost as much money is just raffling shit during
live streams, um, really?
So we started doing a thing where, um, like initially we printed something on a hat, like
cause I accidentally, while I was scanning in May's drawings of Pokemon that she does
for the edited versions of our, uh, live streams cause we're doing like a Nuzlocke.
So you know, she, she draws all the Pokemon as like whatever stupid nickname they have
and, um, puts it on screen.
So I accidentally printed one of her drawings cause it was in the scanner.
And so we just put it on a hat cause we were like, fuck it, it'll be merged for the stream
and we'll raffle it.
So you know, if you give us at least a dollar in super chat, we put your name in a, in a
cup and one guy gets chosen at the end to win.
So it's basically like you can just donate a dollar and be in this raffle and you might
win something that's worth more than a dollar.
Some people will put in way more than a dollar trying to win it and not win it.
But you know, those people have a lot of money.
Yeah.
It's usually like butthole weave, just throwing fuckloads of money into our, uh, into our
super chats, but like in a couple of people who will just stop by and they don't really
care about the raffle.
They just give me a whole bunch of money cause they, they like me, you know, it's way easier
for people to just give donations to super chat, I think, because it's not, it's just
like a less complex system than Twitch.
And also I have more automatic audience streaming on YouTube because I'm on like my main channel
streaming, you know, um, so like, but yeah.
So initially we were just doing this hat, but then I raffled off one of my t-shirts,
um, and that did like a little bit better.
And then I had the utterly brilliant idea of I'm going to cut a page out of the Ari
Fureta light novel where there's like a sexy loli on it and write the word boob on it and
send it to whoever wins this raffle.
And we made like $300 or something in super chats, like raffling.
Was it like that?
Yeah.
It was, it was a lot.
We made a lot of money in super chats, just raffling off a page of Ari Fureta.
It couldn't have been 300.
I need a loaded audience.
Like you have.
Jesus Christ.
Well, just cause it was like a, they thought it was a funny meme and, uh, you know, a couple
people were competing kind of to get it.
It couldn't have been 300, but I think we did make that on the last stream.
Cause then the, the one after that, not the, no, not the last one we did, but the one before
was, um, we had an Ekans cock and balls because May drew, like our Ekans was named something
like penis or some shit like that.
I don't know what the fuck is his actual name, big old penis, right?
In reference to the Aaron Hansen song.
So we have an Ekans that the chat has named big old penis and May draws it as like the
Ekans as the dick and two polka balls as the balls.
And I had accidentally printed that onto a piece of paper again.
So I was just like, all right, we'll get, we'll, we're raffling a t-shirt with Ekans
cock and balls on it.
And that was the one where I think where we made like $300 off of the raffle.
And then we probably made like, uh, probably over a hundred because we got a couple of
big super chats on the most recent one.
Um, so basically what I'm talking about right now is just that I have tons of alternate
revenue sources opening up and it's really great.
Um, it's a good shit.
And like, I think that a lot of us could capitalize on it because selling the t-shirts
yourself is not as big of a hassle as it seems on the surface and way more people
will do it.
Like we had already learned this lesson with the I am gains shirts because like when
we did our initial run where Tom was hand making them, we sold out of the 10 we had
in like fucking hours.
And then we could not even sell 10 shirts on like heavily promoted over like eight
months that we were selling through Redbubble and spreadsheet.
Like, yeah, I mean, even now they're still all up there.
Like they're integrated with the T spring and nobody buys them.
I look at the numbers.
No, they don't sell it all because people don't want to buy shit from those websites.
They just don't, like it's too expensive for a shitty shirt.
You know, and it's like, if you can print it yourself, it adds value there.
And even then you could just get higher quality material if you really wanted to
like be serious about selling shirts all the time, you know, like get higher
quality shirts that people really want to buy.
Like Dick Masterson sells a lot of fucking shirts because his shirts are
high quality and they look great on you.
So like I will buy multiple Dick Show shirts because he goes through and he
sells them for only like 22 bucks.
So it's not like he's, you know, raking you to get profit.
He just sells it for a lower profit margin and sells way the fuck more shirts,
you know?
So like I think that that's something you can do when you either work directly
with like a specified, you know, shirt sales people like he does.
Like he doesn't work through just spread shirt or something.
He's working through people who are better and, uh, and like, but if you just
make him yourself again, there's an added value even in that just because you
handmade it and like people just want to receive something from you.
It's way cooler.
It's just like way, like the thought of, oh, my favorite creator threw an
image into this website and it has generated a shirt that I'm going to buy.
It's very different from my favorite creator put this shirt under a heat press,
put his face on it and then mailed it to me, you know, right?
It's way more personal, way more interesting story.
It's interesting that you're bringing up this topic because like I'm gearing up
to, uh, start kind of dipping back into this myself.
Cause I have a tier on my Patreon where it's like a quarterly care package.
So cause I'm, I'm going to, the idea for the tier, I have a couple of people
on it already is that, uh, every three months I'll put together like a bunch
of exclusive merch that'll only be through this tier and ship it to you.
So like it'll be t-shirts and like, I had, that's, that's an idea I had too,
but I would have to be like, if you want to do that kind of thing, you're
at an advantage cause you have like a button maker and shit.
And people do like the buttons and stuff too.
Um, and I could get one of those, but it does eventually be like juggling
a lot of balls.
Like if you're mailing out a lot of that shit, you gotta do a lot of
fucking work each month to, you know, make sure you have all the pieces together.
My idea for getting around this is that like, first of all, the tier is quarterly.
So it's only done four times a year, even though it's a monthly pledge.
Like it gives, it gives me time to like, I'll have three months to put all
the pages together.
So do you have to be a page in for all three of those months to get it?
Yeah, it would be, you know, I would just check the numbers and make sure
of all that shit.
Um, I wouldn't have that seems like it could be cheesable.
So I'd be careful.
It's definitely could be cheesable, but like, I'm, I'm small enough now
that I can easily keep track of like three people and make sure
nobody's like causing any bullshit.
But another thing I was thinking of doing for limited runs, I just real quick,
I found out that people can cheese my rants because somebody like just
changed his name and posted another, cause I did it as like a thread of
comments, like on a, I say, like post your rant topics here and then people
just comment on that post cause that's the easiest way to keep it all on one
place and make sure I don't miss anything.
But they were like, yeah, you can change your name and comment again.
And it doesn't, you know, indicate that it's a different person or the same
person rather.
Um, so, uh, you know, they use that to get two rants and they were like,
you should close this loophole on Patreon, really?
Yeah, they changed their name and posted in that chat again.
And I just didn't know it was a different person.
So, or didn't know it was the same person rather.
And, uh, did a second read and they were like, they did it just to like,
kind of like, see if that loophole was exploitable and then let me know.
But like, it definitely happened.
And like, so now I'm like, well, I guess I'm going to have people PM me so
that I can, you know, it'll always show me that you PM me before, like, uh, you
know, it won't be any mistaking, but that just means a way more to keep track
of, you know, I have to go into every single PM as opposed to just one thread.
So yeah, that's just like the, the kinds of things you have to account for
when you get to a size where people can cheese your thing, you know.
Yeah.
I mean, the thing I was, cause I was, I want to start doing limited run shirts
again, and that's the whole thing.
I'd have them be limited run.
Like, I mean, like you're doing, like I'd only probably want to have like 20 to
50 had a time and I was thinking of doing pre-orders, right?
So instead of like making 50 shirts and hoping they sell, like I just a month
before, but like if you want to buy this design and then make exactly how many
are ordered, cause if you have the like pre-order money, you can use that to buy
all those shirts and shit, or at least to guarantee like, even if you're not
charging before you, you know, buy it, just to guarantee that you will have that
money afterwards, you know, um, cause that was the scariest part is like, do I
want to drop $150 on 50 shirts and maybe I only sell three of them, you know,
like that would suck.
Cause then you definitely didn't make back the money, you know, unless you were
charging a lot for the shirts.
Um, but the fact that I sold out was like, I mean, I had like two left that I
gave away at Otacon to the two people I hung out with there, but, um, cause they
had respectively given me weed and given me free art.
So I gave them free shirts.
Um, but otherwise I sold through all the shirts and, um, like what I'm planning
to do is not to just sell more shirts, but to try to sell different types of
things in like a cycle.
Cause like Anthony Fantano will like maybe once a year, um, maybe once or twice a
year, release new shirts on a store that are all limited run.
It's always a new design that he commissioned from somebody and, um, you
know, he, he sells like a hundred shirts of it or something like that.
I have one of those from like a few years back because I like that kind of
shit.
I will buy these.
This is why I think it's interesting, you know, to do these experiments is
like I, I'm selling the kind of thing I would buy, but, um, I personally
though would usually buy higher quality shirts than the ones that I'm selling.
Um, you know, like I would, I, that's why I want to sell better shirts.
Cause I know I would buy only buy it if it was like, if I knew it was going to
be kind of good, um, to wear cause I have a lot of good shirts.
So, um, God, that, that was a fucking rabbit hole of me geeking out about
fucking shirts.
It's exciting.
I mean, there's, there's something really, I don't know, maybe it's because
like I'm just a fucking doomer piece of shit at this point, but like the idea
of making physical goods still intrigues me because like when I was a little kid,
that just seems so far beyond what a normal person could do.
Right.
And also it's like, I grew up collecting shit.
Like I'm, I have a huge collection.
You all know this, you know, and like, I like having weird exclusive
shit that like tells you something about me and where I was.
Like I have that minds got rocks in it art book where it was like all the really
like fancy, my little pony, um, like creators, like artists, like all the
ones who had like weirder styles did an art book together and like they probably
only made, you know, a couple hundred of them and they sold them on Tumblr
or whatever and at Otacon or Brony con rather.
But like I have one, there's not a lot of them.
I have it because I like, I wanted to say, oh, this is like what represents
me in this community is like this cool wispy art that's different.
And, um, you know, I never even looked at it.
I literally have not looked at the book at all.
I bought it just to have it and did not even look at it, which is how it's,
it's true for a lot of the art books I have.
I don't know why.
I just like to own a book that represents my aesthetics, but not necessarily
to actually look through it regularly.
But, uh, yeah, uh, the, so for me, like I want to sell all kinds of physical products.
Like if I, I feel like if I was selling a shirt every month, like a different shirt,
you know, very quickly, people are going to be like, I already bought a shirt from
you. I don't need, I don't need fucking six shirts from you.
You know, like I'll do a couple.
So I'm only going to run shirts probably once, like every, maybe four or five
months or six months or something, you know, long enough that, and, and make a
very different designs.
Like I have an idea for my next design, which I want to be like a white on black
of like just my like sunglasses, like, like, or just a part of my face that has
my sunglasses and under that, it'll say void gazer and like a scratchy hand
writing style.
And I think that would be really cool.
Sounds dope.
But I would have to be able to do white on black shirts.
And so that's like a whole other thing to learn, you know, um, but like what
you'd probably want to do for that.
And like, unfortunately, the big problem with white on black is that you need
to be able to ideally print white ink, printers don't do that unless you get
a special printer and those cost infinity trillion dollars.
So the way to get around that is there's paper that's designed to be white.
Um, yeah.
And you just cut the image out and then heat press it, but it gives it's that's
the kind of material that gives you the kind of plasticky feel on a shirt.
Right.
That makes really no way around that at our budget level.
So like you can either cut it with scissors, which sucks, or you can get a
cry cut machine and you basically load the image file into this cry cut machine.
And then it will cut on the paper.
Exactly that design that you have based on the alpha channel of the image.
How expensive is that thing?
Uh, not too expensive.
Probably around the same price as the, uh, the heat press itself is probably
around a hundred, $150, $200, depending on the model you get.
Matt got one, uh, DB pony.
He bought one because he was making custom stickers.
And so by using the cry cut machine, it would cut them exactly to the right size.
This sounds like a fucking hacker ass machine.
I didn't know fucking technology like this existed.
Yeah, it's like not, it's not like a super new age thing.
It's been around for a while.
It just, it uses the alpha channel of a PNG to like crop the image to, uh, it
just cuts it based on the, the transparency.
And so you can get it cropped exactly to how it should be.
That's really fucking cool.
Um, yeah.
It's a solution to everything.
If you Google enough longterm, I'll probably get that.
If I keep making shirts, like this run went so well that it made me want to do
more like it and like, um, I don't know how frequently I can, you know, like
interest the same people or if the same, if it would only be the same people who
are interested in shirts every time, you know, um, but that's why I want to
mix up the product.
So like, I think I might sell some kind of magazine, like some kind of
self-published magazine, um, as one of my next ones.
Cause people have told me that they want like print copies of some of the stuff
I've written, um, particularly the, uh, I wrote this light novel in like a day.
It sucks.
And I hate it.
Um, like people have said they want a print copy of that.
And I thought about doing that, but like, it seems like it would be a lot of
effort for me to do without going through like Lulu or something.
Um, cause it's, it's, you know, it's like the, it's like a couple hundred pages
probably in a lot of it is nonsense.
And I'm not that proud of it.
Like I think it functions better as an audio file that you can skip around in,
you know, then as like a physical book to read.
And I would rather print a book.
I was just like, had worked harder on like one that I didn't literally
write in a day, you know?
Um, and then I had written this, this sort of mini book last year, uh, it was,
well, I consider it a pamphlet.
It was 40 pages that was called, um, fixed that for you, which was basically
my like, I don't know, like my, my manifesto, like my, my like, you know,
here's what the world should be like book, you know?
Um, and, uh, that was like the one that's that, like, I was planning to print
and I was definitely going to sell them and ship them out.
And I was also going to make a video book out of it, but, um, enough time
passed, but with the me not having edited the rest of the book.
And now when I read it, I'm like, this is fucking weird.
Like this, this reads like somebody who, um, has just become a complete
bad scientist trying to explain to you why, um, like why everything in society
is fucked up, but like it was way too dense.
It's hard to read.
It's like hard to parse.
So like when my own writing is hard for me to parse, I'm like, maybe
this is not something I want to publish, um, that strongly, but I think
for, I suppose.
Yeah, but like I, I have been working on other like fiction novels that I
would love to publish.
Like I've been working on a proper light novel.
And so like I'm only like maybe a fourth of the way in or maybe even half.
I might just make it really short, but like I'm considering finishing that
and selling that as a physical book.
But like, I also just thought the other day, like, well, I've always wanted
to make a magazine.
I have the technology at my disposal.
Like, you know, I know how to print this shit.
All I have to do is staple them together.
Um, I know how to use the, the, the programs that, that let you design
magazines, like basically Adobe InDesign, um, which I love because I took a
class on it, you know, I know how to use this fucking shit.
So I should just make a fucking magazine because I've always wanted to do it.
Like I've been dreaming of it since I was a kid.
Um, I mean, I've made magazines before.
Like I've made with them out of pen and paper, you know, but like this
could be a real one that I could actually sell.
And that would make, that would be like the biggest come for me in the world.
Like if I managed to sell like 50 of some, you know, limited run magazine,
and then people were to like deconstruct it and scan it onto the internet.
That would be the coolest fucking thing that's ever happened, you know, in my life.
That would be like the height of what my aesthetic is.
Like I really love magazines.
I love the format of them.
I've always loved the idea of just a whole magazine written by one person.
Like basically just a dojinji, you know, but like one that is stylized
like a magazine.
And, um, yeah, I think that would be the most Digi bro thing I could possibly
sell and like seeing that 50 people bought my shirt.
I'm absolutely certain 50 people at least would buy my magazine.
I might even try to sell more of it, but like it depends on how much it costs
to print it and how much I'm charging for it, you know, you could do that really cheap.
I mean, if you went like, if you wanted to go to like the kind of more grunge
indie zine kind of aesthetic and do it like black and white and really like
lean into the whole zine aesthetic, you could do that super cheap.
It wouldn't cost a lot.
I'm more into the idea of it being like a high production look, like looking
like a proper anime magazine, you know, like, I mean, I wouldn't have to like
print it on like super expensive paper.
I don't think, but like I would go all out with the design of it, although
like my design sense is also very fucking bare bones.
So like it's definitely not, I don't have the skills to make it look like
an actual anime magazine, you know, but like the format of it will be like one.
It'll just be like a weird, like visually off.
It'll definitely have the zine feel just because that's my visual style.
Like, um, you know, like there's no helping it.
I, I cannot be professional enough to not have some level of like, okay,
this is clearly made by a guy, you know, not a team, not a graphic artist,
not somebody who, you know, not somebody who studied graphic arts as much as
just typography and in design, you know.
It'll still be cool.
I mean, I don't know.
I'm definitely with you on that romantic, romanticization.
That's not the way to say that word, but you know what I mean?
Of physical media, well, and it's just, it's worth a lot more money to people,
which is like another part of the great thing.
Like making $1,500 in one go is a lot of fucking money.
And that's like just because people want to own something that they can like have,
you know, and it has more literal value than like data on the internet.
And you and I are both huge advocates of like, like you still buy all your
games physically, you don't even buy any digital games.
So like you understand how much you value, like having physical property
that has resale value and like, you know, potentially even growth value.
If we, if we continue to become more popular and like maybe people want
to collect our old shirts and shit and like you can resell the shit on eBay
one day for more, who knows, you know, or at least enough to recoup some of your loss,
you know, like even if you can only sell my shirt for like five bucks on eBay,
at least you could make five bucks on it when you don't care about it anymore.
You know, right?
I don't know.
It's just like you're giving away money.
I want to have something tangible in return for it as opposed to like permission
to access something on your storefront that could be turned off tomorrow.
Exactly.
Guess I'm just a fucking boomer that way.
And that's I think that might be how it feels for like people to use
something like spread shirt.
It's like, you know, we had designs taken off of it.
We kept trying to put our fucking JoJo meme shirt on there.
And like if we had just made and sold the JoJo meme shirt,
we definitely would have sold a couple, you know, I guess we could still technically do that.
I mean, I'm still salty.
I still think about it every couple days.
I'm like, I have no hands and I must fap.
Why did I not make that shirt?
It was perfect.
Yeah.
I think that shirt would still sell because JoJo is still popular.
And like, you know, all we got to do is mention it at the end of a video on my channel.
I'll just be like, Hey, here's the JoJo meme shirt.
Tom is selling this, you know, it says JoJo meme on it.
But I demand a cut if I do that because I came up with the shirt.
That's fine. It seems that seems reasonable.
Get into the joint merch venture.
Alicorn Princess all over again.
Oh, Alicorn Princess is the failure that taught me everything, though.
Yeah.
Cut our teeth the hard way on that one.
Can you can you tell me what's the Salicorn Princess thing?
It was the t-shirt I made back in like 2013.
When me and Tom were first like really starting to get like big on YouTube,
we were talking a lot about how to monetize it because like I had
initially I've been making a lot of just before you even get to deep into it.
The reason we were talking about this because this is before Patreon.
So this Patreon did not exist yet.
Patreon didn't exist.
And initially I would be making like $600 a month on ad revenue
for like two months before the big thing happened where like every pony
video got demonetized or blocked.
And I had to completely change my style so that I could even post on YouTube,
which is why I started using the pony avatar and all that shit
was just to get past copyright, which is the biggest reason we all did it,
you know, because if you posted full screen footage, your shit got blocked.
So like in that time where I wasn't making any money,
I had like already left my job and I was like basically had enough
saved to stay afloat for a little while.
But me and Tom were like, we have to find a way to make money off of this.
If we want this to be what we do, you know.
So we were talking about building our own like email subscription service
where people would pay just to watch our videos in the first place.
But then it was like, how do we market the videos?
We were trying to do a kit.
We planned a Kickstarter that was going to be to just fund like us doing the videos for a while.
And then if like we had like a crazy stretch goal that we would move in together
and make videos every day if we hit 40 grand.
Um, not realistic, but you know, just a dream naive, but, uh,
eventually while we, we also talked about doing shirts cause Tom had a shirt press.
So I commissioned him to do a design of the moment where I say,
I'm a fucking Alicorn princess cause it was like my most famous catchphrase
in my most popular video.
And, um, Tom drew a picture that was like my pony as like that moment
when Twilight first grows her wings and it says, I'm a fucking Alicorn princess.
There was both an uncensored and censored version, but, um,
I learned a lot of important lessons from that. First of all,
hiring Tom to do the design meant that it was in his style and there was not a t
shirt of my pony in the style that it naturally appears.
So like I don't think that people were going to gravitate to it as much because of
the fact that it's not like the way they know the character, you know,
um, but I was like nervous about using that character because I had not paid the
artist who designed it. You know, she just did it as a fan and I didn't want to
like capitalize off of it without them getting a cut and she seemed resistant to
receiving money for whatever reason. Um,
so I hired Tom to make a design and also the shirt says fuck on it and most
people don't want to wear that computational of a shirt, including me.
I have several shirts to say fuck on them that I'm like really nervous to wear in
public. And I like always feel really embarrassed when I realized that I'm
wearing it in public and have not noticed. Like I have the, I have the fuck off.
I'm autistic shirt. And also the, um, you know, the, uh, the, uh,
world as a fuck born to die world as a fuck shirt,
that meme from Tumblr, the like 200 billion dead cops or whatever,
except I have the devil man version. Um,
so it's the two characters from devil man,
but it still says born to die world as a fuck on it.
So I feel a little weird wearing it in public.
I feel it. Like there's this song, uh, from Carol on Tuesday,
like the, the galactic mermaids,
I want to desperately make it my ringtone because,
because they're saying fucking bullshit.
It's like, and it's such a good song. It sounds so good.
And I resonate with the lyrics,
but I'm too shy to put it as my ringtone,
but because what if I get a call in public?
I don't get calls, but what if I get a call in public?
Just, just got to be a badass about it. It's funny.
I did, I made a similar mistake because I've been like in,
I've been bedridden for like months now,
but I went out and got like snacks a couple of days ago,
not realizing what shirt I was wearing.
I was wearing a game of throne shirt, like a meme shirt.
That was just, uh, uh, the hound and Aria,
like sitting on the horse when, when, uh,
like from one of the later seasons where he's just like, fuck the king.
And it says, fuck in huge giant letters.
And then under it, the king and this huge image.
And I was just walking around all day in this shirt, like in public,
not realizing that like I had this emblazoned on my chest. Yeah.
It was, it was a power move without realizing it.
So I'm a fucking Alicorn princess.
Even the censored version, you can still say it's tell it says fuck.
So not a lot of people going to buy a shirt that says fuck on it.
And I think that like we pretty much only sold
like the on the censored version to anybody other than I think Victor.
So who did buy one?
Because he thought it was fucking hilarious because it says fuck on it.
And it's got a pony, you know, and it's my pony.
So this is obvious why Victor would want this shirt.
Not so obvious why anybody else would want it, you know?
Because like, even though it was a memorable moment for one of my videos,
it wasn't like a repeated catchphrase.
It wasn't like it doesn't mean anything to the guy wearing it.
Like I kind of thought maybe you could wear it and be like,
yeah, I'm a fucking Alicorn princess.
But like it just seems to be in reference to me, you know?
Well, yeah, I guess it because it is you on the shirt itself,
which is kind of undercuts that ability. Exactly.
So like that's why like my like when I do the void gazer shirt,
like I don't want it to be too like I want you to be able to tell.
It's my like sunglasses look, but like, you know,
it's not like just a picture of me and that's implying that that's who this is.
You know, it's like anybody could be the void gazer, you know,
just got to wear the sunglasses, basically.
But yeah, like just I think if you're going to,
if I'm going to make a shirt like out of myself,
it has to be a better meme.
And so like that was why it for years,
I've considered trying to like hire Munchie to do his shirt.
And like we were talking about it like a year and a half ago,
where I had a few ideas.
I was going to have him make me a human content machine shirt,
which just says that in and like one that was like anime.
It's a Japanese colloquialism.
And he gave me a few designs that I kind of liked,
but weren't really what I had in mind.
And like I felt like getting exactly the visuals I wanted was not going to be
possible communicating with somebody else.
Like like I have a really specific vision in mind for what I would want for my shirts.
So it's like I can't just commission an artist.
It's going to feel like their art.
It's not going to feel like Digi Bro's art.
It's just going to be art of Digi Bro, you know?
So like with the me versus the Kirito's one, it was like, OK,
this is a piece of art I can create that like is within my wheelhouse
that is totally going to be something only I would do, you know?
Is it's it's like a it's a screen cap of me from one of my videos.
You know, about to shoot a array of Kirito's.
It's I had to like seek out, you know, pictures of each of the characters
from behind to use in this image, which was not necessarily
was neither as hard nor as easy as, you know,
whatever you're thinking, it would be it's it's the opposite.
And it yeah, like the the layout is from Fantasy Star Four
because I'm a huge fantasy star fan.
So like, you know, I even used I tracked down the specific
font that's used in Fantasy Star to write in all the all the names and shit.
So like, you know, even if all of this is not really like an
it's not an artwork in the sense that like I drew it,
but I compiled all these elements from around the web.
And it's basically like a a a collage of different PNGs,
you know, but into something that is that looks cool.
So that's a very Digi Bro design.
That's what I wanted to sell, you know.
It's pretty sick.
I've gone on about these shirts for way too long.
It's just basically the shirts, the podcast episode, dude.
This is this is the real shit.
This is how this is how we're going to we're going to make money
in the post YouTube apocalypse that is slowly marching its way toward us.
And evidently, well, it's really funny, Tom,
that like I'm really interested in going into all this depth with you
because everybody on the PCP is like interested in alternative revenue
sources, just having cool merch and stuff.
But it's like we all have a tendency to like dabble our toes
into something and take forever to really get into it and figure out
what the fuck is going on, you know, like when it comes to doing merch
or like streaming, like we spent a lot of time like, OK,
we'll we'll we'll work on it while we're doing the stream.
But we do not think about it again afterwards.
And like there's a lot to learn, you know, to like optimize how we're doing it
to, you know, create, like, especially when we were on Twitch
and we didn't know anything about the culture of Twitch, you know.
And like we did not learn anything about the culture of Twitch
because we didn't take the time to do that because it's like a side venture.
But like the PCP, when we talk about like merch, it's the same story.
It's like everybody likes the idea of having merch.
We have ideas for what merch we want.
But like when it comes to the action of how do we get that merch made?
Let's just go through spreadsheets so nobody has to think about it, you know.
But like if somebody was dedicated to making all the merch and like,
you know, obviously, that person would get more of the money
and they are more incentivized to just make their own merch for themselves.
But everybody should do that.
Like, yeah, get into it.
It's a good, it's fun, it's beneficial.
Like if you're into merch and like the idea of people having merch of your shit
by the materials, they will pay themselves off if you market it well, you know.
Yeah, because we fucking sold again.
We sold those 10 shirts in like no time, like off of a tweet.
Literally, we just tweeted that we were selling the channel.
It didn't exist. The stream didn't exist.
It was just there's a name and that did better than when we actually had
a channel and stream and we're actively advertising it in every single video.
We were wearing the shirts on the stream.
Like we were pushing the fuck out of these shirts and nobody was buying them
after that initial 10.
It's so much different if you make it yourself.
Yeah. God damn it.
I've really got to fucking make it hard.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
All right, go go relieve thyself.
Mage. Yes, I am still present.
Fucking dead this entire time.
You're not you're not riveted by by the the in depth intricate
backyard or insider baseball on fucking shirts.
I don't sell any merch.
Well, that's your problem right there.
You got to you got to start whoring yourself out.
You got to make that's how you make the big bucks.
But I don't want to.
God damn it, Mage.
What is it? You fucking not.
You don't want all the money.
You don't want to fucking milk all these peasants for all their worth.
I don't.
I mean, I'd like to sell things, but like, I don't know,
selling shirts, selling medicines and stuff like that.
It seems complicated.
And I don't want to do it.
Mage, am I going to call you?
Are you drawing?
Have you been drawing this whole time?
No. Are you sure?
I'm positive.
I drew a little bit in the middle.
OK, because you because we before we started recording,
I was like, hey, Mage, what's up?
You're like, I'm drawing. I'm like, oh, yeah,
I just wanted to finish up some line art quickly while you were.
I didn't think this would go on.
But like, well, you should be fair line art for in like five minutes.
I didn't think it was going to go on that long either.
And I did just sitting.
I just been sitting here.
I've been listening.
I just have nothing to say.
That's all right.
What have you been doing?
What's going on in Mage Land?
You're back. You're back in the UK.
What are you working on?
What's what's going on?
What's happening?
A secret thing I might have mentioned a few
times ago that I cannot tell much about anything
because I can't.
I cannot like a collaborative thing or sort of.
Yes, me and a friend working on a thing.
And that's all I can say.
It's been it's been it's been going going sort of rough.
Like, of course, I'm I'm the one drawing the things
that I had to redraw everything I drew so far.
So I'm sort of starting from scratch.
Yeah, but it's OK.
I'm a lot more happier with how things are coming out now right now.
Can you tell me the the medium?
Is it a comic book or an animation or I know I cannot tell you.
It's not an animation.
I can tell you that much.
So it's not it's not that.
So don't look forward to that.
It's not going to be on my YouTube channel, probably.
So it's not a video format.
It's just some drawings for things.
So, yeah, I've been completely restarting from scratch,
but I'm happy with it because, like, I don't know.
I just leveled up, I guess, since the last time I drew it.
And it just looks so much better now.
So I'm happy with that.
And I've been playing a bit of Warframe if you heard of Warframe.
I have played a bit of Warframe myself in my day.
It's so fun. It's pretty cool.
It's fun. I dig it.
I haven't. It's not like one of those games I can get super into.
Just again, I'm not a big multiplayer guy.
But yeah, yeah, you did being being a spaceman.
Just fun slicing things up.
It's pretty cool.
Yeah, I got since I have discord nitro.
I got a Warframe for free sort of because discord
did a thing with Warframe.
And that's how they got me in.
They were like, hey, I mean, Warframe is always free.
Yeah, yeah, like free stuff.
Give you like a bunch of goodies in the game
because that's how they make all their money
as they sell you stuff.
But like discord is like, we'll give you the first hit for free
because that's how we roll.
Yeah, they were like, well, because you have discord nitro,
we're going to have like give you like $50 worth of goodies for free
in this game. And I'm like, I like free stuff.
So I download the game and I played the game just because I got the free stuff.
Yes. So discord nitro.
I've known that discord nitro has existed for a while now.
Never, never for even a fraction of an iota.
Have I ever considered, hmm, maybe I'll buy discord nitro.
You have it. Yes.
What's what's the benefit other than getting free shit in Warframe?
What's what made you say?
Yes, this is something I will purchase because I don't understand the appeal yet.
OK, OK, listen, listen to me very carefully.
I'm ready. I'm ready to get schooled.
I can I can put love emojis everywhere I want.
That's my benefit.
That's all I need.
Is it just the animated emoji?
Is that not just animated emojis?
Just like any any emojis from any server I am from,
I can put I can put in any other discord that allows custom emojis.
And I just I can just put them everywhere.
And it just it just I cannot.
I cannot function without them anymore.
This is my life now.
To everyone who's not in the chat right now, just literally everybody listening,
mages mages spamming with these emojis as she's making her point right now.
Yes, I'm just I'm just putting off every single one, not every single emoji.
There's a lot of emojis, but yeah, I can it's just so good.
It just feels so good.
I can it's it's it's it just makes me happy.
That's it. That's that's all there is to it.
I'm just happy I can do this.
I wasn't sure if there was more to it because I kind of figured that was
like the the the excelling point for you because I see these all the time
when you're when you're talking in the chat.
But I wasn't sure if there's more to it that I was not aware of.
There might be more to it, but that's what I'm using.
That's all it took for you to fucking clinch the deal.
All right, all right.
Since I've been sitting on my ass doing nothing because moving is basically impossible.
I've been marathoning half in the bag and and best of the worst constantly.
Like that's just been my life like all week is just getting caught up on that media.
Right. I didn't know you were not caught up on that.
I mean, I watch it every now and then.
I mean, I'm caught up on all the Planket reviews and stuff.
But like I just watch I don't usually watch everyone that comes out
just if they're talking about a movie that I'm interested in.
But I've been super bored.
So I've been marathoning a ton of it.
And best of the worst is like the greatest idea in the history of the Internet.
I knew that would be your type of show.
Like because best of the worst is awesome.
But like I'm not as into it as half in the bag just because I'm not that into
like those B movies that they watch, you know, like I think it's really funny.
Some of the stuff they'll get out of it.
But like it's not my aesthetic so much.
But like I've always wanted to do something like it with something that would be that.
I mean, that's kind of it was basically what the inspiration was for Cleveland.
The Wii like we pretty much were copying best of the worst mixed with half in the bag.
Like it was meant to be like a little bit of both just watching these these videos.
I made a tweet about it earlier in the week, I think, just being like
it just made me realize like, oh, there are like people out there
who have like real friends and like hanging out to something that happens.
No, you got to remember these guys are they're like us.
They all met online and then moved into the same place.
That's why we want to do.
But now. But now.
But now they're just like, hey, it's the weekend.
Let's spin the wheel.
This is what we want.
Like this. That's what I.
That's why I know it's such a like long term goal where it's like
because, OK, lately, people have been like down on the idea
that it was still possible to have
PCPHQ just because like Ben and Munchie really want to live in Boston
and they're not really interested in leaving for PCPHQ.
Like they both are they want to live there.
They have a lot of stuff going on there.
So they're like they're the kind of like out of the picture for that.
You know, and I don't want to live in Boston at all.
So like it would be easier if I was there and everybody was there.
I hate Boston.
I love living in Virginia Beach.
Boston is way too expensive.
And I don't think it's worth like I understand
why for Ben living in the heart of Boston with like a group of a ton of people
that keeps his rent super fucking low and he likes public transit.
That's fine. Very different lifestyle from mine.
I want to live in a fucking house and I want a car, you know.
So like it like Boston is way too expensive to live that life there.
Not expensive to do that in Virginia Beach, you know.
And it's also a lifestyle I'm used to.
And I moved into a much better part of town than I used to live in.
Like the area I live in now is way cooler.
Than the area I used to live in.
So like I'm completely satisfied living here.
I am not going nowhere.
I like even just down to the neighborhood I'm in.
Even if I wanted to like buy a house later,
I would want one nearby, you know, like to where I am right now,
because I really like where I'm living, because the there's not.
I have like no complaints like everything I want is here.
I have a car, so I'm not that worried about public transit.
You know, I understand why it would be harder for Ben.
But even then, like down where I'm located now,
there's a lot more in walking distance than there was.
I mean, there was nothing in my old place.
Now I can walk to pretty much anything I would want to walk to.
So it's not a big deal.
Fucking sick. Yeah, it's a great area.
So like for me, it's like I'm I'm definitely trying to settle down here.
There is an apartment complex directly behind me with
availabilities that is not expensive, you know, like Nate or you
or you and Ben or whoever could get a place right behind me
and literally be able to walk to my house in like two minutes,
you know, or fucking Nate could take his fucking boosted
board to my place in two minutes, you know, I just I'm just thinking like,
oh, man, it'd be pretty cool to do like an I am games video game version
of best of the worst.
People just send in like the shittiest games you could find
and you just like dig through them.
I'm like, oh, my God, I have a huge room.
Like, first of all, my living room is gigantic and I bought a fucking couch
that seats like could potentially seat like nine people on it, you know,
like I have a huge couch for use of purposes such as big group watching,
you know, and I fucking have this one other room that's just
a big room that could easily be filmed in, you know, like I don't we don't live
in that room. I just use it for like crafts.
So build a set in there and it could just be like, you know, Nate takes
his boosted board to my house every Saturday.
We set up the set, we film a bunch of shit, you know, and anybody else
who lives nearby can be a part of it.
Or if we want to do Radcon, we already have a set built.
Me and Nate already have a show.
It's easier for us to fund it because we can talk about it on that show, you know,
like I would think that Nate and I doing a regular show would be at least
as popular as like the difference in subs between the two of us,
which is he already has over a hundred K. I've got 350.
A lot of people are excited to watch our videos, you know,
I think we would at least pull the same view counts we currently
pull through like our main channel videos, you know, and that would be
much better advertising for the rest of the PCP for, you know,
for any projects we were doing together for Radcon.
Like it would be a way bigger signal boost to all of that.
So like that's why I want it so bad because I think, oh, man,
this would be a way that if Nate and I live together and we built
the foundation of this and everybody else could be involved,
everybody's just going to make more money like just because it exists, you know,
it's going to be easier for me, even if it was just me and Nate running the main show.
If Ben comes in for an episode of a show that's got 40,000,
you know, views per video, huge signal boost to his fucking empire, you know,
like that would be the cool thing about it.
Yeah, that's that's that's what I want.
That's what I want to happen. I still, I mean, I'm not like super negative
on PCP HQ. It's just like it definitely doesn't seem like it's going to involve
everybody at this point, but there are people who are still interested.
But it's kind of like like Ben and Munchy don't want to even be involved
with it on like a fundamental level.
Like they would rather probably show up once every six months and it would still be
it would still be enough for them because they have followings like they don't
necessarily need to make way more money and they're having a lot of fun
doing what they're doing without worrying about money, you know, like endless war
is a nonprofit venture and it takes a huge amount of effort,
but they're both really proud of it and they want to be a part of a community
of people and they're making enough money to live up to the lifestyle that they
that they consider to be enough, you know, like Ben is not like crying about
money all the time, you know, he's he's well, he's crying about money,
but more about crying about taking down the system.
Right. It's he's crying about money because he would like to have more of it,
but not because he's miserable with his life from not having enough of it,
you know, like big difference.
And I think a lot of artists who are at the same size as some of the members
of the PCP like would not be able to sustain themselves on the amount
they make through their art, but like because our fans are so passionate
and so like, you know, cultish, like it's a they just care enough
to like fund our lives, basically, you know, so like granted, we're not
like we're not bending them to their dollar to fucking be able to afford
these lifestyles, but like, you know, like in other words to say,
we're living cheaply, but it's entirely fan funded, you know, right.
So so like, I understand why they would want to have like closer
interactions with fans and a more thriving community around them,
because that's what interests them as an artist.
For me, I'm much more insular.
I don't really want to communicate.
Like I have a discord and I'm in there pretty frequently.
I only go into the Discussing Digi content board.
Like I'm only there to talk about myself and answer questions and talk
about my videos.
I'm not there to like, just discuss anime with all these guys
because I don't want to get sucked in.
I will not get enough work done, you know, anytime I start talking on
discord, it's like hours gone.
And, you know, I will get sucked up in a conversation and just fucking
totally lose track of time.
And I want to I just like working a lot harder, more than that, you know,
I would prefer to keep getting things done than to have a conversation
that goes for hours and I don't really get anything out of it.
Like, you know, in terms of like contributing to my career, you know,
like, I think at the end of the day, the people into your work would
prefer you get more work done in the long term anyways.
So especially if they just like everything I do, which a lot of people
do and I make a lot of shit.
So like, for some people, I'm like their biggest source of entertainment.
It's like, I watch an hour of DigiBro content every day because he
releases an hour of DigiBro content every day.
So, you know, like, that's a lot.
That's a lot of consumption of one person's work, you know, if I was
watching an hour of somebody every single day, I would definitely consider
myself to be a huge fucking fan, you know.
Right.
It's pretty wild.
So, um, there are people, I mean, I will watch.
I might save it up for a while, but I will watch all of Jesse's content
and I will watch all of Dick Masterson's podcast, you know, which is like three
hours a week.
So that's like stuff I consider myself a big fan of in the same way that
people are a fan of me.
So which is why I get it, you know, like, I totally get how people feel about
me because I feel that way about Dick, you know.
I feel that way about Dick.
Sorry for cutting you off, mage.
What were you going to say?
Yeah, that's okay.
I wanted to say maybe we should like start moving on to voicemail sometimes.
Yeah, we haven't been going for like a while.
We went for close to two hours.
Yeah, almost two hours now.
Yeah.
We can go to voicemails.
I've gotten everything off my chest.
I really went on about shirts.
Dude, shirts, shirts are important.
I feel like coming up the next 12 months, shirts, shirts are going to be a thing.
Shirts.
I want to get back into shirts.
You're doing shirts.
It's all about the shirt life.
I just, I don't want to like overdo the shirts and have people be like,
I have too many shirts of yours.
But at the same time, you can never have too many shirts.
Oh, let me tell you about an idea I have, though, that I might do next year.
And if I do this, this will be how I do shirts, which is that at the start of the
year, I'm going to buy like basically just a massive amount of shirts.
And I'm going to create a unique shirt for every day.
And I'll make a vlog basically just for every vlog, like just have a different
shirt every vlog I'm in, because again, it's very easy to make them, you know,
like to just make one, just fucking slap it on the thing and it's done.
So I'll wear a different shirt in every video.
And then I'll set up a website where you can buy any of the shirts that I
weren't any of the videos they're just made to order.
So it would be like, yeah, buy a medium shirt is what, $25.
And like you can choose whichever thing that I've worn as your shirt.
So like each of them would just have been worn in one video.
But like, if that's the particular phrase you thought was funny, then
that's the one you can buy.
And it would just be like endless options for shirts, you know, that's pretty neat.
I like that.
Um, so that's, that's one idea I have.
And like, obviously no one of those shirts would probably sell all that well.
But, you know, as soon as you find the one that really makes you laugh,
that's the one you buy, you know, right?
The possibilities are.
But I'd have to set up a store that can like do that automatically.
Cause the way I did all my sales was through email and that was a pain in the ass.
Um, just because a lot of people don't really know how to write their address.
They, uh, don't remember to put the zip code or they forget little details.
Have you looked into Etsy?
Isn't like the whole point of Etsy is like selling handmade items?
I probably should.
I mean, especially if I'm going to do a lot of this, then I should look into it.
I don't know if they take a cut, like bandcamp either.
I haven't looked into it, but like, I'm sure they do.
That must be how they make their money.
Yeah.
Cause like, I mean, the best part about doing it the way I did it was that it was
like all profit, you know, like I get a hundred percent of the proceeds.
There is no, you know, it either is going towards paying off what I spent
on the cost of the shirt, or it is just money I have now.
There is no other money involved.
Nobody else is getting my money, you know,
you should like set up a Google form that people can fill out if they want to
buy a shirt and then you send them a paypal.
That would probably be closer to what I would.
And then cause when you send them an invoice, they have to put in their
information and stuff in order to have it go through and pay you.
That might be a good way to do it.
That keeps it all in house.
I just want to set up a system that'll do it for me, you know,
automate it as much as possible, but without having to pay for a site, you know,
or like I'd even pay for my own hosting for a site just to have a shop site
because that would be cool.
But like I would do that over going through like a spreadsheet or something, you know.
Yeah, look into Shopify then.
I know there's like a Shopify plugin for how self-hosted websites to let you do that.
Yeah, I'll look into that too.
All right, let's go to voicemails then.
Let's do it.
All right, I have five voicemails for us to go through today.
If they suck, you can yell at me.
Tom Oliver says it's Twitter.
This is the best that I could pull from the ones that we have before we get started.
There was a lot of voicemails.
I didn't include any of them because they were all long,
but there were like five or six people who called in specifically to defend peeing,
sitting down.
I guess that was a hot button topic from one of the previous episodes that I haven't listened to yet.
But yeah, there was there was quite a few people who voiced their disdain
at I guess we were not too kind to the sitting down,
well, I believe Nate included that it was inhuman in some way.
Oh, OK.
Excuse him for for guys.
I'm assuming it was a specific gender issue.
Well, he was the guy's story was that he was getting up to use the bathroom out of bed
and he doesn't want to have to turn on the light.
So he sits down to pee and he was asking if that was acceptable
and we concluded that it was not.
I disagree with you guys with your conclusion.
Well, as a girl, you would normally sit down to pee.
That's why I don't find it all that way.
All right.
So our first voicemail is from a gentleman named Pony Lore.
And I figured this seemed to make sense considering
the the the event going on right now.
It's so let's check it out.
See if I remember how to actually do this.
You can do it.
I have faith since major is going to be appearing on podcasts about now.
I want to ask this question.
Why is major in the PCP?
I don't get me wrong.
I'm not one of these major haters who's against major being in the podcast at all.
But I still think it's kind of weird that she's in the podcast.
In the old horse cast, she was only mentioned once
and doesn't actually appear in the show.
While I do know that she did found a Skype chat and name it the procrastinators,
I still don't understand the connection that she has to the rest of you.
Clear up this pony lore.
I'm friends with you guys.
Right. That was what I wanted to say.
Is that like, I guess maybe people who don't know the pony history of us
might not be clear of how we met you.
But like you did.
You had a YouTube channel.
You did pony stuff.
You did pony drawings.
You were in the community.
I had promoted Mage on Equestria Daily, I think, like, right?
Because you did a couple of analysis videos back in the day.
I never like talked to her personally,
but I know that you you had started talking to like Ben and Hippo.
And I think you like you've always talked to those guys, right?
Like, I sort of welcomed into the rift
the Tibet brothers, the above of them.
And then that's how I started talking with Ben more so than Nate at that time.
It was I forgot about the rift.
And that that would be also connected to it for those who don't know.
There's this thing called it was a Skype chat called the rift cafe
where everybody who was doing my little pony analysis videos was invited to
because of some weird meme where a couple of guys had collaborated
and said that there was like a rift in space time between their channels.
It was very typical style, very that glasses.
But like they made a giant chat and all of us were at some point in it
because that's what we were doing.
But like it was kind of like those of us who were in the the horseshoe group
of friends were like we all knew each other and didn't really know anybody else in the rift.
So it was like we didn't really hang out there
because we would rather just talk to each other, you know.
So but I think Mage had, like you said, you invited the team up in there.
And so like you started talking to them that way then.
Yeah, I think that's how I also met Hippo.
He was there as well.
Like neither me nor Hippo can I remember how we met, but we just met with you.
Did you I actually the first interaction I have with you was when I did fanart
for your cousin, I think, when you asked to design the oh, you did one of those.
Yeah, I didn't even know that.
Yeah, that's the earliest interaction I have with you.
But like, yeah, we never really talked to did you much before that we were sort of a sort of like.
We were sort of like it's kind of like how you're in the same house, but never in the same room, you know.
Yeah, well, it's also that you like you hadn't really done many videos like you did three.
And then I hadn't really heard from you in the time that you were not making them.
So like I didn't know you were still in the community really when then you like put us all on the chat together.
And I was like, oh, it's Mage.
She did good videos.
I remember promoting her like, you know, I mean, I made a few not too many though.
But yeah, I was I was quite active in the Rift, though.
So yeah, like I said, in the same house, different rooms with Tom, how we met initially.
Do you remember Tom, how we met?
I don't remember specifically.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, hold on.
I remember I remember how I met with you now.
You might have been in the Rift at that time, maybe not.
But I know that somehow it got in contact to you with Skype.
You were having like financial issues and then I did commissions.
But then the money went to you.
Remember?
Oh, God, I think I repressed that because I was so ashamed.
But now you remember it.
I'm sorry.
But yeah, that's how I met with you.
Who else was just I just met through you guys.
I think when I created the Skype group, that's initially how I met Jess as well.
And then the man she came along.
But yeah, just we would just sort of hang out.
I was it was sort of in the friend group.
And I just ended up with you guys, you know.
Yeah, the point for playing the same as that may not just come out of the ether
as the diversity hire.
She's she's been here from the very beginning and we all are friends
and it is true and it is real and mage is good.
So there's this major list.
There's no one.
I think so.
Either that or we're all suffering from a very violent delusion.
Oh, that would be so funny.
I'm your imaginary friend, a collective imaginary friend.
OK, but yeah, it would it would explain your colored history in Lithuania, I
suppose, but yeah, no, I I sort of get why people question that
because I originally wasn't sure if I should be in your friend group
because I just need the chat.
I should have left.
That's how I felt initially.
But, you know, like I kept talking with you guys and we're friends
and I was like, you know, you know, it's OK.
I can I can come on the podcast to and then I did and now I'm here.
I mean, mage, the voicemail reference that you were only mentioned
like once on the horse cast, I was never on the horse cast at all.
So famous never on the horse cast person.
I don't know if we've I mean, I'm sure we've told the story of like how.
How you got involved, right, was just basically that like you went to
Brony like it just so happened that you were going to Brony Con.
And so were Nate and Ben and you guys all lived in Boston.
So they were just like we'll like you were just like looking for a ride
and they said they would do it.
Like I don't think you guys had really even talked before then, right?
We we had talked like casually, just like two people with similar interests,
you know, on we were both doing videos.
We talked but not like super hardcore or anything.
Right. I was a fan of T-Bap, but that was pretty much it.
I think that the the procrastinator's chat probably already existed, right?
Maybe I think so.
I think because I think we were all like we all knew each other
and like we were calling ourselves the horseshoe crew by that point, I think.
And like you came down with them.
And so like you just heard Ben and Nate for like eight straight hours
talking in the car and it was like a private eight hour T-Bap episode.
So that's just how they talk to each other.
It's it's crazy like and you still hear some of that on on this show.
But like, yeah, when they start talking to each other, it's just like they go into a.
They go into a fugue state, like they just won't stop.
They'll talk together forever, you know?
They literally can just keep going because they're like close enough in age
and interests that they're almost the same person,
but like reflected in a weird mirror way from each other.
Yeah, it's like the yin and the yang of a singular person
separated into two distinct entities.
Right. And I know what that's like because, you know, me and Victor are really close.
And so we can get into a certain mind state where it's like we're operating
like how we did growing up, you know, like making decisions together
in a way that reflects how we have always done so, you know.
I'm a little jealous and because I have an older sister,
but I just I sometimes forget that I'm the younger sister.
I just forget that I have a sister sometimes.
We're just that not close.
I wish I had a sibling that was close.
That's what happens when you grow up and lift
away and you're expected to fight to the death of your siblings.
I mean, for what it's worth, I now see my brothers very rarely,
even though I now live back in the same area as them, like they're just busy as fuck.
So it's like I grew up super close to them.
But now that we all have girlfriends and we're all like developing our own lifestyles,
we're getting like further and further away in interests.
Like there's tangential relationship between our interests.
Like we all like anime, but not the same anime.
We're all like video games, but not the same video games.
Shade is really into like Twitch streaming and shit.
And like playing, you know, MOBAs and shit like that, that I am not interested in.
Not as maybe as much as that, but like, you know,
he plays with his work friends who I don't know.
So it's like, yeah, I'm not really like hanging out with Shade all the time
because what the hell are we going to do together?
Other than like go get something to eat or something, you know?
But nonetheless, yeah, I do have a closer
relationship with them from like growing up.
But yeah, I don't I don't see my family all the time anymore.
And I don't think that's true for most of us.
I think most of us maybe Tom, you're living back at home, right?
But your little sister would still be there.
But I don't imagine you guys hang out every day or anything.
No, I mean, I have two younger sisters.
My younger younger sister is still here, obviously, because she's still in high school.
But my other sister has moved out.
She has like a professional job.
She makes like $90,000 a year.
She has like her apartment and everything.
She's like a real human being.
She's a real human being, yes.
I think I'm actually on track to make six figures this year.
That would be pretty sick.
I think it's I think it's going to happen because like my
Patreon has been really successful.
I have all these alternative revenue.
I haven't even found out what Manga Mondays is doing for me with the Amazon
Associates link yet, because it's always three fucking months behind.
Yeah, Amazon is Twitch is the same way.
Same company. I mean, they're owned by Amazon.
So yeah, they're fucking literally.
I was still sending Tom money for I am Games like last month.
I don't know if there's maybe another check coming possibly this month.
I don't know how far behind it was, but like fucking mystery.
Yeah, you make six figures this year.
Did you might actually be able to pay your fucking taxes finally?
I hope we'll have that done before the end of what I'm dreading the most
is that like I figured out the tax situation kind of.
I haven't actually resolved anything yet, but I've gotten advice on like
basically, I just need to hire an accountant.
It's probably going to cost me like a thousand dollars,
but they're probably going to save me a lot of money
because they're going to find more things I can deduct than I would have found on my own.
The IRS has a program where if you're a small business,
they will forgive the interest on your missing payments.
So you just have to pay off whatever you would have paid in the first place.
So I will not if I, you know, qualify for that, which I think I can.
At least that's what the accountant who I've talked to for advice said.
Then like.
Who I just know because of Econ.
So shout out to Econ for putting me in contact with them.
But yeah, they they basically said that, you know, I could and you can set up a payment plan.
So it's like, it's not that scary to me because my dad went into like a massive
amount of tax debt from like, like over the course of 10 years,
like not filing his taxes properly.
And the amount of debt he ended up with is similar to the amount I already have
after two years from just not paying taxes at all in the first place.
But, you know, nonetheless, he set up a payment plan where it's like he just
pays like a few hundred dollars a month over the course of however long it takes,
you know, I'm going to try to pay it off faster than that.
I don't want it to be like on my head for years.
But like I have a bunch of money saved up.
So like I'm close to a point where I could do it.
I just have to actually hire an accountant and go through the steps.
What I'm more worried about is saving up enough to pay the taxes again next year.
But I don't know how much they're going to reduce it by.
Like people have said that when you work with an accountant, it will often
dramatically reduce the cost.
But I don't know if that'll be true for me.
I already feel like I take a lot of things into account that I write off, you know.
Hopefully they know that secret black arts.
That'll, I mean, if Amazon pays nothing in taxes, there has to be a way for
me to pay nothing to fuck it over.
Like right, we're all working with the same general principles here.
I don't know.
Anyways, fucking let's move on to the next voicemail before we get lost in the weeds again.
Yeah, it's about to talk about yengeng.
Oh, no.
There's no Ben here.
We don't have to go down that road.
This is from Marlowe.
Marlowe has a message for us.
So you guys at Bronycon have a confession to make.
I could never get into my little pony.
I remember back in 2012, 2013, when the fandom was starting and blossoming.
I heard about it, so I watched a couple episodes and I just could not see what
other people saw in it, like maybe it's because I was an entire audience or maybe
I just wasn't autistic enough to enjoy it, which is weird because I feel like I
should have been no offense to you guys.
Like it's weird.
The PCP is giving me a lot of insight on the fucking debacle that was the MLP
fandom and like I feel like I missed out on something.
But at the same time, I feel like I missed out on nothing.
So I'm wondering now that LP is effectively over, what's the final autopsy report?
Tom, do you want to go first or should I?
I'll go first.
I think I mean, the reason I think I probably got into it as much as I did is
just because like I was just like really fucking depressed when I started
watching the show and it was just a beacon of positivity and like genuine
authenticity.
Like, did you coin the term at the time, like the new sincerity?
I did not coin that term.
I actually, when I first found out about MLP, the Wikipedia article considered
it a part of new sincerity.
Like it's not something that anybody in the fandom talked about, but it was on
the Wikipedia article.
What's?
Yeah, sincerity.
The new sincerity is a movement of basically just really sincere work.
Like the post irony era, basically, because like the nineties was very much
all about irony and a lot of our media is influenced by that.
But I believe it was actually the term was made up by the guy who wrote
Infinite Jest, David Foster Wallace.
He was like big into the new sincerity as an idea of like a rejection of that
former irony.
But I think like maybe Idea Channel made a video where they compared my
little pony to that, and that's why it was in the Wikipedia article.
But it seems about right.
You know, I, yeah, you're the one who introduced me to the term and it made
sense, just like the show was very sincere.
And I think that in the beginning, especially in 2012, 2013, the community
around it was very much embodying that sincerity.
It was very much expressing enjoyment for the show, understanding that
it was fucking weird and not giving a shit and not letting that like outward
stigma be reflected in people's appreciation for it.
And it was just kind of genuine in the beginning.
There's a very big difference between when you're looking at it from a
social angle and when you're in the thick of it.
Because like when you look at what my little pony represented, like the
community around it on like a macro level, it's like a bunch of people who
came together over this show and did a lot of good things and like, you know,
really seemed to get something out of it.
Like it made their lives different or better in some way.
And so like you can look at it as well.
I'm glad the show provided that for a lot of people.
And when you first get into that community, that's the way you're more
likely going to see it because, you know, you're looking at it from the outside.
Once you're in it, though, and you realize that, yes, it's true that it
does mean a lot of things to a lot of people.
There's also just a lot of weird fucking people who are, who are treating
it as this weird fame circle jerk and who are really like really oddly
defensive about the show to a point where they cannot handle the idea that
it is imperfect in some way.
And then there's the people who like have all this drama in the community.
You know, there's all these different factions.
There's all these people who have problems with each other.
And it's very petty, you know, and there's, there's people who, you know,
who like their entire self-worth is tied to their success within this fandom.
Or there's people who aren't really interested in the show anymore, but
they're still going to the conventions because they need to sell records.
And that's the only way that they can sell their art, you know, so like, or
people who are just doing commissions because it's a popular show and they
can make a lot of money off of it.
You know, like there's so many different elements to it that are once you dig
deeper, you're not going to see it in just the most positive light that you
could see it in.
You're going to see it as like, yeah, well, I, you know, I know that I got
something out of it and I see that it gave something to a lot of people, but I
also have interacted with a bunch of fucking morons who were into this show.
And, you know, like it's, I know that in order to be deep into this community,
this is something you have to deal with is this, this, these people, you have
to encounter them if you want to be such posted on a question daily, you know,
it was such an interesting blend of just like progression of events.
Cause like when I started getting into the show, I wasn't doing YouTube videos.
I didn't, I was never interested in being a YouTuber at all.
I was just doing art and stuff.
And I was interacting with that side of the community.
And it was back in 2012, when I first got into it, it was super small.
It was super tight in it.
Everybody pretty much knew everybody else.
And that was the weird thing about it too, is that like it hit like a second
renaissance in like 2012, 2013, where like, yeah, for the first two years,
most of those people were the only ones talking about the show.
So they all met and networked right away.
They all became friends and then it immediately got too big and too weird for
them.
And so they became like a totally different group.
And like when we went to Otsuk or Bronicon the first time, like you knew a lot
of those guys.
So I hung around them because I just followed you around, but none of them
had any idea who I was.
And it was really surreal because I got to see like from their perspective,
this is like a place to hang out with their famous friends.
Um, but like for new people coming in, it's a whole different click.
Like the analysis community has nothing to do with those guys.
They all came in later, you know?
So it totally changed the nature of what Bronicon is for everybody involved.
But like for us, it's much more like on the ground, talking to fans kind
of thing when we're at Bronicon, you know?
Yeah, it was, I mean, I kind of found myself torn between those two things.
Like, I mean, 2014 was the second time that we went together.
Like I was jumping back and forth between like hanging out with you and Nate and
Ben and Hippo and everybody and also trying to like go hang out with Saber
and Jax and all that because like everybody has a little like sub clicks
and they don't intermingle all that much.
So it wasn't just like, Hey, Digi, Ben, do you guys want to come hang out
with me and Saber and Jax and go like get lunch?
They have no idea who we are and they're pretty insular, you know, like, right?
Everyone kind of had their little bubbles and it was never like an aggressive
thing or anything.
It was just like, you know, like you have your friends and they're the people
you hang out with.
So like I was in this weird position where I had multiple bubbles.
I had been like very much like a 19th wheel.
Like nobody knew who I was and I could tell it made people a little
uncomfortable that I was there.
And because I also had Victor and Shade with me who like, even if you
know who I am, these guys are just my brothers, you know, but like I wanted
to hang, like to just be able to say that I like saw all these famous
Brony people because I had consumed everybody's work.
I knew what everybody was known for, you know, but none of them knew who I was.
So like, I'm just kind of using you as an excuse to hang out with all these
guys and like get a sense of them as people.
But like, it's weird for me to be there, you know?
And so that's why I tried not to do that other times.
I was like, okay, I have my own click now, you know, but like I was as famous
as any of those guys at that time.
I had just come in way later and gotten big really quick, you know, we were
establishing a new niche, essentially, that was separate from this.
And it's funny because between 2013 and 2014, we both doubled in size.
That whole community came into its own, became a big part of the overall.
So we were a way bigger thing and like people knew about what we did by next
year, the tables had basically turned, but it was really funny because even
though you and I pretty much like started it as a popular thing, it quickly got
away from us and there were channels that were as big as us who ended up doing
it for way longer and being way more respected because of the fact that you
and I quote unquote quit the fandom.
Like we, a lot of Bronies really just hate you if you, if you say anything
negative about the show or if you just leave, if you're like, oh, I'm not covering
the show anymore, they're like, oh, you're dead to me, you know?
Yeah, I mean, that was the big problem that we were facing a lot of friction
because like we were trying to analyze the show.
And so when it did something bad, like that kind of sucked.
And that was, if you said that, that was like, you know, cursed or not, you're
not allowed to decry God.
That's part of the reason why I quit the fandom as well.
Just, just part of it.
But yeah, people like, I started seeing like, you know, more issues with the show
and people immediately assumed I started getting negative or jaded or whatever.
Inspired or simple ones, though it wasn't.
I recently, well, recently, I say a few months ago, like some person I had
added on on steam, like forever ago, messaged me and, and they, they, they
started off nice and they just like, oh, hey, you're the mage.
You did the pony things and they started eventually going off at me.
It was like, how dear you are.
Like abandon your friends, how they must feel.
You're a terrible person.
And I'm like, oh my God, still now in the year of our Lord 2019, people are
still butthurt.
Yeah, I blocked them.
But like, because they just couldn't understand the idea that I, it's like,
it's not like I had a fight with anyone.
I just decided to not do the pony stuff anymore.
I'm still, I mean, I still welcome if people like, okay, like, let's say Persian
poetess messages me and be like, hey mage, you remember me?
And I'm like, yes, I remember you.
You're a good person.
We were friends.
I, I'm still, I'm still welcoming people.
I used to be friends was to talk to me.
It's not like I blocked them or snubbed them or anything, but they just assumed
I ditched them and I betrayed them and everyone's crying about it.
That's not how it is.
This person was so.
My hypothesis for all of this, like weird energy that the community always had was
that in the beginning and even to this day, but to a significantly lesser degree,
people on the outside would look at it and Bach, right?
Just like, what the fuck?
Why are these like adults into this children's cartoon for little girls?
And so you would get flack for liking the show.
So you'd come into the community and you'd want to like get positive affirmation.
You'd want to be like, oh, this is okay.
I am okay for liking this.
And so when people on the inside would say anything bad about it, that would
like threaten that narrative that, oh, I'm not a freak.
This is okay.
Like you just flash out at this is where the biggest problem.
I think that we as the PCP ran into and why we couldn't really participate
for too much longer is that all of us are proud internet weirdos.
Like we are people who identify with the weird or stuff that's on the internet.
We like are into like furry shit or we're into like, you know, weird fetishes.
We're into anime.
We're into like nerdy hardcore shit.
And we don't paint ourselves as like good guys.
You know, like we're not out there trying to say like, oh, it's, it's
like morally okay to be a fan of my little pony.
It doesn't threaten your masculinity because I'm like more likely to say, fuck
your masculinity, you know, like I'm more into like, there was a huge element
of transgender people in the My Little Pony fandom, huge, huge element of gay
people, huge element of autistic people that was in my opinion, the majority
of the hardcore fans would fall into one of those categories.
And so like to paint it as, oh, like, you know, it's okay to be a guy who's
into My Little Pony.
Yeah, but it's not really so much like that's not the appeal of it.
The community is comprised of like a lot of people who, you know, who only
really find representation in a show like this.
And that's what the appeal is to them.
It's not just that it's a girl's show that appeals to guys because it happens
to be good.
It also is like a weird pink horse show that is about identity, you know?
And like that is going to draw a lot of people.
And I think that that element of it attracted me, although I don't really
fall in with a lot of the like the Tumblr crowd who is, you know, who, who
makes up a lot of the people who cared about it on an identity level.
But I see it as just like, this is an interesting gathering of people
with mental disorders of which I am one and I want to explore that angle of it,
you know, well, that's, that's the thing.
I think that was really the separation and something that I don't even know if
it's like an age difference thing or like a generational gap is that like we're
doomers and like, I guess the doomer mentality, at least like our flavor of
doomer is just like, I'm fucked up and I accept that and I'm okay with it.
Because I feel like it's kind of like the world invites this, you know, like
this is what this is what happens because things are the way they are is we
end up with, with these weird mentalities and like we end up being weirdos.
And like we, we shouldn't have to feel ashamed of that.
Like we should just embrace the fact that yes, what we do is strange, but there's
no objective way to determine what is the right way to live.
So just enjoy being the freak that you are and like, but acknowledge that what
you're doing is not normal.
You know, that is the difference because I feel like people who came after us or
just like the current culture now is that what I'm doing isn't weird.
Society must can say this is normal.
I am still normal.
No matter how fucked up I am, I am still actually normal and I must change
society to redefine what I do as normal.
It's like, that's the difference.
You know, I'm, when I watched my little pony, I was under no illusion that this
is weird, abnormal and fucked up, but I was okay with it.
There were other people are like, I'm watching my little pony.
Therefore it is not weird anymore.
We must change all of society's perceptions.
And like when I initially watched it to just answer the original voicemail, um,
like I was huge into magical girls shows at the time.
I like, I had just gotten really into hard catch pre cure, card capture,
Sakura, um, I just like cute shit, you know, and I've always been like a cutesy
and like I've been a weird anime guy for a lot longer than I've been a bronie.
You know, I was like an outspoken lolly con and like just into weird,
cutesy little girls shit, you know, since way back.
So my little pony falls in line with all that.
And I saw a lot of people talking about it.
And most importantly, at the time, the whole show was available in 1080p on YouTube.
It was very accessible.
And that was the biggest thing that made it spread so much was that it was so
easy to just type in the name of the show, get all the episodes and just
watch it out of curiosity for why are people talking about it?
And like, it didn't stick with me at first either.
I think the first, the Tom and I agree, the opening two parter is like some
of the worst episodes of the show, I think.
Yeah.
Um, it's just not very good.
But like once you get into the character specific episodes after that, it gets
more appealing, but like I watched the whole first season and just thought
it was pretty good the first time.
Like I was just, yeah, that was fine.
And I wrote a blog post about it, then I caught up to season two and some of the
mid episode, like mid teen episodes of season two, I thought were really good.
Also, like the first five episodes are all great.
Um, just in terms of going farther than you would expect the show to go into
having like bigger narratives, more artistic presentation, like big villains.
Um, interesting songs, like pretty good production choices, uh, good character beats.
It's just like, wow, this is going better than I expected, you know?
And then I discovered the community right after that.
And there was just so because first thing I saw was friendship as witchcraft,
which is a pretty good parody show, you know?
So like that was my introduction to the idea of the Brony community.
And it's like right off the bat.
I know there's actually good stuff being made here, you know?
So I just fucking consumed all of it because I was a Hikikomori neat.
So, you know, I spent two months just consuming all of the fan culture.
And then it wasn't until like six or seven months after that that I actually
started making stuff that got popular.
So like I hadn't even, I had already gone through a phase where I wasn't even
into pony anymore before I got famous for doing pony.
Like I kind of came back for season three just to do videos on it.
And then I got really famous.
So I kept doing it, but like I had already kind of exited my Brony phase.
I just kind of re re entered it because suddenly it was the, the, you know,
my entire career.
Yeah, pretty weird.
But I definitely think like for me, being into a show long term like that is very odd.
It's by far the longest I kept up with the show weekly in my whole life.
By far the most knowledge I had.
Never been as into something like that and never hoped to never be again.
It was probably a bit too autistic.
I think the only thing that's ever been close for me was Undertale,
but that ended a lot quicker than my little pony did for me.
This is just one game the last four hours, you know?
Yeah, but I loved Undertale so much.
You haven't a clue, but there's just a lot of animation that got like a million views.
Yeah, an animatic year.
It's not even my most viewed video at this point.
But yeah, anyway, yeah, I just, I just loved Undertale.
I loved Metaton.
It's just so good.
When I first saw Metaton, I wasn't too impressed and I thought, you know,
he's probably going to be very popular.
He has that sort of anime aesthetic to him.
Then like I sat around just for like two, three days and then I was like,
holy shit, I love Metaton.
He's my favorite character.
All right.
What are the voice bills we got, Tom?
Next one's from Chorb Nohital.
I don't know if I'm pronouncing that right.
But what do you have for us, dude?
A topic is brought up.
The topic is regarding a group of people.
Did you bro mentions how the discourse on this topic misses the common sense points?
It should be addressing native agrees with Digi, but states that he doesn't
understand the full extent of the issue.
And perhaps if he knew more, he'd think differently.
Ben St.
Halfheartedly agrees, but says that if things were different, things would be better.
Nate agrees in a conciliatory manner, but says that it's probably the people
that need to change, not the situation.
Ben St laments the current state of affairs and says that if the situation
were different, the people would be different too.
Munchie laughs absentmindedly at something in the conversation.
He's thinking of endless war.
Hippocrite tries to chime in, but he's cut off.
He tries again, but is cut off.
He tries the third time, but stops himself and decides to think about it
more in his own head first.
Tom Oliver says that the entire argument is based on a faulty premise to begin with,
and no solution can be reached from this point.
Mage brings up a point related to her childhood in Lithuania.
Man, her upbringing was freaking whack.
Digibro says he agrees with everybody, but also disagrees with everybody.
And was just as working on a script about this topic right now.
But halfway through, he gives up the truth.
Exactly.
The who is off the grid.
Nobody knows what he's up to.
Munchie proposes a move to voicemails just when Hippocrite is thinking of what he wants to say.
The voicemails are brought up and mine isn't included.
I'm disappointed, but not surprised.
That was fucking great.
I'm glad that after 170 episodes, we fallen into a predictable rhythm.
That was really believable.
It's like exactly what it is.
I was like, damn, he's fucking got us pinned.
I'm like, we can just play.
We just play his voicemail for every episode from now to the end of time.
That kind of stuff for me, that kind of voicemail is the ultimate
like fan wink for me because they simultaneously are like kind of making fun
of you for your flaws, so it's funny and you laugh.
But at the same time, they have to know you really well to know this.
Like they have to have seen a lot of fucking PCP episodes
and really paid attention to the way we communicate in order to understand
how to break it down that well.
And that is how you know you have real fans.
Yeah, I thought I thought it was too too good, too good.
Had had to give it some love.
It was fucking great.
All right, next one is from Jor, not Jorb, like before,
just Jor and go.
You know, I've been kind of annoyed with the things
Ben has been saying lately on the cast, because a lot of it has been
political hot takes that aren't really funny or interesting to hear about.
But I really have to give him a pat on the back, a handshake,
a bro fist, a limp dick hand job in the middle of the night
because this Equifax one twenty five dollars thing,
I never would have heard about it if it weren't for him in the latest cast.
And it worked. I mean, I'm not American.
I'm Canadian, but my girlfriend's American.
And I had her put her shit into the website.
Turns out she's eligible and she's making one hundred twenty five dollars
for doing nothing. So I have to have to get handed to you, Ben.
You did a good thing. Thank you.
Oh, so one hundred twenty five dollars for.
So last I think it was the last episode.
I haven't listened to the last episode yet,
but I'm assuming that's what they were talking about.
But I've read about this.
Do you remember like a year ago, the Equifax scandal?
Like what happened?
Like there's the big this big company that handles
like everyone's private information like the entire country, Equifax.
They had a huge data breach and like
50 percent of the entire country's social security number is just out there.
So you could just get like one hundred twenty five dollars from them as like
a like a coverage.
It's like part of a settlement that if you put in your information
and your information was out there, they'll give you one hundred twenty five bucks.
Every once in a while, May will get one of those from like Kmart
because she worked at a Kmart that went out of business.
And like, you know, it's like, oh, if you were if you were if you were severed
because of the fact that we couldn't have your job anymore, like here's a
piece of a class action lawsuit or something like that, you know,
just weird shit like that comes up sometimes.
Yeah, so I guess you could it's at least one hundred twenty five dollars.
But like if you spent time,
like they'll compensate you for your time by the hour up to like I think you can get
up to five hundred twenty five dollars depending on how much time or if you've
been affected or like you had to like work with the bank to get something
reversed or anything.
However, the reason I included this this voicemail is because I wanted to say
we're all fucked because I read another article that Equifax
has only put aside thirty one million dollars for cash payouts because what you can do
is you can choose to either have them give you free credit audits for the next six
years or get one hundred twenty five dollars in cash.
And technically the six years of auditing is worth more.
But why would you trust Equifax with your information again is beyond me,
like especially if they fucked up this bad.
So most people are taking the cash payout, but they've only put aside thirty one
million dollars.
So according to people who are like smart and are following this issue,
because of how many people are picking the cash payout versus how little money
they put aside for it, we're actually going to get a fraction of one hundred twenty
five dollars, probably to the point where it's going to be basically nothing at all.
Well.
So, yeah, fuck everything.
Good job.
Equifax probably did this on purpose to avoid having to pay huge amounts of money.
So I just want to let you everybody know, prempatively, don't get too excited just yet
because there's literally not enough money to go around.
Amazing.
Yeah.
So keep your finger on the pulse of that if you're waiting for your check,
because I have a feeling sorry to that guy with the voicemail.
Yeah, the decimal might be moved over a few places by the time the check comes
in the mail, not in a preferable way.
All right.
Our last voicemail is from Jack V.
All right, Jack, bring us home.
Oh, hey, PCP.
I just wanted to make sure that it wasn't lost on anyone that on episode one
sixty nine of the procrastinators podcast, both Nate and Ben
emphatically and loudly agree that there is nothing morally wrong with adult
consensual incest all the while their sweet sister graces within earshot.
You're a dog.
You're a dog and I'm sick of it.
Well, there you have it, everybody.
Another procrastinators podcast in the bag done completed.
We did it.
We did it a lot quicker than it seemed like it is two and a half hours.
We didn't feel that long.
It did not.
Well, when you're talking about just hard, I don't know what is going on.
That's true.
Politics drags forever.
T-shirt talk at just that just that just the time just flies by.
This episode of merchandising or something, I guess so.
Patreon.com slash the procrastinators speaking of merchandise.
Go there.
Give us your money and you can get access to bonus episodes if you pay five
dollars or more bonus episodes.
We should probably come up with like some kind of merch tier.
I feel like that would be like, I think it would be really neat.
Me and you had talked about this idea for I am Games called like the monthly
shirt club where it was like a subscription service or something where every
month we would send you a different shirt.
Again, I don't know if this is like overkill on the shirts or whatever.
But like, you know, I mean, I have a care pack with my subscribers
where I I just mail people a a USB stick full of exclusive content
and like an art card with a poem written on the back.
And I sell that for $40.
I make 20 of them.
It's pretty good.
Yeah, we should do something like that for the PCP and just send them weird
PCP related shit every month.
It would probably go over pretty well.
Yeah, let us know what you think about that idea in the comments.
If you would pay for something like that, how much would you pay?
What kind of stuff would you want?
Let us know. Yeah.
Between all of us, we could probably get a lot more varied content
out the door with something like that, as opposed to just one of us.
So yeah, join join the Patreon.
Five dollars get you access to the bonus episodes.
The newest bonus episode is a mage and Nate exclusive bonus podcast
because everybody else was asleep or not aware it was happening.
You guys played Minecraft, if I understand correctly.
Yeah, we played Minecraft on a Pixelmon server,
meaning there were like Pokemon in the background
while we were just doing Minecraft stuff.
That that is the most mage core episode concept I've ever heard of.
So if you want to check that out, five dollars a month.
So it's all it takes bonus episodes.
That's what episode 21, I think, or more.
There are over 20 bonus episodes.
Twenty eight, twenty eight.
We're almost 30.
What are you waiting for?
Give us your money now.
If you enjoyed the dulcet tones of Tom's voice on this episode,
you should also go over to I am Games,
which is an active channel still because Tom is still making gaming videos over there.
Yeah, every week script.
He just sent me for I don't know if this will be out by the time of this podcast
before like an eight page script about Dark Souls healing systems
that was blisteringly in depth.
So if you want to hear Tom go full souls fanboy after years of shitting on it,
subscribe to I am Games and do it.
It's good. Tom's Twitter so you can support his actual art.
Please do play my game.
Public demo on new grounds, so patrons get access to beta.
It is the only morally
acceptable thing to do considering the state that Tom is in.
You your only your only option is to give this man
support me for the quality of my art, not the lack of quality of my spine.
God damn it.
But do you want if Tom dies,
do you want it on his conscious that you didn't help to fund him to have back surgeries?
Fund my back surgery, donates my Patreon today.
Yeah, mage, anything you want to shill before we close out?
As ever, never, nothing matter.
Purple's still good.
Yeah, purple love, I guess.
Purple, purple good.
That's it, everybody.
Maybe one day, maybe one day I'll have something, but not today.
When your secret project's done, hopefully you'll probably.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
When my secret project is done, I'm going to I'm going to show it off like like my child's drawing.
All right, sick.
Well, until the secret project revealed, you can all ruminate on its contents
and give us money and follow us on Twitter at tbcrasnators.
I think we still use that occasionally when we feel like it.
Follow all of us on our Twitter, because we're all over there all the time.
And yeah, have a good day.
Like a billion pictures of all of them at BrodyCon.
Yeah, all the non fucking stop.
Rapid fire.
Munchies channel for more.
Munchie and Gibbons channel, I think, have been posting videos from BrodyCon
if you want to see all that shit, too.
Bye.
Goodbye.
Yeah, I'm supposed to be working right now.
I'm supposed to be working right now, but I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
Why did come jerking?
Myself, I'm sucking.
I am an asshole.
I am a stupid.
I've got a deadline.
Don't want to do it.
Delicious.
I eat when people have like this ASMR when they're eating food.
It's like the worst ASMR.
Stop.
What do you want me to say?
I should.
Stop.
No.