This program contains dramatic reenactments and material that may be disturbing to some audience members.
Viewer discretion is advised.
When two cousins set sail across the Sea of Cortez, they expect the weather to be blue skies and fair winds all the way.
But when an unexpected storm blows in off the mountains, their boat is torn apart and they're dumped in shark infested waters.
Oh my God! Oh my God!
There are only refugees in uninhabited islands where there is no food, no water, and no shelter from the burning sun.
All they have left is the will to survive and the hope that that will be enough on I Shouldn't Be Alive.
Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
We're back again to talk about things.
Woo! Yeah!
I like things.
I was about to say that.
I stole his thunder.
Donnie, how could you betray me like that, Donnie?
Donnie, how could you get your own catchphrase wrong?
I like your own brother, the spicy key chain, Donnie.
I am the best guy ever, as you know.
The coolest cat in the cabbage patch.
That's me. That's my new catchphrase.
And I'm joined today by my good buddies, Hippocrite is here.
Hello.
As is Ben Saint.
Oh.
Distinctly not my buddy, you'll notice.
And my good friend, Jessicaleys.
Endless Jessicaleys.
Jessicaleys, named after my testicles.
You named after your own testicle.
The testicle is cometh before the name.
And Tom Oliver.
Yeah, I do.
All right, buddy.
Okay, so here's our topic. Let's not fuck around.
Our topic was a suggestion by this guy on Twitter.
He goes by at the Hippocrite.
Here's a suggestion.
At TP Crastinators, I am dying help.
A podcast on when you almost died.
So that's a good question.
Yes, we got to get that guy on here sometime.
We probably should.
Hey, are we going to get accused of what's the word, nepotism?
Is this not cool to take questions from people that you may or may not know?
Ah, fuck it. Fuck you, Twitter.
Nobody knows who actually runs the Hippocrite Twitter.
It wasn't me, that's for sure.
And by the way, peeps, make sure that you send us questions
about topic suggestions throughout the week.
But especially on Saturdays when we record these things
at TP Crastinators.
So go do that because we always need more.
Anyway, we're out of topics.
I mean, we're all washed up.
We're on our last legs here.
You guys got to step up or this shit.
We're going to hit the ground real hard.
We're coming in for a real rough landing.
You know Denzel Washington and that movie Flight
where he has to flip the plane and they do all this crazy shit
and then there was a big, there was a big trial about like malpractice
as a pilot and I don't want to, I don't want to lose my kids, okay?
I don't want to lose my seven sexy daughters.
So please send me your suggestions TP Crastinators.
That's what I need to do.
Hippo, I'm feeling like you might have some suggestions
for times that you were almost dying.
Yeah, I'm right now, I'm in the moment of death.
I'm dying currently on the stream, on live because
I don't know what I have and it's the weekend so I can't go to the doctors
and it's something about my throat.
Is that how that works?
Well, I don't know, maybe.
Maybe they just, they probably go home.
I just assumed I can't access the medical guy.
That can't be right, right?
I mean, I'm sure hospitals are open, right, because they're always open.
Yeah, hospitals are always open.
But like the doctors are only on...
Doctors appointment, checkup or whatever.
That immediately strikes me as fully retarded, but yeah.
I'm probably wrong, but anyway.
I have been having trouble breathing and for the last few days
I've been trying all sorts of things to try and stop it from making me not sleep
and cough all night and I don't like it.
So the problem is like your throat is like constricting?
What I thought it was was that my room was too dusty so I cleaned my room for a whole day
and then I went to bed and I was like all night so I was like, no, that's not it.
So it's like, maybe it's a cold.
So today I woke up really late because I couldn't sleep.
I woke up at 6 p.m. and I put like this weird, like I don't know what it's called, Vicks Vapor Rub.
Yeah, yeah.
And you put that in a bowl of hot water and you put your head over it with a towel
and you just breathe that in for like an hour.
So you don't actually involve rubbing on your body anywhere?
Vicks Vapor Rub?
I thought you were supposed to rub it on your chest
and then let the vapors rise up from the chest?
That's how you do it for like putting it at sleep time.
But you can, like it's more intense to just put a bowl of hot water and drink that up
or sniff that up.
How's that working out?
It didn't do shit so it's obviously not like something in my throat.
It is my throat itself has decided to close and I don't know how to do anything about it.
Okay, I've got a suggestion.
Oh God, I've got a suggestion.
So you basically, you need to widen up that passageway.
I have a tool, a cylindrical tool.
I have a cylindrical tool.
No, Nate.
That's pretty long.
Nate?
I think we can widen that thing up.
Nate, that's enough.
Get that in there.
That's enough.
You're gay now, Kim.
You're gay now.
I got you.
I got him.
I tried to stop him.
You know, I also, when I've been out for runs over the last, I don't know, like six months
or whatever, very occasionally I will get a thing where I just like my lungs don't seem
to be absorbing the oxygen I'm breathing.
And I have to do these big like, I have to like force my lungs to expand and contract.
It's really weird.
I wonder if it's the same thing that you're having right now.
I don't, I don't know what caused it.
I'm afraid I might have asthma.
Cause my dad has asthma.
I'm afraid I might have asthma cause I don't want to be a nerd.
Yeah.
I don't want to carry one of those little things go, and be, you know, the guy who gets beat up on,
and stand by me.
I already have glasses.
I'm halfway there.
I don't want to, I don't want to do that.
You need some headgear too.
Hey, did you guys know that I wore a headgear all of like elementary school for one full year?
I was just thinking, just the other day I was thinking about the fact that I completely forgot that you wore headgear for a while.
It's like the fun.
I opted in.
And you kept hitting yourself.
It's hilarious.
No.
Okay.
So this was, this was purely a teeth straightening thing.
And I was offered a choice to either wear headgear at night for like two years, or just wear it all the time for one year.
And I'd be done sooner.
And I just, I didn't even register any negative consequences of wearing it, you know, for a whole fucking year in school.
Of course I'll wear a weird apparatus on my head at all times.
I can't believe I did it, but I fucking wore that thing an entire year straight.
It's obviously worked, because you don't have crooked fucking teeth like did you?
That's true.
Did you get some headgear?
Shout out to Digi's teeth.
I had, I had some weird orthodontia.
I had braces.
Did you get the palette expander?
Yeah, yeah.
I had braces for a while, but before that I had the palette expander, which is a thing that...
Orthodontia sounds like, like the realm where dentists come from.
I'm sure it is.
It goes on your teeth and it like, it like attaches to your top teeth.
And there's like, it's like a flat thing in the middle, but there's a gap in it.
And there's a little twisty thing.
And you have a little key and you jam this little key up into your roof of your mouth in this apparatus.
And you twist it like a couple of times and it gradually expands your fucking jaw.
And you do that for a while.
I had that.
And I also had another thing where like, it was these like metal things where like bonded to my teeth.
And on the top row were these rods, these metal rods.
And on the bottom row were these metal tubes and the rods slotted into the tubes.
And it was intended so that my jaw would open and close in like a straight line instead of like a curvy line.
And the thing about that is as I got older, I eventually became able to open my mouth so wide
that I could unhing, that I could remove the tube, the rods from the tubes.
And then I could have, and then I would have these four weird little like, these weird little like straight metal dealy things
that I could pop out of my mouth and like wiggle around like a, like a, like a, like a, like a beep.
Like a metal vampire man.
Like a pencil, like a bug mouth pincer.
But then I would open up again and I would jam them back in because, you know, I wanted to keep my orthodontia working properly.
That would take them out for fun.
Anyway, that was weird.
On the topic of times I almost died, the orthodontist is a very relevant one.
Wait a minute.
Man, it's fucked up the stuff we do to our fucking jaw and skull.
I mean, it makes sense.
Like you get good results and all.
It's because our bodies suck.
Yeah.
Your bodies don't look right on their own.
It's just crazy.
It's weird because I've never heard of, you know, I mean, stuff like that being done in England.
Like the most you would get is braces.
Well, the whole, the whole T thing in England is a big meme, right?
Sometimes buzzer nature just needs a little help.
I think what it's, what the difference is, is that Americans don't like having fucked up teeth, even if it's healthy.
They just want it to be a certain shape.
We're just insanely superficial over here.
It's definitely a superficiality.
In America, you're expected to have nice teeth.
I know I'm superficial as fuck.
Like I'm just lucky that my teeth and jaw are just sort of normal.
So there's no problems there really.
Yeah, you could be a digi.
Oh boy.
I actually was supposed to get braces and shit from my teeth and I didn't because we couldn't afford it.
My dentist or whoever, I remember as a kid was like, if you don't do this, when you're old, you're, because I have like a really bad overbite.
You're like, your overbite is going to get so bad.
Your bottom teeth are going to start digging into the gums of your top teeth and all your top teeth are just going to fall out.
What the fuck?
Did, did that happen?
Holy shit, that's exaggeration.
So I've never, I've never.
It did?
Wait, it did?
Well, it had, I haven't been asked if that really happened.
It hasn't happened yet, but I don't know how, how, how far into the future he was talking about.
Times ticking.
So I'll definitely, I'll update it on that because like, I never had wisdom teeth removed.
I never had braces.
Never had any of that shit.
So I'm out.
Yeah, you can still get it done when you're older, I think.
So it's not like the end of the world or anything.
Yeah.
But they have like the like Invisalign things now.
If you want to get braces, but nobody knows.
I do, I do have, I do have in, in Boy Scouts when I was like in high school or middle school, I did have a bike accident that broke my two front teeth.
Oh yeah.
I remember that.
So now like half of, well half of one of my front teeth and a little part of the other is like, you know, it's like fake tooth and like it's fine.
It looks fine, except I guess it's just, I've had it long enough that like the edges just kind of like the edge of the fake part is kind of starting to get a little dingy looking and it really, it really pisses me off.
It really pisses me off every time I look at it.
The whole thing about like our vanity in regards to our teeth and making them like white enough, like I've been drinking more coffee recently and I have been getting extremely concerned.
If my teeth will turn darker, get stained because I have always been very proud of my teeth and I've gotten a lot of compliments on my smile and my teeth over the years and it's entirely a vanity thing.
But I would be very upset if my teeth were to diminish in quality.
I don't know man.
I wonder.
Yeah, I don't know.
I worry about that too.
It's all kind of pointless.
I don't drink a lot of coffee, but I do drink a lot of just like Mio.
Yeah.
I drink a lot of Mio energy.
You'll have rainbow colored teeth.
Oh, beautiful, beautiful.
I guess that's why my teeth aren't fucked up because I don't drink soda ever.
But you drink tea.
Tea's not.
Tea's got to be better than soda.
Tea's not that dark.
Tea's definitely not that bad for you at all.
I mean like in terms of like teeth rotting because like, I mean they might stay brown with teas, stain, I don't know.
Yeah, that's all I meant.
Soda will make them disintegrate.
Soda's bad.
Yeah, that's what they say.
Soda's bad in every way and know what you drink it.
I bought a water today and I got a soda instead.
Well, the President of Nintendo RIP.
Dumped it in the trash because it is trash.
Wait, what?
What about Nintendo?
You said you got a water.
The President of Nintendo RIP.
He did, nigga.
He did.
He is.
Wait a minute.
Dig up his grave, you monster.
I did.
I kissed that.
Okay.
This has nothing to do with death dying times and what?
The death we were referring to.
Nate, we actually said what the topic is.
I feel like you said the topic before but we never actually introduced what the topic is.
Okay, I read the question but the topic is in between.
That's right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Times when you almost died or whatever.
With Hippo talking about how he's dying right now and then we just tangent into dental incidents.
I do have another time that I actually almost died.
Please.
Okay, cool.
I mean, maybe I was panicking at the time and I'm overreacting about what happened.
But there was a time when I was just out on a trek on a hike just around the countryside with family.
And I had a cold at the time and it was kind of cold outside but whatever.
But there was this moment where I had so much mucus in my throat that I could not sneeze it out.
I could not cough it up and it completely blocked my air passages and I fell over.
Oh, God.
And I just was like, I was trying as hard as I could to gasp for air and it wouldn't happen.
Oh, my God.
And I nearly fainted and it was the scariest moment ever.
That reminds me.
There is, okay, one of the worst things I've ever read is there's a scene in Infinite Jess
where a burglar, okay, a guy, like this rich diplomat, he was going to take a family vacation that day
but he was sick, right?
He had a cold.
So his family left and he stayed home because he was sick.
And a burglar or two burglars knew that his family was taking a vacation and they were going to break in that day.
But they break in and find that he's still there, sick.
So they're like, oh, shit, what do we do?
So they tie him up and they gag him.
Oh, no.
And the thing is, he's got a stuffy nose and like, yeah.
This has been my nightmare, my entire fucking life.
Literally this.
It takes him like an entire day to die.
Oh, God, no.
No.
You don't know how long I've had this exact thought.
Like, what if I, guys, I've got a stuffy nose.
They're like, well, just shut up and nobody cares.
What if I get kidnapped right now?
I've had the fear of someone literally putting duct tape on my mouth has been my exact fear my entire life.
No.
Why kidnapping specifically?
Because I understand.
He spends like the entire day like fucking snorting and blowing his nose and trying to keep the nasal passages clear.
Trying to breathe.
And he like sort of manages it for a while.
But like he can't.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's really bad.
Jesus, Jesus, you fucked up, dude.
You should not have fucked with our lungs that way.
Why'd you make me this way, Jesus?
I hate you.
Fuck you, dude.
Fuck you.
Yeah, it's pretty bad.
It's pretty fucking bad.
It's a similar like sort of fear of just being in a place where you can't call for help.
Yeah.
Like, you know, it's something like, you know, the fear of like falling asleep in the bath and just drowning because nobody knows.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
Or you fall over in the shower.
It's like a mundane sort of sort of way to die that could happen at any moment if you're just not able to move.
Yeah, I'm with you.
But for me, it's like even worse if like if you're just like in a crowd, but like I don't know for whatever reason, if you like choke on your own snot or maybe even like a piece of food.
Like if nobody knows and they're around or even if they do know, but like it's you like fighting against your own body and your own biology and like just no one can like fix you immediately.
Like they have to rush you to the hospital to if they can like so you can try to reach down and pull it out or whatever.
Yeah.
But just like that fear of like me being powerless against my own body, I find particularly terrifying, especially for like the suffocation thing.
Oh, God, no.
Oh, that's the worst.
This is going to be an awkward podcast.
I'm thinking about suffocating now and I've really got, I've really got the fucking, the fucking, the howling.
I've got the goose pimples back.
The howling fantasies.
Everybody take a deep breath.
David Foster Wallace would say.
This, this, this entire topic is why I'm such a huge advocate of transhumanism.
We need to fucking get robot bodies, fix all this shit.
This is the worst.
The best thing about being a robot.
Sure would be neat.
The coolest thing about robots and robotics is that I mean, if you're a cyborg, you can probably like turn yourself off and then turn yourself on again.
So if you repairs will be easier.
I can already turn myself on.
Thank you very much.
Oh, sure.
You can make yourself unconscious for sure.
Whoa.
Yeah, it just takes this rock to my head and I'm out.
It's great.
But, um, but like also like little robot, like I always like the idea that we're like advancing in like micro technology with robots and stuff and tiny little things.
Cause like in the future, you won't have to have surgery or anything.
If there's something inside you that's going wrong, you can just send a little robot guy in there to dig it out with a spade, you know.
To dig it out with a spade.
Little lasers or little drills, like just send them in there.
I just, I just, I want there to be artificial organs, artificial, just like body parts that can easily be swapped out that don't cost like dig.
It's just like, oh, you're having a heart attack.
Well, let's just put a new heart in there.
I guess that one's fucked up, you know, and just easily fix all that shit.
And then I want like fucking nano machines to fucking like augment your, your organs and stuff that can like repair damaged cells.
And, and, and you can just live forever.
And, and, and aging is just a different sort of thing.
I mean, I'm a little more concerned about the technology for micro machines that, you know, enable dick extension and retraction on command.
They just build cells, you know, like I assume that's what everyone was thinking about.
The ultimate technology.
No, in the future, in the future, you're not going to need to worry about your dick size because you're going to have your robot wife who's perfect in every way.
And she doesn't care how big your dick is.
It's always the perfect fit because she's designed.
And, and plus, once we get the full ghost on the shelf thing, you can just swap into a body with as big a dick you want or whatever.
Listen, listen asshole, listen asshole.
I don't want, I don't want a big dick for her sake.
I want a big dick for my sake.
I want a big dick because I enjoy it.
I enjoy it.
Because you deserve it, Ben, because you deserve it.
You think this is for them?
You think I do, you think I do this for them?
You think I jelk every day?
You think I jelk to satisfy a woman?
You think these kegels are for her dog?
Who satisfies me?
This is, this is, this is what I need to feel, to feel like a man.
And god damn it I do.
Ben said gesturing to his physique, just brushing his body.
Yeah, you think all this is for Ben?
All this?
Look at these curves dog.
Hippo, did you have any other death defying incidents that you wanted to bring up?
Or Shelly Moomunda, somebody else?
I can't think of any. There's been, yeah.
If you think about it, you can always bring them up.
Yeah, I'll just, I was gonna mention, Jess, you've been like having a bit of medical stuff.
Also, you're homeless and everything sucks.
Oh yeah, I have AIDS.
I thought everyone knew, I thought everyone, you saw what happened with me and Action Giraffe at Radcon 2.
You saw the AIDS get transmitted through the docking station into my brain.
That's what Action Giraffe does.
Made of AIDS. I'm not a human being anymore.
As Action Giraffe was fucking your ear hole, there was a sudden time stop.
There was like a freeze frame and then the AIDS crawled out and went inside like a yerk, like a yerk for animals.
I'm not really like a human anymore.
And Resident Evil Zero, how the zombies are made out of leeches.
I'm like a bunch of AIDS leeches, like morphing and swapping around in the form of an AIDS-y human.
Particularly AIDS-y human, more so than any other of my ilk.
I have a time, I wasn't actually nearly dying, but I thought I was and it was bullshit.
This was like, I don't know, I think I had allergies or something. This was in my teen years, Nate.
And I remember on this particular Sunday, we were going to church.
And I don't think you were there, I don't know why, whatever.
Because I'm a goddamn pizza-faced atheist.
I don't know, you were somewhere, it doesn't matter, you're not relevant to the story.
The story is, yeah I know, fuck you.
The story is that I had allergies or something and I took a Benadryl, right?
Like my mom or dad gave me a Benadryl and I was like, I still feel kind of bad.
So I took like another one, like I took two Benadryls and I felt weird, like I started to feel tingly.
And I was like, oh, you know, dad, I took two Benadryls and now I-
Just kill me dad, please.
I was like dad, I took two Benadryls because the first one didn't really work and now I feel weird.
And dad was like, oh god, Ben, you took two Benadryls, you could die.
You could die, Ben.
Oh my god.
He said like, if you do that, you could die.
And I was like, oh god, should we go to the hospital?
Dad, and he was like, nah.
What the fuck, dad?
You handled this situation, you're escalating it as hard as you possibly could.
And you should be like, ah, don't worry about it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, he told me that what I had done could kill me.
And then when I was like, should we do something?
He was like, no, it's fine.
And then we went to church and I sat there in the fucking pew feeling weird,
feeling kind of tingly and thinking I was gonna die.
Just feeling closer to God than you ever have before, yeah.
Put that fear of God in me for sure.
He would never strike me down in his own house, would he?
Oh my god.
You know, dad is like the worst, he assumes the worst in every situation.
You know dad, he's very melodramatic.
At least, if you really thought that.
Yeah, that's the thing, if he really thought that was the case,
he would have taken to the hospital.
So clearly, I don't know.
He clearly didn't actually think I was in danger, but like, he still said it.
He said it and then did not.
The seed was planted at that point.
He did not walk the statement back at any point.
What a legend, dad.
I can imagine he just wanted you to freak out so he could laugh.
Maybe he did, maybe he just wanted to scare me into not take doubling up on doses.
But you know, I don't feel like there was any premeditated strategy going on here.
Who can predict the inner workings of a dad?
It's impossible.
Well, that's interesting.
Well, since we're on you, you got any others?
Mmm, yeah.
I was at home jerking off.
Yeah, fuck yeah.
What else you got for us, Ben, any other times?
Oh, again?
Well, yeah, I actually do have a second one.
I was going to save it, but yeah.
We could go around if you want, we could do a round robin or whatever.
All right, well, I'll tell you the whole story,
because there's a bit more to it than just the death.
So in college, right, like me and my girlfriend had some friends
that had been going to the same school, but then they transferred to another school.
This was another couple.
One of them transferred to another school, they went together,
and we were going to go visit them.
So we rented a car and we drove to New York,
and it was like a several, like four or five hour drive or something.
And I remember on the way there, like I accidentally ran a red light.
And the girlfriend was like, you know, she was really mad.
Like she was really angry that I had like fucked up
and kind of like done this weird thing in this red light.
And like, yeah, it was dangerous and I fucked up and it was bad.
But she was very upset at my driving.
So then on the way back, she drove.
And she was in the right lane,
and there was an 18-wheeler in the middle lane, right, like next to us.
She got spooked being like sandwiched between this 18-wheeler
and the edge of the road.
This is why women shouldn't be able to drive.
Can't handle it, can't handle it.
This is just my fucking data.
I'm not saying anything, but...
This is just one data point.
And she, you know, hit the gas,
she tried to pull out ahead of the 18-wheeler
and then changed lanes to get in front of it.
She changed lanes too early and fucking...
Fucking just rammed into the thing.
Yes.
And this fucking 18-wheeler, like, crunched into the fucking car.
All of the windows exploded.
What?
Yeah, there was...
Holy shit.
The windows exploded.
She was like screaming, she was like,
Ben, Ben, and I was like, oh god, oh god.
And Ben was like, oh, this is why I told you
I shouldn't have let a man drive.
No, I think I like fucking...
I think I like held her hand or something,
because we were like...
Because it was long.
This was an extended sequence of the windows exploded
and then the car was dragged.
Like, yeah, the car was...
We fucking were attached to the front of this truck now
and the truck had to come to a stop
and we were like sideways.
We were dragged the whole way as this...
as this truck fucking came to a slow stop.
And then, you know, it slowed down
and we were like, oh god, we're still alive.
And like, the windows were everywhere.
There was glass in my pockets
that I found the next day
because it had gotten into my fucking pockets.
And...
Yeah.
They're decaying that Ben, in fact, did not change his clothes
at that point or any other time.
It was wearing a jacket.
Yeah, all right, all right.
And whatever.
And, you know, we called fucking AT...
What's the word?
AAA, AAA.
Yeah, we called AAA and fucking they came
and it was terrible.
And I remember that I had a thermodynamics test
the next day that I really needed to study for,
but because this shitty thing happened,
I did not get home in time to fucking get my textbooks
and study this shit I needed to study.
Did you get an extension on the exam or anything?
No, I just didn't feel like it.
I was just like, fuck it, whatever.
I'll take the test anyway and I didn't do great,
but who cares.
Fair enough, fair enough.
Yeah, everyone was like...
Oh boy.
The teachers the next day were like,
I heard you were in a bad car accident.
And I was like, yeah, that was, it's fine.
I'm just saying women might not be the best drivers around.
That's all I'm saying.
Ben was an advocate from that point on.
In this case, she didn't really hit it out of the park.
Well, Ben, I was curious though,
what your conversation was like immediately after this accident.
What, you know...
I mean, I don't know.
I think we were both just like really happy to be alive.
You know, that's fair.
That's fair.
And also like, you know, just bummed that it had happened
and that we now had to deal with the fall.
It was mostly her, because it was like...
No, it was her car.
It was her car that she had done this to.
So it was like mostly her.
She had to deal with the fall out of fucking messing up her car.
So that was sad.
Man, that's a crazy story.
It was a real fucking scary, almost sad.
We both did.
Man, all right.
Well, cool.
Good story, Ben.
Got any more? Got any others?
I think that I just...
Was that the topper?
That's the...
It might be.
It might have been so far.
I don't think I have anything in the topper.
Another successful PCP podcast.
We did it.
No, we're not...
28 minutes.
No, we've reached the top
and now we have to plunge back into the ground
to go below the bottom point.
I think we can talk about,
unless anyone has another like actual almost died story.
I mean, I'm constantly...
Plunge into the metaphorical.
Like when you...
When you died inside.
Well, wait a minute.
That's every day of my fucking life, dude.
We can get to that.
That's not even worth mentioning at this point.
It's just a given for every day.
I died once.
I was run over by a car once.
Yeah?
Hang on.
When people say they got run over,
a lot of the time I find that the actual event
is that a car hit them
and they rolled over the top.
Oh, no.
That's not what I mean.
I mean, I was literally under the tires
being ran over by a fucking jeep.
Fuck.
Is this why you love Jeep Wrangler so much?
Do you have Stockholm Center for Jeeps?
Is that what's going on?
Is that it, Jesse?
It's okay.
You can admit this problem.
Okay.
So what happened?
What happened?
My stupid idiot friend back in high school named Ryan Gentry,
who I'll say his fucking name.
I don't care because we all hated him anyways.
We kicked him out of the group
shortly after this.
But we were driving.
We were in the drive.
We were about to pull out.
And I like wasn't in the car yet.
And I was like getting my seatbelt on.
And he like fucking zoomed out.
And I'm like, slow down.
I'm not in the car.
I'm out the door.
And I was like, hey, not the door.
And I like got wrapped up in my seatbelt.
And I couldn't.
Oh, no.
I couldn't move myself.
So like, I just like plummeted out of the car.
And like, he kept going.
And like, he didn't have to keep going.
He wasn't going that fast.
He could have stopped.
He knew I was down there.
But he just kept going.
And he ran right over like right up and over my fucking
my ankle.
And I was like tied up in a seat belt.
And you ran over my leg.
And I'm like, well, you're not my friend anymore.
What happened to your leg?
It just hurt a bit.
I mean, I did.
Did you break anything?
I didn't have to go to the hospital or anything.
But he's still though.
It was a Jeep Wrangler and not a fucking.
I don't know.
It wasn't a Jeep Wrangler.
You invented that part of the story.
I know.
I like that better.
That's the story now.
A Jeep Wrangler showed me mercy.
And now I'm indebted.
Jesse told me the story about how Colt Corona ran over
with a Jeep Wrangler.
Colt Corona tried to save him.
It was actually the K-Fib commander driving the dreaded
mobile on a mission to hurt me.
I like to think that it's your friend has his face
and as he was driving this thing, he pulls off the face mask
and underneath is that sheer metal plate
of the K-Fib commander under the face.
He's wearing the mask under his human face.
Give a man a mask and he'll show you his true face,
Oscar Wilde, K-Fib commander.
AKA the K-Fib commander.
As he left me there in the ditch
with my broken shattered ankle
and zoomed off into the night, I could hear him laughing.
Mustard on my burger.
That phrase has haunted you as nightmares ever since.
Fantastic.
Well, I've got one that isn't as dramatic as that,
but it was a very trippy experience.
So I was kind of tripping.
So there's not much to it.
Not a full-over trip.
No, I did not trip or fall off a cliff in this case.
Well, I mean, a quick one was I went skydiving once
and there was nothing crazy about it.
I didn't think I was going to die intellectually,
but the experience was very much of dying inside
and being reborn as the hero of mankind
that I knew it would become one day.
So I'd highly recommend everyone go skydiving.
It was super fun.
But the other time was, so I just had a fever.
Nothing crazy was going on.
I just had a fever one time when I was in fourth grade.
But what was interesting were the side effects of this fever.
Later on, I would find out that I had a temperature at the time
and I went to the hospital at some point.
My brain temperature was around, or my body temperature was 165.
168.5, I want to say.
Yeah, something like that.
Are you sure it's not 106?
It was really hot.
Not 106?
Sorry, I think that was it.
165.
Well, I don't remember the exact number there.
I remember it being 106.
I thought it was like 126.1.
Okay, whatever's the reasonable number there,
whatever's the reasonable one, that's what it was.
But it was like 6.5 at the end.
Like standard human is like 98.
Yes, okay.
All right, I think you're right.
I think you're right here.
And the thing is brain death begins to occur at 106.8.
So I was 0.3 away from starting to die.
So it was pretty close.
But nothing bad happened to me that I know.
I remember.
After this point, I started to like animate.
It was kind of a weird, you know, I don't know what was going on there.
I remember that day because I, again, because of our dad,
basically told me you were going to die.
Oh my God, what the fuck, dude?
And I was terrified all day at school.
Understandably.
Yeah, because like dad basically said,
like Nate might die.
And I was like, oh God, what the fuck?
Dad, this is not optimal for my studies.
Just don't tell me until he's actually dead.
It really wasn't optimal for my fucking studies.
Didn't do me any goddamn favors.
So what I remember about that day was that,
so at this time, I think I was in like, I don't know,
like first grade I was like really young or something.
And I was really into the Power Rangers.
And the Power Rangers like second movie had come out
and it's the one with like Lord Ooze.
Ivan Ooze.
And they got all the Ivan Ooze.
Yeah, yeah.
All right, all right, my mistake.
The CG in that movie is fucking amazing.
Really?
Yeah.
I have to go watch it again.
And I mean in like the worst way possible.
The CG of like the new zords coming together
to form the new Megazord is the most embarrassing thing.
Like it is so bad.
It's incredible.
That's fantastic.
Fuck you.
Yeah, I want to watch, I'll have to watch it again
because it really left an impression on me due to this story.
So like the point is that like this guy Ivan Ooze
was like he became like the main character of my brain
during this day that I was having this bizarre fever dream.
So like, oh, it was weird.
Like I obtained Ooze powers and got my own,
I got my own Megazord.
But the way these worked was you had to turn it to Ooze
and kind of merge into your Megazord,
sort of like a year merging with the brain
of the person they're possessing in Animorphs,
which I was also into at the time.
What the fuck are you talking about?
I'm talking about my experience of what was happening
during this day where I was almost brain dead.
So this was like a fever dream you were having?
This was a fever dream, yeah.
I see, okay.
I mean, just what was interesting about it
was how like everyone in this fever dream
was like an Ooze man like me
and I formed a whole Ooze civilization of people
and we all had Megazords.
And Ivan Ooze was our king, I believe.
It was nuts.
I experienced being an Ooze man
for a while for that day
and I'd highly recommend it to anyone
who has the opportunity to give it a try.
Being an Ooze man?
Is this a fever dream?
I don't know whether I've had an actual fever dream before.
Is it different from a dream in that you remember it better?
Well, what was different was that I was...
It's just a really crazy dream that comes about
and it was kind of like I was conscious at the time.
So I was conscious of what was going on around me
but it was just really like distorted
and I wasn't like processing information properly.
It was really weird. It was really weird.
I don't know, that's basically it though.
Like Ivan Ooze, I will never forget.
And I wish I could like paint the picture
because I have some very specific imagery
that occurred to me on that day
that I have never forgotten since
and I don't think I ever will forget.
Like there's this one of Ivan Ooze's face
like stretching off the rest of his body
just like towards me and kind of curling around
into this like bizarre, disgusting face.
It stuck with me for like 20 years now
so I don't think it's going anywhere.
It's going to be with me till my dying day.
Well, whatever, yeah.
I'm just saying it was a crazy trippy time.
That's all I'm saying. Really the story isn't that interesting.
I had a crazy dream. That's what happened.
You know, I'll tell you one time,
speaking of...
I mean I assume you were speaking of something, I don't remember.
But I'll tell you some time.
One time.
I died a time.
I'll tell you guys about the time I had appendicitis
when I was in high school
and nobody believed
that I had appendicitis.
Nobody would take me to the hospital.
Oh, Jesse,
with your crazy schemes
with your wildest audience appendicitis.
Oh, come on.
Don't pull my leg.
To make it to the top, but he's kind of in the middle
because he's always getting caught.
God damn it, Jesse.
That's me. So I was laying there,
you know, I was like saying to like my mom
and my grandma, like everyone who was there,
you know, my stomach really hurts.
I think I'm really sick. I think I need to go to the hospital.
My mom at a certain point
just like left the state and like went to
North Carolina during this week
and said, you'll be fine.
So like no one was there to take me anywhere.
Everyone who came in the house
said that I was just, you know, a big fat faker
trying to skip school or whatever.
So I'm laying there.
My fucking, my cousin comes in one day.
My cousin who's this
a woman of
sizeable size
right, a big fat slut.
She's a big fat slut, yeah.
Yeah.
You know, she's like a
like a 250, like a
300 pound lady.
She comes in, she comes in
and she goes, I'm laying on the couch. She goes, oh, you're not sick
and she fucking sits on me.
She sits on my abdomen
where my appendix lives
just like squishing it,
killing me.
So finally, on like
the fourth day,
my uncle Tony came
and he was the only one who believed me
because he's the only one who ever believes me.
So he took me to the hospital
and the doctor just said, yeah
you're like a day away from dying.
Your appendix is going to burst.
We have to put you in surgery right now.
So they put me in surgery
and then I woke up and
they took it out of me
to like a party and I
like
I just like showed up at the party like all my friends were there
and I'm like, hey guys, guess who
just had a surgery and I like looked at my
shirt and I had a little scar and they were like, yeah
you're cool. We're all going to suck your dick.
Oh, the girl said that and they
did and that's how I got well
laid for 100 years. I had sex
with every woman I ever met
and that's the moral of the story.
What a great story.
I love a story with a happy ending.
And Colt Corona was there too
and he even got laid.
Yeah, imagine that.
And you guys hear each other high fives.
Yeah, the K-Fabe Commander
on an Eiffel Tower. The K-Fabe Commander
thought he could poison my appendix to put me down
for the count but it is planned backfired
and it got me and horse boy laid
a thousand times. All these stories
just K-Fabe Commander
and Colt Corona.
I was at the party
having my big fun orgy
with all my friends and K-Fabe Commander
was like watching over it from
he was overlooking it from like a cliff side
going curse you. You've eluded my
vengeance again.
And I was
I was yelling back at him. Fuck you.
Who's that guy in the
WWE? He's like the, he's not the goat guy
but he like thinks that he can take over the world
by like winning the WWE championship. Which guy is that?
Oh, Bray Wyatt. The crazy guy.
Yeah, I was thinking like
instead of, it's like that. The K-Fabe
Commander is like him only it's reversed
where he thinks by like pulling these evil schemes
to like defeat you that will get him
the championship belt. He'll become a wrestling champion.
Yeah, that's his plan. He defeats you.
He becomes champion. Right.
That's his master plan.
He's completely detest from reality.
He doesn't understand anything. He's an idiot.
He's a madman.
He doesn't even know the rules of wrestling.
He's an idiot but it only increases
his evil retard strength.
That's right.
He gets, the stronger he gets.
I'm like
Corona who gets weaker
the more he
the more love fills
Corona's heart the weaker he gets.
He's constantly getting weaker.
Aw.
Isn't that nice? He lives a charmed week life.
So, Tom
you're a man on Death's Door
every day so
what's your story buddy? I am he says matter of fact.
I was going to say
I'm dying inside right now
because I'm at work
Right. Fair.
Oh my god, that sucks.
Okay, we'll come back. We'll be here.
Fair point.
Okay, we'll come back. We'll come back.
We should have had him tell some stories
when he was actually available.
We really fucked up.
That's true.
That is true.
You, you audience
you really screwed the pooch on this one.
At TP Crasinators
send us good questions
that we can answer.
Okay, so why don't I give, you were going to say something.
Let's talk about dying inside in the meantime, right?
Oh yeah, dying inside, well
I mean obviously depression
and all that sad stuff that happens
all over the time, all over the place every day
but I can think of
a very specific moment
where I was at my lowest point ever
and it was before I was a
YouTuber.
I had left school
because it was ended
and then I was like, okay, what do I do?
I want to maybe go to university
but I don't know what I want to do at university
I don't know what I want to do in my life
and so I took a year off
before I
made a decision. Everyone else in my class
had made their decision and was going away
and getting the funny hats
and getting kids and all that
shit and I was like, okay
I'm not sure about doing animation
it seems scary
so I was
all sad and stuff and my parents were like
well, if you're not going to
go to university, you should
get a job or go on the dole
which is the benefits thing
for working
for looking for a job
and so I went
to the thing
and it was really depressing because
they really
it's like a corporate
building with people who hate their job
sitting in a stuffy sort of building
and I have to go in and
stamp the thing and files
and paperwork and all that
they had recently changed the law
when I got this
so usually you would go in
I'm looking for work and then you would write down
a bunch of things, say, proving
links to websites that you were looking for
work, obviously
nobody had any proof, they just said they did
and that's how they got money
but they changed the law
I did that
on unemployment benefits
at one point I got laid off
from a job and I had to pretend
I was looking for real work while I continued
while I got unemployment insurance from that
it was great
it would have been great for me too
except for this law change where it said
while you're looking for work
in addition
to proving that you're looking for work
you have to do a certain amount of hours
of volunteer work
at charity shops
Jesus
so I would have to get up
really early and get on the bus
to this
quite far away place
across the river, I don't know where it was
in the part of time that I didn't understand
or knew
and I think it was because I made a mistake
on the paperwork
they just sent me far away so I had to get up at
like six every morning
like three or four times a week
probably three times a week
to this charity shop
and the people in there were really
no nonsense
nobody liked me, nobody would give me
any sort of
let me get away with anything
you have to work for this amount of time
the first day I got there
it was closed because the owner of the shop
didn't turn up because she was sick
and I didn't get any
hours
for that day because she wasn't there
so I had to go for an extra day and work overtime
and I was doing this for like
two weeks before I decided
that I would rather just walk the streets
and die
and it was this one time
where I was on the bus
you know
even my music in my headphones
just sort of like
and this lady
at the front of the bus
she for some reason
at some point and I didn't notice
because I didn't hear because I had my headphones in
she said alright everyone off
this is going not in service bus
at the moment and I was right at the back
and everyone else got off
and they looked at me and I looked at them
and they thought why aren't you getting off
but they didn't say anything so I was just like
everyone wants to get off at this stop
and then it kept going for a bit
and I realized wait
she's
not stopping at any of these bus stops
she doesn't know that I'm here, what do I do
and then
at one point she glanced behind
she saw that I was at the back of the bus and she said
what the fuck you doing there
she was like one of those you know
real chevy, real sweary, angry
bitches
she said get the fuck off the bus
you can't you just
I told you to get off
I told you to get off I'm like I didn't hear
why is she so mean
because she works in a bus
that's fair
wait
why were you still on the bus past your stop
he didn't hear dog he didn't hear the NS
I didn't hear that the bus had gone
out of service and she was driving to the bus
station to put it away
so did she just drop you off like in the middle of nowhere
yeah she dropped me off in the middle of nowhere
I didn't know where I was
I didn't know how many stops I had to go
and I was like you know what
fuck this and I just started walking
in the direction I assumed was home
I went into a library
I thought I could just stay here all day and then
you know the police would get me
something they'd file a missing persons report
yeah
but I decided I was
going to go on an adventure this was like
this is the coolest thing that happened in the
worst time possible
I was so depressed of life
I thought let's just walk and see if I can
find my way home
up to this point was this the time
lowest of your life when you wanted to die
when you were dumped off this bus
yeah it was like
I thought that's what you were building too
it was the lowest point in my life
but it was the moment that I snapped
and said you know what
fuck going to this stupid thing
I am just going to walk
aimlessly until I can see a bus stop
or a bus you know a bus number
that I recognize I can get on that
and I can eventually find my way home
and it took like six hours
and I finally got home and I was like okay
time to play
video games I guess
and then soon after that
I you know
applied for university college
whatever stuff and I got on
and all that and it was
just a really cool moment where I decided
to go on an adventure and I enjoyed it
because of everything being
terrible
I think we could all do with a little more adventurous moments
like that in our lives
I condone such things
yeah
and then I made a youtube channel
and it was up on up
that was a mistake
alright cool
so it sounds like that actually
got a little bit better at the end
of it so that's
I wanted to end on a higher note because I don't want this
this is like a really dour topic
like oh did you almost die you're dead
and sadness and oh
nobody believed that I was going to
kill myself
it's not a nice topic
you know it's a really depressing thing
I know this has been spoken at various times
but like you know when you're really upset
I did just talk about this a couple times
but like no one around knows
and you're just sitting there
just want the world to burn
and everyone else is acting like there's nothing wrong
oh that's my least favorite position
to be because you can't even say anything
you know you don't want to ruin everyone else's life
with your shit
it's also when you don't realize that you're not
looking sad enough
because you do
and nobody pays attention
you have that moment in your childhood
where you realize
or childhood or teenage life where you're depressed
and you realize that
nobody's going
nobody's looking out for you at the moment
or at any point you just have to make sure
you tell people things
it's sort of like a transition
sort of like you know
your kid your parents are always looking out for you asking you
if you're okay
and if nobody asks you if you're okay you can't say
I'm not okay
and it's like you got to get over that
that moment
and you become a real boy
one day I'll figure it out
one day I'll be a real boy
but until that day
I'll just be the best guy ever
until that day
like, share, subscribe, comment
subscribe
donate to my patreon
patreon.com slash cultcorona
is that real
this cult has got
to heaven
oh my god do you think I would
get more money if I just made a patreon
cultcorona
he's the only one we love anymore
watch it eclipse all of our patrons in one day
I think cultcorona is the only
member of the PCP that is unanimously
like universally
by everyone
for sure, agreed, totally agreed
I mean people would
all like action giraffe but he's just too successful
and it really rubbed some people the wrong way
everybody
everybody hates Jess but they love
cultcorona they have no idea
I taught that horse boy everything
he fucking knows
I don't believe it
he's got a pure soul that you could never touch
jesse you couldn't
you can't teach that
I gave him that soul I imbued it
within him after stealing it from
a thousand babies
you breathe life into him
with a kiss
I went to fucking china and I took
all the dead female baby
souls out of maiden astrea's
swamp pit and I put them into
that horsey body
that horsey baby boy
and I created the perfect
person
the perfect person
the cutest and the strongest
the perfect person cultcorona
with the soul of a thousand
innocent newborn chinese female
babies
not tainted by the patriarchy one
iota, thank god
there's no patriarchy in the
furnace room ladies
everybody come on in
it's a safe space for women
everywhere
women and horse boys
so who else is
a time I forget even what this
fucking subject was like when they wanted to die
was that what it was?
it sort of merged into that
it was times we almost died but there's
only so many moments that you can even say
I was sick once
I mean I don't know if it's like
technically almost dying but I do feel
like living in this room
for six years has dramatically
decreased my life span
quite possible
I feel like I'm generally ten thousand times
less healthy than I was before I moved here
you gotta run away
you gotta escape
I gotta get all my stuff in like a stick
with a little like a
a bindle on a stick
cause you got so many comics
and games
and most of the only things you have
no food
no black dust
just a raft made out of long boxes filled with
comics and I'll sail the seas
on them
as all the comics get wet and ruined
sailing the seas
of the man child marsh
so
I had a time
that I wanted to die just for fun I thought
I'd bring this up just for fun
I thought so there was a time
when
I've said before there was a time when I was
really into the pickup scene
and at one point I made
a critical error
I would go out with my friends sometimes
in Providence
and on this particular occasion
I made the crucial mistake
of telling my friend Doug
that my plan for the day was to
talk to X number of girls
just for my own personal checklist
to get better at it
what Doug did
Doug you fucking traitor
I've never addressed this to him because I'm too embarrassed
but he then went around
telling everyone
hey that guy's got a goal of like
he's trying to talk to a bunch of girls
every girl go talk to him
what are you doing over here
that's fucking helpful
he ruined it
thank god I'm so charismatic
I was able to spin it into a positive
but he should know nonetheless
he eats me up it was the worst thing Doug
has ever done to me in his life
and one day I'll work up the courage to tell
him that that's the case
you can't trust friends man
not with stuff like that
anyway not with stuff like that
so that was probably
the time I was most embarrassed
in my life I think
and would have happily accepted death
yeah
indeed
so
if anybody else doesn't have anything
we can just go to questions before Tom comes back
I got one
there's one time in TF2 where I got headshot
and then Pyro got me with
the fire and I was on fire I was like oh no
I'm gonna die
and then
there's a thing where a scout sometimes
uses a weapon and if he kills a guy
he drops a health pack and he did that in front of me
and I got a health and I live
I almost died
there was this one time
in League of Legends
I don't know who I was playing but I went down to 1 HP
in this big team fight but I didn't die
it was epic
god I fucking hate video games
if you die in the game
you don't die for real
I think that if you die in the game
you should die for real because then
fucking people who play video games will all die
because video games are gay
and they're not art
and they're standing in a crime
what if you read a book and a character dies
absolutely
you definitely should die
let me tell you
let me go on a totally unrelated tangent
that has nothing to do with anything
because I have the power to do that
and I'm gonna abuse it
there's a scene
it's a French movie called
The Rabbi's Cat
and it's animated and it's great
but there's like
a Russian guy
it takes place in Algiers
it's a Muslim city but with a big Jewish population
it's kind of Middle Eastern
isn't that where from Camus is from
who the fuck is clopping
I think Tom is walking around
stop it
you damned innocent boy
you don't know what sin you're committing
okay well anyway
so the main character is this Rabbi
and there's this Russian
adventurer guy
and he's there in the city
on some shitty quest
and they're talking with
his Rabbi teacher
and this kind of like fucking
sort of like Libertine Russian guy
and the Russian guy is like ah you
old man in your religion
I care about, I don't care about
God or any of that bullshit
all I care about is like
adventure, women
and literature
yeah
and the Rabbi is like
man those are all things for young men
and I was like oh my god
even literature
especially literature
he threw, he basically
I mean if literature is for young men
then all art is for young men
as far as I'm concerned the guy completely
threw all artistic endeavor under the
fucking bus and you know what
I was like oh my god maybe he's right
in fact to this day
to this day I'm not convinced that he wasn't right
that literature and by extension
all art is just kid shit and we're all
just fucking fooling ourselves
that's fascinating
while you're young and you have the information
and now you don't need anymore because you've got all of it
who was this guy?
I didn't listen to the first half of the story
but now I'm intrigued
it was a character in a movie called the Rabbi's Cad
you know what
and he was like this fast living
kind of like nasty
amoral Libertine Russian dude
well I can see
his point that art is all worthless
oh no no it was the Rabbi
the Rabbi said that art is for
young men
I think I kind of agree with that
I agree
I was compelled
from that guy's perspective
I think this is where he's coming from
he's concerned about his community
and the people he knows in his life
and his relationship with God
is what's important to him
right so from that perspective
I totally get it
I'm very utilitarian
about my
usage of art
I think that art that doesn't
do anything useful is basically garbage
but if there's art with a good message
or is trying to convey something valuable
to the people intellectually
I see a value in it there
but it's just like a tool
like anything else for
the betterment of humanity
I don't even think God could do that
I think just maybe
doing things with your community
or talking to people
hey I'm a cool Rabbi in my neighborhood
what's up peeps
that might just be a better way to spend your time
I don't know
this guy doesn't see any practical value in art
and you know what he's fucking right
man this is a big left turn
this is a big left turn of a topic
but I really like it it's real cool
I don't know he's right
I think we can all agree art has no value
utilitarian value I suppose
you know what value
is there besides utilitarian?
well all value
well I'll tell you
there's no such thing as inherent value
I've never
I've never regretted
a moment spent with friends
or loved ones
whereas I have regretted
everything artistic I've ever done in my life
and everything that's come from it
in spite of everything I just said
I have never regretted
any time that I spent making anything
but I regret so much of the time
I spent hanging out with friends
making is different from consuming
I feel a little bit like Ben
I don't really
there's only a few people I enjoy hanging out with
in real life
and even those people it's not like I want to do it all the time
yeah no
totally
but that's the thing there's a balance to be found
I think
I think it's like
you need
you know
on a more base level
you need human companionship
more than you need to be entertained
because like entertainment
as it is
art as entertainment is just
to make you
escape from reality
because reality is kind of shit
if you have everything
you have food
you have shelter you have family
and friends
you don't really need anything else
but if you have all that
then I think art is a nice little distraction
nice little addition
cherry on top
and to your first point
how much of the art that we consume
especially like anime and stuff
how much of that is just made to simulate human relationships
to take the place of the hole in our lives
that art is just there
a ton
I'm seeing
I'm converting to Judaism as we speak
like when people
I don't know
like if two people
two people are fans of Harry Potter
two people love Harry Potter
what that means is that the two of them
have fucking shared
this simulated experience
of like fucking being
a wizard
and that's what it is
what Harry Potter fucking does
simulate for anyone who reads it
the experience
of being a wizard child
and like
I don't know where I'm fucking going with this
I've got a point to go with that
it's weird and bizarre for me to think of it that way
but it makes sense to think of art is just
all art is just a simulation
it's basically no different
than just putting on a VR headset
it accomplishes the same fucking thing
right and in that way
you might ask the question
why not just with that person
just go have an experience
and then like bam
you've just increased your human connection
but there is a difference there
well hang on
one answer to that is that art can give you experiences
that you can't actually have in real life
that's what I was going to say
and that's fair but
are those experiences more valuable
than ones that you actually can have in real life
that's exactly where I was going to go to
because like everything you experience in that way
is like there are things that you normally wouldn't get in life
and you know what
to some extent I think they could be useful
because what an average human
would experience in their life without VR
we cannot say for sure that it is necessarily
the most optimal way to live your life
in terms of pragmatically and enjoyment wise
so there may indeed be a place
for simulated experiences in real life
but we should find out what that is
we should find that out
I just want to say
the question for me then becomes
for sure art can give you experiences
that you can't have in real life
but is it valuable to have experiences
that are completely removed from reality
we need to find that out I don't know
I don't fucking know
I was going to talk about the fact that he didn't like literature
and it's like not all art
because literature is a story
I'm just going to say that I think
art in terms of like
a painting
it's not the same sort of thing
it's just something that makes you think
you need to look at just to experience
something to make the place
you live in feel more pretty
and decorative
art as like
as an expression
of emotion is sort of different
from art like literature and animation
and film and stuff like that
well you know I mean that's interesting
hang on I just want to say
I think he's got a good fucking point there
fair enough but I was going to say
that I was actually just doing a little bit of reading
I was watching some video I don't read anymore
there was some thing I was consuming
which was talking about
the history of art and it talked about how
like classical art work
specifically it was like paintings and like drawings
and stuff like that was depicted
things that we like understand
as real experiences that could be had
like as human beings like there was
photorealistic pictures of like
fruit which is you can appreciate the skill
with which they crafted it but really it's just
a picture of fruit at the end of the day
like the experience of fruit
hang on I'm making a point
and then there was like
there's also like depictions of great scenes
which capture like a snapshot of human life
but again that's basically like a real
thing or a story that we can understand
and it's not really making any grander
point other than illustrating perhaps the value
of that thing as a human experience
but like modern art and post-modern art
are taking that thing and
turning it on its head and they're exploring the ways
like if that's even a valuable thing
by doing things like like showing the
absurdity of putting like just
a drawing on a pedestal or putting like
you know something like a urinal which is like this famous piece
from the 30s making a urinal
with no special qualities saying
that that's art and having people like comment
on if that has any inherent value
by itself so it kind of raises the question
about if any of this is
valuable to begin with and like how far
does the stack of turtles go before we actually hit
like something that we're like
learning or like achieving through art
you know? You know what I mean?
I think if an art, if a piece of art
can help us to better
improve our social life
or you know
like the base level stuff
the social life and the
stability of your community
and art can help that
then I think it does have value in that way
Personally I really hate
I feel like art is useful in
just making people feel better
and being able to do things like that
Personally I really hate the idea
that like the purpose of art
and the value of art is some like
pragmatic like tangible benefit
that it has on other areas of what this is
What else could there be? What else could there be?
You're talking about like a pragmatic value
So there just is none?
I don't know, well yeah
Art can have social benefit
but like I don't fucking
think, I don't know
like if that's what art was
if the value of art was like
it makes people feel better
it makes people not kill themselves
it makes people's communities better
I would not do it
Kill yourselves fags
Kill yourselves
I was only like presenting that as like
a reason for art to be
cause like personally I think art is just like
if it's fun to make then you know
it's a fun pastime that's good
if it's fun to look at then yeah that's good
that's just nice, why wouldn't you make art
and have art
the act of creating art doesn't have to
necessarily be
what people get out of it like Ben you could make
something just cause like I feel like doing this
but people could get something more pragmatic
or like deep out of it that you've never intended
to do so it really
could really not like
your responsibility but I need to make this
but that's not why I do it
and you know I don't think that's good
personally for me that's not
good enough that's not enough justification
and I would say I do
like that idea but what I would do
is I would scientifically like
study what art form produces
the best tangible results and whatever that is
that's where I would focus like
artistic endeavor if I controlled society
cause I am interested in
progressing and making
cooler shit really I'm talking about making art
to make like the iPhone 8 or you know
to like get to the next level whatever
yeah go to Mars
what you would do is you should make
sci-fi fantasy
so that scientists will be
inspired to make new
I totally agree but yeah
but I don't care about that as much as you seem to
I'm curious
Ben brought up just the concept of
value itself and like what we define
as having value and I think you were saying
that there is no inherent value and it's just what we
there absolutely isn't
I mean it depends on what level you're talking about cause like
at the deepest foundation at some point
yes we have to decide what we think is valuable
such as human life or
or currency or you know all those things
we have basically decided to place
value on so I guess that's your point
that is my point that is ultimately
what Bob boils down to
yeah it depends on whether you think
I mean I guess you know our nature
as humans to procreate and keep
the species going is like
do you believe that that's you know something
that you agree with do you agree with your nature
or do you not care and think everything
is valueless I just think that
at a basic human level
we are more or less
all able to agree
on like the rules of the game you know
what are generally winning moves and what are
generally losing moves and
I think what just once we've
established that then you can build a society
and I don't think it's crazy
to establish rules like
life is generally preferable to death
and like pleasure or
I guess lack of pain is better
than pain you know like
things like that and then from there you can
find out ways to
pursue all that stuff and that's what I base my shit on
here's the point here's
what it all boils down to this is a spoiler
I'm gonna spoil the end
of the rabbi's cat
it's a good movie you should watch it
and don't let me spoil it but I'm gonna spoil it anyway
you see the rabbi
and the Russian guy
and like a fucking
what's the word for like a Muslim priest is it an imam
I think it might be an imam yeah I think that's right
yeah and an imam and
a couple other guys
like some painter guy
they all get together
and they embark on
they embark on a quest
across Africa
to find
the shared
ancestors of all blacks and
Jews
they believe that all blacks
and all Jews share a common ancestor
and they find a tribe
and they find
a tribe like hidden in Africa
of these giant
they kind of like Aztec looking warriors
but like they're so dark
that like they're blue like they're literally blue
and they're just
giant like 10 foot tall dudes
and they're all these big like fucking
like African warriors living in this
in this temple city reading the Torah
and like fucking giving each other
giving each other bar mitzvahs and stuff
and they're there and they're like hey our brethren
but like you know they're so fucking
removed from their culture
that they can't even fucking understand what they're saying
they don't even they're just
even though these guys come trying to forge a connection
they're like oh shit an intruder
we're so fucking we're so removed from culture
that like we can't understand this as anything other than
an intrusion and we must destroy
and so it doesn't really work
they do find the shared ancestor
of all blacks and Jews
but they do not make peaceful content
contact contact
and it's a really good movie
I mean isn't I mean so
there were like people in Saudi Arabia
and then Muhammad was born
and then you know
like people became Islamic
and the rest is history
but I don't think those people were Jews though
I think they were unrelated
I don't think that there actually is a
fucking common I don't fucking
I can't speak to the fucking historical
veracity of anything that I just said
that's just what happens in the movie
that's the end of the story
I don't know
does that have any
no that has absolutely no bearing on anything
I just wanted to say it because it's really funny
I was trying to
figure it out
this is not going anywhere
fair enough
like most of Ben's contributions
adds nothing to the podcast
so thanks again for that Ben
I was thinking about what the rabbi said
what was it, women literature
and something else
yeah it was something women in literature
and that's all he cares about
and he said it was for young men
the rabbi said those are for
young men
they have a purpose
not for me, I'm old
maybe his point, maybe we were totally wrong
and he's more like a guy that when you're young
pursue these things to develop a life
philosophy but when you're old stick with it
or something like that
if a thing's value
eventually goes away
and you're no longer valuable once you're old
was it ever fucking valuable
I mean maybe his point is just that
our brains solidify and we're not as able
to absorb new ideas in an effective way
but this fucking comes back around to that thing
about how I hate to think
I don't believe that art's value is
the fucking pragmatic
the tangible benefits that it has
unlike it makes us function better
I don't accept that
we need to talk to this guy and get his point
I think all value in everything is completely subjective
I disagree
of course
for me
I don't think
art is valuable
because young men read it
and it makes them better people
I don't think that's good enough and I hate that
if that's what this rabbi believed
then I have to say that I'm not satisfied
with it
I think that art just isn't valuable because
people watch it
and people are dumb and they don't deserve it
yeah
people who make it dumb too
I think that art is only worthless
so much in that human beings are worthless
well that's
if human beings are worthless and art is
for human beings
I think that art is
for me
and I think that human beings just exist
to ruin art wherever they go
by not being me and not appreciating it
correctly
but that's not what I was going to say
and I
one day you and me will pull a Columbine
in this whole country Jesse
and then we'll find out
who's the real artist in town
and we'll find out who's the real procrastinator
yeah we'll get around to Columbining America
eventually
we all get together
we all get together for Radcon 10
and we're just like
and you know Digi's just passing out guns
and he's like are you with us
or against us
if we fucking get to 10 Radcons
I will start killing people
not even a joke
somebody's gotta start dying by then
somebody's gotta die
yep
to keep the content fresh somebody has to die each time
we have to
we do like a poem
I definitely think that we're the critical mass
where if we add any new members
an old member needs to leave this fucking group
yeah
hey maybe now's a good time to bring up the fact that
hey guys over
we've been getting messages every once in a while
just saying like hey dude what do I have to do to join the PCP
and like oh I can't wait till I can join
I just want to let everybody know
that we are not looking for new members
and if you're confused by Munchie and
Munky's recent addition
those are guys that we've known for a while
especially Munchie
and like they were always sort of
like there are buddies and they were sort of being introduced
after a while
a terrible mistake has been made somewhere along the line
they accidentally presented the PCP
as like a club
I think giving it a name even
was wrong cause we're
yeah it was a necessary evil though
cause we had to call it something
yeah like I never set out to be part of a club
I don't consider myself part of a group
I just these are
this is a goofy podcast with guys that I
kind of like sometimes
and
I don't know I just see you guys as friends
and we're not a fucking like coalition
aggression to add people
if anymore people get added
I never
saw it that way either but like
the people that listen sometimes
do seem to see it that way and they love it
so I mean
if they choose to interpret it that way
that's fine and I've wanted to work with you guys
for years which is why we started this
so that we could do something and there's no
avoiding being grouped together
when you're making something so
it's a sacrifice I'm willing to
there's no
path to like earning your way in
it's just
the PCP is just who we all
happen to know and like
and you know occasionally maybe want to
fucking work with on stuff
like Mumpy was a guy who we found
and we all instantly liked and then we got
to know him over
like a year and then it was just like
hey let's just bring him in to do stuff
and then it just was perfectly natural
to add him so I mean just you know
if you're a creator and you are making
perfect stuff I don't know maybe
all that is is that
you know people will just think well
I mean they say I'm not allowed in
but if I'm like a really good content creator
maybe they'll just like me and they'll
look I have a problem with that
if you're a pretty girl
if you're a pretty girl and you have sex with me
then you can be my friend
but you still can't be in my fucking
PCP
I wanted to hear where Hippo is going with that
well I mean
people are going to like assume they can
like if they make good enough content
they can get in the group and that's
the thing is
it's not like we're saying
no one will ever be our friend
because that's not true we will make friends
eventually with other people who are cool
it's just that this particular group
it's not really
like it's not really something
you can join and just suddenly be in the chat
we'll make friends
we'll make friends and make connections
and be in like other little groups
but it's just this is sort of like full
we're just getting a lot
of prepositions lately
from people that we then have to
spurn and break their hearts
it's like being a single white woman
guys are coming after me sniffing around my cooter
I just want to focus on my career
I just want to be a lawyer
in the big city
in the big city and make it on your own
it's like being the only femme boy
in the house dance
everyone wants your attention
and you can't service everybody
who comes knocking at your cell door
there's only enough booty for one man at a time
that's right
so
stop asking that question
that's the fucking point fuck off
shut up
shut up and fuck off
but we love you anyway
we do
so should we swing back
do you have time to tell us your stories now dawg
I mean I can
I feel like we've gone off the
existential deep end
that's true
I just wanted to give you an opportunity
maybe there's one that's particularly
interesting or something
the only one that was even
semi interesting was when I almost killed myself
from working too hard
that sounds relevant
I don't think I've heard it
I think I've heard bits and pieces of it
it was back when
I first got started doing horse stuff
and I was working a job
and I was working all night on making
the picture book
and I was downing tons of
energy drinks
I had like 3 a day
and my heart was like
tweaking out and I had to go to the hospital
and I was there for like a few hours
I was sitting with my dad
he was just like fucking retarded
and I'm like yeah that's true
they had me hooked up to one of those
part beat monitor thing
am I still in this?
and it was weird because we like skip a beat
every time you go see it as it did it
oh my god
it just shut off
oh fuck my dad's like
I gotta get somebody like the equipment
fucked up and I'm like yeah I guess
and then like 3 seconds later my whole body went numb
and cold
and I was just like
it's not the equipment
at the time I assume you were
I couldn't move
it felt like instantly I was in a freezer
cause like my heart stopped so there was no blood circulating
and I was just dying
and for like it was a solid like 15 seconds
before it like beat
really hard and like my whole body jolted
and it started again
and like
the closest I came to death was like
when my heart stopped for like a very noticeable
amount of time
fascinating
and on that note thank you for listening
to the Procrest days
speaking of death
did I miss anything?
no I mean you can listen back he told a story
and it was equally traumatic as the first time I heard it
I missed it
listen back god damn it it was the rest of the audience it'll be there
tell it again make the audience
I've never listened to a PCP
episode and I won't start now
what a hero
alright well how about we
shift over to questions now what do you say folks
let's do it
we have run for over an hour
we're at an hour and 20 minutes
let's see here
what do we got
I think there was some
decent ones here
fill time
somebody fill time give
what's your favorite color
blue
you're fired
that's the one
what the reference
hey here's a fun one to fill a little bit of time
ok by
at batsling1234
would someone take up this challenge
describe the PCP to someone who
never uses the internet
oh man it's a bunch of guys
and a girl
and then mage
oh got her
who's the girl no one will know
it's a loose coalition
of gays
in a straight world
united against the oppressive
matriarchy
do you remember that one kid in your
kindergarten class that ate glue
imagine if there were like seven of them
and they all talked to each other for an hour
do you say that was you Gib?
I didn't eat glue I like putting glue on my hands
and peeling it off when it dried
oh fuck yeah dude oh fuck yeah
that was the shit that was the jam dog
I'm serious
I remember doing that a little bit
ok here's another question
oh shit where'd it go
oh Gib this one is directed at you
it's actually not specifically but it's for you
it's just have any of the PCP members
played Fire Emblem Heroes
and what are your thoughts in your main
teams
let me look at my main team right now
I'm playing this game currently as well
oh yeah I'm not playing it because
I already played too many mobile games
I got Lisa
from Fire Emblem Awakening
Florina from my favorite game ever
Kane from something
and Faye the dragon
and I got their like four and five star
characters and they're really good and the game
is great and I like it and it's good and I like it
so I was just curious oh sorry
go on top go on top I was just going to say I only started a couple days ago
I have nobody good my
my summons have been shitty
I only have three star guys except for one
four star ninja dude who's kind of cool
the game is really fun
yeah you got fucked
and every time my guy levels there's just like one stat boost
and like that's it so like I can't even win
the training mission now so I might have just restart
entirely
the only thing I don't like is the fact
and not even that I don't like it but I just find it odd
that because they outsourced all the art to a bunch of different people
like there's like 15 different art styles in the game
and it doesn't really match very well
I thought they were recycling art styles from like the original
games for some is that not true
no they're all different
but some of them definitely look more interesting
what's annoying
I can see why that would clash
I would at least expect it to be like one
by the way the voice actor
for Florina is the cutest
ever and if you get her you will enjoy
the fact that she goes um
when you look on her
please make a video where you document
these audio sounds because they're not on the internet
and I want to hear that
yeah I will I'm going to make a miniscule review
oh excellent fantastic
I'm looking forward to it
what was I going to say
the only reason I'm at all tempted to play that game
is because I'm sure it's the reason 99%
of people play because I want to see
Camilla and Lynn and just
you know just be around them because they're the hottest women
you know ever that's it
that's the only reason
there's like a 3% rate of getting
like one of those 5 star characters
so you have to grind to infinity
yeah I'm very lucky in that
I've already got two 5 stars
so that's cool
here's a question
Jesse this one's for you
how do I become a sweet shirt
first of all does he even want to be
a sweet shirt
sweet shirts good yeah you just got to wear
sweet shirts yeah it's a combination
of the sweet boy and the shit shirt
but it's not like actually a combination
it's just a combination of the word
well no a sweet boy is bad
the shit shirt is definitely bad
a sweet probably the worst
but a sweet shirt
is like right in that happy medium
of traits for a human to possess
damn
all you got to do is describe yourself as a sweet shirt
what about a shit boy
oh the best
I haven't quite cracked the code on shit boy yet
I think I'd like to give that one a spin
you know all you got to do to be a sweet shirt
is just just wear sweet
shirts damn
and uh you know
yeah but I mean it's
like a fellow it's a minute to learn a lifetime
to master yeah that's right
you know it's more complicated people think
I mean people don't realize you know what
constitutes a sweet shirt you can't just throw
any old rag on you can't just have some
shirt with some shit you like on it because
some shirts are cluttered the designs are too
complicated some shirt you know
I'll give you I'll give people some advice for
finding a sweet shirt
look for simplicity look for like
something that's iconic look for logos
always be on the lookout for logos
and and that like the
Patreon like the Patriot
yeah I should get a shirt with that
that's the one who did that
there was that who was always that fan art
of the PCP logo made out of patreons
that was dude Tom did that Tom made
that dude
fan of all a guy who's here
that's great you know that's a
that's an emote that's a fucking
reaction image or an emoticon or whatever you
fucking call them in the in the fan discord
now I saw that I saw that
I have a shirt press at home
it's oh my god dude
let's get serious let's talk about this
let's talk about about selling these
things why don't we have that
that's because it takes effort and I'm the
only one who does anything besides Jesse besides
Digi who edits them together I'll do that
and the iTunes Jesus Christ someone has to
fucking step up to the plate I know someone
does oh by the way I'm sorry
I wanted to say the names of people after
these questions I forgot to the fire emblem
question was by at hooded lefty
and the
fuck where those good fucking question
I can't remember what it was
the the sweet shirt was by at track
master track so thanks guys and
one more question here and this was actually
I'm taking this one because this is personal
Jesse this is sort of a question for you
this actually wasn't a question at all it was
just I'm taking it because I have
a personal interest because I watched a video about
it even though I didn't watch it
I only the only good royal rumble
this year was by at TP
crashed by the procrastinators
fuck Roman those by Jen is
maku do Mario and I
was just wondering I I tweeted before
there was this compilation of everyone
disappointed that the 30th Royal Rumbleman
was fucking Roman Reigns
and I was just wondering how that worked out what
went down well they just they just
won't they just won't quit
they won't give up on the Roman Reigns they won't
accept that like Roman Reigns is not going
to happen they they can't accept it
and they keep trying it's been like
like three years of him getting boot out of
the building and he just won't stop
did he win did he
win the thing thank God but it's like it was
especially dumb because like he had already
had a match earlier in the night
Oh for like
okay and like the match earlier in
the night was for the championship
and he lost and
the good like the prize
of the Royal Rumble is a chance
to get a championship match
so it's like
if he was already in a championship
match that night and lost how
in the fuck did he get a spot
in the Royal Rumble that's a great 10 minutes
like you assume that the spots are
filled up before the fucking show starts
like did he go up did he go
after his match and like assassinate
whoever was supposed to be number 30
and take this spot if he if he did if they
had showed that it would have been okay
but they it's just a weird I hope dumb
plot hole
it was glue man it was gonna be the
glue man glue man who was finally
about to make his debut and Roman took him out
that monster
I was gonna say that
there was there was another new contender
was gonna take that 30th spot
but he was assassinated and the crowd could just hear
the faint
from backstage
during the
during the vile act
okay that's it everybody
alright thanks for listening thanks for
sending your questions make sure we send us
we're done we're done we're done
we mind all the good questions and all that's left is garbage
so keep stepping up your game people
better questions for fuck's sake
even the ones that were acceptable
and don't ask us about anime
fuck you we're not an anime show
we hate anime we're not
it's not even that we hate anime we just hate you
for asking us about it
this is not an anime podcast
in case that wasn't clear so
you know fuck you buddy
seconded
yeah
oh that was good to say
everybody but still
tweet us good questions at TP
Crastinators throughout the week and on
Saturdays especially because that's when we
fucking will read them no as we're doing the
goddamn show oh hey hey we should shout out the wiki
yeah yeah I was about to say oh that's totally true
we're gonna shout out the fucking wiki
there is a procrastinators
podcast wiki
with lots of lore and stuff it's new it needs
work it needs your it needs your help
it needs your help viewers
that's right
dainxjack
has begun it and he's there's a lot of there's
stuff on there but like fucking it's a
community project you know it's a fan
wiki so if you've got thoughts about
our shit go contribute them
there what's what's the here it's
the Https
procrastopedia
procrastopedia.mirahees.org
that's procrastopedia
we'll put a link in the description
yeah yeah
procrastopedia.mirahees.org
yeah link in the description
and so just so you know most of the
stuff there was not made by us so there's
totally possible there's tons of inaccuracies
whatever there is it's terrible I
definitely want to die looking at it
the only good page
is the one that munchie made
for the undertailer 587 which has
extensive lore
that lore didn't even exist until he started
writing that page and he's just going ham
feel flushing out
that's the only
he's been established that the undertailer
is a code red threat
that's right
I forgot about that
watch out for that guy
that's my favorite part
code red threat
we need to establish a whole system of codes
based off that the implications are far
reaching
no doubt thank you munchie we appreciate
your spirit and your hard work okay thanks
everybody for watching we'll see you next week
make sure to send us questions at tpcrasnators
buh bye
bye
I hate ya
yeah
I'm supposed
to be working
right now
I'm supposed
to be working
right now
but I'm not working
I'm doing nothing
my dick I'm jerking
myself I'm
sucking
I am an asshole
I am a stupid
I've got a
deadline
don't want to do it
what the hell is wrong
with me
I'm supposed to be
making money
I'm supposed
to be creating
funny
things that the people
gladly will pay
for
artistic genius
that's what they came
for instead I'm
tweeting
hashtag repeating
that's why there's no
weed and holes in the ceiling
yeah
it's quite the burden
it's a hard knock life
being
a genius