I'm going to bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
I don't know, whatever. Hello, welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I got nothing,
I don't know, I got, did you like that opening jingle? That's all you're getting in terms
of your intro. Jumping right in, jumping right in, watch out. We're starting off as a Ben
Cast this week. I am all by myself. I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I know nobody likes me. I know
nobody likes me. I know, everyone just tolerates me. For Gibb's sake, for poor, sweet, it isn't
Gibb's sake. But alas, she's not here. And I'm just going ahead. I don't need to explain
myself to the likes of you listener. You don't even have a podcast unless you do. Let me talk
about some stuff. Let me talk about this channel and what I did to ruin it recently. That's
not true. Well, I was trying my best. I was doing my best. I fucked up. I fucked everything
up. Not really, but a little bit. Here's the story. A while back, maybe we've been talking
about doing this for a long time, but a few months ago, we finally did it, which is Nate
wanted to transfer ownership and management of all the various PCP accounts, like the
Redbubble and the Google AdSense and the YouTube channel and what other things are there. Oh,
the Patreon, patreon.com slash the procrastinators, I think, if I've remembered the URL finally.
The Minecraft server, obviously, which is free now, free now to anyone who wants to
join. Link in the description for the Discord server, which will get you set up with that
if you want to join that. By the way, I hope we can stream some of that soon. I'm getting
new internet. My shitty internet has been a big problem for a while when we've tried
to stream, but I am supposed to be getting new internet supposedly on the 13th, which
will be, I think, the day this comes out. Will that be this Friday? Yeah, it would be
this Friday. If that happens and it works going forward, I might be able to stream. I'm
a lot of apologize for how inconsistent that's been and how shitty that's been and how my internet
has gotten in the way of more regular streaming of the Minecraft server as well as other things,
but I'm sure that I will want to stream more once my internet is reliable, so that will be great.
I'll also be getting way off topic. I'm getting way off topic, but I guess I'll also mention it.
Once my internet is up, I will want to start streaming on my Twitch again, the BenSaint Twitch
channel, which I used to do with some regularity. I had built up a little bit of momentum on there
a couple years ago, and then I fell off of it, so I would like to get back into that. My plan for
that is I'm going to be streaming Mega Man Battle Networks. I've never played them. I'm going to
play them for the first time, and I thought might as well do that on stream, so that's what I'll do.
I mean, maybe even starting next week, if the internet thing works out, that would be great.
But anyway, that's all off. By the way, I'll talk more about that, and in regards to Mega Man
stuff and Leicester stuff, I guess I'll mention that I do have a bunch of, I think I have like
14 or 15 unanswered questions for Q&As. I'll probably do another on my personal Patreon Q&A,
probably do that soon, actually, over on Patreon.com slash BenSaint, which has, by the way,
I said in the video that I would hold a Patreon vote for a lecture, let people decide a lecture
for me to do at 100 Patrons. At the time I had, I think about 35 Patrons-ish. Now I have almost,
I think I had 80, and then I lost like one or two after the end of the month or end of the year,
so I have like 78. So that's pretty good, but not quite at 100 yet. But soon, and a lot of people
have asked me for various, various different lecture topics, some of them are things I had
heard of and some I never had. So I genuinely don't know what I'll end up doing for that.
Probably will not do it, probably will have to get another lecture out. Maybe it'll be the
Battle Network one, or I'd like to finish a different one. I'd like to finish another lecture
on something else while I'm in the process of playing through all the Battle Network games.
I'm rambling. I'm so far off the original topic right now. Let me get back to it, all right.
So the Patreon and the YouTube accounts and the PCP accounts, Nate, you know,
wasn't really managing them, or he didn't want to manage them anymore. He gave them to me.
And one of the things that needed to be moved was, okay, there was an AdSense account for
Nate's channel. There was an ad, or actually, bafflingly enough, Nate's channels, like all
of Nate's channels and all the things he uses AdSense for, all used the, the T-Bap
AdSense account, the associated AdSense account for that. He, there was another AdSense account for
the PCP. And then, of course, I had my own, you know, Ben St. AdSense account. And I guess
YouTube got really, or Google got really finicky about multiple, multiple accounts on AdSense.
And even though it would make so much more sense to just have separate AdSense accounts for
separate channels, I guess it's really picky about like, oh, no, they don't want you having multiple
AdSense accounts. They want you to connect all your, your YouTube channels, all connect them
all to the same AdSense account. Whatever, right? So the P, it ended up, and this might have been
a result of the, the Garling House hack that might have been what caused the initial, this
situation. But the point is there were $82 in, in ad revenue in the PCP AdSense account.
And Nate had switched to the T-Bap AdSense account and the $82 was just in there. So he
transferred ownership of the PCP, like the email and the Gmail account, the Google account.
He transferred that to me. He gave me that and I, and I was hooking it up to my AdSense.
And it was like, it would, it wanted me not to use its own AdSense account, the one with $82
in it. It would let me connect the YouTube account, the PCP YouTube account to my AdSense. So now
what happens is ad revenue from the PCP, instead of going to its own AdSense, it goes directly to
my AdSense. And this is actually annoying because now I have to stretching. I just woke up, by the
way. The AdSense for my account and the PCP account both come and they're not differentiated.
So in the account, I just see one amount that I get every month and I have to manually go into
my YouTube analytics and look at the analytics and the views and the revenue and I have to personally
sort out how much of that is mine and how much of that is PCP money and then divide it up on that
basis. So it's annoying. I would prefer they just go to separate accounts so I could know this money
is for this, this money is for that, but they won't let me. Oh well. But I was really annoyed. I
wanted that $82 of PCP money. So I'm like, okay, well, I'm going to try and do, I'm going to try
and hook it up. So I tried to switch, right? I tried to switch back to the PCP account for the $82
and it wouldn't, and it gave me, and it said like, you know, this account is not approved. This
account, this is a duplicate account. Delete your duplicate accounts before you try to connect this
account. And I'm like, okay, well, I don't want to delete, I don't want to delete my account.
Nate doesn't want to delete the tbap account that he's using through that all of his stuff is
connected through. So no, I won't do that. So it just thinks it's a duplicate account. I'm not even
sure if it thinks it's me or if it thinks it's Nate, but it knows it's a duplicate or it thinks
it's a duplicate. And so it just said, I tried to connect it and it said, no, you can't do that.
So instead of just not switching accounts, it disconnected from any AdSense account.
And it said, well, now, since you've tried to do this, you can't connect your account for 32 days.
So it disconnected the PCP account from any AdSense account for 32 days. In fact,
in fact, the channel is no longer monetized for 32 days.
I don't know why the 32 day restriction, but that's what it did. So
so basically for one month, the channel is no longer monetized,
which will cost about so that's about it varies month to month. But generally,
the channel makes about like 120, maybe 150 on a good month dollars in ad revenue.
So unfortunately, in attempting to retrieve this $82, I ended up costing us about $150.
Tragic, tragic. So I have to wait until I think like near the end of January,
because I did this near the end of December. I have to wait until the end of January to try
and fix this back and get the channel monetized again. Costs cost us money. I'm sorry. I did
my best. I wasn't trying to do I didn't know this guy. I didn't know it would do this. I don't know
why it would do this. I did, however, figure out a way to get the $82. The way to get the $82
is I just had to close that AdSense account, which is fine because it would not let me use it
for anything. So I just closed the account and it said like, yeah, when you close the account,
if there's more than they don't pay out regularly unless there's more than $100 in there. So $82
wouldn't hit that. But if you close the account, it will send you whatever is in there as long
as there's more than $10. So supposedly within the next two to three months, they will send me
because I switched the the associated like bank account to my bank account. So it will send to
my bank account $82, probably minus some fees. So at that point, what I will do is I will take
that $82 and I will apply it to the total PCP pay as though it were the money that had been that we
lost due to ad revenue that month. And so I hope to somewhat mitigate that loss with that still
will end up losing like, you know, $50, $70 or something. But it's, you know, so that's how
that worked out. Very stupid, very dumb, very bad. But what can you do? I'm hungry. I might go get
breakfast. I might just leave this recording on and just go get some food. I'm gonna do it. Fuck it.
Fuck it. A few moments later, I'm back. I put a quarter of a Kirkland brand
Supreme is it a Supreme Supreme cauliflower crust pizza as recommended to me by
by what's her name not a big jerk on Twitter. Yeah, that'll be so that'll be 20 minutes. So
let's see. So how much how much dead air can I feel for the next 20 minutes before I got to go
collect my pizza? The I changed my mind about that guy, that guy who moved in to the room
with the girl that lives downstairs in my house, I said in a previous episode,
I thought it was a feminine that they they cook all the time. Because it's like, I don't know.
I don't know why I said that. No, I do know why I said that is because I don't like cooking and I
wouldn't like spending cooking. So I just assumed I naively just assumed foolishly that he also
probably didn't like it and that they were just like he was like doing it like, I don't know, to
either as like a thing to do, or as like, I'm doing this for my girlfriend or whatever. And
that was stupid. I've changed my mind. And what I think now is that that guy just likes to cook
because I just see him doing it sometimes with the girl and sometimes but also just by himself.
So I think he just likes to do it because I never see her cook like when it's when it was just her.
So I think that's just his thing. And so I've changed my mind and I've decided that no, he's
he's he's drawn her into his world. It's it's alpha actually. So I salute it.
This is why you should never listen to me about anything.
You know, sometimes I sometimes I just have a sometimes I just I just form an opinion
off of preconceived biases. And then I just go with it. And I just and I just throw it out there.
I just throw it out there and I let the world tell me what they think about it.
And sometimes I revise it later. And sometimes I don't. And that's and that's
you know, I'm just drawing every I'm drawing everyone else into my own world. I'm at it's
the alpha thing to do. That's that's the that's the plan. All right. I have nothing else to say
about that, nor indeed anything. I used a okay. I don't know if I've ever mentioned this before,
but like my dad got me I think he got like everyone one year he got these these rotary tools
which are not drills. I mean, I think you can drill with them. They have drill bits in them,
but they're not really for drilling. They're like a drill but weaker.
They're just like a thing that you hold and you plug it in. And you can put a little thing on
the end and it'll spin. And it has all these attachments for it. And I think they're mostly
for like grinding or sanding or polishing. And I don't know what possessed my dad to think that
like, people definitely need to have a rotary tool for grinding, sanding and polishing. Maybe
one time he found like such a thing useful. And it came in handy in a pinch. And so he thought,
you know what, people, everyone needs to have one of these lying around. Just just in case.
Well, I use it for something for the first time this week. Because it had some
it has a like a like these like kind of rusty metal discs that are called cutting discs.
So you can use it to like cut stuff. And I just wanted to see if I could do this. And I took one
of the RFCK pins, one of the unsold RFCK pins, one of the ones that had the most one just like
extra ones lying around. Specifically, it's the one like the number one, the the orange and yellow
and white number one design. And I took that and I use the rotary tool just to cut the actual pin
part of it off like the pointy part that sticks into the backing that sticks through whatever
you're attaching it to. So we just cut that part off. And now I just have this little this cool
little like metal and enamel number one, I don't know, token or whatever. And I don't know what
utility that has. But I guess it's kind of cool. And I guess I quote unquote made it myself. And
that's neat in its own special way. I don't know. I don't know why I did that. I just did. And I
don't regret it. Yeah. Well, I guess I kind of no idea. I guess the reason I was thinking about it.
Part of the idea was to turn these things into into tokens. And the and the reason why I was
thinking about tokens is because okay, and I'm hearing from and I just asked Munchie. I just
asked Munchie and whether he minded me talking about it publicly. And he said he would rather
keep it a secret. And I think that's totally reasonable. We can put it in a bonus episode.
It's not you can't go in the main episode. Lamal. Oh, God. Now what do I do? Now how do I fill air?
Okay, Eleazar, but leave in but leave in me mentioning that it's been cut and put and resigned
to a bonus episode. That that stuff can all go in a bonus episode. Leave in me saying that all
that stuff I just said can only be in a bonus episode because I guess it's it's a secret
for a future project. So I can't I don't want to talk about it publicly, but a bonus episode
is fine, I think. So that's the that's the another plug
for the for the for the PCP Patreon as if as if you didn't already have ample reason
to pledge a mere $5 a month only $5 a month keeps us keeps us fed keeps us keeps us bread
whatever that means. And also, you know, will help mitigate that all that ad revenue that I
cost us by trying to get the $82 please please patrons help us save us save us by pledging
to our Patreon mitigate mitigate the ad revenue that YouTube has fucking stolen from us with its
draconian 32 days policy why why 32 days why by attempting to link an ad sense account that they
thought should not be allowed is this why then am I for being rejected am I then not allowed to try
again for 32 days why 32 all right I got my I got my pizza I got my one quarter of a Kirkland
Supreme cauliflower crust pizza you know it costs a little more it costs a little more but the benefit
is that I can have a quarter of the pizza and it's only like 300 calories instead of being like
600 so I feel like that's I feel like that's worth a premium and you know I got my I got my
birch beer so you have a classic combo of brek of birch birch beer and and and and pizza for breakfast
uh try it if you don't believe me uh there's nothing better
truly I've got it it's got a nibble the corner because the center is too hot
I took it out a little earlier I like it usually I like them a little undercooked usually I prefer
you know cook them cook them at home pizzas I usually prefer them a little softer
rather than being too crispy more flavorful in my opinion
ah shit all right I had shit I had an idea I was gonna there was something else I was gonna bring
up um what was it okay oh yeah I still have not I still have not finished the um slime and punishment
uh uh end section the reason why and again maybe you can see this coming is I just it's not the
stuff that I had already done is done I just keep thinking of more I just keep thinking of more
things to put in it um basically if I have not explained this before maybe I will what I'm putting
in I think I have said this before you know I wrote the end notes that explain the pages
because a lot of the pages are references to two things that were going on at the time or are just
rfck in jokes or whatever and then on top of that I wanted to go back and I wanted to put in
context in the form of like things chris said because a lot of the many some of the comic is
like directly responding to things that chris said like weird weird takes that chris had about the
story weird takes that chris had about endless war at rfck or and of course her weird insistence
that slime must be destroyed by a storm of bicarbonate soda water rain um so I'm putting in
like her her messages and her tweets and her dms like about that and and I I remembered the other
day a little while ago that she had been in the server and she had interacted with some people
and she had made some posts in there and people and she had people had said like why do you hate
slime chris we love slime it's our it's our life blood and she uh you know was weirdly insistent
and I think that's really funny so I think that's worthy of inclusion so you know this was another
thing like oh you know I should add a I should add a page or two just sort of cataloging that
part of it as a I just I just think that stuff's funny I think I think reading her
you know across all these in tweets and retweets as well as twitter dms as well as like discord
messages in the endless war server you know you read it all in or the idea is that I assemble it
all in order and it all paints a picture it all tells the story of this person who just has this
crazy idea that like I like it's it's my job to destroy the slime that like powers this place that
like and and I don't know I I'm not really want to want to provide commentary I'm not really like
commenting on any of it I'm just kind of putting it there and the idea is that you will read through
the footnotes and you will read you know her own words about all of it and you will come to your
own conclusion and that conclusion will be like this person is really weird and and I just I just
think that's funny um just really funny that she was on a crusade against slime I don't know I feel
like so anyway uh yeah I keep I keep remembering little bits like oh wait didn't didn't didn't she
say this and she said that wasn't there a moment when that happened and so I keep like going back and
finding uh finding a tweet here or a message there and being like oh that's part of it yeah I put
that I honestly I I bet the point where I should probably start parrying it down and maybe I need
to go back through it and actually pick out things that like maybe that doesn't need to be here maybe
that response doesn't really add anything to the narrative because the point is to build a narrative
the point is that you read through these notes and it gives you more context and it paints this sort
of behind the scenes picture of why what was going on and so I think yeah I started I I I
finished putting everything together and then I started a new I duplicated the file and I started
a new version of the file and the goal of that file was to go through and and cull you know
and edit crop out things that are not necessary but then as I was doing that I remembered the
like the in server messages and the server interactions and I like that's funny I gotta
I gotta I gotta get I gotta find those so I had to go find them which was a little bit hard because
she's her her discord account well it means she was removed from the server I think her
discord account still exists but it's hard to search for messages from someone who has left
a server I did figure out how to do it um but I don't know I kind I kind of want to find like
because it's it's funny that like she was in there and she got killed right the story is she
joined the server and she postured as though she had all these like powers in the game that
do not exist she said she could exclamation point mock speed dash or exclamation point goddess
protection um and there's a really funny part where like it's it's it's gib gib actually asked
her like hey what's your do you have a slime so now like do you have an rfck character and
chris posts um it's like it's the card it's the twilight sparkle she she secret ship fake folder
card of her like goddess sonichu form like with all these rainbow like beams coming off or whatever
and it's like and she's like my goddess body is immune to the slime I uh I use I use the I use
dash and protect myself at will so I am not so I am unkillable and cannot be corrupted by slime
and it's a really funny response by a bunch given a couple other people they're just like cool awesome
that yeah nice nice and it's really good so I was glad to find that I would like to find I would
like to find the person that killed her because somebody somebody killed her and a couple and
somebody scalped her um because you can scout and I would like to find those commands I would like
to find like exactly who did that because yeah chris's scalp was like an item that was circulating
through the economy for a while I think there were two of them and there's a part where there's
a part where during a conversation someone like a date date checks her data and it says like yeah
she's dead she's riddled with bullet holes blah blah blah um so uh I would just like to I I figured
out how to find a person's uh messages even though their serve their chant their account
is no longer in the server uh I have not I tried to just search for their at to find like
commands directed at them like kill kill at cwc 1982 or whatever um and it didn't work so maybe
there's a way to do it and I just have to figure it out but anyway this is this is the this is the
endless sycophie and struggle that I find myself in constantly thinking of uh hey what about that
one thinking of new things like oh I gotta put that in I gotta put that into the index part
even even as I'm constantly trying to like cut as much as I can because I want to cull it down to
be the most the cleanest and most the cleanest narrative experience of reading through like
the this this record as possible I'm trying to cut but I keep thinking of things I want to add
basically okay I've I've said it I've said it enough ways time to take another bite of my pizza
I said a bite but I ate the whole thing delightful all right enough I'm sure you don't want to hear
me talk about my breakfast uh I think maybe I'll just jump right into voicemails I think I've
prattled on long enough and it probably won't even be that long after all that shit I had to cut
there's probably what like 20 minutes what can I what can I say there's just not I'm just I can't
you know uh uh uh uh it's tough you know you you try podcasting you try solo podcasting for uh
you can't do it it's impossible okay whatever uh anyway speak pipe the first message is called odd
I think some messages disappear oh wait I didn't no I don't want to no I don't want to read the new
one piece chat I'll wait until next week and discuss it with gibb now sorry no no one piece
discussion this week because uh I would just be like uh mm-hmm yep and then that happened and then
that happened and then that happened um pretty neat okay well that's all I have to say also great
my internet is uh fucking up did I mention that I'll hopefully have new internet by the 13th
because you know here here I am and it's doing the thing again where it uh it doesn't load the it
doesn't fucking load speak pipe even though here here's a funny thing uh yeah I clicked to download
the message download a speak pipe message and then I clicked to refresh the speak pipe page
and it did successfully download the message the the the message was was downloaded no problem but
the website itself uh site can't be reached there's no internet you're not connected to the internet
my dude so that's great all right first message is called odd I think some messages disappear but
I also almost spam three two one go oops I mean Pokemon ranger they have two they have a that
it has a sequel and poke park that has two versions as well they are really good I remember I looked
these up before Pokemon ranger and poke park poke park we Pikachu's adventure Pikachu must engage
in battle with a Feraligator in order to befriend it that's when I that's what I see when I go to
the plot section of the poke park we Pikachu's adventure Wikipedia page is it like an action
platformer like a 3d you can run around a 3d world and just kick the shit out of other Pokemon to
befriend them uh Pikachu sent to the poke park with a mythical Pokemon you tells them the 14
pieces of the sky prism has shattered with his friends Pikachu sets on an adventure to find them
in the poke park blah blah blah blah does it say genre does it just say what's action adventure
interesting um looks kind of neat I mean I don't have a we I guess we can emulate it
but I won't I got other games I want to play I got oh I got Disco Elysium I finally downloaded
Disco Elysium and I will play that soon but I have not played it yet uh
maybe I'll stream it I don't know I don't know if I want to stream that one I feel like streaming
might distract me from the game I feel like I just kind of want to experience that game because
everyone says it's so it's so good and it seems like it's like a very reading heavy like it's it's a
it's a from what I gather it's a you know an isometric basically a tech I mean it's I mean I
don't know I guess there are rules but it's sort of like one of those what the fuck do you call
games like um like planescape torment uh and I mean it's like an isometric RPG that's very like
dialogue tree heavy so I don't have streaming that game would really be that good of a way to
experience it um but anyway uh I'll play it soon next one is called at ask in rules for skin rules
I think four skin rules three two one go hello PCB remember that one time Aaron from Game Grumps
floated around the idea of regrowing his foreskin and immediately his bitch wife Susie
burst in the room screaming about how if he does that she's getting a divorce so uh yeah
would you regrow your foreskin would you be okay with your girlfriend trying to control your body
like that I mean I don't remember the exact moment you're talking about I have to imagine that Susie
was I mean was she serious like that that would be weird that would be weird if she was serious
about I assume she was joking um I don't care I don't care about my foreskin so uh and also I mean
let's we're all clear on that we can't regrow it right uh it doesn't it's not me personally
me personally I think it's fine I wouldn't regrow it if I could I would not have any desire to do
that it's it uh uh but I mean um uh I hate circumcision you know what we should ban circumcision
just because I hate talking about it I hate that there's a debate about it uh it's like the most
annoying uh subject to discuss in the world so I'm against it just because I don't ever want to hear
about it again that's my that's my new take um nice the next one did I download that one
yes I did the next one is an imager link so let's freaking look at it shall we the procrastinators
ben saint hypocrite rebel pixels beska ever I mean yeah those uh I might have mentioned a while ago
this was a go this was a while ago now but Nate had already not been on the the pcb for a long time
and I tried to and I removed him from that list and he got mad at me he got angry I don't know why
so yeah they probably should be removed I think maybe I'll do that again and there's no there's
no good reason for him to be angry if I try to do that again I'll do that at some point um because
yeah it's it's me and hippo gibb now uh next one is another imager link uh let's see uh what we got
yes I mean first of all I mentioned this already that our ad is procrastinators 9667 no I don't
know why it's like that might have been for the garlinghouse thing yes I know the descriptions
is under construction I think that's also a brad garlinghouse thing no no it shouldn't say that
but like what should it say I don't know what are you pointing this out for I know all this I know all
this uh next one is um let's see here r slash the procrastinators the pin okay I see this actually
should probably be changed the pinned link on r slash procrastinators is radcon 17 2017 the playlist
and apparently it's a dead link right because we removed right because we remove the playlists
the radcon playlist they're now linked wait are they is that a dead link let me let me try it
yes the playlist does not exist okay you know what that's fair that should not be that should not be
the pinned should not be pinned on the subreddit uh reddit user reddit user rival underscore
steven if you're listening uh maybe you could remove that um why is divu a moderator gross
okay next I mean all right all right guy you make you make a fair point you make a fair point
next one I'm gonna fucking add the http colon slash slash all right here we go full episode
pcp playlist multiple missing episodes okay well there's nothing I can do about that one buddy
because uh a bunch a couple of them have been removed for copyright or something and I can't
put them I can't put them back on the itunes google play spotify okay okay yeah I know those are out
of date I've been saying for a while that I need to update them I just haven't gotten around to it yet
I I know I've been meaning to so but that's why and if you listened you would know that like yes I
know that those are not up to date and they're missing episodes the google play is apparently a
dead link okay that's probably fair join the pcb minecraft server yeah I mean maybe this was sent
late I I already I already removed that part of it uh the and I've replaced it with a um a link
to the pcb minecraft discord server which is not you don't need to join uh a a patreon to join
now so that part I already fixed and then the pcb wiki yeah the pcb wiki dead link that one
probably should be removed because that is a dead link I guess I was hopeful that
the owner might restore that at some point but that's probably stupid so that one's fair okay
some of these are valid and some of them are annoying maybe I'm being too sensitive about it
um I will I know I have not updated the itunes google play spotify feed
it's really it it's really annoying to do it's really really annoying
and I know that a few people do want them and would appreciate it and I will do it at some
point but you got to understand from my perspective it's like a really annoying thing to do that like
what like 10 like 10 people like 10 fucking people are gonna listen to it that way
or that's how it seems to me anyway um anyway next one is bus girl speaks out
it's another fucking imager link and it doesn't include the http so I gotta add it myself
huh okay bus busera autobus kizi in December okay this is this is this is very funny
in December 2022 I was approached by it's also a little waiting for my bus despite
his weird smell and withering hairline I tried to make friendly conversation
unfortunately he preferred to follow me stammer about horse slime and androids
only to make the most pathetic attempt at coming on me I have ever experienced I feel
violated and want to warn every woman on here that he is a sick little freak and a menace to
women around the globe uh this this is some kind of copypasta right I that that line withering
hairline I feel like I've seen that before somewhere um honestly this this picture actually
looks not that dissimilar from how she looked so I guess all the Turkish women all look the same I
don't know uh this uh good one you freaking you freaking got me you freaking got me with this one
I have nothing to say but kudos to you sir okay next one spread the cheeks and like the whole
ugh the scent so pungent okay three two one go Ben if you actually end up doing the digital
diaspora lecture make sure to mention the sticky piss floor for wiping her teeth with a t-shirt
instead of brushing them in the time she didn't shower long enough for her scalp to form a uniform
mass of dead skin blood hair and puss don't forget the weird philosophy of how she is actually so big
brain mega intelligent that she watches Marvel movies in an avant-garde type of way that she
adopted in the past six months as a part of the ongoing being online is bad actually project
also let's say for the sake of argument that someone was able to reverse engineer the location
of the compound from the videos of bird and trixie petting diseased stray dogs while already
been through the dump that is Corbin Kentucky already done with menace to women Ben saint
hypothetically do that information it's already been done and the answer is nothing uh it would be
really weird if i if i like did anything with that uh so yeah don't bother doing don't bother
don't bother trying to reverse engineer her house is it's it's done and i'm not doing anything with
that information just so you know uh but she also doesn't live there anymore i mean i'm convinced
i'm i'm pretty convinced that like uh she's been kicked out of that house um because she's
been posting she's been posing from california for like a long time now and uh they don't
the ye the yeag posters she's she's taken sucker punch out of her bio so i'm pretty sure she's out
of there either either sucker punch is dead and no longer exists or she is just out of it which
would mean that she doesn't live in that house anymore i don't know where she lives i think i
thought she was living with her parents crashing with her parents in california but she i don't
know recently she's been like on the road again she's driving somewhere i guess maybe she could be
driving back to Corbin Kentucky to live there again i i don't know why she would do that because
like i know that they have this tiny little apartment and call it the Corbin crack house
i know that they have this tiny little apartment and like three other people three people live there
and i don't think and and that seems like too many already like five people like his bird
and tricks like that's too many people and they were living there like five people to this one
bedroom uh little hole uh and that must have sucked really bad and so you know if she's going
back that would suck really bad too but the fact that the fact that sucker punch is out of the bio
is what makes me think more than anything that she probably doesn't live in where she's going
or where she actually lives i don't know maybe she's going back there i have no idea i try to keep
my finger on the pulse of these things because i find it because i find it funny to watch her um
um nobody nobody understands uh uh the the humor for me is like every single time she says i'm
going to do something and like if i pay attention i can see every single time it falls apart and
doesn't happen um like in yeah in the in her i'm quitting youtube video she said you know
you we're starting sucker punch you know we're we're a sucker punch we're on Spotify that's
what we're going to do we're going to be rapping we're a rap group now also uh my day job is going
to be editing youtube videos for mint salad to sub to promote uh mint salads uh only fans
uh right and i know that both things didn't happen because now sucker punch is out of the
bio sucker punch is dead um and uh cranberry dave is mint salads editor and there's absolutely
no reason why she needs more than one and i'm pretty sure she's been kicked out of that house
that she was intending to make a living and working in her job so all of that crumbled but in a very
in a non-public way in a way that you wouldn't know unless you're a genius like me who keeps track of
everything uh so that's why i do it uh because because i get i get because it always pays off
it's always gratifying in that way um so well anyway these things um yeah i probably would
the poor hygiene yeah i probably would mention that i probably would give the example of like
the gray goo on the head the gray bloody scabby goo on the head the brushing the teeth thing definitely
um i don't know if i would specifically mention the morrow i mean it
i probably would not devote that much time of such a hypothetical lecture to the the yig era and the
post yig era i would pretty much just because like that pretty much is the end right like
the like i mean on the one hand trixie is digi bro there is there actually is no separation
between those two despite what she claims because she was never playing a character she was just
being her the most authentic version of herself that she could on camera and that's what digi
bro was despite the fact that she claims otherwise now uh nevertheless digi bro as a brand did pretty
much end it turned out with the um with the yig rebrand because the content dried up or just became
worthless uh and unnotable and you know the the the enterprise collapsed monetarily and and then
ultimately was uh officially dissolved so i mean i i i mean i would probably touch upon all the
stupid i mean it would touch upon like the weird way that the yig channel was organized
yeah and i probably would talk about like how all her announcements were like how anime is bad guys
if you still watch anime you're addicted to it and anime is an addiction and you have to break it like
me you have to figure out that like actually going outside and standing in the woods is like
real enlightenment and if you're online you're a loser actually uh i mean i would probably i
would touch on all these i think i would touch on all these things that you've mentioned um
yeah fair fair enough okay next one oh it's just one image um it's it's munchy saying purple is
literally such an ugly color i mean i don't know what the i don't know what the context of uh this is
i mean why would you say purple is such an ugly color that's so dumb i mean i guess it's kind of
funny how munchy would say it because he's a rowdy and killers and rowdies grouties kill
killers and killers kill rowdies they don't like each other you don't like purple i get it i get it
um next one is another image link from ibb.co that's an outside the box choice for an image
hosting website let's look at it does anyone have any questions okay career day does anyone have
any questions about being an artist comic artist how much money do you make have you ever had a
useful job don't robots make comics now what would you do if your drawing hand got mangled
does anyone have any questions that won't make me cry on the drive home ha ha ha ha
good one artists poor art worthless ai makes art even more worthless
what would you do if your drawing hand got mangled i mean drawing hand got mangled that one's fair
the other the other three are true don't robots make comics now the answer is just no
because uh nobody's ever made a good ai-generated comic like a painting maybe a comic no except
except of course for um that one about the hand drawn boyfriend dating his ai girlfriend
that's the only one that's uh that's good and the only one that ever will be good actually
uh okay next one is called ben's annual reminder get a job yeah okay thank you next one is called
the great eight-bit debate three two one go so in episode 342 of the pro crass naters podcast
one person called in into the voice mills with a little like b-mo sounding ass like ai-generated
voice talking about ai art and i'm sorry but like the message was really really annoying um
first of all they go off and they say that people who are like complaining on art station about
like ai art they're just like looking out for their own job security and they're going against
progress who are completely disregarding the fact that like all the current ai models that
produce ai art are completely based on stolen artwork from all across the internet which like
immediately go fuck yourself for saying that and then on top of that they go with the nonsensical
point that like oh you know like it's democrat it's democratizing art because you see uh you
know normally you would be limited by money in order to you know for instance recording you
know for musicians you would have to buy record recording equipment in order to like record and
now with with ai music the shit you wouldn't have to do that yeah of course of course that's
you're right you know we're completely removing the process of having to do anything is is
absolutely the solution to needing money for recording equipment instead of just fucking i
don't know just democratizing access to recording equipment fuck you
hmm i think i agree i mean uh hmm it's kind of uh hmm what point what what are the salient points
that i can comment on in this voicemail um okay the the thing about uh the thing about like most
ai is being based on stolen art uh i i that seems true to me but i've i've heard people
more and more okay there was a video by shat diversity that i didn't i admit i didn't watch the
whole thing but i started watching it and he was art he was saying he was saying pro ai and now
you remember that i am amenable to the idea that that ai art can be a an okay thing under the right
circumstances but not that is not the case if the ai if it's like stolen okay if now all right i
guess i guess here's he was saying he seemed to be saying it's not stolen or if it is stolen
oh it's not their fault because they didn't know they were stealing oh they just stole by accident
it wasn't on purpose and that sounded fucking stupid to me um but i think there was a point
raised that made me ponder and it was like okay okay okay a lot of these a lot of websites
i think there are there are websites where when you post art i think sometimes you post under the
understanding that anything you post is considered creative commons it's it enters into the realm
of creative commons and i'm not an expert but i think what that means is that other people are
allowed to use it in certain capacities uh maybe in in just non-commercial capacities i don't know
but i i guess if you i think i think maybe ai has changed the game a little bit and that maybe now
maybe people would have been okay posting content under creative commons that now they
feel that they don't want to do that because uh ai might take advantage of it and i feel like that's
not necessarily ai's fault and i feel like maybe it's not fair to hold that against it because
like if it if it's available for use in that way i feel like ai ought to be able to take advantage
i don't see any reason why i shouldn't so i don't know if there's some if and if ai's are built in
a way that uses stuff that's already like legally and and and in every sense you know ought to be
available for people's use um then i think it's good and i don't know if there's any ai's to do
that because like at the end of the day honestly someone who someone who makes ai an ai program
or whatever would probably like to claim that and i genuinely i don't trust the the tech bro
sort of dude who makes a thing like this or what or whatever i don't trust them to tell me oh yeah
it doesn't use any stolen assets everything it uses creative comments because like of course
they would say that and frankly the way that i know that it would shake out is that they would
just say that because they know that it's what they're supposed to say and the onus would be on
anyone else to prove that they are wrong so someone would have to it's like it's like innocent and
it's innocent until proven guilty but in like a bad way like really they should have to demonstrate
that like yeah this thing is not stealing art this thing is operating in a in a in a legal way
there's a there's a fine line i guess i feel like if um they they i'm getting a little bit
i'm thinking multiple thoughts at once here um they would have to they would have to
i feel like they should have to prove and demonstrate that like yeah my system does not steal
art my system only uses stuff that's creative commons my stuff does not uh infringe on anyone's
but i think there's not plagiarism there's not a plagiarism machine i feel like they
should have to demonstrate that first but i know that in practice they would just say that it's not
until someone proved that it was and that only then would anyone be like oh this is bad because
because you know if if art theft is the main complaint against ai art now people are going
to start saying well mine's the one that doesn't do that actually does it is that true who knows
they're not going to be honest about it um
all right i i i guess the long and short of it
i guess the long and short of it is there there are certain cases i'm i'm i'm i'm never okay with
plagiarism but i am okay with theft under certain circumstances under certain cases
and so for me to for me to give like an ai my thumbs up i would have to be like really sure
that it steals only to the only to the extent and only in the cases that i think that's cool to do
and i just don't have any confidence even even if i am assured of that i don't have any confidence
in the people that would be doing the assuring uh so yeah i have to i have to just i have to mistrust
it uh so i think i'm with you on that one okay next one is called final rant i promise three two one
go and then one other thing too the this might be a little bit more of a controversial opinion
that i have uh that not everyone agrees with and if they don't that's fine but like for me honestly
like if you have some kind of creative idea some kind of idea for a video game and artwork a song
a painting whatever you have some kind of idea that you want to see right and you
put that into an ai in order to generate it in order to see it provided the ai is created ethically
you know uh that's fine you know you want to you want to create it you want to look at it good
i don't care to see it like i genuinely don't care about the creative output of people who
just want to make the ai make it for them i don't care because you don't care that's the problem
you don't care enough about this idea to even fucking work at making it what this these are
just the types of people who are like dude what if the game was like skyrim but it was also like gta
that would be fricking epic and then they don't know how to code they don't know how to do art
they don't know how to do voice acting they don't know how to do fucking anything they just want
to see the idea being created and then like be rewarded for it they're a fucking idea guy that
that's what this this fucking ai craze feeds a idea guys who don't know how to do fucking anything
and i am not interested in the least bit in their creative output yeah yeah in in theory i can imagine
like oh what if what if there's a guy who's using ai generation to any and he's generating like
oh really cool wacky things that like nobody's ever seen before what if the computer
is spitting out like some really weird honestly like some of the most interesting ai stuff tends
to be when it goes wrong and you see like the faulty decision making on of a computer on display
and you see like the the problems the unique the unique ways that a computer can fail to understand
how to how to put an image together or or to fail to understand a request usually when a when
an ai generates an image that is what the person controlling the the the prompts and stuff wanted
it just it just looks like a painting and yeah i've i've never i've never seen and i don't think
i ever will see an image that like ooh an artist an artist could never have painted this unless it's
like the computer just the computer fucked up in a way that like a human just wouldn't think
a human wouldn't think like this uh what jumps to mind is that image maybe you saw of the
it's the woman it's like a big titty anime girl but it's like her it's a big titty anime girl
but coming up she's got huge cleavage right but then you look up at the cleavage and the cleavage
becomes uh her legs and like her legs uh uh and like her an entire other woman is like sticking
out of the neckline because it interpreted the cleavage of the boobs as like the the cleavage of
like the the the the the crotch and and the legs pressed together and so it like made these this
weird fucking chimera um and that's awesome you know yeah i don't know in in theory if someone
were had a really great had really great aesthetic taste and they were generating images that looked
really amazing and they had like lots of visual ideas going on in them ideas that i hadn't seen
before and i looked at them and i go oh interesting oh interesting you know that's fine and all in
practice that's not what i see out of out of the uh the ai people at at best they generate things
that look like somebody painted them uh which is uh fine um next one is uh another image or link
okay and this guy included the http and i appreciate that because that means i don't have to type it
hey sugar tits i heard your dog jin artist ghosted you i'll draw one for you for only 500
dollars i'm superius to the previous guy because i don't watch anime um is this like a pun on dojin
oh it's because it's because ed ghosted it's because ed ghosted on the uh the thing yeah um
kaijuku is working on it uh very slowly uh but he did show me a little bit a tiny little bit of
progress there's literally like three pages left to draw and he has drawn like it took him like a
month to draw like a quarter of one of them so you know we're going we're going next one is uh
whatever it's another image i'm ben saint yeah this was my my legendary banger i'm ben saint tweet
and then michelle is that supposed to impress me and then i guess this is me and her
and i'm a chad and she's a a coffee drinking emo boy yeah true i guess definitely true um next one
is another uh thing uh let's look at it the boy i don't know yeah makes like being
this is good this this fucking rules man uh yeah this this is this one's 10 out of 10
munchie sneering uh that's good that's good shit that's what they call the good shit all right i
appreciate this one i appreciate this one a lot okay next one next one is called follow up to not
my voicemail three two one go so a few months ago someone asked ben if gib was his best friend
and while he said no i was surprised he did not mention munchie at all is munchie not your
best friend inquiring minds would like to know i i yeah i don't think i would say that i have like
a best friend that is my best friend that i would place on like a higher tier than any of my other
friends i'm sorry uh yeah i mean me munchie hang out would i say that like would i definitively
say like oh yeah i'm better friends with munchie than i am with gib not not really no i wouldn't
uh yeah yeah man i don't believe in i don't believe in the hierarchy
i'm a communist uh next one is called i thought i fixed it sincerely three two one go
am i the tin can man
then that that's kind of sick i'm a character base the tin can man i think you are the tin can man
tom you're tom right i think your name's tom pretty sure you are the tin can man yeah
this is good congratulations uh next one is called get them tiger three two one go
the fire tail guy is gonna make another thing honestly pretty cool what are you
who are you talking about who is the fire tail guy i have no the fire tail guy i have no idea
who that is i'm sorry uh next one is called this is so sad can we eat this is so sad can we eat
our green gurns uh okay there's a youtube link i usually don't look at youtube links but
just for you let's let's see what what is this
okay it's it's the it's the you've got to eat your greens song with the major is
mad the the the ocarina of time song okay his voicemail three two one go i was replaying ocarina
of time and i i i walked in the kakariko village and all that was running through my head was
you've got to eat your greens and i just gonna take it i started sobbing the memories of the
yesteryears of pcp all came flooding back and they'll never be the same again
yeah yeah man nothing's ever the same
i'm glad i'm glad it made you cry uh okay uh good good one uh
kakariko village yeah that's that's that's the that's the song
okay i'm almost done with this nightmare um next one is called uh will i will i even
hit an hour will i even hit a goddamn hour on this episode uh might even be i'm not um maybe
next one is called cake uh well there's an image and a voicemail so i'll look at the image first
what would we got here it's that girl from that webcomic that no one has yet told me what the
webcomic is uh holding a cake time for some k it's time for some cake my dear it's time for
yep yep yep yep uh let's listen to the voicemail uh three two one go
attention everybody celestia swat swat fed bare wobbly ass 50 kilometers away to the left
go that direction you will see the mountains of celestia great bare wobbly ass
i want it yeah i i understand i understand what you're saying uh i do want it it's good um
um thanks for noticing uh won't somebody please listen somebody's gotta know what
this fucking webcomic is okay somebody tell me every week that goes by i just hate myself
more and more because i can't i should know what this fucking comic is called i saw it years ago
i'm something awful
okay next one is called brony pavia lombardi italy three two one go
some bastard in the comments probably already pointed this out but i don't read those oblivion
i appreciate that the backing track to homo genius was europe brony's diamond dogs i haven't
thought about that song in ages europe beat brony's diamond dogs i mean okay i know who europe
brony is i might not have recognized the song uh well thanks for pointing that out uh
brony pavia lombardi i assume that's a real place uh you know good good uh good you know
an informative uh informative comment uh appreciate it um okay well that's uh that's the last uh
that's the last uh that's the last voicemail we're done uh i everyone i'm sorry i apologize
profusely for making you listen to me um again but i had no choice i had no choice if i don't
listen if i don't put out a procrastinator's podcast we already miss christmas we miss the
christmas weekend and if i miss another one squatters writes kick in and brad garling has
gets the channel back i'm sorry so i have to keep i have to keep on the ball with it i have to
release content even if everyone hates it in its dog shit as as obviously is the case this week
you gotta understand there's legal we gotta set legal precedent um all right but i've said all
i have to say this week um read one piece catch up on one piece and then uh we will talk maybe
we'll have two chapters to talk about next week um for some of that bonus shit that i can't talk
about that i had to cut from this episode um become a patron patreon.com such that procrastinators
get access to what like 52 53 former episodes and a new one at some point in the future um
um we will we will be doing some bonus stuff when the last of that rad con shit is finally done
which i can't i can't exactly say how soon but much like one piece ending we're closer to it
happen we're closer to it happening than we are to the beginning uh hopefully closer than that
that's that's probably still years away i probably shouldn't make that comparison
um i think that's everything i have to say um um um thanks for listening i'm done i could call it
yep okay uh goodbye and uh see you next week peace