I was like, oh cool, these guys seem really dedicated to their story, they're really creative,
and they have a whole team, and they do a lot of stuff, and I respect this, I like it a lot.
But then, I went and I found their other Patreon, and it was for the porn version.
The canonical porn stories that happen with the same characters in the same thing, and I was like, oh, oh dear.
I don't, I guess I just don't respect it as much.
Hello everybody, and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I'm your host, not best guy ever, Tom Oliver!
Wow!
Already an improvement.
And we're here today to talk about some shit that we don't like, but we fucking hate,
but today we also have with us, Mumkey Jones!
Hey everybody, it's me, the deep-voiced, leather soothing sounds of Mumkey Jones.
I'm scared, the Davoo!
I got my standing mat ready.
Ben Saint.
I'm here to take a shit on all the pieces of garbage on the internet today.
I can't wait, and the responsible one keeping us all on track, hopefully, the Hippocrite.
No, that's not me at all. That's that you got that wrong. That's the wrong description. Okay. What do you want to be then?
When you go up, okay?
You're on the right track, and now you're probably thinking but PCP
Didn't you already do this topic before?
Good question, viewers.
I'm glad you're paying attention, but it's well the answer is welcome to
creators we hate part two
The day of recording this today is
International podcast day. This is a thing that apparently exists Twitter told me so so and Twitter doesn't lie
So what better things to do on international podcast day than to revisit a topic?
We've already beaten to the ground and just
Accept our nature as human beings to just thrive on hatred and things that make us angry
So that's what we're doing today more things that we hate
But before we start another announcement that coincides with
International podcast day is that we finally did it and by we I mean me because no one else did it, but me I spent five
grueling hours getting the PCP up and updated completely on iTunes and Google
For all of you fucking peasants use an Android phone everyone's instead of an iPhone
Everyone who has been requesting that we put it on iTunes go you can now go and there it's there
We do that right now. It's there right now every single episode correctly formatted with description
It took way too long, but I did it. I bit the bullet for the team as
There it is as someone who's never used iTunes and legitimately doesn't know
I'm what I want to ask this question for the sake of people who are maybe retarded like me
How do you find the PCP on iTunes? Well, it's a huge pain in the ass
Basically, what you have to do is first you have to install iTunes
Which is like basically knee-capping your computer for life unless you're a dirty Mac user
But if you can get past that first step if you install iTunes definitely uncheck the automatic updates
Otherwise, it'll never leave you alone
Okay, but you just go to the podcast section and you there's a search field you search for the pro crastinators
And it should pop right up. I've tried it multiple times
It has worked. It's the same thing on Google Play music if you're on Android
You just go to the podcast section you search for procrastinators and pops right up along with some other shitty podcasts that we're gonna kill someday and
Yeah, that's that's that's how it works. It's pretty simple unless you're retarded, which I mean some of you out there
I'm sorry. They're just gonna have to consider the audience
Consider the audience we're talking to I gotta say I never wink wink nudge nudge
I never thought I'd see the day. I never thought I'd see this happen. Well, but here we are
The Urban Dictionary definition of hatred
Urban Dictionary defines hatred as the trademark sign of love between two cynics often accompanied by sarcasm and clever insults
What the so true that sounds like me and Ben
Yeah, geez, maybe I've learned something about myself today. It sounds like a home stuck to me. I don't know about that. Yeah
Hussie wrote that um
Who has somebody who they really fucking hate?
It's me it's me. All right, so my
creator that I hate is
He's a pretty big one. He created the universe. It's God
Where do we go from here did young shells and just walk into the room
and
It's probably not what you think but because I see I see God as like the John Tron of deities, you know
Created the universe and he had some pretty good content in like, you know
Yeah back when he was in D is you know just doing all that stuff
But then he sort of fucked off after the Bible and he's he's never been he's really done nothing
He's there's there's been no miracles. There's been no new stories
He really he's just sort of the face of the earth and I works at Bed Bath and beyond, you know
He pulled us just say the same thing
He promised this big like second coming of his son and fucking up everything and you just collected all the followers and their
Money hasn't done shit with it. What it doesn't we've all been funding him this whole time
Just not he's not and he's not even transparent about it. It's somehow he's gaining more followers despite not doing shit
Not a single update on Twitter or anything, man. Do you know how many views the Bible has?
The ad revenue must be holy shit
Here's the here's the real question though. The Bible
Does Google let it be monetized? There's rape. There's murder
There's there's tons of things in there that really shouldn't be advertiser friendly
But seems like it gets a free pass for his like history of like, you know, creating everything. What a nepotism
Yeah, I don't can't say I'm a fan that this that just makes me hate it more, you know
It's nepotism and it's the appeal to authority the divine authority
We do
That was um, yeah, that's it. That's all I got I couldn't think of you wanted to do this episode
You're like, I got this great got this great yucker for the beginning. They're gonna be chucking and yucking all night
I was just gonna duck out for the rest. I've done his part collecting his check. He's good to go
Well, I've got a YouTube creator that I think yeah, let's bring it back down to the realm of mortal men who we can actually
Really sink our tea to figure it out. Literally. It's a recent event that I think should piss all of us off equally
Maybe maybe not a maybe not the divus in the bends
But I think the rest of us will have a bone to pick now. It's no secret that I hate great a under a
But typically it's just in the past. It was because I didn't respect his content and I thought it was unfunny and lazy
But boy, howdy, he made a new update video and he said one of the dumbest things
I think I've ever heard and it made me go from distaste to actual pure hatred
His excuse for not making videos for months was that he was depressed and at one point in the video
He says it is a literally impossible to be funny
When you're depressed and he said that as if it was a statement of fact and that just got my blood boiling so much
Instantly you think of Robin Williams Jim Carrey
Tom Oliver
Hippocrates did you throw all these funny guys who are cripplingly depressed?
So I'd how can he how can he put that statement out there and not expect massive ridicule and hatred, you know
I guess when you have all that ad revenue
You can you just don't have to dig deep and actually try to be creative under pressure
You just use coast for a while. You see, I don't think the problem was that he was depressed
I think the problem is just that he can't be funny in general. So he needed the excuse
It's literally impossible for to be funny under any circumstances let alone. Yeah
Doesn't matter how he's feeling. I I the first few like the very first few great a under a videos
I stumbled upon before he was like a big drama guy and I thought you know, that's that's kind of funny
It's like sort of observational humor, but
Since he's like he's just I I stopped following his following him since and he's like he's just stopped being funny
He stopped being creative or interesting. I wonder whether those are initial videos were just copied from something
Like sketch or sketch sketches that he's seen. I've heard he's a big douchebag
Yeah, I don't know much about him
I mean, I don't know. It's it's I didn't watch a lot of great a under a but it felt like a formula that wasn't gonna last and
I guess
that was correct because here we go and
He's really it was it was what I want to bring this up ended by jumping on the drama train
He's kept it. He's kept the lifeblood pumping
With that with that development
delicious, yeah, and and the reason why I bring this up is not because you know
Like we don't need to dissect his content because we can all agree like you okay
Maybe it was better back in the day, but it went to shit
But just like this one specific thing about depression is what really put him on my radar of hatred
And that's that's all I wanted to say about it
I hadn't heard that that he said that I made I think you maybe tweeted it or something. Yeah, I was just like
Because I was thinking about that when you tweeted it and I was like mmm
Cat is like that. There's probably something to that in like there's a certain type of humor that you can't do when you're depressed
I didn't look into it at all. I don't think he did either, but it's not impossible
It's just like when you're depressed everything's more difficult
So I think most of like all the comedians that I have as my favorites and all the ones I respect are very open about
Being depressed you have like a I mean Greg Gerardo back in the day before he fucking died from overdose
Louie CK George Carlin like all these guys were pretty fucking depressed
And I think it fueled their humor and made them funnier because it gives you a
I think a more unique and more comedic outlook on life when you wish you were dead
Yeah, it's weird. It's it's like he I think it's like the impossible part like it was impossible for him to make content because he was sad
doesn't
Work you can't just say that and have it be okay. You're you're just it's just a pity party
He's trying to throw yeah, and he's trying to write off all comedians as oh, I bet they're all you know mentally fine
And just because I personally could not make content because I was too lazy and depressed
That's that's all I gotta say about great a under a let's move on if somebody right so, you know beginning this podcast
I'm like, oh geez
I mean the only one I really have to think of immediately is I hate everything but we all talk about him a lot
Really my main problem with I he is that he has obnoxious editing
But in a way that I feel like no one else would agree with me
So I don't know how to make that whole rant coherent
But I was just scrolling around YouTube trending to look for other people and I was reminded of someone so immediately
Anyone who does parody songs song parodies, but we're like the the parody is that it's like a review of the song that they're parodying
so I believe the most prominent example is
The key the key of awesome we're like they do song parodies, but like it's not like its own
Idea, it's not like a weird out parody where like they take the lyrics and turn it into like a different song with different meaning with a different point
It's like it's like it's like a song about the song that it's a parody of and it always makes like some snarky points
I don't think I've ever seen something like that, but I can try to imagine
Is it like that they're just replacing words and saying it in like a slightly snarky sarcastic way
fucking obnoxious is what they are
Because it's like it's like God they have one that's a parody of bad romance, right?
And it's just they're like a but do it but like they change the melody it's supposed to be bad romance
But I guess for copyright reasons they change the song. I'm like, well, what's the fucking point?
I guess it's supposed to be a stylistic parody of Lady Gaga, but it's obviously trying to be bad romance
And this was you know several years ago when that song was new but then like it's not just Lady Gaga
Lady Gaga is in the song. It's a woman pretending to be Lady Gaga again. It's a parody, but it's the same fucking thing
I know but then there's also a lot of bizarre
I know I know I know but like then there's also I believe it the key of awesome is mostly two people a guy and a girl
So there's also Lord Gaga, right? What the fuck is the point of that?
So she's like I'm Lady Gaga and this guy comes in the I'm Lord Gaga. I'm like, okay
How is that a fucking parody of of Lady Gaga?
The only way I could imagine it would be is if there was a twist that they're both the same person because Lady Gaga has a dick
Because that's a joke from 2009, right? I don't fucking know. It's not played up that way and like also it's film
It's the joke supposed to be that they're saying I'm Lady Gaga something like that, but then like no they play
Look isn't Lady Gaga so much like this. Yeah
I think it's not even that I think that the joke is her name is Lady Gaga and the male equivalent of a lady is a Lord
Yeah, not terribly insightful and like also the music video
The music video is like filmed in like some random fuck-off hallway
That's like all white because obviously they want to look like bad romance the music video where it's all white
But like they obviously didn't have to budget to make a studio look all white
So it's some hallway and like some factory or something that they were able to find and get permission to film in so it's
Really fucking awkward because it's all filmed in a goddamn hallway just to get it to look white
And it was constantly distracting on top of the entire entire fucking premise of it
Just being weird and they have lyrics like oh doing weird stuff
You know, I believe there's literally lyric making up this shit as we go along like oh wow
You're totally parodying. You're just telling us what Lady Gaga style is okay. I gotcha and like they have like another
parody of like one other one direction songs and like as it goes on
it's like about how certain people react to the song and then uh
Then it also talks about how the one direction song is similar to the Backstreet Boys' famous song and so they're like oh, yeah
You didn't think we'd notice that did you but like this is woven into the lyrics of the parody
It's so fucking confusing the key of awesome as a parody of um of E.T. by Katy Perry
And it's like the whole premise of the song is about the fact that Katy Perry is trying to make a song
But then Kanye West is in the song and so like Katy Perry is singing to the melody of E.T.
Con yeah, why are you here? This is my fucking song. Don't intrude on it something like that, right?
Like by the end they talk about how like Katy Perry just made the song for the check or something or something fucking like that
I'm just like what's the goddamn point of these things. I hate them, you know
I hate I hate it when there's like a parody but like there's not like a strong premise to it
It just makes me cringe. It's what I call hashtag conceptual cringe
You know it sounds like it like Jen they're putting in like generic
Oh, celebrities just do things for the money like that's the joke. Yeah, it's not got anything to do with Katy Perry
Delivering the mail just for the money. What a fucking
Yeah, I find it to be like the worst the worst parody people like you know at least fucking
Rucka Rucka all these got like his own like personality and funny jokes that I like and he talks about 9-11
Yeah, but like
Yeah worst fucking parody people. It's really the um
It's just the natural byproduct of any medium or industry getting saturated with fucking cash
People just jump in with no ideas, but plenty of fucking budget and props. You know what I mean?
There's just I remember one time seeing like um it was fucking what's the one?
What's the one republic song about shooting stars and no more counting money and shit?
What's that one fucking stars a fucking one republic song? You would not believe your eyes
Yeah, something like that right. Yeah, of course. Yeah, fucking obviously. Yeah, definitely. You got it. Monkey, but like, okay
It's that song. It's that song
Like the lyrics are all the same, but it's performed by Disney villains
But like some of the lyrics have changed so it's like it's like it's like a live-action
Interpretation of some of the Disney villains in a music video and they're singing it and even King Scarra's in there
Just a guy dressed like a fucking King Scarre and I'm like, okay
It's like a cornucopia of terrible ideas. Yeah, and I'm like it's coalescing into cringe
Yeah, and it's like super produced probably a few thousand dollars at least probably like a studio that you know is actively producing shit
But they're like, okay, what are we gonna make this time?
Yeah, just there's just like there's no strong like premise there
So yeah, I hate those people and of course they get like millions of views and are super successful and you want to shoot
Oh God one last thing I'm like fucking there's like I remember my girlfriend playing this this like
Combination a medley of fucking maroon 5 just a maroon 5 medley made by some generic youtubers
But like a full music video and everything, you know
It like is mostly centered around that fucking whistle jingle from moves like Jagger
And I was just disgusted by the thought that people care that much about maroon 5
This reminds me of I think his name is Brock Baker. Does that sound familiar to anybody? Not I
So he he does a similar thing
But like he'll he'll sing a popular song but in the voice of like a hundred different characters
And he's a really talented voice actor
And I think it's like the right version of what you're describing because it's just like him standing in front of the microphone
And then each lyric is a different
Performing like a different character. So it's impressive and it's not like overly produced or like it's not trying to be a parody
So I think that's if you're gonna do something dumb like this
That would be the good way to do it, but we're what you're describing sounds horrifying bad. Yeah
All right, I have somebody who just who's a brand new creator
That's fucking horrible, and I hate it and I'm disgusting that exists
Susan wasiske. I don't know how to pronounce her last name. She is the CEO of YouTube
Oh, no, and she started a YouTube channel last week
Oh, no, oh my and and and it's probably the most disgusting thing ever because it's like the videos like titled something dumb like
How do I make videos on YouTube or something?
It's like I asked a bunch of my friends and so it's just like her saying like
I'm gonna start making videos and then it's like these are the people who are gonna help me and then it's all these like
It's like the rock and like a bunch of other celebrities talking about like, oh, yeah, we're youtubers
We know how to make you two videos and then there's like Instagram models and vinyls
I'll giving her advice and it's super just like corporately produced and
disgusting and the most horrific thing of all time and it's just like
Everybody hates you right now, and this is the time you decide to try and like
Reach out public facing like I'm just gonna sit here and have fun guys
It's like no get your shit back in the office and fix all the things that suck balls right now
What is wrong with you Tom this is an interesting scenario because you've seen it none of us have
I think we should all try to guess what advice she got and you can confirm if we get it, right?
Because I'm guessing I'm guessing somebody tells her just be yourself on camera and and the audience will follow through
Absolutely, that is one of the points
Anybody else got to guess?
Get a good microphone probably
I don't think that was mentioned, but you know real advice you'd actually should use
So so okay, I know I know what they said they said go to the the use the YouTube creator help tools in YouTube and
And you know they're not shit use them. I don't remember that being there
But oh they probably said upload constantly they probably upload as much as you possibly
Said you got it you got to be consist consistencies the most important thing just vomit out that content every day
Yeah, and here's anything we'll do this is the thing that I'm gonna be really
Really interested to see is cuz I I have ad block
But like is this video monetized and if it is of course fuck you
Because like there's only so many ad
To play on videos and so the CEO is gonna take ad revenue from the people whose site she
Like who just posted the light counter and it's 7,000 thumbs up 33,000 thumbs down
7,000 people are either working for Google or need to be executed immediately or they're 12 years old
I have to like from now on in my in my life when I see something stupid on YouTube either like a high
Like or just like bars are stupid comments. I just always
Assume it's a 12 year old cuz what else could it be? I can't imagine a real
Those 12 year olds are the ones who are watching your diary of a wimpy kid video and make yeah, that's where that's where I'm seeing all these likes and comments at
Dude fucking have the top voted comments on that video or is this video demonetized, too?
I mean right it's it's it's it's funny once guys, but don't don't beat a dead horse
That would be that would be fucking hilarious if her video got caught as like not suitable
Oh, man, but she would never admit I hope I hope everyone flags the video and yeah
I wouldn't be fucking surprised if shit loads of people like try to flag the video
But obviously like they're just gonna unflag, you know, the you know, you people like automatically
She has CEO shields and just bounces off like
She's got mod power. Yeah, her channel just gets no no strikes at all. It's whatever
Yeah, so I hate her
Because it's just horrible and terrible and disgusting and I can't believe I'm gonna I'm gonna keep watching and see what other cringy shit
That's there and just watch this site continue to fall apart
It's gonna be great. She have right now. I didn't even look I hope zero
It's got to be at least 40 you never know
The board of directors is all following
yep
Um
Well, uh, I'll go am I last am I the last one? Yeah, we could probably go around another time
This is gonna be a very short. Yeah, we keep going until we got a channel more hate than that
I mean, yeah, well, I got a I got a general one. It's not about anyone specific. That's that's fine
We can all jump in then go what what I the
just in general the thing that makes me hate anyone is
Just if they're it's just that they're overappreciated
Even if I like what they do then like if I see that they get more appreciation for it than I feel they deserve
I hate them. So just anybody that violates your your your personal
You know such such such beloved content creators such as Digi, bro
You have to have absolute hacks
And I don't I don't even think did you would disagree
He's said before that he thinks it's weird that he makes more money than like
Animators that make anime so I don't know but but but they're they're small they're small fry
They're small fish in this pond we're talking about someone like like Jim Sterling who I like and like I like his content
But he makes like he makes like 12 with like $12,000 a month on patreon for like he's been stuck at like 11,000 since forever
I think it's like 10,000 thing. I I know I know a pretty decent place to be fucking stuck
Yeah, yeah, I wish I was stuck there
I mean, that's how much I make in a year working full-time. So I I see something like that
I see something like that and like the good will that I have because I like the things he has to say just
Drain's away and it's left with nothing but resentment in its place
Just so yeah, take some solace Ben and the fact that he's gonna be dead in like six months
That's going good. Oh, is that true? No, but I mean well could be I mean yeah
Is clearly not
Not designed for longevity. Let's put it that way. He'll he'll be crushed under the weight of his himself
Is he a big fat?
You've never seen a gym story video the gym position. I only follow like five YouTube channels
Everybody keeps saying oh, mom. You are you ripping off age three age? Like I don't fucking watch that
I don't even know what it like I know what it is, but I have never watched the video
So stop fucking saying I rip off all this shit you you're definitely doing the right thing
There's just too much shit and it takes away from time like I'm gonna go watch Fargo season three
I'm not gonna watch fucking age three age three productions, you know
We could we could all learn something from this attitude just so we have to I was going to say
Another another example that that girl on patreon who does the art
Sakee me chan sakee me chan like yeah her art's real nice her arts real nice and everything
Is it worth like fucking $50,000 a month? Of course not fuck fuck right off
It's just like it's she all she does is she does the same like like
busts of popular animation characters and then behind the patreon is them without a shirt on or with tits hanging out
And you have to pay for that and that's how you get $50,000 a month
I think I think she offers like you know you get to see the process and you see like the sketches and like you
Maybe you can see like videos of her drawing them and stuff
So it's like it's kind of like disguise. It's kind of like sort of educational like ooh learn how she does it
But like it's also like a cam girl where the tit you're seeing are not hers installed on her body
But drawn by her hand, which is just as hot. Oh
There was that there was that girl there was that girl who who I don't know what her name was
But she was like some not particularly well-known artists, but she like she got in some financial
Trouble something in the game grumps like tweeted her around and like fucking like help this girl and they did and now she's got like a
Whole bunch of money on patreon and she and she kind of like started doing like some fucking quote like erotic photography on the side
She's like this chubby girl who like post-cropics and yeah
Yeah, yeah, so that's the lead of it. That's the monster. That's the kind of monster that's created by situations like this
What I'm gonna milk digi bro to get that sweets push that we all need to start making a million dollars
Soon I'm I'm calling the police
I'm waiting for I'm waiting for his next stream and I'm gonna swat him. We're gonna swat
You know come to think about it in general
I often find myself being find myself with a lot of distaste for like people on the internet who like do art
But like disconnected drawings. There's not like something big and ambitious. They're doing like a big old webcomic
It's actually good and stuff. You know what I mean? Yeah, like
Something that annoyed related to that
People that yeah people that have like OCs and they'll they'll draw like they'll draw like fan art of their own OCs
And they'll call them OCs and then but there's no story to go with it
And it's like yeah, like what's like in general people who like just do a lot of pictures
Like if I really like your art and like your attitude and I can be a fan of you
You know, there's there's a PCP fans who do great art and I love them
But I just feel like when they start becoming like personalities and like becoming famous and stuff
It's like are you really doing enough to justify that? Are you like weaving an incredible artistic experience?
I can change my life to justify you being someone who is revered. You know what?
I mean, I don't know like yeah, you know going wait. Can we switch topics to another person or are you not done yet, Ben?
No, no cool. So talking about art people, right?
I I was looking at the trending tab and I see there's an odd ones out video. Do you know?
Do you guys know the odd ones out?
I'm not from no style of video where it's basically just any other kind of YouTube video
We're like you just talk about a fucking thing, right? You just talk about a thing any topic at all, but it's like drawn, right?
So it's basically like desperate technique to justify my art major
Technique number 375, right? It's like well, I gotta make YouTube videos
But obviously animation isn't fucking gonna ever work on YouTube again
So instead you just sort of have like a slideshow of like your art to like tell us to like make a point, right?
Or like have a rant but instead of like Google images
It's like you fucking tablet all of your images, right?
And instead of just having an OC that stands perfectly still that you cut to you actually kind of sort of
animate the OC, right? So like the I've seen some of those things that that they're so
Like banal and like and then I this is the first crush
Yeah, this is me and I look like a cute little cartoon. Yeah, that's why you click
But instead of being a vlog they just kind of draw a bunch of stuff here. This is what happened in my life
Yeah, I don't I oh, but it's so relatable. Yeah, so I like that
I just don't understand how it even achieves critical mass like that, right?
Yes, like something yeah, and generally related to that is like people like owl turds and like the four panel so relatable comics
Yeah, and how those just blow up everywhere. So like the odd ones out
It's really just because a lot of people who consume that stuff are like
Teenagers and they just want somebody to say I know what you're feeling because you know parents don't do that
It's just young young people who haven't heard it before the thing that I've always found interesting about people who make content like that
It's like how can that feel satisfying?
You know because right when you think about it the people who like that content they have no they don't care about you
They don't care about your vision. They like their content because they see themselves in it
So so when they like your work, they're just it's just an ego trip like it's just like so they just see themselves in the work
And that's why they oh this this is me
But like you the artist and the content itself is completely
Substitutable with anything else they would find like you're not you're not building anything for yourself the minute you stop doing that
No one's going to care anymore, and it just feels like such a fragile thing to build I
Think like the people who make that sort of content aren't
Clever enough to realize that that's true, and they will just see all this praise and think oh they love me and they'll feel fine with
That well no that was what I had in mind, but of course I guess it's all true
But okay, so the odd ones out specifically I posted a screw I posted an image of like the OC for that channel in the chat
It's like this big tubby white and by white
I mean like actual white guy with a big old mouth mouth red pants, and he presents himself
You know the characters all like I'm a cutesy you know you know and I get it
You know I've drawn OCs of myself, and I just draw it all like cutesy and simplistic whatever I get that kind of fucking ego thing
Right, but like the guy who voices him you know the real guy does not convince me that he's like a lovable tubbable guy
Right I heard about him during the fucking cool cat controversy because it wasn't just I hate everything who got his videos
Fucked with this guy also did a cool cat review now like the I hate everything review of cool cat
I have not seen the I hate it the odd ones out review of cool cat
I never bothered to see them, but one thing that was really telling to me during the the daddy Derek
Controversy is that you know he didn't delete every fucking video review of his channel
He didn't ever go after YMS directly as far as I know I mean he did like cut ties with him eventually
But like he didn't want to take down YMS's review
But he did want to take down the other guys's reviews even though YMS's review was pretty cutting
But it was respectful and based on what I could tell it seemed like I hate everything and odd ones out
We're not being very respectful to Derek Savage or whatever this fucking that's not savage
I don't know fucking everyone's names are but like I watched odd ones outs review videos talking about the controversy with
Derek that he had and he showed a bunch of fucking emails that
He he and Derek had exchanged with one another, but like it felt like a weird sort of like leak
It felt like he shouldn't have been showing this on the internet
It felt like a violation of violation of privacy and also like the way he wrote some of the emails just seemed like he was being
Addict to Derek and I'm like yeah, like I know legally the laws and you publish emails without permission. That's disgusting
Yeah, it was fucking weird, and I think he had like certain reasons or justifications, but it was fucking weird
He was not convincing me that regardless of his legal us
Justifications did he have like the the etiquette justifications, right?
And so I clicked on another one of his videos where he talked about his time working at Subway, right now immediately
You know every Subway employee I've ever met was addicted. I know where this is going
but like
He talked about like, you know, it was a shitty job and he had like shitty customers and just talked about like various things and like
He
Thoroughly failed to convince me that like all these different little stories
He was talking about and complaining about weren't just him being bad at working at Subway
Like it's always interesting to me when like someone tells me their story about people who pissed them off people who fucked them over and yet
Even though I only heard it from their perspective just by gathering the information
I disagree with their their own conclusions that they weren't in the wrong
Like he just made himself sound like a really shitty Subway employee, but he never like really indicated as much, right?
Just by based on the information he gave me right?
He did not he did not garner any sympathy for me
And yet it was all presented with this big old tubby blobby white Pillsbury Doughboy face and I'm like you're fucking disingenuous
You're just you again. It really comes
Obviously I'm probably wrong, but it comes off to me like oh shit
I have an art major got lots of bills to pay can't make animation for a living
You're not wrong because I've been to Subway several times and I've never seen a good Subway employee
Because yeah, I know it's because it's a shitty job, but also like seriously
There's a fucking thing on the menu, right?
It's a fully made sandwich with all these different ingredients all listed all in the picture
I point to it saying I want that and they go okay. What do you want on it, right?
And I don't know when the message is gonna get up to fucking Subway corporates fat fucking skull
When we point at the image just give us the fucking image and we'll customize it if we choose
Why do we have to come up with how to make the sandwich every time, right?
So yeah, that's the cup that's the best when I tell my mom to make the sandwich. She just fucking does it
I don't got exactly the kitchen and point out every little one on corporate cuckoldry that the odd ones out
participated in so I don't I don't yeah, I don't sympathize with him
But he presents himself a sympathetic, you know, I fucking get it, but yeah annoying
Yeah, I have I mean, it's really I was thinking about like who do I hate? I don't really hate like many people I hate like
Practices that people do and it's really always based around like Ben was saying
Undeserved stuff like if somebody just sucks and they're and they're getting no views, then I'm like, well, I mean all's right with the world
Market has spoken correctly
Wait, so wait wait timeout Tom. So are you do you mean to say that sometimes the market can speak incorrectly?
According to my own subjective interpretation. Yes
But it's the invisible hand. It's like whatever happens
Balls I mean you saying you've never seen have you never seen something monkey that's been like real popular and you're like
I can't believe people like this. I hate it. I wish it would go away
I can see why I personally don't like it
But like I said earlier all every youtuber is 12 years old so I can see why it is popular
Well, that's my whole thing like why I wouldn't like like like at the end of the day people are gonna like what they want to like
And I'm just saying in my personal opinion
They're retarded and so when when my personal subjective
Opinion on what the way things should be and life itself syncs up
There's like there's a quaint little moment of Zen where I'm like, yes, things are okay guys
And then I shouldn't say that the market is wrong. You should be like well, I guess I disagree with the market. I
Was talking about my perspective what the market be not the market
Well, it's like let me let me give another example
It's like when someone when someone gets popular like by accident or like by random chance
Or just because they happen to be in the right place at the right time and thereafter
They they continue to make content that is just like what anyone else makes but because they struck at the right time
Well, the iron was hot their videos can succeed their art can succeed or whatever
Whatever it is where other people's wouldn't even at the same level of quality, you know what I I have I have the guy
I hate the guy who changed or created the YouTube algorithm. I
Hate that guy whoever he is. He created that programmer. It's probably Nate fucking
I
He made it so that he made it so that people can just succeed by you know random chance
And then they don't need to be good and everything sucks and a YouTube sucks
You can only be popular if you make videos about gals or videos about diary of a wimpy kid. Yeah, that's pretty much
Yeah, fucking spider-man and
Can I say that I hate Nate? He's one of the creators I hate
Already I already called him out as one, but yeah, please go on
Not not do you think he's gonna listen to this episode?
Of course nothing to do nothing even to do this content is contents fine
But can I just say the man the man I have a bone to pick with the fact that a couple years ago
We went to a convention and I owed him money and I had to pay him back
He was like I you you're short 80 cents, buddy. I had to pay Palom 80 cents. Oh my god a load of fucking shit
Oh my god
Bastard ever and he's not here so I can say it Nate that was fucking gay. I was not cool with that at all
That's a little weird. It was it was it was disgusting
Yeah, but you know, it's only 20%
20 cents off and just like almost a whole dollar. That's like I'm that was like, you know like two packs of gum
I could have enjoyed it. I'll never have
Yeah, but I don't like I don't care about him I care about me
And then PayPal probably took out 60 cents out of the 80 cents that you sent him probably I do see the gesture
Yeah, I do see you wanting to get back the money you're owed
But when it's such a little amount and it's one of your friends. That's when it sort of gets weird
And the thing was is like this was like like back in like I think it was like 2014
So we had only known each other for a little while. So I was just like, oh, oh, huh, how can I make our relationship even stronger?
I know. Oh, bitch about 80 cents
Sounds like him
Back so yeah, I just I had to get that off my chest. It's been burning in my soul. You can't say that on an episode when he's here
No, I couldn't
Beat you up. Yeah, I can take potshots and not have to feel guilty about it until later. Oh, hey guys
I got some good news
Digi bro, you might have heard of this guy. Did you bro?
He told us in the chat that he is like 16 episodes behind on the PCP so we can talk shit about him too
And he'll never know. Yeah, but the hammer won't come down for another several week
Yeah
We can avoid punishment his is wrathful vengeance. Yeah, we're in the eye of the storm right now
We can do it
Funny though is we could tell the audience like go tweet this thing at Digi and nobody explained
What's going on and then he's not gonna have any idea where it's coming from
We like what should we make everybody tweet at Digi right now something stupid
Pictures of like cantaloupe or something shit like everybody just tweet Digi a picture of a cantaloupe and yeah, the hot new meme
Oh, yeah, that's a good one. Yeah, that's something
And no one tell him why we're what you guys
Yeah fucking mean if you if you fucking tell Digi what's going on
I'm gonna come to your house, and I'm gonna give you a
I want so much on this on the PCP Twitter. No, no, no second chance. You're done. Yeah
This is serious. Yeah, but I'm in charge of the ship now and there's new rules
What I want to see what I want to see is Digi just coming into the chat one day and saying what the hell is up
And for us to just type LOL in caps
Oh
See folks if you let this happen, I will send the screenshot of us all laughing at Digi on the PCP Twitter page
Looking forward to that what a reward
What a good meme. Oh, man. We're so funny on the PCP podcast legendary. We like to have jokes
We like to we just don't do it very often. We like that fill that audience involvement, you know building some rapport
Keep your eye out for the for the PCP cantaloupe t-shirt up for sale eventually
And in the corner of the t-shirt Digi's like sitting there with a confused face like
Hey guys hippo is that the end of your your your thing
Well, I was gonna go a bit more into go ahead. I got a good one, but I'm gonna wait for it. Okay
So I was like yeah the people who
Undeservedly get views and stuff
It's it's always annoying when they're just they're not very good and they don't try very hard and they get everything
They could have ever possibly need but what I you know what I hate specifically is
I had I had something in my head
I'm just trying to just trying to you know trying to figure think of it think of it as I say these words that like mean nothing and I
Really shouldn't have like continued to say one, but I just shoot
Just
Monkey you really hate people who like don't think about what they're gonna say before they say it and then they just start speaking
Bullshit, I thought I could remember it. Oh god. Tom is ruthless tonight. They're in everybody. I'm drunk on power now that Nate's not here
Now I'll kill you guys. Here's the worst type of content creator on the internet again like what Ben was saying
It's like a broad category
People who live stream video games with their girlfriends. Oh god
absolute shame
Disgusting I never watched anything like that, but just the description alone sounds more
That's all I got to say like does anybody want to add to this like DeVoo Ben
Yeah, I got don't do it. I got a thing. I
mean with
With such a practice the only reason a woman should be on a live coming to bring you a sandwich
Not from subway though
They probably made it wrong
She pointed in a picture you didn't understand what was going on I
Will say that like it doesn't matter unless if the person is funny, right?
But here's a thing. I hate the most of all is
Mike and Ryan on Cinemastica. Oh my god. Yes. I hate it. It's it's it's it's it's the same
Principle as bringing your girlfriend on because it's like
because
You know not all girlfriends are like perfect for YouTube if you're a youtuber
You just you don't look for people who are good on camera if you're a youtuber. That's just not exactly how it works
Really so as you know if you have your girlfriend on it's because you're there
They got to be in this spotlight because they fucked someone and basically it's the same thing with Mike and Ryan
This guy I don't say I'm not saying he's fucked. I think Ryan did fuck Mike
But um this Ryan guy is so boring and Mike is not as funny as James
Keep doing it over and over again. Why is he there killer?
Cuz Mike Mike starts off as the like sort of unfunny sidekick to James
And then we make him the main guy and then give him an even unfunnier sidekick
It's like it's two degrees of unfunny sidekick. That's been forced upon us. Yeah
Because like you know I haven't I unsubbed
Cinemastiker I was like phasing in and out of being subbed to cinemastiker for a couple of years like around 2013 or so
But I've officially unsubbed it and stayed unsubbed
It's just like I'll watch the ABG in episodes when I feel like it
Maybe I'll watch a couple other James centric videos when I feel like it right but because I'm not subbed
I don't feel the pressure to get back to it really what it is is the whole cinemastiker wagon just couldn't
Keep it's real it just kind of got fucked in the modern YouTube era of constant upload
It's because James just doesn't do
Constant uploads and he needed to like get some other like shitty people to attach on to himself to like to like pump out more
Content, you know like he sort of treated the the monster madness where he did a one review every day for all of October
Which he came up with in 2007 he sort of treated that like a big special thing that he literally said takes all year to work on
So for him doing consistent content, even if it's short videos doesn't work
So that's what has fucked his channel right and it first started around
2012 when he first went off to film the ABGN movie and he sort of gave the channel keys over to
Mike during that time and Mike made some of his own videos
And this was when Mike finally kind of stepped into the spotlight really up to that point
All Mike had done was play like special characters in certain ABGN episodes in which he was really funny
And he also drew AVGN title cards
So like he was like this guy in the background behind the curtain who helped a lot but in the modern YouTube age
It's like get as many faces on as many videos on as many days the calendar with as much runtime as possible
So James has exhausted all of the fucking people he knows
And yeah, it sucks. I never I've never watched the Ryan videos because as soon as I look at them
I'm like well this guy's obviously never gonna say anything interesting ever
Yeah, but whenever I accidentally click on one like I'm like, oh wait, that's Ryan immediately
You know backspace like I I I've never seen a single second
I mean, I've probably seen one video to see wait
This is like where I discovered that I hate this idea right and ever since then right and like
And like honestly equivalent of having like game grumps be exclusively Barry and some other
Yeah, I'm trying to think of like the least funny game grumps
It was like Susie and Holly only I wouldn't want to watch it
Yeah, the thing right is that is like good
I think the worst thing and I I'm gonna talk about out of my ass at least slightly because I'm like
Seven episodes of AVGN behind which is to say like a year or two behind but like I honestly feel as though
All that extra content them like dilutes the AVGN series in a number of ways first of all the set right originally
The eight the nerd room felt like an area in a show
It felt like this sort of magical property that was put together through the force of storytelling because that's how it was presented
Yeah, but once it's used for like everyday vlogs and all sorts of let's plays and other things
It just feels like this guy's room. It it breaks down the barrier right it makes it less of a character, right?
Yeah, oh, no, this is pretty much all just really me
After all right well, I mean that they don't shoot in that room really that much like they've done okay
Well, they've done a few let's plays and Mike and Ryan is usually just in a white. Okay
Well, I remember originally it wasn't like that maybe in Ryan's house
But like also like James like the nerd as a character like the whole fucking character thing does not work anymore
I mean it still works on a yeah, just not as well because
Everyone knows because you see him being himself so right you see yeah like like for example
Imagine if mr.
Betong did shitloads of vlogs and let's plays his whole like persona that he puts on in
His actual videos that he makes every like couple of months or handful of once or twice a year
Wouldn't work as well because you know this guy way too well like like you know the mr.
Plinkett series has to really bend over backwards to keep like a building up the illusion of the character by like being
Really extensively written having a totally different voice from what's the class that actually sounds like and shit
You know what I mean like they have to like really
Do so much to keep justifying the character and it works fine, but with James versus the nerd
There's not that much difference
It's more like the nerd is just sort of certain cartoony voices James naturally does just all the time rather than some of the time
And it's just like he's wearing a white shirt instead of any random dark shirt, right?
I think actually James probably goes out of his way to wear dark shirts to make himself not look like the nerd
Otherwise he looks to say exact fucking same and like the whole format is just pointless
You know you see people like like Digi and a lot of us who originally just made like regular sized videos before the whole modern YouTube
Eric I kind of got like a fish it officiated
And they would just do regular videos and the occasional podcast
But once Digi started doing vlogs and let's plays constantly
He changed the nature of his main channel content to reflect the fact that like the way that you absorb his
Narrative is different now and like the AVG and format's just kind of dated for that reason and like I you know
There's a part of me that wants to say well James would be able to keep his head above water and make plenty of money without
Falling in line with the modern YouTube format just by doing a patreon
But he's got a wife and kid and probably still debt to deal with after that movie. So, you know, I get it but fuck I
Think AVG and should start wearing a hat because seeing the nerd
Balding is this discerning to me. Oh, I want to see that happen. He heard he's he's project
I mean like for example that there have been little tiny hints or like jokes rather of the idea of that the nerd shows gonna
Be around for a long fucking time and James is gonna get really old like like one time
He pulls off some games already happens right. Yeah. Yeah
Like there's one time where he's pulling games off a shelf to talk about a certain company and they're like now
This company also made this game called raid
2020 maybe I'll review that game in the year 2020 at the time I laughed right now
I'm like, oh, he's really gonna do that. You know, his fans aren't gonna let him forget that shit
He actually who who would have ever thought he'd still be going right back
Right, this was back when we didn't realize that youtubers just never fucking died and never stopped like on rare occasions
They'll stop this isn't like a show forever right doesn't end right just because it's just a guy because it's just a guy in his
Basement, yeah, we can see we can see through the veil right James actually said years ago that he's like
I'm never gonna stop doing AVG and even if it's only one a year because it's so it means so much to me
And I'm like I like that because I want to show to continue forever
But like he even has like a Christmas special episode from 2007 where he like he goes through the fucking Christmas Carol
So he sees his future self and it's like him was like a white wig and a big white beard reviewing the Wii
He's like remember the Nintendo Wii. Yeah, that's what they called it
And so he like plays boogie and like us like
Monkey ball and I'm like dude if if James gets to be like his fucking 60s
And he decides like you know what I'm gonna actually be that version of the character
I'm gonna grow a beard and be like a really fucking old nerd, you know
Yeah, I think he'll I'd still watch he will look I don't think it's and like look the show is still good
The show is not a wash. He actually does update the character like he updates the way the character like
Feels like the the style of anger that he portrays in the videos has evolved tons of times
So the show is gonna last forever. It's never gonna get shit
I am a Joe. It's just the modern format that he has to fit himself through. It's just kind of unfortunate
That's that's the real worst thing ever is is YouTube as a platform
Just becoming more sterile and cookie cutter and allowing flexibility for anything. I've I've fucking I've fucking got it
I've got something that I hate
It's another broad category and this is way fucking broad
This is like literally everyone is guilty of this in some way. Oh, no, and it's
Creators whose art is basically just about themselves or about their art. Yeah, everyone
Yeah, yeah, like people eat that shit up like like when a like when a story gets gets like when a piece of work gets
Real cheeky and like breaks the fourth wall and ooh references this song this thing or says something that only the fan base
Would get his little nod people eat that shit up
But like over you go to go overboard on that shit even a little bit and it's like what the fuck am I watching like this
This thing that I'm consuming is just jerking itself off about how important it is and why do I even bother, you know?
And when someone like yeah, like like drama channels like great a under a or like
I don't know the fucking so many people like like they're they make YouTube videos like vloggers
They're making YouTube videos about the fact that they make YouTube videos
That's the story that I'm watching and it's like oh my fucking God
Fuck do we need Ben you have no fucking idea? I have that I have that like a pevney like weekly if not daily of like
One so you just need to have it once
I don't know what the word doesn't go anywhere that that that moment of morbid
Nihilism I guess because it's like I often am triggered by it by something like something
It's very obvious like a lot of rap which is just like I'm a rapper and I'm rapping and people think about this about my rap
And this is what their reaction to my rap is and this is my response to that reaction
It's like damn like the whole point of rap
Hey, that song is really good. Yeah, I know right. I don't know there's there's a place
There's a place. Oh, yeah, like meta commentary in art
But like when when I feel like what someone does is just comment on themselves. It's like yeah, fuck this guy
Yeah, yeah, so like so fucking so I think about that
But then I think well ultimately everything you tell even if it's a fictional story
It's just things you're thinking about yourself. It's just it's just all you and your ideas
That's just represents you but then like deceptively
Woven into a narrative and ultimately everything's like that and then I think well literally everything not just art
But like you know people selling hot dogs like they're just there to perpetuate the selling of hot dogs walking down the street
You're just there to get somewhere everything everything doesn't have a point like everything is like
Sort of goes into my general philosophy of no matter what life you're living
You're always thinking you're not really living the life of living, you know, like you're not really really living a real life
It's like if you decide to live your life one way
then all you can think about is how you're not living all these other ways that you could be living and
Representing all these other things that you could be representing and ultimately there is no point and ultimately everything is basically life
Is a game of hot potato where you go from one vice to another vice to another thing you have to do and
Until you're dead right and that's like the whole point of life
So the whole point of a YouTube video is just like it's just justify itself
And then you're watching the video and then that's the point and then you go to buy a burger and like the whole point of the
Burger is just to get a burger the burger doesn't enhance your life in any way
But then like you can get money and the money doesn't enhance your life because you buy things that don't enhance your nothing
Nothing, but nothing matters. There you go
So basically you can go from complaining about meta commentary going it immediately escalated to absolute nihilism pretty quickly
So that's kind of why I try to avoid thinking that way, but it's kind of hard, you know
But my but my do I do I do agree that money does not improve your life
And I'll take that burden off your hands if you want to just well
So you don't worry about it anymore
But but I my two points are related because when when I see someone like a vlogger
Who whose whole deal is they just talk about themselves and their life is them making vlogs and it's a big incestuous circle jerk
I see someone like that and then I see someone getting super popular for doing that and getting tons of money on patreon
And I'm like what are these people seeing in this? What are they paying for?
What is that would make Casey Neistat was there was that something else?
I didn't more or less. I don't really know anything about him
But I can like the back when Pokemon go is a thing hippo, you know, but the trainer tips guy
I started watching this vlogger who's the trainer tips guy because he would talk about the game
And I was interested in the game at the time and the dude blew up and he just fucking vlogs now
It makes daily videos about his life playing Pokemon go and people fucking eat it up
And I'm like geez like just like Jim Sterling like I like this guy like I like what he's saying
I don't understand how it fucking can blow up like this. I don't think he deserves this much success from something
So, you know fucking fucking not fucking basic
God damn, it's I mean with trainer tips. It was really just he was the
When it when it came to actually explaining the mechanics of the game and what's you know the updates and everything
He was like the best YouTube channel for that
But then he did like like there were less updates
There was less stuff going on and he just sort of started vlogging and then vlogs became so much of like the part of the video
But it makes me know people got invested in his life because he's I don't know. He's got loads of charizards
He's just I mean he's he plays the game a lot, but he's just regurgitating stuff that like people are posting on the on the on the
Subreddits, he's just regurgitating info that people on the subreddits are posting. I know what the
What is the point? I know the reasoning I think I well
I think what it is is is that like people who watch YouTube generally when it's like a vlog or a let's play
They want to feel the company of another yeah, exactly. I was a friend. Yeah, I want to pretend
I understand like like I'm saying all this I'm saying all this with with the nut
Like I do understand the appeal because like I was watching the video
So I get liking it, but then the fact that like when it then it gets really popular and I'm like, oh fuck this
You know, this is this is what I'm this is the phenomenon. I'm describing in action
You're seeing it right now someone whose content I like then I see it successful and like no
I don't like it anymore. Fuck you buddy. Well, then let me ask you just called being a hipster
Yeah, let me ask you a question just to gauge which which vlogs are okay to which ones aren't
Okay, sure a vlog about going to a water park. Yeah, your name
Depend if it only if it makes less money then the trip costs well if it turns out
Definitely did so okay, if it doesn't turn a profit, then I'm okay. I think I put him in debt
Good that's true. I only like water park vlogs when the person at the water park eats a whole bar of chocolate before
Did he do that in the video? I think you did. Oh, yeah, that was his breakfast. You're right
This mystery person
Is them with their shirt off making like a weird gesture towards a water slide
But we'll never know that that episode of PCP has way less views than any other one
You're talking about like it's we're entering a we're entering the fucking Wally society where you know
Everyone is just sort of in shares just doing nothing like that's but that's the world
We're going to where people just plug themselves into YouTube forever
And all we need now is just 3d printers to make food and and it'll be done. This is why this is why I think Isis
Isn't yeah, I think the constant threat killed and beheaded for no reason really makes you appreciate
That we really need yeah, yeah
We really need some some strife in our lives if we're gonna do it's just a big difference
I think fundamental difference between the way that I
Especially when YouTube was branded new was like getting engaging with YouTube the way it was originally engaged with the way it is
Versus the way it is now and especially by like just you know kids who are discovering it
You know as it's already in this this modern era of like YouTube is this thing you throw on and just endlessly
Swimming forever, you know and
For me, you know for people when it back when YouTube was new and limited didn't have that many videos
None of the videos were that good. It was like going to like a weird store to like a trinket shop to think
Whoa, what am I gonna?
What am I gonna pick out?
It was sort of like going to the movies and like what movie am I gonna see like what YouTube video?
I'm gonna watch going to blockbuster. Yeah, it's like on a blockbuster and picking out videos based on the code
Right, but now it's like just you just throw something on you know and that's literally how you get popular
You got to get popular by like engaging the I'll throw something on audience and not the ooh what video am I gonna watch audience?
You know and I think it's shit and it didn't have to be that way cuz you know like my fucking you know
The invisible hand of the market logic goes well YouTube optimize itself or what would you know make you know?
Get the most eyes glued to the most screens and wreck in the most cash
And I think that eventually once social media has hit like a fucking
Event horizon where everything just spills over and it hits this like the bubble bursts
You're gonna see the the rise of like rebellious social medias that really focused on like culling down the quantity and really ramping up
The quality and like they'll finally be real competition for YouTube assuming that this fucking adpocalypse reaches critical mass
right and like people will will pursue these other places these other YouTube alternatives as like a fucking
Identity statement and like the algorithms of those websites will be all about
About quality over quantity and and yeah that that I feel is the only thing that's gonna stop the critical mass of longer
longer longer pointless or pointless or pointless or vlogs about everyone everything all the time is
Outright rebellion outright like the human nature's desire to say fuck you to the establishment
So we just got to wait for this whole vlog to get established. I believe in that I
I
Think oh that I hope you're right. That sounds like a miracle waiting to happen
It does it I mean that does yeah, it's a miracle because I feel like cuz I've seen a talk by a guy. It wasn't a Ted talk
Fears right now this was no Ted talk viewer
Yeah, he was explaining that the possibility is there that in the future
Privacy is not going to be a thing that people grow up knowing what it is
Technology technology is going to to turn all this sort of YouTubey
Just mindless entertainment into you know technology like phones and chips you put in your head that
Stream your whole life and experiences
Across the internet for everyone to see and everybody else is also doing that and it's just a big sea of everybody knows
Yeah, we're already in we're already entering this era with say, you know elected officials where they're constantly having scandals about things that
Politicians have always done in every administration every country ever
It's just that they never got caught because they we didn't have camera phones back then we didn't have gorilla investigators and like
Half the time I think like half the shit that people got that that that put Trump into the hottest of waters was like some random thing
He said one time at some point 20 years ago that there was a mic in front of and someone uploaded it
Right and eventually, you know cut to 40 years from now or even 30 years from now when like millennials start running for office
We're gonna have a place where like everyone who wants to be there like a fuck
Everyone's so fucked like it's gonna be like you tweeted this one thing when you were 15 right?
Well, I think it's gonna end word and you you're fucked. Well, you guys are fucked
No, no what it's gonna be at the end where it's gonna be a goddamn critical mass of like well now
Everyone is exposed on the internet. Everyone is bad. We now know everyone's dirty laundry
So now you have to select your vote based on entirely different parameters
And then people will just stop giving a shit about all those things because everyone will know who I don't know if I have enough faith in
Humanity to believe it'll become a question not of who's got the least dirty laundry, but who's dirty laundry's smell is the least
Cuz the example you used was Trump and that was some dirty-ass laundry and then he won
For saying the n-word all the time but hit by the way
My my biggest creator that I hate is Donald Trump
United States of America
Creating because he's creating plans to destroy Isis and we all know we need
Yeah to appreciate life
We need Isis to stop walley from happy ready for questions
Donald Trump wants to fix all our problems and I hear to say no we need our problem
I feel like we've been going for an hour. Is anybody else have any like last minute?
I think so I have a couple of ones a little quick like tiny one couple just one just one just fucking one
Can we do a third episode? I have only have one
Which is innocent obviously right and I have fuck yeah
My opinion goes without saying worse worse and has always been like well obviously they just slap these videos together
What the fuck ever it's mildly amusing sometimes if I care about the movie whatever but then no, but it's fucking nonsense
Yeah, well then a friend of mine recommended me these videos called like cinema sins sins
I don't remember what they're called, but there's this guy who like rebuts cinema sins with like just yeah
I mean one of the he's not like only five of them
Which is all you really need to be convinced most of them are of the Marvel movies reviews like yeah
I watched the Civil War one right right where this guy rebutted their
videos
Yeah, he made really good. Yeah, so like at first
I was kind of naysaying this guy because the way he made his case especially in his first one against them
Sounded just like a stupid fucking comment of like oh cinema sins is misleading the audience misinforming them about to the movies
It's just so inaccurate the videos are inaccurate and it's just blue and like he had a really respectful tone
I was like under tailoring him up there for comedic effect
But it was just I was imagining the transcript of this guy's video pissing me off
Especially if I liked cinema sins or if it was like a video that I made right, but I have to admit
This is an instance where the amount of actually being factually wrong reaches a critical mass of okay
Yeah, your videos suck right cuz like commenters love to do that. Oh you got this point wrong
You got that point wrong there for you're invalid and it's like fuck you
But like this like he this guy over the course of several videos, especially the one on the Marvel movies
Convinced to me that cinema sins are shitty not just that like making videos or analyzing them
But even watching movies and paying adequate attention
I am convinced that cinema sins are not just doing cynical YouTube clickbait
You know shit to like get the views but are also just outright lazy in general right because I remember at least last time
I checked cinema sins uploads once every three days right that and but and yet I think he does two movies a week
Yeah, something like that right
Let's just say once every three days right and like this guy convinced me that they only watch the movies once maybe twice
And are probably taking down notes as they're going through without pausing by the sheer level of like fucking up that their points have
But when I explained to my friend yeah three days is a lot
But three days is enough time to watch the movie raw not taking down any notes
Take down some notes after watching it watch the movie again
Taking down notes while you watch it and then watch the movie a third time to make sure you didn't fuck anything up
Right you can do all that in one day if it's a full-time job second day
Edit the video make the whole fucking video and then have your lunch break because it should only take like three hours tops
Right then you could take the rest of the day and the whole third day just doing whatever right so clearly shit channel
And it's like it's just one channel that has been objectively proven as shit by another channel
Extensively analyzing them. So uh, yeah, fuck cinema sins. I have a video game where you beat them up. It's it
It's it's really it's really like
Telling when you when you realize, you know, most people don't have a very good work ethic and
They still manage to get videos out so quickly because they're they're just not that they're not using their brain that much
Yeah, it's just
When I when I when I feel like I have to work a lot harder than other people to get things out faster
And I realized that they're not working hard themselves
Yeah, so guys if you want a visible hand at work if you guys want to beat the shit out of cinema sins
I have a flash game for it. Just Google footwear man beats up cinema sins
I made a long time ago. Just add Jesse's request. So there you go
The other thing I hate about cinema sins is that they've spawned so many imitators. Oh god. Oh, no if you want a
Oh, do you remember the bro? There's multiple brony ones early, sir. Oh, right?
Cinema
No, if you want objective fucking proof that your video style is easy
There is one channel I saw that's like literally an 11 year old girl doing it for every episode of sonic boom
It's great
Yeah, I actually like the idea
The point stands though, it's it's a very easy formula to ape
But yeah, that's the only I mean that was kind of long for a lightning round thing
We think I was just gonna say two things off the bat that I always hated that I don't even pay attention to much anymore
The channels where it's just like a girl with big tits
They're like being pushed up with a broad just staring at the camera and that's it
They get a million views and get tons of money. I hate them. Oh, yeah, like Ben and Jackie's College fund
Yeah, that's pretty much
Hate that hate Ben clearly
Haven't watched it yet, but if that's what it is then
Then the other thing is just reaction channels in general, they're all terrible like Ben and Jackie's College Fund. Yeah, we're pretty
We're pretty much guilty of everything
Yeah, that's all I got anybody else have any closing remarks quickly before we go to questions because
Where we're we're pushing an hour here. I don't like people who do twitch and
Are really in board and they get hundreds hundreds of billions of
Currency
Every five seconds is like oh
Some guy gave you a hundred bucks. Well, yeah, thanks. I'm just gonna keep
Which is a platform I don't like like there's nothing on twitch. I enjoy it's all bad
Especially I don't make tons of money. I don't understand the drive
To watch to watch someone play like Hearthstone or League of Legends or something and be like, yeah
I just I just don't get the idea of watching video games. I've tried
I've really tried to get into it and like if you do good on you, but I just I don't get it
I'm just when I watch because I only want to watch people playing games that I I like or I want to play and the whole time
Just like I kind of want to just play the game now and then I just turn it off and I'll go play the game
So, yeah, I don't I don't really get it. I mean
Everything has its audience at market blah blah blah, but yeah, not my thing
Okay, we're going to questions. All right. Good. Yeah, let's go
question from the
PCP patron lounge if you want to get to this exclusive lounge while where we all hang out and chat with you fucking sheeple
Go over to the PCP patreon and throw in a buck. You'll get access. You can ask us these questions
You can I think I think did you posted pictures of his pfimosis cock in here the other day?
So if you want to get on that go ahead
Does that count as false advertising if I just like give out a blatant lie and then say give us money?
No, it's because it's true because it's I can see them right now
Okay, here's a question from
Cucked by the laws of aerodynamics who wants to know if you could get any movie sequel made. What would it be? Oh
God
The brave little toaster for oh shit I
Love brave little toaster even though the two and three were made by Disney and they weren't as good as the first one
I want them. I want more toaster. No, I I actually have a great answer to this
Okay, um, I don't know if anyone's ever heard of
Fucking Rhapsody Street kids believe in Santa is a
Abominable Christmas special. Yeah, we reviewed it on the college fund
Yeah, and it it was supposed to have a sequel like the end of it ends with like will be back for Easter
But it was so bad and and was received so terribly that it never got made and there's nothing
I would rather see in this world than Rhapsody Street kids to Easter Easter Feaster or whatever
Oh
Yeah, so that's my pig. I'm gonna cheat because it's what I do and instead of a sequel
I want a prequel because I want to see more movies in the inception universe
But I don't want to see a sequel because that'll ruin the ambiguous ending of the first one
But I want to see more adventures of you know, Leo and friends going into people's dreams and fucking around
I think that'd be a lot of fun. I
Know Leo young Leo meets young. Yeah
Incept young Sheldon to convince him to be an atheist
It's where he learned his it's inception. We you find out that young
To his brain young young Sheldon events of the dream the dream die of technology. Oh my god
By accident well, we did it we we came up with the perfect movie
Honey, honey, I incepted
The time what movie do you want to see the suicide diaries to?
Yeah, totally that's I'm gonna make it myself. Just you wait one of these days
Oh
God
Nothing nothing's really spring to mind to be totally honest
Yeah, I'm there's no nine eleven two. Oh, oh that's coming to at the rate. We're going. Let's be real
What the Trump Tower?
Maybe
Man imagine just imagine not saying I want it to happen
I
Was making the veil threat the Trump
We're gonna blow up Trump Tower good on you ISIS the heroes we deserve they did it
Okay, well great question monkey. Let's move on to the next one I guess unless the view had an answer
Yeah, I was thinking about it because I was thinking thinking of every movie
I like and like I don't want sequels to any of them
You know I'm it's down on the whole sequels remakes reboots read everything is that anyone is your name too
What was their name?
Well, but no, um, so I was thinking well, you know, I don't like the idea in general
So how can I turn it? How can I spin it into a win?
Right and I had the idea a while ago that like Hollywood should just read everything all at once in one giant thing
And then like kill everyone so I had like how can you do that?
Well, I'd also being the ultimate showdown
Revengeance and just make it like all the actual fucking people not just flat shitty flash animations full score by lemon demon
Of course who has lately gotten really good at combining fucking music together deal Cesariga that guy
So like just yeah, he just come good at that for yeah
He fucking he fucking like smashes every fucking movie soundtrack into one
We're using his incredible skills and like all the actors are brought back for a final movie and they all get slaughtered and
There we go
We can finally have new IPs because I'm as big on we need new IPs as anybody because IP every day
Fantastic um
All right, anybody else have a question
I'm looking through the chat most of them. Well, here's what here's what I don't know
There's one from me at you underscore flame
Why does digi insist on shaking his gross phymosis cock even people with regular foreskin have to wipe their dig?
Find out on the PCP patreon where did you posted several photos and this is not false advertising? I
Think it's just because
There's another question in there about like how has having girlfriends improved our hygiene and I have to imagine digi's toilet is no
Longer a giant piss-stained mess, but I don't know. I have not seen images of that. Can anybody confirm I?
Have not been there. No, I have not I can answer the question on the procrastinators fan chat
Yes, but not directly so so like I actually do take showers almost every day now
But like I mean my girlfriend does not but like what it is is that just like you know having a fucking relationship and sex just
Sort of balances out my fucking brain and I can make better decisions for myself like oh
Hey, if I take a shower
I will immediately like get that 15 minutes of time back by like how much faster I'm gonna work for the next couple hours
Cuz I'm gonna feel so fucking clean. I'm gonna feel awesome. So yes indirectly, but it's I
Still do and have always had better hygiene than my partner in question
Well, there you go all right whose girlfriend it I guess is disgusting
Every other day it's normal. Oh, yeah, that's fine
What about you Ben?
marginally
Just not as beard. I
Probably brush my teeth a little more often nowadays, you know to be polite
So that's pretty good, but everything else is pretty much the same
Yep
That's my answer. Do we have any other Twitter questions today? I want my questions Leo J. Larkin ask
Is there a literary device that makes you immediately stop caring about a story personally chosen one slash prophecy?
Oh question
That that's my big one for sure
I feel it's just so tired and played out that I
Almost like I almost want someone to put a spin on it that makes it interesting again
Because I feel like everyone who does it does it exactly the same
Hmm. I I did I did mention earlier the bit about like like breaking the fourth wall
If you break the fourth wall too much it makes me stop caring if you break the fourth wall so much that it's like
This isn't even a real story anymore, but Ben Deadpool likes Jimmy Changus, dude
That's that's that's in can okay
Well to answer the question
I mean the first thing that springs to mind it mind is like
When the narrative device of that like lets me know immediately that there's gonna be a big dramatic people getting mad at each other
Seen over a misunderstanding or the liar
But I thought that I was really unique with that whole point about the liar revealed until
Nostalgia Critic coined to the term and started talking about it a lot and so that's that that whole crusade
I guess is basically covered like we're learning our lesson from that fucking one hopefully
But to go really really broad like the biggest connecting fiber between my disengagement with most stories
But mostly most movies is when the goal isn't clear when like the point or like the objective or like how the characters gonna go about their
Objective isn't clear regardless of whether or not it's an action movie like I got to save the president or a romance movie
Like I got to get that girl to like me, you know, it's just whenever the
It's just the movie is not telling me exactly what the point or what the goal is
I just get so fucking confused and it's such a common thing with like Hollywood movies
Like I remember Star Wars episode 7 having this where it's like, okay
We kind of have to go here, but we kind of have to go there
But we're kind of gonna do this, but we're they were kind of not I die
I remember the Hobbit movies having the same problem
I couldn't quite like get like why everyone is doing the thing that you're doing. I'm done
You need you need to establish your stakes like very clearly because that's like the linchpin of getting people to actually give a fuck
Right, you don't do that the whole everything else just doesn't feel like it has any context
I also agree that like I think you basically just to this one. We're gonna reiterate it is that any any fake character like
Protagonist versus protagonist conflict that you know is going to be solved. It just feels like I'm I
Instantly get like really stressed out because I'm like this whole conflict is completely pointless
It's not gonna affect anything like they're not gonna keep fighting forever
Like so just can we just I have like that. I'll just flip through the pages and skim it until it gets over with
Yeah, I have a VH. I have a VHS tape. That's like pause
That's like stuck right before that scene happens the rocketeer, right?
I watched the handful of years ago or I almost did but then like I knew that basically I could tell based on like everything
Red flags were were blaring out of the screen up my ass like there's gonna be a scene where the guy
Can like meets the girlfriend and she's mad at him and she's probably gonna slap him and a little bit
Like rocketeer juice is gonna come out of his rocket ass or something
I just know it right and like like based on what how the scene was being framed. He was like he got off his rocket
He's walking into a building where the girlfriend is and I know all the plot beats that are happening
So I'm like, yeah, there's gonna be a scene where she's mad at him and he's at his lowest point
And I was so mad preemptively I was so preemptively mad
Knowing it was gonna happen and bring down my entire opinion of the otherwise perfectly okay movie that I was watching
So I I paused the movie stopped it took took out the tape and I have not gotten back to it for years until this day
It stays exactly at that point and I'm just ready ready with a fucking shotgun
Everybody likes to suck the dick of the new it movie
But even that like for no reason the kids all
Stopping in friends and then like not even two minutes later. It's resolved like
Hornet into every fucking movie. It's so
Much I'd much rather they do it that way where it's like something it's just done
Just don't do it at all. I agree. But if you're going to do it quickly
What does it fucking add? I don't I don't know it's very I mean for me
It's not even the for me
I don't even get as mad about like the forciveness of it as the I can't believe the characters would act
I guess it's related to the forciveness
But it's always stupidity on the part of the main character right like I remember hearing that there's like
What's that one movie about the fucking lizard iguana guy who can camouflage and therefore he lies and like that has a liar revealed
Seen in it. I haven't seen it
But Nostalgia Critics said that it's an example of a movie that works because that Rango Rango
Um, I won't say like Django Unchained, but that's not the right movie. So anyway, he was saying like that movie it works
Because the movie is fucking about that
It's like a movie about a character who's like thing is that he's deceptive and he has to learn his lesson about it
And I'm like, there you go, right?
I hate it when it's like a character who I'm supposed to like relate to or has any sort of arrangement of personality
Things or things going on with them and they always somehow find themselves in a place where they're incentivized to lie about themselves
And they always go about lying about themselves in the same fucking way or they fail to communicate in a certain way for me
I never fucking put up with people misunderstanding me. I'm gonna push
I'm gonna put them down in the seat get out the fucking whiteboard if I have to and visualize like a fucking
Chalkboard youtube video why they're wrong and misunderstanding something to the point that they're exhausted and don't give a shit anymore
That's how all of my liar revealed scenes go all of my misunderstanding scenes go it goes with them saying I don't care anymore
Fine shut the fuck up. I just I'm so taken out of it by the fact that like when the character gets the misunderstanding happening
They just sort of sit there and like sigh and let the girl character slap them in the face
You know, I'm just like why don't they like why can't there just be one character just beat that one?
Yeah, just one character who's like shut up. No, I remember there's like one movie
That's like a fucking child above who gets framed for being a terrorist and he literally says
I would be the stupidest terrorist in the world if I did this that and the other this doesn't make any sense
He actually stands up for himself and I'm like that eagle eye eagle eye. He stands up for himself
And I was so fucking good at this baby. You are yeah, I was so fucking relieved that he finally like said something for himself
That's the for me. It's not the forciveness the obligation is as much as the character sitting there and taking it up the ass
It I can't relate to that at all and uh, yeah, I hate it
It's every episode of friends. Oh really
You know what? I want I want to maybe I also ties into like oh, we don't believe you like if there's like a
Supernatural thing happening and like the main character does a terrible job explaining it, you know
And so therefore no one believes it
I want to have a thing that has the misunderstanding and the no one believes you thing
And like it causes his life to be ruined
But then like people finally find out, you know through the plot that it actually was real all the time and they like
Have a little cell and they all killed themselves. No, no, he kills them. So they have a celebration about it
Right. Yes. Yeah, they have a cell. I want that. No, no, no, literally. It's like this
It's like it's going to be like, okay
You know like from dusk till dawn which has like a horror movie twist halfway through this is going to be a like
Does that this is going to be like a horror a horror movie twist that happens in the last scene, right?
It's otherwise a normal family movie or some shit with a mysterious r-rating
I guess where like, you know, he like just sort of takes it, you know
There's a couple of signs early on and throughout the movie that he might be psychotic
But otherwise he acts like a perfectly normal fucking 80s protagonist
Just sort of taking this fucking bullshit from all these people who don't like understand him for no fault of his own
And then at the end they have a little party or a little festival
They're like, yeah, we're really sorry about that
You know once the plot revealed to us that you were right all and then he just like he gets up to make his speech
But he pulls out a fucking uzi and just fucking slaughters them and you like see individual characters
Like the older mom character from some other family who like set a particularly nasty line to him
You see him stab her with a fork until her neck borderline comes off
But he gives up and moves on to someone else, you know, that's what I fucking want as a movie
Well, you know, your life's work is ahead. You know what you have to do
It's time to get to the real life story
Be the change be the change
I remember I remember like happens in like Home Alone 3 and I'm like yelling at the characters like don't be nice to him
Now you remember the fucking I want you dead. They you should die you y'all should die and my dad was like what?
Jesus calm down
Like I want them dead
Wait, you were saying that stuff out loud. What was in front of your family? I wasn't saying fuck
I was just saying like casually like I hate those characters. They should die. I was just casually saying
I want them to die
My dad was so offended on behalf of my threatening of the murder of these fictional characters
Well, Home Alone 3 is a lively event at the Davoo household. Yeah, this was like 15 years ago
It's a family tradition. Oh, I remember I remember at rad con 2 you were telling us all about Home Alone 3
I was
Yeah, it was in the car. I recorded a vlog of him telling us the details of every
Oh, yeah, I remember that. Oh my god. Did I just confuse a youtube video with real life?
Well, no, because you were there you were in the passenger side. Oh, okay. I just got the time mixed up. Well, never mind. Nope. Listen to me
I'm gonna kill myself. Oh, no, just like Davoo wants
well, uh
The thing I don't like
When stuff happens is when a thing tries to be funny and they don't do it right
And uh, it's not even funny bad. And that's all I have to say. Are you talking about my videos hippo?
I
God damn it
And with that, hey, we've been the pcp folks on lumpy tomes. Yeah. Yeah, you're all welcome
Oh, bye
I guess that's another we don't we're done all the other questions are gay
Yeah, I didn't look at them, but they're probably gay if you're gay question didn't get answered
Keep keep tweeting better luck next time page patronize
You can listen to this episode and every other episode of the pcb on itunes and google play now because I slaved away
I'm never gonna let that go. It was the hardest thing of my life
Um, if you want to hear the bonus episodes of the pcb that aren't on itunes or google play
Go to patreon.com slash the procrastiners. Is that what it is? I remember the url
There's a link in the description. There's a link in the description
Go there five bucks to get access to all the crazy bonus episodes that are too hot for itunes
And uh, a dollar gets you into the lounge so you can I'm just gonna say right now
Our $5,000 pcp patreon goal is digi will probably post his phymosis cock. So let's get it up to 5 000 folks
I know you can do it
All right
Oh
I am a stupid I got a deadline don't want to do it