Food, I love food, and I'm really in the mood for a big corn dog, a poo poo platter, two ding dongs, it doesn't matter.
Had some tuna helper, I'll be racing back for more, but don't add any salsa, cause I'll blow chunks on the floor.
Wait!
I need to get back.
Welcome back to Stillin' Your Dads, if it was easy. Today we're- wait a second.
This isn't the greatest podcast ever recorded that can be found on munchyshatsky.com to videogame.com slash channel.
Go to the description and look at that. This is some weird dystopian alternate reality, where the cool nuclear holocaust never happened, and the vintage hipster modernist super teenage nihilist world didn't get completely and utterly obliterated by the thousands of sickest stage 3 neurosophilists, radical galactic eternity Maltovs, which changed the chemical makeup of the planet into the individual atom level, forever thrusting the world into an infinite aesthetic of cyberpunk, post-cyberpunk, biopunk, nano-punk, steampunk, diesel-punk, stone-punk, clown-punk, elf-punk, etc.
Mith-punk, dream-punk, atom-punk, weasel-punk, trash-punk, dad-punk, seizure-punk, fancy-santa-punk, and most of all, cluster-punk, all at the same time, even the ones that contradict each other, especially the ones that contradict each other.
That never happened, this cock-suckingly terrifying timeline. Everything's just like normal, not completely obliterated, it's physically, mentally, and spiritually.
They haven't figured out how to thoroughly utilize an irony's fully and unbelievably destructive force and use it against one another.
Holy fuck, did you- I'm freaking the fuck out, it's crazy dude, it's crazy.
I know man, I thought that we were always gonna be in the future, and now we're not in the future, but in the other future, the not-good future is fucking-
We have to go back.
Also known as the present.
Oh my god, it's other people.
We have to go back to the present.
Well, you don't fuck it, whatever, we're just here now, alright.
I forgot about other people.
Well, good work guys, hey everybody.
Welcome back to the PC bit for another fun episode.
Welcome back to the dystopian multi-punk podcast, the piece, the procrastinator's podcast.
Multi-punk?
Yeah, multi-punk, that's how I condense all that bullshit.
Yeah, multi-cultural punk, yeah.
Multi-cultural punk.
I'm the best guy ever, Ben Sains here.
Yep.
Did you bro?
Hey, I'm here from the other future.
Hippocrite?
I have just eaten many chicken nuggets, so this is appropriate.
Oh, perfect.
Munchy.
Alternate universe Munchy from a different union?
You can write slash fiction about Munchy and alternate universe Munchy now.
That's juicy stuff.
Alternate universe Munchy just has like an eye patch and like where's like, instead of the light and good Munchy of this universe that dresses like a hamburger,
the evil one dresses like, he has an eye patch and he dresses like, I don't know, like a dark chocolate cake.
That's fucking wrong.
Yeah, it's fucking wrong.
All right, hey, shut up everybody, because Eddless Jess is here.
Yep, I sure am.
Okay, there you go.
That settles it.
So our topic today is food.
Wait, did we introduce him?
I don't remember.
Yeah, we did.
I said chicken nuggets.
That's right.
LOL.
So, Urban Dictionary Food, here we go.
No.
A substance that, here we go, a substance that you eat, then poop out, usually followed by a nap.
That's a good one.
I like it.
Wait, who naps off to pooping?
I napped directly on my poop, you know, it's out and then I fall in a heap.
You roll it out as like a bed when you lay in it.
I like to be asleep during pooping.
So, God, what the fuck are we even talking about?
Yeah, I like food.
It's good.
Yeah, of course.
Well, I think you're going to talk about is the contentious food thing.
I think you're all going to take the opposite stance on this one.
Yeah, I think you're all going to be surprised by my nuanced take of what I think about food.
I fully expected, coming into this, that Jesse was going to be the opposition to the idea that food is good.
You know, guys, I've said it before, but this might be the most Jesse is right episode of this entire show.
Food in real life is the curse of, is the dark sign of real life.
That's what addiction to food is.
That's what it is in real life.
It damns us all from birth to the grave.
There is no escape.
We just keep coming back like the poor saps we are.
We have to have energy, but we've come up with plenty of ways to make the energy that we intake interesting enough and different enough to be kind of fun.
Kind of, you know, you're making a best of a bad situation.
We have stomachs, we need to feed them.
We may as well have good food.
Running in your body is secondary to being cool.
Okay, eating with my bros is more fun than eating alone.
Because when you're eating with your bros, you have that intimate experience of like, yeah, we are re-consuming.
We are vulnerable.
We could be sexually assaulted at any time, but you know what, we're just going to rock that.
We're just going to rock it.
Does being in a group increase or decrease the chances of being sexually assaulted?
Increase.
It depends on the group and if they're eating or not.
It makes it all the more succulent.
Yeah, all the more succulent.
Well, let me, I think I will also probably have a slightly different stance than some people here because I see-
I think I know what you're going to say.
I think you're going to come down on the food as fuel side of it.
That's exactly what I'm going to say.
Food is food.
You know, we are slaves to our biological impulses that, by the way, are 100% outdated.
The lust we all have for salt is because way back in a fucking billion years ago when you could find like one grain of salt,
you know, fucking an entire lifetime, that's when like our desire, that's not even a lie.
That's true.
Right.
That shit was programmed.
Before this goes any further, I just want to say, I want to fast forward and say,
okay, Nate, you're right, but I don't care.
And also-
Hashtag weird utilitarianism.
I kind of wanted this podcast to be-
You just predicted like the end of every podcast ever.
It's true.
But I kind of wanted this podcast to be, we each say a food and then the others say,
oh my god, I can't believe you like that and that would be the whole thing.
Can I start with one?
Yeah, go ahead.
Big dick.
Big-
Flap.
You know it.
Dog.
Yeah, okay.
I can't believe you like that.
Don't like that.
Well, we've all learned a lot here today.
All right, here's the thing.
Here's what I'm going to say.
Pepperoni sucks.
What?
No.
You piece of-
I know, I agree.
He's right.
Get the fuck out of here.
Get the fuck out of here, you hot piece of ass.
You sexy little babe.
He's right.
Pepperoni.
He's a little army.
Just wants to ruin everyone's time and just fucking stick their wax in anyone else's ears.
The thing about pepperoni is that I like all that sort of like Italian sausage stuff,
like the parma ham and the, you know, the pepperoni-
And the prosciutto?
The pepperoni!
You like the prosciutto?
Yes.
I like all that sort of stuff.
But it's nice as like a cold meat to have with like cheese or olives or something.
I got some cold meat for you, my dude.
Why is it cold?
Have you been fucking in the fridge?
I don't know, because I got fucking jaundice.
My extremities are dying.
Yep, yep.
That's what I mean.
Ah, there's another person who hasn't had my attention.
But pepperoni, as I have researched, is an American invention which is sort of like
taking what it's from and then inventing it and making it gross and greasy and salty and disgusting.
And they put it on every pizza.
That's American cuisine.
The reason I don't like pepperoni is because it's so ubiquitous.
If it wasn't so ubiquitous, I'd be like...
So he's a hipster, is he, Ziai?
Yes, I am.
He's a hipster crit.
That's the funny thing about it.
And I don't know if you've made it this far and biggest problem with the universe hippo,
but Maddox had a whole long argument about why pepperoni was bad.
Essentially, raising that point that you should eat the better versions like salami and fucking all that shit.
Well, no.
I think it's okay on pizza.
I just don't like that everybody likes it and that's like the default pizza when it's not my favorite topping.
It is odd.
I do wonder how it came to be that pizza's two default flavors are now nothing or this one specific sausage.
Well, I gotta say that while I appreciate how weird that is,
it for me is one of the few victories I have in life because I...
That you have.
That you did this.
This was your doing.
No, no, no.
Just a spiritual victory, you know, because I love pepperoni pizza.
And so the fact that I can go to any place and guaranteed they will have my shit.
Like, if someone says, oh, we're throwing a pizza party, I can show up with some confidence knowing they will have the pizza I like
because everyone has the pizza I like, which is not true of any other food.
There's nothing I can show up and be guaranteed they're gonna have it, you know.
That's true.
But across the board, pepperoni is like this thin, disgusting, greasy, little slab of meat that's not even very flavorful.
I got a thin, disgusting, greasy, little slab of meat for ya.
You know, I always think that pepperoni's not that flavorful until I eat a pizza without it and then I just miss it.
It is very flavorful.
It's just a specific flavor that I don't like.
And I don't think salami, putting like better quality meat on it would solve the problem.
I think just, you know, maybe a different, maybe like jalapenos and chicken or something.
There's no other meat that I really like on pizza.
But vegetables can, yeah, you can eat a pizza with just jalapenos and it's all right.
But a lot of people can't handle the jalapenos.
I'm not that into jalapenos personally.
Hey, here's a quandary for ya.
I have here something I'm very excited about.
I have a can of Diet Code Red Mountain Dew.
And I want you guys to weigh in on whether this is food or not.
All Mountain Dew should be fucking abolished and drinking it should be punishable by firing squad.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
That's right.
What, diet? Diet shit?
No, all Mountain Dew.
Oh, all Mountain Dew.
Okay, I'm ready.
I was ready for someone to jump on me for diet.
Cause I'm a big proponent of diet beverages.
They're like my favorite shit in the whole world.
Mountain Dew is just like radioactive yak slime put in a can.
It's the same as any other bullshit.
No, like all pop is poison, but Mountain Dew tastes like the poison that it is.
I don't disagree and I drink a lot of it.
It's just this fucking sugary, ogre sweat.
It doesn't belong in anyone's body.
It doesn't belong in anyone's mouth.
Guys, let me, let me, let me get down on soda.
I consider myself an expert on the, on the soda issue because I have gone roughly three years now drinking next to no soda, just like the occasional soda when it happens to be around.
I spent an entire year.
I went for a rose dedicated effort to drink no soda at all.
And let me just tell you, when I came back and drank a soda after that, it was like, it was so powerful.
It was so like my body was just like, what are you doing?
You guys, if you're, if you're drinking soda and this tastes like good to you, I'm just letting you know that you are, you have done damage to your body.
You are fucking it up right now.
That's all the shit.
I had gone 23 years without drinking soda.
I've never, I hate it.
Really?
It's, it's never been nice to me because of that, because of that carbonated burp afterwards.
You know, Nate, that's actually a plot point in the dark tower because Roland is not from our world.
He, he gets his, like his finger bitten off by a giant lobster and like he goes to our world and he gets like some aspirin and Pepsi to like wash it down.
And he's never had Pepsi before and he drinks it and he like becomes a superhuman because he's never had Pepsi before.
It blows his whole perception of the universe, opens his mind, it increases his Christ consciousness.
That's cool.
That story reminds me of, have you guys all seen David Lynch Cook's quinoa?
I am.
No, but you've told me about it.
It's, okay.
Well, it's like, it's this like dark, like black and white, just, it's just, they're just filming David Lynch in his kitchen, just like cooking quinoa.
And he's kind of shit at it, but whatever.
He like cooks this quinoa and talks about what he's doing.
And then he goes out and sits on his porch and has a cigarette and tells this bizarre story about like a train ride through like fucking Eastern Europe or whatever.
And part of the, part of the story involves like taking this girl from Yugoslavia to like Paris and like buying her the first Coca-Cola she's ever had.
And meanwhile he's like, yeah, he like, I don't know, he just peppers the story with weird, like they get off the train and moths.
Like moth larva are crawling up out of the ground and leaping up into the air like frogs and these frog moths are just flying around.
And I gave, and I gave the cashier, and I gave the cashier this tiny, the tiniest little, little coin.
And he gave me a big piece of paper money in return for change.
And then I go to the next place and I paid with the paper money.
And then he just pours handfuls and handfuls of coins into my hands.
So many I have to use both hands to catch them.
And my, they're just about to overflow.
And there's so many coins until the moment I look up at him and then he stops.
And that's beautiful.
I did make a giant batch of quinoa once and it was pretty good.
Yeah, that's my relationship to that.
Anyway, I just wanted to plug, I just wanted to plug David Lynch Cook's quinoa.
It's really great.
Well, let me just say about that.
What's cool about that is I like that he gave someone their first Coca-Cola.
Because there is nothing wrong with occasionally getting down and dirty and drinking some absolute garbage like soda.
Yeah, that's a soda pop.
That's real edgy shit.
That's real edgy shit for me.
I'll tell you guys.
I'm just saying, but you can't do it all the time or you're not going to appreciate it.
That's what I'm saying.
I drank nothing but Mountain Dew for about 13 years for my entire, like, I don't know, 9 to 21 or something.
And like, yeah, it's addictive and it's bad.
It makes you feel like shit and it also doesn't taste good.
And then I got off of that and on to diet green tea.
And then at some point I started working soda back in because I just, what's great about soda to me is that it is like acid.
Like, you drink it and it just melts away everything, you know?
You know what else does that?
Brushing your fucking teeth.
No, no, no.
I'm talking about like when you're eating food, like it's a palate cleanser.
You know, like you go out to lunch and you eat some stuff.
If you consider like acid washing your fucking mouth, palate cleansing, like I guess.
Yeah, like you take a drink of Sprite and then it just completely clears out all the flavors and stuff that run your mouth and makes you feel refreshed.
I agree.
Yeah, you take a gulp of soda and it just like sears away all the other flavors.
That's the whole point of it for me.
Weird.
I don't know.
That's what like water is for though.
You take a sip of water and then you still taste whatever you were just eating.
Exactly.
Then you down a gallon of that shit.
And maybe you should eat some good stuff that is nice to taste for the whole day.
If you drink like a juice or something, it just kind of like mixes with the flavor of whatever you're eating and it's just not quite right.
That's true.
Like tea, especially hot tea, will have this effect of like it'll, you know, it'll burn away everything that's in there.
Yeah, hot tea.
But soda will just, you take one sip and it just, it feels like you swallowed a bunch of acid that just burns away everything that's in you.
Surely you could get that same feeling from like orange juice because that's quite citric.
Yeah, I was going to say, I'm a big orange juice and soda guy.
I just said the orange juice taste mixes with the stuff that's in your mouth.
Yeah, orange juice is really kind of lumpy.
Lumpy?
Well, I mean, did you mean pulp?
I told you to get the kind with the pulp.
Let me just say, one of my, I'm the biggest orange juice fan of the world.
It is by far my favorite thing.
I'd sacrifice everything else in my life.
But the thing is, you cannot get orange juice anymore that has lots of pulp.
When I was a child, lots of pulp was a thing you could buy.
Now the most you can get is some pulp.
No, that's because nobody likes the bits.
I love bits.
I love lots of pulp.
I know, I know that they still have lots of pulp orange juice.
I've seen it.
Not in my fucking city, dude.
I've been to every grocery store.
I don't know.
There's an embargo just on your city.
Yeah.
It's possible.
Maybe they just hate fucking citric.
There's a pulp, there's a pulp, a quota that has to be met.
Whenever I went to Florida, I could get some fucking pulp in my eyes.
I can't believe you like that.
Here's my Breavage Diet.
For every one liter of soda I will drink, I will drink two, like boxes of orange juice.
And then for every two boxes of orange juice that I'll drink, I'll drink four,
I'll drink four, whatever they're called, of water.
You know, I'm glad you said that because I was going to say the thing about juice
that a lot of people don't just, they probably know, but they just don't think about much,
is that juice is incredibly calorie dense and you can get super fat just drinking juice.
Yeah.
That's why orange juice is like, like now that I'm off soda completely,
drinking an orange juice has been elevated to like a god-like experience.
It's just the most delicious, satisfying.
It's like, if that's my cake, like orange juice is like eating a fucking piece of cake.
Decadent.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
It is fucking decadent.
I love it.
I know what you mean because it's just like, it's like candy.
It's like, it's like fucking sugar syrup is like what a, what a juice is.
Yeah, I don't actually drink that much juice.
You know what, maybe this is fucked up, like me being fucking health conscious is me going,
no, no, I won't drink that glass of orange, of fresh squeezed orange juice.
I'll have this diet Mountain Dew Code Red instead.
Well, the calories make sense there.
Yeah, in certain, in certain, looked at from a certain angle, it's reasonable.
There's a couple of very important questions that I think have to be answered by this podcast
or else we will have failed this miserably.
The first important question is what are you eating right now?
I'm, I'm eating.
So I actually went to the grocery store right before we started and I have a big old bag of pistachios.
And these are rather indulgent.
Oh man, I fucking love pistachios.
I mean, they're kind of salty, but they're delicious.
They got excellent unsaturated fats.
Oh, it's the good stuff, man.
I have not had pistachios in a while.
I'm all about cashews when it comes to nuts because they're smooth.
Well, okay.
I do, I do have a bag of cocoa, of like cocoa powder, like coated almonds in my pantry right now.
Those are delicious.
I don't like almonds at all.
I don't like that.
Oh, I fucking, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Do you have toasted almonds?
When I, when I bite into an almond, all it does is just go into every tooth in my mouth.
Like it just immediately gets stuck everywhere.
Untoasted almonds are shit.
Toasted almonds are the shit.
One time for Christmas, my mom got me a bag of almonds and I was like, these are pretty good.
But they're not toasted.
So I toasted them myself and I learned how to toast nuts.
It was the best day of my young life.
I've had some toasted nuts for you, my dude.
Alright, well that's what Nate's eating, is anybody else?
I'm eating the leftover chocolate syrup and this double-sharp espresso that I poured myself to do the intro.
And now I'm just wallowing away.
Are you sort of sticking your tongue down the glass, trying to lick it out?
Yeah.
I'm doing it.
Sick.
I'm not eating because I've just eaten, but I am drinking cis-white male tears of my own brand.
And I'm looking into freezing them into ice cubes to sell as like a food product.
That's good.
Oh my god.
Cis-white males of the world.
You're sitting on a gold mine.
Oh man.
One more advantage cis-white males have over the rest of the day is they can sell their tears.
Everyone's gets rich is a gold rush.
Is anybody else eating your chocolate?
He's got like a beehive out back full of cis-white males constantly producing tears.
Jess, are you eating anything?
I'm drinking tea, sans chicken, today.
Okay.
Because I feel like I'm not eating again.
No!
Don't bring him back!
We haven't spoken of him in months.
He was almost gone.
No!
The dark emperor of the PCP is just trapped in the corner.
Occasionally being like, let me the fuck back in guys.
Don't forget me.
He's over there fucking rattling his chains like Marley and Marley.
Exactly.
I'm not eating anything.
I'll never eat anything ever again because eating is wrong and cowardly and no human should ever do it.
I'm sick of it.
It's certainly cowardly.
I hit my breaking point last night where I had to put my foot down and say no more.
I'm drawing a lion in the sand.
I'm done.
I'm boycotting food for the rest of my life like fucking Gandhi because I was fucking sitting there.
It was like three in the morning and I'm watching Nates.
Everybody be a fit boy and exercise video thinking oh man Nates.
Such a pretty boy.
Would that I could be so pretty.
But I'm sitting there at three in the morning watching this video and I'm shoveling chocolate cake in my mouth.
And I'm eating like three slices of microwave leftover pizza.
And I'm dipping the pizza in like this fucking sugary sauce because I went with my woman to a restaurant.
We got this sauce at this restaurant and because we're both such disgusting slobs.
We went to the waitress and said can we please have some of this sauce and like a jar or something.
Can you scoop it off the wall so we can take it home.
So I've got this like restaurant sauce and this pizza and this chocolate cake.
And I'm just sitting there being a piece of shit.
Being an anti-human abomination.
Watching Nate be a monkey king on these fucking pull-ups.
And I said that's it.
I'm Gandhi now.
Never again.
I'll never eat a food until I'm dead.
And that's my goal for this month.
You're not like an anti-human since that you're like the opposite of a human.
You're an anti-human since that you're like an anti-pasta.
Like before you eat a human you will be like the appetizer before the ogre gets to the actual humans.
Let me just say the whole anti-pasta movement is just the opposite of everything I like about human civilization.
I can't help it.
Well anyways what I'm eating is this beautiful roasted pork over what is it called mustard greens.
But they're called like something mustard greens preserved.
Preserved mustard greens and cabbage.
I got it at a Chinese restaurant last night.
This one this is Chinese restaurant in my town that has two menus.
They have a white people menu and an Asian people menu.
They give you both if they're not sure.
You know what you're there for.
They say dude with this lucky star shirt they're like we just don't know where this man lies.
The one menu is just like all the standard crap you get at a Chinese restaurant.
The other menu is like frog and fucking jellyfish and like all this weird shit.
Which I ordered this off of that menu even though it's not particularly strange.
But it's a steamed pork.
It's like in like a soup and the soup just tastes like it's just salt.
But it's pretty delicious.
The meat just fucking falls away.
It's like a very tender you know you take a bite and it just comes right off.
And then cabbage man.
Cabbage should be in everything.
I fucking love cabbage.
Boiled cabbage.
That's great.
It's such a good base.
It's really good when people discover a vegetable that they like and then they can eat fill up on it.
I'm surprised.
These fucking mustard greens which just looks like a fucking like a disgusting black massive bullshit.
But it's actually great.
Everything in this is great.
I have discovered the miracle of Brussels sprouts.
Brussels sprouts cooked in bacon fat.
They see it well.
They're pretty good on their own.
But if you cook them in a little bacon fat they become a transcendent experience.
Possibly my favorite vegetable.
About Brussels sprouts is that I've always hated them and I decided one time to just start liking them
because you know every Christmas you have to eat them so I was like I may as well look like a good boy
and finish everything on my plate and I eat them.
I don't think that's a thing in America having to eat Brussels sprouts on Christmas.
Oh well okay whatever it's just a thing.
They're all looking at Oliver Twist over here.
He's the only one who has to eat that shit.
Can I have some more?
Oh I don't want any more.
More Brussels sprouts with my Christmas gruel.
But yeah it's like there's always been a thing in my family of you know finish what's on your plate.
I mean my dad doesn't care so much but my grandpa was always like if you don't finish what's
because you know the war was a time when you had to ration your food.
Otherwise you've got to eat everything you have.
You have a grandpa.
That sounds fascinating.
Who would your grandpa be?
He sounds like the most interesting man in the world.
I mean the grandpa I'm talking about is actually very quiet and reserved.
Is it Winston Churchill? Just tell me it's Winston Churchill.
That's what I want to know.
He was an RAF pilot but he was very quiet and he's like me but if he didn't make a YouTube channel.
Oh no.
That sounds awesome.
So anyway there was this one time when I was a little boy and I was like you know he was looking after me
because my parents were doing something and we were eating food and I didn't like the vegetables.
I was like yeah because usually I don't eat vegetables as a kid and he's like I don't want to finish it.
I can go play now and he said no sit down you have to finish it and I'm like but that's never happened to me.
I've never been told to stay at the table and he kept us there for hours.
We were crying near my brothers.
It was traumatic but ever since then ever since then I felt bad if I leave food on a plate
because you know I don't want to waste anything so Brussels sprouts I eat them now.
I don't like them but they're okay.
There you go.
Trauma is good for children.
Whoever is cooking those Brussels sprouts just tell them to cook them in bacon fat.
That's the secret.
Yeah.
I'll tell you Nate I totally am with you on this.
I'm going to eat some blue pills right here.
I'm totally with you on the magic of discovering a new vegetable because I grew up,
unlike a hippo's grandpa my parents were not strict at all about making us eat everything
and so I just ate no vegetables at all for like the majority of my life except maybe like a carrot here and there
or some corn which doesn't even do anything.
So like as I was becoming an adult I remember I had this moment of discovery with onions.
Like I had always just thought onions were shitty and disgusting and then all of a sudden I don't remember what it was I ate
but it had onions and I was like oh my god this is a magical experience and I got to a point where I would just
literally boil a whole onion and eat it.
What the fuck?
That's pretty sick.
I just eat onion all the time.
It's delicious.
I wouldn't just eat an onion.
Yes.
That's because you're weak man.
Onions are good for you because they make you cry and that's emotionally healthy.
It's important.
And you can sell what is.
They also have.
That onion paid for itself.
If you look up like any vegetable and then like put it into Google like is this healthy?
It'll just turn up like 80 articles about how healthy that fucking vegetable is.
So.
The issue of health is so complex.
Because like every vegetable has some nutrients and every nutrient like does something and so like.
I honestly think your average person is better off like not actually digging too deeply into like oh my god is this healthy for me?
Yeah.
Is that healthy for me?
Like the general rule of like eating lots of vegetables.
Just if you stick to that and if you can do like the Mediterranean sort of diet.
Yeah.
That's like the healthiest diet.
You know you can't be like you can't be like.
You can't be like oh lime beans prevent colon cancer better throw some of them in my diet.
Oh and right and celery prevents eye strain or better better toss some of that in for lunch.
God I hate celery.
Celery sucks.
I was more.
Yeah I mean that's true.
But what was Jesse saying?
You cut them off.
Oh.
Like a rude piece of shit.
Left my ass.
I think we cut each other off.
Isn't it like a known phenomenon that like nobody in like the nutrition community can decide if eggs are good for you or not?
Well I mean there's a debate.
Some people think eggs cause cancer which is a bit strange.
I mean I don't know all the details.
Well I mean everything causes cancer.
I mean soda pop is liquefied cancer.
For what it's worth.
Most people still prefer that.
Eggs do cause A cancer.
They cause A cancer on the breakfast industry.
And I'm glad I get to rehash this rant that I called into the dick show and they didn't play my voicemail.
But eggs have ruined all of.
Look I don't wake up at 5 a.m. like normal people right.
I just am up at 5 a.m.
And I want to get something to eat cause I'm hungry and I go out and all anywhere will serve me is fucking eggs.
Because somehow it became determined that breakfast just means eggs.
Like it doesn't.
That's all it is.
It's just stuff.
But we put eggs in it.
You know so like you can go to any of the fast food places that open early.
Anywhere that you go that's like a breakfast place.
All they'll fucking give you is some variation of eggs.
And I don't really like eggs.
I mean I can eat them.
They're fine.
But I just think they're bland and boring.
I like eggs but I also resent being served eggs as a meal.
Because I know they cost the restaurant like 30 cents for that.
Like I know that that's true of everything.
But I feel especially ripped off.
Because they're so cheap that like you know it's like this cultural institution of like
hey breakfast is eggs.
And every restaurant is going to be like hell yeah I want to serve fucking eggs with everything.
Two poached eggs.
Six and a half dollars please.
You know eggs are really revolting if you think about them.
Sometimes I'm eating an egg and I think about like what it actually is that I'm eating.
Like this is just like a toenail that came out of a chicken's butt.
And inside of it there's like a goopy fetus that's like not fully developed.
And I'm just shoveling that in my mouth.
And like sometimes you crack open an egg and you get those twins.
And that's even more disgusting.
You're like oh my god that's two goopy fetuses.
But I'm going to eat it anyways.
Sometimes you might crack open an egg and it's like kind of developed.
And you're like oh my god am I going to eat that one.
Yes I guess I will because I'm a piece of fucking garbage.
I sometimes feel like there's like eyeballs in it and like little feathers.
Sometimes I think of that.
But a lot of the time I don't.
But the reason is because I like scrambled eggs the most.
Because it doesn't look goopy and slimy and disgusting.
It's just nice and kind of rubbery.
And you eat it with bacon and toast.
It's good like that.
At some point, I was always against this.
But at some point Nate converted me to the runny sunny side up eggs.
Dude.
I don't know.
You squish the runny yolks over your toast or your hash browns or something.
I hate that.
It's so good.
If you are out there fucking cooking your yolks all the way through,
you are thrown away 99% of the fucking flavor.
You're thrown away your life away if you don't eat runny yolks.
If I'm going to be devouring chicken fetus, I want it as goopy as possible.
Fuck yeah dude.
Fuck yeah.
I will admit, if you're doing it like sunny side up,
it shouldn't be hard in the yellow bit.
I am a human chicken abortion machine.
That's my rank and title.
Isn't fruit pretty much all just like plant vaginas or dicks or something anyways?
Yeah.
It's all tree ejaculates.
We're always just guzzling cum, just in every direction from all things.
Everything is cum and vaginas and goopy shit, poopy.
Everything is gross and I love it and I want it all.
Here's a trick.
Here's a bizarre thing that I just learned.
If you're cooking eggplants, if you're buying eggplants,
go to the store and look at the bottom of the eggplant and see whether the little hole
at the bottom where the stem or whatever, the little point at the bottom.
See if it's round or if it's like a slot, like a line.
Because if it's a slot, that's a female eggplant.
If it's a round dot, it's a male eggplant.
Yeah, and the female eggplants have more seeds and are worse.
So you always want to buy the male eggplant.
What kind of Seth Rogen food fight shit are you on?
And you always want to buy the ones with the dots.
Hashtag dots not slots.
I learned that from Chef John of foodwishes.com
who I've been fucking watching shit tons of cooking videos on lately.
This is a story about eggplants suck.
Well, my shut up monkey, I just want to answer Nate and say that
my girlfriend Jackie is the best cook I've ever met in my entire life.
And yes, we watch a lot of cooking videos together.
Gross.
And it's great fun.
You sound defensive about that, but I'm not being accusatory.
When I was a baby yesterday, I was eating an egg
and my mother was in the room and she said,
you know what that is?
And I was like, what?
That's meat in its purest form, bitch.
And I was like, fuck yeah.
I guess it is.
It's actually not meat at all because meat is muscle
and there is literally no muscle involved.
Yeah, it's like pre muscle.
It's like a pre before it becomes an actual meat chicken.
Well, OK, I mean, sure.
All right, so there's a second very important question
that I felt had to be answered by this podcast.
It'll also be a huge failure.
Which is what is everybody's favorite food?
Obviously.
Here is something that Ben St. has stolen from me
that he can never repay.
OK.
His love for cherries.
I'm the only person that's supposed to like cherries.
I actually don't even like cherries that much.
I'm the only person that's allowed to like them.
I actually don't even like them.
Everyone else is a fucking poser.
Except in the context of the hashtag Ben St.
The Greatest Beverage.
What's the hashtag Ben St.?
Why don't you explain that for the audience?
Well, it's the greatest beverage ever created.
You know, created by Munchy Shatsky for whom it is named.
Yeah.
It's whole milk with maraschino cherry juice
and a couple of cherries and you put ice in it and you stir it.
You put in the cherry juice until it's pink
and then you fucking stir it up and you drink it
and it's nice and thick because it's cold from the ice
and it's got the nice juicy cherries at the bottom
and it's creamy and it's sweet and it's delicious
and it's the best thing ever made.
Oh, it just makes me want one so bad.
I'm gonna have one.
I'm gonna have one tonight.
Tonight?
I'll have one too.
We'll dine and wine and slime and chime.
Mmm, slime.
Chime has come spell wrong.
Delicious.
I mistyped in my voice.
The Ben St. is one brand of slime, but it's a good...
It's one of the rare good-aligned slimes.
You should do it.
You should respectful the slime.
You two should do it.
You two should do it stealing your dad as if it was Ben St.
That would be good with the cherries.
Then it wouldn't be a kidnapping.
It would just be a murder.
Well, okay.
Is that actually your favorite...
Is that actually your favorite food though?
Who?
No.
Well, cherries.
Cherries are like, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Cherries are my favorite.
Okay.
Some notable mentions include hamburgers and shrimp
and fridge dips.
Doesn't that probably change?
Oh, that.
Speaking of which, when is that fucking...
Speaking of French dips, when is our stealing your dad's coming out?
Yeah, I've had it for like a week and then I forgot.
But I have all the autos, so probably come out like...
It's got to be Arby's, right?
Right now.
It is Arby's.
Yes.
It'll be out right now.
So, my favorite food.
Now, it's a shit choice.
It's a shit choice for babies, but I can't help it
because I have too many fond childhood memories of eating mashed potatoes
for them not to be my favorite food.
It's fine.
Yeah.
I'm always a big fan.
And you can prepare them so many ways.
You can spice them.
You always leave the peel on.
Leave that peel in there.
Yeah.
That's where the flavor is.
Of course.
Yeah, I fucking love mashed potatoes.
Do you mix milk?
Do you mix milk into your mashed potatoes?
Yeah, some.
Yeah, of course.
Some.
Before we get to...
I guess you don't have to.
Before we go any farther, though.
Potatoes.
That reminds me of your favorite game of all time, Ben.
Did you let Jim spot?
Portal 2.
It's a good game.
It's not as good as Portal 1.
Both of you guys have named very general food, like hamburger or mashed potatoes.
That's fine, but I also want to know, do you have a specific favorite food?
Like, Munchie, when you say hamburgers, surely you don't grade all hamburgers the same.
There must be a place you have a favorite.
I can't pick a specific favorite food, because like every other day, Jackie will make something
that is literally the best thing I've ever tasted.
Yeah.
So it just keeps evolving.
Girl plans.
It just keeps evolving.
Eating real food.
People are disgusting.
Yeah.
It's fucking sick of me.
Munchie!
It is disgusting.
It's disgusting and it's vile, but I can't...
I'm learning.
I'm learning what food is meant to be.
It's funny that we mentioned the bin samed, and then I get to unveil my very own the Munchie,
aka the Chastity Fortress, which is my name for my custom-made hamburger.
It is the following.
Make this at home, everyone, and send me screenshots.
You know that one Twitter that I have pinned, and like send me pictures of hamburgers?
This is what this was made for.
The Munchie.
Two buns.
Three patties.
Preferably buffalo.
You know, buffalo isn't kind of, you know...
You can't really kill them without people like slapping your ass.
Then, for the cheese, you get pepper jack.
Then you get two slices of bacon for each leg.
Sorry, Munchie.
I have to interrupt you because Digi is tapping or something, and it's making...
It's annoying me.
What am I tapping?
What's happening?
I think maybe you're tapping...
You're moving your leg and it's making a noise.
I think you're tapping that ass, bro.
Yeah!
Not my own ass.
I'm shaking on my desk.
Alright.
Continue Munchie.
The secret.
The fucking secret.
The way to make...
The way that elevates the Munchie is when you have the pepper jack, you have to use a
one sauce and Worcestershire sauce.
It brings out the flavor and the peppers.
Right.
And also you can add...
You can add more...
Preferably a lot of pepper jack will be there, so it gives you that tang, and that slang,
and that slime, and that plime.
I think I might have to try that.
I think I might have to make some of those pretty soon.
It's really fucking good.
The Munchie, aka the Chastity Fortress.
The Chastity Fortress?
That's fantastic.
Okay, who's next?
Well, I have difficulty choosing a favorite meal, because every time I've had a meal,
I'm like, well, I haven't had that other meal in a while, so I sort of switch between a few
favorites, depending on how long.
This question is just so did you can talk about his favorite food.
No, I don't even care that much about mine.
This, to me, was the only thing I could imagine this podcast being, was talking about your
favorite foods.
Because it's one thing to talk about food on a broad conceptual level, like we usually
do on the PCP.
That's what I expect this to be.
But that...
If we're going to do a whole podcast about food, it has to get into the bones of it.
We're doing fine.
I was going to give some examples.
I expected Nate to be like, guys, the thing about food is that when you step back and
look at it from a cosmic scale.
That's right.
What even is food?
It's just a little way to delay the inevitable decline of the universe.
That's fine.
We need to evolve beyond food.
We kind of do.
I could talk about nutrition all day.
I could talk about this and that, but I am legitimately just interested in hearing about
individual food items.
I really want to know if you tell me, hey, I ate this at this place.
I'm like, I want to know about that so I can go there and also eat that.
The thing I'm going to say is not necessarily something you can get in a restaurant, but
it is a specific food that is made in England.
It's a Cumberland sausage.
The specific meal I like with it is a Cumberland sausage with olive oil and a bunch of vegetables,
chili and garlic and salt and pepper and a bunch of spices.
Just a bunch of vegetables and Cumberland sausages all mixed up together in a thing
and just roasted for like an hour or something.
It just comes out and it's just perfect.
I don't know how to describe it.
It's probably some sort of thing my dad picked up by watching cooking shows or going to Italy
or something.
He's a very well traversed culinary guy.
He knows a lot about different foods from different places.
He made it and he's great and it's great and I really like it.
Is the dish you're talking about the toad in the hole?
No, I like that as well, but that's more like the hole is made of batter.
It's very easy to make that a euphemism and the toad is the sausage and the hole is like
the weird batter that you make and you put the sausage in there and it's kind of nice.
I got a weird batter for you.
I got a food podcast.
Please let me have sex.
Finally the truth comes out.
I was impersonating you fucking cowards.
It was a joke.
You're not involved.
Yeah, cumberland sausages are the best sausages because they have the most crap in them.
A lot of sausages like German, like bratwurst and stuff, they get rid of a lot of mostly meat.
It's like 90% meat and like 10% gristle and fat.
The cumberland sausages have a lot of the grist and the crumble and the gross shit that makes it just so strangely delicious.
What percentage Dorito and what percentage G fuel is in those and what's the mountain dew ratio?
100% probably.
Here's a thing about food, right?
When I was in college or something, like late in college I got real into exercising and I was like,
okay, I'm going to eat real healthy because at the time I was on college food plan.
I could basically eat whatever I want, but it made no difference.
So I would do like paleo.
I would eat like lots of like lean meat and stuff and fruit and whatever.
And I was fine.
I was like, yeah, eating healthy.
But then I got out into the real world and I was like, wait a minute, I have to pay for my food.
And then I was like, you know what, it's not worth it.
I'll just eat.
Oh no, I'll not let you spread those kind of lies.
That's bullshit.
I'll eat whatever I can survive on.
There have been times, especially like post astro camp when I was just like living in someone's
like side room for free for a while.
There were times, I think at least one day I would like wake up, like go to the kitchen and be like,
hmm, what's here?
What's here that no one remembers buying that I can survive?
And I would eat like, I don't know, like mix up a pie crust and just like eat the pie crust
because that would be my food for the day.
That's pretty alternative.
Yeah, like that's pretty good.
That's pretty good.
Well, over saint for a reason.
I would get creative with it.
Like I would take that pie crust, maybe I'd sprinkle cheese on it or something and maybe make some like,
maybe make some like some cheese straws out of it or something.
Just, you know, just trying to fucking survive in this harsh world.
But it is true that you do need a certain base level of, you know, money to be able to live,
but it is not like it's not like you'd have to be on the fucking whole diet to survive and be healthy.
Yeah.
Don't be like Ben, folks.
Don't be like Ben.
I'm not saying anyone should be like me.
I'm just telling the story.
Ben is necessarily saying that healthy food is more expensive than unhealthy food.
What he's saying is that any food costs any money and he would rather eat literally like,
like Ben eats shitloads of leftover.
So in that case, it's just, it's free.
It's free food.
So the question isn't what kind of food is it?
There's something.
Who is eating it?
I don't know.
I don't know if this is like a learned association I have from those lean times or if it's just
what I'm about naturally.
But I have some kind of, I get some kind of primal satisfaction from taking something that is barely food
and like turn it and like, like, I don't know, like last night I had like a bucket of,
I had like a Tupperware thing of gravy and I was like, I have nothing to eat.
Like we're all out of biscuits.
I can't, I can't, there's nothing I can eat this gravy on.
So I toasted bagels and I put the gravy on the bagels and I was like,
this is an untraditional way of enjoying bagels and gravy.
But you know what?
It's satisfying.
Sure.
All I'm saying is, yes, if you're in survival mode and you'll take whatever you have to
in order to survive.
Which is the only mode that Ben has.
I'm constantly in fight or flight mode.
I understand that you'll just, you know, you'll do whatever it takes.
But I am just saying that it's like, that doesn't apply to anyone currently on this podcast
or to probably anyone listening.
If you're listening to this podcast, you can afford to, you know, eat.
Like all it is is like, instead of buying a fucking 12 pack of fucking bagels and downing
them, instead of buying like a big fucking thing of lettuce and chopping that up and eating
that instead, like it's, you're probably saved by eating.
Fruit is quite cheap, man.
If I had it, yeah, yeah.
If I had any...
Fuck pre-packaged foods.
Pre-packaged foods are the biggest scam in the world.
Never do that.
If I had, if I had like any disposable income at all, I would, I would probably spend it
on food and to like, yeah, I would buy like, you know, like lean meats and stuff because
that's, you know, but whatever.
That's fine.
No, that's fine.
The problem I've always had, this is kind of not exactly food, but cooking.
The problem I've always had with eating healthy and stuff like that is that if I wanted to,
you know, cook food and, and so that I would eat food, I would have to know that I want,
I'm going to be hungry soon.
And I can never think when that will be...
But you, but you know, that doesn't make sense because you always know you're going to need
food in the future.
100% consistent.
There've been a couple of times when I thought, you know, I'll probably be hungry in an hour.
And then I wasn't hungry when I finished cooking.
And I'm like, oh, and then...
That doesn't make sense.
How did you get not hungry after a while?
No, it's that he, he wasn't hungry, but he was like, I should make this food before I
get hungry so that I'm not waiting an hour after I'm hungry to eat fucking food, which
is what my problem is.
Well, the problem there is there's a lack of a routine.
You need a routine.
You got, this is a mechanical thing.
It's not special.
It requires practice, but fuck it.
I was, I was getting to something about talking about like taking like bullshit food and turning
it into a meal.
There's, there's something that, there's something I really appreciate because, because
like I've been watching cooking videos, especially Chef John.
And there's something incredibly satisfying that he does that I did not realize is like
a part of cooking.
But I think this is something that like real cooks will do is he'll take, he'll take,
like he'll take all the ingredients and he'll cook them together, but then he'll like, he'll
use like the runoff bullshit, like, like the extra, the excess crap and he'll reincorporate
it.
Like he'll, like he'll, like he'll be like making a stir fry, like a stir fry filling
for like a pie or something.
He'll fry it in a pan and then he'll take that out, but then he'll like put water into
the pan and like sizzle the like the seared like, like oils and shit off the pan and like
boil that down into like a sauce and like pour it onto the stuff.
Oh dude, I invented that back in high school.
Look at my friends.
No, it's true.
Me and my pals, we invented this recipe and you can do this at home kids.
It's real cheap.
It's a real disgusting experience that will kill you.
But if you're young, if you're, if you're a teenager, if you're young, if you have years
of your life to burn with recklessness, if you try this great recipe that I invented,
it's called the fat noodles.
What you do is, is, is nice.
Fat noodles, aka the endless chess.
I got a fat noodle for you.
That's what it seemed after.
If it's the first to make a bunch of noodles, right?
Just a bunch of regular noodles.
Any kind of noodles you want.
You can go crazy.
It's the choice of noodles is up to you.
This is a free form.
Anyone is like a Western RPG stat building.
Make your own goddamn noodle.
I don't give a shit.
You make, make a bunch of noodles.
Then you fry up a bunch of sausage.
Now this is where it gets tricky.
After you have your sausages, throw your sausages away.
Put them in the garbage.
You don't need them.
They're worthless.
Throw the sausages away and just take, just take the excess, the sausage grease in the
pan and pour them over the noodles.
And now you've got some delicious fat noodles that will kill you.
And it's very important that you do.
Why not just put the sausage in this?
That's good shit.
I'm explaining that.
It's very important that you throw the sausages away because the, the sensation of being a
fat American who wastes food is part of the fat noodle experience.
You have to be as wasteful as possible.
You have to be wasteful and slimy and greasy and just pour this disgusting grease all over
your noodles and then you can be a fat noodle boy.
Yeah.
You can be a real American.
So instead of, instead of, instead of reincorporating the, the stuff, you're just, you're just
destroying the main part.
Yeah, that's the opposite of what I'm talking about.
Throw them in the garbage for Ben to eat later.
You can have your fucking family.
Yeah.
I was gonna say, variant, variant on this recipe.
Don't throw them in the garbage.
Seal them in an envelope and mail them.
Mail them to Ben St. and eat them.
Ben St. send them your sausages.
Yeah.
That's, that's the fate, that's the fate of all disposed food in this world.
Eventually all food flows to Ben St.
It's just the nature of this world.
Imagine, imagine there's just, I'm just like sitting under a funnel with like just bits
of sausage just dripping down into my mouth and then like camera pans out to do this huge
network of gears and like steampunk cogs turning and tubes just funneling food from every landfill
and you mean it here, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da.
Just like you are like a Sephiroth at the core of the Earth and like you have sent out
your avatars, your Ben Saints around the world to gather the resources that you need
and to, you know, complete your little missions.
But all the energy is being funneled towards you at the center.
All this garbage food.
You're standing there, you're standing there in the temple of the ancients next to a garbage
can about to throw away your sausages and Ben St.'s avatar commands your mind to walk
over and hand him the sausage and you're waiting it with all the strength you can muster.
No, he can't have the sausage to destroy all mankind.
I can't give it to him.
But you give him the sausage.
You can't help it.
He controls your mind.
I want that sausage.
I want that sausage more than in life itself.
Get a fucking job, Ben.
Okay, move it on.
Like, like, like Chef John, he'll like, he'll like, he'll take a lobster and he'll just
like murder this lobster right in front of you and he'll pull out all the meat and he'll
pull out all the meat and he'll be like, oh, yeah, just leave, you know, leave the shells,
leave the guts all in there.
That's fine.
And then he'll like, he'll put, he'll put like, he'll put like the shell, like the dead lobster
shell into like a stock, into like a pot and like boil it with some herbs and shit.
And then he'll like take that fucking boiled shell water and like pour it over and like
and cook the meat in that shit because he wants to just retain.
He wants it.
He doesn't want to lose an ounce of that precious lobster goodness that costs like $40 a pound.
You know what I'm saying?
And that's deeply, deeply satisfying.
It's always about Father John with you, isn't it?
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Father.
Father, oh, I was going to...
Earlier Nate brought up...
Father Aden from Secret of Kells.
Nate brought up Doritos and I had to ask, which Doritos are you guys?
What side are you on?
Good question.
Spicy.
Spicy nachos.
Is there a sides?
There's the Cool Ranch and the Nacho Cheese.
All right, here we go.
You fucking racist.
Fuck the Cool Ranch.
Fuck Cool Ranch.
I'm a nacho cheese boy for life.
It's hard.
I think, I just like the texture of like the powdery, the powdery cheese.
Doritos are bad.
I like the nacho cheese.
I just don't think the nacho cheese is bad.
There's a spicy, there's a spicy, fiery one that these people aren't talking about.
It's a third party one that know that the big wigs won't elect.
I'm munchy.
I'm not in the Doritos binary.
My favorite Doritos.
Doritos that are good.
There's that one that Tom's obsessed with and those ones are probably the best.
Sweet chili, I think.
The purple one?
Yeah.
But the thing is that I mostly eat Doritos because they come with sandwiches.
Like you go somewhere to buy a sandwich and they have a chip thing set up.
And the only ones they're going to have are this Cool Ranch and nacho cheese.
That's why this distinction is important.
If the purple one was everywhere, it would be no contest.
It's way better than the other two.
But I think the nacho cheese ones just taste like chips.
They just taste like any other chips.
But the Cool Ranch is like a completely unique flavor to Doritos.
Oh no, man.
The thing about Doritos is they're such garbage and I'm not knocking them.
I like them.
But they're such garbage that it doesn't even matter what they taste like.
Just the fact that they're like a piece of hard bread with salt on it.
Like that's what you're paying for.
And that's what you get regardless of flavor.
I detest the entire Edo's family.
Fritos, Doritos.
I'm going to make a YouTube series called The Ten Edo's
where I categorically go through all of the different Edo's
and why they're all fucking disgusting.
Fritos? Fritos are just toenails.
That's all they are.
They're not even a snack.
I...
No, they're fine.
Love Fritos.
They're gross.
No, because those are the actually greasiest chip on the planet.
They are disgusting.
I hate Fritos.
You got to put them in some bean dip and shit.
No.
If I just put my toenails into a Fritos bag,
you wouldn't be able to tell the difference.
That's true.
Here's the real God-tier chip.
Sour cream and onion laze.
Oh, no.
That's the good shit.
That is the only good shit.
I like the ridged ones.
I also like the ridged ones.
Laze is Wolkers, right?
I think that's the alternative.
The same company, Wolkers and Laze are the same.
I've never heard of Wolkers.
I've never walked before in my life.
Maybe that's the British version.
I think...
Yeah, it's the British version.
There's a flavor of Wolkers that is the best flavor ever.
I'm not sure you have it.
It's the prawn cocktail.
Have you ever had prawns?
The prawn cocktail?
What?
It's a very strange name, but it's a very tangy, delicious flavor.
It's hard to...
No, it doesn't taste like prawn or shrimp.
It's a very strange...
It just tastes like the seasoning?
It tastes like the seasoning you put on?
Wait, is it like prawn as in like PR0N, as in like GamerSpeak for porn?
Is that...
No.
Yeah, prawns, cocktails.
I'm just gonna explain.
These chips just come with a big picture of an anime girl on them.
Every English person knows that is the best flavor of crisps ever made.
No.
And I don't know whether America has it.
I guess not.
I've never seen it, dude.
Every Japanese person knows that consomme is the best flavor
because you can take a potato chip and eat it.
Eat it.
Alright, I don't even like chips that much, so I don't want to keep talking about chips.
Let's get back to the question of favorite food.
Wait, wait.
Who hasn't gotten it?
Okay, yeah, finish your point.
Finish your point.
Well, I was gonna go on something else.
Oh.
If somebody wanted to talk about their favorite food.
I had a dream.
I had a dream one time that I lived in a dystopian America feature.
Then there's just nothing to do with your favorite food.
It does, though.
I had a dream one time that I lived in a dystopian future and America was at war with
the Middle East and things were getting bad.
Things were getting real bad.
Only.
That would never happen, Ben.
But in this world, in this world, the economy, the Middle East was still like the cornerstone
of the world economy.
However, they were not so because their major export was oil.
No.
In this world, the Middle East's major export was breakfast.
Oh.
Yeah.
And one more.
And I awoke in this nightmare and I came downstairs to my bathroom medicine cabinet where
everyone knows is where you go to eat breakfast.
Right.
And I opened my bathroom medicine cabinet and looked inside and was horrified to find
there's no eggs, there's no sausage, there's no grapefruit juice.
No grapefruit juice.
My favorite.
And they're like, damn you, George W. Bush.
What have you done?
We're a war criminal.
How many have died in a war criminal?
Where's my breakfast, George?
And that was it.
That was my dream.
That actually had nothing to do with your favorite food.
It was about food, bitch.
Son of a bitch.
He's going on talk shows now, talking about his paintings.
Everyone's clapping like he's such a good guy.
They didn't, they all forgot he started the breakfast wars and doomed millions to go without
grapefruit juice.
That fucking war criminal.
Oh, god, I fucking.
That, you know, that should have been the plot of food wars.
That's really a bore.
Let me, I know, I know there's divided opinions on this issue, but I fucking love grapefruit
juice.
I know that.
It's not for everyone.
Dude, I bought a big old, I bought a big one the other day and drank that shit.
It was great.
Actually, I like it best mixed with a bunch of orange juice.
I like the orange juice.
I'm all the way into grapefruit juice.
I'm way into grapefruits.
You know, I'm way into fucking love grapefruits.
I'm getting, like, the older I get, I'm starting to acquire this brain thing where, like, the
healthier your food is, the better it tastes to me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because I know that I'm dying and I just can't take it anymore.
You're getting unretarded because you were raised in a retarded, stupid system where,
literally in our country, no one gives a fuck about what you eat because we are the most
retarded civilization.
Yeah, I was raised on fucking poor food.
And now you're learning.
I ate nothing but fast food until I was 20 and I got used to it.
Disgusting.
How do we even survive on that shit?
It disgusts me.
Like, I eat, it's gross.
I eat fast food and I'm like, this doesn't taste good.
It tastes like poop.
I've finally gotten to the point where I can't, like, fast food tastes like shit to me and
it makes me feel sick, but I keep eating it just because I get in the car to go drive
to get food and then something in my brain goes, I don't want to have to wait.
I don't want to have to wait even one minute for my food.
So I'm going to eat fast food and then I regret it for the next six hours.
And then what happens?
You go to fucking Wendy's and you order your spicy chicken and they say, oh, it'll be
about 10 minutes.
What the fuck Wendy's?
I only come here because I want food now.
If my fast food is going to serve me shit and also take long to serve me shit, then
they should be fucking nuked from orbit.
I hate that shit.
You gotta pull to the side and sit, like, on the, on, like, to the side of the drive
to you.
And then the fucking, the girl, like a fucking, like, like a, like a surf, like a lowly peasant.
It's embarrassing for her.
It's humiliating.
I'm embarrassed for her.
I want her to have a better life.
I hate you.
Wendy's.
Die.
I had that happen yesterday where I went, it was, it was like pouring.
I got in the car and the second I got in the car, it started just pouring rain, like
super hard.
And so I was like, all right, well, I'm going to go to a fast food place that I know has
an awning.
Like, so I won't have to get wet at all.
I want to get out of the car.
So I go to Chick-fil-A and I don't notice until I'm like at a point where I can't leave
that there's this huge line.
So I'm in the, like, I'm thinking, oh, go there, so it'll be fast and I won't get wet.
And it's like 20 fucking minutes that I'm waiting just to get some fast food.
Uh, yeah, it was pointless and it wasn't even raining by the time I got the food.
I have an old war story that I have never told about the horrors of the fast food industry
and what happens when their gross incompetence, uh, you know, fucks you in the ass as it does.
It was, it was a long time ago back in my high school days, me and my friends were at
a place and we, and like, like two, two of us were sent out to get KFC for the whole
crew.
The whole group was all there waiting for us.
We had a mission.
We had a holy crusade to find KFC and bring it back.
So we go in our car and we get, we go to KFC and we go to the drive-thru and KFC says,
and I quote, we are out of chicken.
Yeah.
I've had that too.
So what the fuck is worthless?
We're like, what the fuck do we do?
We didn't even know that was possible.
It blew our minds.
It shouldn't be a thing that happens and if there was a just and loving God, it wouldn't
happen.
But so KFC was like a chicken.
Right, right.
What do we do?
The people at the house are expecting KFC.
We had no other alternatives.
We had to go to Arby's.
So we go to Arby's.
Those people are bloodthirsty.
You cannot come back to the house without chicken.
It'll be a bloodbath.
We learned.
Because we went and we got Arby's.
We got these beef and cheddar.
It's like, well, it's not chicken, but you know, maybe they have to understand, right?
Surely they'll understand that KFC was out of chicken.
Yeah.
These are our friends.
They care about us.
They wouldn't cast us out into the cold.
We go back to the house with our fucking Arby's.
We give them the Arby's.
They go, what the fuck is this?
And they like, they like, don't let us come in the house.
They take the Arby's, but they don't let us come in the house.
They take the Arby's too.
We're finished to the outside all night.
It's like, it's like, like 35 degrees.
It's really fucking cold out there.
We can't go in the house.
This is all night.
We are in the backyard.
Me and my buddy, we had to go.
We got shovels.
We dug a trench, an actual World War I trench in the backyard and we huddled and cuddled
in a trench for warmth all night and slept in the backyard because our friends wouldn't
allow us in the house.
We had, we had the dog next to us.
Eventually the dog got let in, but we were still in the backyard.
Even that dog had more honor.
I'm sure the dog had some Arby's once it was in there.
I'm sure they enjoyed our Arby's.
I'm sure the Arby's went over well once they actually started eating it, but we were full.
By that time we were persona non grata.
We were banished from the land.
I just love the idea of them like in there, just like, you know what, I've kind of enjoyed
these Arby's.
No, fuck Jesse though.
Fuck that guy.
How dare you betray our trust like that.
They opened the curtain a little to peer and they can see you shivering then and just
like, fuck that guy.
We were seriously, we dug like a six foot hole in the ground and we were like, we covered
the top of it with like sticks and leaves so it was like a little cave to hide in from
the elements that were battering our flesh.
Meanwhile, meanwhile, these fat cats inside lick their, lick the Arby's sauce off their
fat winged cats.
Holy shit.
Oh my God, yes.
That's the greatest fast food story of all time.
What did you say to those people when you finally got to see them again?
He said, I'm sorry.
I'll never do it again.
Forgive me.
Please.
I'm so sorry.
Jesus.
I'm sorry.
I've brought dishonor to the clan.
Please forgive me so I don't have to commit separate goo.
Those guys are fucking traitors to our race.
God damn.
That's that's some of the sort of race we're over right there.
That's that's that's one.
Well, I have one more thing to bring up which I alluded to in another podcast and I really
hoped Mage would be here for this because she really, she really has strong opinions
on this and doubtless.
She is in the comments right now like angrily attacking me viciously for liking thin crust
pizza.
I mean thick crust pizza.
I hate thin crust.
That's the one.
It's time for this debate.
Thin crust is objectively superior.
It is the best way to have pizza.
I'd be totally happy eating, but I don't why can't we all just get along?
I'd be totally happy eating thin crust and thick crust pizza.
There's skin in the game, Ben.
We've been all about it.
Define thin crust real quick.
What are we?
What kind of thin crust are we talking about?
Okay.
Have you ever had Papa Geno's?
You probably never have had Papa Geno's.
Are we just talking about like normal pizza versus like deep dish?
Because I'm actually not that into deep dish.
I don't know.
But when I think of thin crust, I think of crust that is like it's almost thinner than
the toppings.
Yeah.
Is it hard?
Are you talking about hard?
No, no, no, no.
It's not.
It's not hard.
Like, okay.
There's this place Papa Geno's where I actually worked for.
Actually, I am talking about hard.
I don't like it.
Yeah.
I am talking about hard as well.
Okay.
Well, let me just describe pizza from Papa Geno's.
Because it sounds to me like thin crust is getting a bad rap here.
What was it?
I mean, I'm assuming Nate that what you're describing, what you're going to describe is just New York
style pizza.
Or dictionary.
It's pretty much just normal pizza, but a little thinner.
Like, well, okay.
New York style pizza has extremely thin crust, but it's like, it's that kind that's like
super, it's thin, but it's like almost watery.
It's like, it's like, well, it's like when you pick up the slice and it folds in half,
you know, like that's normal, but when you specifically order thin crust from somewhere
like Pizza Hut or something like that, or like any of the places, they'll give you
like this hard crust.
It's like a super thin, it's like a chip almost.
Okay.
Those, those people are fucking it up.
They're giving bad name because it's supposed to be you because that's what I don't like.
I don't like it when it's crispy.
You.
Yeah.
Thin crust.
It's like really nice.
Yeah.
You like the, you like the.
Oh, because he's a, you're a Pizza Hut boy.
You're a Pizza Hut boy.
I like the cracker shit.
I like it.
It tastes good.
I don't know, dude.
No, dude.
No.
It tastes good.
It's like a party in my mouth and no one of the minorities are invited.
I kind of like, I kind of like, I kind of like the thin, but like floppy, like thin floppy
bottom to my pizza.
Yeah.
I mean, I like all crust, but thin, thin crust is getting monopolized by, they're getting
mistreated.
They're getting the slaver bowl.
I'm a bit of an expert on this.
Okay.
Cause I was, I was a pizza boy for many years here.
So about specifically, specifically, I am, I'm a quarter.
I am a big pizza boy.
Um, so okay.
The great thing about thin crust pizza and it again, like it can't be that hard shit.
That's garbage.
You can't overcook it, but it, it, the, the, the really idea is that it highlights the
sauce.
When you're biting into that, you're not like, you don't have a mouthful of fucking bread.
You've got some of the bread, just a sort of a base foundation, but that's when you can
really enjoy it.
And Papa Jio's has really good sauce.
I think, I don't know.
I really love Papa Jio's.
They're really good.
I mean, to me, to me, a pizza place really comes down to how good is their sauce?
It's all about the sauce.
That's the main sauce.
Like when you eat New York pizza, they're all cooked the exact same way, but if their
sauce is better, then that's the one you go to.
I, I, I went to, I had a lot of New York pizza, you know, cause I went to school in New Jersey
and was always, you know, in the area and, uh, yeah, like they were good.
I don't know.
Papa Jio's is better.
I guess that's the point I'm trying to make.
I love Papa Jio's.
If you're in Massachusetts to the whole Northeast, go to Papa Jio's.
You'll love it.
It's the best.
Get the, get the barbecue chicken pizza at Papa Jio's.
That's my favorite one.
That's pretty good.
I have a feeling.
Got barbecue sauce instead of, instead of tomato sauce.
It's got red beans on it.
I want to take you, Gib.
I want to take you to Papa Jio's Gib someday.
Yeah.
I have a feeling that maybe pizza in the UK is just overall shit because that one time
at BronyCon where we had, we had all that, that pizza delivered to that room.
Yeah.
And it was really nice.
It was, it was just like an actually nice sauce.
Oh yeah.
That was pretty good.
It was a thin pizza, but it was nice and floppy and the, the tomato sauce on it was actually
really, really good.
I've never had a sauce on a pizza that good, which is why generally when there's a pizza,
I only think of what meat is on it and how thick the bread is.
And I like bread.
So, you know, that's, that's the best thing about a pizza for me generally.
Weird, weird thing in, in Poland, like they had like pizza places and like burger places
were not as common there.
And it was weirdly different.
Like I couldn't pinpoint exactly what it was, but like the pizza that I would get in
Poland was just a little different than any, it's like they didn't quite have the same
like, like grade of ingredients they were making it out of.
Yeah.
It was all like, it was all like big and soft and like, I don't know, like a little, like
a little too cheesy and the burgers there, like the burgers you would get there, they
were always like, they were always kind of floppy and pinkish in some, in like the meat
was like pinkish.
It's hard just to cook a fucking burger.
I don't know.
It just didn't, it just didn't, I think like the meat was different or something.
When I was in Tokyo, like pizza was like a deluxe thing that you would, you'd see all
these dudes out on scooters, like driving around delivering pizza, you could, they didn't
even have like in store shit.
You had to order it and like the dude would deliver it.
And this was like a luxury item, but the pizza was still garbage and the pizzas were like
way more expensive and they were fucking tiny.
They're like literally a quarter the size of a pizza here in the Philippines.
Like, there was a point while I was there, it was about two and a half weeks in where
I was just thoroughly sick of Filipino food and I was like, I need pizza.
Like I'm having withdrawals.
But you can't even get like a big pizza boy.
So there was one day it was like raining and I ordered a pizza from somewhere nearby
and it was like, I ordered a large and it was the size of an American medium, you know,
and like I ate the entire thing.
It was, it was all right.
But the thing is like in the Philippines, because they don't really have regular New
York style pizza and they kind of have like two different variations.
You've got Pizza Hut, which is everywhere over there and Pizza Hut looks like a fancy
restaurant there because it costs the same amount that it does here.
But it's, you know, because of the conversion rates, like five American dollars is like
15, like the equivalent of spending 15 bucks in the Philippines.
So like pizza is treated like a gourmet thing.
But then the only other category is like the actual gourmet pizzas.
The ones that are like artisan crafted, you know, they've got like all these really interesting
ingredients and stuff and it's always like 10 toppings and like those, I love that kind
of pizza like California pizza kitchen, you know, but it is fundamentally so different
from pizza that I can't even really categorize it as pizza.
When I was in Japan, yeah, like I always associated like the pizza they had there were kind of
like those like weird gourmet sweet shops would like put all this bullshit fluff and
I'm like, I just want to eat a fucking sweet cake.
I don't need all this extra shit sticking out.
It was kind of like that.
One time in Poland, I ordered a pizza and it was, yeah, like, because pizza is kind
of a specialty item over there, it was a bit on the expensive side, like for pizza, like
considering even though everything's cheaper over there.
Anyway, the point is the guy brought it, he gave it to me, I tipped him, I just didn't
give a fuck.
I tipped him like a convenient amount, which is 20s Lotties.
I gave him 20s Lotties, which is like, it's like seven or eight dollars, but like in over
there, like because of the fucking economy or whatever, that was like a $20 tip.
And the guy gave, the guy looked at me, the guy like looked at me like he was weirded out.
He was like a little like confused and weirded out by the fact that I gave him this like
fucking monster tip on his pizza.
And I was just like, well, I just, I was like a pretty fucking huge tip for a pizza.
Pizza delivery in itself.
I guess it was.
I don't know.
It just was like, here, have some Lotties you fuck, fucking stinky pieces.
Shit.
Well, the subject of pizzas and comparing them, that's part of why I like that pepperoni is
universal because when I go to a new pizza place, I'm going to try their pepperoni just
because that's like, to me, the baseline.
Like you have to, like that's how I'm going to judge whether I'm coming back here.
Then I'll get into your weird shit, you know, but like, I got to know.
Can you do the basics?
And if so, then I'll come back for a second.
Here's the thing about the pizza, here's the thing about pizza is you can, you can eat.
We know from Oolulilia that you can eat nothing but pizza, but still lose weight.
And all you have to do is just eat a normal amount of pizza.
You just got to degrease your pizza.
You just got to soak your pizza with napkins or soak up all the grease from it.
And then you eat it.
And then, and then you're a healthy boy.
I can't, like, on the one hand, I'm imagining like, okay, pizza without grease, that's,
that sounds great, but you're using, you're just going to get napkin all over it.
Like does it not come away tasting like napkin?
You got to pay to play, dawg.
Is I turn it upside down and I squish it into the plate and then you get another plate usually.
Yeah, you just, you just fill it up.
As I drop all my pizza into a fruit juicer and I squoze out all the grease and then I
take this coagulated, destroyed lump that was once a pizza and I shove those in my mouth
like fucking Timbits.
Funnel, funnel the pizza.
I take the whole thing before I cut it into slices and I roll it up and I squeeze it like,
like over a pale, over a pale to squeeze all the grease out.
Jesse, I think you just described how Tostino's pizza rolls were made.
Funnel the pizza.
What did I just invent?
Tostino's pizza rolls?
Funnel off the pizza grease and cook your Brussels sprouts in it and you will have a
new favorite vegetable, my friends.
The farthest part of Radcon 2 was eating those pizza rolls and jerking around.
That was good.
Just go and fucking find all the pizza trees, burn down the pizza forest and fucking smoke
the smoke.
I was eating, I was eating those leftover pizza rolls for like two weeks after that.
I fucking, my body is now your communion, Ben, my body is now your communion.
Ben, do you remember those days when we were up late watching anime and I'd microwave some
disgusting Tostino's pizza rolls and we'd just watch adults swim?
I remember those days.
I mostly remember eating Hot Pockets.
Yeah, there were those two.
God, disgusting.
Don't eat Hot Pockets.
Oh, but closing the statement, Thin Crust Hard is really nice.
It's like a cracker and you can crunch into it and it's really, it's really pleasant and
all of you are aliens and I'm going to eradicate you and stay at the human race.
You know, I honestly don't think I've ever had Thin Crust from like Pizza Hut.
Nate, what's your favorite reserve?
Fucking food.
Right.
Okay.
Let's wrap this up.
I would have to say my favorite food, I'm definitely, food disgusts me in general, so
I only think about it as a tool to live a better life and but you know, it matters to
me how food tastes because I'm a weak human being.
So I would find that my favorite food is definitely, and it is a very specific thing, but it's
not a store thing.
It's this, it's this crock pot, right?
It's just the life of the crock pot.
It's the fact that you can take a crock pot, throw in all this meat and vegetables and
you can, you know, put in everything you want in there and you cook it up and this is the
crucial step.
You got to spice it right.
I do not understand spice, so I have yet to obtain the correct way to make a fucking crock
pot that isn't gross, but I'm working on it every day and it's, it's, it's the joy of
the hunt of the perfect crock pot experience because I have tasted the perfect crock pot.
When I lived, when I first moved to Cincinnati, my, my roommate who was like a Navy SEAL or
something, he, oh not a Navy SEAL, he was like in the Navy or something.
He, seven Fiddles dog.
Yeah.
He, he made crock pot stuff occasionally and he would just be like, yeah, if you want
some, you know, like I made a lot, so feel free to have some.
This fucking dude was the goddamn wizard of the crock pot and like the thing is he spent
so little time making it.
He just had the knowledge of how to do it correctly, which is exactly what cooking is
all about.
You know, it's about, once you understand you're efficient, you get your shit done,
you eat right, you get your, your nutrients in, it's delicious and the stuff this guy
made was out of this fucking world and I'm going to quest to, to replicate it here, but
there you go.
So there it is.
Crock pots.
I love crock pots.
I just want to say as a final word on this topic, uh, that all food is bad and no one
she'd eat it.
It's all bad.
Right.
We're not on the final word.
You haven't even, two of us haven't even given our favorite foods yet and you're one
of them.
Okay.
Yeah.
I meant my final word.
I don't care what anyone else's is.
Okay.
Everyone don't eat food.
It's bad.
There's only four, uh, food groups that matter.
There's only four good foods and those are, uh, sushi, pussy dick.
Sorry.
Don't fucking, don't poker and co-opt my joke, you son of a bitch.
My fucking punchline that I'm building towards is going to blow out anything that you can
think to interrupt me.
You know, I'm so sick.
That's the number one problem with this podcast is I start a bit and one of you cock knobs
interrupts me with, with your own bit and you fucking ruin it every time.
You guys, you don't deserve my bits, but I'm going to keep powering through it.
This is my fucking Kramer moment.
I'm on stage right now at the lab factory.
I'm blowing up on the audience.
I don't even care if it's funny anymore.
You're all blacks.
You're all a bunch of blacks and minorities and I hate you.
We should work on the interruption.
That is true.
Uh, okay.
Well, I don't know.
Who, who hasn't gotten one?
Does anyone who wanted two more favorite foods?
The point that I was making, the only four good foods in the world are sushi, glass bottle
Pepsi, lemon lime, Gatorade, and chicken and tea.
I have discovered.
I'm glad chicken and tea is one food, by the way.
That's the, that's part of the fourth group.
I have discovered cucumber, lime, Gatorade, and I think, or cucumber, something Gator,
it is the most delicious, refreshing, it's, it sounds weird, right?
But it's so fucking delicious.
I highly recommend, uh, wait, what is it?
They serve Pepsi and glass bottles.
Duh.
Fucking idiot.
Yeah.
Cucumber, lime, thirst, quenchers.
Highly recommend.
Go out and buy some right now.
Everybody.
Oh, the fucking Mexicans who, who raised me obviously before I jumped in order.
They have some crazy, some crazy concoctions, some, some crazy modern day potions that they
have since, uh, stored in various home depots across the nation, across this glorious nation.
And if you go to a home depot, you will find there, they're crazy nectar and they're, they're
they're wicked nectar.
Is it called paint thinner?
That's good stuff.
It's called fucked up Coke, AKA just Coca-Cola, but it has really sugar in it.
Oh, is it?
Oh.
Is it Mexican Coke?
Yep.
I actually knew this like 50-something, seven foot tall monster of a man.
His name, his name was Nate and he was like a fit, no, not, not this guy.
He was, he was a fucking, he was, he was like a freelance, he was a freelance physicist
known in the industry and not making this up as a dragon slayer.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
No, because, because like companies, corporations would have like some like intractable science
problem that they didn't know how to solve and they, that would be the dragon and they
would hire this guy to come in and fucking like do experiments and theorizing and theory
crafting and stuff to fucking slay the dragon and fucking, and fucking come in.
That's literally, that's literally me from the future.
That is me from the future.
I guarantee it.
Okay.
It's, it's you and I after we merge into one being.
Right.
And I obtained dominance of that, of course.
It takes your name.
Anyway, he, he swore, point, point is he swore to me that Mexican Coke was the ultimate
hangover cure.
That was, that's where that story was going.
That's cool.
All right.
I just want to know how you met him.
He, he was, he was, he was one of the friends of the people at Monkey House.
Yeah.
Okay.
What's the difference between Mexican Coke and American Coke?
I don't know because I never actually got to try any, but it's just used with sweat
and like ball of sweat and like.
Munchies right though.
There is, there is a difference in the recipe because they're like, you're not legally even
allowed.
I don't know.
There's some difference, but yeah, they, there's, there's a difference.
Here's a funny little story that'll make you laugh every time.
You know how I'm, I'm right, I'm right next to the water.
In fact, I'm underwater right now using my sick underwater mic.
Um, uh, you know how there's like, there's like food in the ocean, which is fucked up
number one.
Yeah.
Like plankton and shit.
Like plankton.
Yeah.
Like eat it, eat it with your, eat it with your grill.
I'm imagining like, like Taco Bell bags, you know, like trash, you know, that kind.
That's straight up silly.
That is straight up silly.
Anyway, one time I, I would never really dabble in the dark arts, AKC food.
I once went to the city of Denver, um, the, the, the weed capital of the universe where
all the, where all the sick illamouts get their good shit.
I once went there and it was a bubblegum shrimp and I reluctantly tried a shrimp and, and
I thought it was really nice and now I really like shrimp.
And more of the stories I had to go to a mountain to, to learn the secrets of, of, of the ocean.
And that's it.
That's just good to show you that food, um, bridges cultures and if you go and if you
go eat a Muslim man's brain, you may learn his actual secrets.
Food works in mysterious ways.
Yeah.
That's, that's a beautiful story, Munchie.
God, I miss the fucking ocean.
I hate being this piece of shit Midwest state.
Ocean is great.
Guys, move to San Diego.
All the other places are gay.
I'd like to move somewhere to a coast.
I honestly hate living here.
I hate these fucking mountains.
I hate this shit.
Where's the fucking sea?
I miss the smell.
Okay.
Anyway, moving on.
Uh, so, uh, did you, I guess you're the last one.
Yeah.
Right, right.
I'm wondering if, if Jesse is still here or if he screamed chicken and tea so loud that
he exploded.
Um, I think it sounds like the explosion.
Yeah.
I am chicken and tea.
Devour me.
I like this guy.
Devour my flesh and drinketh of my flesh.
I am chicken and tea.
It's what I made of.
It's made of me.
I need our audience to appreciate just how often the phrase chicken and tea was uttered
in the Digi Ben and DeVoo household because Ben, DeVoo legitimately ate like mostly chicken
and drank mostly tea as, as did Ben much of the time.
I was always frying chicken and I was always buying a Wawa tea.
So we'd all just like eat up in the kitchen sometimes and we'd all just stand there and
just stare at each other and go chicken and tea, chicken and tea, chicken and tea.
The Doritos, the Doritos chicken that just didn't, just didn't work.
It just didn't hang out.
Right.
I'm just picturing like two guys in a dark, like an empty room sitting at a table with
like a, with a single light hanging over it like in a, like a spy movie, like an interrogation
room just sitting across a table staring into each other's bloodshot eyes just back
and forth chicken and tea, chicken and tea, I'm gay, I'm gay, chicken and tea.
To work, to work, like the video for DNA by Kendrick Lamar.
I don't know if you've seen that video, but it's exactly what you're describing.
Oh yeah.
Yep.
The Doritos chicken would work if you fried it and then you dusted it with the powder.
It doesn't work when the powder is on it before you fry it.
It just doesn't.
It doesn't survive.
It doesn't survive the, the, the frying.
For what should be obvious reasons?
Yeah.
Live and learn.
Well, anyway, yeah, my favorite foods.
Uh, uh, a broad, broad category favorites would be macaroni and cheese, all kinds,
and uh, it's Philly cheesesteak.
Everywhere I go, I try to, like, everywhere that has a Philly cheesesteak, I gotta try
it and like 80% of them are disappointing, but the few that are good are great.
You were just in Philly.
How was the cheesesteak there?
I didn't, uh, didn't actually end up eating cheesesteak there, which I fully intended to,
but it turns out the place that we were at was like deep in the heart of Chinatown, like,
which is massive in Philly, like all we, like we, we, we walked several blocks in all directions
and it was all Chinatown.
So we ate at a ramen place.
We ate at a ramen place that, that was Naruto themed.
Everything in there was Naruto related.
They literally served our cheques in volumes of Naruto.
That is fucking unbelievable.
Go, I tweeted a whole bunch of pictures and stuff from it.
If that we ran into Sean, that, that seems like a likely spot where he would be hanging
out, the Naruto ramen place.
Funny story about that.
I was in Philly maybe like two summers ago and I, like, I had never eaten a Philly cheesesteak.
So I tried to order one and the waitress was like, dude, I live here.
It's like a meme.
It's like a force to me.
Yeah, it is a bit of a meme.
It is a meme.
That's, that's the thing.
I don't think it's any better there than it is anywhere else, although the place with
the best Philly cheesesteak in my city is a place literally called Philadelphia.
So, um, I don't know.
Yeah, I'd love to try on there.
I mean, I'm sure it's just as like much variety.
Like there's probably some places that are good and some places that suck just like
anywhere else, but, uh, but yeah, Philly cheesesteaks are generally great.
But my number one favorite specific food in the entire world is the Kona grill
barbecue chicken flatbread pizza.
You have to go there.
I, this pizza, this fucking thing, because the only place I've ever been to
Kona girl, it's right next to the Baltimore convention center, um, where
Brony con and Otacon were.
And like a couple years back at, I think, Brony con, I, I was, I was just getting,
I was drinking a Kona grill because it's also a bar.
And I ordered this flatbread because it was like, there was like a happy hour.
It's only $7 for like what would be.
It's like half price.
So we, I ordered it and it was the best thing I'd ever tasted in my life.
And I was like, holy shit, this is so magical.
How could this be?
And like afterwards I started ordering flatbreads at different restaurants.
None of them even came close.
So I was like, what is it about this Kona grill one?
And finally a year later, I go back, I go back to Kona grill and I order it.
And I legitimately cried when I ate it.
It was so good.
You know, all the memories, you know, I just want to say, go back to Kona grill.
And experience that again.
There we go.
All you have to do is pledge to the greatest podcast on earth.
The pony cast.
If we raise a thousand dollars, we'll go back to briny con and we'll all have
Kona grill forever.
We'll do it.
Pledge to the pony cast.
The best podcast of all time.
How is that going to get me to Baltimore?
It'll get you and hippo there.
Well, I mean, you can come on your own dime and you can be there with us.
Now it comes to my business executive to say, do not associate with the pony cast.
This is the PCP podcast.
Fuck those guys.
Those guys are trash.
Don't associate that with El Rapia.
They're bad people.
Hey, with that kind of attitude, you're going to walk the plank.
Nate, well, there are Kona grills in other cities.
That's a lie.
I listen to Baltimore.
But but yeah, I've had I even I talked up this thing so much
that people like several people at different conventions like went there
and sent me pictures of them eating the pizza.
And they all said that they completely agreed with me that it was a magical
experience. So, you know, dude, I remember.
Yeah, we were all having dinner there.
It was like you, me and a bunch of these guys.
I know, like Jeff Bridges was there, I think, or not Jeff Bridges.
Fucking that, dude.
But yeah, birches.
And I just I just throw it out of hypothesis here.
I remember we had such a good time there.
Perhaps that sort of instilled that particular flatbread pizza chicken.
I think it was all the good vibes.
I mean, that's the funny thing about you saying that, Nate, is that when I went
there the second time, I was upset because nobody would go with me because
everyone I was that like, I think Otacon and everyone I know is poor.
Like no one could afford to eat Kona Grill or was organized to do it.
So I went alone and it was like a long ass wait.
Like I was waiting forever and I was just like, oh, my God, this thing is
this really going to be worth it?
Like have I have I named myself and then I ate it and it was so good.
I actually cried.
And then I went back the next day and ate it again.
You know, I have one thing I have a confession to make, guys.
There is one soda that just appeals to me on such a deep level that I have no
choice but to enjoy it.
All right, I'm going to post a picture in the chat here.
Here you go.
100% natural berry sparkling water.
Luckuck is my favorite drink in the fucking world.
It's just it appeals to me on so many levels.
Okay, there you go.
Well, I have an actual thing to say.
Thank you so much, Nate.
I want to say I want to say I was going to say the thing about the thing about
the thing about the thing about that is I it smells it smells like like a sweet,
delicious thing, but it's not sweetened and I just try as I might.
I can't get into unsweetened soda.
Are you telling me this is a drink?
This is like a photoshopped image.
It's not actually called luckuck.
Yeah, the drink is that's a terrible joke.
You got me and I got me.
Damn it at our at our cousin Alex's wedding, which was like the most miserable
time of my life, I went to the bar and I looked.
I was just looking for soda and the only soda they had was LaCroix and I took a
sip and I was like, oh, it's not sweet.
I can't deal with it.
So I grabbed some grenadine from the bar and just poured and poured it into my
LaCroix to try and sweeten it and some fucking second cousin or aunt I've never
met before was like, huh, you spike in your drink.
And I was like, no, just just putting grenadine in my in my LaCroix and they
were like, oh, and that wasn't fun.
So they left me alone.
They were weird out and never talked to you ever again.
LaCroix is disgusting.
He committed a serious faux pas that day and they'll never forget.
All right.
Here's a thing that I can't believe none of us have really brought up yet,
which is dessert.
And I have a very specific dessert that is always the best thing after any meal.
It's it's it's literally perfect.
It's one scoop, one big scoop of vanilla ice cream and a hot fudge brownie.
And I have that too.
Mm hmm.
Sure, that's a good one.
That's perfect.
It's it's like it's like God and the devil.
Like the God is the is the vanilla ice cream and the devil's like, you know,
skin, the thick skin, the leathery skin of the devil is the fudge brownies.
Delicious.
The brownie, the brownie is classic.
However, in my opinion, the best thing ever to eat with ice cream is my
favorite pie, which is strawberry rhubarb pie because the strawberry rhubarb
cooks give us the sweet, like the two, like the slightly too sweet and mellow
strawberries with like the tartness, the tartness of the rhubarb combined to fill
this, the strawberry rhubarb pie with this red tangy goo that is just the most
succulent thing on that sweet vanilla ice cream.
I really want to try rhubarb because I've seen people like eat it.
It's good.
You got to come to our neck of the woods one day because our mom grows rhubarb
in our garden and that she makes these giant ass strawberry rhubarb pies and we
get ice cream.
It's not it's not a popular pie.
And I think it's just because people are scared of rhubarb because it just looks
like celery, but it is.
In fact, if you cook it right, it is just wonderful.
It's true. It's true shit.
Yeah. I really want to try rhubarb.
It I've seen it on loads of cooking shows that like people make in desserts like
it's going to be a rhubarb, a souffle or whatever.
I. Oh, I was trying to find rhubarb for the longest time because it was out of
season and I found some in a store and I brought it home and I made a strawberry
rhubarb pie.
I came out OK and then I couldn't.
I wanted to make another one and I couldn't find it anywhere.
And then I was in Atlanta for a while visiting Jackie and and and while I was
gone, Davoo found rhubarb and bought some for me, which was very nice.
Yeah, he was like, hey, I picked up some and he sent me like a picture of him next
to the rhubarb, giving me like the shit eating grin.
And I was like, yeah, so he he brought some rhubarb home for me and I took that
and I took a I took a bag of frozen strawberries and blueberries.
Because so I just I put blueberries in this one.
I cooked it with that.
So now officially, if you make a strawberry rhubarb pie, but you put
blueberries in it, that is now officially the Davoo barb pie.
So all right, hashtag, hashtag, hashtag Davoo barb tweet tweet pictures
at TP Crastinators of you making your homemade Davoo barb pie.
Please fuck making art.
Let's make food.
We're all going to make our own restaurant.
The PC, the PCP Geron.
It will be really nice.
Any one every food, all the food is PCP in it.
That's as Antoine Ego from Ratatouille says, like, not not anyone can become
a great artist, but a great artist can come from anywhere and watch Ratatouille.
It's a good film.
It is a good film.
You're a rat.
Anybody else?
Dessert or we I don't like dessert.
No, no, no, no.
Deserves real quick the best.
OK, OK, two things.
Number one, if you've ever wanted to be raped, go to Mexico.
But also ever wanted to have the most sucky thing ever inserted into
your mind into your mouth and consensually also go to Mexico.
Because I was in Tijuana.
Those two sound like the same thing to me.
Those sound like the same thing. Funny story.
But but they have like they have fried ice cream there.
They have fried ice cream where it's like it's like a hard shell.
And then when you eat it, it's like there's ice cream in the middle.
It's fucked up.
It's not real. It's illegal.
And in fact, I think it might be the most scary thing.
I've had my greatest scary I've ever had.
They have those flamb.
There's there's a couple of combinations.
What was that called?
What is that called when you blow torch?
Yeah, that's flamb, but fried ice cream is different.
Fried ice cream is like fried in like in like in like a bread shell kind of thing.
But but the greatest scary effect.
That was a lie.
My greatest scary is in fact, flan, because I get so scared when I eat it
because I know that nothing else will be better.
So you get some flan and flan is my favorite and it's all it's all it's all like jelly.
And it makes it makes me laugh every single time.
I just look at it and I can't help but I see it's just so fucking funny.
Flan, you make you make you got a good flan going.
You got the night's meal and entertainment.
Flan is really nice.
I like to watch it dance.
And that's the only thing that can get me.
All right, also, also, also another great ice cream thing is literal honeycomb pieces
with dark chocolate and an ice cream.
What the fuck man?
That's deep.
Like if you get literal honeycomb with vanilla ice cream and dark chocolate sprinkles.
I sound that sounds amazing, but I don't know because I've never eaten actual honeycomb.
Honeycomb is delicious.
I've had it.
It sounds fucking awesome.
Speaking of ice cream, there reminds me of something traumatic
that happened to me when I was a kid.
When I was in first grade, my hot, beautiful teacher took me out to get a banana split
at Dairy Queen and she didn't even have the courtesy to molest me.
Why take me out on a fucking on a banana split date if you're not going to have a banana split date?
Wait, is that why it was traumatic because you weren't molesting me?
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, I feel you, dawg.
It's an always sunny bit, but it actually happened to me, so it's still, this is the real thing.
I relate very strongly to that episode.
Here, let me say my favorite real quick.
This is very simple.
There's this particular type of friendlies ice cream, I think, just called forbidden chocolate.
And it is like the deepest, darkest possible chocolate flavor.
And just a scoop of that is just the most delicious fucking thing.
Nate, I remember that on our family outings as youths, when we went out for ice cream,
I know you would always get a black raspberry ice cream.
Was it black raspberry or black?
Yeah, black raspberry with peanut butter cups.
That's correct.
And I stand by that as a fantastic combination.
But I just don't eat ice cream a lot at all anymore.
So if you like ice cream, black raspberry and peanut butter cups is great.
So go ahead and try it, you piece of shit idiot.
I mean, to be honest, what I consider like a dessert, like literally the glass of orange juice
I mentioned before is my dessert, and it's fucking great.
If you can trick your brain, or not trick, but like fix your brain into being like this
glass of orange juice is like, oh my god, this level of sweetness.
That's where you want to be, yeah?
You reminded me of two things that I'm not sure people will agree on.
Orange chocolate is great and also salted chocolate.
Yeah, I agree on both.
Both good.
I agree on both counts.
Do you ever have hot pepper chocolate?
They're the best to have.
Well, what hot pepper chili?
I've had I've heard of that.
I haven't actually eaten it.
It's chocolate with chili powder.
My mom likes it a lot.
I've heard of like chocolate with garlic in it.
OK, that's too far.
Weird, weird.
If you guys had white chocolate, I used to like going around as a little kid.
No, that would be racist.
That would be racist.
I don't eat that shit.
You know what, you know, I do love Hershey's cookies and cream though.
This is white chocolate every day.
Are we still talking about food?
This has been going on for a couple hours, guys.
I mean, I was trying to see our conversation towards something more fun like child molestation.
Yeah, we haven't even gone off topic.
Holy shit.
That's true.
Well, that's because food is the greatest topic.
And I knew it would be.
Yeah, I could go for like another one.
When are we going to do the who got molested the most cast?
That's the one that I've been preparing all this time for.
I've had all my notes for years.
We all like we all I'm imagining like we all come to this to sit down by the PCP.
Like we've all like we're all ready to hear our hot childhood molestation stories.
And we all sit down like we're playing poker and we're all like I and each other.
We're all I and each other up and then someone someone shoots the gun.
Someone shoots the gun to signal that we begin and we all throw our hands down.
We all got nothing.
And we're all like, oh, and then we cry for hours.
We cry for hours on the fact that we haven't been molested.
This is where I find out that my teacher molested all of you and me.
What was wrong with me?
I thought I was your favorite.
Oh, man.
Yeah, dog.
Yeah.
Well, food.
Okay.
Foodcast is the only podcast that I was actually excited about enough to sign up for at the very
beginning.
Like the second the Google doc went up, I was like, boom, food.
First guy there.
No one else is intruding on this.
Well, I mean, food is just incredible.
Everything about it is great.
And there's literally no negative whatsoever.
And the fact is we've only barely scratched the surface of discussion of food I would like to have.
But thankfully, if you, if you too would like to hear much more food discussion,
go subscribe to Munchieshatsky and listen to our podcast.
And all together now, you can watch the best show in the universe.
Steal the bird!
As if it was easy!
Okay, here we go.
Biotch!
Hey, there actually is a relevant question here as I'm looking at our, as our hashtag
askpcp questions.
Make sure you do that shit.
You don't even have to add us anymore.
Just hashtag askpcp.
So let's, let's transition over here.
Here's our dude at Dr. Butts asking, what's your go-to meal that you cook?
Do you got, and he's like, you guys do cook your own meals, right?
Did they know this was a food cast or is that just-
No, no, this guy didn't know.
This guy had no idea.
Unless Dr. Butts is some sort of time wizard.
The thing that I cook all the time is, is, is, is fucking something with pasta.
I don't know.
Undescended proctology.
The last time I cooked was like literally a month and a half ago when me and Munchie
made ramen for the Stealing Your Dads podcast.
Yeah.
I don't think I cook anything.
That is cooking.
Yeah, you boil the water, you pour the powder, there you go.
Wait, I made a loaf of bread today.
I made two little loaves of bread today just because we didn't have any bread.
That's awesome.
So that's, I don't make, I don't make it often, but yeah.
You can make bread?
Homemade, dude, is the shit.
Homemade bread rules.
Oh, you guys, you guys should look into homemade bread yet.
It's fucking great.
I make one thing all the fucking time and it's called a bread basket.
And it's just a piece, it's this goofy little like thing I learned at Boy Scout
camp a million years ago, which is just a piece of bread.
And you like, you put like olive oil on it and you put it, you actually like cut out the center
of the piece of bread and you crack an egg and you put it into the center hole and you
just fry that and then you flip it over, you fry it again.
You make sure that that yolk stays fucking runny so as to not ruin it.
Oh God, my fucking lucky star is falling everywhere.
And then you just eat it and it's delicious.
It's the best.
I used to make, I used to make, I used to make egg sandwiches for myself all the time
because they're super cheap and easy and delicious.
Put a little tomato on there and you're all good.
But since I discovered Digi's Deep Fryer ever since then, I just, I fried chicken,
just homemade fried chicken is what I've done with my life.
That reminds me, there were two, there's two things that I will, I don't know,
call it cooking or not.
I prepare two dishes that I used to eat all the time that I was kind of proud of.
One is just ramen, but ramen with all kinds of extra shit in there where you just like boil
a bunch of onions and stuff in the pot like up until adding the ramen and then like add in
sriracha and all this, like every fucking spice you can find in the cabinet.
Just make a chaos ramen and meat, the lunch meat.
You know who'd be all about that shit?
I mean, this is a fucking gladiolus from Final Fantasy XV.
There is legitimately a plot line where the real ramen, you know, branded top ramen has
like this plot line where gladiolus is like just going on about how like fucking, this guy's like
the biggest, most jacked dude in the fucking world and he's talking about how much he loves
fucking top ramen and like making these piece of shit recipes where you just like, oh,
it's the ultimate flavor experience.
You can add a bunch of extra shit and it's fucking fantastic.
I'm just saying like, I just want to put you guys next to each other.
I want to put you guys next to each other and be like, these guys both eat the same shit.
What is happening here?
What's, what's the difference here?
Well, yeah, I mean, I don't eat it all the time or anything.
But the other thing that I enjoy making is egg salad sandwiches where you make your own egg salad.
Like just take a cup, hard boil a couple of eggs and then throw in like a shitload of mayonnaise
and mustard and hot sauce and pepper and salt and anything else you feel like having in your egg
salad and then just grind that shit up and it can make a couple sandwiches out of it and it's
fucking delicious.
But get it on like giant bread.
Get like a big crazy bread with like a thousand grains.
Bigger than a continent piece of bread.
Here is the second, the second munchie delectable
called Father Guts because I just love dads so much.
Here's what you do.
You crack literally 12 eggs.
That's how much I eat normally.
I eat 12 eggs.
That's like Gaston level eggs.
Okay.
And then, and then you get a huge fucking pan.
Then you make scrambled eggs like normal.
Then you put in the following pepper jack cheese because I fucking love pepper jack cheese.
Then you put in honey ham and you also put in like little bacon bits and then you scramble all
of that and then you just drown it in fucking pepper.
Like table pepper and like normal like actual like big boy like actual like real man pepper.
And it's pretty good.
Sick.
And it resembles guts that I would eat from a father.
By the way, update, food update everyone.
I have transitioned to eating a giant fucking piece of broccoli and raspberries.
Excellent.
I'm living like a king.
Yeah.
Good.
Excellent.
I think we're, we might probably be done for, for the food.
So shall we go on to questions?
You're already on this question.
We are literally in the questions right now.
Sorry.
I think I zoned out.
You idiot.
You're dead to me.
The question who else, what do we cook?
Oh fucking stupid question being topic relevant.
That's confusing.
It is confusing.
Okay.
Well, here's, here's a question that's actually like the worst question ever,
but like maybe we could just say something that's useful.
This guy, this is piece of shit idiot at solely claw asks,
I don't know if this was talked about in the past,
but what's the origin of the PCP?
You dumb piece of shit.
Are you stupid?
I feel like that's been talked about more times than anything else.
So many times.
Okay.
Maybe this guy's a new guy.
We just, there's nothing we like to talk about more than ourselves.
Here's the story of the PCP.
I wanted some clowns to entertain me and juggle.
And so we thought really hard and then they started to materialize.
You know, the ones, the, the, the wicked jesters,
they started to show up and then, and do their sacred jigs
and their, and their cursed juggles.
And oh how I, oh how I laugh.
Oh how I LOL every time I summon them for their powers.
I feel like we should write a, a, a, The Saga Begins Esk History of PCP song.
And then just have that out there.
We should do a lecture on the PCP, University on the PCP.
Love, you know, that there's just go in a fandom far away.
Some ponies were dammaging shit, I don't know.
Digi's Unreleased Footwear lecture was almost a history of the PCP.
It kind of was, it was.
Yeah, I just, I want to see it.
I want to give credit by the way.
It's unwatchable because the fucking audio was fucked up.
Oh, there's a, oh, oh, oh, oh no it's not.
Yeah.
I found it. I have it.
I have footage of your lecture with pretty decent audio.
Like your audio is good, but my audio is dog shit.
No, no, your audio is fine in the footage I have.
Really?
The only problem with the footage that I have
is that it's a close-up on you and you don't see us in the audience, but the audio is fine.
Huh, because when I listened to it, it was like the audience's mic was on, but not mine.
So like you, you can hear me, but I'm like way in the distance and I sound shitty
and uh and everybody in the audience sounds great.
So some, some find the, I still don't know if it'll ever see the Lloyd of Day though,
because the lecture itself is terrible.
Yeah.
It was done at like four in the morning.
None of us wanted to be there.
It's like seven in the morning and I'm, I'm drunk.
Everyone else is tired because either they've been up all night
or they had to be woken up for the lecture.
So like no one is interested in doing it at this time.
The lecture was about me and I was like the least invested of anyone there.
No one was invested at all.
I wish we could do it again and do it better, you know.
That lecture was too long and rambly and you're, the fact that you were drunk really
showed through a lot.
Also I'm shirtless the entire time and I kept knocking down the board doing the
exact same things over and over again that we told you not to do because it would knock
down the board and you kept, you persistently did it for the entire
journey.
Yeah.
If you want to tell the people the story of Endless Jest, just make the Endless Jest
analysis video that you've been saying you were going to make for four years to finally
make me have some success in this neither farce of a life that I've been scraping by in.
I've been meaning to do it but you kept, over the last six months you kept insisting that
you wanted to leave the internet and not draw more attention to yourself.
So I was not sure if I should do it anymore.
Well that's also true but the impetus is on you to find a compromise between my two wildly
contrasting opinions on the subject of my own career.
How about you make an analysis about a mysterious guy that you won't name?
No, I'm not sure we know enough about the mysterious rhinoceros to actually make a full,
yeah, you know, he's just too mysterious.
Well, okay, so but seriously, do the analysis of Endlit G finally the people can see and
it's just me and a Donatello mask.
What's, I'm going to the thing.
It's Procrastopedia.Mirahis or what's the one?
I don't know.
Mirahis.
Like the, there's a wiki, okay here we go.
Yeah, it's Procrastopedia.Mirahis.
It's like a guy's personal thing.
It's not actually a wiki.
If you go to Procrastopedia.Mirahis, we'll put a link in the description.
Dot org, that's like some, you can at least read up to get the basics there.
But just like, if you just watch from the start, you're going to know like 90% of the
shit.
I'm sure we've had podcasts just dedicated to telling you.
The bottom line is that it's all thanks to me.
I'm the reason that all of these people are friends.
They all got together because I am great.
So everyone, the comments that I suck on every episode.
You're fucking welcome for this podcast existing.
Those people have mostly gone away.
Mostly people love you now.
Yeah, I mean, it seems like every episode is Jesse was right.
The comment section.
Yeah.
All right.
Do we have another question?
Yeah, let's see.
What do we got?
Okay, here is a fun one for you folks at home at Muhammad underscore H.
If you were a female, what boob size do you want to have?
And how much would you actually show?
I've thought about that a lot.
If I was a female, I would immediately feel myself.
Well, I think I'd be a modest lady.
The way I've thought about it is that I like girls with like smaller to moderate size tits.
Like I like smaller tits, so I would rather have bigger tits.
So that like I could attract those girls.
Like because I'm assuming I'm a lesbian if I'm if I'm of course.
Whatever you want.
Look, I think about this literally every day of my life.
I've no doubt what I would do if I was a lesbian.
So my ideal is I've got big boobs.
So other girls think I'm hot and they won't like girls with smaller boobs.
Probably don't think there is.
They probably have, you know, aren't as confident about their attractiveness.
So they see me.
Is that real life?
I'm not sure that works.
I'm the hot one.
And I'm like, no, I think you're the hot one.
And you know, if I was a girl, that's kind of romantic, did you?
I like it.
I guess so.
If I was a girl, I would go trans and then be a mannequin.
And then yeah, that's it.
But how big would your booze be?
I would circumvent.
I would still have boobs and they would be gigantic.
Like like dragging it down on the floor.
Like I would trip over my own lips constantly.
Oh my God.
I'm sorry.
Can we just skip ahead to this other question?
Because this is fucking gold.
All right.
Okay. No, I'm sorry.
I'll come back to that.
I'll get to it after you finish.
Munchy, how big would your tits be?
You piece of shit.
My tits would be not, they wouldn't be real.
And you know, I wouldn't like it.
So the answer would be, if I preferably really big,
so it would hurt even more when I cut them off without surgery.
Like an Amazon warrior.
Right.
Yeah.
Well, for me,
I know I talk a lot, you know,
about hashtag killing all women.
You know, that's me.
I started that hashtag.
That was all me.
But I actually think,
I actually have some empathy for chicks with tits
because I think I might be embarrassed about it
if people were looking at them too much.
And I know that I would definitely be modest.
I would definitely be modest about,
I don't know what size they be
because that's a retarded question.
What, have I got a fucking fan fiction
about my own fictional fake female tits?
Yes.
I don't fucking know.
That's what I, I've written so many stories
about lesbians where I'm just projecting myself
into one of them.
I don't know.
Probably small.
Yeah, I'd be modest too.
I'm, you know, I'm the rainbow-dash person.
So, you know, flat DTF.
That's me.
What pony are we guys?
What pony are we?
Oh, definitely, you know, gay.
That's all of them.
Let's just move on to the next question.
Okay.
This is a fantastic one.
At Yukari K. Forgold asks simply,
do you tolerate children?
No.
Never.
Under no single day of my fucking life.
No.
They're unacceptable.
I'm not always.
They are an abomination.
Literally put them in a concentration camp.
You would ever like an entire life.
I'm not around children that much,
but there's definitely an age range
which is always bullshit.
Yeah.
And then there's an age range beyond which they're okay.
So, as long as they're okay, I'm okay with them.
But if they're like yelling and screaming
and they don't know how to not do that,
then I will kill them.
Everybody under 25 should be in jail.
I agree.
Well, that's what we have school for.
That's not even inaccurate.
That's completely true.
Yeah, I advocate for the concentration camp solution
for children.
They should be, you know, brave new world.
That's what we should do.
I think I get along with kids a lot better
than most people seem to.
Everyone I know.
That's because you're a pedophile.
Well, everyone I know is always like,
Yeah, you have to.
Oh, my God, kids are just so terrible.
They're so obnoxious and they're so the shit
and I'll never have kids.
And I'm like, I think it's just because I see myself
as vastly more powerful than them
that like nothing they can do can bother me
because I think this is just the screams of a child.
You know, you're just some kid.
Well, that's why I said if you can talk to them
and they can talk back,
if they can like understand words
and they'll be like, well, what does this mean?
You know, I would humor that for a bit.
I think I could talk to a young child that can speak,
but like a like a screaming baby.
I mean, you gotta eat.
I think of it in terms of like oftentimes,
I'm thinking of this in terms of like,
would I would I want kids of my own, right?
Because like when you see a terrible child in public,
you always think, oh, God, kids are awful,
but it's not kids.
It's just that kid and his shitty parents, you know?
But like, when you meet kids who are great,
you're like, oh, right, kids can be great.
It's a matter of like what kid it is
and how they're being raised, you know?
And it's like, if I know what I'm doing,
to at least some extent,
maybe I can manage to have a kid who comes out cool, you know?
Well, I mean, it's still going to ruin my life,
no matter what, I know that.
Like, you know,
if anything, code name kids next door has taught me
is that we must destroy them.
They're coming for us, dude.
They have the technology.
Yeah, Vincent and Charlotte will be the perfect children.
It will be, you know, twins.
They're going to be raised properly.
They're going to be good boys and girl.
You really named your son after Ben Saints Comet?
I've fucking, Ben probably named his character
after my potential son,
because I've liked that name for a fucking 15 years.
I didn't even know.
I didn't know about that until you,
it's been like 20 years I've been talking about that.
Much later.
And then I remembered Vagler's,
oh yeah, you did say you like that name.
Well, suck it, nerd.
I don't have a fucking copyright on the name,
so I don't like my name.
It's actually been 20 years you've been saying it.
You've been thinking about having kids since you were six.
Final Fantasy VII,
Final Fantasy VII came out in 1997,
which is when I played the game,
and it's been 20 years since then,
and ever since then I liked the name Vincent
and thought I'd name my son after him.
So there you go.
When I was a teenager,
I really hoped I would have a kid and name it Comwy,
and now I want to kill myself.
Oh, God.
Oh my God, like from X?
Yes, like from X.
I can't believe you knew that.
I can't believe I know that either,
but fuck you.
Yeah, it means it translates to child of God,
I believe.
Holy shit.
I'm gonna name my son Naruto.
I just realized that that,
I was like,
why are you all laughing so hard at that,
that I realized it makes it sound like I am God
if I name my kid Comwy.
That's not what I meant.
What the hell?
How could you name him after Comwy and not Kusanagi,
the actual only good character in that show?
In X?
Well, I never watched the show of X.
I only saw the movie.
You never actually watched the show?
No, I watched the movie.
I too only saw the movie,
and I thought it was the coolest shit
when I was like 12 years old.
Because it is the coolest shit.
Let's all go back and watch X.
Yeah, I'm dying here.
Is this the one about the brother and sister
who are reincarnated angels?
Is that the one?
Not quite.
I don't fucking know.
I think it's the angel sanctuary.
No, it's about a guy.
That's what I'm thinking about.
It's called Neon Genesis Evangelism.
X is the one where there's the dragons of heaven
and the dragons of earth,
and there are two different seven-man teams
who have to duke it out in like these like,
this version of Tokyo.
They're fighting in Tokyo,
but they'll open up like these things
where it's like they don't affect the outside world.
And they duke it out with superpowers
and psychic abilities and shit.
But in the movie, it's all about the deaths.
It's all about the crazy ass ways
that people get killed,
and then it ends with a fucking apocalypse
and everything gets destroyed.
And you see people fucking,
there's this hilarious moment
where all these people are running out
of like a church or something,
and you just see a pillar just fall on a guy
and crush him completely
and fall through the earth.
It's fucking awesome.
And then at the very end,
everyone's dead except for the main character,
and he's just sitting there like crying
and cradling his best friend's head
because he had to fight his best friend.
So we're on the side.
Oh, I remember that.
Yeah, I've seen that image.
Yeah, okay.
It's awesome.
Well, 10 out of 10.
Very nice.
And my socks.
What?
Okay, there's another one here.
I cannot believe I remembered
the main character of X's name.
What the fuck?
I saw that movie once like 15 years ago.
I think it's like both the main characters
are named Kamui,
and the fact that they are named that
is a big deal in the movie.
So that's why it's such a memorable time.
I was going to say it, Ben,
because I remembered it too,
but I was like, no, I shouldn't say this.
It'll be too gay if I out myself.
No, Ben, that's not no problem for me.
You took that for me,
and you got us on a cool anime conversation.
Yeah.
Hero.
Here's...
You left over St. U.
Okay, here's a simple question
with far-reaching ramifications.
So maybe this will be our last one,
but it's at Zilovich,
our old friend Zilovich the Minan,
asks,
pessimism versus optimism.
I like to think he's asking,
what's better,
what's more useful?
Optimism.
Optimism, why would you tell me that?
Optimism would be helpful.
Pessimism actually does have some advantages.
It helps you plan for bad things that could happen.
It helps you be a coward and not do anything.
Have you heard of the phrase,
cautious optimism?
Optimism is nicer.
I like nice things.
Like, say that again, did you?
Like, have you heard of the phrase,
cautious optimism?
Like, just...
Sure.
Like, to me, optimism,
it's not about thinking that things will go well.
It's about hoping that they will go well.
Like, just not as...
Like, if pessimism is to always assume the worst,
to think this is going to go badly.
And I think that's actually more limiting
because people won't, like, do things that are helpful
because they just assume they've already lost.
Okay, well, there are degrees, right?
If you think things will go bad for sure,
you'll never take any risks.
Exactly.
Well, okay, if you get paralyzed by it,
then sure, I'm with you.
But, I mean, I don't know how scientific this was,
but once I think I read somewhere that in general,
people who are at least have some elements
of pessimism in their life
are generally actually happier,
and it's because they always expect things to happen for them
that will turn out bad.
And so, when they are surprised that they turn out good,
that actually has a larger happiness boost to their psyche
than people who are optimistic,
who are continually disappointed by the world around them.
What a stupid question.
Have a think about that.
Who cares?
That really breaks that...
Like, because, like,
when I think pessimism or optimism,
I'm thinking like an extreme version.
Like, my parents, my mom is a pessimist,
and she just always thinks that things are going to go wrong,
and my dad is an extreme optimist,
and just always, like, he's just always like,
oh, it's going to work out.
It will work out, no matter what, it's going to work out.
And both of them are, like, wrong in the way that they think,
because my mom will just not do things
because she thinks that it's not going to work out,
and my dad will just, you know, make,
like, assume too much good is going to happen,
and then it's never as good as he thinks it will be.
You know, like, you need to be somewhere in the middle.
You can't just have one extreme or the other.
Right, right.
But, like, I think overall,
if your mindset is things can go well,
then you will be, you'll be more ready to take risks
and do things, as opposed to, like,
always assuming that the worst is going to happen.
Okay, all right, we've got,
here's our actual last question.
This question is the best.
I totally skipped over it before, but here we go.
This is fantastic.
At Slapdash Studios asks Dream Company to shill for?
I love this question.
Patreon.com slash Ben St.
Dream Company.
Okay, well.
Uh, Taco Bell.
Dream Company.
From Software.
He's asking, yeah, like, what company do you want to be like?
Hey, guys, I'm here today on my shitty YouTube channel
to play a fucking gay, gay, guys from gay.
Takati.
Yeah, it's a good game.
Sign me for my mother's basement,
here to show you another great product.
What, mine is exactly, mine is Takati.
I, the beer.
Who, is that again?
I know you've described the beer, right, right, okay.
I want them to just, if they would give me free beer
to shill their beer,
I would shill their beer constantly.
Right, right.
Taco Bell, I want that free Mario Kart, bro.
I want that free Mario Kart.
Are they the Mario Kart, you know,
do they control the means of production for Mario Karts
everywhere throughout the world?
Dude, and when Mario Kart 64 came out,
they were like, if you fucking do that shit,
then we'll fucking hook you up, bitch.
And I was like.
Here's, here's a weird, here's the thing.
Here's the thing I thought as a kid.
It's not directly related,
but I thought that if I bought stock in Nintendo,
the corporation, that would mean that like,
a certain percentage of all Nintendo consoles
in the world belonged to me,
and I could have, and I could have them.
So I kind of wanted to like, invest in Nintendo.
I was like, yeah, I could have tons of Nintendo's.
I don't know, it just sounded like a really good idea.
You could never have, dude.
You could never have.
It sounded like a real good idea at the time.
No.
Does that, would that mean you could go to a friend's house
and take their game because you own like, one percent of it?
Yeah, this is one of the ones that I am in legal possession of, friend, here.
You should have invested your money.
I own one percent of all these games,
so therefore I get to have your games for one percent of all time.
So you'll get this back after that time is done.
Actually, I like to change my answer to a whorehouse.
I would like to shill for a whorehouse and get free whores.
That also sounds great.
That would be ideal.
I appreciate the efficiency evolved in the whore setup.
I really think it's not to be under,
I wish we would invest in that kind of infrastructure, Trump.
That's where our money should be going right now.
I don't even disagree.
So much.
I literally don't disagree.
Oh, God, Alex.
I really really believe that.
I would like to shill for the Calypso Foundation
for the annual Twisted Metal Tournament,
because that's really what we should be investing
and building towards as a country is an annual tournament where
I can drive around in my car and shoot missiles and kill people
and destroy pretty much the entire country
and just leave smoldering fucking ashes
and ruins of cities in my wake and then get a wish at the end.
It's yeah.
It's kind of like The Purge,
only with sick nasty monster trucks and shit.
So, you know, just better in every way.
Dude, a fucking guy in traffic flipped me off the other day
and I'm just like Twisted Metal, man.
How much longer till we have fucking Twisted Metal?
There's legislation in Congress right now
to legalize Twisted Metal.
It's coming.
I'm coming for you, man, who flipped me off you.
You thought you got away from me,
but the Twisted Metal Tournament is coming.
Hashtag it.
It's just the way the wind's blown, dude.
It will be legalized.
Yeah.
Like state legislation is already passing it
across the United States.
Eventually it's going to be adopted federally.
Yeah.
Okay.
Here's mine.
So when I made my or I just I get a lot of shitty comments
on my, on my like Final Fantasy 7 remake
is going to be a piece of shit video.
And this one guy, this one dude, my hero,
was like, dude, you fucking fag.
You fucking know that if Square Enix was paying you
to fucking make videos, you'd be on their fucking nuts
saying how great this remake is.
And I just want to let that guy know he's 100% right.
He's 100% right.
I would definitely sell out in a second.
I would tell everyone how good video games are.
If I could work for Square Enix, I would suck Tetsuya Nomura's dick.
I would do it all.
It's I'm just looking for a chance.
Just give me a chance, guys.
I want to shill.
I want us to be a Square Enix shill.
I want to, I want to shill for, for Mickey Mouse,
not Disney, just, just the mouse, just him,
just whatever he's doing.
I just want to tell people about his, his, his sneaky dealings.
I would, I would shill, I would shill for the Crown City Melee.
Come and see your favorite fucking friends and allies
and heroes all fucking murder each other
and gut each other for fun, for your entertainment.
Where can you, where can you find a broadcast of this?
SaintComics.com, baby.
Handcrafted in Notepad with love.
In another four months, you might get two more pages, folks.
Fuck yeah.
We'll kill you, but not before myself.
I'll take you all out with me when I go.
Okay, sounds good.
I got a better, I got a better sponsor.
Matt, game theory, game, Matt Pat game theory.
I'm going to tell everybody to go, to go over there and ju,
it's just a YouTube channel, a game theory YouTube channel.
And thanks for giving me money.
Fucking mad pat.
Okay, that's enough.
We're done.
Actually, I want to change mine to Arizona iced tea.
So my entire pitch could just be Trayvon.
Trayvon, Trayvon, Trayvon.
I don't understand what that means.
It's because you put tea on a tray.
It's because you put shot, Trayvon Martin.
Oh, right.
You fucking set that up and it shouldn't have worked.
And we all fucking, we all fell for it.
We fell for it.
Thank God.
That was masterful.
Patreon.com slash munchy slash calypso slash twisted metal.
All right, everyone, make sure you send us more questions.
Any time of the week now, hashtag askpcp.
Just send us that shit on Twitter.
We'll see it when I fucking log in.
I wonder what Nate thinks my feet smell like, ha, ha.
And then you should ask that.
That's a good one.
Or what's the gayest thing munchy is doing on today?
And he'll tell you, he'll tell you what it is.
So there you go, people.
I think that's his commenting on a YouTube video voice.
I think that's what he's doing there.
All right.
Thanks for listening, everybody.
We'll see you next time.
Bye.
Okay, done.
XD.
Right now.