Hello everybody and welcome to another exciting, fantastic, jam-packed, dream-free episode of The
Pro Crastinators Podcast. Today we have with us my very best friend and newcomer to Instagram
LeelaloraMate. We got Hippocrit with us today.
Fine bone China. Sick. Sure, Nate is here.
Instagram.com slash bestguyever. Make me an ethernet juggernaut.
It's bestest guy ever. Shit, it is bestest guy ever. Thank you, Tom.
Don't give that imposter who somehow got there first, the follow. Fuck that guy.
And we got Ben Saint. Hey everyone, it's me, professional gerrymanderist
Ben Saint here. You see those lines in the sand, those corrupt politicians drawn. I'm
here to change the whole system. We're reworking all this fucking shit.
I'm going to fulfill a number of useful functions, none of which I will specify.
Fantastic. Let's talk about Instagram, everybody.
Let's get into Instagram. I've been on Instagram for a while. I've actually kind of fallen out
of favor with it as well to a certain degree. But yeah, Instagram, Instagram's an interesting
beast. And I guess they're like changing up the entire algorithm that they've been using
for like this month, I guess. But it sounds like it's a good thing though, because like
the big thing that sucks about Instagram right now is that like, I like the platform a lot
and how it works, but the culture around Instagram is very normie and very fake.
Like it's very thoughty. Too many women. We've got to get rid of some of these women.
Yeah. All right. We're doing a good job. We're going to convince Mage to get off the platform.
So step one down. Let's instigate the Instagram execution
squads. I volunteer to lead this organization and I will serve you at your whim, fair viewers.
All right. That's me. Yeah. But the thing that really sucks about Instagram is just
that like it's it there's tons of the strategy on Instagram to like get big is like make
a repost account. Don't make any original content and then like pay for services to
like automatically to like inflate your account. Like that's a whole thing. There's like things
called power likes where like you get like big, big followers, like big accounts to like
your posts that helps you in the algorithm. And there's that or literally just be any
kind of reasonably attractive woman. And I'm pretty sure that's the only other way.
Women just automatically succeed on the internet. All right. We're not talking about women. We're
talking about like the superior gender that actually has to put effort into things.
Look, just think about this, everybody. Think about this. Endless Jess. Not to I don't think
this is too much information, but like he talked about once his younger sister or something
just had an Instagram. Think about all the stuff that Jesse has done and all that he's
created. And like his little sister on the basis of being a reasonably attractive girl
had like 10 times his following. I mean, yeah, sanity.
Of course, that's just how it works. It's just like attractive women appeal to literally
everyone. And that's not the case.
That patriarchal guy is keeping women down. God, they just can't get anywhere in this
society.
By the way, it's fine. And I accepted that and I will overcome these cruel women to
tell me to get one over on beat them all. Yeah. Okay. But mage, mage, you have the floor.
Tell us your grievances with this platform. Okay, I created Instagram literally just like
a few minutes ago. Wow.
It was my Instagram.
Oh my God.
You guys.
I'm sorry, mage, mage is like, like on a flight tomorrow or something or leaving and she has
no patience for her shenanigans today.
Patience today. We have work to do by that. I mean, we need to communicate like friends
that we are. Come on.
It's just such a burden.
Why do you hate Instagram?
Yeah, yeah. So I created my account just literally a few moments ago just because I needed to
upload a few images for I went to show people like a few images I took yesterday for a trip
I took that that might be a different topic for a little bit later and he was so late.
At first I couldn't figure out how to bulk upload from my phone and then I realized I
have to use the app. I couldn't just do it from the browser. And the reason I couldn't
I wasn't doing it from my computer is a I don't have the photos on my computer and I
don't have the time to upload it them on computer.
You can't upload anything from the computer anyways. It all has to be from the app.
Oh, that is.
Okay, one more reason why it sucks. I hate it.
So, yeah, so I figured out how to bulk upload and it's so tedious. You can only choose up
to 10 images per bulk and that's like shitty because I had like one, two, three, four, five,
six, like 70 or so images. And so that took a bit of time and it's like it's not enough
that I'm limited to 10 images. It's just like after that, after I choose the images, I have
to click next like three or four times and that's really obnoxious. I don't want to share
with anyone. I just want them to be there and I'll link people what I wanted.
It sounds like your problems with Instagram is that you're using Instagram like it's
flicker and it's not flicker.
I haven't used flicker. What's a flicker?
It's another site for sharing photographs, but it's more of just like an upload like
a repository just dump all your photos in. Yeah, it's like Imgur. It's like something
called Flickr.
Oh, okay. I'll look into that.
Instagram is more like a look at my tits, give me money.
Okay, well if I can show them that.
One more thing.
It's like an Apple product and it's really fancy and classy looking.
If it's an Apple product, why can't I install it from my Android? Android, you're doing it wrong.
It should be uninstallable. It's not like.
It's like you can deactivate it, but not uninstall it.
Whoa. I've never heard of Instagram being bloatware built into the OS on Android.
That's pretty cool.
It's for Samsung Galaxy S6 or something like that.
What?
Yeah.
I'm suspicious of this clay image. I'm suspicious. Are you sure that you aren't just making a
mistake?
No, I went to download it on, like I told you, I'm going to download it and then I look,
it's already downloaded. I just had to activate it and was like, whoa, shit.
Because a while ago I was on like deactivating and like deleting whatever apps I wasn't using.
And I guess I couldn't delete it, so I just deactivated it.
So, whoa.
That's weird.
Okay. One last thing. One last thing.
I super enraged that they didn't notice up until right now when I started looking through
the photos, they cropped the photos.
They cropped them to make them square.
I hate that.
Oh my God.
They ruined a lot of the photos.
At least not ruined the display.
That's that.
If it's ergonomic, that's just good visual design.
That's just good spatial reasoning.
Instagram to post their damn fucking, you know, their personal preference on a photo that you
tailor to be a different shape or size.
Come on.
It's a private company.
They can do whatever they want.
Of course.
I had actually heard that they like weren't doing that anymore, but I guess that's not
the case.
No, you can zoom out and have a, you know, a cuboid, a rectangular, that's the word,
picture.
Oh, so does it like just zoom in to make it into a square?
It zooms in to make it into a square and you can move it around to see which putt is
the square.
Well, you're uploading, but like I can customize 70 fucking photos into the span of five minutes,
you know?
Fair enough.
You're using the wrong site.
I was told by a certain person to, it was named draft, but yeah, I guess I'll upload it
after the career if I have the time later on.
But yeah.
Okay.
As Instagram is a normie cesspool, I have had like kind of, I've had fun like being a
normie in that part of the internet and not having any trouble because there's not really
comments.
People don't really comment on anything and I can show it to a family and it's, you know,
I take pictures of my dog and pictures of my cat and pictures of fine bone China.
It's really quite nice.
Follow instagram.com slash hypocrite for all your fine bone China needs.
I actually have an image of a fine bone China teacup that I drank tea out of at a wedding.
So people are just wild for that fine bone.
I'm scrolling down to find it.
Where?
Are you allowed to display images of fine bone China in China?
Not because of the China thing, but because you're not allowed, you know how you're not
allowed to show skeletons, like showing skeletons as considered in a pro, yeah, in China, like
they had to, like they changed the, they changed the models in World of Warcraft of the, of the
undead because like every skeleton boss had to be turned into like a weird zombie guy.
Yeah.
Because it's like, why?
Because I don't know something about something about skeletons is like considered.
I would not want to go to the doctor in China if they've never seen a skeleton.
They don't understand.
Well, I mean, you go to the doctor and you show him your dick.
That's not appropriate in polite society either.
That's a fine bone China for you.
There we go.
Finally, someone did it.
It's like, wait a minute, wait a minute guys.
If it's, if it's, if, if vaginas are so inappropriate, how does anyone give birth in a hospital?
No one can look at a vagina.
You know, I was watching the Handmaid's Tale recently and they just do a thing where like,
they set up like a barrier where like the, the handmaids are like behind this wall and like,
like the doctor can see the vagina but not the woman who it's attached to.
So like they separate it out and it's not, it's like morally pure.
That's the, that's the, that's the both worlds.
If you know what I'm saying, that's the, that's the idea.
Talk about getting the milk for free.
Yeah.
Am I right, man?
Am I right?
Internet high five.
Yeah.
There it is.
Yes.
Um, well enough about Instagram.
Uh, let's talk about a problem I'm having right now.
Okay.
All right.
What?
No, no, you go.
No, you go.
It's not, it's not like I just completed a, it's not like I just completed a, a massive
gauntlet and a milestone achievement.
Let's talk about that actually.
No, that's good.
Yeah.
So I went, I went the entire, uh, so last episode I mentioned that I had started fasting.
I went an entire week without eating.
Holy shit.
Yeah.
I went starting last PCP episode recording day.
It was, it was the day before that.
Okay.
So yesterday I started eating again and, uh, it didn't even feel like anything.
Like Ben, let's just hang on.
Ben just went for seven days without consuming food.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
That's what happened.
Disclaimer.
I want to do this.
Okay.
Disclaimer.
I may, you may say I cheated because I did put lemon in my tea and water.
No.
So I may have consumed.
So I may have consumed up to maybe, maybe, maybe 30 calories or something.
Or maybe 50 calories tops over the entire week.
If your water has, if your water has any atoms of like anything that isn't water, any particulates
you failed.
Yeah.
Do not drink anything homeopathic because it has like, it has the spirit echoes of food
in it, of things that have calories in it and it actually magnifies the caloric content.
Having less of those things in them.
Ben, please tell us the impetus for this and your experience of doing so because it's
quite interesting.
Okay.
Also, how do you feel right now?
I mean, well, you're eating again now.
What have you eaten since then?
Since, since ending your fast?
I mean, I ate a bunch today.
No, not today.
I haven't eaten today.
But yesterday, I just ate, you know, I'm staying keto.
So yesterday I ate pork rinds.
I drank heavy cream.
I ate some leftover pork that was in the fridge.
I ate a bunch of natural peanut butter and celery, you know, just a bunch of keto shit.
Like a normal date.
People warned me that I should ease back into it.
I totally disregarded that advice and threw caution to the wind and it made no difference
and was fine.
Okay.
So Ben, what you're telling me is that all our viewers should, without consulting their
doctor and with wild abandon, stop consuming food, just add infinites.
That's right.
That would be best for that.
That's right, best guy ever.
I mean, I'm Ben St.
Professional Jerry Manderer and professional, non-professional medical advice giver.
And I'm here to tell you that you definitely shouldn't eat anymore.
Look, we talked about being post food.
I've lived it.
I've been to the other side and I've returned and I can tell you, it's really weird.
Around day three, like, okay.
It's hard to imagine doing it.
Okay, okay, okay.
Like day one and two, you know, I was a little hungry.
I was kind of, I was, on day two, I was hungry.
Day three, I was kind of hungry.
And then day four and after, I like, wasn't hungry at all.
I got a little weak, right?
Like I had, I had, there were sometimes where I felt a little fatigued and sometimes I might
get a little bit dizzy, not like to the point that I was going to faint or anything, but
I would kind of be like, you know, but it would, it would, it would pass.
It would pass.
And most doesn't sound great.
That doesn't sound like a great thing to have happen.
No, it wasn't.
It wasn't great.
But 90, 95% of the time, I just felt normal and not hungry and fine.
All right, Ben, do you think that part of the reason you felt okay was because you sit
at the computer drawing and or not drawing?
Yeah, I was going to ask.
And not like moving around that much?
Yes.
I do think that that helped.
I think if I had been like walking around, moving around, you know, lifting crates or
you know, tilling the soil, probably it would not have been as easy.
I feel like this is a thing that people in like history have done.
Like because they need to, you know, people survive because there's no food.
Yeah.
Their body adapts to the lack of food, but they can't go forever without food.
They need it eventually, but they can have like a, like a, a small thing of rice can
keep them going for a week or a month.
For a year.
Like the last day, like, I mean, I walked, you know, I walked like, you know, down the
street to the corner store and back and stuff.
And like I didn't, it wasn't that, you know, it was fine.
Yeah, I probably, if I'd been doing like manual labor or something, it probably would have
been more difficult.
But the reason I did it, you asked before, I mean, because I'm doing the keto thing,
people in the keto, in keto circles talk about fasting a bunch, usually in the context of
intermittent fasting.
But sometimes, you know, I listened to this, I listened to this podcast, well, actually
I haven't listened to it in a while because it got really old and samey.
And I was like, all right, guys, I get it.
There's this podcast called two keto dudes for a while.
I was listening to it and they're like really fat guys.
You know, they're like, you know, they were morbidly obese dudes, maybe still, I don't
know.
And you know, they, they talked about doing like extended fasts like for several days
and stuff.
And I just thought it was interesting.
I was like, well, all right, I want to try it.
And then, yeah, so I started doing it and then, but after a certain point, I was like,
I was like, okay, I know this is not a sustainable thing, although maybe it is.
But I was like, I just wanted to see if I could go for a week just to say I did it and I did
and now I'm a hero.
And yeah, there was a guy who did it for an entire year.
He was a more, there was a morbidly obese guy who, yeah, he fasted for 382 days.
He lost like 300 pounds.
The weight, he's, the weight stayed off.
See, I feel like obviously he was drinking water and he was taking like multivitamin supplements
and like salt supplements and potassium and stuff, but he was taking minerals and stuff
so he wouldn't die.
But he did not consume calories for over a year.
A bad act.
And his body, his body just consumed the energy and the fat.
He was carrying around a year's worth of food.
Yeah.
That's exactly the reason he was able to do it.
I don't think so.
No, no, no.
Of course not.
But like that's like fucking nuts.
Man, I feel like this man became like a plant, you know?
He became like a full synthesizing individual.
How many weeks of fat am I carrying around right now?
I want to do the calculations.
I bet I'm carrying around, I bet I'm carrying around at least a month, at least a month or
two.
God.
How disgusting.
I mean, I, all right.
Maybe, yeah, probably more than that actually.
People get too hung up about having any fat on their body.
People forget the point of fat is that exact reason.
To make you uglier.
To have...
Yeah, talk about Tom's right.
To have fuel on your person.
Right.
You don't need that much in day-to-day life.
The point of fat is God's punishment for decadence.
No.
For our decadent body.
I agree completely.
I hate it.
Which is why it's celebrated in some circles because they're celebrating decadence, which
makes sense.
It's not about being a big bloated boy, it's about having something on your person so
that you don't have to carry a satchel full of granola bars.
Give, give.
I'm hearing a lot of fat envy going on right now from skinny lads such as yourself.
I don't want to be fat.
The position of privilege you speak from.
I've never been fat.
I couldn't ever even become fat, it's impossible.
Exactly.
Fuck you.
Ha ha.
I'll bet we could make it happen.
Begin training montage.
Like a rocky style training montage of Ben coaching Hippo to get fat.
It's like Hippo's doing pull-ups and the camera pans over to me shaking my head like
mmm, mmm, mmm.
And then he's like sorry.
No, no.
We see Gib consuming massive amounts of food in this montage and everything looks good,
but then at the end the music turns to a sour note and then Ben looks down at heart.
It's like oh no, that's not milk you've been drinking, it's heavy cream and everyone's
got keto labels all over it.
He's been losing calories.
Like, like there's no tomorrow, he's become the most fit man.
This is the opposite of what we wanted.
No, no, no, you should drink, you should drink the heavy cream.
You should drink, you should eat, okay what's that stuff that the fucking sumo wrestler's
eat?
I've always wanted to try it.
I love the food.
Chicken nuggets.
There's some.
Yeah, that's right.
Have you guys had buttermilk before?
No.
You're not supposed to just drink it though, right?
The thing is, in Lithuania there's a type of buttermilk that is quite drinkable what
not.
It's a common drink, but it's different from the buttermilk I found in England though.
Is it called kefir?
Yes.
Okay, okay, okay.
When I was in Poland, like when I first got to Poland or close to it, I went to the supermarket.
It was called Biedronka, which means ladybug.
So I went down to my local Biedronka and I was walking around and I couldn't read any
labels on anything.
And I bought what I thought was milk and I drank, I thought it was like peach flavored
milk or strawberry flavored, you know, they have like weird or melon flavor, they have
weird flavors over there.
And I bought it and I drank it.
It was actually kefir, which was very unpleasant because kefir is like a thick buttermilk like
yogurt kind of thing.
So I drank this thinking that it was milk and I was like, oh god.
And then continued.
For you, for losing weight I think, or at least like it's a better alternative to milk.
Is it keto?
Was that Ben's first experience?
Probably keto.
I don't think it's keto because it's like, I mean yogurt's not keto.
Yeah, I guess so.
It's got lactose.
Well, Ben, I've relinquished my title to you as long as fasting person in the PCP.
So I've gone three days and you've surpassed me.
Yeah.
Good job, you did it.
Thank you.
It was total five days or seven days.
In some degree or another, going into the post food lifestyle, which is good to say.
It was seven whole days.
Seven full 24 hour periods.
Wow, that's loud.
I woke up on Saturday and I didn't even want to eat.
I wasn't like, oh finally.
Okay, during the week I had been, occasionally I would be like, I missed food emotionally
much more than I was like.
Exactly.
It is absolutely a mental battle.
Your body doesn't give a shit.
Yeah, yeah, my body was pretty much fine.
But I would be like, man, I wish I had a sausage right now.
I don't have Italian sausage.
I was thinking about salt.
All gay.
I know.
It turned me real gay.
That's just like every day just magnified.
But 99% of the time we don't need food.
Yeah, pretty much.
Our minds that want it.
But I woke up on Saturday and I was like, I don't even want to eat.
I bought this bag of pork rinds, or keto, and I looked at them and I was like, I said
I was going to eat them today so I guess I'll eat today.
And I did.
And I was like, all right.
The deed is done.
I think that was wise.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I didn't want to make this permanent.
Fasting definitely is like an enlightening experience.
You definitely transcend to a higher level of existence.
I feel a little bit differently about food in general now.
It's become optional.
What is the religion that fasts for a heck of a long time?
Ramadan?
Well, there's Ramadan.
Ramadan, I guess.
Or is that just one day?
I'm trying to think.
You can only eat when the sun's down or something in very small amounts.
Yeah, yeah.
Ramadan is intermittent fasting.
Yeah, right.
You know, actually that interests.
Let me tell a story.
I was like maybe three or four, I was maybe three or four days into the fast and my room
or my housemates invited me out to a party.
So I went out and, you know, it was just a small little gathering.
And, you know, there were snacks and, you know, I was offered snacks and I, you know,
I declined them and I explained like, you know, I'm fasting.
I'm not going to eat anything.
And I got, you know, for the most part that was fine.
A couple, there was, there were a couple of like very negative reactions that that got.
And.
Ah, yep.
Yeah.
Those people, I know them well.
Okay.
Well, there were two people that reacted negatively and they both.
All right.
I'm going to give like a complete, here I'm going to break down the complete psychological
makeup of two complete strangers who I know nothing about.
And I'm just going to assume that I'm completely right and you're all going to think I'm really
smart because nobody can dispute me.
All right.
So the first one, right, was a girl and I, and I say that I'm fasting and she says,
and I had a, I had a monster ultra, right?
The zero calorie, because I was drinking like zero calorie drinks because that's that.
I didn't think that counted.
Sure.
And she's like, you're fasting.
Oh, but, you know, you, you know, you're, but you're drinking a monster.
And I'm like, oh, well, it's no, no, no calorie kind.
And she's like, oh, but, you know, it's still, she seemed kind of like miffed about it.
And, you know, based on, here I'm going to be a big racist right now.
Big fucking racist.
Just based on, just based on her complexion and on the fact that she seemed sort of a
little bit like insulted, like you seem like an, from an emotional place.
She seemed a little insulted by suggestion that I was fasting while drinking a monster.
I think that she might have been either, you know, Muslim or maybe just raised in a Muslim
household or have some like cultural and maybe she thought that it was like an, it was like
an insult to the idea of fasting that I was saying I was fasting while drinking this,
this decadent Western chemical swill.
I think that's a possibility.
And then later on, another girl, she was like, um, she was like, uh, you're fasting.
Oh, like, you're, she kind of got mad.
She was like, you're, you're fasting.
I was like, yeah, yeah, you know, oh, I'm keto.
Haha.
Yeah.
Notice how this was both women.
How interesting.
It was, it was two women.
And she's like, and I say that I'm fasting.
I'm cute.
And she's like, you're not in ketosis.
You're in starvation mode.
Your body's eating itself.
And I'm like, well, first of all, you're wrong because those two things aren't mutually exclusive
and you can totally be in ketosis while you're starving.
Like, of course you will be.
Um, and, and she, and she was like, oh, I don't believe in that diet.
I don't believe in that diet.
So, so this person, right?
This person, she was, she was, she was kind of husky.
I wouldn't say she was obese or anything, but she was husky.
She looked, she had the look about her.
She looked like she was on, uh, like women's rugby or a college softball team.
You know?
Okay.
Right?
A large lab.
Well, no, no.
I mean, you just know, like there's a certain, there's a certain kind of look.
Like, you know, like women's softball teams.
Interface or in her like body build?
Both.
Okay.
Sure.
Yeah.
And I think that this person was probably, this person probably had a certain amount
of athletic training, a certain amount of like knowledge about like exercise and diet
imparted to her by, you know, coaches and stuff that was probably in line with the,
um, you know, with the, with the more conventional wisdom of like a relatively high carb diet
and lifestyle for, you know, for, for peak athletic performance.
Yeah.
And this person was probably invested in that idea and had.
Whereas Ben's going for peak intellectual performance.
That's right.
And this person, and this person was probably invested in that idea and had spent a lot
of her, her life, you know, you know, working under that paradigm and was probably sort
of insulted or sort of, sort of subconsciously insulted by, by the, you know, by the presence
of someone who was going about like a completely different strategy and, and she's like, you
know, she had some, I think she had some emotional stake in this, in the idea that Keto, that
Keto is just a fad and it's dumb and like her way is the way to do things.
So there we go.
I broke it down.
That's pretty common, I'd say.
I broke, I broke down the two people that, that gave me, I mean, neither of them gave
me like a huge resistance, but I could tell, like I could tell in both of these people,
there was like a noticeable like things like fasting, Keto, imagine being the kind of person
and I like, I get why I'm not saying these people are crazy or anything, but to, to like,
when someone says, Hey, I'm doing this, this is the lifestyle that I'm choosing to live,
to like, begin to berate them in any kind of way, like, I get it.
If she, she probably really has, believes that she has some degree of expertise here.
Yeah.
You know, if she is an athlete and whatnot, and she sees you in her eyes, making a mistake
and also like propagating a belief system or whatever that she feels is wrong, I get
it.
Yeah.
You know, relax.
Well, I feel like if I was in a situation where somebody told me about a lifestyle that
I didn't agree with, I would mention it, but I wouldn't get angry, I guess.
I'd just be like, well, yeah, it's your body, it's your life, whatever.
Yeah.
I might be a bit passive aggressive.
I mean, I mean, yeah, it sounds like a proper discussion is, you know, a normal thing to
do, but you shouldn't get angry about it or like, don't get aggressive.
No, you should.
You should punch them.
Don't get aggressive because people will get defensive and you'll get nowhere.
Like, you're not going to get listened to if you just come off really strong, like, no
one's going to want to listen to a stranger that's yelling at them to do something different.
That's like the opposite.
Yeah.
Of what you want to do.
By the way, I had, I had a question for Ben.
Did you shit all of the shit out of you and then there was no shit left?
Yes, actually, I mean, all right, I'll, I'll go, I'll go into it.
Yeah.
I basically did not poop for like three days.
I finally did a little bit on like the fifth or sixth day and it was very small, you know,
as you would expect.
Of course.
The guy who fasted for a year, he would, he would go like 30 or 40 days between poop,
but he did, but he would, but he would, yeah, but he would poop occasionally, which is the
most surprising thing.
Well, because your body, I guess you still poop isn't just food.
It's dead cells and, you know, stuff from your body.
So, you know, and then, and then I don't know if it was a coincidence, but after I, but
after I finally ate like, wait, I did, I did poop again.
I don't know if it was like, I don't know if it was because I ate or if it just happened
to coincide.
Um, I will say that it made my poop and farts.
Uh, guy, this is really funny.
Uh, I love it.
It made them smell weird.
Like they, did it?
Yeah.
Like they smelled less like poop and more like, I don't know, they have like a weird musty
smell.
Victory.
Yeah.
Right.
So, I don't, so that's a little, that's, that's some, some TMI for y'all.
I'm inspired, Ben.
I want, I want to go eight days.
I want to top this Saturday.
God damn it.
Christ.
Let's not start another fasting arm race.
A fasting arm, arms, race, arms, race, arms, race, arms.
By the way, the PCP does not encourage you to do any of this shit.
No, no, no.
Without talking to your doctor.
Yeah.
Please.
No, but Ben St. does.
Um, and there you go.
And that's, and that's, no, that's the next PCP race.
It's the, uh, it's the PCP fasting arm race.
The PCP race to the grave.
Here we go, everybody.
It's doing great.
First one to get there with.
I mean, you don't have, I mean, there's faster ways than fasting.
If you know what I'm saying.
I hear you.
Fasting, despite the name, is actually quite slow.
Yeah.
Hmm.
Ironic.
Well, that was a fascinating topic.
Uh, let me, let me mention mine that was so rudely displaced by this whole diversion.
It was you.
You said you talked about it.
You hear this?
That's my ice rattled around in my cup of iced tea.
And when I sip, it hits my teeth and it's cold.
This is my problem.
I don't want to use a straw.
I don't want to use a straw like a pussy.
And I love lots of ice in my big old cup of tea.
And when I drink it, it gets too cold on my lips because the ice is touching it.
What's wrong with the straw?
I don't get it.
Why can't you just get like a manly straw?
There were plenty of straws around me, but I don't like them.
I like to pick up my glass like a man and tilt it like I'm swilling some grog and what
up.
All right.
Who cares about straws?
Why is it hitting your teeth?
Are your lips not there?
It actually hits my lips.
That's what I meant to say.
It's not hitting my teeth.
Yeah.
That was strange.
Yeah, I guess.
I suck it through my teeth like this.
I mean, I have a similar, I understand the problem.
I guess I just don't have as big of a deal with it.
I just use a straw.
It's been like the biggest problem in life.
Like I curve my lip, my top lip like inwards so that the more sensitive part is like sort
of hidden from the ice cold.
But then you get like the liquid on the top of your lip and it's, you can, you can try
something.
Then you just sniff it up.
You can try something.
You just sniff it right up.
Sipping.
I got nothing else, guys.
This was, I feel passionate about this.
I have a talk.
This is the most asinine problem I've ever heard in my life.
But wait, what's, what is, the problem is that the cold ice makes your teeth cold?
Yes.
No, it makes my lip cold.
It hits his teeth.
What the fuck?
That's my problem.
Yes.
This is my biggest problem.
Talk about it.
You know, in China, I don't even have ice nates.
They don't even have lips.
I have a topic though.
Okay, sure.
I mentioned it earlier.
I was, I was on a trip on a guided tour with my mom and it was amazing because I don't
actually go outside of my house that much.
Wait, where was the tour?
Yeah, where was it?
It was in a different part of Lithuania.
It wasn't in one specific town, but it was near a beach town called Konus and that was
the end destination, basically.
And Konus.
Konus.
I think the proper, technically proper pronunciation is Kaunus, but most people just call it Konus
now.
Okay.
It comes from the words to fight, sort of, kind of.
Oh, is this the battlefield of the violence?
No, no, no, no.
It's not my town.
Um, so yeah, like, I just assume all of Lithuania is just your home town, the entire thing.
We talked about Konus before, like, I'm, look, this sounds really familiar.
I don't.
Is that where the tower is?
Is that where, like, the, remember the tower from, uh, from the flag, from the flag episode?
God damn.
My brain has all the, remember?
When they make it a flag, there's like a tower?
No, Ben, no one remembers this.
So let's move on.
No, I'm having a panic attack.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I just remembered.
No, it's from Vidinus, I believe, a Gidman-esque tower.
No, no, this, uh, Konus has its own castle, and I forgot how it's called, god damn it.
Anywho, um, but yeah, the point is...
Bowser's castle.
We visited a few castles and stuff.
And, uh, did someone join?
Yes, but it's a secret. Oh, okay. It's a secret. I worry about it. Sorry. We have a secret ghost
That spoke me and threw me off. Okay, but anyway, any who so yeah
We went to visit castles and what's and then and then the ghost
The death the death of the ghost, okay
so like well
What surprised me is because I was sort of under the impression that most if not all of the castles were completely destroyed in the second
war in Lepinia and
Like both me and mom we're quite
Ah get fucked retards
So both me and mom were surprised was like castles as in plural like we're gonna see more than one
The one in the in the capital. So yeah, it was a pretty fun trip. We had no clue where we were going technically
I mean, we knew the final destination was gonna be Kona's
But yeah, we haven't seen or heard about these places before so it was gonna be pretty interesting
and we learned about a bit of history and stuff and I took a lot of pictures and
I I took a lot of pictures of nature and stuff
But you can see all these pictures
Instagram.com slash legal or me. Yeah, I was I was surprised about how
like
Like two of the three castles that we saw
They're like they were completely ruined. They were like just just like
In complete ruins up until like people started restoring them and even now they're kind of like a little bit shitty
But I guess that's like, you know, the authenticity
We I've had shown bricks that were like over 600 years old and I remember like the thing that I could show you some dirt
That's over 600 years old
Listen like the bricks are held together by some sort of mass and I remember one one of the
Things they used to create that mass was like eggs
And it was like holy shit, and it's still keeping the bricks together
And there was like egg in it and egg yolk or something like that. Did you get to eat some? No
Those bricks are keto. It's like it's like the fight like the final the final stop on the tour is you stop at the mess hall
And you get a free brick
Everyone
It wasn't the brick it was the thing holding the bricks together. I forgot. Oh the more the mortar
I am guessing so that's that reminds me of a quote from the Bible that reminds me of a quote from the Bible
And
I found this I found this while I was making I was making the new map for endless war and I was looking for quotes to
to put in it's like flavor text for each of the different areas and
and
For I found this one, and it's from like it's from Genesis
I think it's from the part where they're building the Tower of Babel and you know the whole endless war slime thing the connections incredible
Beyblade the the tower you remember when Moses part of the Red Sea with Beyblade
Hell yeah, anyway, the point is when they're talking about the Tower of Babel
okay different versions translated differently, but
The King James verbal translated as come let us make brick and berm them thoroughly and they had and brick
They had for stone and slime they had for mortar and let us know about this
Yeah brick they had for stone and slime they had for more and they build us and we'll build us a city
Something something and a tower that reaches under the heavens, and it is so fucking appropriate. It was so great
Literally and speaking of towers
There were quite a few towers with the with the with the castles and like there was one mentioned
No, wait a state thing that we visited as well
It was pretty neat and like there were a lot of towers and I climbed every single tower
And then we also visited a few hills and I climbed every single hill. There were so many fucking stairs guys every single hill
There's a lot of
The ones we visited I meant
Okay, and like oh, it was it was so like my legs were literally shaking. They were literally shaking in their boots
They were like, please mage no more no more walking and it was like it's only 3 p.m
We still have a bit to go and we still walked and we still climbed and I was not
I've never left her house before ever ever since retiring the violent violence
monitor
Thrown back out into the cold uncaring world
Not physically prepared for the hardships that awaited the hills challenged every fiber of her being
And and I conquered every single challenge. It was great
I was I was I was I was very very tired, but I was very happy with myself like one of one of the hills
I'm not sure if it's impressive or not, but like it's just one of the things I climbed
It was like 30 feet high and
It's just one of the things I climbed and and there that was like
Like after climbing like two or so towers in one church
Tower and like another hill basically a lot of climbing a lot of stairs and those stairs weren't even comfortable guys like in the
Towers, they were like old rickety crackety like wooden stairs
I was so I'm really bad at climbing stairs because I have very bad balance. So I was gonna I was gonna fall
I was afraid I was gonna fall, but I never fell so that's good
Glad to hear it. Yep. You know, it's weird
That's all pretty dope. Just just as an aside
Castles are cool. I
Drive by on my way to the store like two or three castles or gigantic churches
Like on in the middle of Ohio in Cincinnati. I mean, yeah, there's more churches, obviously
But I swear to God. There's there's a company nearby
Okay, rather there is just a castle tower that's being built next to a bunch of houses with the sign next with it's just like
Custom-building, you know
Whatever Sanford and Sun's construction and they've got like pictures of castles
They just build castles out here for like people who want to live in a castle and I drive by like every day
Yeah, it's pretty dope. It's pretty dope
That's like sort of neat but imagine having to maintain a castle
If you have a castle, I'm assuming you're paying people to do the main I guess but I wouldn't trust people
Maybe you just maybe you're just like one of those like maybe you're like that girl. Maybe you're like the girl from
That's that fucking that fucking dragon anime
You just love being a maid and you just
And you want and you want to live in a and you want to live in a castle
Specifically because you want to have you to never be done cleaning
Wait, is that what does that true of Toru? Does she want to but she's a dragon, right?
Isn't isn't like her thing that she just loves being a maid and
Kobayashi because she saved her from dying also, she's a big lesbian
Okay bad example then maybe maybe just like maybe you're just naturally servile
And you want to live as a as an indentured servant to your home and to never
It's the situation we're like you've got those like
They're all color-coded and named individually yes. Yeah. Oh my god. I want this
I want so many you give them tiny little like night's pommels on the top
Like they have like like crests like helmet crests like nights
Just oh, yeah
No, they shouldn't hurt each other. No
You make them joust each other
Yeah, yeah, of course the the you have to mount the the lance is too high
So they just miss each other every time they just keep driving by over and over again
And and like and if any of them go out of line you like you you publicly execute
You have a gallows
That's good. You just like pull the power supply out and just watch them like slowly
No, no, no, don't make me sad I love Roomba. They're my boys
They're so good but speaking about it public execution and stuff like that back to the
Speaking of public execution, I have a topic that's near to my heart
Mange publicly executing all her enemies back. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, no
I took a picture of like a tree that has like seven trunks technically speaking of speaking of public execution
Let me tell you about growing up in Lithuania
What about this tree relates to yeah, yeah, and like they were like it's not just a public execution
But it was rumored that people that went out of line were there's like this metal rod coming from the
Well in between the trunks of the tree and it said that people were strapped to it and like got like what's it called?
Like with the whip lashes. Yeah, I think so. Yeah, something that they were punished against this tree
As the rumor goes but the person who was talking about it's like always just a rumor but and like why is there a metal rod in between the
The trunks and why is it at a very convenient height for stuff like that to happen?
How long do you think that rod has been there? Oh a while. The tree is very big
Splits into hundreds and hundreds of years
A few hundred I'm guessing. Okay. Well, that's pretty dope
I like castles. Oh and
I like the castles too as in the same castles as well
Like one of the first things we saw was like this hole in the ground with a big chunky boy at the bottom
Like it wasn't an actual person. It was just like
Like this white mass that's meant to look like a human, but he's a very chunky boy a very obese boy
But it's meant to represent like a human and it was like
This was like the dungeon hole and it was like six feet
Not six feet six meter six meters in so that's like a lot of feet a lot more feet
Yeah, like 18-19 feet. Like 18 feet or something. Yeah, like you ever take
So without any sort of light or any sort of anything it was just a hole in the ground and the people who
disobeyed the owner of the castle were
You know put there and it was very damp very dark very
Lonely and like the only way to get out is if they dropped a rope from the ceiling and and and the god pulled out
And right I took a picture of that
I managed to take a picture of that hole because it was very hard because there were a lot of people in our guided tour
So a lot of people can photo bombing my photos. So
Disgusting
They're trying to get they're trying to get in with the PCP they're trying to yeah
They're trying to achieve that coveted status of being PCP adjacent
A lot of people were hurling themselves into that hole just to obstruct your picture of the contents of the hole
Know what mage it looks like and all of you dear PCP listeners do not
Think about it this way. They don't know I'm mage
So right but they know but they know in the back of it some deep reasons of their mind
They will always remember that they photo bombed you and it's like remember who it was the look of utter
Distain that was shot their way. These these people are all these people are all gonna go home, right with their with their nice little
They're nice little family. There's little family photos
To their into their homes to their homes with their white picket fence and their slime wives
These fucking juvie scum are gonna go home and look at their at their holiday pictures their photo album and they're gonna pull it up and
You know you're gonna have been in some of them, but when they look at the photos again, they're just they're just they're just gonna see like a purple blur
There's gonna there's not gonna be a bird a person there
They're like what what's gonna be like but but the picture wasn't black and white
They have an inventive color photography over there yet. Yeah
Like what is what what is this weird this weird cryptid this weird purple cryptid like?
No, nobody knows nobody knows
One tassel had like five legs around it
Is that a ghost rattling chains do you have chain mail? No, it is it is I the gatekeeper
These are my rot iron keys
I got I got a whole thing I
I'm saying this I'm doing this a new character new character with gatekeeper. He has keys and he rattles them around
I got this bunch of like actual like wrought iron keys on a on a on a circular like
Wrought iron thing like there isn't an opening. You can't take the keys off. It's just connected
Oh, and I got it at a castle gift shop in Leeds castle. No, that's that's if you want wrought iron keys
And they had a whole thing of actual chain mail. It was very expensive
Yeah, and I really wanted well my brother really wanted any cried all the way home cuz he didn't get chain
But um Leeds castle very cool place if you ever I mean I typed in like I was trying to think how many castles
I've been to and which ones they were and I typed in English castle into Google and there's so many oh
I've I've got such a wealth of choices. I think I've been to like 10
Give is I want us to do a rad con
In England come to you come to your pad and then like we just we just either if we have enough money rent a castle
And if not, we just have to shoot. Oh my god
All of our footage at a publicly available castle and make everyone think that we're having rad con in a castle
Not completely impossible. That sounds super sick, and I want to do it right now
Red rad con for a night is like Bodium castle is is one that's like the most stereotypical like castle that all like generic
Playsets were based off of it's a square
With four like circular, you know pillars and and it's like got a courtyard in the middle
And that's basically and it's got a moat and it's like you can go everywhere in that and you can go up to the
battlements and all the cool stuff and
That would be great
Shooting a fate like a YouTube show where people are looking at imagine imagine red con arena
Imagine like a the nerf battle in a castle. Oh, but but but a melee version with real swords
We get the go pros back out with so oh we got to do a melee we got to do a melee
Is there an English word specifically for hills that castles are built up on on
There is I can't remember at them there's a mock for the hills themselves
Yeah, because like the Latvian use is full of them, and I never realized up until like very recently
I guess I like for a while, but
It's called a mutt an m-o-t-t-e a mutt. It's like a an artificial hill used to
You know make a castle be bigger and yeah, okay
Those hills but not a lot of castles because those were all destroyed like yeah
See in like when I was little and people kept like mentioning those hills those moths and I just assumed
It's just another word for a hill and like up until recently just hit me
It's like we talked about a man-made one. Yeah
We used to have like a shit ton of castles that means because we have a shit ton of like moths
So wow it looks like I'm looking it up. It looks like it looks like a burial mound, but it's I guess it's not
I guess it's just a man-made hill. I think I think I think in America. Maybe certain like
Maybe I'm crazy. I feel like maybe certain like Native American tribes or someone had they built these very similar looking mounds as like burial mounds
I know
That's what it looks like to me. I
Don't think it's yeah history. Yeah. I mean, it's possible. Really. It's not really yeah
I've got an important other topic to talk about
And it's great. So it's Dr. Who release trailer that just came out
Have you guys I linked it in the in the chat. It's 30 seconds long. You should take a look
Yeah
What what I'm a busy guy. You think I got 30 seconds to waste on this bullshit. Fair enough, okay?
But I guess this is the funniest round to play. I got cookie clicker to play mother fucker. Yeah, you're right
You're right. This is the funniest thing I've ever seen though because in this trailer
The only things that happen are the camera zooms in on this on her
You know girl dr. Who obviously they pan up as she literally shatters the glass ceiling
Whoops, and she says it's about time
Are you fucking?
So what I was saying is it's time for a woman. I mean clearly
Why do you like that give to that seems really corny to me is my is my
All right, I don't know that really watch dr. Who a lot but I don't it is a very corny show
It has never not been a corny show. It's just that's fair
Oh, all right, the way I would describe it is that you know how one piece has a lot of goofy shit
But it's also the coolest thing ever. It's basically a corny show that occasionally becomes the most incredible
sci-fi badass thing with the characters that you love so much you cry when they die and they're dead and they're not coming back
Oh, it's that was one of those but let's not forget this character has done nothing to endear us to her yet
Obviously, I mean, but I don't know. I mean I can't remember whether they did another like
Hey get ready for Matt Smith or like ready for Peter Capaldi and he says
Here's catchphrase. I guess her catchphrase is whoops, which is adorable. I'm sorry
But by the way, Jesse was here commenting is that when I posted that and he's just
Well, hang on. I just said I just he said like imagine be the boy that gets to put his wiener in girl
Doctor who to which I replied is it gay thinking about her male history. She's and then
There's a debate we could have well
She had a male body and now is the same person in a female body
So, I mean, you know
Jesse just saying I hope the season is about confronting the philosophical conundrum of is it gay and I
Expect I expect at least a line of her going. Huh. I'm not used to this much estrogen
It just am I am I the only one the things she kind of looks like Hillary Clinton a little bit
I mean, I mean, it's her time. It is
This is the best we can do for she didn't get the presidency, but we can give her this
It's way better to become the doctor than to become the president
Kind of well, okay, maybe not you can time travel and me and not change the past and win the presidency
What if I just shit and what it what if what if in this season
Doctor who goes back in time and changes the 2016 presidential election and get Hillary Clinton
the like instead of Trump like what if what if that happened?
That's only a little far-fetched in my opinion
Can't we can't change the past I think they had one episode specifically with Rose going back in time and like changing like like trying to
Save her father from dying and what if they make the one exception for the
Racist evil hero
You know one thing we could only change one thing in history and I think this needs to be it
Rips a hole in space time
Oh, what do you have a problem with holes you fucking misogynist some of us have holes
You wouldn't understand what it's like. Eww, male splater. Come on. That's that's heinous. You're hang on has at least
You're not you're nasty. You guys are all nasty. Don't talk about holes here
I don't like the amount of holes we have
Seal them up. We got seal them up. Y'all are assholes. That's true. Hashtag seal the holes
All right
I just want to bring that up because that was very funny to me what cartoon it was but like oh
I think it was I am weasel and like the IR baboon or whatever. He tried to plug every single hole with plugs
Does that include like his mouth and shit? I don't remember but it
It was there was a very big hole and I am weasel. Yeah
Man, that was that was in my childhood. We're talking about holes in his body
No, no, no, no, like he was like a little hole in the ground and he was trying to plug that up
Oh, I thought you mean in that in that episode. I I think his hashtag plug him up
I think his trade was basically just selling plugs for holes
And I think he did plug I am weasel's mouth with with the plug but just just as like a joke with a
mouth plug
I I have a I have an anecdote for my real life
Right. Um when when the when the gatekeeper was rattling his uh his keys, right? It reminded me
It reminded me of what's going of what what I deal with what I deal with every
Yeah, yeah, it's like it was only yesterday
No
It's what I deal with in my real life, which is that my my housemates have a bunch of bizarre memes
Okay, I'm not the like we've all got like bizarre memes about each other
Sure. Um, so I won't go into everyone else's but I'll they'll talk about mine. Uh mine is um
Uh, they call me they call me thumper because um because apparently because I'm a I'm a lumbering
I'm a lumbering brood of a man
And uh, and when I walk around when I when I walk down the stairs or like walk across the living room
You know, I shake the ground because I have I'm a grace. I'm a graceless gorilla
And um, yeah, yeah as well, you know, uh, but they also call me. You just got that giant brain resting on their shoulders, you know
Yeah, and but but so first I was thumper, but then it evolved it evolved to
Rattle bambi. So now I am called rattle bambi
And
The joke is uh, that uh, you say rattle bambi
Rattle those chains
So that just the idea is that rattle rattle bambi
Jake lives upstairs in his like upstairs attic dungeon or whatever and he rattles his chain and he rattles his chains and eats fish heads
And that's that's rattle bambi and I am rattle bambi and that's that's keto
They are key. They are. Yeah. In fact, okay. All right. So I'm okay with it. Yeah
Rattle those chains
So I'm like, all right. All right gatekeeper. Can we get a rattle for for rattle bambi please?
Yeah, yeah
Hashtag rattle for rattle bambi. No hashtag rattle those chains. Oh, sorry. I wasn't paying attention, but the gatekeeper was
I should send you a picture though. Yeah, please do. Let's put a picture on it. That's a good idea
What are you taking the gates from though?
I would I keep the gates from
Well, any well any of the foreigners well any well any of those keys undo the giant padlock that I have my wrists thrust through
Perhaps no
The stocks that I'm that I'm in as I rattle my chains. These fake keys only open fake doors
Hey, so
This is maybe a dumb topic that I shouldn't even bring up because I I can't even talk about it
Um
Because I don't want to spoil it, but anyone see the the adventure time finale adventure time just finished
I have not seen it and I want to um
I had I had kind of thought
I had I had kind of thought that adventure time ended like a year ago, but I guess it didn't
Yeah, I guess not. They're like announced it was gonna end a year ago
Okay, I remember before before I moved in
Mage turn your fucking mic off. I'm sorry
Ignore
It was okay. Um, so so um
um
So two years ago when I before I moved into digi's place before rad con 2
I remember me and me and my friend, uh, we watched like
We watched what was then all the rest of adventure time
and uh, I remember at the time thinking that like adventure time
Was almost over like the next season was gonna be the last one
But I guess I was wrong because here we are two years later and it only now ended
Uh, someone in my discord the other day said that he thinks, um, he thinks we probably a lot of people thought it had ended
And that we probably are experiencing the mandela effect that in another universe adventure time did end
But we've been transferred to one word where it only just ended now
Um, so I'm so I guess I'm two years of note
So I guess I'm two years behind but I want to catch it up because I was a pretty big fan of it
I remember like back then when I when I when I caught up on it two years ago
I remember that like the general feeling was that adventure time was not what it had been and it had declined in quality
Since the early days, but I remember that time we watched like a dozen episodes and like
I had a great fucking time and we laughed like a shit ton like it was like those episodes were really funny
And I remember coming out of like, huh?
I just kind of assumed that it wasn't the show it used to be but like that was great and like I think it's still really strong
Um, so I wonder if that state I wonder if that held true through to the end
Maybe they've they found like a second wind, you know for the for the end a couple of seasons. I would hope so
Yeah, I didn't I didn't like I didn't like the um
I didn't love how much focus the whole like who's finn gonna end up dating got
I thought that I thought that most episodes focusing on that as a primary point of interest were the weakest ones
um
I I fell off the adventure. I stopped adventuring
In season four at some point. I think it was during or after
Some like spat with flame princess or something. Yeah, and I was just like
I can tell you exactly what episode I uh checked out permanently
From uh from adventure time and it was uh, let me see the 22nd episode in the fifth season
And I hadn't seen every episode but it's the episode the party's over
Isla de senorita
And it was the episode where they attempted to make a real character out of the party god and that's when I knew
Yeah, there was nothing left for me here, but that was bad. That was a bad idea
Because I've been so checked out from adventure time. I loved the pilot years and years before the show ever got serialized
I was the biggest fan when it first came out. Everyone else is a baby compared to me
Uh, but I uh over time like whatever I fell out of it because I was so disconnected
I felt completely safe the other day watching someone's like review slash summary of the final episode
And I gotta say it looked awesome and I want to watch that now, uh because I really liked it
I've been totally spoiled
I've only been I've I've I've received some slight spoilers for the finale
Nothing nothing too big. So um, they were gay the whole time. Yeah
Well, I mean that is that really a spoiler. That's the only thing I know about the finale personally
Right, that's the only thing that 99% of the fandom probably even cares about
Frankly, I don't want to spoil it
But like the message at the end is just exactly what I want to see from like this show
And I was just like when I saw them get to this in this little summary some lady did I was like
Hell yes. Hell. Yes. This is exactly what I want from the show
Adventure is good
What I want what I want is somebody to like put together a
What is important? What is an important episodes to watch of adventure?
I've already saw somebody putting together a tier list of like episodes you can skip to just watch the good adventure time
I want to finish it. I want to I want to wrap up things because yeah
I only vaguely understand that the lich exists. Oh, I kind of want to I kind of want to know
I kind of want to know a bit more about all that because it seems like a villain a lot happens with that guy. Yeah, yeah
Um, yeah, I mean, I think you're in luck
I think people are working on that at these at this very moment
I when I when I saw this finale thing it just filled me with all the happiness
Uh that I had when I first started watching the show
And man, it made me want to just like jump back in and feel those good vibes again
Because adventure time was really good when it was at its best. Yeah
Gets me all for all kinds of ways. Yeah
And it started is am I wrong that adventure time was like the first show that started this whole
Cal arts thing going on. Um
It was like the most intellectual cartoon of the last like forever. Yeah. Yeah, I think there may have been a show
Before but it wasn't as widely known. I guess it was just the biggest one
I think before people god hung up on the whole cal arts terminology people did
Call it like all the adventure time style. I at least I've seen it before
And now that's changed a little bit to the steven universe style
Especially when they love the gaze as they sure do in
the adventure time
I mean the the steven universe style like, um, I I don't want to rant about it for too long
But you know the cold crunch roll original series. Oh, hi guardian spice. Yeah. Yeah. Do we mention it last time?
Be like because the thing it does not look like
Cal arts, it doesn't look like steven universe so much as it looks like. Um, what's that little witch academia thing?
I mean, I would argue me a little witch academia. Yeah
Is that the little witch academia thing? I was I wasn't sure if that's the correct
Naper but hey kudos for me for actually remembering the full title. Wait. Yeah. No, hold on
Was it high garden spice?
This is really remind me of the main character from little witch academia. Dude, are they gonna have it? No, no, there's definitely
No, no, you're 100% wrong and that's that that's literally the dumbest opinion I've ever heard
The show definitely looks western like no one's gonna look at them like oh
A little like more detailed and more anime, right? They're adding a little bit more detail. Um, I don't know
It's funny. Me me and did you're just talking about this on iam games last night?
Uh, we're doing another stream as soon as this episode is done recording. So if uh, you've missed it
So if you can go back in time fair viewers
Six days. Yeah, so
Definitely watch the the upload that we'll have if you missed it you fucking peasants are playing spider-man on ps4 and it's great
Oh, you know what we're doing fable
No, we stopped doing fable because digi got bored and then we went to red dead red dead redemption
And then and then we were playing that and we both hated it thoroughly. So now we're doing spider-man. Yeah
I was like, I would love that. Yeah, that's why we stopped doing it because like if we make a video about this and just trash it
We're never gonna get anywhere. So we'll probably get a lot of views though. I mean if you have a contrary opinion
That's something right and if you sincerely believe it, you know
It was we're kind of at the point where we're trying to like build some good faith for us before we told you
Here's what you do. No, no, no, you make a video doesn't matter. What's in it and you call it the red dead redemption rant
That's all you do and then you get a thousand
And then afterwards after your mind has been changed you do the red dead redemption arc
Oh
Well, the thing is that we didn't want to play through an entire like game that we hated
So because we still have to do all the live streams. It's just like neither of us wanted to play it
um
But yeah, so now we were talking about high guardian spice because it was just like
Because digi obviously made that video that blew up and like because I wanted to be as big as you know and got a bunch of shit for it
uh, but like
I don't think I don't know if the show is going to be bad like that's the whole thing like everyone
Oh, yeah, like this show is going to be garbage
It's like if we if we there was a trailer like they put together for high guardian spice for steven universe
I would have thought the show was going to suck balls, right?
Like because it's it totally has the same kind of virtue signaling kind of like
All we know about it is that the conceit of the show is heavily virtue signaling
So like of course people are going to react like steven universe made it work like somehow
So like I think the aesthetics of the show are are nice like it's clearly not anime
Um, and I don't think this is the way crunchy rolls should be spending their money
See that's the biggest thing for me about this whole crunchy roll thing when I really sat down
I don't agree that like anything any criticisms of the show are valid yet
Uh of the show itself criticisms of the marketing and the advertising so far
I get but the main thing is that people pay crunchy roll to support anime and this is not anime. That's my main
That's my huge issue. That's the big one. I can't wait to illegally watch high guardian spice on kiss cartoon
Instead of kiss anime damn. Oh, what a savage
That's fucking sick. Uh, I will do that for sure
It means you got like the staff who made it like they themselves like I'll show them
I'll upload this to kiss anime myself
God
Yeah, so I think that whole like controversy is way fucking overblown
Did they ever sort of like even
Announce it as an anime?
What was that made did anyone like crunchy roll or the staff ever really call it an anime at any point?
No, no, but they are an anime company and the fact that they're using the money they make, you know
I'm just trying to see how pretentious
I mean, I do not think they've done that particular sin
Yeah, I feel like I feel like they would probably know if they were like, yeah, check out our new original anime
I'm pretty sure that would be you know what I kind of want them to that would be hilarious
Yeah, it would be pretty funny, but I feel like they're too much on the pulse to make such a people like complaining about the name
And I mean it is a fairly dumb. It is like whenever I heard it
Like it is a pretty dumb name, but then I thought about it a bit further now
I think the the main character is called rosemary if I remember correctly and yeah, they're all spices spice
Yeah, and I was thinking like well, maybe that's the thing the high guardian spice spice is kind of like maybe their group name or like
You know how ruby is our wbi, whatever
They basically wanted to make steven universe, but with condiments pretty much
I can't wait to see if I can salt and pepper the the the twins
That's a really cute idea
Oh, I can't wait to make my spice. Oh, see this is gonna be great. That was that was already and that was already in bethy
Yeah, this the blues clues fandom is gonna have some things to say
I want uh, what about I can't wait until uh, I can't wait until the new like the green ranger of the group, uh, horse radish joins
That's gonna be my thing and then the uh, the the asian hire wasabi will be a big
I
Was almost the same thing okay guys
But to be fair like if I didn't know about the whole staff the whole crunchy roll thing
Like all the controversies and I just saw the poster and like the art style and whatever
If I just saw that and knew nothing about it, I would be like, oh, that looks pretty neat. I'm kind of interested to see where it goes
I agree. Yeah, I think it's not offensive. The criticism is more specific than that. They're about right, you know
It's all like like that's the whole thing like that trailer was like the worst possible move to make
And they did it was so up their own asses. I just yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it's true. It was pretty
The one thing that about that that actually made me annoyed is that they said you've never seen a show like this before
And I'm like, here's that stupid. What the heck out of here? I can't I can't imagine
Like the only reason they're saying that I think is because
You've never seen a show like this before because we've got the perspectives of people who are usually
Because the writing staff is 100 like it doesn't like the part. Yeah. Yeah, but like writing staff being agender
Agenda or another doesn't necessarily mean that the show is going to be something right like special
You know 99% of women are just normies like 99% of men are also just normies and they all have very similar opinions
I hate to break it to you guys
But uh, yeah, I mean that whole kind of shadow your glass ceiling all over you ladies
But uh, you know, I guess a man needs to do it every once in a while
So you can see the light all that glass of dr. Who shatters just all over the high guardian spice production
Edit that trailer so that the glass ceiling shatters and just the high guardian spices just come flying down
It's raining down onto the doctor and she says it's about time for high guardian spice on crunchy roll
Basil leaves flying everywhere
I just I like the idea of like people named after spices. It's cute. It's it's mage
How upset you're gonna be if none of this actually happens and it's just like not a thing
I will be very glad because I'm already I'm already standing salt and pepper. I love them
If they're not gonna be twins and they're not gonna be cute, I'll be very sad
Waiting for that horseradish. Yeah, it's gonna happen. It's gonna happen. Our version's already better
Let's all just look like Steven universe is our version of high guardian spice like every gem that everyone knows
Is the thing now in Steven universe? I'm waiting for uh, I'm waiting for a tarragon
Uh, who else we got we got uh, uh, ginger maybe ginger's around cumin
Definitely cumin
Uh, oh, oh wait a star anus wait shit. No, that's actually cool. I meant it to be funny, but it was actually cool. Fuck
lemongrass
Lemon grab ha ha. Uh, you got them. Um guys, uh, let me there was this shit. There was a topic. I wanted to say
It's a it's a uh
Way more serious thing and I completely forgot it. I'll get back to you when I remember. Fuck
That's what I have to say. You made you made smash brothers
Let's talk about the funny fucking earthquake that killed all of Japan. Oh, yeah
Let's talk about those problematic gamers guys
So there was an earthquake in japan recently in Hokkaido. Uh, it's true several people died
I think at least a dozen. I haven't kept track of the numbers
And because the next day there was a smash bros or actually it was not specifically smash bros
There's a nintendo direct that let's be honest. We all know there was going to be some smash stuff
And they delayed that and it has been several days and it's still delayed by the time you hear this
It'll probably be out fair viewer, but uh, but right now it's still delayed and uh, what's the deal? What's the deal?
Uh, I see people being like why are these gamers complaining about getting the thing delayed?
But uh, you know, I get why I'd like a human life is more important
But I don't actually understand the causal connection between delaying the trailer. I think it's really just um
Well, I guess like I don't know. Okay. Look if it is literally isek from uh, uh, from fucking, uh,
Golden sun who has earth shaking earthquake superpowers. I will very much understand why they delayed the trailer
It could have been like, oh, we can't now we can't we can't uh, show him at this time
What if he just gets cancelled?
No way. There's no way
That can't be holy shit. That would be this. Oh man. I mean look most likely
Uh, it's it's somebody else and this is just a delay because it's possible. There wasn't even any smash in the direct
It is possible. So you want to talk about you want to talk about like a company like cucking themselves way too long after the fact
Apple has an event on uh, this wednesday
On the uh announcing all the new iPhones and stuff. They announced that that's coming a couple weeks ago
However, it's a wednesday all like the vast majority of apple events when they announced these products is always on a tuesday
and the reason it's
The uh, uh wednesday is because it is wednesday the 12th because tuesday is september 11th
And they were too much of a pussy to fucking announce their new products on september 11. Okay, you know, uh, uh, uh, that is
Fairly pussy-ish, but but you know if they're just like look guys, we just don't imagine
How fucking sick would this be if like in the middle of the news cycle remembering 9 11? It's like great guys
We gotta stop talking about remembering 9 11. The new iPhones are out
Yeah, yeah
I kind of get on a corporate level. Why'd they do that? Just oh, I get it
I just think it'd be hilarious to just have to jump back and forth between 9 11
You could you could imply you could put like you could put like a little memorial thing in like the video for the new iPhone like
You know, uh, just like the default wallpaper of the new iPhones the freedom tower. You know what it is
You know what it is? It'll be like it'll be like um
The the the terrace tried to destroy america. Yeah, but we came back and we're stronger than ever with the new iPhone
You know why people won't like that. It's because people are made uncomfortable by capitalism
Uh, they don't like the idea of people like profiting off of other people's suffering. Which I get which I get
But you can you imagine the new iPhone, uh, 10 s with reinforced steel rails
You'll both melt this phone
The new 9 phone 11. Yes official for our fallen soldiers and heroes
I mean, it would be the iPhone 11 technically if the 10s the last year's version the 9 phone 11
Oh man, this is a change that the eye to a nine. We've done it team. There's so much good shit
I can't believe that we live in a world where this wouldn't be funny
They do like a the strength test where they where they fire a plane into
Like the jet fuel can't even melt the steel of this iPhone. It's too powerful
Oh, god
Mange you're not american you should you should be more than happy to indulge
No, I don't I'm not I'm not a particular fan of dark humor in general. That's that's the thing
It's not just this specifically lethal aurora mage. What's uh, are you saying you don't like black comedians?
Damn hashtag exposed. All right
Um, should should we should we like move on to questions mage has to leave soon. Yeah, I think it's about time
Unless anybody should we should start with voicemail. Shall we voicemail? Of course, of course. Yeah, let's do it team
Okay, here we go everybody. Uh, remember peeps you can send us some shit at uh, what is it speak pipe dot com
Slash pcb voicemail. I believe yeah, uh, as everybody knows we're we're taking voicemails now and we're we're listening to them
And we're gonna fucking answer them on the show
So let me see what we got first here
Uh, first up is from uh, I think we've gotten one from the sky before at ssb mk1p
I think he has another name, uh, but that's what he's got. All right. All right. Let's see what we got here
Uh, tell us what you got
Hello pcp. This is mudkip slaps here again
With a message regarding turtle gate. Um, I have two pet turtles
Uh, two about two years ago. They made a third little pet turtle
It's box turtle, but he's sick and he has like the flu and I'd like you to wish him good luck while he's getting
Chops every three days. It is very painful for him, but he will endure
Uh, let's see if he's wishing him the goodwill. No, she's on in his kundalini. Oh, thank you
Bless his kundalinis. Yeah
Oh, I just got the flu
Um, yeah, good good luck. May your may your markable may your markable spin you through the through the cosmos
Made the small turtle, uh, board the little battleship and save us all
Yeah, that'll help us out. Is the love is the love battleship like the giant murkaba that's like under the pyramids
Well, it's a it's a three atom thick flat plane that is a spaceship somehow. Yeah. Yeah, that's that's yeah
God love battleship. Uh, okay. Well, I'll pass that on to munchie. We got to let munchie know
So he's the one with the highest christ consciousness
I feel that was directed at munchie to make him mad that a guy can touch turtles
You're right. I think oh my god. You're so right. That was actually a passive aggressive like
You can't touch turtles. Oh, man. I'm touching all these turtles. Well, maybe that's all that's so manila
Uh, all right next one we got uh, here's one from um, omni tanius. I think is how that's pronounced. Uh, hit us up
Is that a
Is that an accordion
Keyboard
Wow, was that was there was it was that going anywhere?
See you next week guys
Yeah, man, buddy
Oh, that was good. Um, all right, we are new outro
Oh new outro, new outro
Um, okay, here's one from um that fucking weird guy. Uh, all right. I don't remember calling into the show
Yo a question for the fuck boys, you know, Nate, digi, munchie, you know
Fuck boys and your head in this modern world where everyone's so fucking into them
So fucking the press and everyone want to fucking kill themselves
Because i'm a i'm a fucking high school boy and there's this girl I like and she loves music and I love music
And we share the love for music and we're very good friends
But I don't know what the fuck to do to make her my girlfriend
Uh, I don't know what the fuck to do and I don't know me. No me me answers. No fucking me me answers
Oh good. I feel so
Oh my god, I do a lot of existential fear and terror from the same
Doesn't he know that fear leads to anger and anger leads to hate and hate leads to suffering
It leads to no gf. So stop that right away. First first first tip. Uh, don't don't clip the mic when you speak to her
Girls girls hate it girls hate it when you clip the mic
You got to work on your gain control dude. That's step one. Wait. He said no meme answers
He uh, he was very specific about
He also specifically directed this to the fuck boys me digi and munchie, but yeah, feel free. Yeah
I think uh, no, I think I think we're no we're we all we all gotta wait
We all gotta weigh in and help and help this poor
Yeah, help this poor guy get get the get the lady that he originally deserves this is as it is as is his birthright as a proud white man
um, that's right
I think he's argentinian actually. Have you considered uh, have you considered have you considered stealing something dear to her and holding it hostage?
Do not listen to Ben
To to to be real if he has like he likes music and he knows she likes music then there's your answer
Just talk to her about music and then maybe find other things you like to figure it out
You know, I know this guy's main problem. This guy's main problem is that he's in the depths of the friend zone for sure
For sure. I mean, I'm not clear on if he even knows this girl at all. Like he said they're good friends
He said yeah, that was gonna be my thing is that dude you're you're too late. You're too late. You're too well
It's not too late. It's not too late, but here's what you here's the thing
Definitely uphill here. Well, here's what you gotta do. Here's it might be too late, but you know, you never know
You just gotta fucking say it
You just gotta say hey, I have feelings for you because yeah, if you do that may
And she doesn't reciprocate might it ruin your friendship? Yep, but guess what your friendship's already fucking exactly
It's already fucking weird because you feel this way in the first place
Yeah, you gotta you gotta man up and like if you get rejected you get ljbf
You gotta be like fine by and just so don't don't even fucking sweat it don't even sweat it bro
Ben is right but Ben is right
But the reason why like think about it like this the reason why it's a good idea to just say something instantly is because
That shows
Confidence is because that and like so but like and that's really the important thing here
Like if you want to actually get this girl, I know I said this is somebody in the past
But like okay, like it depends on how deep in the friend zone you are with this person
But here's what I would do if you want this girl
I would honestly assess your sexual market value. Are you actually someone who would you would want to date?
If not, then here's what you do
You begin working on that and becoming a better person and then you start dating other girls
You start dating other girls and you can do this in a cold sociopathic way
Just so you can get experience so you can come back and get this girl later
No, this is this is good. This will work. It will take time, but it does work. I know that's right
You will take a long time this guy that's gonna take like years and like but this is this is why I say that
There's no fucking time for there's there's no fucking time for that bullshit. I mean as it relates as it relates to this girl
He was a high school boy. So he only has a certain number of years to get it done before that
That's all the more reason to just you can just put it out there and then drop it if it doesn't work out
What do you mean you can have it done in a month? You can like totally change your whole public persona in a month
You can totally change you have
Okay, okay. Sorry. Everything here depends on how deep in the friend zone
He is only he knows that that is the crucial element here
If if this person if you like grew up with her
It's like it's been a long time and like you're just like her buddy and she doesn't think you're like cool or anything
And like what do you what would she want to date you if she just met you today for the first time?
That's that's an important question to ask
But like I look if you want the short the shortcut version
Uh, that's actually fine. I would say go with ben literally tell her instantly that you are into her and just don't delay
There's no reason to wait. It's fine
There is no reason to wait
But like I guess if you want to take a slower longer path that like if you need to work your way up
So that you would even possibly consider it
Then I would say literally stop being such good friends with her
And go do other things so that you don't like she needs to know that you are a valuable guy
Weird Machiavellian. I don't know. I don't know exactly what it is. That's how inter gender dynamics works. That's like like, okay
Yeah, you should go and work on yourself and improve your your sexual market value
Is you make make yourself a better a cooler and more more more interesting and attractive person that people want to be run
Obviously, you should do that. You should not do that for the purpose of getting this one girl. That's weird 100% right
That's right. Yeah, the real the real solution here
And I know that this is impossible the real solution is to not care about any one specific girl and have oneitis
It's to just you get it. Whatever like like like like
It's like it's already set in stone. Either this is on or it's off. I'm gonna be real. It's almost definitely off
But it doesn't matter
You should you should you should just say something anyway, because because nothing ventured nothing right right now
You're just suffering your own mental prison. Yeah, fuck that shit get out one way or the other
My strategy. Look, maybe my thought would I'm actually with ben here now that I've thought about it more
Literally just say like whatever dude. Don't make it a big romantic thing. Just like no whatever when you're hanging out with
Everyone's is like just to be like, hey, I like you like I want to date you or whatever
I think that you're really special and I like hanging out with you. Let's you know, I'd like to date
I think you're cute whatever
You just got to make it clear in some way and do not worry about the details too much
It's important that you just do it because that shows that you're a cool guy
That is someone worthy of dating her just by by not look every guy out there
Is is a pussy who likes a girl and doesn't just say something to her and I've been there too
I'm a pussy too in a lot of ways, but uh
Be not a pussy and just go for it and if it fails. Well, sorry about that buddy
But don't and don't go school shooter when you get rejected
That's an important step would be would be my final word on that
Oh god, no, we gave another meme answer now. He is gonna become a school shooter. We did what he said not to do
Nuts, we did our best
Okay, here's one. I think that was a pretty great answer. Yeah more than he deserved frankly
Um, here's one from the argentinian guy. Uh, let's see what we've got here
You're back and what's the deal with manji and his hate for south america and argentina
You know, we may have chosen they were on people to run our countries
We may be racist between each other
We may have forgotten the spirit that our ancestor had when making our countries free from the europeans and
Oh
Yeah, he's just responding to I think manji said something about he's in south america people
Oh, he realized he realized that manji was right. Does manji hate south america?
I mean, he was meman about it. He wasn't even about it. Yeah, okay
I mean manji's basically south american anyway. He's like a quarter mexican or something. So, you know, yeah, so it's the same thing
close enough
Wow, I mean nobody. Yeah, let's move on. I mean, I think I hate south america now after hearing all after hearing that
That argument. Yeah, that's fair. That's fair. All right. Here's one from uh from one spar
Let's see what he's got for us
Hello procrastinators. Once again, it is one spar of one spar weekly indeed
This voicemail is not actually for you. This is for the viewers viewers
I am posting a public bounty right here right now
I'm looking for timestamps of
Nate bestman aka the quote unquote best quote unquote guy quote unquote ever
And specifically timestamps of him mentioning star fleet
That's right all timestamps of Nate bestman mentioning star fleet on the procrastinators podcast
Just pay a lot for this post them in the comments or post them on the pcp patron discord where I am for right now
And uh, if you do it fast enough, they will show up
soon in a compilation that will
prove just how
star fleet
Nate
is
Wow. Yeah, all right. Wait, wait, wait. There's a specific detail not mentioned in this voicemail is this is a bounty
Yeah, so what is the reward? He said a bounty
Um, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. What's the what do you get?
I I think he needs to clarify a little bit. There are 124 episodes of the procrastinators podcast
That is like in the ballpark of like almost 400 hours worth of content. That is a lot of time invested
I want some financial
You just need 124 people to watch each one. That's true. That's true. See it's possible
You gotta pay a lot of people then
I mean, maybe the bounty is literally one cent. You know, he didn't specify. Maybe it's maybe it's a firm handshake
Maybe it's just credit in the video description
Did he did he say how to contact him?
He did not. Oh, well, he did say a one spar weekly. I bet if you google that he said on the page on the page
He said he's in the patreon discord order just leave it in the comments. Okay. Well, like well, I guess contact him there or somewhere
Oh, yeah, this may be a slightly out of date
Uh question
But I won't go into detail. Never mind. Well, I mean he he should know what did he die? Uh, he didn't die
Well, we talked today and he might be just like leaving the discord. So this might be in
Oh, no, so, you know, whatever figure it out. We've lost. We've lost a great ally today. Okay
That's weird. Yeah, it's just don't worry about it. It's fine. All right. Let's move on. Uh, okay. Never no question
Here's a question from from russell russell. Oh, no a resident ghoul
Oh, it's not russell. It's coming back. He haunts ben. He haunts me. Uh, he's a real problem. Let's let's see what he's got to say
I want to pose a hypothetical tea wall
Say you just returned from home from your nine to five having suffered allergies the whole day
Sneezing runny stuffy nose watery eyes the works
However, for tonight only
Stormy daniels is in town at your local titty bar as part of her making
Stay home
God russell's such a fucking villain. He is a villain. So just just to put us in a situation
We have to react to this evil question. It's just fucked up enough as is
Um, it's got a good voice. I didn't know what his voice was. Yeah, I'm looking up. I'm looking up stormy daniels
Make america horny again guys. Um, I've got to say well, she's not exactly my type. She's not exactly
Is to go look at least for
Is is to go and look
At least for like curiosity's sake. Yeah, I uh, you don't want to miss that. I don't think I mean
You want to be able to say I went to that and then people like wait, do I do I want that?
Ben, do you not want to make america horny again or what?
I would personally even if I was interested. I literally don't care interesting shit happens around me every single day
And I don't care. So and she loves dreams don't count me. She's not seeing any
I dreams dude, uh
I mean, uh, all right. All right. Well, I mean why you guys I'm not I'm not taking it for I'm not taking it for granted
That I'm interested in this event. Yeah, well fine. Ben
I think don't go. God damn it. It's it's it's it's impure. It's immoral
You know, I would know I would go I would go specifically to arrest her to place her under citizens arrest
What's she's doing? I would I would I would I would yeah, I would I would apprehend her and I would say in the name
Stop in the name of the law
Yeah, um, and I would you know, she actually did get arrested. Um a while back
Because uh, so there's a so there's this whole thing with she's like suing Donald trump or something
Um, but there was there was the situation where in in ohio
Is she the she's the one she's the one? Oh
Okay, she got arrested specifically for she was at a titty bar and in ohio where I live
And she let a patron touch her like like briefly in a I don't know
I like I don't think it was too hot and heavy at the moment
But like there was touching going on and that is illegal
So she got like arrested everyone thought it was like the libs thought this was a big over like uh
Look at them trump's trying to attack the person who's getting them
I don't know how trump was involved exactly but because it's like technically prostitution if
I mean yeah, it like crosses into that sort of field. I think which is why it's against the law
She's the one like like trump like got her pregnant or something
Allegedly trump had sex with her which I totally believe but I don't have proof of and uh,
He paid her hush money to keep her quiet about yeah
And specifically it's a campaign finance issue because like the money that may have been used came from a guy who ran
His thing which might have used the money from the from the campaign and then he paid him back
But was that legal like that's kind of the gist of it. It's not a legal fuck of a porn star and then
You know pay her off to keep quiet about it, but to use campaign money or is
But it could be if I mean maybe maybe we gotta we gotta push that now. I'm sure yeah after ben's done with us
It will be yeah, after after I after I arrest stormy daniels and and publicly execute her alongside all my rumbas
Stormy daniels can go but let me just leave the room. But wait
I think that the scariest thing about this voicemail wasn't even this this hypothetical
It's that even uh, once you're dead once you're a spirit, uh, you still have to suffer with allergies
Uh, what what a horrible thing. Oh, yeah, right. We forgot about the allergy thing
Or maybe maybe rustles mocking us because we all suffer from these human maladies of our physical bodies that he has been freed from
His superior ectoplasmic form has no such limitations. Yeah, maybe he's putting this this symptom on us
But not himself. He's made of he's made of shadows and poison. Yes, or something if I if I'm not if I'm not much mistaken
um
Hey, uh, I actually want to this is a topic that I let me let me bring this up
Let's talk about titty bars in general. I think the concept of titty bars is super weird
I've never been to one and I have so dumb
I have noticed in conjunction with like a strip club like the same thing or is that not are they not the same thing
Yeah, well, I'm asking you. I mean you did okay. I mean I think
I think there's I mean I've never I've never I've never been to a strip club or a titty bar or whatever
Anything like that and I don't I don't get the appeal at all. I think it's I don't
I'm 100% with you ben this idea in the age of internet porn. I don't see how this is in any way now ben
Ben still functioning would you say that ben if it was for example?
Like a brothel at least at least there's a reason to go wait. Is that an accurate statement? Wait wait wait say that again
You like if it was like instead of a titty bar if it was like a brothel
At least that sort of makes sense as to like why you'd go because you can like have sex with a woman or or a man or whatever
Yeah, yeah, sure. Yes. I understand. I understand the appeal of direct quote
Women don't matter unless I can have sex with them. That is what ben just said
He's confirmed this here on the pcb today. Please write that on his grave when he is executed
I don't know just like what what I don't know. I just I don't get it. What do you do?
Why why would you want?
Why would you want to go get a boner in public and be able to do nothing about it?
Like I like it seems weird to go by yourself and just kind of like get off privately to like, you know
Semi-nude girls walking around that seems weird
But it also seems weird to like go with friends or like go with go with people and like weird. Yeah
I don't know
But I feel like that's what most people I feel like most people like go with their bros and it's like, uh
Yeah
They jail each other
Because obviously the girl obviously the girls can't do it. It's you know, yeah, I guess that's true
That's true. We don't want a stormy daniel situation on you. You need you need that burst link squad
burst link squad
I mean
I guess I like I don't know like it is a bar and then they're just our naked women
So it's like okay, so it's got all the features of a bar plus. There are naked women like, okay
That's the naked women. See someone the naked women are a
Are a detraction at that point for me. Like I don't even like bars in general, but just like to have to have a distraction like that
Uh, does not sound fun to me at all
But like a distraction from what like drinking your beer at this bar. Here's okay. Yeah
Do you want to do you want to be like hanging out with like friends and just be like, oh, no
That girl's pretty hot now. I have a boner around my friends
I guess you could just go horrifying. I guess you could just go if you just wanted a drink like any other bar
Sure, however
I I'm I would be I would be put off by that because I feel like there would be this um
I feel like there'd be there's expectations on you like I because like the girls are there to the girls are there to make money
By by paying attention to guys and and you know getting like, you know
Getting them to tip them by by you know paying attention to them and making them feel good and and whatever and I don't
Okay, I I walk into a titty bar and and what I imagine would then happen is that you know, some girl would be would be like, okay
I'm gonna I'm gonna you know
I'm gonna go talk to him and and you know be nice to him
So he'll give me money and then I have this girl talking to me and and
You know, like I know it's fake, right? Like I know she's some some stranger
Yeah, good looking a good-looking stranger
I cannot think of a single thing more off-putting than the idea of a good-looking stranger
Coming up to me and acting really nice to me and me knowing that it is an act like that is
Horrifying well sure that that makes me a little sick to even say out loud
It's really the same thing with like a waitress
Who's like trying to get you to give her tips at the end of the meal because she's being really nice
I mean, sort of uh
It's sort of like that. Yeah, like I feel I feel that that that same type of awkwardness when with interactions like that
where they're always really nice to you even though that
There's something about the way that they maybe look at you as like, uh, you don't you
Yeah, I'm trying to eat being nice to my future money right now. I mean you guys. I think you guys are generally describing
Uh, what I would call millennial cowardice
You know the most part
Like I know look I know that this is like a share. I basically agree, but I think I'm afflicted as well
And it's like listen, you just be you're just being contrarian when a normal human
Not us but a normal human would like go out to be a social person just to like go out and like go to a bar
Whatever it is not a problem if someone like says anything to them
It's not a problem, but I feel like for our generation. It is a problem and like this is
Whoa, that is not that's you that's totally different than what I would just
Is there just a sense of insecurity about like being talked to by customer service people?
No, that's not the problem. You it's not that someone's talking to me. It's that someone is being fake to me
It's that someone is coming up to me and complimenting me
Yeah, it's different with a weight. It's different with a waiter. Oh, well sure. Okay. I just a real point here
That is a criticism of you and me. I have never been and neither have you
So are we not just talking out of our asses here as to what it's actually like at a place like this?
I I guess you're not wrong. Like maybe it's totally fine. Well, then fuck you too. So what so what so what's your angle here?
Well, I guess my angle is that I suppose it seems like I know there are people who enjoy it
So I good for them. I suppose and I have nothing further to say
I don't know if if you if you if you if you're a fan if you're a fan of strip clubs
And you think that I'm totally off base and what goes on there and and I and I'm mistaken and it's not like this
You know, leave a comment and explain why I'm wrong. You know, but you know, I've
But you know, I mean I've I've read about it like I've read I've read stories
I've read like stories from like women that work at them and I've you know, I've read people
I've heard people talk about their experiences going to them. This is the impression that I get of what goes on at these places
I there was one time in my life. I almost went to a strip club
And I know that makes me sound like a pussy because there's plenty of people who just have actually gone
But this is why one time once upon a time me and my friend Adam who I was working with at at a peer one up in
Up in Massachusetts
Like I found out that Lisa and the porn star was coming to Massachusetts to do like strip shows
Which she does and I am a fan of hers and I was very excited to go to this and I was like, let's do it
Now I basically pussied out by not following through because I was nervous and like, oh, this sounds like a real boy thing
I don't want to make myself embarrassed about
But I would have I wish that I had gone
I do wish I had gone
Just to see what it's like and to be more of a an actual human being and not a coward as I am
I mean, I kind of I kind of appreciate
Then the idea of an environment where it's okay to to look at the girls in a way that is like
Yeah, yeah, they they know why you're looking and that's fine. Yeah, like if I ever went that would be cool
I agree with hippo like
When like we're talking we're none of us experienced it. I'm guessing and like none of us are god. We're all such pussies
Mage is definitely gone for sure. He's the only one that's been
But no, no, I mean no particular interest or at least no no burning interest in going them. So like
We're not really talking with any sort of authority interest or even like knowledge of these things like
It reminds me
It reminds me of people who like
Talk shit about people who watch less plays or or some
Or listen to podcasts or whatever. Oh, it's just people talking
Oh, it's just why are you watching someone else play a game when you could be playing the game yourself, you know
I mean, I mean you could be playing a stripper. That's true
I see I see I see the I see the comparison. I see that I do see the comparison. I'm not judging anyone if they like
I'm just saying I'm just saying that the appeal of the
From what I understand. I don't see the appeal. We should go next rad con. We should go
Rad con entirely in rad con the divergining. That's let's call that and let's rid ourselves of this cursed virginity once and for all
Finally
We'll just title the video the burst length squad
That's good. And we'll wear the gopro
Okay, if if I'm there big if and we go there and I go you guys will have to come with me to a guy bar as well then
You know what that sounds funny
Yeah, I'm going to be completely honest. I'm not interested in either of them, but I I just want to go
I would believe a lot of ladies are looking to have sex on that day. So that's cool
Well, when's that not true?
Can you guys like send me candy corn? I never had candy corn. I've always been curious about it
I like candy corn. A lot of people shit on this and I think it's I think it's pretty good
Both sides and it's like you either love it or hate it. There's no one between and I really want to try
It's like a p.o. Box open a p.o. Box so people can send you candy. It's like sugar wax. It's pretty much what it is
It has a kind of a caramel taste
About a p.o. Box, but I'm not sure if there's anyone any any near me. So I don't
Uh, well fair enough. I mean, yeah, we post office around here. There's a bunch of them around
I opened a p.o. Box in georgia and um
Literally one person because people were saying they were going to send me stuff
Literally one person did
And and I didn't find out about it until after the p.o. Box had expired and I never got the package and I felt terrible
That's funny. People say a lot of things that they're definitely going to do
I don't believe or have faith in anyone. Uh, which is why my whole p.o. Box was formed around like
I give them something which is inclusion in weaguar and stuff. So that that keeps them coming that keeps them coming
Yep, yep
Hey, here's a question from uh at sam x amu 99 if given the choice
What would you do destroy anime or save anime? I think we all agree. Uh, it's time for it to go
Fully coolly was like 20 years ago and every it's been downhill ever since then have you seen fully coolly two and possibly three are like
I have I know that they're out. I haven't seen them. I don't want to I don't even want to acknowledge that they exist
I want to watch them
One day, I definitely will watch them and I probably will at some point
I'm not looking forward to the consensus though, Ben. You'll be happy to know is that they're way worse. So there's
Well, no, well, no, no, no, shit. Yeah. Yeah, who could have who could have seen this coming god damn it
I'm sorry. I have to read this question. I actually I feel like I've seen a pretty mixed response
Like it seems like people are not entirely negative on them, which is deeply disappointing and but yeah
Yeah, I mean they're probably I mean as long as as long as people
As long as people know that it's no it's not the original. That's I guess it's fine
Yeah, yeah, I just I hate that you have like the original good things getting buried under sequels and spinoffs and that's
As long as that I mean that's probably not gonna happen here, but whatever. What was that made?
You mentioned some sort of question and and then oh, yeah, uh, here's a question that I'm sorry
But I'm just selfishly going to answer it's at alien observer asks
When will Nate realize that communism is the ultimate weird utilitarian mode of production?
And also myth but a card is literally called Karl Marx
God, I think this is a total meme and he's just like mocking me and getting me all upset because fucking starfleet is not
communist you pieces of trash
I just hey, there's one answer this last way
Wait, there's one sign one one time stem for you talking about starfish plate thing
That the oh, yeah, there you go. That's that's a free one. Everyone go claim that bounty. Yeah, that's right. Get your one set everybody
um
I'm just gonna say uh, I'm just gonna give the short version here
Uh starfleet is post
Uh, what what's the word post something scarcely post scarcely the normal economic models
We have no longer apply uh in the same way they do now
So you cannot think of it in the same way stop being silly alien observer and everybody else out there
All right, who's got another question?
Let's see what we got. Let's see what we got. Um, I can tell you guys are being lazy and not looking
His only mage and I have offered them
Uh, oh god, okay. Yeah, you're right. Oh, you're right. I'll look
God, I'll look at them and I'll know if they're bad. Yeah. Well, I mean we that's a safe assumption
Um, uh rocks and asks, uh, do you hate all tabletops or just dnd because there is a cool pokemon tabletop
Are you guys on this excuse?
I have I have a I have a legendary video defending dnd from ben's bullshit
And I have an equally legendary video assaulting tom for for his terrified
Dnd in concept, but I've never really experienced it in practice. I liked it till the end
D the the the the act of getting together to play dnd is
Usually a nightmare
For one pcp, we should all gather and play dnd for two hours
I would I would play dnd with the pcp. I would do that. Um, but it's not something that I want
But it's not no
Terrible, it's not something that I want a lot of in my life. It's a big hassle. I don't know. It's been it's it's fun
I don't know. I guess
I don't I don't I don't disagree if anyone thinks it is fun or or under or because I get it but
I don't know. Um, so we'll but like like in in general
In general my problems with dnd extend to all tabletops
But I do think that there are there are other tabletops that I think are better than dnd
Like mutants and masterminds. I think is is pretty neat. Um, for example, and just generally generally
That that's that's a pretty rules heavy one, but in general I think that rules
Uh, it's it's got kind of a class. It's not really like a class based system. So yes, basically
Yeah, you can basically do it. You basically do it. I mean like settlers of katan and that kind of shit. No, no
Yeah, okay. All right, you know, you know, let me tell you a little anecdote
I think I think I just want to say I think that the like the more rules light a game is the more
I'll probably be disposed to like it. Yes. Also. I like there's kind of the shorter the better
Just like I don't want to play for like months and months in one campaign
I would love to sit down for like one time playing and uh, which I know is kind of not what tabletops are designed for
But that's why I don't play tabletops
Um, uh, but I was going to say on this the other day. Uh, this wasn't a tabletop
This is a board game thing
But I just I walked downstairs out of my apartment and I see there's like a there's like a little thing
Uh, like a little kind of glass enclosure, um, where I live that like another person lives in and I see a guy in there
Like my my my not my roommate, but like another guy who lives whatever in the same place I do and I see him like with friends
Uh, a bunch of guys gathered around us in a circle playing a board game
And I'm just my face is pressed up to the glass and I'm like, I want to play too
I want to have fun with friends. Um, but I didn't and I never will that's it
That's the story
Wonderful, uh, there was another question I liked. Oh, here we go. This is an important question from uh gays
Guys eric gais eric. Okay. It's um when society inevitably breaks down and the gamers rise up
What will your be your loadout fellow gamers magic?
I don't know. Oh, well, I'll definitely use my mace. Um, yeah, good. Definitely use my mace, uh, from the video
Where I smashed the mouse. I actually do have to leave because I have stuff to do before I go
Okay, mage quick. What's your loadout?
Magic that's not real mage magic
You have to be a real gamer
No
And she's gonna throw them at people
I don't know
Being killed to the black mage will be one of the the helpless
Lambs that are slaughtered by me and my gamer crew when we roll through
Yeah, yeah, all right. She'll she'll have she'll have the creative us
She'll have her roblox character to defend. I don't I don't know anything about that. Um,
All right, mage. Well, we'll see you later if you got to go. No worries. Okay. Goodbye everyone. Get the hell out of here
Halo energy sword, uh, and uh, the sniper rifle and, uh,
This needler. I mean needling everybody. That's yeah, that's me. I halo weapons
I'd use I'd use the stealth boy from fallout to go completely invisible and then shank you from behind
sense
I probably use the rules here amaze my real weapons amaze in one hand and I don't know how this works
Probably use a shotgun. I like shotguns. I like like scattershot buckshot kind of weapons. They're cool
I want that grappling hook shotgun from the new doom game coming out. That looks pretty helpful. Yeah, that looks pretty useful
Oh, fucking I get the hook shot from legend of zelda. What the double hook? How sick by the way was getting the double hook shot in
Twilight princess that was like my favorite upgrade ever. It was so fucking sick
Just saying just saying
Gamers rise up everybody. It's time. I want when I say gamers rise up
Do they mean like the nuclear fallout will give gamers the ability to make video games real life
Yeah, to make their favorite video game
Manifest destiny the only manifest destiny that ever mattered was games becoming real life. That's what needs to happen
What if the pcp got trapped inside their favorite video games? Oh my god. Oh
Yeah, what were you saying?
What if I became sad?
We're already living life sans video games, which is paying enough for me
Are you the undertaler would become sans in this reality? That's probably true
Yeah, um, all right. That's enough questions. I think we're done here folks. I think I think we're good. We're like just at two hours
So yeah, we've got our contractual obligations
Yes, it feels good feels oh so good now now we can now we can avoid each other for the rest of the week as we do
Uh, thanks everybody for listening. Uh, that's uh patreon.com slash the procrastinators to support us
Which I know you want to do we've got like I think 16 bonus episodes now
Remember when those bonus episodes are just a twinkle in our eye. Well now you've got a million of them for the little
little price of five dollars per month
And now if you're not now the value is basically unbeatable. Yeah, you're not spending the five dollars
You're literally retarded. Oh
You can't afford not to
You'll get when you hear the wisdom embedded in those bonus episodes
You'll you'll you'll recoup your losses
Think think about how sad your life is right now because it's the end of the episode
And now you have seven painful days before another episode comes for five dollars. That's so that feeling evaporates
Instantly you can have like 16 episodes. You can have like 20 24 hours of content. Maybe yeah for for yeah
Just I it's at your fingertips. The power is yours
The power is yours. The power is yours. Not to mention uh, you get uh first as low as one dollar
That's for the five dollar pledge for the one dollar pledge. You're in the chat
We care about you more. You are a valued member of the pcp community. That's pretty much everything you could ever want
Uh speakpipe.com slash pcp voicemail go to that url link in the description to leave us messages
Oh, we will laugh. Oh, we will joke. It'll be a great time for all
Uh, uh, and uh, what else is there? Oh, yeah at tpcrasnairs on twitter
Follow us for the thing for the question thing whatever and announcements and new videos and stuff
And uh, go check out the radcon 3 playlist if you haven't watched it already a lot of good stuff and still more to come
Believe it or not. There's still stuff. Uh, that's not out yet. That will be soon
There you go. Yeah. All right. Thanks for listening everybody. We'll see you next week with another hot meme
Another hot take
Oh
Oh, oh god
Let's get a new pair of pants
See see you next time