Welcome everybody to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. We're here, we're
back, we're listening to, we're doing the corporate thing and listening to audience feedback.
Oh, PCP, why don't you get a guest? God, it's so boring listening to the same three people
over and over again. Why don't you get Cybershow on the podcast? He's like, he's a fan, just
came back, made some good videos, he's a good boy. And we were just like, God, imagine
listening to the viewers, imagine giving them what they want. So here's Cybershow, everybody.
I gotta say, they asked me to join them on this episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast
and I told them no, I will absolutely not do that, that sounds horrible. I'm no interest
in doing that and I hate all your fans and don't listen to your fans, whatever you do.
And then I said, that's so such a coincidence, we feel the exact same way, that's why we
get along so well.
Anyways, we got along, we started talking about how much we all hate the PCP fans for a few
hours and then like, eventually I agreed to come on the show.
Yeah, I mean, everybody can talk about how much they hate the PCP in the comments, but
nobody hates it more than we do.
I was going to do a bit, I was going to do a bit where I started crunching on some chips
and I was going to say, hey, welcome to the crunch cast, but I'm too, I feel too sick,
I feel too ill, I can't bring myself to do it. I can't bring myself to put anything in
my mouth.
Yeah, I think Ben's dying, I don't know what's going on, but he's dying guys.
I broke Keto this weekend and I went out and I splurged and I was like, you know what,
if I'm off Keto, I might as well eat some carbs that I like, so I've been eating, I
eat Dunkin Donuts, I eat Doritos and I don't know man, one or two of those things must
not have agreed with me.
We're too old to have fun.
I'm going to die.
Without food.
I'm going to die right here.
It just doesn't work like that anymore.
Every time I have Doritos, I feel good for about 10 minutes and I feel bad for about
10 hours and it really is the worst thing of all time.
Once you hit, everyone's like, oh, your 30s are your best years.
No, no, no, no, no.
As soon as you hit 30, it's your life's basically over, you're no longer living.
You've just begun the 50 year process of dying when you hit 30.
They just contain all the same.
They say this to Cybershell on the verge of 30 himself.
I'm sure you're really looking forward to it now.
Yeah, I turn 30 next month in October and I'm not looking forward to it at all.
I know.
Party, this last month.
This is the last, this is the last month of my life I get to be happy and enjoy things
before my body just gets destroyed by itself.
I can still remember what it's like to eat fast food in Doritos.
I remember eating fast food Doritos and feeling happy and they just made me feel
happy and good and I didn't die like a party pack from Taco Bell and just like not missing
a beat.
The idea of eating 12 tacos was like, it wasn't funny to me.
It was just like, yeah, that sounds like a good idea.
I'm going to do that.
Now I look at a party pack and I feel like I'm dying.
It's the worst.
I actually, I seriously actually am considering going and making myself vomit because it's
like that serious.
The feeling when you want to vomit, but you can't vomit.
That's the worst feeling.
That's so much worse than actually vomiting feels good because then it's like done.
I mean, doesn't feel good to do it, but it feels like such old people right now talking
about how good it feels to vomit.
But like, can we just, can we pause and can we appreciate?
I love it when I have a smooth bowel movement, but just Ben, can we just appreciate for a
second viewers, listeners that we have the virgin Nate who won't come on the podcast
for months because he just doesn't feel like it.
Then we have the Chad Ben who's like wants to make himself puke because he feels so bad,
but is still on the show anyways.
I'm just saying credit where credit is due to hell or high water.
People thought I was joking, but no, I'm Ben is actually like on the verge of death right
now.
We might have to delete this episode because he could die during it.
That would be, no, I want, I want to die.
I want to die on air or die on recording, not to get like super dark about it, but it
would be so like, think about how legendary it would be to like die in the middle of like
the live performance.
Like I'm not saying I want him to like imagine if Kanye West was like right in the middle
of the Super Bowl halftime show.
He just pulled out a gun and like blew his brains out.
Everybody would be talking about that for the rest of all time.
I don't know.
I'm just saying hypothetically.
Don't tempt me.
It's like that episode of boondocks where he's like, I got shot.
He's like, no, I got shot for real because he gets shot singing the song.
I got shot.
What a classic.
What a classic early 2000s reference that our audience is too young to remember.
Classic interpretation of the boy you cried wolf.
And yes, our audience, your audience, I should say, I'm sure the average age is around 12
years old.
So they don't even know what adult swim is, let alone the boondocks.
They certainly act like it.
They're all, they're all at home wearing their no Nate, no watch shirts.
They're new, newly available.
We got the no Nate, no watch and the no Nate.
Yes.
Watch you get to choose your team.
Choose your side.
Pick a side.
How will history remember you?
This is the time.
This is when legends are made up on the tea spring.
I've been going crazy on tea spring lately.
Every week.
We got new shirts.
It's so easy.
Yeah.
Just to make things.
No one will ever buy.
Haha.
I actually did it.
Dog.
Everybody bought an I have COVID shirt.
Oh my God.
Do you think they actually have COVID and that's why they bought it?
No, I don't.
That would make too much sense to actually do that.
That wouldn't be me me enough to actually broadcast the fact you have COVID with an
appropriate t-shirt.
It would be misunderstanding the purpose of the shirt, but I do think that if you're
listening to the show and you do get COVID, you probably should buy the shirt.
It would be pretty not epic of you to have COVID and be a PCP listener and not buy the
shirt.
It would be the ethically responsible thing to do to let your community people around
you.
I think it would be doing your part for society too.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
We live in an age where you can just go online and make a t-shirt.
People in the middle ages, peasants, they all wanted their own customized, personalized
t-shirts, but they couldn't have them.
They just take it for granted nowadays, I think.
They wanted their, you know, I have the bubonic plague shirt, but there was no way to make
them back in the day.
Now we can do that.
They had to like stitch their shirts together out of hay and papyrus or whatever they had
back in the middle ages.
God.
They didn't have screen printing.
They didn't have digital monsters.
They barely even knew about the concept of slime.
They didn't even heard of slime.
They couldn't even process it in their pee little pee brains, and they certainly didn't
know how to use text commands.
Simon, how do you feel about Digimon?
You mean digital monsters?
I mean digital.
I'm referring to the digital monsters, yes.
Digimon?
I love Digimon.
I always thought that childhood drama of like Digimon is just a Pokemon rip off and then
all the kids are like, no, you don't understand.
Look at the Japanese release dates.
It's not, it's not true.
And then they're all, I mean, I can still vividly like relive all of those arguments
every time I hear the word Digimon.
Have we, have we talked on the show about getting the Digivices for a potential Radcon
5?
We have, because that was from a voicemail.
Okay, it was from a voicemail.
Oh man.
I just, I watched, did I already talk about, I went and I watched some, some like, some
YouTuber who is specifically a Digimon YouTuber.
He does like product reviews.
Oh of course.
He's, he's got like 500 subs, but he puts out like tons of videos.
You know.
It's amazing.
Dude, I love, I love those people who have like 100 subs and they put out videos every
single day.
Those guys are the backbone of YouTube.
They really are.
Yeah.
I don't have a spec for them, but I have someone who has like millions of subscribers and
makes garbage.
You know, they're doing it for the passion.
I want to shout this guy out because he has got, he is like in it.
He's got like, like banner art of himself with his favorite Digimon and, and stuff like
that.
Digimon, how would, how would I find that specific guy?
Just go to your history if you were watching videos, they're probably in your history.
I was, but this was like a couple of weeks ago.
Well, we got to scroll for a little bit.
Shout out to Elecmon.
That was always a Digimon.
I wanted to be my partner back in the day.
I thought his design was really cool.
I liked them.
I liked, I liked the, I liked a couple of the, I didn't like any of the small versions,
but there were a few of the ultimates that I liked.
I liked the, I liked Megacaboo Terrimon a lot.
He was pretty beast.
I liked, I liked Lily, Lilymon, I thought was, was cool in a totally different way.
Garudamon.
Garudamon was maybe my favorite.
I liked its beak.
I don't know.
Garudamon was pretty dope.
Do you ever see Hercules Caboo Terrimon, the mega form that was never in the show?
No, he's even bigger.
He's all gold and had big, giant fucking horns.
Super cool.
I'm really bad at remembering their names, but I always love that big fucking cactus.
I don't know why, I just like cactuses.
Yeah.
Togamon was this shirt.
Super cool.
Yeah, absolute badass.
You know, something about Digimon, it didn't like, like it didn't like viscerally frighten
me as a kid, but like the idea that like a little weird blob could turn into this like
gigantic angel creature.
It was so different from Pokemon, which was like, you know, Charmeleon was like a little
slightly bigger, slightly different Charmander.
You never knew what the fuck was going to happen with Digimon.
That shit was wild.
It really was so much more creative than Pokemon, just in terms of just like whatever drugs
they're around, they came up with the character designs were insane.
Yeah, you know, the weirdest thing in the world is happening to me right now.
I'm going, I'm on YouTube and I when I go to YouTube, it goes to like YouTube.com
slash app underscore shell, question mark, courage underscore shell equals one.
And then it just keeps refreshing itself over and over again.
I YouTube is having a refresh loop.
Yeah, that's peculiar.
What's going on here?
OK, no, it's fine.
No, it's fine. It's fine.
I fixed it. I fixed it.
I don't know. That was very scary.
That was very scary.
I don't like it on my computer, just since I don't understand.
I'm still looking for this guy because he has like he I was so charmed
by his by his tiny little channel.
You can always tell when like it's a YouTuber that's just doing it
for the love of the game.
You know, they really like they really aren't doing it for fame.
You know, you can really tell there's people that just like they don't.
They wouldn't care if no one watched it.
I guess they would probably want someone to watch their videos,
but they don't need like a million subs.
They're happy with like a hundred views, you know, they're either.
I found it super.
His name is his name is Digital Dream, and he has two point six case of.
Oh, OK. So not quite as few as I that's that's still some hustle.
That's impossible right there.
You got, you know, that's when you know someone's either like super
passionate or super autistic and that they're just keep going.
He seems perfectly, perfectly like normal in his videos, not to be not to be.
What's the word?
Neurotypical centric or anything, but he seems like a perfectly reasonable fellow
who just reads, you know, he's got his room full of Digimon toys
and Digimon posters and stuff and like every fucking couple of days
he puts in a new video reviewing a new if he has a room.
Digimon product, which I'm shocked you're even still coming out.
Well, the thing is like a lot of those old Digimon things are worth
stupid money at this point because they're so hard to find now.
So if he has a room full of stuff, it's probably worth like thousands and thousands of dollars.
Oh, my God, he got it.
He got it two weeks ago.
He got a new tattoo.
He got a new Digimon tattoo. Oh, my God, that's based as fuck.
It's a do you want to guess?
Oh, God, I don't have no concept context for this guy.
So I have no idea.
There's so many choices. Yeah, how would you even know?
It's it's Graymon. Fuck.
Yeah, the classic is I think is I think his favorite is the Graymon.
I mean, that's like if you started watching with the original series,
you got to love I'll go.
I wish I could clown on this guy, but it's it's actually not that bad of a tattoo.
It's pretty cool.
Yeah, it's fine.
It could be the worst.
It's just a while to me that like it's just a for a Digimon tattoo.
I mean, I don't know how much of a pussy magnet is going to be.
It's got a little intro drawing of him and Gilman. Fuck.
Yeah. Oh, oh, we filmed at the film.
I'm doing it. Yeah, Gilman.
That one.
The the one in this icon from series two from series three.
Oh, OK. Whatever.
Yeah, that was such a cool fucking concept for a show.
Man, season three of Digimon was so good.
I don't ironically incredible.
I stopped watching it when they changed the main cast.
No, well, they changed the main cast like every season.
But like season three was so cool because like they frayed.
The concept of the show was that like the characters existed in our reality,
where Digimon was a show and a card game and stuff.
But then like it was still real.
That's pretty meta for a show back then.
I got to say, you see that kind of thing nowadays.
But I'm pretty sure one of the people who was involved
in Evangelion wrote the show because the show gets super dark
and fucked up and weird and insane and like Digimon straight up like die.
Like one of their characters like partner Digimon just dies.
It's fucking sick. It's a 10 out of 10.
That's what I wanted season two to be.
Watch Tamers. Tamers is so good.
I love it.
And like they change the evolution animations from like just like,
you know how in the olden's just kind of spin around and then get bigger.
In this one, like they turn into like like wireframes
and their skin gets ripped off as they like slowly like change.
It's like an animorphic sort of thing.
It's so fucking based.
Tamers is the shit fucked up as the animorphs transformations.
Is as close as you can get on Fox Kids in 2002 or whenever the fuck this came out.
It was super cool. Super kid.
Tamers is a classic. It's a legend. It's amazing.
Are there are there still new Digimon things?
I mean, I feel like they're currently airing right now.
A kind of like spiritual successor to the original Digimon adventure.
It's like a retelling and like augmentation of the original storyline.
I've only watched the first couple of episodes.
They stopped airing it.
Yeah, I guess I guess this year or maybe last year they reissued some old.
I guess as I learned from Digital Dream,
you're not supposed to call them Digivices because they're not Digivices.
They are, you know, V pets or virtual pets is the word for the like the toy version.
Yeah, they take care of the original V pets.
They made some Digivices in the US that were kind of just like pendulum games
that didn't have like the pet raising part of it, which I had a bunch of those to some unrelated.
I don't know. What did you do with them then?
They just like you just like clip them on your belt or whatever.
And you walked around with them and then you just they just go through like these little levels.
The levels were divided up into steps.
So every time you took a step, your little Digimon walked through this level
and you would just fight other things that showed up and it was just like kind of a game
where you just fight other Digimon that at the end of every level,
there was a boss and if you beat the boss, you move on to the next level
and kind of followed the progression from the television series.
Kind of like a V pet slash Poke Walker sort of thing.
Yeah, it was like a Poke Walker like 10 years before the Poke Walker came out.
Yeah, I was going to say once again, Digimon does it before Pokemon.
Look, Digimon is objectively better than Pokemon.
Fight me. It's true. It's just cooler.
It's the show is better. The lore is more ridiculous.
You have one where a little a little cat turns into an angel,
which then turns into a dragon and you're just like, that doesn't make any sense.
But it's am I am I crazy or would Digimon lore make for a pretty good lecture?
Oh, it would be incredible. Yeah, OK.
That's what I'm thinking. That's the first thing I thought of
when I saw fucking mega evolutions of Pokemon was just like,
they they're never going to stop ripping off Digimon and they're never going to stop.
And they're going to keep getting away with it, too.
Oh, now they warped. Did you evolve? OK, I get it.
You fucking hacks work in a tent.
And that was like from season one where they unlocked their mega forms.
They had Wargreymon and Metal Guru Ruman.
I can't believe I still remember all of this,
but I watched these shows so much as a kid.
I could like I could do a lecture on Digimon right now, I bet.
Well, but I won't take the time for that.
Take the floor while I go and throw up.
Are you seriously going to puke?
No, probably not.
But I wish I could. I wish I would.
I did throw up on Friday.
I did wake up in the little bit of vomit.
Well, I mean, it's I just we've all been there.
It's just a Friday night for Ben saying, you know, I needed,
you know, my sheets needed to change anyway.
So it's fine.
Abhorrent.
The only the only time I've ever puked from drinking too much
was the first day of Radcon four.
I mean, that first stream.
I forgot that you did.
I remember that I did.
It was a nightmare.
I very rarely throw up from from drinking,
but I guess once in a while it happens.
And this I'm usually just one of those days.
I'm just usually in charge of my own drinking
and I'll stop way before that.
But when you have people paying for you to keep taking shots,
you can't stop and you go past your limit and you die.
It was pretty legendary, though.
It was it was a great time.
It was totally worth vomiting.
The first day I'm there, I'm just like, this sets the tone.
It did. It was a perfect tone setter.
I wouldn't have had it any other way.
Speaking of lectures, it's not the same, but the cyber shell.
I I had not I had not really seen your channel before,
but someone someone told us there's people.
A couple of people said, like, hey, this guy,
cyber shell has been away from the YouTube from the YouTubes.
And he's just he's just came back.
And apparently, he is or was a PCP head at some point.
And I was hearing about it because people were saying,
Ben, he mentioned your Tales of the Troll lecture in a video,
a Tales of the Troll video.
And I saw a bump. Indeed, I did. I saw a bump in views.
I probably made.
I probably made about like 80 or $90 just an ad revenue
from the fact that you mentioned my videos.
I saw a bump in views and ad revenue for for a while.
I might still be in it.
I haven't checked it a little while.
So that was pretty cool.
I'm very glad you approve of that,
because I was really this close to just cutting that part out
because I felt bad because my I basically told people don't watch the video.
I said, read the comic.
Don't go watch this lecture,
even though it's ostensibly aimed at people who haven't
don't know anything about Tales of the Troll.
But I do think it is a very good video.
I just, you know, I'm not like I don't hate spoilers.
You can watch the lecture and then read it and it would still be fun.
But then I still felt compelled.
I should also mention the son of two lecture, which is the opposite,
which I do think is you should watch the lecture and then read it
because it's too it's too much to just try and read it.
I agree with what you were saying.
Yeah, it's the lecture is just like fully spoilers for Tales of the Troll.
In it, yeah.
And like the son of two, it's it's like, yeah, you need that extra context.
Tales of the Troll that's, you know, you, yeah, you should probably just read it
yourself first, because it's not even that long as someone who is in the audience
for the fucking Tales of the Troll lecture.
I think even in the video, you can tell I go from like casually
dismissing this idea to becoming incredibly invested by like the halfway point
in the fucking narrative of Tales gets trolled and how it's just from the plot
summary, just from the order of events, you can tell it's going to be a good story.
But I mean, there is something to say about
Laserbot's presentation of the whole thing.
But yeah, it was I really, really enjoyed watching the lecture because I love
seeing people's reaction to Tales gets trolled and I love showing it to people.
So it was it was a real treat seeing like a live reaction to just every absurd
plot point in that entire thing.
I had not seen the the new pages.
I think you showed some of them in your video.
Yeah, see, that was another reason I wanted to make the video, which is again,
I do like your lecture, but when you did the lecture, it was in full on hiatus mode.
And then I it's back up again with new pages.
But I don't know how many people like how how do people like how are people?
Who's going to know about who's going to know to check that?
You know what I mean? I heard that it had started coming out again.
I can't believe it's like it's like done.
It's like drawn by someone else, but it's canon.
It's so weird. Yeah, it's it is.
OK, so it's so jarring, like, especially if you're just reading it,
like you're not even expecting that it's so jarring, the change in art styles.
But like it's one of those things where it's really cool because it's just for a fight scene.
Like it's it's legitimately great art.
It's just so different from Laserbot's aesthetic that it's it's strange.
But good news is that Laserbot is going to come back and start drawing again.
And then it's going to be like he does everything that's not a super complicated
fight scene, and then he's got the guys to do the fight scenes, the chapter 23 team.
You did you talk to Laserbot at all?
I have not talked to Laserbot.
I've talked to the tales gets trolled dot org admin and some of the other people
in that like area I haven't actually I know he commented on your video,
which I thought was really cool, and that made me interested in doing it, too.
He did. And I talked to him on Facebook a little bit.
And I was listening as you were talking about like, OK, I had not heard about
like the polished, I had not never even heard of polished.
Like that's so fucking funny that he thought it was such a strange story
that he's like, I'm going to go back and do this whole.
And I'm just going to add everyone.
Everyone was begging him like, stop, please.
Like every time you put out a new page, people are like, oh, cool.
But can maybe you should do this for this reason and this reason and this reason.
And he was like, he just it wasn't like he like read it and was like, oh,
I see what you're saying.
He was like, no, yeah, no, you're you're wrong.
That's so funny.
So I had not I had not heard of that.
But when I talked to him, he told me that the thing that he was going to do
instead of finishing Tales, Gets Trolled was to remake an old
like YouTube web series that he and his brother made called Micorat.
You seen that? Yeah, that was his.
I don't know the lore of Micorat.
I just know that that was his like avatar and his use.
I have watched all of Micorat and Micorat does not need a remake.
Micorat, the little I've seen seems like a very strange little.
It seems like it's like it is what it is.
Like it's a little YouTube thing and it should stay.
I'm pretty sure I'm pretty sure that Micorat is just like him and his brother
and their friend, like just ad-libbing into a microphone,
like just fucking around with no plan at all.
And then they just like went and like drew these like funny pictures
of like rats and dinosaurs over it.
Can you imagine being invested in something where it's just you and your
friends talking into a microphone with no plan at all?
OK, all right.
Burn. Can you imagine ad-libbing something and then animating it?
Like I'm pretty sure Rick and Morty rip these guys off big time.
And I think I'm seeing a laser ball lawsuit and imagine trying to remaster that.
Imagine trying to go back and remake it.
It does seem like I don't even understand it.
I don't understand what it is yet.
And like I mentioned in the video, like Super Mario Bros.
Z like like there's like multiple projects that like these people
are like creative types.
I mean, they're like, I'm just going to go back and start from the square one
and do it all over again, but better.
But it's like, yeah, no.
The whole point of art is like you get better over time.
Like by the time he catches up to like where he was,
he's going to be so good and even prove to skills even more
that he needs to remaster the remaster.
You know, yeah, it's just it's just one of those
artism things that just pervade the creative mind.
I don't know if it's really good.
Has it ever been a good idea to like for a creator to go and like remaster their thing?
It is objectively bad every time.
If Tails gets trolled or this was completed, like it was done.
Like he finished the entire story, start to finish, told the entire thing
and he didn't have anything else he wanted to do.
Then maybe if he wanted to remaster it, I'd be on board.
But he literally stopped in the middle of a fight scene on a cliffhanger.
And people were like begging him to come back and work again.
And it was after a hiatus.
He came back to work on Tails.
His role. It was so funny.
It was like every single thing made it the bad, like the wrong choice, but he still did it.
Yeah, yeah.
No, so I'm yeah, I'm glad.
I'm glad that like the canon pages are coming out.
That's crazy. I haven't actually.
I'm so glad to see it going on.
Yeah, it just like literally just a couple of days like two days ago,
the fight between Coyote and tomorrow finally, finally ended.
I saw someone wrote a I saw a spoiler for who won.
I won't repeat it.
This is the getting off a fucking the boat moment for Tails gets trolled
as far as I'm concerned, because now things can actually happen.
And then, you know, like spoilers, it is technically spoilers,
but the chapter 23 script was posted to his Patreon like years ago.
So I've sort of like known how this fight was going to play out for ages.
But it was it was really cool to see it like drawn.
And now I'm yeah, you know, it's actually not like not as an insult,
but it's it's really hard to read a laser bot script.
Not just because it's like it's like it's formatted to the point where like
it's genuinely hard to even tell when like one line starts and another stops.
You know what I mean? Yeah.
He'll write the character name and then just write the dialogue.
He'll write the character's name and the dialogue, but like no quotation mark.
So it's incredibly hard to tell what's going on.
But it was comprehensible enough that I got just what the fight is going to be.
I don't know if you have any idea,
but like did he used to like write the scripts out and then draw it?
Or did he just draw it as he goes?
Like, did he did he always think it?
I don't believe he always scripted.
I think he only wrote the chapter 23 script
because he was in one of those situations where he didn't have access
to his computer or whatever.
But yeah, you know, yeah, he had the idea.
He was the one saying, I wish I had a team to draw this for me way back in the day.
But it just, you know, he's not really the kind of guy
who's sort of going to be capable of putting together and managing a team.
You know what I mean? So that's so that sort of happened.
He's one sort of spontaneously formed from the talesgetstroll.org admin guy.
Just he will.
I mean, he just wanted to continue to see where it was going to go.
So he got some guys together and I should really join that discord
and like get better, you know, because I'm just talking over Twitter, DMs and stuff.
So yeah, there's like they they they they're making new pages and stuff.
And I'm very excited to see where it's going to go.
Damn, is this is this like the last chapter?
Is it supposed to like end relatively soon?
No, OK, so it's a little confusing
because the chapter that he's been on and working for for a long time
has been called the conclusion, but that's just referring to the conclusion
of the Coyote and Demaro fight.
Yeah, I'm not sure how much longer the actual comic is going to go.
He said different things.
I've seen a post where he's like, it's going to be 100 chapters long.
I saw a later post where he said it's going to be 60 chapters long.
And then I saw another post where he's like,
I haven't told a quarter of the story I wanted to.
So I have no idea how long it's going to actually end up being where could it even go?
That's what I'm trying to say.
Like, it's like, I know it's like it's he posted something incredibly
like when he canceled it or quote unquote canceled it,
he posted like a question and answer session on his DeviantArt
and people would just ask about random plot points and he did reveal some things.
And I don't know how much of that's going to like stay canon.
You know what I mean?
Because like he talked about the man and ice or whatever a little bit
and some just some of the weird, interesting things.
The man and ice, yes, the man and the ice, of course.
There's so many weird little plot threads that he like like seeds
and like things he's planted like.
And there's so many things it didn't really
even seem like he was wrapping up like he was really introducing
it's not like the ant from ants was still like was like a new thing
that seemed like a complete out of nowhere like twist.
OK, so that's one of the funniest parts about polish.
It was that it really wasn't polished to such a misnomer
because it was so much of polish was new content added mixed in with the old content.
So it was literally like new comic mixed in with the old comic with which new are.
It was so confusing.
But yeah, it's so funny.
The new stuff was not.
I mean, the new stuff was was it good at all?
Or was it just like padding?
The new stuff in Tales.
It's true polish.
I don't want to just dismiss it all as being like bad.
But like I tried to explain to you like, you know,
a lot of the good parts of early Tales gets trolled is things
are just like happening at a very brisk pace.
And like, you know, he's not overthinking.
He he was not overthinking it back in the day.
He was just like, I'm going to get a comic where Tales gets trolled
and then tales and they beat up the trolls.
And I don't even know if he really thought he was going to go further than that,
but he just kept going and going.
Yeah. And there's so many individual plot threads that have yet to pay off.
Like like you think in the early comic, Shadow and Mario and Bowser
and like the Troll Slayers, you seem like they're going to be so important.
They've spent the last like 20 chapters just like sitting in a field planning
that's like all they've been doing for years.
The way that the comic almost immediately pivots to not being about
Tales getting trolled, but being about this weird conspiracy theory
and like this war is like really funny.
And it's seen it really just seems like he had this initial idea about
like, how would have tales got trolled?
And then he had the and Sonic had to go and get revenge or whatever.
And then he like did that.
And then it's like, well, nothing else to say about that, I guess.
But I've introduced all these Troll characters and stuff.
And now I've put all these Sonic the Hedgehog characters together.
And I'll Mario's there and Bowser and whoever the fuck else from League of Legends.
And like, yeah, I'll just I'll just keep it going.
He's got like all these little warring factions that he's setting up.
And for one of the stupidest things I always thought was so funny was he's like
when he's showing off the defenders or whatever, he's like,
now I'm going to show you our two bosses.
It is like leapfrog and a frogger, but you only see him in that one page.
And then like now we'll show you our real main.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you literally never see leapfrog or frog ever again.
After that, it's like, you're informed that they are the boss,
but there's like bigger bosses that matter more.
It's actually all that Pacman.
So fuck those other guys, they're unimportant, irrelevant.
Even then, even in the later chapters, now everything with Pacman is
completely even superseded.
And Pacman himself is just a pawn of the Cheeto man.
And I don't want to get into spoilers too much, but it's like
it's so confusing.
And like a lot of stuff he's definitely like didn't fully plan out.
But I know it's so funny that he's not Chester Cheeto.
He's just Cheeto man.
He's never going to correct it.
It doesn't matter.
That's what he's called.
That's what he's called in this universe and who are you to say otherwise?
Oh, my God.
I do love how he'll take characters and make them his own.
Like he clearly doesn't really give that much of a shit about silver the hedgehog.
He just sort of took the base and used them to make an interesting funny
character. But the weird thing is he does have a weird amount of like respect
for the lore, like silver is using his green telekinetic powers.
Like it's it's not it's not completely like it's mostly lore accurate.
It's just his personality is different and better, in my opinion.
I mean, yeah, I don't know.
I mean, I don't know shit about Sonic, so I don't know what silver is
actually supposed to be like.
I think he's like he's like really smart, right?
He's like some kind of super genius like psychic guy.
He's like it's a little confusing, but he's like from the future
and he's like, yeah, he's got psychic powers and he's sort of like an optimist type guy.
He's not like super smart.
He's just sort of like, I don't know.
He's not really the he's really not the most well fleshed out character,
which is why I think laserbot had more fun just sort of, you know, exploring him.
And I don't know, like, like, I just it's funny just to me to see his
like his interpretation of Sonic was really fucking funny to me.
And I just that almost instantly hooked me in the line where he's like,
sorry, tales of this looks gay to the viewers.
I don't know why that was I died laughing at that classic.
And then and then spoilers.
I don't want to get too much spoilers, but this is pretty early in on.
But when he actually did kill off Sonic, I was like, oh, oh, shit.
This is this is getting real.
I feel, yeah, I can't believe I like forgot to mention it in the lecture.
I just like if I had one tiny little complaint,
though my one and only tiny complaint with your lecture is you glossed over that.
But the fact that you just gloss over the fact that you even could forget
that plot point is hilarious to me because it really does like it.
It's funny. It's funny.
It doesn't really matter.
And it's like there's a point where he clearly wanted everyone to be on the same
page, but then he never had tales found out.
So tales finds out because Pac-Man tells him he can do the soul bond with Sonic,
who's dead. And then he's like, he's in tales like, but Sonic isn't dead.
And Pac is like, oh, shit, nobody told you.
Waka, Waka. Oh, sorry about that.
It was cursed to say Waka from his childhood trauma.
Yes, the elaborate backstory for Pac-Man was so strange and funny.
He'll throw he'll throw characters in there.
And it's like he'll just kind of it almost seems like he's picking at random
like when he needs a new character, like Pac-Man.
It is really, really strange to mix like you wouldn't expect Teemo
and fucking Bugs Bunny in the same team.
Like he's not Pac-Man like like Chester Cheeto or Cheeto Man is not Cheeto Man
because like, you know, he like this character like has like this
this like cool guy attitude like Chester Cheeto.
I mean, he gives him a couple of lines or something
that sort of imply that he's like that he's a cool laid back dude.
But at the end of the day, you know, this is just like an Obi-Wan type guy.
And he could have it could have just if it could have been anyone.
And it maybe if it had been, I don't know, if it had been, you know,
Agumon or whatever, it would be the exact same character.
And just maybe he would make some jokes about fire breath instead of Cheetos.
And that would be that would be the different that would be the different thing.
I don't know.
It is funny to think it is almost completely random.
The characters he'll pick like he could have just done this.
He could have made this entire comic with just completely original characters.
You know, it could have been called laser.
Well, I guess trolled or just some original character, you know,
because it's really funny because it really just seems like he got trolled
and then he was pissed off and he wanted to vent and blow off some steam.
So he wrote a little story about killing trolls.
But then he himself has gone on record saying, oh, no, no, no, that's not what happened.
I didn't get trolled.
I based this story off of my friend who got trolled.
Like a likely story.
Uh, it's it's, um, oh, fuck, I was going to say, I was going to say something about
Oh, it's really funny, the juxtaposition between the like his original characters
and the like people like Pac-Man and and like Frogger and like all these
like goofy like children's cartoon characters juxtaposed against like all
these like weirdly over designed kind of like emo edgy anime people that all have
like it is really funny.
Yeah.
He has like he has his original characters that he wants to be cool like
tomorrow and like Alex who has got the care and he smokes a cigarette.
But he's also capable of making original characters like Rob, the guy with no ears,
who's just perfect in every way.
Yeah, yeah.
Rob's not like Rob's Rob is meant to be funny.
But then he like, I think he's supposed to be cool later on.
Like he's he's so strange because of the most powerful fighters.
Rob is like it is a joke like obviously intentionally supposed to be funny.
But it's like it's Rob is like funny intentionally and unintentionally
because, yes, he makes like he ends up becoming like this really bad
ass character later on is some really fun.
He's a really fun fight scene.
Oh, shit, he's dragon born and it all changes.
One of my top favorite fucking twists in the entire comic
because it's like it really was such a silly thing.
But all of a sudden it opens up all these new powers for Rob to have.
And it's sort of almost makes sense because like his ears
not having ears protects him from the shouts he does.
I don't even know. It's so fucking funny.
Oh, of course, he was dragon born the whole time.
I should have known that in this world, some people are just dragon born
and they have whatever powers that entails.
I don't I'd never play it just like, you know,
Laserbot played Skyrim at some point and then he's just like,
yeah, I'm going to put that in the comic.
Like it's just so funny.
Like he will just put things in the comic and like there's no one in the comic
is ever like, hey, why is Bugs Bunny hanging out with Shadow of the Hedgehog?
It just makes sense. Like nobody questions it.
It's just like what a stupid question.
Like I could point to any two people on the street and be like, hey,
why is that guy hanging out with that? I don't know.
These are just these are people in this world.
Why would you at least in Sonichu there's like this sort of like
alternate dimension and like imagination type lore that almost sort of explains
that there's nothing like that in Tales of Troy. It's just this is the world.
Tales of Troy is simply a world in which the people happen to be
Bugs Bunny, etc.
Yeah, it's not like it's not like Sonichu where it's like this is this
this takes place in the cartoon version of reality where like cartoon characters are real.
The realm of pure imagination C197.
Exactly. There are reasons for the things that happen in Sonichu
with regards to fictional characters.
And then like, you know, they're aware that they're fictional and or at least
for our from our perspective.
Whereas, you know, Tales of Troy, it's like, again, you pretty much could have made
that comic with completely original characters.
You just would have had to have, you know, changed a few powers here and there.
But it's just so funny to me the way he was randomly wouldn't be the same.
It wouldn't.
Oh, that's the thing. No one would have ever discovered it.
No one would have cared about it because it's the beauty of seeing this.
Like this character, these like warped like it's entertaining versions of them.
It's Wiley Coyote, like pulling off this like master anime villain plan.
Like a piece of charm.
Honestly, the story of any of the five people getting neutral powers
and becoming master necromancers, but learning how to hide in the shadows
and control their emotions is an interesting story.
But the fact it's Elmer Fudd and fucking Tom Sylvester and porcupine,
that makes it like God tier.
It's a beautiful juxtaposition.
The new the neutrals are I think I remember Digi
during the lecture says like this is just like cool.
This is just like cool anime story powers.
And it's like, yeah, the neutrals are actually kind of a cool
like at world element in in it.
And it's like kind of it's like, oh, wow, good job, ladies.
But you did it.
You had a good idea when you put it in your thing.
You start reading the comments.
Everyone starts reading the comic like as a joke to like be like,
what's this? This looks kind of stupid and funny.
And but like if you keep reading it, if you actually stick with it,
at some point you're going to get hit with a cool idea that you weren't like
you weren't ready to be hit with like an actually unironic thing.
So you're going to be blindsided by it.
And it's going to like hit you like like as if you were a kid
experiencing a cool thing for the first time like what you'll see.
You'll see fucking tomorrow, like pull out his third eye
and put you in like his mind dungeon or whatever.
And it actually looks kind of cool.
And you're like, oh, shit, fuck.
Well, here it is. Here we are.
It happened. And now it is interesting, although
it is interesting to think also that we are experiencing it
or at least people who are getting into it now rather are experiencing
it differently than the people who were there at the start
because he used to put out, you know, on a page by page basis.
Imagine if your favorite manga like Berserk or whatever
was published on a page by page basis, you know what I mean?
That would feel absolutely torturous.
Like it would feel like everything happens at a beyond a snail's pace.
So people got so pissed off at him when he stopped focusing on tales
and he just wanted to have a cool fight between two of his original characters.
And now when people go back, they're like, this is a cool, fun fight scene.
But at the time, people were so pissed off.
Like a month straight, like what happened to team up?
Yeah, there were a ton of people that weren't
on board with the idea of even attempting to like enjoy it unironically.
They just were like, I want to laugh at the silliness of the tales parts, please.
And that's it. But I was glad that laser was like, I don't give a fuck.
I'm going to do whatever the fuck I want to do.
It's exactly the same as like the Berserk reference you're talking about before,
like the whole boat getting off the boat thing.
Like you read that now.
It's not nearly as bad as it is when you think about like for years,
people were waiting for that to end, but you can blow through it
and like less than an afternoon now, if you're just catching up to get
to where it is currently, like the distribution matters so much
and how these stories kind of like flow.
I mean, some of some of the original character fights are kind of lame.
Like, I think, I don't know.
I think when Rob fights the lightning guy, I was kind of like whatever.
But but but but that was so yeah, I will admit that one doesn't even take very long.
Yeah, it's short.
There's a lot of like new powers in that fight and there's always a risk.
Like it's always more fun to see characters who have like pre established
powers that you sort of like understand going against each other.
Whereas the yellow electric guy strikes me as a completely pointless
like inclusion, who it's like who gets like an orange screen time
relative to like what he actually means to the story,
which as far as I can tell is nothing.
I believe I believe his name is Pindo, which is a strange name.
But I'm not sure.
And yeah, it's like it is funny.
They sort of set him up as, you know, like he's going to be Rob's rival.
And he has this moment where he steals Elmer through the power lines.
He starts showing up in all these Troll King scenes.
I have much, much, much, much less investment in him compared to
way more of these other characters like Troll King, Cheeto Man, like Demaro.
There's there's so many good like antagonists that he has waiting the way.
And there's like interesting things like Troll King and Cheeto Man are
on their own separate factions and they're going to have their own things,
presumably, if they ever interact with each other.
And, you know, there's all the entire words of death plot line.
And even then Alex, the red hair, the troll with a little bit of red hair,
he's like secretly plotting against the Troll King.
So like I said, there's so many different plot threads that when
you're not getting that comic coming out at a regular pace, it's like
it can feel a little, you know, painful when it's like you just wanted
to see something happen with a character that you haven't seen in like 10 years.
Yeah, I'm I'm I don't know.
It's exciting that it's coming out again.
I should I imagine there's not that much new stuff out yet.
I don't know.
Do you think it's too early to go and check it out and like get caught up?
Should I more accumulate now that the chapter
twenty three fighting is done, I'd say it's worth reading that thing.
And like one sitting, I would say.
Yeah, I want to see that.
I totally I'm like on board.
I get it.
Like I love like binge reading through a whole long like longer
or something like having to come up with weekly updates just is like it's so slow.
It's like I just but I do want to support the comic is the thing.
And you know, the only way you can't you can't we're not going to be able to wait
for the volume sales on this one.
We're going to have to support them as it's coming out.
So how cool would it be to own physical copies?
I hope you don't I've thought about it.
I've literally spent hours thinking about this, but it's so strange
because the pages are different sizes and there's all these weird little things
you'd have to consider.
Like there's a lot to have to say.
I'm not giving I'm giving up on it.
One day I would love to own a fucking huge.
I'm sure it could be done.
Yeah, and it would be a fucking it would be a fucking mess.
But I mean, this is tells gets trolled.
We're talking about so like it would be OK.
I would I would just have to take the time to design and lay out a nice solid part back copy.
And again, I would I'm not sure how much like when I'm going to wait for him to finish.
But then it's like, I'll just I'll do a volume one that's like everything up to this point, at least.
And that I would love to have it on my fucking shelf.
That would be awesome.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, man, laser, but you you dog, you devil, you've you've done it again.
It's so easy to just be like, oh, look, it's some silly
M.S. paint drawn with a mouse fan fiction comic.
Look how lame that is.
But it's actually like the coolest thing ever.
It's like, I don't know.
That's what's so good about it.
That's what's so good about it is how low it sets your expectation.
I always I've just been obsessing over this idea of how like cool it is to actually make a thing.
Like it was I'm a big fan of all the PCP lectures I've seen, but I haven't seen all of them.
And there's some I'm waiting to see like I haven't read one piece yet.
So I'm not going to watch that one for a while.
But I just recently watched Kokoro wish and I was thinking like, God damn,
I just came into this to laugh at some fucking autism comics.
And this is actually cool as hell.
What the fuck? That was a mind fuck.
Oh, yeah.
She that that one's weird.
I feel like I feel like Jennifer is a bit of a legitimate law cow.
But like it doesn't really come through and I don't talk about it that much in that lecture
because I'm talking about the comics and the comics are not as bad as people say they are.
So so I could have that lecture could have been a lot different
if I had just if I had focused more on J.D.R.
is a shenanigans.
Oh, yeah, I absolutely believe that there could have that could have been a completely different one
that you could only passingly mention some of the lower elements.
But it was way more interesting to me just to hear about these just ridiculously
complicated and convoluted and like connected comics
that spawned from this canceled game from I've heard enough stories,
but I've never heard anything about like the concepts in those comics.
That was a much more interesting part.
When I when I when I learned about when I learned about
fuck, what was that?
I don't even remember what the game was called, multiverse.
When I learned about multiverse, I was like, it snapped into place.
I was like, oh, my God, this this like this like multiverse idea is like present in all.
Like this is the this is like clearly the foundational idea
upon which all these other stories that she wrote is based.
Like, ah, there's a narrative through line here.
I found it. I found the thread.
I can pull on it until the sweater unravels.
Amazing.
It was very I thought it was a really cool little linchpin
to keep like tie everything together, you know what I mean?
Because I don't know.
It was I thought I thought it wrapped it up in a very interesting story
just the way like, you know, you have all the she had so many like ideas.
And I always like that.
Like I just people that get so bizarrely insanely into the nitty gritty details
of the world building to the point where they're talking about the fucking physics.
I don't know why I like that shit.
It's just like such a obsessive, yeah, like compulsion
to justify everything that happens that like most most works of fiction
don't bother to do because like that kind of detail for the most part,
it's beyond the scope of any story that you want to tell
because most stories are character centric.
So to just like go out of your way to not only
conceptualize those details, but make the story revolve around them
is so atypical that it's like fascinating because it's so fresh and interesting,
even if like the context of it is like kind of rudimentary
in terms of its execution, just the ideas are fascinating.
Good news, though. Good news, though.
Jennifer was online on FIM Fiction.
Only eight hours ago.
So she is she is not gone anywhere.
She's still active.
She is still writing.
Oh, she just posted.
She posted a new conversion bureau story.
I'm genuinely glad she's still out there and creating.
But like you sort of said, I've zero
interested in reading MLP fan fiction fiction.
I'm I'm I'm sad.
I'm sad that it's MLP stuff.
I don't want to read MLP stuff.
Unless, well, unless and, you know, for the only in this one moment,
have I suddenly considered maybe I should maybe I should read one
and see what it's like, because what if it's like tales gets trolled and like,
yeah, there's ponies in it.
But like the stuff that actually goes on in it is like
very non pony centric.
And it's really it's a thing that just happens to be set in even back in the pony days.
I remember I've heard the name Conversion Bureau like.
Talked about like that was something that people knew of.
I never I never heard about it back in the day,
but she didn't make the Conversion Bureau.
She just she just writes within it.
I mean, for all I know, she could be writing in the Conversion Bureau universe
and her stories might not even have that much to do.
Oh, God, there's so many layers.
You might be right.
And it might be like good MLP fan fiction type story.
But like the mere fact that she's writing within another universe
makes it less interesting to me because I like that she created
not only her own physics, but she would like conceptualize the entire universe
starts to finish. I don't know why that's just so funny to me.
It's like the kind of creator that the limitations of fan fiction
would be just another obstacle to overcome and she would find a way to do it, you know?
I absolutely believe it could be like actually really entertaining,
but it is just the fact that it's MLP fan fiction is a little bit of high bar
for me, at least to get over.
I agree completely, but it's just like, well, never know.
You know, I mean, it's like we were just saying, like we were just saying,
Tails gets trolled, Tails gets trolled, sets you up with low expectations.
And maybe maybe that's the same for me with these pony stories.
Maybe that's just the hurdle I need to give in chapter one.
A shot would not be a huge ask in terms of time.
So oh, oh, she's making posts.
She's making posts about Trump.
She doesn't like him.
Oh, she's talking about the election.
Know what my Kokoro wishes that Joseph Biden wins the election?
Yes, yes. Should I?
OK, I kind of want to read some of this.
Do you want to do you want to hear? Oh, how long do you want to hear?
It's it's not that. All right, all right.
OK, I mean, let's get a vibe check on how this feels.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, vibe, vibe, check, vibe, check.
OK, a prediction checklist by Chateau Yance, she wrote this yesterday.
The Trump publicans install a loyal Supreme Court replacement
Barrett for Ginsburg.
The Democrats will do almost nothing at all.
Their reaction will be weak and you know what?
This is boring. Never mind.
She's just whatever. Yeah.
She just leave a comment that's like, go back to talking about world plates.
Go back to talking about ponies.
Oh, man, she's posting like she's posting like every day,
not stories, just like posts on her time.
Oh, no, got into the politics fandom, the worst fandom of all.
God, I really hope she is it's literally more healthy of an outlet
to be writing My Little Pony fan fan fiction than it is to be ranting
about Donald Trump every day on what on a My Little Pony fan fiction site.
Like, yeah, at least do it on Twitter where people will actually give a shit.
Oh, yeah, no, she's she's saying she's predicting that she's predicting
that Trump stays in office and basically declares himself dictator for life.
And we enter a dystopia.
That's that's what she thinks is going to happen.
She's not alone on that thought process.
Write some fan fiction about it.
Let's. Yeah. Yeah.
Write some fucking fan fiction about it.
Go back to dance for me, monkey.
You know, it is kind of funny that you're saying that, like,
I'm sure there are so many people who, like, I'll never, ever, ever,
ever get to consider reading tales get strolled because they are just such
a strong aversion to like Sonic in Sonic autism.
You know what I mean? Right.
And that's what I know. Let's let's not be close.
Yeah, you know, it's funny.
I'm going to I'm going to admit something which is a little rude to you guys,
I guess, but back when my little pony first hit the scene, I was like, yes,
finally, finally, there's a bigger lightning rod for autism than Sonic.
And I was just so grateful that it was like a diverting away the autism
from my franchise. That's fair.
Yeah. Yeah, that makes sense.
Um, OK, but the show had like really great animation
and like the songs are really catchy.
And, you know, it was it was a hell of a joke.
One of the more embarrassing things
that I'll probably ever admit is that I never watched an episode of my little
pony because I was afraid that I would like it.
That I was I thought I would like it because I could get into that.
I like Sonic. Who knows what I like.
It's true. I totally do not understand Sonic.
I the only Sonic I've ever played was like I had a friend in like elementary
school who had a genesis and I would fuck around and play a little Sonic here and
there. I never like, you know, a game or anything.
And I never played any games after the genesis.
There is something really compelling about Sonic Adventure
that I can't quantify, but it's there.
And I really like it, even though they're not.
I know exactly what you didn't own a Dreamcast.
I just I can't see it. I can't see what you see.
I just watched I literally before this episode started,
I watched Cybershell's video on the differences,
like why Sonic Adventure DX is a bad port.
And like you open it, talking about how like it's you first played on Dreamcast
and it was like magical.
I had the exact same experience because I played it on Dreamcast the first time
and like it blew my mind to shit about how just how like playing through
that first level, it just felt like this is like bigger and better
and cooler than anything my other consoles could back in the day.
Every time there was a new console generation,
it was like the next coming of fucking Jesus Christ itself.
And it was the dream that it was the first new console, but I mean,
I can absolutely agree that it's technically I can like I I can hear
like I'll sit down and listen like a two hour long video detailing every reason
Sonic Adventure one and two are objectively bad games.
Don't like sit there nodding along, agreeing with every single thing they say
and then go, yep, and then I'll go back to playing them and loving them
and continuing to enjoy them. And it's isn't a sound job.
I don't know, maybe, maybe I replayed City Escape
like trying to get like a hundred points higher score
and just like trying to like min max my run in Metal Harbour
and all that kind of shit like I don't know.
There was just something so fucking compelling about that those games.
So OK, so even to this day, to go on a little
just quick tangent about it back in the day.
I mean, I could only I first of all, I get why people don't like
Sonic games because if you just pick up, play it, beat it one time
and then put it down, it probably won't feel that great because like
you can just run straightforward in a Sonic game and ram your fucking face
into every single enemy and lose all your rings and pick them up.
And you can beat the level like that.
You know what I mean? The skill like it's not hard to beat a Sonic game.
It's hard to beat a Sonic game and like play it well.
And that's where like the joy comes from.
They actually like put the onus on you to put like get skill mastery
and actually like learn these games.
That's why they spend so much time on these first levels,
making them so intricately crafted because you're going through them.
Who's video about that?
Davoo made a video about Sonic.
Yeah, I did. I did see that video a long time ago.
It was a good video.
Yeah, pretty much explained it right.
Because like Sonic is about speed, you know?
And because back in the day, back in the day, it sound like a boomer,
you know, say good design games with an arcade mindset
that you would be playing it over and over and over again to get good at it.
You know, because like you bought Sonic, it's a brand new game.
It's two hours long.
Obviously, you're going to play it more than one time.
You know what I mean?
But I feel like I didn't get not to get too boomery,
but like Zoomers will pick up a game, play it one time and be like,
yeah, that sucked.
And then, you know, you don't you don't have I don't expect everyone
who wants to get a song to have to sit down and play through the same game
like 20 because I didn't have a lot of games.
And I did what I'd like to play Sonic over and over.
So I just naturally, without having to think about it,
mastered these skills by playing them over and over and over again.
So it's like, I forget who said this, but it's like a Sonic level is like a skate park.
You know what I mean?
Like you can have fun there.
You just have to put in the effort to get a little bit good.
You know what I mean? Like we first are skateboarding.
You're not going to have fun. You know what I mean?
I feel like the Sonic series in general has always had this weird kind of pendulum
of an identity crisis because I feel like the original Genesis trilogy,
like there was a lot of mastery you could do to mid-max your runs.
But I feel like the focus, like they were still operating under
the input, like the idea of it being like a Mario style game of like a platformer.
Like you play through Green Hill Zone and Sonic one, and it's a fucking blast.
And you can just like go really fast.
And there's like different paths you can find.
There's like kind of like, you know, the top, mid and bottom of those levels.
So you can kind of like figure out new paths when you first start playing it.
Like, oh, you can go down this way or like, oh, this part of the wall is like
breakable so I can go through here.
But then you get to like Marble Zone and it's like slow.
And it's about like precision platforming.
And like with with like, you know, replaying it over and over again,
you can like find ways to like cut down on the time.
But like as someone playing for the first time,
it just comes to a grinding halt on that second level.
Big time, big time.
A lot of a lot of the modern Sonic is like, oh, no, but Sonic is like speed.
Like that's the meme.
So it's just like hold X to win where you just kind of like get
build up your speed meter and you just keep like hitting the boost constantly.
And there's very little platforming involved now.
It is really strange how the boost games have basically like they've
always taken speed out of the equation because like getting and maintaining
top speed used to be such an ordeal.
And now it's just press a button.
And again, that boost gameplay has its things that are good about it.
I'm not fully shitting on it or anything.
But like it's just so fundamentally completely different from everything
before it. You know what I mean?
You have you have like the old games that were very much a platformer
with speed is kind of like an afterthought in a marketing gimmick.
Then you have the boost games where it's like speed and the platforming
is like an afterthought.
But like I remember playing Sonic Advance 2 and I feel like that was like
the closest to Sonic ever like finding its fucking zen in terms of I guess
Sonic Adventure 2 speed levels or Sonic and Shadow Levels did this a lot too.
But like speed you could mix like slowing down is like a fail state,
you know, because like you could replay the first level of Sonic Advance 2
over and over and over again, because I did this in math class
instead of paying attention.
Me and my friend would pass our GB ASP back and forth trying to do
the time trial on that.
You could get your run down to like 15 seconds on the first level
if you like did it well enough because they had all these extra little
mechanics of like having like an air boost and like these side boosts
to like keep your momentum going where normal Sonic mechanics would have you stop.
And it's just like that seems like the way to do it.
Like that seems like what this game should be about.
It should be about keep building and then maintaining momentum
for as long as possible and giving you a tool set to do that.
And like Adventures 2 levels have a lot of that too.
Like once you get the light dash, there are gaps where you can keep
momentum going instead of stopping like in Metal Harbor, especially.
You can skip a lot of like the ramps and stuff.
And like that just seems like where the soul of the series really should be
focused on is just like a kind of like a skill based maintaining of momentum.
And there's just like little pockets of it throughout the games,
where it's just like it's so fun and it's so replayable,
trying to like get a little bit higher score by like minimum
like min maxing your ability to go through these stages.
And so much of the franchise doesn't do that.
And it's frustrating because like these like these one like levels
like Green Forest and Metal Harbor and City Escape and like the bulk
of Advanced 2s mechanics like get it.
And like somebody at SEGA understands what the series should be doing.
And it's just frustrating as someone who grew up with it, being like,
there it is, I want more of that.
And then you get like another boost game.
You're like, OK, I'll see you in three years, give it another shot.
Yeah, that's pretty much what I felt about the Genesis games.
And like that's why I like Mania so much, because I absolutely fully
100 percent agree with everything you said about Sonic 1
in that they had they spent ages getting Green Hill Zone just right.
And then they really didn't have they're like, well, it has to be a platforming game.
So they have all these slower zones like marble and labyrinth that nobody
really likes that much.
But I really feel like they started to get it better.
They kind of went really hard the other way in Sonic 2, where they had
very streamlined levels with the top, middle and bottom routes that were
much less just waiting for platforms and stupid shit like that.
And in some ways, Sonic 2 was almost a little too streamlined.
They kind of cut out a lot of the exploration.
That's why I thought Sonic 3 and Knuckles brought back the exploration
where it was it wasn't going fast all the time, but there were some really
good areas you can get some like speed that you could maintain.
Yeah. And yeah, I feel like Sonic 3 and Knuckles sort of perfected
how I like see the 2D games.
I can see the appeal of the advanced games.
I only really had advanced one as the one that I played a lot.
But I was interested in advanced two and three.
They seemed interesting.
I would even now I'd recommend advanced two because like advanced
advanced one plays a lot more like the Genesis games.
Advanced two is different in that you start.
Yeah, it starts you out at speed, which is really interesting.
And then it has it has a boost function, but it's not boost
as we've come to know the boost function where you press a button
to get max speed.
It was like you go fast enough and you will once you maintain your
which is interesting.
I sort of like that idea way more than the current boost one.
But yeah, you know, there's a lot of interesting stuff
you can do in the adventure games, especially to once you get the bounce
bracelet, you know, there's like a lot of interesting things you can do
to like exploit the physics and just the spin dash like you can really
use it in creative ways to get like just do some crazy big jumps.
I'm not even like a speed runner, but you can just like so that was
one of the interesting things about the chow garden, which is like it's
such a ridiculous, pointless thing.
Like why is in the game right now?
I got a button to say that I really liked your video about the chow raising.
I love that shit.
They look weird, esoteric systems.
I had no idea so much time.
I had no idea they could look all these different ways.
Yeah. Yeah.
There's so many different like ways they can look with other
evolutions and stats and cosmetics.
It's wild.
And it's funny because like people are like they should make a standalone
chow game. It's like on one hand that makes sense.
That would be fun.
But I'm just trying to think like how would you meaningfully
gait your chow's progression?
Like how like what's to stop you from just giving them 100,000 animals
or crystals in a row because what you'd have to like hide the animals
behind a minigame or something, right?
But then the minigame would get super boring after the 10,000th time.
So I thought it was kind of brilliant to have like they don't make you play
a stupid minigame to get the chow parts to need.
They make you play a real actual fun game Sonic Adventure 2 and it gives
you incentive to replay those levels over and over again to master them.
If they're the synergy between the two like systems is really interesting
because like me and my sister played Sonic Adventure 2 like constantly
when we were kids, it's funny.
There are people who don't even really like the Sonic part that much,
but they were super into the chow stuff.
So that was my sister. Yeah, exactly.
She bought like probably like 25 VMUs just to like bring all their
chow around and like work on their stats and stuff.
That's really funny because I took a lot of data in the VMU to store the data.
So she would just like get like her allowance money and just buy another
Dreamcast VMU just just to raise another one in addition to like the 15
she was already working on.
We had like a fucking graveyard full of VMUs that are just gone.
Yeah, I love you.
I was going to say, I was going to say they're probably all dead now.
All my old VMUs are fucking batteries died.
But yeah, that's I love the Dreamcast.
There's so many things about the Dreamcast that are just so interesting to me
and like unique and I just love the VMU.
So stupid.
Like why do they make a little screen with like a little it's like they made
their memory part into a little Game Boy.
It's so fucking strange.
I love it.
I love it, but it is so strange.
Like why would you do that?
My sister, like the chow, the chow die eventually.
Like they'll eventually just die off.
And like one of my sister's favorite chow like died.
And so she like restarted the game without saving it.
And like before it died, she just threw it in a VMU to keep it alive forever.
And just like weird little things like that that just emerged from the gameplay.
And it was just like, I don't know.
It was like such an interesting system that I never really got into.
But like I was able to see how complicated and intricate it got.
What do you think are the implications of the fact that a, oh God,
I might be a little off, but I think you'll understand what I'm saying.
That a dark speed chow looks like shadow, but it's not a hero speed
chow that looks like Sonic.
It's a neutral speed chow.
Yeah, I always thought that was really strange.
I don't know what it is exactly.
Maybe it's because the hero version is like this white stripy thing.
And like it sort of implies that there's some other creature out there
that looks like that, that is like a light counterpart to Sonic and Shadow.
Who is this man?
That is a pretty funny thing.
And I have noticed that before because it is strange.
They just wanted all the hero chow to have like this, like they all wanted
all the heroes to basically look sort of the same, you know, white, I guess.
And they didn't mind that the neutral chow
and it could be all sorts of different colors.
But yeah, that is a very it results in a very strange thing where Sonic
like the genetic information that composes Sonic is based in speed
and not necessarily heroism.
And it's deliberate.
It's specifically like morally neutral,
whereas Shadow is like specifically evil and speedy.
I guess the implication is that Sonic is actually so heroic
that he has no natural inclination towards being a hero.
He's completely neutral at all times,
but he still saves the world anyways, because he's that cool.
I guess, I guess so.
I just I just want to meet.
I just want to meet the other.
The implication there is that there must be some creatures
that look like every every form of this that this chow can like be like
whatever like whatever like a hero power chow looks like.
Maybe there's some guy out there who looks like that, but bigger.
And if Sonic ever met him, well, if you want to get deeper into the lore
of like Sonic Adventure and Sonic Adventure, too, there's this whole plot
point where Shadow talks about how he's the ultimate life form and the ultimate
life form. But if you there's this weird thing where if you wait like the final
battle against the bio lizard in space, where you're super sonic and super
Shadow has a five minute time limit, I think it's five minutes.
Yeah, I think it's five minutes.
If you wait for like four minutes and 30 seconds, like right before you're about
to die, like one of the things Shadow can say to you is like, Sonic,
I think I realized something.
I think you're actually the ultimate life form.
And there's a whole what?
Yeah, that's in the game.
So no, yeah, that's it.
Yeah, that's so that's some deep lore that not a lot of people realize.
So yeah, so it might be something related to that.
Yeah. So Sonic is actually the real ultimate life form.
And that explains why Shadow looks like him because Gerald was trying to
create the ultimate life form and it's going to look like Sonic because Sonic
is the ultimate life form. Shit.
That's amazing. No, I never knew I never heard that.
I knew Shadow now that you say it.
I feel like I probably heard that as a kid at like 10 years old,
but didn't like have the brain power to like contextualize it and anything
other than like, oh, it's just it's just game talking to me.
And that was it.
But yeah, it's a line that you could easily just sort of be like, yeah,
whatever, ultimate life form.
They say that like a hundred times throughout the game.
So you get kind of numb to hearing it at the end.
But right. It's like the game is the game even implies that like it's the
bio lizard that was the ultimate life form and not Shadow the entire time.
There's this weird fucking lore where like Rouge will show the bio lizards
like report on screen, but like for like one second,
like no human could ever read it without having to like pause it.
And back in the day, you're going to like pause, you know, that that was no
one's an option. So only later, like a lot of lore came out.
And it's like, yeah, it's so strange that like it doesn't seem to make any sense.
Like how could you have two attempts to make the ultimate life form?
And one is a giant fucking lizard and one is a little shadowy hedgehog thing.
But it makes a little more sense than it seems.
I'm not saying I'm not saying it makes perfect sense or anything like that,
but it makes a little bit more sense than it might initially.
Gerald just got into the Sonic fandom and realized that he needed to make his
edgy OC, you know, like he changes.
There's all this like there's these fan theories,
like he's at the very end of Sonic 3 and Knuckles.
There's this ancient mural that shows Super Sonic fighting like the Eggman robot.
And the theory is that Gerald saw the mural of Super Sonic.
And that's where he got the idea to have a hedgehog shaped type creature.
I got a deep dive into the Sonic fandom.
Look all this shit I'm learning, all these connecting threads.
This is fucked up, I gotta say.
This is way fucked up.
Yeah, it's deep lore, man.
There's deep Sonic lore.
But it's funny because it's also one of the series that genuinely,
like genuinely the creators do not give a fuck about like lore between games.
Like there's like no continuity.
Like the moon is blown up in Sonic Adventure 2.
It looks fine in the next game like shit like that.
Then they just don't give a fuck.
Like it's bizarre.
Oh yeah, they blew up the moon.
I mean, they just forgot about it.
Yeah, it's completely fine.
Never once mentioned again.
Well, they blow up half the moon.
So it should have a giant.
It would have been so easy just to have a big chunk missing in the next game.
It would have been such a small, easy thing to like remind people that
it doesn't matter.
You know, again, it's not something worth getting upset about,
but it is funny.
They genuinely like like they'll practically go out of their way to make the world
not actually make sense.
What's the fan theory for preparing the moon?
I'm sure someone has come up with a theory.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
I I guarantee for a fact, you could easily find multiple different fan theories
as to what the fuck went on with that moon.
Yeah, yeah, makes you makes you wonder.
World sure is mysterious.
Sonic Lore is so funny because at the end of Sonic Oh, six, I'm sure.
I think most people know this, but like he has to go back in time
to undo the events of the game.
So the game retcons itself out of existence.
So I don't even know why people are so upset about that game,
because literally nothing that happened in that game even happened.
Wait, which game still happened to me?
Sonic Oh, six. Oh, a legendarily bad one.
Yeah, the really bad one with the human kiss, which is the most, you know,
it's so easy to meme on because it's funny.
But they didn't happen.
Oh, God, you know, it's funny.
I feel like I should have some sort of more like strong feelings
on Sonic Oh, six. I never even bother playing it.
Yeah, he's from the future on that one.
And then in that game blazes from the future.
But then in Sonic Rush blazes from a different dimension.
And then when they meet in the Olympics games, they can't keep it straight.
It's such a fucking mess.
Do they do they canonically go to the Olympics?
Or is that just sort of like a side thing, like a Mario card?
I'm pretty sure that's not canon, but I I choose to believe it's canon.
There are some really bizarre and hilarious, like not like full on cutscenes,
but like weird things were like omega the robots.
Like I have must give Donkey Kong my gratitude for fixing me.
It's this great show.
Is laser bat writing these games?
What the fuck? Imagine Sonic is Donkey Kong.
It is. It is like that.
Oh, God.
Oh, fuck. Well, I love that.
Yeah, see, the Sonic series is like if there's so much weird cringe,
but like wholesome cringe, I don't even know.
I'm like so past like touched on like the sad AM and the Archie.
Yeah, see, OK, that's the thing about Sonic is like Mario is great.
I wish I could have this whole K-Fade where I pretended to hate Mario all the time,
but I can't do it. I like Mario games.
So like Mario is great, but he has much more cohesive identity
where Sonic is like fractured through this prism where there's like
10,000 different versions of Sonic.
You can just pick the kinds you like and get in arguments
with other Sonic fans over the kinds they like.
And it's a self perpetuating war of Sonic fandom.
I don't know.
Oh, my God.
And yeah, like multiple shows, like five different shows,
each with like a totally different they had they had the sad AM
and the Adventures of Sonic the dog show running at the exact same time.
And they're completely different takes on the character.
I remember because like I was I would rent like the Adventures of Sonic
the hedgehog on on like from Blockbuster.
And then one time I got a sad AM tape and it was totally different.
Like what the fuck is this?
And I was very confused.
Literally, like, again, it's not like the sad AM was so it's not that edgy,
but like compared to the straight up Looney Tunes nonsense
of Adventures on the hedgehog is it's quite jarring the difference, honestly.
It's it's like it's like sitting down to watch Looney Tunes
and then like like Bugs Bunny is like in an episode of like a serious
corner. Yeah, Bugs Bunny joins the resistance to save.
It's like it's like one Looney Tunes show that that is always.
Oh, yeah, lunatics or whatever the fuck.
The one where they're all in like black jumpsuits and they look like.
Yeah, but like that's what sad AM is for Sonic.
Like instead of it being like a Looney Tunes show, it's like he's a freedom
fighter fighting against like an oppressive technological regime.
It is kind of strange that like how many like shows like that?
Like like Robotnik already took over the world.
Like he already won and they're already living in like hiding.
You know what I mean? They're the freedom fighters.
It's kind of a strange setting, honestly, dystopic,
but you don't see a lot of dystopian children's fiction, I got to say.
It was such a strange concept because like even though it's like
I would argue it's a better like storytelling and probably a better show
overall than like the other adventures of Sonic the Hedgehog cartoon.
That felt much more in spirit of the original games.
Like there's nothing like super serious in Sonic one.
It's very much like a cartoony.
It's funny because you're absolutely right.
There are there are and I have always been undercurrents of environmentalism
and natural Green Hill being better than the mechanical robotic
like scrap brain type things, but there was never like overt
like message or anything.
So yeah, I have to agree.
It's funny because as a kid, I really liked the sat and one
because I thought it was so cool and serious and mature.
And I didn't I mean, I didn't hate it, but I wasn't that into the adventures
of Sonic the Hedgehog because it was I thought it was so like it's for kids or whatever.
And now that I'm older, I really, really like adventures of Sonic the Hedgehog.
That's a really funny show.
Sat a.m. feels like a fan fiction.
It really does.
Although it doesn't even come close to feeling like a fan fiction
compared to Sonic Underground, which is literally like fan fiction
that got licensed and put on television somehow.
I don't even know what the fuck.
But you're right.
Sat a.m. definitely has strong fan fiction vibes to it.
God, Sonic is weird as shit.
So yeah, it really it really is such a strange franchise in multiples.
It's like a huge like thing, like all this stuff going on.
And then plus there's the Sonic movie that came out this year,
which I had completely assumed was going to be the most worthless piece
of shit of all time and somehow it wasn't.
And then thank God that Corona virus hit because now we can go down
as the second highest grossing movie of the year or whatever.
Thank God. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, it was all worth it.
Just so the Sonic movie could be a success.
What do you what do you think of the Sonic movie?
You know, it's like I'm of two minds about it because on one hand,
if you want to say that it's not that good because I mean, like it's like
compared to like an actual 10 out of 10, it's it's a kid's movie.
It's like, you know, alien comes to earth, learns the power of friendship.
I can see all the complaints and I agree with that.
But, you know, they unfucked up the design.
They have a lot of cute little Easter eggs and references that I got.
So it was pretty much the fact that it wasn't a disaster means it was a huge success.
OK, yeah, pretty much fair enough.
That's the best you can really say about it is that it should have been
a fucking nightmare and it was just like another movie.
Yeah, I was I was seriously just like, OK, well, there are all these things
in the like their Sonic oh sick or the shout of the Hedgehog the game
that everyone laughs at their Sonic oh sick, everyone laughs at their
Sonic Boom shitty game that everyone laughs at in the Sonic movie is just
going to be other tentpole thing in the history of Sonic that everyone can laugh at
and all just have to, you know, cope and deal with it.
No big deal. But, you know, kids liked it.
And then, you know, the idea that there are kids out there
who just didn't even know about Sonic and then they watch that movie
and now they're like Sonic fans.
Really strange timing from Sega because there are absolutely no games
or anything released like concurrently to like promote, you know what I mean?
Like they really which is very it was such a bad decision from there.
And the fact that they had to pull, they had to redesign Sonic,
which I mean, people think it's like all publicity stunt,
but they had all these toys and merchandise designed
that they had to pull from store shelves.
And when the movie went out, there were no toys in the stores
and people were like posting on Twitter like I want to see the movie
and I wanted to buy a toy for my kid and there's no fucking toys to buy.
Yeah, so great, great job, Sega.
It's wild. God, it's weird.
It's weird that they would fuck up that bad.
It's very strange story.
It's funny. It feels it feels like they thought the movie was going to be a disaster.
Whenever people ask them about the movie during development, they're like,
don't ask us. We don't anything. Just that's about Paramount.
We don't know anything about that.
Like it seems like they were already prewriting an office, a huge failure.
And like they weren't ready for it to be a success, you know what I mean?
Yeah. But like this is such this the the entire story of the movie.
Just it feels like this is exactly what the Sonic franchise would would do.
You know, it is a bizarre little encapsulation of like this coming out.
Like it would be like the fans having a meltdown.
It's is Sonic encapsulated in one thing.
And then the final product ended up not being quite as bad as you think it would be.
It really just sums the whole thing up.
Yeah. And you know, I got to say, there's an Illumination Mario movie coming out.
I think either twenty twenty one or twenty twenty two.
And I strongly believe it's going to be worse than the Sonic movie.
In fact, I honestly do believe unless you are incredibly
based and like the original Mario Bros.
movie that I think the Sonic movie might be the best video game movie.
And I staunchly take the belief that it is much better than Detective Pikachu was.
I liked the Mario movie as a kid.
I mean, I don't I liked it, too.
I don't think I was a kid, too, because it was Mario and I was so stupid.
I was just like, it's Mario.
So I like it. It was so strange.
Like I was captivated.
It was Mario and like I guess I thought it was weird that everything looked that way.
But I was like, yeah, I mean, it's live action.
So of course, it's not going to look like the video game.
I guess this is just how it looks. Whatever. Oh, Yoshi is a velociraptor.
Sure. Yeah, it's funny, because like, yeah, it's funny, because they ease you into it.
Like, OK, you know, Bob Hoskins, Mario, like, OK, I can see that.
You know, and then and then they ease you into the Mushroom Kingdom
and then it's like covered in fungus and it's like, yeah, OK, I guess.
And then it's what fucking the goombas are these little headed monsters.
The certain point you just have to be like, what the fuck are you doing?
Where's anything from the game?
I haven't seen that since I was a little kid.
I'd love to watch it again.
So I guess like there's people that genuinely defend it.
It sort of has like a following now.
And I would love to watch it again as an adult and be like, I they're like,
this is kind of actually I sort of see why I liked it or like, wow,
as a kid's really just will watch anything.
This is like trash.
I mean, there are some legitimately creative, interesting elements, interesting ideas.
I just I'm not.
I just don't know how much all of it ever belonged in a Mario Bros.
movie. That's my only issue.
It's just like it's like what?
It's like the late 80s, early 90s, whenever that fucking movie came out.
And it's just like, OK, it's that time.
You can't do like computer animation or anything.
Yeah, it is a movie of its time.
Everyone was going to do with a Mario movie in the late 80s.
Honestly, that is a good point.
Because like, what are you going to do?
Mario is so animated.
They have there was a Japanese animated.
They should have they should have just an animated movie.
But that wouldn't have made the box office bucks, I guess.
I don't know. So it's not American.
They're not such a strange.
Well, just funny because like nowadays,
nothing Nintendo was such a tight stranglehold over how
Mario can be portrayed in other media.
You know what I mean?
Like the idea that something that strange could ever happen.
I feel like the reason they have such a stranglehold on now
is because of that movie.
Oh, yeah, that's probably definitely a contributing factor.
Like never again. No, we fucked up.
We can't allow it. It is funny.
Like, yeah, even Sega, like when they're like, yeah,
go ahead, make a sonic movie.
Like, do they do they understand how much a big block
like Hollywood movie can affect the public consciousness of a franchise?
Like the that could have seriously affected the Mario franchise.
You know what I mean? Right. Yeah.
I mean, Sega was like crazy, because like not only did they
give Hollywood Sonic and like let his fate rest in their hands,
they didn't have any like again, there was no product out there
to kind of like do damage control if it turned out to be a total nightmare.
Just like, oh, everyone like this,
they would have painted the perception of Sonic for an entire generation, essentially.
Yeah, it really there really could have been an entire generation of kids who,
I mean, beyond like their entire exposure to Sonic is that's the frame of reference.
Cringe movie cringe meme movie and hearing Aaron make fun of it on Game Grumps.
And that's their only exposure to Sonic.
And that makes me a little sad, because like, you know, if you don't like Sonic,
if you play the Sonic games like and try to like them and don't like them,
that's fine. I mean, it would be kind of psychotic if I demanded every single
person on Earth love Sonic the Hedgehog.
But, you know, I just want I just want people to try it, you know,
don't come up to conclusions before you've because I know he has become a meme.
And it's weird because even the Sonic Twitter account, like they've embraced
the memeyness of it all, you know, like it's like we're in a post-modern
Sonic era where he's becoming fused into the memeyness of like
Sonic was in the Sonic movie.
Think about that. Yeah, that was really, yeah.
Yeah, there's a scene where someone was like showing a sketch of Sonic and it's
literally the Sonic meme. That's that's great.
I love it. Yeah, it was pretty funny.
And like, again, it's I'm not like saying it's a bad thing, but like we're like
it's entering an interesting age for Sonic.
And, you know, with the success of the Sonic movie, which again,
I don't think it's the greatest movie of all time, but I think kids probably liked it.
And, you know, it's funny, when they first announced Jim Carrey as Robonic,
I was like, what the fuck?
I couldn't think of like a worse like like I like Jim Carrey, but he's not Robonic.
You know what? He did a good job.
He actually did a good job like he did a good interesting take on the character.
And, you know, by the end,
he even had the look right because a little teaser for fans.
So, you know, I really didn't have a problem with him at all.
It's kind of unfortunate because like that stinger at the end with Robonic
and like Sonic the Sonic world or whatever, like it looked like a fucking
like almost like something out of Spy Kids, like in terms of like just bizarre
like hyper realistic. I could definitely see the Spy Kids.
But like it worked and I want a whole movie there.
I want a whole movie. Yeah, you see, I I actually would love to see him
in that like Robotnik Final Four.
I'm afraid that they're going to walk it back as soon as the second
movie starts. Better not.
I want I want Jim Carrey in that costume for two hours in the fucking Spy Kids
CGI. I would love him to do that.
I again, again, I really actually liked the take on Robotnik.
And it was so funny because like almost zero Sonic media even touches
on his origin story.
So it was actually kind of interesting to see the movie's take on it,
even though it's a little weird, weird owl mother figure.
But, you know, once you get over it, it's over very fast.
And then he's in the human world, which again, there's a whole super
played out Alvin the chipmunks coming to the human world thing, which I
totally get way too much money to have to make a CGI fucking alternate reality
for like if you ask me, I would have loved to see the whole movie
take place in the whole Green Hills zone type area.
But I get it. I get why they had to do it.
They need Joe Normie to connect to the cop guy and whatever.
And, you know, you know what?
Honestly, he was not that bad.
It's like he could it could have been a Chris Thorndike situation where
the human character was insufferable, but they honestly, they were OK.
The characters were OK.
I mean, they were all like very stereotypical, very generic.
They weren't like my favorite characters, but they didn't like it.
So when it's not a dismal failure, you've met my expectations when it comes to this franchise.
I had I had one sort of Chris Chan type
complaint, which is that two thirds of the movie, he's wearing these generic
looking white shoes.
I just wanted him to get in his red shoes.
God damn it.
And I understand why they had to move that scene to the later part of the movie.
And I like the part where the girl gave him the shoes is a cute little scene.
But I want to eat Sonic's red shoes.
God damn it.
He also has tan arms as we all have learned.
You know, it's funny.
I wish I could get heated about that.
But the blue arm design works for the movie because, you know, the tan arms
works in like the smooth like renders or whatever.
I like the way that looks in game Sonic, but movie Sonic looks fine for what he is.
Movie Sonic had tan fur.
That was strange.
It was supposed to be skin.
Yeah, it's yeah.
That's the thing because he has to be spiky because he's a hedgehog
and people aren't going to want to see him with his little tank top sleeve arms
and belly, I guess.
But I mean, yes, it was a little strange that he had tan.
That didn't make any sense.
But I wouldn't I wouldn't have wanted him to have a solid blue stomach either.
So I don't know that early design.
The first design for Sonic, the worst of the teeth were his little white hands.
I don't know what the fuck when they were thinking with that.
That wasn't his little hamster, his little raccoon hands with his human fingers.
Yeah, yeah, the hands did more for me than the disgusting face and teeth,
which also were not good.
But the hands, I don't know why that was the thing.
I mean, the original shoes were also worse, too.
Yeah, the whole thing.
There was a very the Sonic movie came very close to showing his feet.
And I was like praying that they weren't going to.
And then they didn't I was happy.
Dude, that was my biggest fear.
I was like, if they do a fucking joke about they had a scene with him in Sox,
I was like, God, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please,
don't you walk out of the theater.
I'll have to just walk out of the theater and back.
I can't do it. Can't do it.
Oh, my God, they knew they knew they knew not to do it.
I'm just so glad they I mean, on the one hand,
I I I mourn the loss to culture.
The fact that we didn't get the original model in the movie
just because it would have been like, yes.
OK, I am is a little bit of a meme to say, but God,
I would love to see the original the original cut.
Like, I would just love to break into the studio and see like,
I know it's not fully rendered.
They don't have fully rendered, disgusting Sonic,
but I would love to see all the fully rendered scenes mixed in with the work
for this thing. Sonic.
There's like, there's like a real.
There's like a real.
The gross cut.
Classic Sonic is modern Sonic.
There's disgusting Sonic.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean, I feel like you say that everyone would know exactly what you meant.
Yeah. What if what if in the second movie,
they have like a weird clone of Sonic and it's just that model,
but like, I would not even remotely be surprised if they had some sort of reference
or we got to reclaim our costs on this design seems like something they would do.
It definitely seems like like a not out of the realm of possibility.
I just remember. I don't know.
I just remember the funniest thing is like I was with the first poster,
like the teaser poster that came out, where it was just like him sitting on
like the bridge with his like, God, his muscular leg shoes and his shoes.
Yeah, there is that.
And there was one that was like him, but like in a silhouette.
And you could but you could still see like this thigh muscles.
I was like, I said that poster.
I said that poster to my sister, who was a huge Sonic fan with me back in the day.
And we both like still meme on Sonic all the time.
And I just sent her to that and her response and text was that
I thought Knuckles was the one who flexed his muscles.
And I thought it was the perfect response for a Sonic fan.
That's absolutely right.
And it's just so funny, like that they could have made that design
and like let it get like obviously didn't happen,
but they let it get out into the trailer form.
You know, like they didn't anticipate the backlash.
Like that is so strange.
They actually thought they did a good job.
I can't I can't give an objective perspective as a Sonic fan.
Obviously, it looks terrible as a Sonic fan,
but I couldn't fathom anyone ever looking at that and thinking it looked OK.
You know what I mean? Some fucking studio exact.
He looks like he's wearing pajamas.
It's it's fucked up.
It was a little it was strange.
They were trying so hard to make him look realistic,
but like the more realistic they tried to make him look,
the less he looked like he actually existed in the world.
You know what I mean?
Like the more cartoony version actually fits in better.
I don't even know how that works.
Look at that original design.
You're like, man, the Five Nights at Freddy's movies getting pretty weird.
Yeah, dude, if I ever if I ever get roll into some Five Nights
of Freddy's money or some fucking Minecraft notch money,
I'm going to finance a billion dollar
Tails gets trolled movie with those disgusting Sonic design pictures.
Holding you to that.
Once you hit a million subs, I'm going to I'm going to.
Yeah, once I once I become the first billion.
I'm going to be like, all right, it's time.
I've got all the here's all the licenses
you're going to have to buy for this movie.
That's 90 percent of your budget.
But go.
It is funny because like I would never want
there to not be a copious amount of copyrighted characters
and Tails gets trolled.
But it is sad that like that because of that,
you'll never be able to get it like see those animated versions
on Adult Swim or anything fun like that or any sold merchandise
or any sold books.
You have to print my own damn Tails gets trolled book.
Unless you can like squeeze it through with like parody or something.
But I don't I don't think it really works.
God, maybe I don't know.
Yes, because it's like it is an interest.
It's like in a perfect world.
Yes, you should absolutely be allowed to because it's so like
transformative and different.
How many times his family guy who's going to the actual copy.
Exactly.
And that's never going to be a problem.
Tried to sell.
Tails gets trolled.
Yeah, if you tried to.
Yeah, because he does all the copyrighted characters.
It's just like it's in such a limbo that it's not even like it's to the point
where like Alvin Earthworm, the guy to Super Mario Bros.
Z had like a whole like meltdown thing where he couldn't even use his
Patreon because he was afraid Nintendo was going to tell him that you're not
allowed to get money from Patreon if you're making an animated series
about Nintendo characters, you know what I mean?
So it's like, what the fuck?
Yeah, yeah.
But like, I don't know, they can't enforce that.
Right.
I mean, Nintendo has gone out of their way to be like overly aggressive
when it comes to shutting down shit.
It's like, what do you mean like they can't enforce it?
Like maybe they wouldn't win in court.
They wouldn't win in court, but they could take you to court
and make you spend thousands and thousands and thousands of defending yourself.
Like that's like that's how the legal system works.
It's not about whether you're right or wrong.
It's about whether you have the resources to win.
I mean, I guess, yeah, I guess they could say something to Patreon.
And if Patreon saw that, like, yeah, you're you're posting shit
with Nintendo characters on it, they could make you take it down.
I think he already got around this.
But he has he has his own separate, like original creative works.
And he has a Patreon for his own original creative works.
Oh, and also he does this.
He does Mario on the side here now.
Because originally, I think his patron was like, donate to me
because I'm just a couple days ago.
Nintendo took down a patron or a game
that was like some like porn game with Princess Peach.
And they like took that down.
So like they're taking stuff down, like even to this day, it's wild.
And again, I'm not to get too into the whole reliving my youth console wars
from the playgrounds of the 1990s, but Sega continues to be based as hell
not ever issue any sorts of cease and desist.
And in fact, hiring fan game designers and stuff.
Right. That's how Sonic Mania happened.
And it was exactly that's how you should do it.
Shot in the arm, the franchise is needed for like a decade.
It is. There is something deeply hilarious about the fact that fans
just had to like, say, stop, you just stop.
Just let us do it, please.
And after like a decade of trying to do it better, like fine, just do it.
And it was like the best selling game for a moment a while.
And it did really well.
Yeah, great selling game and a highest rated Sonic game of the past 20 years.
Although it is it is funny, you know, like if you talk about Sonic Adventure
one and two, I like the vast majority of people seem to be like, yeah,
those games are not good, but it's funny because when they came out,
everyone thought they were good, or at least not everyone thought they were good.
That's a way over some location.
They got good reviews.
Everyone I talked to knows that thought they were fun.
I didn't hear any of these like, like, yes, the camera is shit.
I mean, the camera is shit.
It's from already 64 and here are people bitching about it back then.
The camera is shit in every game for the like the first like from 1996 to 2001.
Yeah, I know it sounds incredibly defensive, but I feel like people are just
they just tend to be more hyper critical of Sonic games.
And you know, I think it's just there are super easy things to pick on in those games.
Like big, the cats levels are boring as shit.
Like it's really easy to look at that and like look at like knuckles levels
where you just have to like hunt for like little emerald shards.
Make this boring as shit.
This isn't what Sonic's about.
Sonic's about speed.
This game is terrible, you know, and then it is strange because like people
have this vitriol hatred for those knuckles and tails and slash Eggman levels.
But it's like if they just let you play the levels in the order as you want it.
Like I like the hero and dark story as like a like the originally they had
the six stories in Sonic Adventure one that might have been a little too much,
even though I have a huge fucking hard on for that type of Rashomon style.
See things from different perspectives, type storytelling.
But like I see why they wanted to condense it down to just two different
storylines that are playing at the same time.
But like, yeah, because they force you to like people just want to play a Sonic,
you know, and if like if you finish playing a Sonic and you're not
into the other gameplay styles, you can just not play the rest of the game.
And then maybe you wouldn't get your money's worth, you wouldn't like it.
But the fact they force you to play these levels you don't want to play
just to get to the Sonic levels you do want to play really seems to leave
a bad taste in some people's mouths.
I think they sort of just focused on the speed element of like the Sonic levels
and then like did what they kind of what they did with Sonic and Knuckles,
where like they brought another character that added
slightly different mechanics that could have changed.
Yeah, so seeing back in the Genesis games, there was no no one was complaining
that there were too many playable characters because it was just slight
variations on the exact same core gameplay style with new abilities.
It was perfect. There was no problem there.
I feel like for Sonic Adventure one, one of the problems with designing
a 3D platformer where the characters main gimmick is that they goes really,
really fast is that it's just hard to design levels around that in general.
But mainly because like you just go through the levels really fast.
So you have to spend a long time designing.
It is a worse problem in the boost games, but like it just takes longer
to design a level for Sonic and it gets it gets done with so fast.
So that's why they had the like the Knuckles levels in the first game.
So they just reuse some of these stages that they made for Sonic,
these open, expansive areas, but with a slightly different gameplay, you know,
just because I didn't I don't I'm one of the guys that doesn't really mind
the other types of gameplay. I don't I mean, I don't like big levels,
to be honest. It's shitty fishing.
I'm not even opposed to fishing games, but like the level of fishing
you get in big stages is not that great.
But because I've done it so many times, I can beat the big stages
and like I mean, one minute, they're over in no time.
But I understand if you don't, if you're not an expert,
if you just play, you can take forever.
My confession is that I've never beaten Sonic Adventure one
because I hated the big level so much.
I just went on Sega Net and downloaded a file with him.
Downloaded a file.
So I can play the Super Sonic level and beat the game.
Yeah, I totally get why people don't like big
because they gate the ending of the game behind this character
that has a completely different play style.
I mean, I'll still go up to that, say, Sonic's like levels were fine.
Tails levels in the first game were basically just Sonic levels.
So they're fine, although I understand if you don't think they're that great
because they're not that new.
Knuckles levels, if you're not into it, that's fine.
But I think in the first game, especially because the levels were smaller,
his radar wasn't fucking busted so you could actually detect all three at once.
So they weren't too bad.
The Amy, Amy, I'm of two minds about the Amy stages aren't that bad themselves.
Although the gimmick of the robot chasing you I used to hate.
Well, now that I'm older, I realize he poses no threat whatsoever.
You can just knock him down.
He's he's a complete joke.
But yeah, Amy's main problem is that she's so slow
that just getting between her levels, which she only even has three of,
it just takes forever. She's so slow.
And you have to for some reason, they made her campaign.
So you have to walk across the entire adventure fields
for like three levels and they needed to make it feel like that's exactly right.
And it's funny, because on a fundamental level,
I kind of like her movement mechanics.
I like that when you reach top speed, you can do that hammer bounce,
which actually goes really high up and it's kind of fun chaining the bounces together.
But it's just there's so much tedium between the fun parts of the Amy stage.
For some reason, they're like, oh, we'll have puzzles for Amy.
But the puzzles are like, put the green box in the green thing,
put the orange box in order.
It's not even it barely even counts as a fucking puzzle.
You know, I just think instead of like having these this entire dedicated
campaign to Amy that was like half baked, they should have just like done
more speed levels that were the same kind of structure as like a sonic level.
But they're like, OK, Amy has this hammer mechanic.
Let's try and integrate that into the core gameplay loop.
So they had it was more iterative instead of like, let's like
remake everything from the ground up six times with very shout out.
Yeah, I got angry as a kid, because I was like, I wanted to take Amy
into all the sonic levels and then take Tails and Emerald Coast.
And you actually could like glitch.
Which is why Sonic Sonic and Knuckles was so fucking sick.
Because that's what you could do.
It's like, you want to.
Yeah, you want to play all of Sonic 2 with Knuckles.
Here you go. Like have at it.
I can't tell you how cool I thought that was as a kid.
You know what I mean? Because, you know, Mario Mario always had
better fundamentals and but Sonic always had like the craziest shit.
You know, when it was always trying to throw a million ideas into the blender
and just like so cool to like play a game that I had already like been pretty
knowledgeable of and like, oh, but now you can like climb up surfaces.
It's like, how does that change it?
How can I do things differently?
It was like, bro, breathe new light into that entire game.
It's like super fucking cool.
Yeah, on paper, Knuckles doesn't even seem like he's that different.
He has an ever so slightly less high jump than Sonic, which makes some parts
a little hard, but he completely can compensate for that by having his
gliding and climbing, which is just, you know, all you need.
And it was fun.
Yeah, he was a great character just to explore, because back in Sonic 2,
it was the first game with Tails as a playable character,
but he was only a reskin of Sonic.
He didn't have the ability to fly.
So Knuckles was like, it was it was really fun to just explore this.
They even put new hidden one up monitors that only Knuckles could reach
because, you know, they wanted to reward you for looking at.
And it was just such an interesting piece of like technology
that they would bother like, because it's funny, because like there's
you could easily make an argument that Sonic 3 and Sonic Knuckles is bad
business consumer practices, because they're basically making you buy two
games to pay to play the finished one game.
You know what I mean?
But, you know, it didn't feel that way as a kid, because I felt like I was
going to play two games combined into one and had this crazy substantial
by itself. Yeah.
And they didn't go and didn't tell everyone, oh, this is part one.
They just said, hey, everyone, this is Sonic 3.
And then six months later, they're like, oh, and also there's this game
called Sonic and that was originally going to be one game.
But because of development problems, they had to split it up.
Yeah, there was these development problems.
It's only three had a strange development.
And there's also like, like they had a promotional deal with McDonald's
when they're like obligated to get a game out in this certain time period.
Wasn't Knuckles originally going to be a Nike thing?
Yeah, I've heard that for so long.
I heard that I thought it was a complete like meme or joke that his
his little white chest thing was going to be like a Nike swoosh.
But that was apparently actually really in like talks.
And that was really going to happen.
But it didn't happen.
They left the thing on his neck.
Yeah, it was supposed to be a Nike.
Yeah, there was going to be a little Nike thing.
I mean, I yeah, for Knuckles, I don't know why it's so it's so strange.
Yeah, I don't know.
I do not know the full details as I have to do some more research.
But for a long time, I was like, no, that's not true.
That can't be true.
I don't even know if it is the heard rumors.
I don't know.
I I don't know the full details.
I would I still wouldn't be surprised if a part of it wasn't true.
But like, I kept here.
It's such a strange thing.
But it's so sonic at the same time.
Like, yeah, exactly.
I mean, I could I could absolutely believe that, dude.
It's so strange.
They literally got Michael Jackson to come make a music for Sonic 3.
Like, why would you do that?
Like they had in-house people who'd made great music.
But they I don't know, I'm not complaining.
He's uncredited.
Like it was something that like had to like be slowly.
Yeah, it was bizarre.
It was uncredited, but it was like there were so many signs.
And it wasn't just like Michael was the one guy.
He just like team of people.
And there was this dude called Brad Buxer who also contributed
with some song from like a band he had that was unreleased.
It's just a strange thing.
And yeah, it's well documented now.
I don't really feel like I need to make a whole video talking about it.
But yeah, just search like Michael Jackson, the Sonic 3.
And it's just a whole thing where like like the the the the Sonic 3,
when you play it just by itself, when you only play it,
not put into Sonic 3 and Knuckles, it has its own unique ending
like credits theme that's like exactly the same.
Like note progression is Stranger in Moscow by Michael Jackson.
So fucking cool.
So fucking weird, man.
Sonic's wild.
It really is one of the strangest media franchises out there, I got to say.
Yeah, sounds about right.
So so anyway, what you guys what you guys been up to?
How's your how's your week been?
I'm sorry, I can't I have so little I have so little to contribute
to a Sonic the Hedgehog discussion, but I appreciate it.
And you just got to start playing all the games.
I got to go back and get a dream cast.
You know, it's funny.
I always thought like I really liked those PCP lecture things.
And I always would watch them and be like, there is no way I could like
give a lecture on anything because it's just I mean, I'm very reliant
on my scripted content and being able to ruminate over what I'm going to say.
I mean, you just talked about Sonic for like 45 minutes.
Right. Well, yeah, I was going to say, I was just I was just I actually
probably now that I'm really thinking about now that I'm just like ranting
about like these random things, like they just connected to each other.
I probably could do it, although, yes, it would be very helpful to have
like a list of notes and like a blackboard or whatever.
I think we all have.
Yeah, you have notes.
You know, my notes are just like bullet points that are like, you know,
an ordered list of like things that I want to make sure that I touch on.
And, you know, all I do is just like, I'll just look at the next one and be like,
oh, yeah, that thing. So here's how it happens.
Here's how it connects to the last thing.
Talk about it for a bit.
When I'm done, I look at the next one.
Oh, yeah. OK. And then after that, this thing happens.
Just just just fill in the gaps between.
Yeah, as long as you got a rough outline, I can totally see that.
The only thing I would have as an issue with giving
Electron Sonic is like, where the fuck do you begin and like end?
You know what I mean?
Like, if it was the entire history of everything, I'd be there for like 48 hours,
you know, to give yourself some sort of like guiding principle.
That's why, like, yeah, like Tails gets trolled or so I see
or Kokoro wish that it's like a nice, finite amount.
I wish that my son should let you were longer.
It's not even two hours. It's nothing.
That one could. Yeah, you're right.
That actually one could the God.
Well, I mean, for God's sake, you could be talking about Christian for
Electron that for that would.
I mean, there's like a video series on YouTube that's like 40 parts now.
It's like each is like, yeah, and it's just going over every single fucking thing.
I mean, I haven't seen I ever tell you like I.
I was just I got into Christian in the weirdest thing.
This was back in like, I don't even know how long this was like years and years
and years ago, I was I was back in Virginia as a pure coincidence.
I was actually it was a super depressing time
because we were visiting my sick grandmother and it was like clear.
She was like near the end of her life.
So it was like not.
It was like sad, but like we were happy that we got to hang out with her again
one last time. So it's like weird vibes or whatever.
So then I was like in the hotel room and I was just like,
I really need to like have something else to think about right now.
And I'd heard of Sonichu before, but I didn't really like know that much about it.
Did you just do the sonichu ended up on the quickie.
And I ended up.
Yeah, pretty much I ended up on the quickie and I read the entire fucking thing
and it took me like a week.
But I read like every single fucking page on that thing.
And I felt like a goddamn like expert on it.
But that was so long ago.
And I have I have not kept up.
But some of those pages, it's fascinating, man.
The idea that one person's life can be this chronicled is just kind of terrifying.
It's just like you're just like one.
You're a little terrifying moment away from your entire history being exposed.
No, I don't think that's true.
Chris is not Chris did not have one locale moment.
We're we're not.
We're not all exactly like that.
I do get what I do get.
I get what you're saying, though, that like one mistake and you can like
have someone if people get obsessive enough, they'll dig in your online history.
And like, do you have this in this?
Our generation has this entire like paleolithic, paleolithic, like
uncovering like layers and layers of history.
You can go back and dig up someone's old my space and dig up their old fucking
deviant art. I don't even know.
An internet historian video about like that that Japanese lawyer
who got like got like trolled harder than anyone's ever been told before.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
I don't know.
Yeah, I'm actually not sure I know what you're talking about here.
I do. I do like internet historians, so I should watch that.
Oh, God, I'm going to feel stupid if I'm if I'm thinking of someone else.
But like, it was there was like a kid who was getting like cyber bullied
and he he like hired a lawyer and like this lawyer like went on 4chan
and like said that he was like an expert on like trolling law or something
and that like everyone needs to stop bullying right now or there will be
legal consequences and this guy's fuck this is like a famous case.
And I think you'd probably know his face if you saw it, but I don't remember his name.
And it's like, yeah.
And so this this these people like they took this lawyer's face like they knew
which they knew which law firm he worked for.
They knew his full name and they just like they made like this huge
harassment campaign against this lawyer and plastered his face like all over the country.
God, that's so funny that like if you're getting trolled,
the one thing you should never do is like make a big public statement going,
guys, please stop trolling.
I'm he basically said like I will sue you through the Internet.
If if, you know, this is obviously like, obviously,
he can't fucking do anything against a bunch of anonymous posters.
I love when people are claimed to be experts on troll law.
You know, yeah.
And like, you know, the fact that he's there, the fact that he's doing that
just proves that he has no fucking clue, right?
But he's there to he's there to claim he's an expert and to try to intimidate these people.
I'm so embarrassed.
I can't I don't remember.
I can't find the video and I'm not sure if it's in an historian and I don't remember his name.
But I swear in the comments to tell me who this person is, because I know I'm sure this is what
this guy hopes everybody is like.
They can't remember his name.
They don't know where they saw him.
Finally, I'm doing him a big nightmare is over.
The guy just like still is a lawyer.
He still works at his fucking law firm, even though he's like the most trolled man in the world.
Punished Japanese lawyer, man.
Yeah.
I found Chris. I found Chris in college.
I think I don't know.
I would spend a lot of time.
I would spend a lot of time on other kin forums.
I would like I would hang out on other kin forums and just like get mad and see
over like how stupid and like try and troll them
and stuff. And I think through my other controlling activities,
I I somehow stumbled across probably
something awful threat or something about Chris Chan.
And that's probably how I found him or him at the time.
I just found him randomly and I felt bad and I never dug into it any further
until your lecture.
So just like this.
This seems like a sad human that deserves my pity.
No, I can't believe how long he's thriving.
She loves it.
She I don't know if you guys see, but Chris's latest tweet.
Chris's latest tweet has been up for days and it is addressed to me.
Do you are you?
Oh, yeah, I did. I did see that.
Actually, I got to admit, I'm not 100 percent up to date on all the lore,
although I was vaguely aware that you were engaging in some sort of slime war to
it's also ugly.
And it's also ugly. Follow me on Twitter, by the way,
from Chris Chan, Sonichu of the Alpha Timeline.
Your slime and punishment ended long ago.
Our Quickville and Arizona have made amends.
Our mutual grievances remain with you and your motley crew.
Even Phantom Horn himself has a horn to pick with you.
See you.
Oh, my God.
That's pretty much no shame about Phantom Horn.
Phantom Horn is my buddy.
She she must be talking about the other Phantom Horn that she gave the Blue
Podron and gave the Ghost Horn.
That Phantom Horn is fucked up. I hate that guy.
Get like CWC lecture three or four where you enter the narrative
and you have to do a lecture on yourself.
This that'll be fun.
I this makes me very happy because like I had I had had a little
Twitter interaction with her fairly recently and it was about it was about
slime and punishment and stuff.
And she was like, oh, no, that's the Omega Timeline.
That's not the Alpha Timeline.
This is the Beta Timeline.
This is a different universe.
No, I stopped time and I ran away and it didn't happen.
And and and I was like, no, wrong.
And then there was like silence.
I didn't hear from her for days.
And I thought, oh, no, I think maybe she just finds this annoying and is going
to just pretend to just ignore it and leave it be and like go off and do
something else with her time, which would probably which would be the right move.
But I'm afraid she's going to do the right thing and ignore me and go off
and do something else and think about something else.
But no, days later, she comes back with this proclamation.
And I'm like, yes, I'm in there.
I'm in that head rent free.
I'm going to get her to make an entire issue about about Fandom Horn.
And that's what it's going to be.
This is this is the first step.
This is the goal of the pages of Sonichu themselves.
The long game.
Just wanted to come.
I got to say, it's pretty based.
Yes, exactly.
To be influencing the entire universe and then tell.
So I saw at one point that Christine was giving you like five dollars on
Patreon, which made everyone on the Kiwi Farm, Steve anger.
She did. She she subscribed because she wanted.
I told her no, you can't give money to Ben Sainte.
He's not allowed to be making history.
No, she she wanted to see the the pages that I hadn't released before
the the the semi finale.
And I was like, well, I'll release them soon.
But like they're up on my Patreon until I'm ready to make them public.
And she just went and pledged.
I think she's still pledged, actually, which is I don't know why.
But the pretty fucking based, I got to say, you know, I really,
really liked that part of this on a two lecture where you were just like, oh,
yeah, I also commissioned official canon art of what happened to liquid.
I have that in my room.
I haven't hanging over my bed right now.
Right in the corner. I can see it.
I got them.
I don't know if you I suppose you you might not have seen.
You probably wouldn't have.
But yeah, during making this, making the the comic that I'm
doing, the slime and punishment, Chris has made Chris made a bunch of
like response images.
She drew a bunch of like art trying to like influence the story.
And I have I should really get around to editing it soon.
But I have Chris Chan 102, you know, it's in the editing bay.
It's going to come out one of these days.
And you know, I show a bunch of those in there.
And so I didn't even have to commission that.
She just did it because, you know, she couldn't help herself.
She was so offended by the events taking place in New
Los Angeles City, AKA Neo Milwaukee, that she had to set the.
That's a 9000 IQ play where you don't even commission things.
You just be so interesting that you get free fan art.
Oh, boy, those are those are.
Oh, yeah. And she put them on cards.
She put them on cards.
Do you do you know what Twilight Sparkle's secret shipfic folder is?
You probably don't.
I do not know that fan made card game about my little pony.
Brony's made it up.
I don't exactly know how it works.
I've never actually played it.
But she made an expansion pack based on my characters.
And she sent me a copy of the cards for this game that I don't know how to play.
But I have these. That's so funny that she would just do that completely
like unsolicited for like, well, she tried to get me to pay her
for it, like, because I love that.
It's like, please pay me for this.
Oh, whatever. You can just.
I think she she tried to get me to pay her, I think, for the right to use
Nightstar or yeah, and Christian's use of user characters or whatever.
But she gave that up very quickly.
Uh, I don't know.
It it, you know, I wonder this this this makes me think about
Tails gets trolled and publishing it physically.
And I don't know. I think.
Like, I don't think I think I think he could do it.
I think he could publish physical books if he wanted to.
Like, I don't think Nintendo would do anything.
I don't think Sega would do anything.
Sega is like very hands off in that way.
It's so out there, like, yeah, I like it almost seems like it would be worse
move for like Nintendo to even bother trying to comment on it.
You know, like, I feel like even though they're so out of touch,
just a bunch of old geriatric Japanese men that don't understand anything,
they're finally wrapping their head around the like stri-sand effect,
like stop giving attention to these like fan projects.
Like when you shut them down, you're like giving them and making everyone
love them and want to support them. I don't know.
But Tails gets trolled.
It's like it's like Tails is in the title.
I don't know. Hopefully that wouldn't be an issue.
I don't think it would be an issue.
Tails. I don't know.
I really don't know that much about Tails.
How much how much do you think he could reasonably make by selling
Tails gets trolled?
Like, I'm thinking he could make on the order of maybe tens of thousands of dollars
at like sounds about right. Yeah.
I'm not sure. I don't know.
I'm very not sure.
Like, I don't know if that's enough
that that's Sega who's like would find it worth getting their nose dirty.
You're sure it's true.
Like, there's plenty of people that like publish fanzines
and like they just do on a smaller scale that just it's just absolutely
not worth interfering with.
And like, you're right, unless Tails gets trolled,
it gets like giga popular to the point where it's in the shown in jump listings.
It's probably not going to be such an issue where they have a problem with it.
Tails gets trolled is known.
It's known by a lot of people, but like it's very niche.
And how many people are like, how many people are interested enough
that they would like commit money to purchasing a copy?
Me, you, you guys and, you know, a very small slice of the reading population.
And like, Nintendo seems to be much more interested in like, you know,
taking action and issuing C&Ds for video games, because that's their bread and butter.
They don't seem to be as active as taking down like other media,
probably because it's not like people won't confuse it with their brand, I guess.
Maybe that's true. Yeah.
Webcomics and whatnot have got to be like insanely low down
on their list of things to worry about.
You know, did you say in your video that he was thinking of like
replacing the copyrighted characters with original characters or something like that?
Yeah. OK, so when he had like canceled it, he was like,
oh, maybe we'll continue the story, but like in a text based form.
But then he had the idea he was going to split it in half.
And there was going to be the comedy series with the with the copyrighted
characters called the Troll Slayers, but he was going to split all the drama
and serious story stuff into a separate issue that replaces all the characters
with like original characters called Teyel's realm.
Teyel's realm.
I had not heard it.
Yeah, this blew my fucking mind.
Teyel's realm, this blew my mind hearing that in your on your video,
because like I'd never heard this before.
And it's it's insane.
It's total insanity.
It's it's insane.
Like, OK, that was the funniest part to me.
Like, like he gets tailed, gets trolled, polished,
and that's not even the worst idea.
Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, luckily, that one never actually like made it out of the planning phase,
luckily, at least as far as I know.
Somebody sent me somebody sent me a Facebook message.
It was I think it was either.
Oh, man, I have to fucking log in to Facebook.
Oh, my God.
That is the worst thing ever.
It is.
I deleted my Facebook out of anger.
I just sort of I just forget about it in like nine ninety nine percent of the time.
But I think I still have one, but I haven't used it in like over a decade.
I deleted it so I could epically
poned Mark Zuckerberg, but it doesn't even matter,
because if you don't have a Facebook profile,
that it just constructs a shadow profile of you based on information
that gathers from your friends.
Yeah, really?
Yeah. What?
Yeah.
And based on other sites you visit on the Internet,
it's a shadow a shadow clone, because like Facebook has the
has trackers and like embedded in other websites,
because that's like how businesses can like
track like your purchasing habits and stuff.
Yeah. So they can just construct a profile for you.
Even if you don't have a profile, they know a lot about you.
I guess that's a better way of saying it than a shadow profile.
It does sound cooler, though.
Well, that blows.
I got to say, I'm not the biggest fan.
Yep. There's no escaping the panopticon.
We live in the state of total global surveillance,
and it's never going to get any better.
Hey, man, don't be such a downer about it.
All right.
It's shadow profile, more like shadow, the hedgehog.
Yeah.
Hey, yeah, video games.
Exactly.
That's why I think we need to elect
Laserbot as president of the United States in 2020.
We should write a name.
Do you know Ace Watkins?
Ace, Ace, Ace Watkins.
I know that name.
Yeah, the first gamer president.
Yes, I know that Twitter account.
Yes, very funny.
I wouldn't happily vote for the first gamer president.
He's a he's a real quote factory.
OK, now I got a message.
Oh, yeah. No, Laserbot sent me.
Laserbot sent me a Facebook message on September 11th.
This is this was 16 days ago.
And I didn't answer.
Fuck, he just asked me how's everything been.
And I don't know why I don't know what he wanted.
Oh, that's weird.
Because he had to talk to me in like in like two years.
OK, well, I'll have to like carefully consider
how I want to respond to that.
That's I just I just remember that right now.
I've just finished doing a podcast
where I talked about your work for like two hours.
Man, how you do it?
It was it was I think it maybe.
Oh, maybe he wants to come on a podcast.
I feel like that's why because that was that was the initial idea.
That's what we that's what we talked about.
That is really funny timing, I got to say,
because it's like right before I ended up posting that video about it.
Yeah, that's what we talked about on Facebook,
was whether he wanted to come on the podcast
and he wouldn't do it because he didn't have a microphone.
And I'm like, well, there's always some sort of technical issue
when you want to organize something with Laserbot.
Unfortunately, I would I would buy him a microphone
if that's what I said, like you want for like thirty five dollars
and it would be fine.
But it's like my internet doesn't work very well.
Just say you don't want to do it, you coward.
But well, I mean, he's reaching out.
So maybe he does.
I'm hoping the tides of time
because maybe maybe he said would be incredible.
Maybe he's got something he wants to promote.
I'm not going to try and pretend
like I could take any sort of credit for this.
But hopefully my video contributes to a somewhat resurgence
in popularity for Tails gets trolled.
I would be happy for him to get back in the spotlight more.
I mean, he's going to be working on it again.
You guys are both going to draw new pages to the to the legacy of Tales of Trolls.
I hope so.
Like I say, at the end of the video, I really genuinely there is nothing
I want to see more than for Tails gets told to actually finish in my lifetime.
I would love to see that story finished.
You know what I mean?
Just sort of those like stories you have in the back of your head.
It's going to be sitting there in my head for the rest of my life,
even if it finishes.
I just I can't imagine what we've seen so far being only a quarter of it.
Like where the fuck would it go for the rest of its runtime?
I do briefly mention this like in the video.
But like one of my favorite things is like every time you finally like
really sort of like get it, like you sort of get a grasp on it.
Like you sort of get the Troll Slayer situation.
Like, OK, I get Tails gets trolled.
It completely changes it up with like the new Trolls or just introducing
something or like the whole party at Cheeto Man's house and like the mass grave
and shit like that's like a big fuck.
Yes, exactly.
Like every time once you finally get used to the defenders and you're like, OK,
I finally am used to this insane convoluted all this bullshit.
There's no you don't even understand.
There's this conspiracy with the Cheeto Man.
And it is so fucking funny.
He has to I can't even think about that laughing.
Knuckles' plan is to bring over a bunch of hoes who have STDs with God Maria.
So he has to kill them all.
Even though God Maria can be cured in a couple of weeks with Amy Pay likes.
It's so funny.
It's like the funny thing.
It's like Cheeto Man's one way to make a fucking video.
Boy, it sure would ruin my criminal empire.
If someone were to present me a hoe with an STD that I would have sex with,
like that it's a laser.
Bond has led the greatest mind of our generation.
I just want to see what else it can come up with.
It's priceless.
Yeah, it's priceless.
So I've been watching movies lately.
I watched a lot of movies this week.
It's very weird for me because I never watch movies.
I hate all media.
I go through phases where I'm like a movie guy and I'm going to be the coolest guy
who listens to fucking directors, commentary and shit.
And then I'm like, fuck movies, movies suck.
They're all a bunch of Hollywood bullshit.
I was I've been feeling that way for a long time.
And then I I won't belabor this because I've talked about it before.
But I made a tweet asking for recommendations of people about movies
where people just talk, just people talking, nothing happened.
I don't want me.
When you watch my dinner with Andre, I have seen that before.
Yeah. So that I didn't I didn't watch that one.
But I watched like no, I watched an insane amount of movies this week.
I watched like a dozen movies.
That's more than I've watched in like the decade up till now or the previous decade.
I don't think I've watched a dozen movies this year yet.
Yeah, no, I watched Sonic.
I just probably some more.
I just got on one day where I was like bored
and I guess I was procrastinating from doing like sending off books
and doing the like signatures and stuff.
And I was just I just was downloading one movie after another,
just going down the list like, yeah, I'll get that one.
Tarned it. OK, watch it an hour and a half later.
All right, cool.
Um, it feels good to get into a movie zone.
And I know that feeling where you're like banging on movies.
It's like when you watch a movie,
it almost feels like you just finished a whole show, you know what I mean?
Think about a movie.
A movie feels like a big commitment, but it's really not like.
It's so it's so funny.
I have the exact same thing where it's like, I'm like, I can't.
I don't have time to sit down and watch a two hour movie.
I might as well just sit down and watch eight half hour episodes
of some fucking show I don't even give a shit about.
And then I regret my time watching.
But I watched I watched like eight movies in one day
and I felt like I'd accomplished something.
It didn't feel like I'd wasted my time.
It felt like I'd been on a journey.
Right. Well, movies.
I know what you mean.
It's very satisfying.
You feel like you've.
There is something super satisfying about a good movie
that you can't get from like pretty much anything else or like if you binge
like a TV show, like usually if you binge a season of a TV show,
it's not the full story, so it doesn't feel like something's wrapped.
Even if it has, you're like you've wasted your entire day.
And if you kind of like feel almost sick of watching TV
by the time you're done binging a season of a TV show, you're just like,
fuck, and me.
But the movie is like long enough.
It's like designed psychologically to be long enough
to like keep the average person engaged without almost like they did it that way
on purpose. It's like almost like this was like intentional.
It actually it is really funny to think movies can be any length.
The movie can be any length, but they're all pretty much the exact same length.
Well, they're getting longer.
That's the best. They're getting longer and longer.
They'd get. OK, true.
They are getting much longer than they used to be.
So and, you know, that's probably what I just said is getting less true
as time goes on. But yeah, it is funny that it's like we're programmed to just
have this two hours. It's like the perfect amount of time.
It feels totally substantial, but also it is not nearly like it doesn't waste
it doesn't waste your whole day.
Let me just, you know, fuck it.
I'm just going to go down.
I'm just going to go down a list of movies I watched this week.
There's a whole bunch.
I watched Ghost World based on the comic by Daniel Clouse.
Either you're familiar.
No, that's a good I've never seen it before.
Yeah, it was a good movie. It was pretty sweet.
What's your name? Really hot in that movie.
It's really fucking hot.
I don't remember the actress's name.
It's the same actress that plays is the girl in
American Beauty.
Oh, yeah, Thorough Birch.
Thorough Birch.
I'm pretty sure it's her name.
Yeah. Yeah.
Wait, TV shows, walking Thorough Birch, American actress.
I got to make sure I got to make sure.
Filmography.
She was in Dungeons and Dragons, the movie legend.
She was in Dark Corners.
She was in The Atruscan Smile.
Oh, yeah, she was in.
Yeah, she was in it. Yeah, in it.
So fucking hot. I can't stand it.
Ghost World is like definitely a movie that I was like.
I didn't watch for a long time because I don't want to watch a movie about a world of ghosts.
But it's about but it's about teenagers.
Yeah, I don't know why it's called that.
I haven't read the comic.
It's based on either.
I've seen it, though.
When I I got the movie and I found out, like, as it was
as the credits were rolling, it was based on the comic.
I was like, wait, I mean, I've heard of that.
And I looked it up and like, I was like, oh, yeah, Daniel Clouse.
I know who that is.
I watched Cat on a Hot Tin Roof.
It's really good.
It's a really good movie about some drunk asshole.
Getting mad at his rich dad, who's got cancer.
And they hash it out in the basement.
They yell at each other.
Their shitty relatives are shitty.
They bond a little bit.
The wife is talking, talking movies that are the primary
like problem is just like family and type just problems
where people have to talk.
There's going to be really interesting if you have like a well,
well, it's like a plot.
Those are like what basically what plays had to be.
Yeah, I think I think a bunch of them are just based on
chamber chamber plays, right?
Like there's there was one next one on my list.
Carnage is just four people, two or two parents of one kid,
two parents of another kid talking in a room, talking in their apartment
about how one kid like beat up the other kid and broke his tooth.
And they get really mad at each other.
And that's what Carnage is about.
Carnage is a little bit.
If I have not seen Carnage, but I think this was also a play, I believe, right?
I think I don't see it.
I don't know, but I feel very confident.
I just saw a video of James Gandolfini, I think, in a little role for this play.
Because yeah, I like the idea of a movie that's just like
like a big conversation between people, you know, you know, I like my dinner with
Andre, my dinner with Andre is good.
Carnage stars John C.
Riley, so that's pretty cool.
I watched going down my list here, The Man from Earth, which made,
which I found out afterwards, made YMS's best movies of 2007 lists, right?
So very prestigious, hated it, hated it completely, thought it was so annoying.
I I never watched this movie, but I went and I read the Wikipedia page
and I saw the plot twist and I cringed and I thought it was right.
OK, OK, it's not just me.
The plot twist was pretty cringe.
For my first I was so obnoxious and the way that the guy is Tom,
do you know this movie? I've never heard of it, but I'll probably never watch it.
OK, the plot of the movie is this guy is a professor and he's like moving away
and his colleagues are like throwing him a going away party.
And as he's going away party, he decides to admit to them, hey, guys,
I have a secret, I wasn't going to tell you.
But what would you think if I told you that I'm like 50,000 years old?
Like, I'm like a fucking caveman who has survived to the modern era.
And they're like, what?
And they talk to him about they try to like tease it out of him.
Like, is he telling the truth? Is he lying?
Like, can we can we even determine whether this is true or not based on what he says?
It's like, OK, well, he's telling us about history,
but he could have known this just by researching it.
So there's no way to know for sure.
And, you know, it goes on and goes on.
It's it is it is the case that, yeah, he really is this magical,
ever-living caveman or whatever. It's fine.
Halfway through the movie, he's like, he gets like, oh, I didn't want to talk about this.
I don't want to talk about this, but I guess I technically was Jesus.
So I'm sorry about that.
And I'm like, no, no.
Fuck this movie.
This movie is shit.
That's like, it's just it's like a ton of what?
No, it's like a Neil Breen twist, you know?
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, he's he's like, yeah, you know, I preached, I preached peace in Judea.
You know, I didn't tell I didn't want people to fight each other.
I didn't want the Crusades or anything.
I just took the Buddha's teachings that I learned in India.
And I brought them to I brought them to Greece.
And they but they perverted them.
It's like, fuck you. That's fuck it.
What's a note when it it annoys me that, like,
it I feel like I feel like I could have written this movie myself.
I feel like I could have, like, given the premise of a guy
who's been alive for 50,000 years, I could have, like, put all the words in his mouth.
It's so obvious.
Like, it's such an obvious twist, but it's like so obvious
that you don't think they're going to do it because it's not obvious.
I didn't think they were going to do it.
It was too bold and reductionist as well.
To be like, oh, we're going to, like,
reduce the complexity of human history down to the actions of one person.
And it's like so pathetic.
Yeah, I'm not the kind of person who gets offended, but like, that is offensive.
Like, I could see that being offensive to people.
You know what I mean? I mean, it's not. I'm not a.
Yeah, again, it doesn't offend me. I don't really give a shit.
I was offended not because it was like it offended my religious sensibilities,
but because I'm like, it offended my suspension of disbelief.
Yeah, yeah.
So I didn't like that one, that the idea that like Jesus
could go on to just be some boring douchebag who works at a college is kind of hilarious.
Well, I mean, yeah, I mean, he says, like, you know, I was just a normal guy.
They made up all those stories about me later or whatever.
OK, fine. I'm just a normal guy who lived for 50,000 years, you know.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
But other than that, perfectly reasonable.
I watched never thought about trying to share your secret of ever
lasting after lasting life with us.
You know, you never wanted to go get experimented on by the US government,
like any good patriot.
What if he doesn't?
He doesn't want to get cut up in a lab, which, you know, I don't get it.
I don't get that. Fuck him.
OK, I watched what's the next one on my list here.
Friday, a comedy starring Chris Tucker and Ice Cube about getting high
and robbing your neighbors and
and and being in debt to a drug dealer who shows up with a car full of machine
guns to gun you and your best friend down over two hundred dollars.
And at the end, it's revealed that Ice Cube was Jesus Christ and the whole movie.
Ice Cube and the whole movie.
Ice Cube is like, damn, my girlfriend, shit.
And Chris Tucker is like, why don't you fuck this other girl?
And he's like, yeah, I guess I will.
And at the end of the movie, they get together and it's it's a happy ending.
That's the best conflict in a movie.
Damn, my girlfriend, my girlfriend just sucks so bad.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry you're going through this, Ice Cube.
It was it was fairly entertaining.
Next one on the list is called I'm Thinking of Ending Things.
Very creepy movie.
I have been that's on my two watches.
The Charlie Kaufman movie, right?
It is. Yeah, it's like just came out.
New Charlie Kaufman.
Yeah, it just came out. It's on my list.
I love Charlie Kaufman.
I love adaptations of my favorite movies of all time.
I saw being John Milkovich when I was way too young to understand
what the fuck any of the like symbolism or any of it meant.
I was just like, what the fuck?
This is the weirdest movie I've ever seen in my life.
I watched it when I was like in like when I was like 14.
And I probably didn't get it.
Did Charlie Kaufman make Synecdoche New York?
Yeah, that was his directorial debut.
Yeah, I really love Synecdoche New York.
Yeah, I love anything that's just like a massive rumination on dying.
Yeah, we're just going to suck to be dead.
That's just my inner monologue.
It's the last thing I need is more of that.
I'm thinking of ending things is a little bit of that, not entirely.
It's I won't say too much about it, but it's very it's OK.
I don't need to hold another movie that's making me want to die.
Very it's very unsettling.
Um, I will definitely watch that.
I watched a trilogy of movies called the before trilogy
before sun before sunrise before.
Oh, I know this movie.
I was sorry. Again, this is another one.
I have a problem where I just read about movies on Wikipedia.
Then I'm like, oh, I don't need to see this.
Now I read about it on Wikipedia.
That's exactly the same as seeing a movie.
But no, no, I haven't spoiled it or anything.
I'm just aware that this is like a trilogy of movies
based on like a relationship and like at different stages in these couples.
These movies are really good.
The before series is really good.
Yeah, in before sunset, in before sunrise, these they meet on a train
and then they spend the day like they like, oh, let's let's go see Vienna.
And then they spend the day walking around Vienna
and then the other movies are future.
It's sort of a spoiler to even say like what the circumstances of them are
because before before sunrise ends on a cliffhanger
where you don't know if they'll get together again.
So I guess spoiler, like they do, in fact, meet again.
But it would be spoiling too much to say how.
So but yeah, and it's like just and yeah,
the whole movies are just them like talking to each other, talking to other people,
going on nice dates and it's very cute.
It's cute. I like it a lot.
Yeah, I've heard good things about it.
And I'm definitely at the stage of my life where I can handle a movie
that's just people talking now.
I think when I first heard of those movies, I was like, you know, younger.
And I was like, if there's nobody getting killed, then it's not a real movie.
No, I'm I'm ready.
I'm ready for nothing.
I'm ready for movies where things don't happen.
The less that things happen, the better.
Yeah, I've become I've become so jaded and cynical and such a contrarian
that any time things are just different than like the mainstream.
Like just the idea of a movie that's just people talking is inherently
like interesting to me.
Whereas I'm sure lots of mainstream audiences would be like, no,
I'm not going to watch a movie that's just a surprising number of movies like this.
I feel like they're sort of out not the norm.
But and yet it makes sense.
Yeah, there's an audience and it makes sense.
And just it's like it gets an easy not easy that it's easy to make a good
movie that's people talking because you have to have a good conversation.
But production wise, you don't need any special effects
or you don't need any costumes or whatever.
You just need a house and a couple of actors and a script.
If I was going to make a movie, I would love to make a movie
that's my first movie is just people talking movie rather than trying to start
off with something like Space Cop where I completely fall on my face.
I got I got two more.
I got I watched Locke.
Have you heard of Locke?
I don't think I have or if I have, I can't remember.
So fucking sick.
Locke is a movie.
The entire movie takes place in a guy's car as he talks on the phone.
That's the whole fucking movie.
And it's so good.
It's really tense.
He's like he's on the phone trying to he's got like a big fucking
like business project that is like on the verge of falling through.
And he's got to talk his assistant through making sure it doesn't go to shit.
He's got his marriages falling apart while he's like on the phone talking to his wife.
He's like having a baby is being born and he's like trying to talk the mother
through as she's like getting ready, just getting prepped for childbirth.
It's very good.
I thought Locke.
Oh, this is an interesting movie.
I just Googled it yet.
Tom Harvey.
OK, this looks interesting.
Yeah, just him talking on the phone in his car.
Really good.
Last one was dirt.
Fuck. Wait, where was it?
Wait, where? Oh, OK.
This is the weirdest fucking movie I've ever seen.
Death by Hanging is a Japanese movie.
I thought it was going to be like an anti death penalty like propaganda movie.
And I guess maybe a little bit it is.
But the plot of it is that they hang this kid, this guy, who is a rapist.
He is a rapist and murderer.
They hang him, but he doesn't die.
And they're like shit.
They like wake him up.
He's like he's like catatonic.
He doesn't know who he is.
He doesn't know what's going on.
And they're like, well, he's he's mentally incapacitated.
We can't execute him if he's mentally incapacitated.
That's against the law.
So we got to remind him of who he is.
So he remembers everything and admits to being who he is
so that we can execute him again and make it work this time.
So it's these like military officials acting out his crimes,
like his rapes, like pretending to rape each other.
And like, look, this is what you did.
This is what you did to those girls.
And he's just like, what?
And then like they act out his whole family life.
They like they all like start playing the role of like his dad
and his brothers and his mom and stuff and like trying to get him to remember who he is.
And then like the ghost of his sister or something appears.
I think she's a ghost.
And she says like, yeah, my brother's a murderer or rapist,
but it's Japan's fault because we're Korean and they colonize Korea
and they destroyed our home.
And like it's the only way that my brother could justifiably spill Japanese blood
as his as he is want to do in vengeance for what you have done to our country.
And it's like, yeah, I guess that's fair.
The movie is 100 percent on the side of this murderer rapist
because Japan did bad things to Korea.
It's like it's like three fucking hours.
That is a pretty wild movie plot, I got to say.
This is this movie came out in 1968.
That is insane. It's it's the weirdest movie I've ever watched.
Easily.
It's it's way too long.
Like it takes the like most of the movie to get around to the whole thing
with the sister and like the whole like Korean identity thing.
And like, that's the point.
The point of the movie is supposed to be that like these Japanese officials
are, you know, imperialist dogs who are just enforcing, you know,
they're like violent hegemony over the people and specifically over, you know,
people from another country, Korea, which like who gives them any right to do that, right?
That's the point of the movie.
But it doesn't get there until like two thirds of the way through.
And it's most it's like mad captioning
Anagans where these like goofy military officers have to like act out, pretend rapes.
That's like half the movie.
It's so strange.
And it's so hilarious to me that they think it's even worth like,
oh, he doesn't remember who he is.
So we have to make him or like, why?
Just like, if it was America, they would have just shot him in the head.
Yeah. I mean, I mean, I guess that's like.
I mean, I'm not complaining.
I just think it's kind of funny like I get where they're coming from.
Like if you wouldn't want to, like if you made someone mentally incapacitated,
mentally disabled, you made that person mentally disabled, then you were going to execute them
as a mentally disabled. That's pretty fucked up, I got to say.
Like, I mean, I understand where they're coming from.
I don't buy that it would play out like this in real life, but it's, you know,
I understand it's a movie they're they're trying to play up some theater
of the absurd type shit. I totally get that.
But, you know, it is it is it is a very like that's such like,
how do you even have that?
Like, who came up with the idea for that for a movie?
You know what I mean? That's what I'm trying to say. That's so wild.
Yeah. No, I guess I would recommend it.
I feel a little bad to spoil it, but like, I don't know.
It's just bizarre.
It's really bizarre to me that anybody made a movie.
I don't know how much I kind of that was one of those movies.
I think I needed to hear some spoilers,
and otherwise I might have not been willing to check it out, you know,
because I like weird ass movies.
I always enjoy this a nice strange experience.
Yeah, check out this one.
I don't know. I don't know.
Maybe Japanese cinema in the late 1960s was just like this,
and I'm just not that familiar.
But it's see this one seems like pretty uniquely.
Bizarre, just in its whole conception,
just why why would it even exist?
But it does. So, you know, that's something to be celebrated.
OK, so that's it. That's my that's my that's my movies
where nothing happens round up for this week.
Yeah, I hope you guys enjoyed Ben's movie corner.
Yeah, yeah, it's a new segment.
Ellie is our put in a jingle.
Put in a jingle for Ben's movie corner.
What movie is Ben going to watch on Ben's movie corner?
Ben's movie corner.
Thank you.
This will be a segment that comes out once every four years.
When I when I get around to watching another dozen or so movies.
Next time you have a movie day.
Tom, you still awake?
I'm still over here.
You're so quiet. Am I?
You. Oh, you were.
You must have been far away from like, you're so distant, Tom.
Tom, come back. We miss you.
I just caught myself off emotionally to keep myself from getting hurt, you know.
Yeah, Tom was getting too emotionally invested in the movie plots.
Well, what do you guys think of going to voicemails?
Let's do it.
All right, here we go.
I'm going to I'm going to share screen.
Actually, wait, can you guys give me can you guys give me 30 seconds?
And then I'll come back and I'll share speed.
Counties are counting it down right now.
Ellie is our cut this part out.
Ellie is our don't cut this part out.
Let's embarrass Ben.
Yeah, I heard Ben.
He told me that he's a he actually watched movies
that didn't have people talking in them.
And they were just they were just action movies.
Oh, my God, it's funny you mentioned that
because I watched Robocop for the first time yesterday.
Oh, yeah, really? Yeah.
It's a dope ass movie.
I like these movies.
I didn't want I didn't even bother watching them for so long
because it was just like, oh, it's just like a meme right?
It's like an 80s. Well, that's culture.
Like I saw it on Family Guy, whatever I get it, I get Robocop.
That's the whole thing has some interesting stuff to it.
You know, it's interesting.
There are so many movies that are like kind of staples of culture
that I've never seen before.
And I just I just got tired of watching half in the bag
and having them reference movies that I'd never seen before.
I'm like, fuck it, I'm making a list of all these like classic movies
that like everybody knows about that I know about, but I never watched.
And I have a bunch of them downloaded
and Robocop is the first one I decided to watch.
And it was pretty cool.
It feels good to bang some of those like movies
that you've been meaning to watch for so long, like off.
There's some movies I never even thought I would watch
because I just like I don't need to watch this movie.
I just got it all through cultural.
I remember friends worth watching.
I remember friends in like second grade
who were fans of Robocop who watched Robocop and like
I was just too busy watching like Japanese bootleg Godzilla movies
to like watch popular movies at the time, I guess.
And so there's like this huge gap in my cultural knowledge.
I was like weirdly dismissive of Robocop because I just was like, OK,
it's fucking copies of Robocop.
What's the big fucking deal?
I've seen way cooler shit than that.
But it actually is a lot.
There's a lot more to it than that.
This whole time I can't believe you were going to let me do my whole movie
round up and not mention that you watched Robocop for the first time.
Yeah, well, I was going to I was going to wait
until you were done with your movie stuff,
but it took longer than I thought.
So I was like, I have the moments past, but then you left.
And I was like, all right, here's a window to bring it out.
The moment returned.
I probably was I respect the overall
slow of the podcast more than getting in my personal points.
I think I don't feel if I've ever actually watched Robocop all the way through.
I feel like I saw like some of it as a kid, maybe.
And yeah, red, red letter media talk about it a whole bunch.
Got a lot.
I think that I'm going to watch one every Friday.
I'm going to watch Blade Runner next.
I think I've never seen Blade Runner either.
I enjoy I like Blade Runner.
It's one of those movies where I mean, I'm not going to spoil anything,
but like I definitely get where the people who watch it and they're like,
what's the big fucking deal?
Like if you're expecting some sort of super epic, bombastic thing,
it's a little slower, a little more contemplative is all I'll say.
I'm I'm totally fine with that.
So that's why I think I'll probably I'll probably enjoy it.
But even if I don't enjoy it, just don't watch the director's cut,
which don't watch everyone.
Everyone's been telling me.
My understanding was to watch the director.
Wait, which one's the one with the narration?
There's like five different cuts as all.
There's the director's cut.
There's the final cut.
There's the theatrical cut.
There's like different versions.
I believe the totally the not there's definitely legal download
I got was for the final cut.
I think that's OK.
It I there might be something you don't my understanding is that's fine.
The theatrical cut leaves a lot of things out that.
Make sure the only thing I say is don't watch the original theatrical cuts.
That's the only one I would say.
Pretty sure everything else is fine.
So there's a Wikipedia page that's just going over the differences
in the versions of Blade Runner, which is pretty awesome.
Yeah, I was looking at an article that like broke down the differences,
but it was an article written from the perspective of having already seen the movie.
So I didn't read it.
Yeah, it's actually kind of hard to explain the differences
without getting in a spoiler.
So that's why I'm like trying to not really get into it.
I'm just going to watch the one I have.
You'll be fine. You'll you'll be fine.
You know, it's not going to like ruin it.
If you watch, I mean, plenty of people watch the theatrical version
first and end up liking it still. So who knows?
I already know a lot about the movie
through cultural osmosis, so I'm sure it won't be a big deal one way or the other.
But I just want to watch it to say that I have.
And you can watch the the sequel that came out.
Yeah, that'll be interesting.
I can't. I still can't believe they made a sequel.
I thought it was such a strange like I mean, I guess it's not even that strange.
Hollywood has been a whole fucking kick of making these sequels
twenty, thirty years after the fact.
But I don't know, it just never seemed like one that needed a sequel to me.
But hey, it wasn't that bad.
I know franchise no franchise left on milk, as Hollywood would say.
Quite literally, I mean, like we're approaching like critical
diminishing returns of like every franchise has been rebooted or going to
start rebooting the fucking reboots.
I was watching half in the bag and they were talking about like a couple of years
ago, they tried to reboot chips.
And I was like, yeah, that's ridiculous.
And they were just making fun of why you would ever reboot that.
And it's like Hollywood is just that desperate, I guess.
It's because some fucking executive in Hollywood is like, yeah, I've heard of
chips everywhere. Everybody knows chips is right.
Everybody in my age knows what chips is.
Kids will be happy to go see chips.
It was like, have you ever heard of chips?
It's like California Highway Patrol Squad or something.
I can't remember.
It's like some boomer show about being a cop on a highway.
It sucks, as far as I know.
Dude, all TV was like bad before nineteen, like ninety four.
Nineteen, I don't know.
I guess this whenever the Simpsons started coming on the air,
pretty much all TV before that was dog shit, at least American TV.
Yeah, I've never I've never watched TV in my fucking life.
You're missing out on probably, you know, you may miss some cultural things,
but I don't know. Yeah, just stick to movies, be a movie guy.
I guess I have to be a movie guy now.
I guess I have to be a chamber play guy now.
I should be Ben. Ben, what if we what if we start a spinoff podcast
that's just about talking about movies about sitting in a room?
And the podcast is like two guys sitting in a room,
talk about movies about guys sitting in a room.
That's no good, but you could make instead of the podcast.
You should make a full on movie.
That's a movie about guys talking about like my dinner.
Well, community already had a big parody episode
that was like a parody. We have to fight and kill content.
If we can get more subs than content, the podcast will be a success.
Uh, uh,
anything, I'll do anything to to undercut and destroy our our our friends.
Well, you know what they say?
Healthy competition is good.
So if you have your rival shows going at it,
you should have a rival show where it's like
you ostensibly about talking about movies.
But the entire show is nothing but just taking potshots of content.
Yeah, that's the kind of show I can get behind.
Just a flimsy excuse.
Yeah, I mean, I mean, I'll I'll I'll make I'll do a movie podcast.
I would I'm down to do a movie podcast.
You I was I got jealous of you last episode, Tom,
talking about doing your Godzilla podcast.
I'm like, why can't I have that?
You know, what I do?
What did I do?
Podcasts are high returns, low investment.
So I you can do a million of them and you just got nothing but time.
Fuck yeah.
OK, it's it's a deal.
All right, we'll hash that out.
All right, we've we figured it.
We figured something finally, finally, something happened on this podcast.
God, I'm glad the two hours of nothing of dead air led up to this moment.
We're two and a half hours in.
Oh, that reminds.
Yeah, let's let's go to voicemails.
I will share my screen.
I hope this works.
We're trying a new method today because of our guest.
If it doesn't work, I did I did download that zip file.
So it's nothing in the world.
Yeah, that would that would work.
But it's probably more convenient to just do it this way.
Yeah, probably is.
Oh, wait, look at my screen.
Your screen's like winging out and I kind of like.
Yeah, it looks like it's looking at a million different.
My I've seen I've seen this happen before.
I don't know why it happens.
But this is like this is not the first time.
I guess it doesn't matter.
It's just about the audio.
Hold on.
Voice and video.
You're your Twitter page was like frozen on like some guy
like kissing some girl on a cheek.
And now there's like all these little cursors around.
It looks like one of those like
clingy gifts from like early 2001.
No, I can see it.
Yeah, I see exactly what you're talking about.
I don't know.
I don't know who those people are.
How many of these voice ones
are going to have to listen to like this?
Oh, a whole bunch.
Don't worry.
Don't worry about it.
OK, can you can you see what I'm looking at?
No, it's still it's still still speaking out a nightmare.
All right, here we go.
First one is called seething peasants.
Stay seething, Nate heads.
Stay seething over eight weeks since his last upload.
Fucking Lamau.
This guy, the voice voicemail God is no fan of Nate Vestman.
And he he makes, you know, you know,
he uses his God given right to express that in the voicemails.
It's fair.
I'll defend to the death is right to say it.
I think Nate's lucky to have his own personal troll.
Next one, dolphin question.
What? I didn't hear it.
I don't know if that was bad audio quality.
Was that a dolphin?
Let me let me try again.
Christian Christian Christian is a real
character in Sonic Christian is a real character in Sonic something something.
Didn't they like parody him in Sonic Boom?
That's what I was thinking, sort of.
Yeah, there's like an Ardvark who kind of looks like Chris.
Yes, they made a little arms joke.
Yeah, they made a blue arms joke, too.
That's right.
It's pretty like it's it's just enough of a Chris Chan parody
where it's definitely Chris Chan, but like it was vague enough
where they could keep plausible deniability.
Yeah, it could just be any like weird fan.
Yeah, it's like I could I could see theoretically see like just it does
as spoof of the concept of weird fandom just coincidentally happens to line up
exactly for the portrayal of Chris. Yeah.
It's it seemed kind of deliberate, though.
The blue arms thing was so on point.
That wasn't a Chris Chan reference.
I would be I would be shocked.
Well, OK.
Devil's advocate here.
Nate's not here, so I got to play devil's advocate.
Oh, no.
Was was the blue arms thing something that other people were mad about
and Chris just like took it and ran with it further than anyone else?
Yeah, see, exactly.
That's just another case of like it is enough plausible deniability where
there's like I don't think you could prove in a court of law this absolutely
had to be inspired by Chris Chan.
But like I'm pretty sure by far you are the most vocal complaining.
A lot of people saw it and immediately thought that's Chris.
So yeah, I think it was a deliberate reference.
Yeah, I don't know.
I didn't write the show.
It could it could it could have been.
I think maybe yeah, we would we'd have to like ask the writers or something.
And they would probably deny it even then if you ask them publicly.
Yeah, they're going to die.
And you'd have to corner them privately.
And then then what you're going to leak your their private information
that they shared with you. So we'll just yeah.
Next one. Play this one.
OK, there was nothing in it.
It was empty. It was silent.
You just got trolled.
All right, next one.
Next one, I only get 15 seconds.
This is all your fault.
It's not my fault.
I don't expect you to play literally any of my voice mails.
But if you do, then fuck you because you fuck you failed.
These suck.
Well, he's not wrong.
Man, these voicemails have been fucking incredible this week.
Did you guys do you only like?
Do you deliberately say if you're a fan of the show, do not send a voicemail.
But if you hate the show, please send in.
No, it just kind of works out that way.
Well, Ben Ben says it in so many words
because he's made it that like he'll play every voicemail now
and has made that public knowledge.
So if you hate the show and you want to say it and have it be in the show,
you have carte blanche to do so.
We will we will platform you.
We will platform your hate speech, specifically hate speech
about how much you hate that dedication of freedom of speech.
Yeah, absolutely.
Every podcast, every section world renowned free speech defender.
Don't don't tread on me.
Next one, please don't play my voicemails.
Don't play any of mine.
Please don't play.
What? I'm stop.
I think these all might be from the same guy.
We can't tell if the voicemail sounds like shit
or if it's just that I'm listening in it through a stream from your speakers.
No, it sounds really bad to me.
It's not making it any better, though.
Yeah, yeah, we're getting like multiple levels of the shit audio.
All right, we've got another one called I only get 15 seconds.
So let's here we go.
Literally, don't play any of the voicemails
that were sent in the past four hours.
They are all mine and they're all shit, please.
You suck and your timing suck.
I only have 15 minutes. Suck you. Fuck you.
Why? Why?
He's mad at you for playing his voicemail that he sent.
He's continuing the same.
What a great bit.
This is sort of blowing my mind like I'm struggling to comprehend this.
We have to deal with this kind of stupidity every week.
This is worse than usual, I will say.
All right, next one.
After binging all the PCP episodes.
Fuck this shit.
I'm out.
I'm out of nothing.
Don't mind me.
I'm just grab my stuff and leave.
Excuse me, please.
Fuck this shit.
I'm out.
Nope. Fuck this shit.
I'm out. All right, then.
I don't know what the fuck just happened.
But I don't really care.
I don't understand the context.
He he he binged the entire podcast and now he's out.
He didn't.
He liked it enough to listen to every single episode
and send in a voicemail and presumably listen to this one to hear his voicemail.
But he's out.
What does that mean?
He's about to go by a no-nate-no-watch-see-you-next-review-share-you.
Um, uh, it, um.
I don't fuck.
I don't fucking know.
I had something I was going to say, but I didn't I didn't say it in time.
And now it's over.
The moment has passed.
Is that an original song?
That's that's like an internet thing.
There's like a I've heard that as like a as a Twitter reply song.
It's like a stick to your guy.
I don't know the origin, though.
No, I don't know.
Copyright struck on last week's episode because of what because of the clip of the dictator.
Oh, my God, really?
Yeah, yeah.
Wait, that's that's not in the public domain.
Uh, not.
That's so old.
Not according to, I mean, maybe I can maybe I can look up who know who got the strike.
But that's pretty wild.
Yeah, I was going to say, like, what the fuck?
You can always counterclaim, but who knows if that's not even worth it.
Yeah, I lost all the money.
It's so like, God, I fucking hate trying to deal with you.
I know you lost the five dollars that episode was going to make us.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, exactly.
Okay, it was a video and then yeah, on squad Zilla and Harry Potter,
monetization, ineligible copyright claims, see details.
And it is, um, yeah, content used, final speech from the great dictator, Charlie Chaplin.
Copyright owner has monetized it in some territories.
Copyright owner is Merlin, idle distribution.
Somehow I doubt they actually own the copyright for that.
And they're probably gaming the system.
It's so stupid.
Yeah, yeah, people just submit straight up false copyright claims.
It's absolutely bullshit.
And even when it's like working as intended, like my latest video is blocked
in England and or the UK, rather, and Ireland.
And because of a clip from an American TV show, but Channel four happens
to license that show there, so it's blocked there.
I don't know.
It's fucking stupid.
See, they see.
Okay.
Move moving on.
This one is called free the nipple logic.
Oh, God.
It's a minute 30.
Okay, guys, so a couple of episodes ago, you guys were talking about some guy
that was saying that we shouldn't feel the nipple for any reason or whatever.
You guys gave your reasons of why he was dumb or wrong, right?
And what you said was technically right.
It's actually right.
But the same logic that you were guys saying that we only think the way we do
about boobs or whatever is because society says so.
Well, the same way it can be applied to if I were to say that I want to show
my dick and balls to everyone.
And it's literally the same because, well, you can say that, oh, well,
dick and balls are different because they are reproductive organ.
You use it for sex or whatever.
Doesn't matter.
Thing is that even if that's true, a dick and balls is just a body organ.
It's part of my body, just as boobs are on women.
So if I cannot show my dick and balls because women would be obviously would
not like that, we can also say that we don't want women to show their
boobs because we don't like it.
And that's really the only reason.
And you guys, well, you guys were saying it's true, but it doesn't matter.
Doesn't matter.
The only reason of why we shouldn't free the vote is because we don't want to.
I thought the whole Free the Nipple thing was about like breastfeeding.
I mean, I don't understand his argument.
You don't see guys walking around with little babies suckling at their
dicks out in public.
I should hope not.
Yeah, I guess, well, I mean, it's the Free the Nipple thing.
It's partially about breastfeeding.
It's also just partially about like, you know, is it illegal to expose your
nipple generally?
It is a double standard between males and women.
Whether you like it or not, there's a full on double standard.
Yeah, I mean, is it?
I don't know if it's hypocritical if you just like, well, we should just why?
Yeah, we should have this apply the same standards to one and the other.
You don't show both.
Just don't show their reproductive organs.
I think you can make a.
There you go.
I think there's like a difference.
Like, yes, the reproductive organs is a broad term.
Like, I think cock and balls is like, like a little different than boobs.
I don't know.
Yeah, what we're saying, like, OK, like, yeah, they're all just body parts.
But if you, yeah, like, yeah, they're different.
It's different because like, because men can show their fucking nipples.
And yeah, it's an it's an asymmetry.
Just, I don't know, we can hide.
We can we can cover up the nipple as much as we want.
I'm just against it being illegal, especially in a way, especially in a
in a way that's like arrested for having their tits out as fucked.
That's not that everyone should be showing the nipples all the time or has to.
I just think everything should be legal.
Yeah, the idea that it's a crime is like fucked.
Like, I get that it's like can still be like socially faux pas for tits to just be hang.
I mean, I wouldn't mind if women did that.
But I can understand that that's like, you know, a social faux pas.
But yeah, it's like a criminal thing.
That's why people are upset about it.
Like, that's what I think should probably change and also make, you know, I don't know.
People should probably not be shitty to people that are like breastfeeding in public.
Like, I shouldn't do that either.
That should be a crime.
Harassing people that are breastfeeding should be a crime.
So everything should be illegal.
Are there are there like really men's right activists out there going women shouldn't
be allowed to breastfeed in public?
Is it men's right or I don't know.
Is it? I just I'm trying to figure this out.
So I'm not making any I'm not declaring that I'm just like, who who's who's out there
against this? I don't know.
Sure, this is some some like some like pure pure tins with like weird reactionary
politics that are just like want to fucking that want to fuck it.
Hey, don't tread on me, man.
No step on snack.
All right.
It's breastfeeding my child in public doesn't violate the nonaggression principle.
Is he pro free speech?
Like he wants the cock and balls to be able to be hung out or is he saying no?
They shouldn't point out our hypocrisy.
I think that's what this is about.
But there's another half of it, so he'll continue so we can find out.
Oh, boy.
And just in case you're going to say that, well, then the only thing that we need to
do is that we need to stop thinking of boobs that way.
Well, it's just a continuation of what I was saying before.
Then I just can say, well, you can you have to tell all women that it's irrational
for them to think that them seeing my fucking dick and balls when I'm talking
to them, I'm just swinging it, swinging it, swinging it like a motherfucker,
like an elephant.
It's stupid because even if I'm doing it, it's it's just society that is telling
them that is wrong.
It's technically there's nothing wrong with that.
So we live in a society in that case.
If you were a woman swinging my balls, I would appreciate if you guys told Cassie
about this because I'm interested in what a woman would say.
He wants us to tell.
So he wants to give you and your own opinions.
The worst part about the podcast is that you all three.
I mean, I appreciate that you guys are holding the fort or whatever.
But if you guys all think the same things and there's no one saying that you are
stupid beside the commenters, the podcast gets worse because it's only like
a echo chamber.
You guys need other opinions.
So stop saying shit that you guys don't know.
You guys are both stupid.
Fuck you.
That's fair.
I can't tell how genuinely mad this guy is.
I can't tell how much of that is a joke and how much is he is actually annoyed.
Yeah, I don't know.
There was the whole thing was a joke that was funny in this when he's talking
about the cock and balls.
But yeah, you never know.
What I mean, I don't know.
You've got to draw the line somewhere, right?
It's just should be symmetrical.
At the very at the very least, we can make our lives.
I would personally and that seems fair.
I would really like to apologize to that guy for my my part in bringing down
this podcast by making it an echo chamber.
It's for being back at us.
What a fucking joke.
We got to get some real.
We got to get some real fuckers on this show.
We got to get some real like men's rights guys on here.
We got to get some real like a full on debate.
I get some real fuckers.
Then I'll have a real discussion.
When you when you think about it, if like the the contention is that like, oh,
it's an echo chamber now because everybody isn't fighting.
But then before Nate stopped coming on, the problem was, oh, God,
they need to stop talking about politics and fighting all the time.
I really have to ask, what are these people?
Well, it's probably, yeah, I mean, sure.
One people, some people just want to be able to swing their cock and balls
around and not listen to an echo chamber, you know, who could blame them?
That's a fair enough.
OK, the next one is called it's flat dummy.
And I hope he's talking about the earth.
Look, look, look, look.
You have no proof that the earth isn't flat.
The earth. Have you ever been to space?
No. All right.
Have you done the math?
Have you calculated that the earth isn't flat?
No. OK, then how do you know it's not flat?
Do you have a belief, a belief in people who are smarter than you?
Dare I say it? Faith?
Are you a faithful person?
Is that it? Mr.
Atheist Professor.
And do you believe in the sciences?
Who's the atheist professor?
I don't know what to say.
Did I mention?
Well, I'm convinced, honestly.
I mean, the earth is flat now.
I mean, do you have any proof that the earth is flat?
Have you personally gone to the edge of the world and seen the ice wall?
Did you do the math?
You're just taking it on faith of the people who post videos to YouTube
after like snorting cocaine, who believe this?
Just use your eyes, man. Open your eyes.
Can you see the curvature?
No, you can't see that mean that's like proof of the round earth stacks of books,
proof of the flat earth.
It's just your eyes.
The the dimension on the show,
the video that just came out in Uendo studios, not in Uendo studios,
folding ideas just dropped a video in search of a flat earth.
Yeah, that was a good one.
We folded into the QAnon shit.
That was interesting. I like that.
I love that. Yeah.
I've watched it like three times now.
And I've seen it in my rock and roll game, but I haven't watched it.
It's really good.
I like his whole channel, but I think that might be his best video.
It might be his magnum opus.
But in it, he does an experiment that demonstrates the curve of the earth.
Like, you see it.
It's very interesting how he does it.
He uses he uses a lake that has like a long stretch of clear water
that he can see over and he knows the distance to the far shore.
And, you know, and like because it's like several kilometers long,
that means that the curve of the earth obscures a certain amount of, you know,
vertical distance and therefore he takes his camera and he puts it on a
dolly or something and he moves the camera up and down.
And as the camera moves up and down a few feet,
you can see that like trees on the opposite shoreline become
occluded by the curvature of the earth and you see it.
And it's really awesome.
So I guess that's it.
Man, that was all fake video editing.
It was all just water vapor, liberal bullshit magic.
It was all just it was all just globe heads doing what globe heads do.
Falsifying evidence, just it's just the lens distortion.
And if you correct the lens distortion by using a flat line,
it magically makes everything flat.
Whoa, whoa.
Anyone can curve the earth with a camera's lens,
but you have to use your eyeballs as in you have to literally take your eyeball
out and then capture footage through it and then upload it to the internet.
You know, it makes sense to me.
Uh, next one is called Where All Good Things Go.
Konnichiwa, Samurai-sama.
I, uh, I, uh, escape voice jail.
It's impossible.
And now that whole story is over.
And I also released Chris-chan, Beno-san girlfriend.
In fact, Beno-san, you say last week, Samurai in a discolored nototail
and less or Samurai Imposter Beno-san, right?
Fuck you, Beno-san, you are an Imposter Samurai.
You reader of a fake Imposter Samurai.
You walk with a swagger and a cane like Kevin Spacey in hit film.
Usual suspect and also gay.
Okay, I call it in no more.
Joke or not funny anymore.
But until you make the wrong time, sayonara.
The Samurai died on his way back to his home planet.
No, I didn't know how much I loved him until he was gone.
Well, Ben, do you have anything to say for yourself about your complete lack
of following the Bushido code?
I'm flattered by the comparison to Kevin Spacey and in, in, in usual suspects,
not in general, I think he's like a rapist or something.
So only in the context of the movie am I flattered by the comparison.
Ah, I'm going to miss him.
I'm going to miss that Samurai.
Why did I, why did I even run away from the clan anyway?
Why did, why did I leave the chorus?
Fuck, Kurosawa, Kurosaki.
Fuck, what's the name of my clan?
It's all blurry.
It's all blurry and indistinct.
The memory is all gone so long.
You're mixing with one another.
You're forgetting your past, Ben.
Remember who you are.
I mustn't, I mustn't, it's not allowed.
Ben's just screaming up into the voicemail.
No, please, don't leave me.
Please, don't leave me, no.
What a journey, though, what an adventure.
We've learned a lot.
Well, someone's been impersonating him, so I should probably go kill that.
I should probably go kill the imposter.
I'll handle it later.
Fair enough.
Next one, fuck being in goal.
All right, lads.
Last week, one of you knuckleheads said something about most AAA games being weird sports,
which made me think, when I was a kid, here in Joliel Gibbentageland,
the AAA paid-to-win gamehouse service for kids was just straight up going outside and playing football.
I think things might be better now.
Football's got one map.
The character creator is generic, kits and boots, season passes, they cost, like, thousands of pounds,
most of which is like prestige cosmetics, at least with games you don't have to be out in the freezing cold
and the soundtracks are better.
And if you're too fat to stand up, you don't just get put in goal like some sort of big hitbox end boss.
I guess what I'm saying is thanks, EA, discuss.
Oh, and the next US mass shooting, Utah.
It rhymes with shootar.
Well, he's calling.
Can't argue without logic.
That's a solid yes.
He's calling it.
That guy's got a nice voice.
I'm impressed.
I can't tell, because it just sounds like shit over this connection.
I gotta say, he was pretty convincing.
I no longer wish to go outside and play football.
Jerks on you, I've never wanted to do that.
Yeah, but you don't have to pay for that.
No, it's better.
It's better because everyone owns it.
It's better because nobody owns football.
Actually, football is a registered trademark of the NFL.
No, he's totally wrong.
He's talking, first of all, he's talking about British football, the bad kind, which nobody owns, because who would even want to own it?
Fancy a bit of the old footy, then?
A bit of the old footy.
A bit of a foot of your ass, more like, if you come around here with that.
I mean, I would hate to play soccer, so I guess he's right about that.
But I also hate video games, so everything sucks.
Next one.
Nexus is dead.
Konnichiwa.
Nah, I'm just kidding.
It's the imposter.
What an awful introduction.
Anyway, hi, PCP.
I have an announcement.
Nexus is dead.
Yes, Nexus Mania is gone for good.
He does not belong to this world anymore.
Forget about him.
The new shit, the new brand is Kaiju-kun.
Yes, I rebranded myself as Kaiju-kun.
Holy shit, incredible.
Go follow me on Twitter, or patreon.com slash kaiju-kun.
Yes, I made up voicemail just to promote myself.
I'm a piece of shit.
Have a nice day.
It's true.
Nexus Mania is Kaiju-kun on Twitter, and I guess he's got a new Patreon.
He's built up enough clout to have one promotional voicemail, and that's it.
Don't miss it.
Don't miss him, alright?
You gotta respect the hustle.
I don't know why.
I don't know why he decided to change his handle or whatever.
Yeah, I don't know either.
More power tune.
Check out his fucking vaporette in my freaking book that you should have bought already.
Read his web comics.
They're fucking great.
Bunny, Wolf, Ruckado Punch, go.
Do it.
Yeah, Nexus is good.
He's a good man.
He's a good lad.
Next on, Commenter Rules.
In ages long ago, there was a fucking podcast called the PCP, and they had an episode called Commenter Rules.
And there were many rules, but the enforcement of these rules was done by something called banning and muting people.
And, you know, I think maybe you all should go back to that, because, you know, it's fun as it is going into the comments and seeing, like, a no-nate-no-watch 50 times.
I think we only need one of those.
So, you know, maybe the core no-nate-no-watch guy can continue.
But I think, you know, if you're shady in the comments and annoying, you should just be banned censorship-based.
Yeah.
The core no-nate-no-watch guy is an institution at this point.
Most other people saying it are, like, putting a little twist on it.
And I think that's funny.
They're, like, they're mixing it up.
They're remixing it.
I mean, they can downvote and hate comment all they want, but that's just driving up our engagement and making us more powerful.
It's insane how many people do not understand.
Like, if you don't like a video, don't leave a dislike and comment.
You're helping the video.
It doesn't make any fucking sense.
I love when people leave those fucking hate comments.
Why does it work like that?
I've never understood why they built it that way.
Okay.
I don't understand either.
And I've heard from some people that if a video is, like, really heavily disliked, that can affect it in the algorithm.
I've never ever seen any proof of that, but I've heard from those people.
I think it's because YouTube doesn't care about quality.
They care about-
Yeah, they want eyeballs on the videos.
They don't care if you like it or not.
So, if someone's hate-watching something and downvoting it, they're gonna share it and be like,
please hate this as well.
A downvote means you felt strongly about the video.
Yeah.
Doesn't this make you mad?
And then they'll bring more people to watch it and get mad.
And so those videos are great because that's doing exactly what YouTube wants you to do.
Stay on their website.
Consume their advertisements.
That's exactly right.
And they can't tell the difference between angry comments and good comments.
So, again, every angry comment you get is just helping.
Exactly.
It doesn't.
I mean, they're the same fucking thing.
They're both comments.
Yeah.
I don't mind.
I don't know.
I'm kind of over it.
I'm just like, yeah.
Bring on the...
Criticize us in the comments.
I don't know.
I don't feel like it's a banable offense.
Unless you're like...
I don't...
You have to be like, particularly shitty for me to even consider banning you.
You have to be spouting some real shit.
Now, people are gonna try pushing the envelope just to see where the line is.
I don't think there's any amount of...
There's no...
I don't think there's any insult you could levy at me specifically,
or maybe even at the podcast in general,
that I would be like, that's bad enough that it deserves a ban.
But I mean, if you want to try that out,
see if you can push me.
Okay, next one.
Hardwood, Rich Mahogany.
Woo-hoo!
Benno Sento-san!
I am a ghost of your samurai who died earlier.
My revenge for your spirit.
Honto voi someru.
Forever Benno-san.
He's back!
Mamel!
Woo-hoo!
Belly spooky.
What an effect a turn of events.
Woo-hoo!
But until next time, sayonara!
You might have to call an exorcist for your voicemail box, dude.
This is such a rich tapestry.
This is such a rich history for this character.
He's gone through so much.
But you know, his vision remains clear and unclouded, consistent.
Eyes on the prize.
That's what I love about him.
That's what I respect him for.
Okay, incredible.
Ben said, when you worked that out, make another voicemail.
This is probably about morality or whatever, lol.
So last week I left an absurdly simplistic model of utilitarianism and voicemail being like,
oh, morality is like, it's good if well-being is increased and bad if well-being is decreased.
I mean, and obviously there's critique that like, well, yeah, but the world is full of all of these like complicated situations with a lot of context that complicates the decision.
But I feel like that's a, you know, people have that complaint of utilitarianism a lot.
And I feel like it's a weird complaint because utilitarianism taken to its logical conclusion is just to analyze that context as much as you reasonably can in order to ascertain like the like true utility of each option.
You have is, you know, to see like, okay, what does like produce like the situation where as many people are as happy as possible.
And obviously that in itself, as you also said last week is like non-quantifiable because it's all subjective.
But I think that continues to just emphasize the fact that everything should be looked at case by case.
The reason why I use this to describe my moral thinking is because it emphasizes that you adapt your moral thinking to each situation instead of adhering to inflexible moral principles.
Anyway, fuck it titties bro, fuck it boobies.
That's pretty based.
I guess.
Yeah, I mean, I guess it's true that like maybe maybe it's not maybe it's a little unfair to be like, oh, well that that rule you just laid out doesn't like, you know, you can't that doesn't solve every problem by just applying that rule.
You know, we can't just use this one this one concept in order to determine the proper outcome very given situation.
Therefore it fails.
You know, maybe the point is like, you know, this yeah, this is a rule of thumb that we should keep in mind.
But like no one's going to no one's going to have like, oh yeah, here are the rules.
Here's the formula.
If you follow these rules, you get the morally correct.
Don't you think that's that's walking back the point though, like if anyone if you said utilitarianism, or considering the utility of a choice is an important factor when making decisions.
Nobody would argue that point because everybody does that already.
The reason we mocked that voicemail last week was because it was like utilitarianism is the one and only true way.
It's so simple.
Duh.
And our point was, no, it's not.
So like, I don't the idea that we value utility in all of our decisions all the time.
And so by walking it back and saying like, you use utility to help you figure out your moral dilemmas on a case by case basis.
Well, no shit.
That's basic logic that everybody does.
It is kind of like it's insanely obvious.
Like, oh, we should just maximize happiness for everyone.
It's like, yeah, no shit.
But it's like, I mean, I don't know.
I don't trust human beings to determine that kind of shit like with utilitarian like type rules.
So I mean, I'm not a full Kantian, but I'm not saying day ontology needs to be thrown out, you know, like as a baby with a bathwater.
That's pretty much what we were saying last week.
Was that like, it's the world is more complicated to simply make calculations like that.
That can't even be truly quantified from a human level anyways, because we don't know the repercussions of our actions.
I would love to maximize happiness, but like, I don't know how.
And like, I would love to look at everything on a case by case basis, but that's not really feasible, you know.
Okay, oh wait, I'm going to sneeze.
Am I going to sneeze? No, never mind.
False alarm.
Okay.
Next up, cross my contribution.
Nice.
Thanks.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
Pretty based.
Okay.
God, I feel so much better now.
It just brightens my day.
Every Sunday, I look forward to it.
Next up, Margar.
Hey, Margar here.
I bet you guys are probably wondering, where was Margar last week?
Where was the voicemail?
I was at work and I forgot to.
But I'm back now, still in prison.
It's still back and I've kind of gotten over the depression I was in earlier.
And you know, I'm just kind of like doing my slave labor.
Although Samurai, Ben St. Sensei, he's here in the voice jail.
And he's like starting a Yakuza gang and is killing a lot of people.
He must have gotten tired of that.
I'm fearing for my life.
That must have been how we got out.
The goons were one thing, but this Japanese stuff is too much to handle.
Please make it stop.
Well, I mean, he's a spooky ghost now.
The Yakuza...
I love the idea that it's like you're in jail and it's like, you can hit the ghost.
It's like, but this Japanese stuff, it's a little too far for me.
Being in jail and the ghost and slave labor, that was all fine.
But yeah, this is getting a little too Japanese.
Margar, be a little more open-minded in your confinement.
I'll send some goons out to do some sensitivity training with you.
I think that's what we could all use a little bit of right about now.
Next up, if Raiden was raised in Texas...
I'm strong!
I said my tool was a tool for justice.
Not to use an anger.
Not to use prevention.
Now, I'm not that sure.
And besides, this isn't my sword.
Lance Dance.
Everybody knows he'd say this ain't my sword.
Illusion Shatter.
That's a good point.
You had to be up until that last sentence.
Yeah, a little tragic misstep. Stumble at the finish line.
I like the voice though, but yeah, I should have changed that line.
Seven out of ten overall. Good effort.
It sounds exactly what he probably would sound like.
He would whine like that, I think, nasally.
Next up, Ben SSS.
Hello, PCP.
It is I, Ben Shapiro, also known as Spicy Salts.
You see, I did it because I crave to be in your shoes.
May is the sweetest and kindest girl in the world.
I imagine she smells like strawberries and love.
Your house, your girlfriend, your life.
I want to be you.
I crave to be you.
And for that brief instant, I was inside your house with your girlfriend.
In that moment, I was you.
Am I not correct?
And it was beautiful.
I guess we have to explain this.
Unfortunately, yeah, I guess we do.
Do you want to, or should I?
How does one even begin to tackle this?
There is there is a person known as Spicy Salts.
Who's been a a thorn in our side for a while now.
I think I first found him through I Am Games.
I think that might have been her.
It was fine. It seemed mostly fine.
It was mostly just like a typical kind of like just kind of trollish commenter.
It seemed to be in relatively good fun, I guess.
It's just like an annoying person.
Me, me and Digi on I Am Games, when he would message it all the time and say dumb things,
just pegged him as like, this is a kid, like a little kid being a little child.
And I guess it just continued to escalate.
And this guy was way more weird than either of us gave him any credit for.
And I guess like a week or a little like two weeks ago now.
A while, a little while ago.
Allegedly, but not allegedly, but allegedly broke into Digi's house.
That seems to be the story.
Tried to put like May in handcuffs or some shit until Digi chased him off.
Something like that.
It's very bizarre.
The internet is such a fucking weird place.
Cyber, this must be pretty awkward for you.
Yeah, yeah.
I was like vaguely aware that there was some sort of situation with the drama going on,
but that's pretty intense.
So the voicemail we just listened to was a supposed message sent by Spicy Salts to Digi.
I don't think it was.
I'm pretty sure it was just some troll.
I would hope so.
I would certainly hope so.
But you know, I can't believe anything these days.
I can't be sure of anything anymore.
No, we can't.
Yeah, I guess there's not much else to say about it.
I guess it's good that we acknowledge that that was a thing that...
Yeah, like this week, that's kind of big news in PCP lore, I guess, is that that whole thing happened.
That was very bizarre.
And I guess Digi is moving and stuff, and it's caused a bit of a fuck.
It's caused some fuckery.
Now listen, guys, I might not be a member of the PCP, but I feel like I can speak on there we have when I say,
please don't do that.
Yeah, I'm glad we could get a neutral third party to clarify that,
because I know it was obviously a little bit of confusion.
I didn't feel comfortable saying it myself, but I needed someone with clear eyes.
With eyes I'm clouded by hate.
I'm not sure if I can consider myself a perfectly neutral observer, but for my somewhat subjective point of view,
being a weirdo stalker who breaks into people's houses is not good to do.
Generally frowned upon.
I am...
Obviously this is terrible.
Obviously this is a bad thing that should not have happened,
but I will say that I am interested and very curious honestly to learn more about why this happened,
because it's so strange.
It's so weird.
It's so strange, but like you said it, and I'm like, oh yeah, of course that happened, because of course that would happen.
And I'm looking forward to more details coming to light in a very sort of gossipy TMZ kind of way.
I can't help myself.
So you know, very exciting.
So what I'm saying is that I'm glad it happened.
It's good. Thanks Spicey salts.
You really, you really shit things up around me.
No, no, no, no, no, no, disavow, disavow.
Sorry.
Every good arc needs a good villain, so that's all I'll say.
That's right, that's right.
Anyway, Shaggy wants to be you.
Is this just going to be another thing?
Oh, no.
Like I did it, because I crave to be in your shoes, and that means the sweetest and kindest girl in the world.
I imagine she smells like Scooby Snacks and loves you, your house, your girlfriend, your life.
I want to be you.
I crave to be you.
And for that brief instant, I was inside your house with your girlfriend.
In that moment, I was you.
And it was beautiful.
You know, it's too on the nose.
I wasn't surprised when I had confirmed that, yeah, this is probably not a genuine message.
But it's pretty funny, though.
It's pretty fun.
Next up, Ben was wrong about something.
Like the Democrats, they're not good people.
They're not any better than the Republicans.
They're all filthy, disgusting politicians.
And they'd block him.
They'd block his nomination if they could, but they can't.
They can't because, oh, guess what?
In 2013, they legislated against it.
They can't filibuster anymore.
Oh, boo-hoo.
But you regret it now, Democrats.
We went over this.
The Republicans did some filibuster bullshit in 2016.
You know, they did it, whether it was legislated against or not.
I didn't say the Democrats were good.
I think some of them are better people than the Republicans are.
Some of them are.
Not all of them, by any means.
The Justice Democrats are, I mean, you know, they're better.
They are.
They just are.
They're the minority, but they're there.
And that's all I have to fucking say about that.
Fuck you.
Go...
Who is...
Hey, I got a great post for you to read.
It's by Jennifer Diane Reitz, and it was posted on fucking FIM Fiction earlier today.
I'll go and read the whole list of her dystopian predictions for you.
No.
Yes, yes, yes.
This is content.
This is content, Tom.
If someone's going to bring in that right-wing stuff, you got to go as far as you can get
and just blast them with that drumflist from your ultimate Kokoro wish.
Yeah, we got to go as far, we got to go as far left as we possibly can with JDR.
She is...
She is the...
She's the new burning.
Oh, dear.
Next one is, Huh?
The Procrastinators podcast is a show where a bunch of content creators pick a topic and
talk about it until no one cares anymore.
What?
Is that like a...
Topic?
Description?
Why does it say topic?
I don't get it.
At least the podcast probably.
Is this like a VCR?
What's a VCR?
I thought our channel description said under construction.
I think the podcast upload probably still says that because that was never changed.
Oh, no.
Oh, dear.
Well, I mean...
I'll immediately change it to it's a low energy podcast by boring people about that.
Yeah, please.
Yeah, please do.
Please do.
And that way nobody can possibly complain.
Yeah, this is exactly what you signed up for.
They cover all our bases.
Next up is, Them Snakes.
Oh, my God.
The Legend Return.
Them Snakes.
You thought you could be sneaky and climb into my snake pile last night.
Well, I detected you and I found the letter that you left behind.
I'm sorry, but this is pretty fucking cringy.
And I will now read it for the entire world to see.
Oh, I wonder what this could be.
I did it because I craved for it in your metaphorical shoes.
Them Snakes is the sweetest and kindest abomination in the world.
I imagine they smell like strawberries and dead rats.
Your pile, your hive mind, your life.
I want to be you.
I crave to be you.
And for that brief instant, I was inside your wriggling pile surrounded by snakes.
In that moment, I was you.
And it was beautiful.
Love, Ben St.
It sounds like something I said.
I'm sorry, but this is cringe.
You posted cringe.
You lose a subscriber.
No, don't unsubscribe, then, Snakes.
Please.
I just, I just, you know, who wouldn't.
How do you deal with these accusations that you posted cringe?
Who wouldn't, who wouldn't occasionally wonder what it feels like to be a hive mind of serpentine, of wriggling serpentine, you know, Majesty.
Who could blame me?
He'd have done the same thing if the roles were reversed.
He can't prove otherwise.
All right.
Hey, thanks.
Hey, thanks for the message.
Love you.
You smell so good.
I want, I want to, I want more.
I want to be you.
No, no, no, never mind.
Next one is from if you don't like America, then you can get out.
Okay, good.
Hey guys, we're almost done.
Are you excited?
Incredibly.
Well, nothing's gonna be better than that last voicemail, but yeah.
There are so many mouse cursors on your feed now that it's like making me sick.
It doesn't, it doesn't even like look like a screen anymore.
It's too like artifact.
I have no idea why it's doing that, but I like it.
It's, it's better.
Next one is from trans bullshit.
Sorry for the length.
I love you, Tom.
Do you know this person?
I don't think so.
Okay.
Well, let's hear, let's hear what they have to say.
I was just like asleep and I like thought of this.
So I dreamed it anyway.
Secondary voicemail.
Sorry for making too.
Tom at some point says like transphobia wouldn't exist or be like way less prominent.
If trans people instead of like trying to make more pronouns made less, there's like
a ton of problems with this.
First, like traditional trans people don't make new pronouns and like transphobia goes
against them.
I go by she, her typical pronouns.
Nothing new to remember.
People are still transphobic to me.
Two, um, uh, fucking like trying to like impose on cis people and what cis people do would
obviously like, uh, have some other counter effects.
Uh, three, like this is fundamentally, you misunderstand the root of transphobia and
things like the, like the genuine, like how would I explain to my kids?
It's like, it's like real, but it's not like the roots of transphobia or in like, uh,
uh, fucking, uh, sexism and fucking, uh, uh, like all the isms, you know, all the bullshit
that you already know.
And like maybe in disgust on some level, uh, like the roots, like, like the reason fucking
trans people are mad isn't, um, you know, or trans people.
The reason people are mad at trans people isn't because they have to learn, like they have
to learn to use they them on like more people or something.
I don't know.
Like a new pronouns aren't the common, but like, like the reason someone's disgusted
by someone who uses neo pronouns isn't cause they like fucking are like, are too stupid
to remember an extra two words.
It's cause they fucking, uh, cause of like complicated societal and, uh, and whatever
factors, you get it.
Anyway.
Yeah.
Uh, not sure exactly what to say to that.
Um, well, I mean, I, the quality wasn't great cause I'm still listening to your speakers,
but like the, the point that I was making last week wasn't that I think they, them like
producing pronouns, just a genderless pronoun would solve the problems.
My point was that by, if they would, it's gone in that direction instead of creating
multiple new pronouns, you just would have removed that, uh, that counterpoint from the
discussion, right?
Cause there was like a whole, there's a whole bunch of like jokes and memes and like,
it would have been one less thing for them to make fun of, but I mean, we wouldn't have
like changed everything, but I do see where you're coming from though.
People are going to, are going to push back against that concept societally because it
goes against, uh, the general kind of cultural consensus for the last like forever, right?
This is still a relatively new concept, uh, socially, especially in the West, uh, in this
culture where Jen, the gender binary has been heavily, uh, reinforced and used honestly
for marketing purposes and for a bunch of other stuff, right?
So like to, to push back against that, you're going to meet friction like regardless, uh,
just because that's the nature of change.
All of my, my only point was you would have one less obstacle to go over if you were trying
to simplify things rather than expand complexity because more complexity makes that problem
more complicated to digest to someone, uh, who might be on board, but not understand
and gives people who are detracting against it more ammo to use against you.
Not that that was going to blanket solve anything.
I mean, I feel like, um, I feel like if there, if there is a benefit, if there is some benefit
to like a, a neo pronoun over like they, them, then I can see why you might say like, no,
it's, it's not helpful to say like, oh, we'll just go with they, them it's simpler.
But like, I feel like I would need to be someone who uses neo pronouns to understand what's
useful about them.
I don't need them, but like they're not for me.
So it's like not, it kind of doesn't matter if I think they're useful or not, uh, or if
I think they're overly complicated or something, uh, so, um, on a, hmm, uh, I guess on a case
by case basis, I'd have to judge if they increase overall, uh, well-being.
Sure.
Hmm.
I mean, I was about to go that angle as well, like utility, like the utilitarian angle versus
like subjective interpretation.
Yeah.
I mean, I, I don't know anybody who uses a pronoun outside of they, them, or, you know,
the typical binary.
So like, some would have to make a case to me, this is why I use this and this is why
it works.
I would have to judge for myself if I feel that that is a coach and argument or not.
Well, I wouldn't, I don't agree.
I don't agree.
I wouldn't, I wouldn't say they have to like explain it to me.
Like if they, if they said that they're, that's how they go by, then fine.
Like I'm not going to argue with them.
I'm not, I'm not going to tell them they can't use it.
Right.
I mean, when they explained to me to see if I agree with that perspective or not.
That's all.
Not that I, I mean, I mean, I'm not going to be persuaded to use any different pronouns.
But, you know, not for me personally, but if I, if I understand their perspective or
not, like I, I can respect it.
I'd be, I'd be curious if someone was like, if someone was like, yeah, I'm a, I'm, I don't
know.
I don't know if this is one people use or not, but like Zeezer, I mean, I would be
curious why I would be curious, like why that, like why is they, them, not something you,
you are okay with or comfortable with?
Like what's the, I would just, I would just, I would just be curious why not.
I wouldn't, I would never really thought about this, but I never met anyone who uses like
an extra pronoun like that.
So like, I just don't consider myself very knowledgeable enough like that I'm willing
to make any sort of declaration that whether it is or isn't helpful, but like I've never
met, I've never met anyone who uses that.
So I would be interested in hearing their like their point of view on it.
The only time I've ever heard Zeezer is as the butt of a joke.
Well, exactly.
I've heard it million times as a joke.
So that's why I'm wondering like, again, I don't know, which was my entire point from
last week that if it was just they, them, and there was a simplification of pronouns,
that wouldn't be a joke that could be used, which was the only point I was trying to make
last week.
I think the problem is that like, okay, I think, I think with, with this voicemail would
say to that is like, aren't you, aren't you, isn't the problem there not that something
invites a joke to be made about?
Like it's not the thing's fault for that, like that one could, that he could make fun
of it.
The fault lies with someone who chooses to make fun of it instead of trying to understand
it.
Right?
Yes.
But all, all, all I'm trying to say is that objectively, the thing not being there would
remove the joke from the table.
I'm not making a prescriptive statement on like, therefore, it shouldn't exist.
I'm just saying.
Yeah.
If it wasn't there, it wouldn't be there.
That's, I can't, I can't argue with that.
Yeah, I agree with you.
They would be one less thing.
I mean, the only thing I'll say is like, it doesn't, the actual thing doesn't matter.
They're going to like make fun of them with something else if that wasn't there.
But I mean, I do, I do get what you're saying though.
Like it's not like, you know, you're not, you're not trying to say it would fix the
situation.
It's just like.
As somebody who has never heard any sort of explanation of why other pronouns exist,
I cannot say whether they're helpful or not.
All I could say is that they are more confusing because you're adding more language.
Yeah.
Right.
And that is something that is not, is not equivalent to him and her because they're
not, they're no biological cues or aesthetic cues to help you make that inference.
So there was no way for me to know you're using ZZer, if that's what you're using, without
me specifically asking for you.
So you've increased the complexity of language.
If I could weigh the magic wand, I would reduce the complexity all the way until we're just
like finished and we just have, we just, we're just all it.
I mean, that, that, that to me seems like the more efficient way of going about, if,
if you have a problem with, with the gender binary, which I'm assuming a certain, a certain
degree of people do, instead of adding more choices, get rid of the gender connotation
and language altogether.
And then you can identify it as whatever you need to, and language will still accommodate
everybody with one blanket term and therefore reduce any, literally any chance of ever being
misgendered because there's no longer any gendered language, as opposed to creating
new pronouns that everybody has to learn.
And they have no way of inherently understanding based on your appearance, like we do with
traditional gendered language, we can make pretty accurate assumptions on who is, you
know, a male or female based on the, you know, traditional paradigm.
So that was all it was implying is that the more complexity is going to be inherently
more difficult and harder for the average person to digest, then less complexity is
that the ethical thing to do.
I have no idea, because I have no idea what the argument for increased pronouns are until
I know what that is.
I can't comment on it any further other than the empirical statement that you're adding
more complexity.
Yeah. Sure.
When it comes to complexity in language, though, I mean, we are just talking about
English, there's all these other foreign languages that have like gendered fucking
nouns and all the shit that I barely even understand.
Moving past the fucking binary is going to be like, I can't even fathom it.
I mean, you're moving the gendered pronouns wouldn't, you know, remove the gendered binary
as like a concept that we have in society or anything.
But we're just, we're just, we're just simply talking about English language at this point.
This is a huge, massive, complicated issue that no amount of podcasts will ever be able
to cover.
Oh, no, no, no, I just agree.
I don't know.
I think we spent another half hour.
We can fix this.
Yeah, we can we can fix this another half hour.
Just get through all the genders, all the everything we can have that sorted out.
Let's just pull up gender on Urban Dictionary.
And we can pass us all out in the next 20 minutes.
You know what?
Let's fucking do it.
Urban Dictionary gender.
Just feel better to feel like you all came home.
Legacy PCP view.
Here we go.
Gender is the range of characteristics pertaining to differentiating between
masculinity and femininity, depending on their context.
These characters, it's may include biological sex, i.e.
the state of being male, female, or an intersex variation.
Sex based social structures, i.e.
gender roles or gender identity.
Traditionally, people who identify as men or women or use masculine or feminine
gender pronouns are using a system of gender binary, whereas those who make this
outside these groups fall under the umbrella terms, non-binary or genderqueer.
Some cultures have specific gender roles that are distinct from men and women,
such as the hegeras of South Asia.
These are often referred to as their genders.
Well, that wasn't very funny.
See, that was less funny than the average Urban Dictionary definition.
But, you know, it was pretty accurate, I guess.
But. Oh, but don't I was just like the dictionary definition.
Oh, but don't worry.
Right underneath, we have the September 6th word of the day,
STEEZY, which is to style with ease.
So in case you were wondering, God, I love learning urban words.
I don't know how urban I think that is.
It's on Urban Dictionary.
It has to be.
I guess by, I guess by definition, even if it wasn't before, it is now.
What's the definition for Urban Dictionary on Urban Dictionary?
I'm really going to do it.
No, no.
How deep is the rap?
We have one more voicemail.
We have one more Urban Dictionary, a site where it's a challenge
to find one subject where no one talks about sex.
That's the top definition.
Incredible.
OK, one last, last voicemail.
Play this to pass by Nate Heads.
I love Clarissa.
Ha, ha, wee.
I am here with an explanation of why Nate is not back on the podcast.
I understand this man's filthy rotten little brain.
Basically, what is happening is Nate likes to do big celebrations
when something finally comes up.
He tries to make everything a big event.
So what he is doing is he is currently editing the Brad lecture.
And I think he's doing the OV as well.
Someone's doing the OVA.
So when those are up, he's going to come on the podcast
and try and make a big stink about it and say, hey, guys, look,
you get a double reward.
The thing's out.
And so am I.
I'm out the closet because I'm Nate.
Whoa, look at me.
Also, you can go watch all his old videos if you need to hear
this strange man's voice and also all the old episodes
of the podcast will exist.
Tom, Ben, Hippo, whoever else is on this episode.
You're pretty cool.
I understand.
Do your best.
I'm one of Mary Clarissa.
I'm not very cool.
That thing I like it.
He likes Clarissa.
That's pretty good.
It's pretty based to like Clarissa.
Indeed.
I mean, Nate is working on some Brad stuff.
So this is partially accurate.
We've we had to do some some some a little bit of voice acting this week.
Very simple, simple shit.
But yeah.
Brad Brad stuff I should I really should get around to fucking
finishing that son of two one or two lecture really should
probably honestly how I want to finish that.
I thought it was already out.
What? What?
Why? I just I just assumed it was already out.
It's been so long.
No, you rude.
No, I have not put it out yet.
Sorry, I had more faith in you than I should have.
Yeah, that was your biggest mistake, I think.
Truly, I was a fool.
Big, big problem, big problem.
I'm excited to see Son of two one or two.
That's going to be good.
Son of two one or two.
I mean, have you have you read like the later chapters?
I have not actually like sat down and just read them.
I have like read a little bit about them.
But no, I'm not.
I don't consider myself an expert on it.
No, Son of two gets very unstructured as it goes on.
And very right.
There's interest.
There's one chapter in particular where it's just all
everything goes right out the window and like complete chaos
breaks loose.
The canon of the story is just completely fucked.
And that's that's probably the best part.
It sounds like fun.
Yeah, it's pretty good.
It's just imagine me just kind of like reading like events
in a list of just like things that happen.
That just each one individually is like really fucked up beggars
belief. Why would why would the story?
Why would that happen?
Example, a wild song to becomes a meth head.
There you go.
That's a little incredible.
That's I know I'm the guy who is specifically saying not to
like lump them in together.
But that is one thing I love about things like tales gets
trolled and Son of two is that like there's so much of media
that you can sort of predict what's going to happen.
Or at least you can like know the things that definitely won't
happen.
But you just you have no idea what's going to happen in these
things.
I I certainly didn't expect Chester Cheeto man to just fucking
butcher those women and throw them and like every female
character in the story into a mass grave.
Didn't didn't see it go in there.
I don't think anyone could have possibly predicted that.
But that's what happens.
Spoilers for.
Well, he is a dangerous weed dealer.
So you know, deals the best weed.
And love that smart weed.
I'm smarter when I'm high and you should watch out for it.
Man, very.
Hey, you know, it's been a it's been a session been really
fun just talking about tales gets trolled with you, cyber.
I've enjoyed I've enjoyed our conversation a lot today and I
want to say thank you.
Thanks for being a guest on the procrastinators.
Yeah, this was really fun.
I enjoyed it.
I like talking about all this weird shit like Kokoro wish and
fucking Sonichu and tales gets trolled.
And I appreciate you having me on because I know that
traditionally this is not exactly a super guest heavy
podcast.
And I'm very much like to say that I'm super happy that I
ruined this episode for all the PCV heads who can't stand the
guests.
Whoo.
Fuck yeah.
Yeah, everyone check out cyber shell.
He's on YouTube.
He's just made his big a big comeback.
Oh, you know, I wanted to ask you have you seen a video called
the rise and fall of cyber shell?
Have you seen that video?
Yeah, you know, actually, I went on my way not to watch
anything related to me because it's hyper cringe for a long
time.
But then when I came back, I was like, well, I should probably
watch the things that are yeah, the guy that made that is
that he's a nice dude and we're on good terms.
OK, I watched that the other day and I was like, I wonder
what cyber shell thinks about this like it is funny because
you know, I mean, I just I just basically dipped without
saying anything because I just I don't really like when people
know about my personal life.
So I can't I can't really blame people for just wildly
speculating on all sorts of shit, you know.
Sure, sure.
As we've learned, that's what they do when you don't spell
things out for them very clearly.
We we wouldn't know about that.
We keep all of our listeners up to speed on everything going
on all the time and there's never any confusion and no one
ever is wondering about like who is or is not on the podcast
or why.
That's because everybody who listens to the podcast
follows us on Twitter at TP Crasnators and is a patron at
patreon.com slash the procrastinators where we keep
everybody abreast of everything that's going on down to the
smallest minutia.
Ab so literally if you're not even a patron, then you don't
even deserve to know what's happening, frankly.
No, that's fair.
And if you know, it's an accident and you weren't supposed
to and also everyone probably sends voicemails to speakpike.com
slash PCP voicemail because I don't know if that's also a
cool thing, a cool thing to do if you want, if you want to get
your voice, listen to your voice and listen to your stupid
bullshit, listen to your dumb bullshit on the show.
We'll do it.
We'll do anything.
Um, anything else?
I'm pretty much by a t-shirt by I don't know if I'm up with
another dumb t-shirt idea this week, but we didn't.
Um, what if we just sell CyberShell t-shirts?
I don't think I even, like what my pay, I don't even know if I
own the rights to my own like avatar, you know, so that's
one reason I haven't sold merch.
I see.
Um, well, we'll come out of, we'll think of some way to
commodify you.
Just put the text CyberShell like on a plain white shirt.
Just taking, I'm being cool shirt, cross out cool and just
write CyberShell under it and you too can be
CyberShell.
I'm tempted to do it for real.
Every, every joke shirt I've ever like said in the last couple
weeks, you've just made real.
Yeah, it's fine.
It's it's the beauty of the internet.
You can just make these wallets to loop it all around.
You know, people wanted to have their little shirts when they
were peasants and, you know, you are actually allowing these
peasants who listen to the podcast to have that opportunity to
actually make the I have the bubonic plague shirt and send
them back in time to all the peasants who needed them.
Anyone, anyone could make these shirts
theoretically, but they wouldn't.
They became an or official realist.
Yeah, they could only spring.
They could only spring from a mind such as ours.
They could only spring from the well, the font of creativity
that is the PCP.
It could only emerge organically in this in this chemical soup
that we've created here of ideas.
We were the modern day Duchamp and the
Bay State t-shirt is our fountain.
Go give it all the credit it deserves.
It's it's about it's not about the shirt itself.
It's not about what's on the shirt.
It's about the context that the shirt exists within.
Indeed. Think of think about it.
Think about that.
All right, let's we've got three and a half hours in.
It's time to wrap this baby up.
We got fucking go.
We got to go.
That was a got to go fast.
I got to say for a guy that doesn't do podcasts.
I had a good time.
Can't believe we got we got Cybershell.
Cybershell never do pot does podcast.
We got him.
Yeah, he's you're going to have a hard time finding me on other podcasts.
Unless you're watching this video in like four or five years.
But hopefully I'll have done more by then
unless I'm dead and I might be dead by then.
Then the podcast will be worth even more value Shanghai.
We shanghide him into it.
And we've we've made it.
This is this is all this was all the plan all along.
All right. I so I wish I had something more
for myself, other than I just go I guess look at my YouTube channel
and give me money at patreon dot com slash Ben Saint.
Yeah.
Everybody shows your picture.
I got to get somebody on here to show mine for a change.
No, no.
Even the odd.
No, no, no, no.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
OK, OK, OK.
Great everyone.
Thanks for listening.
Thanks for being on.
That's the end of the podcast.
Good night.
See you.
No, Nate.
Yes.
Watch.
See you next week.
Bye bye.
Goodbye!
Bye-bye.