Can I intro? Please, go ahead.
What's up everyone on the episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Why'd you hit me? Listen, we all have our sins that we have to atone for, Ben.
We aren't all free of the vices of humanity. We have to be punished.
And in this glorious Wild West saying that this episode takes place,
and yes, that's right, we are in 1986, aka the pure barbarity of man in nature.
I'm able to do whatever I want to you, my wife. God ordains it.
You know, Munchy, I'm glad that it's the end of history, and we've scientifically discovered
that all morality derives from religion and that there's no God, and therefore everything is permissible.
It's very liberating.
I agree. We also have Nate.
A friend to all the peoples of the earth, but most especially what is known as the honorary Aryan race, the Japanese.
They're my favorite.
What? Any particular reason? I can't imagine anything that they've done that's worth.
Name one thing done by the Japanese or the Aryans.
I'll tell you what, Ben.
Or the Aryan's effect.
In a supporting role in 2003's smash hit starring Tom Cruise, The Last Samurai,
and gotta say, big hit. Big success. Way to go.
Actually, speaking point for later, you know what the Japanese also did? They did...
That's one piece you're hearing right there. We'll get into that in just a second.
But we also have Meij.
Oh, yeah. I'm back, and this is what I come back to. Okay.
Meij, you've been... You're our prodigal son. You've been gone for...
You're our hell of Troy, Meij.
You're our hell of Troy.
You're our Joan of Arc. You're our Steve Brule.
Where you been?
I've been in Lithuania as I usually do during the summer.
Stuff happened. A lot of stuff. I don't want to talk about it.
But I'm back in the UK now, literally.
She's been running drugs across the border for the cartels.
I've been gone for literally one episode, but I feel like it's been a lifetime
since I've ever talked into a microphone.
I feel like I've aged a century at the time that I've been gone.
Now that I think about it, I'm actually surprised that you're here, Munch.
I was expecting you to be continuously occupied.
Aren't you on a road trip or something?
All secrets will be revealed, but I have one thing to tell you right off the bat.
This is the last PCPM recording in the house that I've spent my entire internet career in.
I'm leaving at 10PM this evening, and I will not come back until Christmas, if even.
If not for summer. This is the end of an era.
It's actually happening. The wheels are in motion, and I'm going to college.
Literally, I'm heading to Boston tonight.
Actually, that's not entirely true. I'm heading to DC and then to Baltimore and then to Boston,
but the idea is there.
Hey, aren't we all getting a bus together?
We are. We're all going to be jammed out.
So after BronyCon, me, Ben, Cassie, and Hippo are all going to run the same Greyhound together,
and it's going to be glorious, and we're going to have the whole place to ourselves,
and we're going to force everyone else out.
We're taking the bus there, too, right, from Boston to Baltimore.
Nah, nah, I'm flying in.
You are?
Yeah.
So I think you're, yeah, as is Gib, I think you guys are just taking the bus out together?
Yes.
Right?
Yeah.
Okay. All right.
So let's just be super clear.
Most of us, not Mage, but the bunch of us are going to be at BronyCon next week,
which might mean that this is one of the super rare occasions when no PCP gets made.
We're not quite sure how that's going to work out, but they're going to make it.
I'm going to go on my own.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Dude, we need like a, it's got to be the PCP, the PCP B-Listers, you know,
all the second-rate characters that nobody likes.
Digi, Jesse, Mage, Davoo.
God, that sounds so much better than us.
Monkey Jones, Jeff.
I can't tell you how sick I am of us.
Nino, Econ, the, you know, the gangs all here.
Yeah, yeah.
Ben, why must you increase the sniper red dots on your face to more
than the already astounding 20 that it's at?
Or I guess like 15,000 or whatever the Twitter followers have started on Avocados.
God, well, I want it, I just, I want, I'd like him.
I'm like a little cat.
I like to fucking, I like to paw at them with my little paws.
Ah, curiously killed the cat, they say.
Hey, anyway.
I'm just asking questions.
You were right, Ben.
I was an original.
I know.
And I got back from it.
I went to Chris State.
Originally, the plans were quite-
What is, what is Chris State?
Oh, well, you know, cross the state means you go one way.
Well, Chris goes upwards.
Oh.
Chris crossed them.
Okay, all right.
So I went to Chris State.
You went, you went, you went, you went Chris Country skiing.
Yeah, basically.
Yeah.
And it was great.
And I'll spare the details as a matter, but I went from my hometown of San Diego, my soon
to be ex-wife of San Diego.
You capped any motherfuckers?
I capped a few.
There were many instances.
Oh, one of my friends got scammed by a fake homeless person.
That was cool.
There were many people to cap.
There were many, there were many like, like unfortunate shadowy figures.
I assume you'd be, by that, you mean like TF2, like capture the flag like along the
way, just like capping territories and, you know, that's basically the case.
I mean, basically in between Los Angeles and San Francisco, there's, there's nothing
really of note other than Monterey, which we stopped in, but there's basically nothing
there.
So it was a lot of long driving and the only stop that we had on the second day while
we were going through that long, like five hour stretch of basic nothingness.
There was like a really like shit hard to describe tourist trap, which like, oh God,
it was like, it was, imagine a gift shop for a theme park and the theme park is themed
as the Wild West and it's only the gift shop and it's this really tacky antique shop.
The place is called Bravo Land.
It's called Bravo Land.
Look it up if you can.
Johnny Bravo Land?
Basically, Bravoville, the Bravilians call it, of course.
It's this antique shop, but the only antiques are literal trash.
I'm talking used soda bottles.
That kind of stuff is on display.
Well, some of those are collectibles, I guess.
For $10, you're going to get a used Dr. Pepper from 1980s.
Is that, is that worth $10?
If it's some kind of collectible to some, perhaps, I don't know.
Maybe, I don't know if that's the logic or not.
There were rusty wrenches.
There were like, there were just like logs of wood that you could buy.
Was there an old Nokia in there?
There's what?
An ancient Nokia pose.
No, there was no Nokia, unfortunately.
I would have just snapped that in a second.
That was great.
Here's the only thing I want to talk about about this.
Here's the only thing, is that I had a sequel to something that happened in Rome and something
that I want to talk about on this very podcast.
And that's, I fell back into my old, disgusting ways.
This was the Leaning Tower of Pisa 2.
The San Francisco Chinatown.
The Leaning Tower of Pisa 2, 9-11.
Basically.
Now there's two of them.
Listen, I didn't understand what the big deal was about 9-11,
but now I understand after a personal tragedy has happened to me,
I understand what it must be like to experience pain due to 9-11.
The San Francisco Chinatown.
I understand what it's like to experience pain, period.
It's a fucking nightmare.
The San Francisco Chinatown is a fucking nightmare.
Imagine the most generic tourist shops you can imagine.
Not anything themed towards China.
Just get your key chains here, San Francisco.
Oh, get your fucking giant's caps.
Who buys the generic New York tourist things?
Who buys, like, I love San Francisco.
Or who buys, like, giant shirts?
Like, who does this?
What kind of person to be?
The thing is, like, I actually asked myself that same question when I was in an airport.
And I thought, like, you know, they're marketing to the wrong people.
They're marketing to the tourists.
But, like, I think the people who would buy such things
was probably people living in those places because they have pride in where they live.
So I'm confused.
You can only buy so many pieces of merchandise.
What's the merchandise you live?
What's the merchandise we're talking about?
We're talking about really tacky touristy things that say I love San Francisco
and just have, like, pictures of California on them
and that are just, like, I mean, in every other place.
Well, here's the thing.
The people that live around there, they might buy, like, one shirt to rep for their hometown.
But the tourists, the tourists that want to show, like, how well-traveled they are,
that's a continually refreshing resource.
There's going to be more of those guys every fucking day.
Day!
Indeed.
I guess.
But I would totally buy an I Love Lafainia T-shirt.
Yeah.
Except no one would ever make such a garment under any circumstance.
I want to get, sometimes I think about getting, like,
sometimes I think about getting, like, a map of the Boston T-System, like, tattooed on me.
Dude, oh, okay.
I want to team up so much.
I'm looking at, like, right now I'm looking at a map of Boston that I got.
It's a really, like, cool, like, almost, like, three-dimensional, old-timey map.
And it's sick as hell.
I would totally get, like, Boston merch.
I'm way into that.
Dude, Ben, you remember when we were in the traditional center?
I would get one thing.
When we saw those, like, play toy, like, T-trains that you could, like, buy for, like, your kid?
I want, like, a full set of those.
Look at this, look at this link in the description to the fucking thing that Mae just posted.
Oh, shit!
Lithuania T-shirt.
Pretty sick.
Whoa!
Oh, my God.
Yeah, I want it.
Whoa!
That's, yeah.
That's sick as hell.
Hey, by the way, quick point.
Quick point, because we met new PCB character Grace last week.
My sister, who was on.
My sister.
She's mine, damn.
I'm sorry.
Who are you?
All right.
But the point, I was just, I said to Grace, as I said before, like, the one tattoo, and
speaking of tattoos, that I ever thought of even possibly getting, was, like, the Joe
Star Star on the Joe Star place on my shoulder.
Oh, wow.
And I just said to Grace, because she's a tattoo artist, and I just said to her, like,
Grace, I just, I'm just curious, like, has anyone ever asked you for, like, and I describe
it's on this exact spot, and she's like, like, one week ago, this guy comes into my shop
and gets this exact same tattoo.
And I was like, oh, I just felt the wind rush out of my face.
And you were just like, oh, yeah, yeah.
I mean, I mean, I'm sure you knew that you wouldn't be the only one.
But to have, to have, like, the first tattoo artist my sister, who I talked to, is like,
yes, this is extremely common.
You're a basic bitch.
You're not cool, Nate.
You're not interesting.
Your idea sucks.
I mean, come on.
You're talking about, like, a popular anime, right?
Like, a mark on a character's body.
A mark on a character's body.
Populars it is now.
God damn it.
I read the manga.
Which anime?
What anime?
Joe Joe's Bizarre Adventure.
Maybe you've heard of it, Mage.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, Joe Joe.
Yes.
Ah, whatever.
Okay, sorry, sorry.
Anyway, Munchy, finish your tale, please.
So Chinatown sucked, and it just was all that.
Right, right.
Also, a bizarre genre of store.
I don't even know how to describe it.
Like, money laundering ridden all over it.
It just is a marble statue store with no cash register and no one manning it.
Imagine you're on, like, a popular street, so just Chinatown.
You turn into a store, it's full of, like, bronze and marble statues,
and no one's inside of it.
I guess someone's gonna make those.
That is weird.
Oh my God, Mage, that's the coolest piece of merch.
Look at this fucking Lithuania basketball.
Is the world exploding?
No, it's being dunked.
It's being dunked.
This is like the Lithuania, like, actual Olympics basketball team jersey.
Look at these skeletons.
Oh, I love it.
Oh, the skull dots.
Holy shit.
That's crazy.
Did these represent Lithuania in some way?
Are skeletons integral to, like, the lore?
Or is it the origin story?
Basketball is like the second religion of Lithuania.
Are you serious?
They were one of Lithuania's original settlers, the skeletons, who played basketball.
I had no idea.
This second one was just the skeletons playing basketball.
This is like some big dog shit.
I think it's a variation of an original design in 1998 or something.
I'm not sure, but this is like the original.
It was really popular at that time, and people are bringing back it.
This is incredible.
Ridiculous.
I didn't...
Is it all...
Is that...
That's so weird.
I didn't know there were any European countries that gave a shit about basketball.
Yeah, I mean...
I wouldn't imagine.
I guess Lithuania...
Mage, you're known to be quite tall.
Are Lithuanians tall?
Is that why they play basketball?
I don't know.
I was pretty tall in comparison, but the guys were taller than me once they hit puberty,
so I guess we're kind of tall on average.
And we were pretty good too.
I see.
People who play basketball in Lithuania.
Yeah, I suppose there's probably some Norse genes going on.
They're Viking blood and whatnot.
They didn't even know to dunk.
I found out.
I learned a term.
I learned a historical term.
Fuck.
Lithuania is in the region called the Balkans, right?
No.
Baltics.
Fuck.
I always confuse those two.
Okay, nevermind.
Baltic is the sea.
Yeah, okay.
I see.
Balkans is the World War I.
I learned what the word balkanize means.
I think I'm thinking of...
It's like a...
Down in like a Middle Eastern, like Russian, like Turkey kind of region.
Balkanize a region means to divide it into mutually hostile states.
Huh, okay.
Yes, so that's something you don't want to happen.
Oh, like they did with India and Pakistan back in the day, right?
That's...
I guess so.
Okay.
And like, I think this is what happened to a lot of the former USSR.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, all right.
You go to Slavia.
I learned this.
I heard this word thrown around and now I know what it means and I feel intelligent.
Good job, man.
My IQ points.
I gained two IQ points.
Yeah, the Balkans, I'm pretty sure they're like in the southern part of your...
Let me see.
They are.
They're just north of Greece.
Looks like the Balkans are...
South of...
Slovenia, Croatia, Bosnia, Herzegovina, Serbia, Kosovo, Albania, Macedonia, Bulgaria, Romania.
Enough with the fucking geography lesson.
I'm sorry.
Let's get back to the epic meme story.
All right.
Okay.
Meme away, my friend.
We're actually learning something for once.
I hate learning and I love losing information.
Oh, and Montenegro.
Take it away.
I forgot Montenegro.
Everyone's favorite.
I start dancing for Nate's amusement.
That's right.
Tippity tap, tippity tap.
Cool.
Excellent.
Hey, by the way, as I said before, I'm leaving this house and I've built up such like a genuine
friendship with the people that staff my Chipotle.
They know me by name, by order.
I walked in to my Chipotle, my last visit and it seems like everyone was on staff.
There were like 20 people in the kitchen and that line for some bizarre reason.
It's like a small store and everyone like jumped up and said like, hey, double-stake
queso, double-stake quesos here.
I took my order.
They said, oh, like, oh, you're going to leave.
Oh, you guys, you got to come back.
Wait, wait, wait.
They call you double-stake queso?
They call me double-stake queso.
Like when I said that it was my last day, like everyone was like upset and sad.
They gave me my meal for free.
They said, like, come back as soon as you can.
Is that true?
Did they really do that?
No, no, I'm serious.
I'm 100% dead serious, Nate.
Hey, that's crazy.
I have an absolute kinship with Chipotle, with the Chipotle staff at my local venue.
And it's great.
The only family I've ever known is the only time I've really felt loved by another group
of people.
It's great.
Like, just like walking and having new people you've never talked to be like, hey, wait
a second, are you the double-stake queso guy?
I'm like, yeah, I am.
I am a double-stake queso guy.
Hey, hey, everyone, check it out.
It's that double-stake queso guy.
Literally, that's happened, man.
That's literally happened.
Like, oh, hey, guys.
It's double-stake queso.
He's here.
What a weird quirky order, double-stake and queso.
Are you kidding me?
Wait, I genuinely don't feel the audacity.
Why are you double-stake queso?
Because the frequency of my visits is because I'm such a regular.
They know me by heart.
They know my order by heart.
Because in fact, the order itself is significant.
The fact that it happens like every day.
Chipotle shares your cultural and genetic background, an ungodly mix of the white man
and the red man, and out comes double-stake queso onto God's green earth, offending us
all with his presence.
Anyway, that's what I call my dick.
But delighting us as well.
Gross.
Delighting our humor.
Our four humors.
I'll miss them so.
I'll miss them from the bottom of my heart.
The Chipotle's in the east coast are terrible.
They're abjectly terrible and are disgusting.
They're like...
No base for comparison.
They're so bad.
Yeah, I'll believe that.
I'll believe that.
West Coast Chipotle's are the way to go.
And I'm going to miss them.
The only family I've ever known that's upsetting.
Well, that's the end of that chapter, I guess.
Welcome to the east coast.
Well, I'll come back.
I'll get off the plane, I'll rush back into my Chipotle, and then I'll go to the grounds
where the Chipotle once stood.
And it's going to be like the dystopian wasteland from the end of Joe's garage.
Music is going to be outlawed.
Chipotle's going to be outlawed.
I'm going to have to eat a Chipotle burrito in my imagination because there's no more
burritos to be eaten.
It's going to be like a barren, like it's going to be like a junkyard.
It's going to be just like death and decay all around me and just brown, rusting pipes
where the Chipotle once stood.
And I'm going to beg God, I'm going to drop down my knee and start bawling.
I'm going to ask God for a burrito.
And it's going to be like, hey, is that double steak queso guy?
Hey, Jesus, go right, it's double steak queso guy.
Uh, sad.
I know, literally.
Ben, you were looking really rowdy on Twitter yesterday.
Uh, yeah, my hair was supposed to be purple, but it ended up pink.
Okay.
Yes, I have pink hair now.
Um, the, the, I kind of don't want to make it purple though, because when it's like
dark, it's like, kind of looks like it's not, like it looks like you kind of, you can't
even tell that it's purple unless you sort of look at it like in the right lighting.
And that means yourself, or did you go to like, uh, I did, I did it myself.
I did it myself.
Okay.
Maybe, maybe you had a professional do it.
Maybe it would look good.
Uh, well, I'm not going to fucking do that.
You kidding me?
Well, do I, what do I look like I'm fucking Mr. fucking money bags over here?
All right.
Uh, uh, when it looks, well, it's purple, it looks like an accident, so I might just
keep it pink.
I don't know.
You know, that's, that's fair.
But I mean, we have to address the elephant in the room that, that killer morale has never
been lower.
It has never been lower than right now.
No, no, no, it's not the image.
It's kind of pinkish purple.
It's like a symbol.
Maybe it's the symbol of unity.
No, that's a lie.
That's not.
Don't blow me on that.
It's the symbol of unity.
No unity.
So there is an unnamed, if you were to look at the chat, there's an unnamed individual
and I won't name any names.
He has pink hair.
He is looking at the camera aggressively.
He is breaking the law as vandalized a, a fire hydrant by posting a sticker claiming
that his heinous act of vaping is not a crime and he's wearing the smoking gun.
He's wearing a rowdy pride shirt.
Tell me.
That's not right.
It's a pajama pants on with Japanese kanji plastered all over it.
He's crouching in the middle of a darkly-lit suburb.
It's shiny as you raise this.
That's literally rowdy.
Tell me it's not right.
How's it not rowdy?
Ben, tell me how it's not rowdy.
Tell me how.
Okay.
Well, he's wearing this shirt.
Shut the fuck up.
You piece of shit.
He's wearing this shirt ironically and he didn't put that sticker there.
He found that sticker there.
Someone else had put it there and he, he felt a sense of camaraderie and he had to express
it.
This is the most rowdy image I've ever seen in my time.
That's my read.
This is my personal image.
I can see it in his eyes.
Listen, photographs are all about cultivation.
They're all about exclusion.
There he is.
Maze posted it.
Maze found it.
Ben, okay, so what has made you want to be a total fucking faggot?
A total fucking asshole.
Yeah.
I just, I thought it'd be funny.
Will the descent ever stop?
No.
Into madness.
I just, I'm uncovering new depths.
I'm uncovering new depths to sink to every single day.
Okay.
Wow.
This re-encouraging.
If I remember correctly, I think Ben has described wanting to do things of this nature
for a while.
Of course.
I wanted to, I wanted to do like a purple hair and killer thing, cop killer thing.
Right, right.
And then I ended up liking how the pink looked better.
It doesn't mean anything.
Yeah.
We'll see.
This is gonna be just a fucking killer piece of propaganda and the fact that you're not
denying it more vehemently and not rejecting it.
I did it purple and it was like, it's too dark.
I don't like how it looks.
Oh, it's too dark.
Did you hear that?
It's too dark.
I put more bleach in it thinking it would become a lighter purple, but it ended up,
but it ended up pink instead, like pink and purple swirl, like a fucking, like a cotton
candy swirl.
It reminds me too much.
It reminds me too much of, hey, hey, I don't like your girlfriend, reminds me too much
of that shitty pop singer.
I'm gonna go thrash, ladies and gentlemen.
I'll see you later.
I'm really a quote from Ben right now.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, get my fucking lawyers on the case.
Yeah, I will.
I'll kill them before you're able to call them.
Listen, have my people call your people and let them know that I'm supposed to be suing
you right now.
All right.
I'll have my people call your people and give them death threats over the internet.
We'll settle this.
We'll settle this on the court, on the basketball court, on the Lithuanian skeleton basketball
court.
Nate, I'm sure you know, you know about that Japanese lawyer that was so hardcore doxxed
and it was like a whole like needy of frenzy for a while?
I'm not sure.
No, I don't think I know what you're talking about.
His name escapes me.
I think it's Karasawa, I believe.
Anyway, it was a funny event in Japanese history.
Japanese internet goers are like the scariest fucking group of people, like basically like
ever.
I feel like if you were to offend like the Japanese like two-channel audience, like your
life could just be like over and like an instant.
So there's this Japanese lawyer who like, I don't know, was trying to defend some anon
on two-channel who was made fun of.
Anyway, he got so hardcore doxxed that people would go to his house every single day.
People were making like art of him and posting it everywhere in the city.
It was this whole like giant like media frenzy and it was crazy and Karasawa, here let me
see.
Let me see if I can find it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Karasaki, here.
One second.
I will post in just a moment.
But it's crazy that people are able to just like completely shut down like a person's
career.
God damn it.
Where is it?
Hold on.
I'm not fully following the story here.
Yeah, I need more information.
Me either, yeah, yeah.
What happened?
Who?
Where?
When?
Okay.
Some random douche was being bullied online.
He calls a lawyer.
Okay.
Yeah.
He calls a lawyer and the lawyer is like, hey, I'm going to sue two-channel and he posts
it on the web, on the forum.
Because he got bullied there?
No, yeah.
Well, not the person himself like he calls a lawyer and the lawyer steps in and posts
on two-channel.
Okay.
And then.
That's really funny.
The lawyer's identity is discovered.
And then people go on a trolling spree and docks the lawyer and the client, of course,
and just like makes a ton of art to ruin the reputation.
And it's a big, funny meme here at Google.
Okay.
I was not there.
I mean, the lawyer was just doing his job.
I mean, you know, okay, but didn't he do a stupid thing?
Didn't he do a stupid thing by saying he was going to sue two-channel?
Yeah.
Like, isn't that being bad at his job?
I mean, that's, look, a lawyer's job is not to know ahead of time if they're going to
necessarily win or lose any given case.
And like, I don't know, lawyers just do things that they think they have a chance of succeeding
at legally.
I don't know.
I don't have the same kind of, I don't know, animosity towards lawyers doing shit.
They're just trying to see what they can get away with according to the law.
I get being annoyed at like all the law shit, but, you know.
But it seems like, I mean, it seems like his goal was to take down two-channel, which is,
and it's really stupid.
So I can see why they would be like, they're defensive of their site.
And also they're like, look at this, look at this fucking clown thinking he can sue two-channel
over this.
I mean, what I would have, if it was me, I mean, you know, this is me, but I would have
allowed him to attempt this and then just fail because there's no grounds for this.
Well, I mean, they, well, they didn't stop him from doing it.
But they did, it sounds like they did far worse than that.
What exactly did they do?
What exactly did they do to destroy him?
So like, they defaced a family shrine of like a tomb of his family.
That's fucked up, man.
That's just illegal.
And they stalked him constantly, like they sent drones to his house to try and observe
him in old times and like constantly rang, like went to his house and tried to like talk
to him, like did like funny like worship of him, made him really uncomfortable.
And they posted like, like, like bizarre photos of him, like everywhere around the city, like
on like, like, like train stations and stuff like that.
They tried to make him famous.
Yeah.
It was a good old time.
No, that's a little too far.
I mean, like making fun of him online for being a dumb.
It's, it's quite excessive on, and you know, I mean, I don't know, people are silly about
it, but like, even when you do things by the letter of the law, it can still be morally
wrong and like not a cool thing to do, you know, sounds like some of the things they
did were illegal.
Other things.
I don't know.
I get it.
They're defensive of the site.
They don't give a fuck.
A lot of people on 4chan and 2chan or whatever are very nihilist minded.
Fair.
I understand.
You could expect these sort of things.
And lol, it's funny that bad things happen to them as a consequence.
I'm with you.
I mean, I wouldn't want a fucking family shrine to face.
Yeah.
But you mess with the bull, you get the testicles.
I guess.
It would have been okay if they just sort of made fun of him, but then doxing him and
stalking him and then the shrine thing, that's a little too much.
Well, I mean, I mean, of course, yeah.
Well, did they dox him?
I mean, he must have doxed himself if they found out who he was.
Well, he probably was like, hi, I'm this lawyer and I'm fucking gunna sue you or whatever.
Well, yeah, but his home address was not publicly known.
Well, I mean, it sounds like I have, I bet it was publicly available.
Like if he knew his family shrine was to though and include that information in his post, I
mean, probably not, right?
Probably not.
No, probably not.
Well, okay.
Nonetheless, we don't know the details.
Who knows exactly how bad or good it was, but very funny.
I'm going to go with 100% good.
Yeah.
I think that's the default state that everyone should go to for any event.
You know, just assume that it was a blanket positive.
Since all morality derives from religion and we've proven that God is fake, I'm going
to call this 100% good thing that happens.
What does this mean?
What is this new like line that you're parroting then?
What did thought slime say that once and now it's the new thing you're saying?
Yeah, he said it and I was like, wait a minute, wait a minute, there's no God.
I can do anything I want to do.
And then I started smoking weed and now I'm a libertarian.
Wow, that's a great story.
It's just that easy, folks.
It's just that easy.
You know, you never know.
And a little things going to come along when you're going to take a bite and change your
life.
You know, speaking of all this Japanese defacing of family graves and whatnot, I got to tell
you, the last samurai global box office smash hit from 2003 starring Tom Cruise is a real
roller coaster ride.
Ladies and gentlemen, I highly recommend.
Boy, this is a fucking timely review.
Yeah.
Just in time.
I was just thinking about should I watch last samurai?
I mean, I'm talking about I'm talking about a hundred and forty million budget of four
hundred and fifty eight point eight million dollar box office intake.
Just just excellent work, everybody.
Warner Brothers pictures are really knocked out of the park.
Fantastic.
I can't watch a nobby commanding performance.
This could be a big break for for this up and coming young star Tom Cruise.
I hope to see more of him.
Hope to see more of him in the future.
I hope he boxes Justin Bieber and that that happens.
Did that happen?
Pretty cool.
Justin Bieber tweeted that he wants to in the style of these YouTubers who have been doing
fights for entertainment, he wants to fight Tom Cruise, you know, in the ring.
Because Tom Cruise is like 70.
Yeah.
Yeah, recently.
I mean, I think Tom Cruise would kick his ass personally, but you know, what do I know?
I don't know.
He's like a hundred years old.
Let's see how old Tom Cruise is.
Just for fun.
He's got the church on the side, dude.
He's got Scientologists.
He's going to drink like some like secret potion.
He's going to become the whole.
He's at least 60.
Tom Cruise is 57.
Oh, wow.
Okay.
And Justin Bieber is probably like 25.
So like prime of his life, obviously.
I still got to put it on Tommy.
I think Tom would have some.
I mean, they're both.
They're both.
They're both manlets.
Absolutely true.
He's going to get some like 11 year olds to like a bath and some sort of like spirit
cooking pot event.
He's going to drink.
He's going to drink some of their essence.
And then he's going to grow tin sizes and become a literal God and destroy.
Ken Watanabe literally surgically implanted the spirit of the samurai into Tom Cruise
during 2003.
Smash it.
The last samurai wet, which can I can I just remind got over 300 million dollars in
profits at the box office.
Just incredible work, everybody.
Got to give it to a Han Zimmer for that score.
Read our pictures.
The Bedford Falls Company.
Cruise Wagner Productions.
Everybody just did such a fantastic job.
This is my timely review.
The last samurai.
Good work, everybody.
I was going to say, speaking of Thought Slime, everyone's on the Thought Slime train now.
Hippos on it.
Jesse's on it.
Everyone.
Soon we're all going to be.
I'm going to convert the whole piece.
That's the entirety of the world right there.
I'm going to convert the whole PCP to a narco communism.
OK, but my contrarian nature does not allow this.
I will not consume any Thought Slimes.
Well, I'm sorry.
You're going to be left behind in the revolution.
Good.
Prepare to have your fucking.
Oh God, what's the word?
Prepare to have the have your means of production seized.
Is there any place in this lonely old anarcho communist world for an anarcho capitalist just
trying to make a buck?
Yeah, in a fucking grave.
It is the place.
Tom Cruise looks like Keanu Reeves in the poster for the last samurai.
This guy looks so like.
OK, tell me it's not true, Nate.
Tell me he's not the last samurai.
Tell me there's more.
There's hope for man.
Even even now there has to be hope for man.
Well, you know, interestingly, the last samurai focuses on how Tom Cruise is not in fact.
Well, he kind of was the last samurai standing at the end of the film.
I guess I'll spoiler alert.
It's about the transition from the the way of the samurai from Japan incorporating like
1870 and whatnot, more like Western technology and the emperor being all up on up on that
business.
But then Tom Cruise, a lonely old soldier from the Indian uprisings in America and the
Civil War and whatnot.
It's about him addressing the sins of his past and finding comfort in the ways of the
Eastern samurai warrior and learning to quiet his mind in times of tumult.
Is this really just a parallel to your life, Nate?
Is it the big screen?
Yes, the answer is yes.
God, I hope so.
This lonely soy boy twink roaming around the streets of America begging for a cock to suck.
It's shipped off a cargo crate to Japan and just learns the way of the of the of the piston
punch is able to become a full blooded samurai and make YouTube dollars like no one king
or emperor had ever seen before.
Oh, you know, I don't know.
I suppose this is whatever it doesn't.
It's just that there's something real.
There's something like it's it's you feel there's a hopelessness.
The movie ends with the samurai just being like, yep, our time's up.
Samurai are done.
So we're just going to go fight and then we'll all die.
And Tom Cruise who became a samurai, you know, whatever.
He became one of the peeps during the thing.
He became fell in love with their ways.
He like everybody else died except for him.
So he is, I guess, the last one and everyone else is like, yeah, that's it.
Samurai are done.
But oh, there was beauty in their simple lives.
Oh, there was there was a there was a humble, these noble savages.
Ain't nobody calling them noble savages.
They're just noble, Ben.
They're just noble.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah, I it's been a long time.
It's been a long time.
Some people have called this like a white savior film.
It could not be further from the truth.
It's about how the white man could learn so much from the East and how they're better than us.
And now I need my samurai sword to cut down these filthy Western enemies of God's creation,
a.k.a. the samurai and God, I could not be more on board.
Wait, no, they fucking lose the war, right?
Like Tom Cruise just gets absolutely like gunned down by like the like new invention of
the tide of history turning slowly against them.
Yep.
Yeah.
But there's there's beauty to be found in that history.
Oh, it's beautiful.
I fucking love it.
That's so good.
That's it.
PCP is over.
Nate says like playing off his his kabuki armor.
And his beetle off my armor.
Nate Bestman is the last podcaster.
Listen, everyone's going fucking VR.
Everyone's going on hologram.
Yeah, they're just getting they're just getting auto directed like like like via syringe
directly into their fucking eyeball.
No one's got time for podcast anymore.
We can't fight the tide of history, man.
We all know the way of the future is Internet drama, Internet blood sports, you know, etc.
But I sit here making my humble whittling away bit by bit in my humble anime reviews and
I will not cease.
I will let history crash around me as I stand against the tide because I would rather die
on my feet than die on my knees as a slave.
That's how I am.
And that's how it will go for me.
Remember me, the last anime reviewer on YouTube.
Games upon video essay.
Clicked new track over a thousand times just completely completely made into a mirror shine
polished into oblivion.
And I will slice down any of the naysayers.
Point being, I just watched The Last Samurai before recording this episode of the PCB and
it was a great time.
Highly recommend.
I can't tell if The Last Samurai is like genuinely good or if it's just actually good.
I'll let you know what the difference between those is never.
I actually had like ten minutes left but I gotta say, you know what's funny, here's
my little bit more of a review.
I could not have loved this movie more.
It was absolutely fantastic.
But like it ends with, so like the thread going up through the background is that like
America wants to do an arms deal with Japan and Tom Cruise has brought over to like train
the Japanese soldiers in the western ways or whatever.
And like that's all fine.
Then it becomes a samurai later.
But like the idea is that like Tom Cruise decides to join like the honorable samurai who are
defending like the ancient ways of Japan.
And like they know that history is going against them.
But like we can't forget who we are like Japan, you know, whatever we've got the spirit.
We can't just be cut by the west or whatever.
But like it ends with the emperor just being like, they were cultivating this whole deal
between Japan and an American weapon or whatever.
And just like, nah, fuck it.
At the end he's like, I am convinced by these samurai who all died in defense of their ways.
Like we can't forget that we are Japanese.
So I guess that means we won't use modern technology and we won't progress.
And I'm like, is that really the lesson to take away?
I didn't learn anything.
That's kind of like, I'm with you.
Like remember the spirit of Japan.
Don't forget who you are.
That's all fine.
But like you got to buy new weapons to like defend yourself.
So what have we learned here?
Like they did.
So it's weird that it's like painting as though it didn't happen.
I don't really understand exactly what the point of it is.
I guess just don't forget the spirit of Bushido or whatever, which is pretty cool.
Yeah, I wish I was a samurai.
That's how I feel.
Living a simple life.
I think we can all learn something from 2003 is the last samurai.
And about Tom Cruise's role in the history of Japan.
Directed by Edward Zwick.
Is that kind of fucked up?
That like Japan was wiped off the face of the earth because they weren't able to like buy new weapons
because Tom Cruise stopped them from participating in the Meiji Restoration like in 1870.
Isn't that fucked up, guys?
Isn't it fucked up that in America their invention of the guilty gear system nuked all of Japan
and no survivors were reigned afterward?
That sucked.
That was too bad.
I think I saw a lecture about that.
I think so.
One historical document.
It is Tom Cruise's soul bad guy.
I think we can pretty much all agree.
Is Tom Cruise Tom Oliver and he single-handedly destroyed Japan?
God, I wish.
Well, there you go.
There's my review of the last samurai.
Speaking of goddamn movies that we saw.
Alright, here's the bombshell that I want to drop here.
I'm going to spin a yarn here because it is like the lowest point of my entire life.
I did something really bad.
I did something like naughty.
I did something that I'm going to have to get on my hands and I'm going to have to confess to you guys.
I saw the live action line king movie and I know.
No, how dare you pay for that.
I know.
Listen, this is a mistake.
That's human core.
Seeing Disney remakes is the most human core thing you can do.
No, seeing them is fine.
It's paying for them to see them.
They're both wrong in their own way.
Listen.
Okay.
Here's I want to paint a picture for you.
It's the last day of my trip in San Francisco.
This is the last moment that I'll be able to have in San Francisco.
So far, it's been a wash, really.
I mean, the piers were nice.
The fishmen's worth were nice, but I didn't really get a sense of anything truly local.
It just felt like a bunch of tourist traps.
And Chinatown the previous day was the epitome of that.
It was just completely just four numbskulls come in here, spend a lot of money and then get out.
There was nothing of actual substance inside of it.
Sure.
The next day, we're walking across the city.
We see a lone movie theater and we see the lion king is playing.
It's about, you know, maybe four or five.
We get seats.
We watch the lion king.
It's a nightmare.
And, you know, we ha ha chuckle about how bad it is.
You know, we think that we've made a fine decision in watching a movie that was bad for the sake of just joking about it.
And then we vowed to watch the original.
Big mistake.
And then we walk to what was the point of that day.
For you see, we wanted to check out Chinatown's sister, Japan Town, because we thought there would be a great time.
Wait, is that a real thing?
It's completely real.
What town is this in?
San Francisco.
You have a Japan Town?
Yeah, Japan Town.
Do they do they frequently perform Nanking reenactments on Chinatown?
Are they next to each other?
Oh, God.
Tensions are high.
They're actually separated for fear of riots, so, you know, they're separated by people.
Race war!
So, so, so we get out the lion king.
We had just spent $14 to see live action lion king, the sun setting.
And San Francisco, if you guys don't know, it's vertical.
It's a TF2 map.
It's a quick green map.
It's vertically integrated.
Literally.
It's a vertical slice.
There are vast mountains we must climb up to to get to our destination.
We're crawling up talking about how John Oliver Azazi was so bad.
Seth Rogen is poomba was so bad.
We're walking.
And so far, we're just twiddling our fucking thumbs.
We've wasted our time here in the city.
We get to Japan Town, ready to have some fun.
We're ready to, hopefully, Japan Town to live up to the promise of what we thought China Town would be.
We're here to save the trip.
It's closed.
Every single shop in Japan Town is closed.
Just like Japan after they dropped the bomb.
I mean, by that, I mean, Guilty Gear happened and Japan was wiped off the map.
Literally.
So, we're rushing through.
We're seeing, oh, used anime VHS store.
We're seeing cool, like, manga book stores that we've got inside, too.
We're seeing all these little food like sushi stands we could have gone into.
We're seeing all these things that we would have loved to see.
We're seeing all these things that we have spent an entire day inside of.
Just this one little mall in Japan Town.
And we gaze upon the iconic Japan Town Tower Pagoda thing.
You can Google search.
And when you Google search, like, it seems to go to Japan Town, there would be like a needle looking thing.
We looked upon that.
And we saw, and we thought, we wasted our time in San Francisco watching the live action Lion King.
That was what we spent today doing.
That's what we spent our last day doing was, was paid money for our own bondage, was paying money for Disney
to monopolize more and more and more and to enslave us instead of actually living our lives.
I already ruined the trip to San Francisco.
And as we laid there, depressed, sobbing on the floor for our own mistake,
it's no one's fault but ourselves that this calamity was done to us.
We sit there and we think, and we think to ourselves that even now there's hope for man.
Don't say this is how it has to be.
And then the next day, we had our steely American resolve, our steely Japanese resolve.
We were the way of the samurai.
We were, at that point, the last samurai looking.
The tide of history, us going home, it cannot clash upon us.
The spirit flowed into you, giving you power.
And did you know, Munchy, that when a samurai, according to the Code of Bushido,
I think I said this last time, but when a samurai rides into battle,
he considers himself already dead as it makes him deadlier.
And I'm sure you felt the same way beginning your mission that day.
And so we woke up extremely early.
The crack of dawn, like seven, we got out to the city
and we spent our final moments before we were set to leave.
And keep in mind, this is a torturous drive.
This is like a seven hour drive to our destination.
We had to have left as soon as possible or else we would be dead tired by the time we got there.
If you could factor in stops and stuff like that, you know, do the bathroom.
So we had to get in there and out.
And we willingly flogged ourselves and made it to Japan Town
in time for everything to open.
And we spent a few cursory moments looking over the anime VHS store and the manga store.
It didn't, we was saved. We saved the trip.
You did it.
And at, I believe it's called like Sakura Books or something in that effect,
I bought the first volume of One Piece.
And I'm starting my journey.
Of course.
One of these days, I will become a ship captain.
Like I guarantee you.
The journey, the fact that you, oh my God, that honestly, that's an inspiring story.
You persevered and you did not give up on your quest despite all the hurdles you face.
And what did you get?
What was your prize for pursuing this and obtain your goal?
It was the greatest prize of all, the beginning of yet another new journey.
Adventure, yes.
That's what could be better.
And that's why that's how One Piece is going to end.
Mark my words with the beginning of a new adventure because that's what life is about people.
It's about pursuing your goals and find fulfillment in doing so.
That's how the samurai lived.
And that's how you live, Munchy.
And as the last samurai myself, I'm happy to dub you.
My samurai for life.
Welcome.
Welcome to the club.
Oh my God, honorary samurai.
This is like the reverse of what we were talking about at the beginning.
This is callbacks.
This is true narrative stakes.
This is it.
Yes.
It's happening.
It's Ghazam Kutsverk of epic proportions.
They're going to get to the monopoly, the anarcho-capitalism island.
And then Luffy's going to get up and he's going to watch live action Lion King.
And that's how One Piece is going to end.
Incredible.
Well, Munchy, I could not be happier to hear.
You know, people talk, even me, you know, when I'm week to week, me and Gib doing the
potty cast, we get all wrapped up and like, what's happening right now in these chapters?
Actually, when we do the potty cast, you guys probably don't listen because you're not on
the latest chapter or anything.
I wouldn't know.
But like, we can be very critical of like, what's happening on any given chapter, especially
considering reading chapter to chapter is kind of the most critical way.
Cause you're like, is the thing that happens next going to live up to our expectations?
Is like, like, is this art going the way we want?
We can be very critical.
But every time I look back and read like any section of One Piece, if there's a reason
why I do it every week, it's the only thing I talk about every single week because it
has brought me the most joy of anything I've been involved in my life.
And I'm such just a humbled fan to be able to, I don't know, talk about and share it
with people like you and other people who I've had the honor to get into One Piece
through listening to the stuff I've said about it.
So I'm just, I'm so happy for you.
And I'm so, whatever, you don't owe me anything.
You don't owe anybody enough that you could hate it.
And that's fine too.
But it just very, makes me very happy to hear.
I mean, so far I'm obviously only a chapter in, but just the art itself is a loan for
me to want to keep watching.
It only gets better.
I mean, I believe you.
It's so different.
It's not, it's not your, like, I don't know, we all, there's a lot of discussion in anime
circles about how like anime all looks the same.
It's all the same.
One Piece is so unique.
It's such a unique style and a lot of people don't like it, but I love it.
People don't like it because it doesn't look, it doesn't, doesn't really look like anime.
It kind of looks like a, I feel like the Otis art style has sort of like a kind of French
Belgian-ish kind of look to it a little bit.
Yeah, I see that actually.
I know what you mean by that.
Yeah.
I think I know what you mean.
But it's very cartoony and, you know, sort of proportion sometimes and whatnot.
Well, whatever, man.
Yeah, I could go on all day about One Piece if I don't want to lecture anybody about it.
I'm just very happy to hear that you're, you're, you're getting on the bus, getting on the
boat.
If you're ever in a new location, here's my advice to you.
And I said this advice before, but I need to reiterate because even myself, I forgot.
Don't go anywhere just because other people go to it.
Have a reason.
If you have a reason to go to Chinatown, if you look up on Google Maps and there's like
a cool restaurant you want to go to, by all means go to Chinatown.
But don't just go there, you know, because it is the thing to do.
Because you're going to get fucked up and you're not going to be able to learn the joys
of whatever your town's equivalent to Japan town is.
There's surely a cooler place you could be going to than something that everyone else
already has.
Probably true.
Easily.
Easy.
Easy fucking peasy.
Well, what a journey.
What a Japan-centric episode.
My favorite kind.
God, I want to play Sekiro again.
Sekiro is the greatest game ever made.
I love Japan, period.
And that's all there is to say about it.
But by the way, also in Japan town, I got a manga that's exclusively in Japan and I can't
read it.
It's a Kirby manga that wasn't released in the West.
Oh, fascinating.
She should put a picture up somewhere.
Yeah, sure.
I will.
Because I can't Google it.
I will take a picture and I will put in the show notes.
Fantastic.
Hey, I have a left turn topic I wanted to bring up that's a total other thing.
Before we switch topics, I just noticed an odd little pattern.
It has absolutely no meaning.
But everyone, all the PCP members currently in the chats, the exception of then has a
six in their Discord number.
And I just noticed that and I thought that was kind of funny.
Fascinating.
Yep.
Once again, I'm the odd man out.
I'm the lone.
I'm the champion.
Oh my God.
Majest number is the...
I don't know if I should say the number, but I will say that it includes 666, just in
the thing.
Is that a coincidence?
What's up with that?
That's weird.
Well, now they only have to try 10 different combinations.
Wait, no.
40 different combinations.
No, there's...
I mean, the thing is, I don't add people if I don't know them.
So, you know, even if they do...
Well, hang on.
Surely there's more than, you know, 9,999 or I guess 10,000 people on Discord.
Well, here's my logic.
I mean, you're Discord...
Yeah.
Wait, you're right.
But your Discord number is only four numbers, right?
I think the name is like relevant somehow.
Like the name is incorporated in your...
The thing is, people can't really add me due to the heart and my name.
Yeah, right.
Oh, yeah, that too.
That too.
The purple heart protects me.
Purple heart.
Just like John Kerry, protected him from losing the presidential election.
Oops, that didn't happen.
Moving on.
Sad.
Listen to this.
I've got five words that I was just thinking of as a result of a recent experience that
I will describe briefly, and it's that magic is IRL...
Oh, sorry, sorry.
Music.
Music is IRL magic spells.
Music is a lot like love.
It's all a feeling.
And it fills the room from the floor to the ceiling.
It does.
Is that what you're saying?
That's basically what I'm saying.
Music is pure magic.
Okay, cool Curb of Manga.
She just uploaded it.
So I was just thinking about this, and this pertains to all media.
But I was just thinking about this.
This is probably a really obvious observation, but I felt it very powerfully the other day
because I've been watching with a pretty strong interest Digi's like top 100 anime openings
that he's been doing because Digi is actually...
This is one of the things that I really like to listen to Digi talk about.
Frank, I'm not that interested in like his music takes necessarily, but obviously we overlap
in anime and I care about that.
But like Digi's taste is very different from like your average like watch mojo top 10 anime
opening, like whatever.
Like I was watching, I commented on his video that just had all the openings and like the
opening to, and this is the song I wanted to bring up, Gunslinger Girls is this song
Light As We Land by the Delgados, which I had never heard before.
I've never seen Gunslinger Girl, but like I was instantly transfixed and like, damn,
that song is really dope.
And so when Digi, he's doing like in breakups of 20 at a time, he's like talking about them
each individually.
And I'm really enjoying it.
At least like skipping around to the ones I like because it was a lot of fun.
And like when he gets to this one, this is the one I was most interested in.
And he just talks about how like actually this song is the first track on the album
Hate by the Delgados.
And it's actually, it's one of it, like he loves the album.
And this is actually one of his least favorite songs on the album.
And so I was immediately like, well, I need to go listen to this fucking album because
the song is incredible.
But I had that most optimal experience for enjoying music, which was I was on a drive
at night in summertime, windows down, wind in my face, cranked up this song in my ears
as like I'm just looking at like the lights of the city passing by as I'm driving by.
And this song, Light As We Land by the Delgados, go listen to it.
It sounds like the soundtrack one plays while you're committing suicide.
That's what it sounds like, only not in like funny like, I want to die like shit zoomer
way, but like the old, you know, doomer way of like life is crushing me.
Classic suicide.
Classic suicide because it's about the pain of life not touching you.
This is what I understand.
Did you describe it?
It's about how while you're floating in a happy state of mind, not focused on the bad
things of life, but that the light as you land that fades as you come crashing back down
to reality.
Now this sounds a lot like suicide.
Yes.
Sorry.
That's the only anime song I know.
Hey, no problem.
It's the only one that matters.
Here's my point.
To get back to my point, I absolutely love the song.
I'm going to go listen to this album hate.
I can't wait to go listen to it because if it's as good as did you seem to be implying,
it's going to be incredible.
I was listening to the song and I'm like, music is the strongest magic known to man
because it just has this quality of like, I think about like the people who write music
like Bach or, you know, any modern band, the Degades who made this song, they sit down
and they like work on riffs and they work on notes and they work on lyrics and they
work on chords and all that shit.
And they're literally weaving a magic spell and this spell has the effect on me.
Someone who's basically music illiterate.
I know a little bit.
Not very much.
I play more guitar later, which has been a lot of fun as a result of Digi's thing and
other stuff.
Cool.
Yeah.
I've been having a great time.
I was actually playing, I was practicing another song from that.
What is it?
Hit in the USA by someone I can't remember, but it's the opening theme to Beck.
Mongolian chop shop or whatever.
Squad.
I don't know.
It's a hard ass rock song and I fucking love that opening.
It's dope.
I have a pedal so I can sound really hardcore and overdrive and whatnot.
Okay.
It doesn't matter.
Point was I was saying like these people, they're like witches concocting a witch's
brew.
They're throwing in there their eye of newt, thrown in their leg of virgin, they're throwing
in their period blood of menstruating mother.
I don't know.
They're throwing in all kinds of weird components and the result is on the other side, people
like me who don't understand music theory basically at all.
And I don't know.
Like we're just totally ignorant to the process.
Nonetheless, it has such a powerful effect.
It just, it's as such a, I don't know, it just makes me feel all kinds of things that
I don't even understand exactly why I feel them.
And this is true of like all media, but it strikes me that like music is like the most
effective because you don't have to have any lyrics.
Yeah.
Music also is like, it can be quite manipulative, not necessarily in a bad way, but sometimes
in a bad way.
Yeah.
And like certain scenes and let's say movies, they wouldn't be as powerful or impactful
or like a tear-jerkingly without the music gets really underrated on us.
I think a lot about Anthony Fantano once said, somebody asked him on one of his Q&A's
like, or one of his ask, whatever, let's argue, I think something like music is overrated
as like a, like a medium or whatever, like, I don't know, like something like video was
better or like music would be nothing without video.
Something like that.
And, and he just said like, think about if you watched your favorite movie without the
soundtrack.
And you know, I was, I was thinking about that as I was watching like The Last Samurai,
it's got a great score, Hans Zimmer and all that.
I was just thinking if the exact same things were happening, I had all these emotions.
I loved the character so much and it was so badass and it got me so invested in like the
way of like this, these humble Japanese samurai just wanting to honor their way of life and
their ancestors.
I was like, I feel you guys, I feel you in a big way.
But if you, if you just play that exact same movie without the soundtrack, I think it would
have, I think I would have been like, I mean, fuck these guys, like time to get, you know,
get with the times, your way is over idiots, gotta buy guns, gotta put down the bow and
arrow, pick up a fucking gun, you're, you're idiots.
Another really interesting thing about the music is a timely lack of music can be just
as impactful as having music in certain other times.
At the right time for sure.
Yeah, exactly.
Absolutely true.
But like, you know, if it was like lack of music throughout the whole thing, it wouldn't
be as impactful.
So it has to be like, like perfectly placed lack of music, I would say.
It's like, I just watched, I was watching a demo, Demolition D, Twitch stream the other
day and it was streaming, or Twitch or whatever, it was streaming Kill Bill Volume 1 and like,
the fight against Oren Ishii after the crazy eight fight is incredible.
And oh my god, that fight is so sick against Oren.
Like this, this like Spanish Latin cover of Don't Let Me Be Misunderstood starts playing
and it's the fucking sickest shit of all time.
And I would actually, I use that exact song in Gurren Logan part two review.
I use it like the hypest moment because it is like the hypest song of all time.
But like, and after, at the end, when Oren finally gets like a hit on Beatrix or whatever,
like the song cuts and then you just have like the two of them kind of stumbling around
in silence and like this, once again, beautiful like Japanese courtyard with like the snow
falling and just these two women, you know, due unto the death, but like it's dead silence.
And then they just like this, the hum of the swords and whatnot.
It's, I don't know, I just after this experience driving, listening to the song and just like
feeling like, like why am I feeling so many powerful emotions right now, listening to
the song that I don't even really understand what it's about.
I was like, this is a magic spell.
This is a modern day magic spell.
I don't understand what's going on.
Isn't it strange that the human body has such a reaction to music?
It is strange.
Because because like what?
Why do we have it?
Yeah, what exactly?
I understand like, for instance, like like pictures or, you know, like stories because,
you know, we can relate to them and we can understand language and we can understand
what it's like to like have emotions displayed by like text and ideas being communicated
to us.
Yeah.
But why do we get ideas from something abstract as noise?
Because like, I understand why something may like shock you.
I like like like like a symbol may jurt you like because a loud sound noise would be
evolutionary beneficial for you to like be alert at someone's coming to get you.
But why are we soothed by certain things?
Why are we like like brought to to feel like a triumphant music?
Why can we understand the emotion of music when like those things don't
like appear in nature or I can't imagine they have a theory.
Sure.
It's like, in a way, actually, it kind of goes with a with a topic I was thinking
about bringing in about like universal sort of symbols in a way, how like a lot of people,
at least in a lot of cultures, let's say red would be a color of danger or passion.
You know, stop signs of red.
It's a very bright color.
It's the color of blood.
It's the color of like it's so bright and a lot of poisonous creatures are
brightly colored and maybe they use red.
I haven't checked out how many of them use red.
But yeah, so it's music is sort of like, you know, a sound version of that in a way
because it might be sort of mimicking like sort of like a sounds or noises that
like represent certain sort of emotions like how red is passionate.
And scary.
So you have noises, something like that.
And like if you combine, let's say, blue with white, you can maybe paint
some clouds in the sky and it's it looks like a bright sunny day, but you can also
paint ice and it'll be cold and snowy.
So music, certain sounds, you combine them together and they can create
different types of moods.
You know, Majaba's thinking that too.
But the thing is, like you bring up the color example and like colors do exist in nature,
obviously.
So like humanity had a long time to like adjust to thinking certain
things about different colors and whatnot.
But like the thing is like music, as we understand it, is not something that
really occurs in nature outside of like animal cries or like like the like, I
don't know, the major chords.
Where do they appear in nature?
You know, I don't know much about course.
Like I'm just, you know, this is just me speculating and guessing like at the
moment I haven't done research about it.
I have a theory, though.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, I think I think most people would probably agree.
But it's like, I think that music, as we understand, it's easy to be like music
exists now, like where did it come from?
Like surely like something like taught it to us as humans.
I just think that as the process of civilization has progressed, like music
is literally we've discovered brain hacks that just some sounds just for
basically pure coincidental reasons, some sounds just sound good to the human
ear and the human brain.
And like we're kind of doing revisionist history if we think that like there's
really any explanation for why what we perceive to be music, like is the thing
that sounds good or bad or whatever.
I think that we just have categorized things that we basically discovered by
accident, by trial and error as humanity has just progressed.
I think music is another form of communication in a way, like a very
primitive one, like how, you know, certain voices to us like sound good, like a
calm voice is nice and gentle.
And then if someone's yelling, then you know, that's dangerous.
So music is sort of the same way.
Maybe it's like to convey like a sense of danger, a sense of calmness.
You know, that's true too.
Like there's a reason why in like rock songs, like obviously it doesn't
really inform you in terms of like chord structure, whatever, if someone's like
yelling versus whispering.
So I totally agree.
Music is like a combination of these two things.
I think like like music theory specifically, like that's the kind of
thing I'm saying is like specific like note progression from note to note or
whatever, evoking like a certain, like a minor chord sounding sad.
That's not something that occurred in nature.
I think that's something that we've just like figured out and then
documented.
And now we just, you know, we all like kind of are aware that a minor kind of
sounds sad or anything like that.
I think it's just music could be like a transformative thing of the sounds we
actually have heard and trying to mimic.
How like, I like to sing how people said like, oh, you know, they looked at a
bird one time and then they decided to make a plane.
So music is sort of like that.
They heard a noise and they decided to sort of mimic it, but in their own
different spin, spin off of that sort of noise.
So something sad sounding that they sounded sad, they tried to mimic it with
music or like, you know, making a noise similar to it and then integrated into
music.
I definitely think that's part of it.
It's interesting you bring up a minor, Nick.
Did you hear about a minor?
No.
He grew up.
He was sexually assaulted.
I don't like that.
I was waiting for that.
Kill me.
No, I love puns.
I was waiting for that.
That was good.
If we want to move on, I have to have a move on.
Yeah.
No, no worries.
Okay.
I just, I remembered this in the middle of this and I've been bursting to get it
out.
This is incredible.
Okay.
American listeners.
Right.
And actually, Munchie and Nate, this is true of you too.
Oh no.
American listeners.
I am about, and maybe you'll know what I'm talking about, I am about to make you
$125.
Do you know what this is?
No.
I think I did hear you discussing this somewhere, but go on.
American listener, you can just fucking send, okay.
So there was this thing, this company Equifax leaked a bunch of data and there was a settlement.
And like, if your data was, and like 147 million Americans were, if your data was leaked by Equifax,
you are entitled to $125.
You can get it.
So I'll put a link in the description.
If there's a link, it takes you to a thing.
You just put in like your name and like part of your social security number.
It will tell you like, yes, you were affected or not.
And if you were, you just fill in your information and Equifax will send you a check for $125.
I'll do that.
I'm speaking of data leaks.
There's also, you can also, if you, there's more like, if you, if you, you can say like,
I mean, I doubt this would apply to anyone, but like, if you spent time like, like doing stuff,
like if it costs you like labor hours, you can like apply for like some more for that.
But like, okay, there's, there's the possibility, like if, if everyone in the world,
like, like if, if everyone like files for this, there might be a run on it and like,
because like the total settlement amount is only like, I think it's like $380 million.
So if like everyone files for it, like, you know, it might, the number might go down.
There might not be, yeah, the number might be reduced, but I don't know.
Who knows if that'll happen.
So yeah, a fucking link in the description.
Get in there fast, I guess.
Yeah.
Well, I don't know if it's fast.
I think it's just going to end up being like the total number of, of, of however many people
file a claim.
And I don't, and I don't know how much longer there is to do it.
But yeah, I saw, I saw a tweet from AOC about this and I was like, huh, and I followed it up.
And yeah, I'm fucking eagerly awaiting my $125 check and you should too.
And letting me know in the comments if it, if it works.
So some people, some people.
Yeah.
Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, Senator from New York.
Some people might represent it.
I think she's a senator.
No, no, no, she's a Congresswoman.
Congresswoman.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Okay.
Congresswoman.
Some people might think like, oh, Nate corporate cocksucker, but I could not be more
okay and totally cool with something like this.
Anyone who abuses their authority or abuses their power absolutely should be held accountable.
And so yeah, I'm gonna fucking do this.
Sounds fair to me.
I want to, I want to quickly mention or rather ask, have you got like, okay, today is 28th.
Have you guys heard about like the supposed discord raid on the 27th that was supposed
to happen yesterday?
No, no, like several weeks, uh, uh, leading up to like today or yesterday, I guess, um,
I keep, I kept hearing shadows and whispers.
I was like, oh, there's going to be a raid.
Is there's going to be a dox?
There's going to be hacking.
There's going to don't delete the PCP discord server, delete it right now.
We have to burn the evidence.
Don't, don't.
Yeah.
Basically just like, don't accept any friend requests.
Don't, don't click any suspicious links from your friends and stuff like that.
You know, everyone's just like, oh, I'm sorry.
But you know what I got?
You know what I got this morning in the PCP mail?
You know what we got?
Labs, we got two subsequent emails that were from, I looked at this, they're from a URL
that's like, it's like YT, they say we are the YouTube team.
YT-creator.ru, which is the Russian URL.
And in the body, they say, um, excuse me, we have detected that your YouTube channel is
uploading spam or something like that.
Like we will take punitive actions unless you provide your name, like social security number,
and password to your fucking account.
They asked, it actually happened.
You can go look at it.
It's fucking in our email.
So did you do it?
Did you give it to them?
Of course I did.
Ben, I don't want to get fucking taken.
Absolutely.
Yeah, okay.
Don't fuck with the Russian.
No, I did not send the main thing obviously.
Give them whatever they're asked for.
Yeah, I've actually seen that around.
Like one of the, one of my YouTubers, I watched hopeless speeches.
She posted it on Twitter as well.
And I was like, holy shit, it's happening.
That's, it's really funny.
Like I wasn't even close to attempting it.
Oh, I'll look at this right now.
This is so fucking bogey.
Isn't it cute?
It's crazy.
You want to screen cap it and put it in the...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sick.
Fantastic.
That's it.
It's so like poorly formatted.
It doesn't look anything.
Like the YouTube logo was like squished and warped.
And that's why the official, official people always says like,
you know, the official team will never ask for your password.
We'll never ask for your password.
If I hadn't been told in so many emails by YouTube previously,
we will never ask for your password.
I may have been more tempted to give them a password,
but I wasn't even tempted because I'm a good boy.
This message seems dangerous.
Oh yeah, there you go.
They're telling us it seems dangerous.
Fucking yeah.
You can see the URL in that picture too.
Fucking Ruskies.
There is it.
Those sneaky...
It's in the gross disgusting audio links.
Oh, incredible.
Yeah.
So what do we do?
Are we fucked?
We're fucked.
We're going to be terminated imminently.
There's nothing to be done, I guess.
We just have to accept our fate like the samurai of old.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
We have to lay down our arms and say something we can do.
We can't fight the tide of history,
aka Russian bots.
Oh, speaking.
That's right.
Speaking of dying, press F for Ben's glass.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, before we started recording,
I tipped over my favorite glass
and it shattered on my desk,
sending tea and apple cider vinegar,
cascading over my desk on all my sensitive electronic equipment.
We heard the crash.
It was not recorded.
I wish we recorded that crash.
It was quite dramatic.
I do too, and I realized that all of my computer shit
is ergonomically designed,
so that none of the tender mechanisms are on the surface.
They're all lifted.
Yeah, they're all held slightly above,
like my microphone, my monitors, my speakers.
They're all held above the water level.
Ben, do the favor.
That's, yeah.
Red pill me on apple cider vinegar.
What's the deal?
Okay, I can't give you-
Do I drink that?
Do I chug it?
Is that what I do?
I mean, I wouldn't chug it.
I just put some of it in like-
That's good.
I mix like-
And why do you do that?
Why do you do that?
I mix like lemonade, stevia,
or lemon juice, stevia, some apple cider vinegar,
mix it in water, add ice.
It's good.
For what apple cider vinegar is good on in salads?
I've read that it's good for your metabolism.
Okay.
And also just think it tastes good in that mixture.
Yeah, so that's kind of just-
I drink a bunch.
Okay, I'm sold.
I'm sold.
Yeah, I couldn't-
There's probably more.
That was like a cleaning product or something.
I think I've used it for like athlete's foot in the past or something.
Okay, it is obsessed with vinegar flavored things.
Why would you use apple cider vinegar specifically?
I mean, if I did, if I'm remembering correctly,
I'm pretty sure I just-
I did like a Google and went to like a how-to,
like how to like treat athlete's foot.
I think it said like soak in apple cider vinegar or apple cider vinegar.
Apple cider vinegar.
Whatever, you know what I'm talking about.
Actual vinegar.
Same shit.
Yeah, it does clean stuff.
Okay, I might just be wrong.
I might just be wrong about that.
But okay, fair enough.
Fair enough.
Yeah, I fucking-
It's fucking vinegar.
Go through that.
I go through that apple cider vinegar,
like it's something you would go through at a very rapid pace.
Fantastic.
If you can imagine.
Do you guys, like in the America,
do you have like salt and vinegar flavored chips?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, okay.
I've never been a fan.
I've never liked them.
I didn't like them as a kid, but-
UK has a lot of vinegar flavored things.
It confused me.
Animals, subhuman.
Not a fan.
One of the PCP heads that showed up to the RCK meetup
was like, oh, you got to have
fish and chips with salt and vinegar on them.
You got to have it with vinegar.
And I didn't-
Dude, you got to have a colonectomy
and a colonoscopy at the same time.
You've got to do it, bro.
It's a euphoric experience.
Same argument.
What do you guys think?
About voicemails?
Yes.
What do you guys think about it?
We can do them right now, if you want.
Yes.
I got them.
Now, we don't have too many.
We've got, I think four today?
Four?
Yeah, all right.
That's a very low batch.
You know, we've been getting fewer,
and I think that we maybe discouraged them
because I've been so harshly critical
on everybody who's been calling in.
Well, hopefully they're good now.
I mean, these are all pretty good,
I thought.
I thought they were all quality submissions.
And you know what, four?
Pretty healthy number.
But I encourage everybody.
Keep sending them, because I like them,
and I'm happy to have as many as possible.
I don't mind.
I don't mind listening to more.
Okay, but let's get to it.
Oh, and a link to the Speak Pipe
is down in the description.
Go click on that, and send us your voicemails.
If they're good, do cool things.
I like cool things.
All right, but our first one is from Polenta Meister.
Polenta Meister.
Yeah, it's a weird one.
Okay, let's see what he has to say.
You know this person?
What's their reputation on the street?
I mean, I like them.
You like, okay, all right, fair enough.
Let's see if they live up to it.
All right, go.
Hello, Pipe.
It's your boy, Polenta Meister.
I just want to tell you guys that we've recently talked
about a topic that has grown near and dear to my heart
at recent times.
Because after going back to my country,
after a period of working overseas in an office every day,
I've gone back to working out and exercising my body.
I gotta say, I completely forgot how good it feels.
Yes, yes, true.
It's really like 20 to 30 seconds into your reps.
You feel like you're dying.
I feel like you're turning into a sludge of primordial soup
and sweat and lactic acid, but five minutes into them
and you start to feel the endorphins rushing through your veins
and pumping straight into your skull.
And man, I gotta say, there is no way for me to say how good it feels
other than comparing it to playing corruption of champions
and slowly turning your avatar into a trembling mound of flesh
and pieces of the giant and changing artfaces.
But it's in real life and you're turning yourself from being a weakling,
a pasty spaghetti man into a sculpted doness.
Yes.
I gotta say, guys, there's no excuses.
Even you, Tom, can just build yourself a new spine and you're good to go.
Yeah, Tom, quote unquote.
Yeah, Tom.
Get that new spine in there.
Tom Cruise, maybe if you'd fucking done more reps
then the Japanese wouldn't have lost the word.
Maybe you'd done more reps.
The samurai wouldn't have been cut down.
Yeah, you'd be like five foot, you know, 10, five foot, 11,
maybe six feet.
If you'd done those spine reps, you cowered.
All right, well, let's move on.
I wait.
Yeah, yeah.
I wanted to say that I've been fucking,
I've mentioned this before, I'm lifting again.
I've been lifting for three weeks now and I'm fucking ripped.
How many times a week do you go?
Three times a week.
That's good.
That's great.
Yeah.
Doing starting strength.
Speaking of those power cleans.
That's great.
I should do those too.
It brings me, it makes me literally want to cry when I think that Tom is too hurt to work out
and he wants to go to the gym and he can't because by no fault of his own,
his spine is just fucked and it's fucked up.
I mean, I've been talking to him.
I don't know if there's anything we can do.
I told him just to let us know, but he can't even work because he's in pain.
I don't know if you should even say it, but like, God, it's fucking not fair.
It's not fucking fair.
He was going to go to BronyCon.
He wanted to go.
He can't go because he's hurt.
He can't go.
Yeah, his spine is just fucked and couldn't walk around.
It's not like he was even like playing B-ball hard in the court
and he like broke his like, like, lol, shoot, I can't go to BronyCon.
No, he didn't do anything.
It's just his back is fucked for no reason.
Oh, it's fucked up.
Tom, thoughts and prayers, bro.
Thoughts and prayers.
Yeah, it's useless.
I just wish I could help.
Okay, whatever.
Enough of that shit.
Seems like seems like I don't know.
I mean, I don't know if I don't want to be pessimistic, but like,
it seems like it's just like gotten worse, like with for no reason.
I mean, I guess Tom says, I think he says.
I don't really.
I should I mean, I probably shouldn't like comment on it without like talking to him about it.
It's just my pressure.
You're right, you're right.
Maybe I'll ask him if he even wants us to include this.
I just don't want to share personal info if he doesn't want us to, but I don't know, whatever.
Okay.
Anyway, oh, and I was going to say just specifically on working out.
So I've been lazy about working out for the last couple of weeks.
I think I went like two weeks ago once and I've been lazy.
But but the good news is I have been perfect on my diet for the last like month.
And I think I've lost, I've lost a steady.
I can see it in my progress a solid six, seven pounds.
And those those are real weight loss.
That's not meme weight loss.
And it's going going pretty good.
I only want to lose like 25 pounds from that starting point.
So once I get down there, I'm going to be going to be feeling good.
But of course, the hardest thing is to gain muscle.
So this is the easy part.
I got to be lifting like a real boy.
Let's go keto, man.
Let's go keto.
I'm telling you.
Yeah.
Wait, I don't know.
I think this is probably fine to say oblivion fall contacted me and told me that he was grateful
that I had spread the good word of keto to him.
Yeah.
He showed me before and after pictures of like the thing.
Oh, did he?
Yeah, he messaged me on discord specifically.
No, no, he on Twitter.
Oh, he could include that if he wants to while he's editing.
Well, yeah, he showed me like before and after pictures from like February this year.
And then like recently he lost, I think he lost like 30 or 40 pounds.
It's great.
Yeah.
That's fantastic.
I mean, assuming he wasn't already underweight, in which case that would be bad.
But I assume that was not his ailment.
He was a little chunky.
And now he's objectively better.
I'm sorry.
Fantastic.
I shouldn't.
That's fatphobic.
You know, I'll say.
No, he's always beautiful on the inside.
Of course.
One can make a comment upon a one's outside visage and bodily structure without being
judgmental of their inside.
Well, he was stoked.
Well, he was stoked about it.
I'm currently, this will be out on the day we're recording this.
I will almost a hundred percent be finishing my Uyagawa on Dunbaru Nankiromotaru,
the anime about weightlifting.
And I'm very excited about it.
Yeah.
This is going to be good.
Talk about.
Did you see May's video about that?
Oh, I did see it.
I like skipped around through it and I thought her point was valid.
I don't specifically talk about like her video because like, I mean her point is good.
The thing is I'd already been thinking about that while I watched it.
While I watched it.
Yeah.
I mean, would you be right to say that she's not really a fan?
You know, it seems like.
Well, to be fair, I didn't really watch the whole video.
I don't remember if she said that she like liked it overall, but it seemed like the focus
of the video was on like the like the unhealthy like body imaging or whatever.
I mean, I say this is my video.
That's absolutely true.
Well, I mean, while it came up, it's absolutely true.
She makes a pretty good point that like, she's like, oh, this girl, this girl is like,
this main character is like a ghast that she weighs like 130 pounds.
Okay.
Well, the thing is like we need to first of all, you need to use Japanese standards,
not American standards.
And yeah, I have no idea what like the average woman weighs in Japan.
So like an American looking at that, first of all, you're already coming at it from the right.
What if the Japanese standards are unhealthy?
Well, but they just, I mean, they have a different build.
They have a different body type than like, I don't know, Italians or, you know, Polish people.
I mean, well, okay.
So we just need to know the facts.
Like what's a healthy body weight for a Japanese person?
I don't know.
Well, who decides what's healthy?
Well, what's the average fucking body weight of it?
Like, let's at least have the facts before we decide.
You can't just look at the average numbers and be like, okay, this is what's, well.
Look, a doctor could tell you what's like, you know, what is healthy to unhealthy.
I'm thinking there's a, maybe I'm thinking there's a, I'm thinking there's like a,
there's a culture, there's a cultural aspect to it too.
It's not like, we're not talking pure biology here.
I mean, that's possibly true.
But I mean, I don't know what the threshold for like, unhealthily overweight is for like,
a Japanese woman, because 130 pounds is, I mean, it depends on like your height and,
you know, a lot of things like your bone structure and, and all kinds of stuff.
But I'll give you what you want.
I agree that like, it does seem like Hibiki is a little bit overly concerned in terms of like,
if her concern is health, but the show couldn't be clearer.
Her concern is, I want to be hot to get a boyfriend.
You can view that as shallow and that's perfectly fine.
But this is her motivation.
And that's, that's all there is to it.
Yeah.
Well, all right.
Yeah, fair enough.
So it is, huh?
What, wait, what mage?
But she's kind of already hot, isn't she?
Well, okay.
This goes to the other issue.
Okay.
First of all, we can, we can talk in the West.
There's, you know, a increasing standard of like, we like fit girls.
Sorry, I meant to say thick, thick girls.
I mean, I'm personally, I'm not the biggest fan of that body type.
But like, you know, I appreciate it.
Like everybody else, I appreciate everybody type.
But like in Japan, I don't think that is the necessary consensus.
I'm sure to some degree it is.
I don't know.
I'm not Japanese.
So I can't really speak to it.
But, but there's another concern that ties into that.
That's like another criticism that may makes.
And I mean, I had thought the moment I saw the anime preview,
I thought this to myself, it's that Hibiki starts the series as, you know,
whatever she wants to lose weight.
I mean, she's not, I mean, there's that, there's that one like close-up shot,
like from like the bottom, like a down and up shot that like emphasizes
how like pudgy she is at an absolutely, at the absolutely horrifying like 135 pounds.
And then there's like, okay, she, she goes through the numbers and like the numbers
don't make sense.
I thought that, that was interesting.
I, the numbers, you know what?
I didn't even look at the numbers.
They give her, they give her like, they give her weight, her height,
her body fat percentage and a couple of other numbers.
And May explains how like these numbers don't make any fucking sense.
And I, and I, and I was convinced.
I mean, I guess that goes to my point.
That's fine.
But I mean, at what point should we think, okay, well, I'll just say that it's,
it's true.
At the very least, I totally agree that based on like the Hibiki we see at first
and the Hibiki in the manga for the most part,
like just your average shot of Hibiki from the anime,
she looks like a perfect idealistic anime girl.
And that doesn't make sense for this show.
It is simply preposterous.
That's the, that's the opposite of what the show's point is.
She was, she was drawing a little thicker in the manga, right?
She was, but not consistently.
So the manga is also not perfect in this way.
It is better than the anime significantly though.
So I mean, that's the stuff I talk about.
I just want to, since you were talking about the show, I wanted to
May's video about it.
That's all fair.
I just happened to see that on Twitter like two weeks ago or whatever.
In terms of, you know, now I'm kind of curious.
I did not analyze the numbers.
Maybe I'll go back and look at that.
Cause I did not even pay attention to where they made sense or not.
I don't know.
Whatever, it doesn't matter.
Okay, anyway, big tangent over.
Let's get back to our next fucking voicemail healer.
We've got one from Zoomer Don.
Zoomer Don.
Okay, ready, set, go.
Hello, PCP.
It's Zoomer Don.
No voice changer, no instrumental,
no asking for relationship advice.
Just a simple request here.
When I am recording this, Nate's last stream was Minecraft.
And man, that shit was cringe.
Nate, you are going to lose subscriber.
Oh no.
But my request is for Munchy, fellow Zoomer overlord.
Oh, hi.
To teach this fucking boomer the ropes, man.
Cause I know he wants to play with fitMC in the future,
and I don't want him to embarrass himself.
Nate was like, guys, what does shift cooking do?
He starts shift cooking randomly.
Chat, are you trolling?
It's not doing anything.
I did do that.
You have to taste your own medicine.
Oh my God.
You don't know what to shift cooking?
I learned.
I learned what it meant.
I still haven't.
What does shift cooking do?
It makes it automatically snap to your hot bar.
Also your inventory from shifts.
Yeah, it basically groups your items,
and it's more efficient than clicking and dragging and stuff,
which is a pain that I've been doing a lot of.
So fair, fair.
And also I just wanted to spell this like,
Nate stays awake at night rocking back and forth,
pining for the day when he can play Minecraft with fit.
If only I was man enough at Minecraft to do it.
I mean, sure that'd be fun.
And yeah, I do.
If I did, I would embarrass myself.
So I'm not even interested in asking,
but the narrative being paint here is incorrect, sir.
You're overselling it, so relax.
Now wait, you fellas, hold it.
You went and oversold it.
I guarantee that you've got their hat and care.
Compare.
Oh, that's an old one.
So if that's an important ingredient,
can't be added on experience quality,
my friends, and quality care.
Quality care.
Oh, do you know what that is?
There's your trivia day.
Don't tell them.
Guess, guess.
So say in the comments what that is.
Guess in the comments.
How much money did you steal from?
Did you ring out of the grasp of Equifax?
And what is that song?
I'm just like one, I'm just imagining right now,
like a Nate versus Finn MC, like Minecraft challenge.
Like they go toe-toe in the arena.
I can't beat him at Minecraft, dude.
I'm imagining, it will literally be like an anime fight.
Finn will have his hacks on,
and he'll just be speeding all around you,
and he'll have the shadow ninjitsu models of his own self.
They have shadow clones all around you.
Okay, that's fair.
You'll hopelessly try to shift click your sword
into your hot bar, and then you miss,
and then you throw it outside,
and you drop the sword onto the ground.
Okay, all right, that's true.
Well, he fucking does the hit, the crit.
That will happen, but that'll be the beginning of the arc
where you face the final opponent
at the beginning, you get utterly dominated.
But that'll be before my like 10 month Minecraft
training montage, like I did in the Pokemon race,
and more successfully in the Dark Souls race,
where I obtained every skill
and practice every movement over and over dozens of times
to obtain god-like speed and agility,
and I will have set traps up
to counter his cheating hacks
and his god potions and whatnot, and ultimately.
If you make the underdogs,
it's just gonna win eventually, because underdogs always.
Smash cut to like a year from now,
like the rematch, fit MC, like cracks his knuckles in Minecraft,
aka post, ashras, cracks knuckles, asterisks in the Minecraft.
I achieved my samurai sword,
mastered Bushido.
He does his shadow clones, and then he says,
Nani, and then he sees the nether crystal in your hands,
and he's like, where'd you get that?
And then he says, you can't teach a new dog old tricks.
And he says, what?
And then you blow him up,
and then you have your blast resistant diamond armor on,
you walk out unscathed from the burning inferno behind you.
And I'll say, fit more like shit.
That'll be my final word on the subject.
And then he'll never be heard from again.
Moving on, we've got a voicemail from Tyga Mike.
Tyga Mike, let's see what you got.
I love this guy, I don't even know him.
Hello, I come to you all with a dire grievance.
Me and my fellow voicemailers are having our vocal labor exploited
by the disgusting host class of the PCP community.
True.
We deserve to be paid an amount equal to the ratio of time
our minute and a half takes up on the show
as we provided the labor of entertainment during that time.
Saying it's your platform,
and thus you don't have to,
is like saying corporations deserve to make a profit
because they own the means of production their employees work on.
As 169 episodes and counting have passed
without this injustice being corrected,
it is only just that we viewers take violent action
to overthrow our oppressors.
Dismantle the pro capitalist podcast.
Bullets for bed, news for bed, burn the mage,
eat the munchies, guillotine gift, ground digi,
wage cucks of the world, unite.
Yeah, hard agree.
Hard agree.
Also just a little trivia.
So we're like 170, almost episodes in, right?
Yeah, this will be 170.
This is episode 170, yeah.
Yeah, okay.
So but like the voicemails weren't around for 170 episodes.
We know mage, but revisionist history is a hell of a thing.
At least get your facts right before burning me.
We've probably played enough voicemails
to comprise an entire like two hour episode by now.
I'd probably give you at, I suppose.
Well, maybe, maybe an hour, I don't know.
Well, listen guys, just be thankful that you're even on the show
because we have an arms deal with guests being on the show
and so you know if we're not gonna need voicemails
because we're gonna have just guests lining and filling all the time for us.
So why get a prerecord message when you have any guests on the show?
Your guys are going the way of the samurai
and I think you better hold on to your culture, you still have it.
I want to acknowledge that we are indeed,
we are indeed exploiting the labor of our voicemail callers.
This is, we must do this.
We must do this to survive in capitalism
and this is why the system should be dismantled from the top.
We don't have to though because we, we did it like for centuries without it.
We are, we are, we are forced to.
We are incentivized to do this.
Oh no, we're servants, we're mere slaves.
Oh, if only our bondage was broken.
If only our bondage was broken.
We have to pay, we have to, we have to
fucking pay into social security
and we have to fucking squeeze our viewers for content.
This is the trade-off.
Couldn't be more accurate, couldn't be more accurate.
All right, we got one more final voicemail of the day
and speaking to capitalism and corporations,
AldiCorp is calling in with another message.
Back to shill his Twitter.
Well, let's see what he has to say.
All right, go, go, go, go.
What a great day for me, CEO of AldiCorp.
Spending the bustling AldiCorp business center.
Nothing could possibly go wrong.
Let me answer that.
Hello, CEO of AldiCorp at your service.
Yes, I remember the Twitter ad from two weeks ago.
What? It was cut?
Oh, no, no, no.
We spent all our marketing budget on it.
If we can't make a return, we're in serious trouble.
What are stocks?
They've dropped so far, the Wall Street Computer's blue screen.
We're literally paying people to take our money.
What is that word?
That's not how stocks work.
I can't believe.
Oh no, it's the PC police.
They're gonna put me in voice jail, aren't they?
It's all over.
This company is finished.
All my life's work gone to waste.
I'm bankrupt.
The rest of my days will be behind bars and debtors' prison.
All for a stupid Twitter ad.
Oh, what have I done?
What have I done?
Lock him up.
You live by the Twitter ad, you die by the Twitter ad.
That's all there is to it.
Okay, okay, I knew what they said.
Okay, you could lock him up,
but it sounds like he kind of burned to death at the end there.
I mean, he's on the run.
It's only a matter of time.
Well, we'll take his mangled corpse to the voice jail.
He's an official member now.
He's in there.
Check the post in the description.
He's literally there.
Good job, I'll die of you've ruined everyone's lives,
including our own.
Listen though, I'll die.
We should, can we privatize the PC prison system?
Can we profit off of this somehow?
Can we exploit their labor?
I don't know about necessarily privatizing,
but I'll tell you what, what we can do
is just be extremely corrupt.
And I'm happy to just,
if Alda just gives us money,
you know, I mean, maybe that could get him out of voice jail.
I mean, that seems like a pretty good idea.
We're not saying anything.
I mean, it just could happen.
I mean, anything could happen, you know?
We're just saying.
We do live in a world of possibilities.
We sure do, Ben.
We sure do.
Well, I guess that's it.
That's it for the voice mail.
Okay, no, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I still have one more issue
about the whole burn the mage.
Mame the mage sounds better, so.
Mame the mage, that's much better.
Okay, me and mage didn't get any,
like, M alliteration for some reason.
Everyone else got alliteration when we didn't.
I got, we got, we got.
Bullets for Ben, news for Nate.
Yeah.
Drown did you?
Guilty gib.
Guilty gib, yeah.
So what the fuck, dude?
You know what?
Yeah, you deserved a rod in the voice jail.
Fuck you.
I got.
What did you get, Munchie?
Eat the Munchie.
How about murder Munchie?
How about fucking murder Munchie?
Yeah, murder, murder Munchie.
Murder Munchie, name the mage.
There we go.
Name the mage.
We fixed it for you.
Yeah, that's right.
And I mean, if Tom was here, we could,
lethal injection, Tom.
Yeah, there you go.
Got it.
He'd thank you for it anyway.
He'd thank you for it.
Lethal ejection, lethal aurora.
Yeah, lethal injection, lethal aurora.
Oh, that's pretty good.
Yeah, yeah.
That's pretty good too.
Excellent.
We made it.
How about, try to think of
what's this tea?
What's a murder tea thing?
Julie, there's something.
OK, so this is what your demand,
your demand compensation for.
You're coming up to us with your
fucking like child's macaroni drying,
a.k.a. your voicemail.
And you're saying, hey, can you put this
in the museum, please?
And then we have to go in here
with our expert painterly brush
and cure it and actually make a real
official painting out of the slop
that you've given us.
It's only us who are stuffing.
You don't see the only victim here
as us right now.
That's the only victim.
Wait, I've got it.
It's true, but I've got it.
Traumatized Tom, because what they're
going to do is Tom will be left alive
as the figurehead of the old regime,
so as to make peace with the common
people who still respect their old
overlords.
That's his role.
Traumatized Tom.
He's already pretty traumatized,
but a little more couldn't hurt.
Tear up Tom.
Oh, that's pretty good too.
Yeah.
Trample.
Trample Tom.
I like trample.
No, no.
These are all great ideas.
He's riding on the floor right now.
His spine doesn't work.
It'd be easy.
Yeah.
Oh, and undress Jess.
Oh, that's, I don't know what that is.
Oh, Lord.
That's a winner.
Oh, God.
Guys, you know what we should definitely do?
We should definitely incentivize
people to come up with all the ways
that we could die.
That's a great idea.
We should definitely laugh and joke
about that.
Guys, post and chat the many ways
that you want to murder us.
I think that's a good idea.
Draw a fan art of us being murdered.
Yeah.
That'd be great.
Why is there no PCP porn yet?
It makes me so fucking mad.
Every single time I go on E621,
there's no Nate Bestman.
Like tag.
Oh, it's fucking nightmare.
What's wrong with you guys?
That's disgusting.
But also real real.
Are we not good enough for you?
Oh, what?
Game grumps gets poly grumps,
and we do get nothing.
We get the scrap, we get the shit.
We get the piss.
That's fair.
I can't wait till the,
there's eventually,
when the PCB dating sim comes out,
there will be an expansion pack,
if you know what I mean.
I'm expanding just thinking about
that expansion pack.
You know, it's going to be.
Oh, are you talking about the PCP DLC?
Oh, that's exactly what I'm talking about.
I can't wait.
Hey, was there more coming from the dating sim?
Yeah, they're still working on it.
They're still working on it.
Was there a date announced for that?
No, I think they said like September,
but I could be wrong about that.
I don't know if I'm,
check out at PCP Dating on Twitter
for all the updates.
So that's where it's all at.
Maybe I'll finally be in the game.
I know Tom just got included.
Okay, let's all go commit deceased.
Yeah, he's right.
She's right.
Let's let's wrap it up, people.
All right, more voicemails.
Speakpipe, link down below.
Click, leave voicemails.
They're good.
And most importantly, patreon.com slash
the procrastinators.
We will happily take your money.
I'll die and others.
One dollar, you're in the Patreon Discord.
Five dollars, you get the bonus episodes.
And by the time you hear this,
there will be a new one.
Isn't that exciting?
So stay tuned.
Go listen to them.
There's like, I think it'll be 28.
I think it'll be 28.
And at tbcrastinators on Twitter for updates.
Can we get a one in chat for Munchie House?
Munchie House will be gone.
Rest in peace.
Press one, press those ones.
And I shall record here.
Yeah, the historical one.
I hope you fucking burn it down behind you
like the Elrics did.
I will, I will.
Oh, dramatic.
A leap of trace.
Don't lose your way.
That's not Elric.
All right, anyway, we'll see you later.
See you next week, everybody.
Thanks for being here.
Have a good night.
Good night.
God bless.
Thoughts and prayers.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
But I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
My dick, I'm jerking.
Myself, I'm sucking.
I am an asshole.
I am a stupid.
I've got a deadline.
Don't want to do it.