I won't bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Alright, what would be a funny way to start an episode?
I can't keep falling back on the classic, hello, I'm The Pro Crastinators,
but there's gotta be something better to do.
It can't just go back to the Doug Walker well all the time.
That's always my first impulse.
Right.
But that's all I can think of.
I stumbled on the Crow Masticators again. Remember them?
No.
Are they still posting?
I don't think so, but all the videos were years old and I was like, damn,
I better remember these guys.
I remember.
I had forgotten.
Semi-recently, I feel like we discussed them again.
They brought them up and were like, oh yeah, remember those?
Remember those guys? It might have been in my discord.
No, I think it was a spiral made like, he was going through all the old episodes
keeping the N-word tally, and he kept notes, and he showed some notes,
and they included like, remember the Crow Masticators?
I was like, oh yeah, the Crow Masticators.
Our rivals, I guess.
What a journey it's been.
It's me, Ben Saint, Gibbon Takes Here, and our guests this week are
Oblivion Fall again.
You.
And Kaijukun, we're also returning.
Right, you were on one another time.
Yes, Kaijukun, art guy.
What's up?
Well, yesterday, we got the tree, got a good old Christmas tree,
and today, I've been decorating all day.
So I've been up and down, step ladders, putting lights on bushes and trees and things outside,
and running around, and people have been swearing because of untangling things,
and you know, it's the worst time of year, but it looks really pretty afterwards,
so I'm pooped right now.
I'm pooped, but it's looking good, I guess.
I helped my dad decorate the tree at Thanksgiving.
He had already done the outside lights.
Yeah, the Thanksgiving tree?
Well, no, but you put it up, it was up early.
You put it up early, and then we decorated it.
It was great.
I loved it.
Okay, right.
Kaijukun and Oblivion Fall, you guys are not from America, so you don't celebrate Christmas,
so sorry to exclude you.
Oh, yeah.
I've never heard of Christmas, ever.
What's that?
Never done one of those.
No, I don't know.
I'm sorry.
That was a joke.
You guys do like Kwanzaa or something.
No, it's bullshit.
We have Christmas in New Zealand, but our Christmas is better because it's hot,
and it's summer.
Oh, yeah.
How bizarre.
Santa is like, he's got a ski...
No, not skis.
What was it called?
Surfing.
He's a surfer, he's an idiot.
He's getting sunburned.
I feel like the whole point, I mean obviously Christmas comes from like,
Norse traditions and stuff of like,
winter feast because it's cold, everybody warm up and try to make yourselves happy
because it sucks outside, but doing that in the summer,
I'd just be like, I'm trying to relax on the beach, I don't want to put up decorations,
I don't want to do all that.
It's summertime, it's the whole time.
Literally, it's defeating the point.
Really, it's like what's even the point of Christmas.
We still have like the fucking Christmas socking,
which is like a big fluffy sock that's meant to keep you warm, I guess,
but it's already hot.
You should do like a Christmas crocs or a Christmas flipper.
Christmas snorkel.
Yeah, that would make no sense.
A Christmas sandal.
A Christmas croc.
Yes.
Totally.
I guess I have to buy some gifts or something.
I fucking hate this shit.
I hate gifts so much.
I hate giving them and honestly, I hate getting them too.
What a disaster.
My family is doing a secret Santa this year,
and that's like the only thing we're doing because a lot of us are poor right now.
Yeah.
I'm supposed to buy a gift for someone,
and it's supposed to be like around a hundred New Zealand dollars,
but the two things that they asked for is something that's free
and something that's free hundred dollars,
and I can't get eye for a pose because the free one,
they could just grab, I don't think they realize it's for free,
so I have to find something else for them.
So get it for free.
I've been putting it off.
So do that one.
What's even the question here?
But if you have money left over, you're supposed to get something else from the list,
it's like, I don't fucking know what to do.
It's also shit you can buy on Steam,
so there's no rush, I can just buy it on the day
or find something else for them, but it's dumb.
Wait until it goes off sale so you can spend money on it.
Oh yeah, good idea.
I have already done my gifts for a family.
They're simple things.
Previous years, I know I've talked about this on the PCP,
but previous years I've said,
ah, you know what, I'm just going to ask people exactly what they want,
and then I'm going to buy that, so there's no chance that they'd be disappointed.
But I found that there's less interest when they open the package,
and that's kind of lame.
They're just like, oh yeah, you got me a thing.
It is lame.
I said, so now I'm not doing that.
I am buying things based on what I think they will like,
and I don't know who of them will be listening to this,
so I can't say, but they're pretty good.
They're like a beyond like a cheap piece of shit,
but not so expensive that it's embarrassing or like too much.
It's just sort of a mid thing.
That's good.
It's good.
It's efficient.
It's economical.
Wow.
That's right.
That's correct.
What I like to do, I actually like given presents,
and I usually look for any excuse to make presents,
but the fun thing about it is that I like to do my own packages,
so I just pick some random paper stuff or something,
and it just draw.
It do random drawings according to giving clues of what the present is,
and people would like that.
That's awfully thought.
Yeah, I mean, that's pretty thoughtful.
That's pretty nice.
That's more effort than I'm willing to put into it.
This is fun.
But I guess that says more about me when it does about you,
so that's okay.
Pretty good.
I guess I'd like to receive a Kaiju gift.
I guess.
You would like to.
Oh, really?
Drawings are fun.
I hadn't thought, because family, they don't like internet things necessarily,
but for internet friends, drawing characters and stuff for them,
that's good.
I could try that.
I could do a bit of that.
Yeah, it was a shitty doodle.
A few days ago, one of my friends,
well, it was the birthday of one of my friends,
and I gave him the volumes 99 and 100 of one piece,
because he likes one piece,
and I drew the entire straw hat crew on the paper,
and it was really cool.
Ladi, that's very nice.
Very impressive.
It's really fun.
I hate drawing, so I don't know what you mean.
I didn't take the picture.
Damn.
What a chore.
Oh, yeah, I took it.
No, it's not fungible.
It's forever a real thing.
No, no, I took a picture.
Hold on.
No, you fucked it.
Now it can be right-click saved.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's off the blockchain.
Before, it existed only in the realm of ideas on the blockchain.
Well, now it's real.
I don't know how to share pictures.
Hold on.
What is this?
Well, you figure that out.
I finished all my commissions.
Finally, I haven't had my commission list clear
in like probably about five years.
Oh, the vectors?
Yeah, but my little pony things,
where I do hundreds of images of people's characters each.
I was working on one during the last episode.
I finished it.
And then I started on that punk Tommy Oliver design,
which I also finish for next day.
I think in total, I did one commission a day
for the first eight days of December,
since I lost a conservation gig.
And that was like 1,500 drawings total.
But yeah, there's an image of like all the different characters
I've done currently.
I know a bunch of these people.
I didn't see the full list before.
I know Sweetie Bloom.
Is that Eliora?
No, I don't think that is Eliora.
Who else do I know on this list?
There's probably more.
No, never mind.
That's not for a question.
It's on there.
Sifisto commission, at some point.
Good.
Not good.
I'm glad.
Oh, Golden Fox.
I see Golden Fox.
I know who that is.
Oh, is he the one with the sunglasses there?
Yeah, I see it.
Yeah.
Well, what a trip down memory lane.
Base, congratulations on getting all that done.
That's impressive work.
This is an impressive Uber, I'm looking at.
A nice body of work you've built up here.
A good resume.
Yeah.
I feel intimidated.
I don't want to share my drawing anymore.
You're joking.
It's never going to be as cool as many, many ponies.
Yeah.
It's never going to be as cool as a thousand ponies.
It's so intimidating.
Oh, geez.
Yeah, that one's good.
That's a winner.
I'll give you that one.
That's a winner right there.
There you go.
Oh, perfect.
What's her name?
Cosmic Flair.
Yeah, this one.
Cosmic Flairs.
The hair was annoying.
So I started working on it in the first half of a year
and then just put it off for six months, finishing the hair.
Wow.
Even though most designs I can do in a single day.
Well, yeah, speaking of getting shown up by many ponies,
work, art, like doing stuff, been very hardworking on the secret project.
And it's stressing me out a little because I really want that done.
And I've got a lot of ghost stories that have all been handed in.
And now I have to make the PDF.
But at the moment, it's really stupid and I feel stupid
because basically all I need to do is like,
intro page, like here are the guest artist credits
and here are all the Kickstarter backers.
And thank you for reading or whatever.
Make the PDF.
I just can't choose the right font.
I can't put the layout and copy paste all of the names.
And it's just like, oh, I don't want to do that.
I don't want to be doing any of this.
I'm the bottleneck now.
It's my fault that it's not being made.
It feels bad.
Yeah.
Yeah, that does feel bad.
I know what you mean, though.
Making decisions is hard.
Yeah.
I got to a point.
I feel bad.
I'm in a bad mood because the last two days,
consecutively, I have been working all day, every day,
on my not secret project.
And I am at a part where I needed to write some dialogue.
I needed to stop coding and stop drawing and write some dialogue.
And it was so hard.
And twice now, I've written it and then I've been like, cool.
And then I've kept working for the rest of the day.
And then at the end of the day, I'm like, you know what?
It's bad, actually.
I need to rewrite it tomorrow.
And I just feel like I'm not making any progress.
It feels like I'm spinning my wheels and I'm upset about it.
What is it with text?
I'm going to take it out on all of you.
I don't know.
It's just too long.
I wrote and wrote and wrote.
And then at the end, I'm like, wow, this is like so many lines.
It shouldn't be this many lines.
It just goes on and on and on.
I have to whittle this down somehow.
But I don't know how.
So I don't know.
As soon as we're done recording, that's what I'll be doing today.
And I told myself I wanted to get the beta version done by exactly one week from today
when we're recording by next Sunday.
Will I do it?
I don't know.
If I don't, it's not a huge deal.
I just, for my own, because that's exactly one year since when I started,
I was like, it would be nice if I could have it done by then.
So I'm trying really hard.
I don't know if it'll happen.
Yeah.
It's many little deadlines that are mostly self-made.
But I would like to spend the Kickstarter money doing the printing
and as much as I can in shipping stuff.
Before the end of the year.
Before the end of the year, before I have to do my taxes
so I can write all of that expenses off.
Yeah.
Because that's going to be done for January.
And it's like, ah, geez.
Every day that I try to open the document, I'm like looking at it.
I see all the Kickstarter back as names.
I'm like, how should I arrange this?
Oh, fuck it.
And then I leave.
That's been like three days in a row.
And I come back to it and I'm like, ah, but oh shit.
Oh, we got to go get a Christmas tree.
You know, I'll help with that.
Oh, we got to put up lights.
Yeah, anything to prevent me from doing this thing.
Yeah.
I feel that way with writing dialogue a lot.
But I can't do it anymore because I have only a week
and it's not enough time.
And now I'm like, I just have to make myself do it.
But then I do it and it's bad.
And I'm like, well, okay, I got to redo it now.
So, you know, it's terrible.
I don't know.
Somebody, I don't know.
My life sucks.
Everything's a disaster.
What more can I say?
I got really mad.
I've been getting really mad at everyone.
And I've been mean on Twitter, even meaner than usual.
I got my account pseudo locked yesterday.
By pseudo locked, I mean that like everything's normal.
It's just people that don't follow me can't see my tweets for 12 hours.
And I think like four hours is left at this point.
So like two non-followers, I look like a locked account or whatever.
And this is a punishment.
And it was, I just told someone to fuck off.
I just told someone to fuck off.
And I guess I had told one too many people to fuck off that day.
And they were like, die.
And they pseudo locked my account.
I told someone to fuck off because they said it was an L.
That I told, what's the guy's name?
Was it not Matt?
The guy who, someone was calling for a boycott of Toei.
A like semi-big YouTuber.
And then like later that same day, he was like,
guys, I can't emotionally deal with this anymore.
I'm revoking my call for a boycott of Toei.
And like that's fucking weak shit.
Hey, that's exactly what I was going to talk about
because I'm the editor of that channel.
Really?
Yeah.
Yes.
Really?
Okay.
Well, let me just, I just, I heard that he called for a boycott
and then he like got upset or something and was like,
never mind, no boycott.
And I just think that's the,
and I just think that's the weakest shit in the world.
So I called him weak and then somebody responded to me to tell me
that was an L for not having enough empathy.
And I told that guy to fuck off.
And it got my account semi-locked for 12 hours.
And I was right.
He didn't ask for a boycott actually.
That was like the community, I guess.
Uh-huh.
So that's what he said.
He said, he said like I'm,
let me find the tweet so I know exactly what I'm talking about.
No, I remember,
I watched one of his, one of the earlier videos,
one of the two videos he made and he's like,
if this isn't rectified,
I will not be, uh, watching your new films or something.
Yeah.
Is that not technically a boycott?
Uh, he said that he didn't want to,
he didn't want to encourage toy animation anymore.
Uh, but people took like that as some kind of movement
and they created a hashtag or something.
And because of that,
uh, a lot of anxiety fell upon us.
Uh, so in the end what happened is that,
because we're, first of all,
uh, we're not used to that.
Uh, second of all,
um, we both have anxiety.
So,
I don't, I don't, I don't get it.
I know, it's really ex, I,
I wasn't expecting you guys talking about it,
uh, uh, before me.
So, um, I'm a bit unprepared right now.
Okay, sorry about that.
But yeah, um,
I just don't get it.
Well, I guess,
Not everyone wants to be the villain then.
Sometimes people don't.
How is it, how is it a villain?
How is it a villain?
I don't know anything.
First of all, I don't even know what Toei did,
but if they did something bad,
if they did something bad that you don't support.
They deleted 150 of his videos in like the span of an hour.
Yeah.
And, um,
Right.
And like the,
Okay.
The, the accumulated current,
you know, the revenue of those videos,
getting views over time is like how he pays.
Basically.
His editors.
Yeah, basically what,
what they did is just, um,
absolute abuse of the copyright system.
Like, um,
Okay.
How this works is like, um,
the company should watch the video.
Check, uh,
check with YouTube if it's actually a violation of the,
how is this, uh,
thing called the, um,
Oh, I forgot.
Content ID.
Yes.
Um,
and if,
if like,
if the channel is actually doing something wrong,
they're in the right to, you know,
block the video,
but they didn't do that.
They just, uh,
picked a number of videos that had Dragonball in the title,
and they just blocked them all.
Just instantly in like an hour.
And with that,
they destroy the entire revenue of the channel.
Yes.
And,
and because, uh,
we're all crew has to dispute all of them.
Yeah.
And,
but he can't do more than like two at once or something,
something about like,
if he does too many at once,
his channel might get destroyed or terminated.
Yep.
If they come back and say,
actually no,
which they always do.
Because it's like,
because it's like, if you look,
because if you dispute,
and then let you dispute is not accepted,
it's like a strike or something.
Yeah.
So he can't do that for 150 videos.
Like saying,
this is fucked up.
Toei, please.
He made a big video pleading with Toei in Japanese.
He hired somebody to speak in Japanese to them
so that they could understand why this was bad,
why this is bad for him,
and being able to pay,
you know,
all that stuff.
And then,
I guess anxiety got to him.
He made a third video.
I don't remember exactly what was said,
but it was sort of like,
it wasn't backtracking, I guess,
but he was like,
not really able to deal with the hubbub that was caused.
Yeah.
What does that mean?
Well, the thing is,
we didn't expect this thing to blow up.
First of all,
like even PewDiePie made a video about it.
Like we wasn't expecting that.
Okay.
You gotta understand from a point of view of a person
that is not really used to deal with internet shed.
Like,
he's also a really nice guy.
He's not prepared for the internet at all.
So,
he just,
What are you talking about?
He's a YouTuber with 680k subscribers.
Exactly.
That's exactly the one thing that is,
people is getting wrong.
Like,
because someone has like a huge following,
they immediately think,
like this guy is a,
I don't know,
is a massive YouTuber,
because I don't know,
he's some kind of an enterprise on its own.
He's used to the internet shed and stuff,
but he's not.
We do videos,
videos get views and immediately,
suddenly out of nowhere,
100k subs just coming to the channel.
But because we had,
like we have a huge channel,
doesn't mean like we're prepared to deal with the pressure of that.
You know?
Sure, sure.
I'm like him and the anxiety stuff,
not being able to deal with it.
I don't think it's too much of like a problem in and of itself.
I don't expect that.
I just feel like,
it's like maybe a mistake to shy away from a community that's trying to support.
Like, I feel like a boycott of Toei is based personally.
I think that's cool,
because they're fucking,
they're fucking with this channel.
They're abusing content ID.
YouTube needs to,
you know, everyone knows YouTube sucks with the content ID robots and stuff.
I feel like it's beneficial for YouTubers and,
and you know, audience members and just people for this to be like,
I don't know, taken as far as it can go,
like make enough of a stink that actually something does change.
Yeah.
But the thing is, like from my perspective,
like the day this happened,
I got so anxious that I had a panic attack.
Really bad.
I had to go to the hospital and stuff because the whole,
like this whole thought of maybe the channels is going to stop existing.
Like maybe they're going to strike it.
Maybe I'm going to lose my job.
It just, it just got me.
It just got me and it was really hard these days to stay positive.
It was really, really hard.
You have no fucking idea how hard was to like wake up every day and remember like,
yeah, right.
This happened.
Fuck.
How do I deal with this?
How do we deal with this?
So as for me personally speaking,
like if I was Mark,
I probably going to do the same thing.
Like I couldn't, I couldn't understand the pressure.
Okay.
To be honest.
Well, I, but the pressure to do what?
Like what, like what does, what does be it?
Okay.
What, what exactly does making a video where you throw up your hands and you go,
never mind.
Like what, what does that do?
What does that change about the situation?
How does that relieve any of the pressure?
Being like that feeling that you're suddenly in the center of the world and everybody is watching you.
And you're getting notifications all day, every day about it.
And you have like a,
It doesn't, it doesn't fix that.
It doesn't fix that problem.
What problem, Ben?
That, that problem, I, the one you were just describing,
think about being, getting too many notifications and it, it's upsetting.
Like it doesn't, it doesn't fix that.
It's not like it's upsetting, Ben.
I mean, I don't know how, I don't know how I even explain it to you.
Like if you don't understand how, how is to deal with this sort of this,
this level of anxiety, right?
This level of depression.
If you don't know how to, how it is to deal with that every day,
with all this pressure of the entire world just surrounding you out of nowhere.
Like it is really hard.
I'm just saying, I don't, I don't, I don't see how making a video where you're like,
where you just say, oops, never mind.
Like I don't see why that relieves any of that pressure or solves the problem.
It doesn't, it doesn't, it doesn't make the, it doesn't make the, the strikes go away.
It doesn't like take attention off of you, really.
Exactly.
It doesn't.
So the move is just to move on.
Cause how can you fight a multi-billionaire company that can strike and delete your channel anytime?
I mean, how?
Yeah, it's, it seems, it's, it's hard to do that.
When we, we got a like a few videos blocked in the past and they,
it took around a whole year to get them back in the channel.
Imagine like how much will it take to fight for 150 videos.
We did the math and it would take around 37 years.
And honestly, with this fucked up system, when YouTube doesn't want to help also,
just reminder that they don't want to help.
They do not want to help.
So we kind of have to fight for our own, for our own.
And you can't just go to trial with toe animation.
I mean, it's fucking toe animation.
Well, all right.
I have, I have a thing to say about that then.
I think like boycotts are legal.
Like, are to a able to shut you down because you're saying boycott or are implied to say boycott?
Cause like, like, I'm, like, I'm honestly confused.
Like, what is the problem because like, is it, is it that you said boycott until he was mad and going to threaten legal action?
Or is it just, or is the decision like, okay, well, I'm simply just not going to challenge it.
And I'm just going to let the videos that are down stay down.
Yeah.
All right.
Cause why would he, we don't want that.
We don't want to fight for 37 years.
I mean, I don't know.
It's not, it's not, it's not my business.
I don't know.
I mean, it's not my business, whether he decides to challenge the strikes or not, or the takedowns.
It's not mine either.
I mean, I just, I'm just the editor of the channel.
If he wants to, if he wants to prioritize his mental health, I think that's not, that's not wrong.
And I think a lot of people understand.
I don't care about it.
I don't care about the mental health, like whatever.
It's, it's either way, it's his decision.
Whatever.
It's beside the point.
Like, I'm not saying, I'm not saying he, nobody is saying like, oh no, he has to fight the strikes.
He has to put his channel in jeopardy.
Like, I don't care about that.
I don't know.
I get, it's, it's, it's, I don't even know what I'm arguing anymore.
I don't even know, I don't even know what we're talking about.
I think the mark probably needs like a spokesperson or a manager to deal.
Like if, if he's getting anxiety from this, I don't know how you get a manager or anything.
But like, I'm imagining the sort of person who like, you got your artist, your, whatever,
a musician and he's like, oh shit, I'm stressed and you got your big manager with big fists
and he points his hand, his big meaty hand at like, people who are fucking with him.
And he says, fuck you, treat him right.
You need people like that.
You know, you need a guy like that on your team.
You need a manager to like punch and take all the brunt of stuff.
It's actually something we did at DA games.
Like Will used to be in charge of everything, but he has a lot of like anxiety issues.
And there'd be a lot of points where he would like, if he was having like a really like, like bad time,
he would like be like, oh, no, maybe I should delete the channel.
Maybe I should do this or that.
And he would make all the social media go black and do that thing.
And we're just like, God, no, don't do that, please.
What was the guy in Bakuman?
Like the manga about manga.
And there was that guy who was like, ah, shit, I don't want to do anything.
And he had that manager.
It's like, just do it, idiot.
And he's like, oh my God.
You mean the guy with the suspenders?
Yeah, he was really good.
The guy who drew Otters 11.
Otters 11, yeah.
Well, that was his editor.
Editor's art.
It's funny to say that.
He was my favorite.
Can I forget his name?
Yeah.
It's funny to say like, because the manager who got at DA games also is seen wearing suspenders.
No, no, no, no, nothing.
The manager, he, the artist guy wore suspenders.
He was the businessman who like retired to draw manga and he had the long hair
and he wore suspenders most of the time.
Wearing suspenders is pretty sus.
Oh my God.
In any case, we had one of our other friends who was on the team
who was very like mentally stable and based, I guess, just like take over the social media
and take over like organizing everyone and telling like all the artists,
okay, you're going to work on this, you're going to work on that,
keeping deadlines, that sort of thing.
And taking that pressure off of Will who's like the face of the channel
so that he can have a better time and it's been good.
So it can be a good idea to do that.
Yeah.
No, I know what you mean that like this is everything is so new.
Like we actually weren't prepared at all for this kind of situation
because we never expected that one day we're just going to wake up
and see that 150 videos were just going to be deleted
and then making a video about it like an updating the situation
will like trigger this reaction in YouTube in general.
Like we weren't expecting that we weren't prepared for that.
We weren't mentally prepared for that.
I think this experience is a learning experience to be honest.
Like if ever happens again in the future, we also need to,
I mean, I don't know what we're going to do.
We're probably going to change the entire format of the channel.
Probably we're going to move on to something different.
But yeah.
Okay.
I lost track of what I was saying.
In my opinion, in my opinion, okay.
Anxiety or no.
I think objectively speaking, if a company does something bad to you
and then you make an announcement and you're like, hey,
company did something bad and then it makes a big,
there's a big reaction, there's a big community like outcry about it.
Like setting aside how you feel about that
or if it makes you anxious or whatever.
I think that's just good.
That's just like a good thing that you want to happen
and that is good for you.
Like the initial thing, yeah, it's bad that the videos are taken down
and maybe it's, maybe, you know, maybe, yeah,
the consequences of fighting it might be bad and not worth it
and risky and you don't want to do it
because it's like a bad decision for the survival of the channel.
That all makes sense and is good.
But I think when the community is mad about what company did to you,
it's smarter to lean into it.
I think Gibb, you were saying something kind of similar before.
It just doesn't make sense to me at all.
Not like the technical aspect of it,
just like the way that it is being talked about doesn't add up.
Yeah, I think that point of view is right.
But personally, if it was me, I just wouldn't be capable to keep going.
So I guess it depends of your mental strength
or your personal situation.
I know Mark has some personal issues too, so I don't know.
Well, the thing is, to close this topic, I guess,
I don't know if you could keep talking about it,
but when I talked to you the other day to talk about the situation,
I was hoping to get into the podcast and talk about,
hey, we should keep pressing Toei and stuff.
I wasn't expecting that.
Mark was going to feel so...
I didn't know he was feeling so bad.
When I talked with him the other day, I was like,
shit, he's feeling really bad.
I guess I understand.
I honestly wanted to keep going.
I wanted to keep going.
I was amazed at the...
When you say keep going, you mean pressing Toei.
You mean pressing Toei publicly,
or you mean YouTube behind the scenes, like challenge.
Publicly, yeah.
I mean, I even was doing my own silent protest.
I do a lot of fun art of Toei shows.
I said on Twitter, you know what?
I'm just going to stop doing this until this situation is fixed or whatever.
But Mark is my boss, yeah, but he's also my friend,
so I need to sympathize with him.
I understand.
I understand because I will do the same thing.
I wouldn't be capable of keep going with all this.
I'm not... I don't think anyone should...
It was the first time it came out of nowhere.
Out of nowhere.
In one hour, our entire lives changed.
Yeah.
It is understandable, but at the same time,
it is an experience to learn from
and to get better at managing this kind of situation
if it ever happens in the future.
What have we learned?
I guess to manage the kind of situation better, I suppose.
I would not hire a thug, get a mercenary with like brass knuckles
and like a sloped forehead
and tell him that he has to punch people on the internet,
and he'll do it.
Yeah.
But we'll see.
I mean, for now, he's having a rest.
We're going to talk about it later.
Here's what I think probably...
Here's what's...
You know, this is...
I think at some point probably...
All right, I'm just going to say it.
I think he's probably going to come to his senses
and be like, no, wait, we actually should...
We actually should keep talking about this,
and then it'll just be back,
because I think that's the thing that makes more sense.
To be honest, I think the best way to move on,
it's still animation.
It's like you're fighting it,
the ant versus the elephant.
I mean...
Situation.
Well, I guess, but like...
Is the fear that they're going to strike even more of your videos?
The fear is that they strike the channel.
Well, yeah.
That's the thing, the YouTube system is so weird
that they give all this power to these big corporations
that they can do anything they want with your channel.
And you, as a creator, can do absolutely anything.
YouTube won't help.
There are no legal help or anything
that can do anything for you.
It's stupid.
The only...
There's a proper solution,
which is getting a YouTube manager
that can give you the ability to
block the videos of the channel on Japan.
But getting one of those managers
is like you have to have inner friends
in the inner circle of YouTube
to actually get a manager.
It's really stupidly hard to get one.
So...
I mean, okay.
A channel as big as Marx, though,
I feel like it would be easier than most
to get some YouTube attention.
I feel like it's...
I mean, the procrastinator's tiny channel in comparison.
We yelled about stuff that happened to us
when our channel got deleted once.
I think it was just once.
We yelled about it on Twitter and we did get response.
For months and months we did, yeah.
It took a while, but I feel like it's possible
to get the Toei thing.
Because I feel like Toei is a giant company.
They're so giant, they probably didn't even notice
anything was happening.
Just do a YouTube sweep.
We need to do that.
And then a guy pressed one button
and he just scanned YouTube for things.
This channel has a lot of Dragon Ball in the title.
I do that.
And it was just a robot doing it.
I feel like if YouTube reinstated a bunch of them,
if you could get in contact with YouTube somehow,
cause enough of a stink on Twitter,
other social medias,
and then get YouTube to be like,
okay, I guess we should look into this
because the community is outraged.
They usually respond if the outrage is large enough.
And then they may be able to put
most of the majority of the videos back,
or all of them.
And then Toei will probably just not even notice.
I feel like they're not really that involved.
I don't foresee them coming down with a real lawyer
and being like, all right, time to kill you
with an assassin.
That's the weird thing,
because I think Toei has been targeting the channel
for quite some time.
They blocked some videos.
We got them back after almost a year,
and then they blocked them again.
So they slowly and progressively
started to block first two videos,
then five videos, then 10 videos,
and out of nowhere 150,
but they've been like targeting the channel
for quite some time.
I guess the channel is on the radar,
I don't know.
But Toei's animation as a corporation
is really fucked up how it works,
because it's like,
animation and production is really cool and great
and all that.
But in terms of corporate,
it kind of sucks because they still live
in the 20th century.
I think it's managed mostly by lizards,
like just old guys that just won't like you.
They will block videos with people that,
I don't know, you know those videos
of one guy talking to the camera
and suddenly, I don't know,
they have a poster of Dragon Ball in the back.
They will block videos like that.
They will block videos like one guy saying one piece once
in the entire thing.
They will do that.
And they do that.
We got several comments of people,
of other smaller content creators,
they have this problem,
they have this problem where they do fun arts
and some guy draws Goku or Luffy or something,
and they get the video blocked
and then they get it back
and they're blocking again and again
and they keep blocking it.
So, I don't know, they're weird.
Such a weird company.
Yep.
This is like Disney.
It's a lot, yeah, Disney and Nintendo
and a lot of companies do that.
They just claim stuff
and there's no real consequences for them
if they are overly aggressive in the videos
that they claim, infringe their copyright or whatever.
This is a problem you hear.
Big enabler of those big companies
because they don't want to get sued
so they'd rather just fuck the user base.
Yeah.
Shift the blame.
One sec, I need seltzer water.
Okay.
KGB.
Boy.
So, yeah.
Anime.
What is it?
Black cherry.
Delicious.
Okay, so what's up?
What did I miss?
Nothing, I just said anime.
What is it?
It's...
And manga.
You probably want a boy
working with anime on YouTube.
It is a Japanese colloquialism, after all.
Impossible, impossible.
It's true, but true.
I wish that YouTube would just stop being a little bitch
and I also think we should do a abolished copyright.
That's over and above the YouTube situation.
But it's true.
They should improve the system.
The PewDiePie...
Yeah, that's a good start.
The PewDiePie made about the whole Mark situation.
He also tells like...
He can't use his own music in his own videos
because YouTube claims he is music.
Like what?
Who is music?
PewDiePie.
PewDiePie makes music like an artist
makes an album and he can't use that music
or what sort of music exists.
Hold on, that makes no sense because...
Exactly.
I know a bit about how that system works
and they're supposed to like let you
whitelist certain channels yourself.
Like you're supposed to have control of that
because GA Games does a lot of music
and they've whitelisted certain channels
to use their content.
They've whitelisted my channel,
they've whitelisted a few of the other team members
and those videos don't get claimed by the bot
or at least we're not supposed to.
So why can't...
Why does a PewDiePie have access to that?
PewDiePie says something about like another company
claiming his music.
Oh well that happens all the time.
A company is just falsely claiming ownership.
There's no filter for that.
Like I did some streams of Hollow Knight
and the Team Cherry is explicitly said on their website
Hollow Knight, you can use the footage,
you can use the music, you can just use everything.
We love them.
And then third-party companies will just
say they own the soundtrack to Hollow Knight
because they distributed it in like Taiwan or something.
So they claim it and I can't do anything about that.
I can fight it and eventually they'll say
they'll do nothing about it but it's like...
It's stupid.
You'll know that but what can be done?
These companies never respond.
They never respond.
I probably don't even hire a single person
to do any of that.
I mean...
Remember...
Sorry, sorry.
I interrupted.
No that's okay, I burped and I forgot what I was going to say.
Okay.
Remember when Mumki got his channel deleted
and immediately he was like more popular
than he'd ever been before and like Keemstar
was making videos about him and stuff?
Yes.
In my experience it's just good
when bad things happen to your YouTube channel
and then people talk about it.
Not necessarily in Mumki's case.
He's never regained all those subscribers.
Okay, well in Mumki's case...
He's still less than half the amount he had years later.
Well yes, his subscriber count.
Yeah, but I mean that was...
He could have played his cards differently.
True, I mean he did kind of fuck up everything else.
The channel could have grown more
if he hadn't fucked up everything else, you're right.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't know.
When PewDiePie is making a video about
your situation about how a company fucked you over
that's what you want.
That's like the dream.
That's the dream of the YouTuber
as far as I'm concerned.
I can assume that the drawcast got some kind of boost
after we got deleted and came back.
What's that?
I can assume that the drawcast got some kind of boost
after YouTube deleted us and then we came back.
Maybe, probably.
I was assuming a little bit.
I mean it's really just the case of people
who otherwise would not say the name of a channel
are all saying the name of a channel at once
and so a lot of people who have never heard of it
are hearing about it.
Because I knew of Totally Not Mark through Kaiju
but I didn't really watch their videos
and I forgot, I didn't realize it was the same guy
when this stuff all started happening.
I was like, wait a minute, that profile picture he has
looks familiar.
I figured it out.
It's Zorro.
No.
I didn't think it is.
It was a contest
of making a fan art of Mark in the One Piece style.
Yeah, he looks mostly like Luffy
but a little different.
No, he looks like Zorro.
It's like a Luffy Zorro.
He's just Zorro but he's sticking his tongue out.
The artist that drew that is like,
he draws really accurate One Piece art.
It's really good.
I forgot the name sadly.
Oh yeah, it's Zorro.
Lots of people have now learned about
Totally Not Mark
and so that's why it would grow
if it had been deleted and come back
there would be more people, new people.
And that's why it's a good thing to happen
but it's not like a preferable thing.
I think you can grow perfectly fine without it happening.
Yeah, that's the thing.
It's like a little boost.
It's like a Mario Kart boost on the track
if you're in 12th place and you go,
maybe you'll get a little further.
It depends on the person really.
Personally, I wouldn't like to grow up as an artist
because of some tragedy, honestly.
Well, whatever.
We're not all you, Ben.
We are different.
You are dumb if you think this is a me thing.
I'm just saying, look, when you're a YouTuber,
you live and die on the numbers
and things like this make a number go up
and that's really the long and short of it.
Yeah, but again, it depends on the person, honestly.
I mean, it would be bad if your 600k YouTube channel
were erased and you had to start a new one.
That would probably be pretty bad
and maybe would probably...
It depends, but it would probably offset
any signal boost that you get from something like this.
Perhaps, possibly, probably, most likely, maybe.
There was a YouTuber who didn't have his house burned down,
but it did, and he was one of the big fires
in California or something,
and he was a science, something I can't remember his name.
But he lived in a van for a while,
and he kept making videos,
and people, the support definitely helped
regrow what was destroyed.
So, tragedy is big money,
and you should try to burn your house down.
You should seek to create...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You should live as dangerously as you can
and hope that something bad happens to you.
I'm glad we all learned a valuable lesson today.
You got to show your Patreon.
The trick is when this happens, you got to show your Patreon.
Oh, wait, it happened to Teleprte, too, didn't it?
Because his channel was growing pretty fast
at the beginning of the year,
and then YouTube deleted him over some bullshit.
They said his videos were too sexual,
but the videos they flagged had nothing in them,
and when people kicked up a statement,
when he came back...
His whole channel got deleted for a couple of days.
I remember that, yeah, I remember that.
And then when he came back, his growth was quadruple
what it was before.
Did he have to start a new one, or did he get the old one?
No, no, no, he got his old channel back,
but he had slowly climbed up to around 1 or 200k or something.
But when it came back, he shot up triple that in no time at all.
Yeah.
So, yeah, that also happened.
I forgot about that.
I remember that happening.
On the topic of finances of content creators and things,
I've had something interesting happen in the last day.
Since the last...
Yeah.
My Patreon, patreon.com slash oblivionfall,
was fluctuating around 250 and 253 dollars
back and forth for two weeks.
It couldn't decide what it would settle on.
And then yesterday, it just jumped up by over 30 dollars
out of nowhere, and I have no idea why,
and I'm almost catching up to patreon.com slash bansane.
I'm only a couple of dollars behind you.
This is a tragedy.
I'm going to have to give you money if I surpass you.
This is bullshit.
That is a big problem.
That would just be terrible if you had to do that,
according to the contract that everyone with the Patreon...
According to the blood pact, yeah.
Oof.
Yeah, this, yeah, yeah.
What a terrible thing to happen.
Maybe when Phantom's Revenge comes out,
people like that, and I'll get a boost or not.
Good, good, good.
Who knows?
I pray.
Did you put anything out that did that to you, or what?
I put something out on the last day of last month,
and I haven't put anything out since.
I've been silent, so...
No boost in viewership on my videos.
I checked my analytics after it happened,
and they're the same as normal, so I have no idea.
Oh, wow, yeah, you're almost...
Yeah, you're only a few dollars behind me now.
Oh, God.
No!
Stop!
No, stop having money.
Only I can do that.
Stop having money.
Quit it.
Stop.
Makes me mad.
I don't want to give Ben Saint my money, jeez.
I definitely don't want you to do that
at patreon.com slash ben saint.
From patreon.com slash oblivionfall.
Yes.
patreon.com slash give and take.
That wasn't funny.
That was terrible.
I was waiting for Kaiju.
Yeah.
So, yeah, oblivion, you...
Last week, you had a bunch of shit.
You were describing...
You said there was a developing situation,
and then immediately after the episode,
you said, like, guess what?
The shit is even worse than you could possibly imagine now.
Oh, God.
Yes.
Do you want to, like...
There after the episode, so please explain everything.
Yeah, I'll recap.
So, my month, starting December 1st, was crazy.
The first day, my job at Pennsylvania
that I've had for three years, just poof, gone in an instant.
Yes.
And, oh, that was spooky.
And then the second day, the Twitter drama
and regarding the plagiarism of my friend's character,
I also talked about that.
Yes.
And then the third day was the thing
that I was considering talking about.
I've changed my mind because I think it's a bit too much
of a personal situation, and since then, I've learned more.
There's more grays going on.
No.
But that involves some stuff.
It involves some very fucked-up individuals, in my opinion.
But I probably shouldn't rag on them publicly.
Maybe it's not the best move.
Bonus episode material.
No, the fourth day, there was just family drama
that from, like, six years ago that got resolved.
That was a thing.
The fifth day, December 5th, this is the new big thing.
So, every single day, it was some new bullshit.
And, yeah, so, on the 5th or 6th, maybe.
I found out through my sister, who works for my mom,
who, you know, is a lawyer in New Zealand,
that a whole bunch of churches, a whole big fuck-ton of them,
including all the big mega-churches, including individuals
such as Peter Mortlock and Brian Tamaki,
who are these crazy nutjobs.
God, I could, I guess, briefly sum up what those people are like.
Peter Mortlock is one of those people who thinks that
COVID restrictions are just like what they did to the Jews
in Nazi Germany.
It's identical.
He's one of those people.
Right, right.
And he's like a mega-church pastor or something?
Yeah, he is.
My sister used to rent from his son.
They're one of those prosperity gospel types,
which is like, oh, you know,
I'm so rich because God gives me money, sort of people.
Yes.
You just have to have faith and you'll be rich like me.
It's like the, yes, it's like the evangelical Christian equivalent
of the secret, where like...
Yeah, it's so fucking hateful.
...only instead of fate and the universe, it's God.
And it's like God rewards goodness with wealth.
So that means that if you're rich,
that means it's because you're a good person and God wanted you to be.
And if you're poor, it just means you just have to be a better
and more godly person.
Maybe then God will give you money.
Like that's literally it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're so right.
I am so right.
I always am.
Yeah, so...
My sister used to rent from his son and apparently like 70% of a year
they were out on luxury vacations around the world.
They had their like $80,000 car parked outside her tiny little shed
she lived in that they were charging like $450 a week
for her to live there when she was a single mother.
You know, that real Christian charity.
It was fucking...
Sure.
It was a shitty house.
We can't live on Christian charity.
It doesn't pay the bills.
So that's like Peter Mortlock.
Brian Tamaki is like...
He's the leader of Destiny Church and he's like...
He's almost like a cult leader.
Oh my God, he has a church now?
Well, he's had a church.
It's called Destiny Church.
He runs it on Twitch.
It's what church he leads.
He's like this nut job.
He put out a bunch of DVDs about how gay people are Satan at one point.
DVDs?
DVDs.
Nowadays he's going on about all these conspiracy theories about the COVID.
It's not real.
It's made up by the aliens or some shit.
I don't know.
He's a crazy man.
So those are some of the colorful characters who are involved in this lawsuit against the
New Zealand government because how dare of a government say that, oh, you know, if you're
going to be standing in front of a congregation, you should be vaccinated or maybe not stand
in front of them.
And that's the only rule.
And that's a rule they have for all jobs.
It's not a rule they made especially for the church.
It's a rule they have everywhere.
I don't know why they can't just sit in another room with a webcam projecting their face on
a big screen with a speaker.
That would solve the problem.
I don't know why they can't do that.
They just kick him feet around.
What cams are Satan?
Yeah.
The justification is one separation of church and state and two.
Jesus said, Jesus said we have a right to congregate however we want.
We have a God given right to spread disease.
This is apartheid.
I've seen some of the legal documents.
It's stupid.
If Jesus were alive today, he would go around.
He wouldn't be laying his hands on people and curing their coronavirus.
He would be laying his hands on them and pulling their mask off and being like, fuck the state.
Breathe free, my child.
It's dumb.
The reason the most fucked up thing is one of the lawyers representing them is my mom
and I can't condone this.
I do not agree with her.
A lawyer representing whose mom?
My mother is representing these churches legally.
My mother is helping them through the government and I think this is fucked up and my mom should stop.
Also, this isn't public knowledge.
I'm not leaking documents.
For all I know, I could be telling fanciful lies.
Did she take the case?
Yes, I'm going to do this.
My mother believes in it.
That sucks.
No, bummer, dude.
It's just...
It's frustrating.
At Thanksgiving, this is not as bad, but at Thanksgiving, I tried to explain...
Did I say this before?
I tried to explain to my mom why I think that means testing is bad
and why I think it's good that the COVID relief checks,
why I think it's good that everybody got them
and how I think that universal programs are better
and means testing creates weird incentive structures, et cetera, et cetera.
And it just didn't get through to her at all.
She just was like,
Okay, but I just think that if you have more money, you shouldn't get the checks.
And I'm like, okay.
Thanks for listening.
Cool.
So it's okay.
My mom sucks, dude.
Don't worry about it.
Well, it's a shame because my mom used to be, in my opinion, pretty cool.
When I was growing up, my parents...
I still consider myself a Christian, I guess,
but my parents were much more intellectual than your typical Christian parents.
They were like, yeah, Harry Potter's fine.
Yeah, just hang out at the university.
They were very much more on looking at...
How do I explain this in brief terms?
Just taking an academic approach to the Bible and all that shit
and looking at the historical context of certain things
and looking at the original Hebrew meanings of words
and how modern-day Christianity has twisted things in stupid ways
and how hell doesn't actually exist.
Heaven's not even a thing
and all these misconceptions that everyone has
and trying to get to the roots of it,
which I think is way more interesting than modern Christianity,
especially modern American Christianity,
which is fucking dog shit.
And I don't know.
I feel like my mom's been talking to some weird people for the last few years
and she's slipping and it's not good.
I understand.
It's too bad though.
So that's an ongoing situation.
Yeah, it'll probably be public in like...
It's an ongoing legal battle
that I guess we'll have to wait and see what happens.
I have leaked government secrets on the PCP.
Yes.
Epic.
Come and get us, government.
I had thought you were going to talk more about the black cat OC person.
I thought that's what it was about.
No, it was a different drama every day for a while.
Not much else has happened with that.
My friends just gone off Twitter because they can't handle it.
They're just stressed out and the other artist,
I haven't heard anything in a while.
It's just kind of gone quiet.
Who's gone off Twitter?
My friend who created the character has gone off Twitter.
What was her name?
Her name is Twi-Pi, Miss Twi-Pi Twins.
I can link her Twitter page for the viewers.
Yeah, shit's...
When you're not getting anything out of the internet,
just log off.
Just close the screen.
How can you get bullied on the internet when you can just close your eyes
and not look at the screen?
Yeah.
Simple.
Exactly.
That's what I was trying to say earlier.
But what happened with this person?
It was explained on a previous episode, but basically...
I haven't listened to that one yet.
Yes, damn.
It was last week.
No, two weeks ago.
Miss Twi-Pi made a character and there was this other person,
another artist who was larger than she was,
had a larger following, loved her OC,
drew it as fan art.
And then slowly or suddenly, I can't remember,
decided that they're going to make their own OC,
which looks exactly the same,
and then just call it their own character
Twi-Pi's character is gay, I think.
And then this new guy...
No, they made her straight.
They made her straight.
My version is identical to yours, but they're straight.
Yeah, and they've been a real bitch about it.
And like a real asshole.
Oh, my God.
Funny shit.
They spent like a year, like the better part of a year
trying to resolve it in private.
And the bigger artist was like,
oh, yeah, you know, I'll tweak the design.
I'll do a thing to show like the differences.
I'll do this and that.
And then he just wouldn't get back to her
and was mucking around and eventually just stopped
responding to her messages.
And then when we went public about it,
he was trying to like cover it up
and hide people's comments.
And then my friend filed a DMCA
and then he played the victim
and called my friend dumb.
Oh, my God.
And it was all very stupid.
Flashbacks. Yeah.
I've been through that.
In the end, it just gave up.
Like a...
Pretty much where we're at.
It seems like he's not remorseful at all
and doesn't plan on changing his way.
No, they will never do.
A few years ago, I also made a character.
It was just a character for illustrations,
not even for comics or anything.
A few years ago, I also just, you know,
my friend had a character and I thought,
great, and I owned them.
So I made a character that was the same
and that bitch never let me
hear the end of it.
Sorry.
I wasn't even Twitter, but it happened
over Instagram.
And yeah, same situation.
Like a huge artist
asked me
if he could draw a fan art.
I said yes.
And then he
stole the character, basically. That's the end.
I wanted to fight, but
same thing.
Same thing way too animation.
I just decided to just
fuck off. Whatever.
See, you and Twilight have a fatal
error. You made a fatal error.
And that is that you are good
at drawing nice character designs.
What you should do instead
is what I do.
Really stupid shitty cartoons
that nobody wants to copy.
And then you can
make so much merch
and nobody will even steal it because
it's like, oh, I don't care. That doesn't look good.
It's perfect.
Well, that's how
the NFTs
protect themselves from getting right-click
just because they look like shit and nobody wants them.
Did you see fucking
John Lennon's son
was like chilling some fucking
some skull NFTs?
Oh, was that actually him? Fuck.
Yeah, it was John Lennon and Yoko Ono's fucking son.
Sean Lennon
or something. Shilling the skulls.
Jeez.
What a fucking bitch.
Yeah, it was something like
all those monkeys or whatever
and lines, they look ugly, but
these skulls are really gonna blow your mind.
Why my skulls?
They look okay, but
only slightly
less embarrassing.
But they're still NFTs with a supremely
embarrassing by virtue of that.
To their credit, they did look better than
the board apes.
I'll give credit where it's due, I guess.
If you want to be Papyrus or Shadman
or something, you can buy
an avatar,
a skull avatar on the blockchain.
But fucking Julian Lennon wouldn't have done that.
Who's that?
The first kid.
Or wait.
Sean was with Yoko and Julian was with
the other
one.
They don't know much about the Beatles.
I know they made music at some point.
Child.
Yeah, I think so.
I think that's true.
So this is
internet nowadays, huh?
Yeah, I did see that
and I was like, oh god, this is weird.
Because it's like,
you always think, oh, what would it be
if people from the history had Twitter
accounts? How annoying or
how would I find out how terrible they are?
And I don't know much about Sean Lennon.
How could we cancel them?
But it's like
an avenue to see
the worst possible take a person can make
public, viewable.
And it's there.
It's Lennon doing it.
Oh god, which was the
which is the Monty Python guy
who? Eric Keitel
who you know is many.
John Cleese.
Yeah, John Cleese.
Did you see John Cleese's like woke
joke tweets?
Yeah, those didn't make sense.
It was like so embarrassing.
I'm curious.
He made a tweet that was like,
I mean, it was supposed to be ironic, but
a woke joke.
And the joke is like
two, three guys walk into
a bar.
One of them says like, I decry racism
in all its forms and the other two
agree.
And it's supposed to be like, haha, it's not funny
because all they said was
I don't like racism.
And it's like, yeah,
it's not a funny joke, John.
It's also like not
observational. Do people do that?
I really don't know where he gets that from.
Like the idea that
people who are
woke or whatever
tell jokes that don't have
punchlines or something.
I don't want to read too much into it, but
the corollary
to a joke like that is that is like
the obverse of it is, ah, yes, a joke
that isn't
a joke that is
self-consciously anti-racist
is not funny because without
racism, how could we have humor?
We've got a little bit.
That's totally not what he means by that
because that would be insane.
I don't think so. It's just a dumb,
it's just dumb. It's annoying.
And you know, he's old.
He made old movies that are really funny.
He basically is
a guy from history
in who's tweeting.
And it sucks.
Yeah.
But it's
a bummer.
Yeah, I don't know.
No thanks to that.
Sort of tangentially
related.
I guess it's like
stupid to have thought of the BBC
as like a good organization when I was younger.
But that was the impression I got was
like they know what they're
they're not like those
American Fox News people
that the Simpsons make fun of.
This is better than that.
Not racist. Of course it is.
But
recently
you may have heard of
the transphobic article
I think it went, we are being pressured
into sex by some trans women
and it's about
a few
bloggers
saying that
trans women,
I'm a lesbian and trans women
are forcing themselves on me
and it's not right.
And that's the entire article. There's no
trans person representation in the article.
I have been following
Sean's videos about it.
Sean has made a video outraged about it
as an encouraged people.
Two videos.
And I have gone along with those videos.
I've left my own complaints
to the BBC. The first one
he covered in his second video
which is copy pasted to a lot of
people. A lot of what was
in the thing he said was
given to me
which didn't address anything I said.
So I sent a second complaint
and I did get a response.
I will read a bit of it now. Hang on.
Just need to grab it.
But it was similar. I love the BBC.
I want to hear
from them.
I want to know what they think.
Thank you for getting in touch again about our article.
We're being pressured into sex by some trans women.
What a silly title.
There was a part in it where it was
clear. What I said to them
in my second complaint was
you are
just being transphobic.
And the response
they're giving me
is
in so many words.
There's too many words.
I'll summarize.
They basically say that
yes,
we understand that this is not representative
of the entire argument.
But,
we have done other articles
and this is part of a series of articles
like
discussing
like transgender
culture and stuff
and things that people have.
So really
we understand that
this article is mostly
like conjecture and has no
studies. But we made sure to mention
that the studies are not accurate and we
said a sentence that is basically
there's not much data to go on.
But the entire rest of the article
and the title imply
that there is something to go on.
And it's blatantly obvious
that this particular
article
is like
we've decided
they don't seem to understand
or they're trying to
not mention the obvious fact
that to make an article on a
topic that has no studies
to back it up, that has no
significant data
to make a claim
the decision to publish
that in the state
is like
clearly the intent is for people
it's not neutral
it's not neutral to publish
some one person said
that Jews are
terrible
that happens.
A literal fact, a person says
Jews are terrible. So we've decided
and no Jews
that we asked for comment
just decided to say anything about it.
So we're just gonna publish it.
It's technically journalism
to find a thing that somebody has
said and say this person has said it
there's no evidence that Jews are bad
people but this guy said it and we're gonna
put that as the title of this article
and we're going to assume no responsibility
for anything that happens
and it's so clear
that somebody in the BBC in charge
of this article is very steadfastly
transphobic and I've called
them out in my complaint that
by allowing this to stay up
you are just
infecting the rest of the BBC
with a transphobic
layer.
If you allow transphobia
to be
defended and published
then there's no part of the
BBC that isn't fucked.
So fuck the entire BBC
you piece of shit. I didn't say it
like that. I said it as
Britishly as I could to make them upset.
I said it very
politely and directly and
currently.
Did you say your wonkers?
No, Britishly
complaining is like
kind of a meme
because whenever a British
I don't know if this is the same anywhere else
maybe it is. But we get all haughty
and like upper class
writing. We try and use the big vocabulary
and we're very direct
we're very
like pointed
and angry but not
where we're swearing. We be very
very clear
and polite and they can't do anything about
that.
So I made it so that
they have to respond and
I expect nothing to happen. I expect this
to be like a confirmation for me at least
that the BBC just has
a transphobe in a position of power
that wants this to be the message
they're sending.
An illusion
of neutrality but mostly
just people, they understand
that people read headlines and just assume
they don't go into the article and find
the sentence that says, this article is bullshit
by the way. We've said that and that means
that it's okay to publish.
Nobody reads that bit.
Right.
So, yeah.
Fuck them.
BBC can eat a dick.
I would say the BBC is really
shit in the bed.
They're really shit in the bed on this one.
It's bad.
I did not write a letter
but
I guess I could have even though I'm not British.
Oh yeah, here's the sentence
they said, we used the word
some in the article
since that clearly does not mean most
nor all.
Others quoted in the article said, there is currently
little data and we don't have figures.
So,
they assume that will be enough for me to be like,
oh okay, you said it.
You did say that.
See how that reads to most people
who are dumb is,
oh, we don't have data so there must be even more
trans people doing this.
I can't wait for even more evidence
to come out about it.
It's incalculably high are the statistics.
You can't even express
the ratio.
Yeah.
Hmm.
Boo.
When you call them out they're like, oh well,
actually there's not a lot of evidence so can you really say
I'm wrong? It's like...
That's...
Someone...
Sometimes I see a thing on Twitter
where someone will
say something about
like, I don't know,
history or foreign policy
or politics or something
and it'll be like
I don't know.
Okay, like the mainstream media, right?
Like,
fucking Rachel Maddow will say
you know,
COVID has killed, you know,
800,000 people
or whatever in America.
And then some idiot on Twitter
with an American flag
in their bio
will be like...
The mainstream media lies.
Like, the mainstream media lies
and therefore,
so I don't believe, I think the number's lower.
And it's like,
alright,
maybe the mainstream media does lie,
but like,
you're still basing your claim
off of what they're saying.
Like, if your reaction to their
like, oh no, this many people died
or it's not even about that,
just anything. Anything that the mainstream media says
and then you're like, oh,
the mainstream media said it
so I believe the opposite.
It's like, okay, well,
I don't know, isn't it just as bad?
Isn't it just as nonsensical?
If there's someone that you think you can't
trust for you to be like, okay,
whatever you say,
I'm just gonna believe the opposite.
Like, it's just as irrational to be like,
whatever you say must be false.
I must believe the opposite of whatever it is.
Right? Because...
I don't know.
It's an attitude that I see a lot.
People just assume
the opposite position because they don't like
what someone is saying, but really
if you don't trust someone's word
you should just take nothing from it.
You should just be like, well,
we can't make any statements
about this fact,
this subject, because
the person speaking on it has no credibility.
So there's just nothing to be gained
from this
thing that's being said.
I think it's probably some kind of a fallacy
but I don't know what fallacy it is
but it annoys me.
Yes.
I don't know. It reminded me
of that, I guess.
There's also the words
used to describe a thing
can very greatly influence the people's reaction.
If you say
a certain number of deaths
or killings
or murders,
if you use language
to lessen the blow
but still tell the truth
tell the truth enough
so that you're not actually lying
but make it seem like...
Like a police-involved shooting.
Yeah, something like that.
It's like
yucky.
Gross.
I'm looking at the thing again.
There's like a few bits.
We believe that seeking the view
of the LGBT alliance was a legitimate
line of inquiry.
Ah, yes.
The wording.
In assessing
if the article breached our standards
of harm, honour, harm, or and offence
we believe the use of language was proportionate.
Fair warning was given
to a strong language contained in the article.
Yeah, sure.
Just say transphobic stuff
and say... You were just triggered.
You were just triggered, snowflake.
What do you want a participation trophy?
You fucking millennial.
Ah!
That's it.
They're acting like you're offended
because they said a rude word or something.
Yeah, the first
response I got was like
didn't address
the offence stuff, like the transphobia
or the implications of
doing this without asking a trans person
on their position.
They're treating it like
very clearly like
there's only two sides to this.
Whether you tolerate trans people
and we're here to get a wide range
between those two points.
Nothing else on the other side.
Right, we're here to ask for compromise
between these two ideological
extremist positions
of tolerance
or not.
Whether you merely think trans people are
they don't deserve to die
or whether you do.
Nothing beyond that.
We're gonna thread the needle and find the nuance
in this situation.
That's so fucked.
They say
if I'm not dissatisfied
and I'm not, I have to go through a different thing
within 20 working days
so I have to do more
complaining and I will.
I will complain
until I'm blue, pink
and white in the face.
Oh, I see what you're saying.
That's good. That's funny.
Oh, yeah, I see it.
I'm laughing.
Sorry.
Well, does anyone have
any topics to raise
at this point
or should we go
on to voicemails?
I mean, we've been going for an hour and a half, I think.
I don't think I have much else.
Let me think.
I didn't have that much of my list this week.
I didn't have that much of my resources with my brain
because I feel like stuff happened
but maybe it was just Christmas
stress and I already talked about that.
All I did this week
was
Phantom's Revenge
and it just makes me upset
so I don't want to talk about it.
Revenge doesn't pay
then.
No, it won't.
Well, all it is.
The next episode we record
will be Christmas Eve
it'll come out.
Oh, really?
This one we're recording now
will come out on the 17th and then the next one
24th.
We recorded our Christmas special
for the drawcast
and since we release on Saturday
it'll come out on Christmas
so that's funny.
What a good day.
Well, that'll be a treat
in your stocking
and your little YouTube subscriber
subcount, subfeed stocking
a little gift
for you.
I am...
I want to get
so many things done
in the next week
so that I can relax,
enjoy Christmas week
from the 20th to the 23rd
and then to the end of the year maybe
just sort of winding down
because I feel like by being stressed
and having all this stuff to do
it would suck so much
if it turned January 1st
I need to
get some of this out of here
open a valve.
I feel the same.
I really want to
at least to have the beta done
if not by the 19th
which is what I really want
then at least by Christmas
or at least by New Year
I really want it to be over
or not over but I really want
to feel like
I completed something.
I feel like I'm able to
relax and then
I want to get back into doing some video game streams
because those are fun.
I like doing that at the end of the
New Year's Eve
streaming and then that part
in the stream where oh shit
fireworks, New Year's, happy new year
and then we go outside and we look at the fireworks
and we come back in and we continue playing.
I've done that for the last few years
I really enjoy that even if
I don't know if anyone watches
it's not New Year's for Americans yet
when I'm doing that
but it's fun.
I want to have that experience again
I want to have just chilling out
playing video games
I remember
video games.
I want to play Phantom's Revenge on Christmas
I want to play Phantom's Revenge live on stream
That's what Crack said
he wants Phantom's Revenge
in his stocking and I'm like
I hope I can get it
I hope I can deliver that
that would be so good.
You don't want to let Crack down
he's going to cry.
Absolutely.
Also
I have another
thing that I want to announce
on New Year's
my other secret project I feel like
I'm going to be able to announce that on New Year's
and
I would like to
announce that the Phantom's Revenge beta is done
and then have like a little time
in between that
to push that a little bit
talk about it
and then New Year's be like
oh yeah and
the secret project is also available
and then there will be a little time between that
and okay
now
the actual final build of Phantom's Revenge is done
and you can play it and it's
available to everyone instead of just patrons
and it's all playtested and stuff
Yeah
I don't know where
I hope so
I'm trying so hard
two days ago
I worked all day
and I was on an incredible roll
I got on a huge roll
of working on the game and adding stuff
and like yes yes yes
progress progress and then yesterday
I wake up and I'm like
upset
and I'm like on edge
I couldn't get on the same roll again
the whole day I felt like I was just
banging my head against it and I was like no
why can't I get that back
why couldn't I have just continued
from yesterday
why
I don't know
I don't know the reason why
but I hope
yeah
we're all gonna
make announcements
by the end of the year I guess
I'm gonna announce what I'm gonna be doing
next year because I'm not gonna be drawing
comics anymore I'm gonna change
directions I'm gonna explore new horizons
oh my god
do you wanna talk about that
or is it a secret
I guess it's not
that much of a secret but I'm gonna be
gonna do the big announcement on Twitter
but I'm gonna move on to animation
from now on
yes
yep
I have a lot of plans
for animated
shorts for the next year
that I wanna do
so that's what I'm gonna do
I guess
I wanna have
millions of comics
but like playing them back at super fast speed
yeah but
I wanna have like something to show
when I do the announcement by the end of December
and I'm actually also working on
a secret project that I can't talk about it
oh my god so many secrets
yeah so many secret projects
but this one is not
mine is like a mission
and you're all gonna see it like
super super soonish
cause it's almost done
okay
sweet
this is like a big secret reveal party
it's gonna be cool
also
I hope
I get back to work
editing videos
cause I'm scared
I need to
I need to pay my bills
so
you know
patreon.com
I don't know
in the meantime
and also
link in description
something I forgot to say
anything I said in this podcast
it's just my own personal opinion
my own personal take
listener please
I'm not speaking
anything Kaiju said
you should assume
the exact opposite is true
you should assume the exact opposite is true
everything I've said is the opinion of god
that should be taken
utmost seriousness
you don't want to
disappoint god do you
well
um you know
wait something did happen I got
I think this week I got my first ever covid test
I had never been covid tested before
is the worst
yeah it was pretty bad
it was pretty uncomfortable
it was
it was not quite as bad as I thought it
was gonna be but it was pretty bad
okay what
is it like different from the little kits you get
I don't know I've never done the kit
oh okay
I've done that a couple times where you get
like a swab you stick it up your nose
and it goes really far and then you put that
in a little tube
yeah
is that what it's called
I had never gotten one before
with like a little fluff on the end
and it goes further than you could ever
pick your nose with a finger and it's like
oh my god I'm gonna hit my brain
no
it's very weird
it was pretty far in there
it didn't feel as far as
like the diagram made it seem like it
was so I was a little relieved
honestly I thought it might have been even
worse
but
yeah I went to
the Boston Medical
Center
did I talk about this last
week? I don't think so
okay I don't think so either
I think this was this week I went to Boston Medical Center
and I had to
wait in line and they told me like
no you got to come back
in like several hours you got to leave
and come back because we got to go to lunch
and like we're full up
it took me like half the day
to wait in line
to get COVID tested
because I had like my tonsils were hurting
and I didn't even think I had COVID I thought
I had strep throat
but when I went for a strep test
they made me get a COVID test too
and
I got the results of the COVID test
like a day later and they said no
COVID negative and I'm like okay cool
and then I got the results of the strep test
and they were like
the results were confusing
because it said like
we did detect
a small amount
of some strep bacteria
but the strep back
I looked it up and the strep bacteria is like
I guess the bacteria exists
in your mouth
anyway
so like I don't know if it
I genuinely don't know if the result
meant yes you do have
strep like an infection or like no you're normal
and I don't know what to do about it either way
Did they not say it was like
a larger than normal amount of strep bacteria?
It said
like streptococcus g-strain
parentheses few
like it had few of them
so I
guess that means I had strep throat but like
I feel better
my throat is still a little bit sore
but it feels mostly better
I've had like a little bit of a stuffy nose
which I don't know if strep throat is even supposed to do that
I don't know if maybe I caught something else
like a flute like a cold or something
or if strep just does that
or if maybe it's nothing
and I'm stupid I don't know
so I don't even know
what the point of any of that was
it was just a waste of time
and put me behind
on my game just like everything else
in life
that exists to do
what a
what a disaster
what a nightmare
I hate everything
that is not phantom's revenge
but I also hate phantom's revenge
you're so full of hate
I am so full of hate
that's why I got twitter suspended
you gotta remember love Ben
I gotta remember love
do you want to talk about that video
and how stupid it is
and how like annoying
I don't really have anything to say
it's just like whatever
all I know is what I read in your chat
and I haven't watched it
I just
I did listen to the video
my take away from it was like
oh my god this is like such
navel gazing like
I literally can't talk about anything but themself
this person is having like
mind blowing revelations
at the age of like 30
that like a child should understand
and then I look down in the comments
and there's like a few hundred comments that are like
they're all like oh my god
such character development
this is such a mature take
like you've grown so much like I'm so impressed
by like the maturity on display here
that's like the fact that
you changed your opinion in some
insignificant way about shit that doesn't matter
and doesn't even mean anything at the end of the day
like oh this video has me in tears
and it just reinforced what I already know
just reinforced what I already know
which is that like
Yig heads are the stupidest people
in the entire world
there's the stupidest
the most easily manipulated
most easily impressed
morons that exist and if you think
that if you like
if you watch it there is something wrong with you
in the head and I think
you are just like an imbecile
and you should seek help
oh it's a new fucking trick
tricksy video
it was
it was just sort of like
a bunch of
semi-connected
thoughts about something or other
it was hard to follow and I feel like the conclusions
were so
like normal
like basic that I didn't really know
when she was making them
yeah
yeah I genuinely couldn't tell you
like what like the point
is supposed to be
but boy those commenters were really
impressed with it
they really got a lot out of it
all of a sudden
I think I also
had enough with tricksy
but long before
she wasn't that infamous
podcast
the thing is
there were some guys
I forgot the name of the podcast
where she went like
full traitor
who are these podcasts
before that
I was done with her way before that
a couple of days before that
it was this thing
that there are some guys
on YouTube that are
creating this
archive
and they put that video
where Digibro
talked about me
but with my old
username that I want comment here
because I don't want to
and it was a rant about
me and it was pretty cool at the time
yes
it was
someone requested it
at the time it was very helpful but not the point
the point is that I changed my
name for several reasons
and one of those reasons
is because I've been harassed
on the internet
and it's not cool
so some people found
that video
the video that this archive re-uploaded
and they
for instance they found me
again and they started harassing me again
so I
tried for several weeks to
get in touch with these people
I got in touch with
other
Digibro archives that I didn't know
they even exist
and nobody knows
who owns that channel
so my only hope and chance was
to actually talk to Trixie
and ask her like
do you know these people
can you do something about it
please help me because this is
harassment and I want
to avoid I just want this video to be
unlisted that's all I want
I put a comment
also in the video and stuff
and ask Trixie for help and of course
she never replied so I was like
you know what, fuck off
Trixie is too good
Trixie is too good to answer messages
fuck off I was like
done with her
isn't it Tarbuk
isn't it Tarbuk transom that runs that channel
I don't know
there's multiple archives
I talked with some
some people
some other Digibro archives
the owners of the archives
and nobody seems to know that specific channel
who runs it
so I just gave up and the video is still there
but
yep
it sucks
well
I don't know
maybe it's not Tarbuk
he was the guy who was in charge
he was sort of the head guy in terms of
collecting all the old videos
I don't know if he actually runs the channel though
what's the name of the guy
well
Tarbuk transom
I
he's in my server
I mean
he runs the
Digi Archive Discord
I talked with him
Tarbuk trans
long ago
he doesn't have any idea who runs that channel
which sucks
I see
but yeah
I don't know then
I don't know
just the
disconnect from reality
of like
people
who would watch that new video
and be like wow
this is so
important
I've learned something from this
as like Trixie
says like I realized recently
that like
people make easy content on youtube
people make low effort content on youtube
not because they want to make art that's bad
but just because
it's easier and it makes them more money
it's like wow
really you figured that out did you
that's great
I'm proud of you
it's almost so like
how could you not know that already
that I thought that was building to a different point
but it wasn't
but she does know she said it before
she said all that shit before
no Digi bro said it before
but Digi bro was just a character
she was playing
that was just a character you idiot
you fell for it
how could you think
you were a real person
I couldn't possibly
think that
how dare you accuse me of that
I would never
when I said that before
you were supposed to assume
that I meant the opposite
actually
okay
okay that's enough
enough
anything else before we go to voicemails
should we go to voicemail
what
alright well let's do one
first voicemail of the day
is called
okay
first voicemail of the day
oblivion
oh sorry
I saw your message and it looked blank
and I was like why did you post a blank
now I see
you posted a snail
very good
first voicemail I'm posting it here
is called sad piece
alright
if we're ready
in three two one
go
hey Ben
it's a weekly reminder
to catch up on one piece
so you can be on the podcast
awww
jeez
you took too long Ben
I did take too long
I thought it would be around forever
this is what happens
when you don't appreciate what you've got
it slips through your fingers
pay of paradise and put up a parking lot
pay of paradise and put up a pcp
uh
yeah
and put up a podcast
no take down the podcast
pay of podcast put up a pcp
basically
I know that was a
sorry sorry
no no I just finished
I know that was a joke
but like it actually made me a little sad
I gotta move on
I don't want to think about it
next one is called
what is your opinion
oh lol
oh sorry the next one is not a voicemail
it's just a question don't listen to this voicemail
it doesn't count
the actual it's just a text question
what's your opinion on Trixie's videos
pre-yig and post-yig
okay
um well we talked about that
a moment ago
post-yig
dog shit
the work of like a delusional narcissist
pre-yig
I would say it's similar like everything that has happened
since has made me reconsider
all the past videos and I now realize
like wait actually it's kind of always
been the case that Trixie like
doesn't understand what she's talking about
half the time
isn't like able to say anything
that isn't like directly about herself
just
is kind of stupid
and kind of always was actually
my favorite
Digi Bro content was
Digi Bros. the Let's Play
series with Victor
unironically
my favorite I had gone back and listened
to that a few times
I'm glad that child's still up
because Victor owns it now
I genuinely think that the real
talent like Trixie
thinks her talents are such
and such but her actual talent
was always only ever
to like make
to make like losers and like weirdos
like think that she is like
them
that's what did it for her
more than like
her ability to like
make compelling points or like
articulate something
something
impactful or whatever
it's like the
I don't know
just terrible
there's like nuggets of good video
scattered around but I couldn't remember
yeah sure
which ones? I remember the good ones
do you remember Love?
do you remember Love? oh no I don't remember that
you forgot Love?
what is it?
where's Urban Dictionary?
I don't know
we don't have Nate to help us
you don't have Nate to look it up
on Urban Dictionary
Nate's always a hero with the link
remember Nate?
I don't
we have forgotten Nate
we have forgotten
the next
question is another text question
it's not the audio
the PCP Corner Guy
we rebranded
the PCP died and we rebranded it
and now we do Tombstones
and that's what happened to the PCP Corner Guy
I guess he's probably also dead
he's also probably buried somewhere
he died again
I guess he died
I guess he's dead
that's the canon answer
okay next one and this is the audio
one is called Do It
so let's give this a listen
go
I was thinking the exact same thing this week
I was looking at the logo it's like why don't we just change it to be PCP
it's stupid
nobody calls it TPC
that's true
it's hard
it would take me like an hour
it would take me like an hour to change the logo
no you're wrong
you're an idiot
because I would have to find the font
and I don't know what font it is
I would have to recreate it by hand
which would be annoying
just copy the P
do different font, different CD
I guess I could kind of just copy the P
and that would take most of the work out of it
yeah I guess I could just do that
no but like because
there's no high res
okay I would have to find the high res version
of it I think there is one in the
Google Drive
the high res version has like the
just cut off
it's always been an annoyance
you just give me $15 to vector it
and then you'll have infinite resolution
no
they'll never get my $15
you're gonna give me $15 when you make more
than me on Patreon
oh shit
that'll be $15 over 15 months Ben
okay well I'll take what I can get
I guess
okay next voicemail is called
it's called why do boomers
and there it is
okay why do boomers
3, 2, 1, go
why are boomers
so obsessed with gas prices to determine
whether or not a politician is good
because boomers love cars
and
they're self centered
I understood
boomers are the real
it's just a very obvious
I listened to gas and I was really confused
what
do you not call it gas
it was cars or gas
there's petrol and gasoline
which I think are exactly the same thing
oh yeah yeah nice
gas
my parents were always like
gas prices are just a very obvious
it actually fluctuates
and you can see it very clearly
every day when you drive
so it's just really in your face
oh gas prices are up
I notice that all the time
so I guess politics are bad now
because the gas is more expensive
it's just a very obvious
it's just a very obvious thing
it's a very obvious indicator of something
god damn gas prices are so high
we need to go bomb some more middle eastern countries
to get that cheap gas
I guess so
although
although we don't actually
import that much gas
we get it from oil rigs
or whatever
well maybe the UK is different
but in America we mostly
create our
oil domestically
the thing about gas
from Saudi Arabia and the Middle East
is mostly about maintaining
control in the region
controlling the supply to our enemies
like Russia and stuff
it's not about acquiring the oil
for ourselves so much
if you control the
oil's patreon page
then you get to
cut a bit off the top
every time there's a transaction
if you make more oil
than your enemy
then you have to give them oil
on patreon
imagine if Russia had a patreon page
I'll donate one drop
I'll pledge one drop of oil per month
imagine that
countries having patreons and then if you pledge
a certain amount you get citizenship
if you pledge a certain amount
you'll be Putin's best friend
I get called to give you a zoom call
every few months I get a call from
some fucking police fundraiser
or another
yesterday I got a call from something called
the Trollmans fund
which I'm sure is a police thing
and I always hang up on them
I think it might be the same guy
under a bunch of different aliases
maybe they just all sound the same
next the voicemail
is called
sorry for sending two voicemails
in a row
okay
three two one go
hey Ben you should sing more often
you have a nice singing voice
thanks
go ahead Ben
show us your stuff
you should try it
I like singing
and I think I'm okay at it
I don't get much
opportunity to do it
like it doesn't come up
that much in like
stuff that I do
I don't know
sorry
I wouldn't mind doing it more
sing
sing right now
no I won't
I won't do it off the cuff I refuse
I refuse
next voicemail is called fried vocalist
three two one go
it's time
to get
organized
yes
you know why
because I say
so
I don't agree
when I say so
and maybe some things are
that simple
yeah get organized
clean your room it's good for you
I guess
I mentioned last week
I have a giant pile of boxes in the corner of my room
my room is like too big
my room is like a little bit too big
and I don't have like enough furniture
to fill it with
so one corner of my room is just a pile
of boxes just because something's got to take
up that space
I don't know fuck it
next voicemail is called
hater
oh no
three two one go
Ben why you always hating
why are you such a hater
sipping on hater aid
gib don't hate
yeah I do
I see the whole time I hate everybody
I am always hating
but like
maybe people need to hate more
I don't know
uh sometimes
there's such a thing
no no no okay okay
seething okay
coping and seething and molding
are not the same thing as hating
being a hater
is being like a naysayer
like a party
like being like oh
yes
that thing sucks
that thing's stupid
you can hate without molding
you can be like a casual hater who's just like
that's dumb I don't like that
fucking cowboy bebop netflix
stupid
yeah yeah
um
some people I think there's
some things
that more people should be haters about
and I am proud
and I proudly hate on those things
um and that's my
official I think it is
I think it's good to
like to throw shit
at things that deserve it such as
big like governments
things who are and like
corporations and all that
like vaccine mandates
no I mean like when they're doing
bad stuff not good stuff
what about our freedom
fuck freedom freedom sucks
you can't what
huh maybe freedom does
kind of suck maybe that's why I should go
and like pledge to russia's patreon
yeah
um
next
okay next voicemail is called
uh bge monthly
cast clip one
uh okay it's loading
this is stealing
there are two clips this is clip one
three two one
go
and you know ben ben is my
literal biological brother we grew up together
we got a lot of memories together and
I mean hey what can I say I love my brother
I love my brother
I love him he's a good guy
uh I got his back
and uh he's clearly got my back
sometimes
uh
that's sweet that's sweet
I'm glad he thinks so
because I think that's generally true
I won't you know
I won't I won't uh
you know
you know did you see the thing the thing in the news about like
Chris Cuomo
getting uh
fired from NBC or whatever
you know what I'm talking about nope
okay
well oh sum up
the governor shit I think
I think he was the governor of New York
or he might have been the mayor of New York City
I always confuse those two
but one of those two was this guy Andrew Cuomo
and he was
really popular for a minute there during
covid the libs were
really loving Andrew Cuomo
but then like he did a bunch of
shit he like lied about a bunch of figures he like
got a lot of people killed
due to like fucking around behind
the scenes with with like the data
and stuff he acted on bad data
he he obscured figures to
make himself look better make the state
look better a lot of people
died uh but that
was fine nobody cared about that but then
there was like a sexual harassment scandal
because he like made he like
made women feel uncomfortable and like
was behaving inappropriately
and that was a big
thing that caused a big scandal and I think
got him like impeached or something
and his brother Chris Cuomo
is like
one of the head like anchors
for a major news network I think it's NBC
I forget
but apparently Chris Cuomo
was basically
like
giving Andrew like privileged information
he was he was basically colluding
with Andrew to like
help him get off these charges of like
sexual harassment which is obviously
inappropriate behavior
for you know a national
news anchor and the governor
of like a state or mayor
of a major city or whatever
so in this
shit came out and they they they fired
Chris Cuomo over it
and a bunch of other
journals were like if my brother
did something illegal
you know I'd have his back right
like I'd have my brother's back
no matter what and it's like you know that's
that's nepotism that's collusion that's
illegal you're literally just admitting to being
corrupt is what you're saying there
so
so I wouldn't have Nate's I wouldn't have
Nate's back if he did anything like Andrew
Cuomo I wouldn't
I wouldn't say it's not
it's not an unconditional back having right
there are things you could do that I
would be like I can't have your back about this
definitely but in general it's true I
yeah but in general it's true
I do have Nate's back and I'm glad
that he knows that
that reminds me of my brother
who
I mentioned this a few years ago also was
involved in a sexual harassment
not sexual harassment he was being sued by Sony
because
I guess I could tell this quickly this is a
fucking crazy thing that happened a few years ago
my younger
brother wanted access to
the PlayStation 4
like development kit or something
it's like some proprietary
software but you have to
that game companies can license to make
PlayStation 4 games or maybe it was PSP or something
but
he was just a guy he didn't have access to
it and he wanted it so he
and my little brother is
autistic and he's like not very good at
like
communicating I guess
but somehow he managed to create
a fake how old is he
he was like 16 17 or something
he managed
to create a fake identity
and a fake company and get it officially
registered with the New Zealand government
and a fake location
like if you look
it up if you look up the coordinates
on the map it's just an empty field where he
claimed his his game companies office
was he got the company officially registered
so that he could like
you know go to go to Sony
and ask for the PlayStation 4 like
dev kit
and they gave it to him
and then he just leaked it
and
they caught him immediately
that sounds like something you could sue over
it's very dangerous for him
they caught him immediately because
when they give the kit to someone they like
they embed your information in there so that they can
track it and they caught him
immediately because he was too young
they tried to sue my whole family and I'm like
oh my god
I don't have your back but also my family
can't afford to deal with this so
I hope
I can't defend him
but
I'm glad it ended up getting resolved
without
a whole bunch of money being lost
for my family
so I mean wait
did that
resolve itself? it did get resolved
again my mom's a lawyer
which helps so
she was able to be like look
he's a minor like they were trying to argue
that like he's narrowed
literally narrowed a virgin and a minor
he's a neurodivergent minor who
they were trying to argue well
it's clearly negligence the parents
you should have known this was going on
for me knowing what my brother's like
he's like a little
little goblin troll in his room
he doesn't like communicate much
it's very hard to know what he's getting up to
of course and if you try to
peak your nose on his business
he gets very agitated
and lashes out so it's
not smart to like do that
you have to give him space
so they were able to get it settled
on those grounds but sony really wanted to
sue my family over that
jesus that's kind of scary
wait one sec I need another
I need another sparkling water
I've got the small bottles they don't last
they don't last long enough
oh jesus oh god it's gone
everywhere
I'm gonna pee
okay
okay I'm back just kidding
didn't go everywhere
ah fuck although it might
it fell out of the
I just remembered another thing
it fell out of the fridge so it might go ever when I open it
let's
no no it's fine okay few
anyway what did you remember
what's up I just remembered
the other time
my mom sued the New Zealand government
and won
I'm just remembering all these things
well what
well in 2008
my mom was
the PA
for sanitarium the New Zealand branch
of sanitarium which is like a big health food company
anyone living in Australia or New Zealand will be
familiar with them they make up and go
that's like a very unappetizing name
for a food company
well the word sanitarium is
unappetizing to me because
that's all I knew them for
I didn't know what that word had another meaning
well in any case my mom was in a car accident
she was just parked
and another car slammed into her
and like it fucked up her neck really badly
and she lost her job
and so she had to go on like a you know
I thought you were gonna say she lost her jaw
like she was like
like Roger Ebert like no jaw
okay
no she got a slip of disc in her neck
she had to go on like a disability
that's awful
she had to go on a disability for people
who've been in accidents
and it never like properly healed
she was just an awful pain
for like 5, 6, 7 years
like the pain still hasn't gone away
since 2008 it's never completely gone
and for the first like 3 years
she was like
on so many like pain killers
that like you're not supposed to take them
for like long periods of time
to like be taken at that dosage
for a lot so
like the pain killers were building up in the system
and like fucking up things even more
she had a surgery that didn't work out
and like 3 years into this
she has an appointment with her
I think it's called ACC
is like the government
organization that handles like this benefit
she had an appointment
you know one of her regularly scheduled appointments
with the doctor to see how she was doing
and they just
were like oh hey this appointment
we're going to see a different doctor
not your usual one
we're sending you our special doctor
and it has to be on this date and if you don't show up on this date
at this time you're losing your benefit
and they'd never been that stringent before
it was like whoa what the fuck
so she goes into this new
office with a new guy
the second she walks in the guy's like
oh hey we're here to talk about your degenerative condition
which is translation for
what?
I mean that's not the car accident
you're just old
my mom was like early 30's
at this point
and so
they tried to like his point
without even looking at the scans
he didn't look at anything
he was just like a government appointed doctor
who just said oh yeah you're getting old
and the car accident had nothing to do with it
and I haven't looked at your records
I'm just saying this you're off the benefit
basically just lying
like this is his job
is to just like come up with bullshit reasons
to kick people off the benefit
and he's done this to a whole bunch of people
who've like sued him in the past
and it is bullshit
and my mom
sounds like a racket
so my mom sued him and the government over it
and eventually won
but because all of the
it took years for the lawsuit to like
actually go through by the time it actually
like succeeded
so she gave her like all three years
worth of overdue payments at once
and for that year
it pushed her over a certain income bracket
and like most of it got taxed away anyway
so
fucking hell
no come on
but like progressive income brackets though
like can't
I feel like in a situation like this
when it's money of a government owes you
like maybe that should like be exempt
shouldn't be taxable
for like someone who has a disability
I
I was on
I was on pandemic unemployment
benefits
for last year and some of this year
and I was a bit dismayed
and confused to learn that like
yeah that's taxable like you have to pay taxes
on that for some reason
like okay
well
why don't you just give me less then
if you're just gonna tax me for it but okay whatever
guys whatever you want to do
yeah
oh well yeah I see
well
slipped slip disc in the neck sounds pretty fucking bad
yeah I live in fear of a slip
disc anywhere I mean
and the neck sounds like basically the worst place
you can get it
I would imagine that probably the lower
on the spine it is the less
bad it is
I had a slipped disc in my playstation
it was awful
yeah
you gotta grip it
you gotta put the pad on
or something
you gotta clean that disc
okay so the next voicemail
is BGE Monthly Cast Clip 2
and how much do you want to bet that
this one just like is the exact opposite
it's like
after the last one it's like but
he sucks and I hate Ben
actually how much do you want to bet
that it's like cancelling out the first one
I don't know
alright well let's see
oh maybe
I just feel like
the fact that this voicemailer left
two voicemails
makes me think that probably one is
like a direct response to the other
but I don't know we'll see
there it is
3, 2, 1, go
I'm a dictator
I literally do things for the greater good
I kill a couple people
who would have undermined my regime
for the greater good and everyone's ultimately happy
but also I raped a bitch
I felt like raping this girl this one time
is that fine
I'm sorry what did I say
I said I couldn't defend you if you pulled some Cuomo shit
frankly
this is beyond Cuomo level
I'm sorry Nate
you're on your own
I can't have your back
the voicemailer knew what our conversation would be
they predicted everything
damn I can't believe Nate really
I can't believe he really is
doing all that stuff
I can't believe that
Nate said that
and since Nate isn't part of the mainstream
media I have to take everything he says
exactly at face value
tragic Terran family's
apart
okay
next
okay there was a comment
and I left a mean response to this comment
I was very mean to this guy
but I feel like it was warranted
there was a comment that was like
on the last episode they said
you guys have to stop with the unironic Nate hate
pretending like he's a literal monster
yeah I saw that as well
I don't even remember what
I don't remember what we said
I don't remember what we said that was that bad
I think maybe we
made fun of him for
not making enough videos or something
or something about being
like disappointed about the
podcast ending
I don't know
I felt like he was taking whatever it was was too serious
it's not that serious
anyway
next voicemail
next voicemail is
it's called once again on my pokemon
pokemon bullshit
3, 2, 1, go
hey y'all
it's AVE
I'm making a pokemon rom hack
and I'd love to include you guys
in the background
or whatever
so could you just tell me some of the like
pokemon that must be on your team
alright thanks
oh
chocolate
well
pokemon
lowpony
lowpony guard of war
sowazzle
definitely
lekitang
hatterine
she has big boobs
it's canon
oh hatterine is good
I have two like
pseudo canon teams
I have my team in the minecraft server
which is
swine, vulcarona
crowbat
I'm forgetting
yes yes
and he's poisoned
just like
the vaccines
he's 5G
oh fuck what else
I'm drawing a blank
I'm so stupid
whatever go watch the streams
okay and then there's my cop killer
my cop killer team
which is what I used in the rfck battle against
the rowdy fucker
and also what is in my NPC
cop killer version which is also in the server
that one had another team
and that one
I think crowbat was on there was definitely a corvanite
I really like corvanite
a bulk up corvanite is one of my favorite
mons
so that one's pretty good
mammoth swine, corvanite
I don't know
just do whatever you think is good
pokemon that I would have
are like
usually cute
and or edgy
I don't have any specifics
except maybe duskull
I love duskull
which is the cute
spooky one
and I like water pokemon
and
sometimes a big pokemon
I don't know there's lots of pokemon that are good
I could think of many like teams
I mostly like edgy pokemon
but I really really like
ulteria and mega ulteria
that's like one of my favorites
it's not edgy
it's just epic
it's like
epic wistful
different type
I remember using a combo
that I don't remember now
but it was between ombreon
and gardavor
it was mega gardavor probably
gardavor, gardavor
but I really like
I really like ombreon
and shackle, shackle is awesome
there should be a goregeist
as well because that's punk
that's a pumpkin
yeah, true
you can't have a shackle
and an ombreon on the same team
you don't need tools
I just like shackle
shackle in general
it's my favorite
there's plenty of pokemon
that I really like but you can't use
there's a poke
shackle is like he's kind of good
but he's kind of mostly bad
but it's really funny to actually win
a battle with shackle
yeah
oh wait, wait, wait
I've got like three, no four
so duskull, sharpido
goregeist and spheal
those are four
I'm not sure about the other two
so cool
yeah, he's edgy
but he's also kind of a ball
I like spherical pokemon
he is so short
sharpido is such a little stump
there is a pokemon that is a punk
that's goregeist
except her like pumpkin
is her thick belly
pumpkaboo and goregeist
that's the line
that's the unevolved form of goregeist
oh
yeah
I see it
I have not played the gen that goregeist is from
I've just seen her and I'm like oh yeah
is he from gen
five
six
I think it might be gen six
I also used a lot of mimikyu
back then
mimikyu is really cool
mimikyu is good
oh shit, wait, there's another one
what's the sun and moon pokemon
lilligant
has the big
wait, no, lilligant is older than that
oh, okay, well whatever
no, no, no, I'm thinking of bolossum
it's not bolossum
lilligant has the big poofy legs
which I really like
was lilligant new in sun and moon?
that's where I first saw her
I played gen three and then skipped straight to sun and moon
I don't know anything in between
how's that plan
pokemon
with huge legs
yeah, with a dress
no, I think you're thinking of
sarena
sarena is like the purple one
that looks like a
you know what
I have a from
gen four on awards
I have this problem that I
begin watching the anime
Japanese
so I have this mix of
American names and Japanese
names of pokemon
it's really, really confusing
starting from gen four
it's like Jesus Christ
I usually name like
I'm not familiar with the Japanese name sadly
it's really confusing, I hate it
I'm trying to think what
mangosteen
the fruit that sarena
line is based on is a mangosteen
I just thought of
like a variant of muck
that was like made of magma
but that doesn't exist
it's actually a dark cloud enemy
oh, I remember that
it was on a draw cast
where we did pokemon
combos
no, pokemon of different typing
this is supposed to be lilligant but fighting type
no, it's specifically
fighting ground
every second she is fighting the ground
it's awesome
it's unsettling
I can't believe I'm looking at it
again
wow, well thank you for
sharing that
it's incredible
the next
the next voicemail
is called
uh
wait
the next one is called
the mentioned link
and it includes a link but we'll listen to
the voicemail first
one sec, it's loading
come on, post please
there we go, okay
3, 2, 1, go
yo ben, give everyone the link
that I put in the title
this is a game called Undertale 2
and it looks like it's just going to be
a little meme, like a dumb little meme game
but if you try it out
you'll honestly be shocked by how good it is
I was
if you like stuff like Undertale
obviously, The Simpsons
Toho, Tails gets trolled
weird RPG maker games
like Hilux and Space Funeral
and fishing minigames
you'll love this game
I could go on and on
about what I like about it but
just give that page a look, see if you like it
try it out, you won't be disappointed
from
I was already going to recommend this
but it became even more relevant
when you talked about
your concerns for the copyrighted material
in your own game
this game has way more copyright infringement
than you could ever hope to achieve
so I don't think you need to worry about that
yeah but it's on itch though
this guy makes other games, they're all on itch
it's not a problem
so yeah, people at home
Google Undertale 2, Revenge of the Robots
it's the first link
you gotta try it
this does look awesome
not to mention the artwork is
extremely epic with a hint of gay
I love it
this does look awesome
yeah
this is on itch
where I was not worried about
copyright stuff being a problem
on itch, I was worried about it being a problem
on Steam, which it probably
still would be
but
yeah
I will probably
play this, this looks
really good actually
you guys see him this shit
I'm looking at it
I went to the page and the animations
maybe we should checkles for hackles
maybe we could do that
maybe we could checkles for hackles
Kazy's been telling me
to play Undertale 2
the other one
Delta Rune 2
for a chapter 2
and I keep saying yeah I'll do it
maybe I want to do this instead
yeah say it's Delta Rune 2
and just put this up
Delta Rune 2
is old news
Undertale 2 is the new
Delta Rune is the new hotness
whatever
okay next
voicemail
is
shit
here this is the link and it is called
it's called Penny Packer
3 2 1
go
hey I sent a voicemail
last time and I misgendered Hippo
since I haven't listened to the podcast
in years I forgot about his metamorphosis
you did it again
you fucking bitch
I also maintained that Ben is pretty gay
but you know at least
he's not as cringe as Nate is these days
who desperately tries to sound smart
but he just comes off as a doofus instead
but you know
at least Hippo deserves to be called a she
she's trying at least
okay if we're talking about whatever
a bitch did you fell into
or whatever gay shit he calls himself these days
bro no fuck off
I know it's just crazy
and I don't want to respect his pronoun
since he's just addicted to Adderall at least dick
no fuck you
his gang is pretty cringe as well
yeah that's about it
the gang is cringe but this voicemail is very cringe
alright I don't remember
when they misgendered me in another voicemail
but fuck you
that's not how
that's not how trans works
you don't get to decide
when and if
you want to respect a person's identity
I think
that trans people
are valid but I don't think
chris chan counts because
chris doesn't
wear makeup
and also did a crime
and that means that
they're a boy now
oh
shut the fuck up
that was irritating
such a terrible voicemail
I would think you would know better
I've said
I've explained why this is wrong
I would
oh no just the ones I like
just the ones that I like
just the ones that I like count
if I don't like you it doesn't count
you're one of the good ones
I'd rather you just not be bigoted
actually it'll be better
guys from the voicemails you have the option
to shut up
don't say anything but you
fucking morons
what the hell was that
I'm going to kiss my trans husband
on the cheek just to spite you
also the go fund me is still going on
I'm gonna link that
the annoying thing is that I feel like
they think of themselves as
like trans accepting
but clearly they don't
they're not really
thinking about it correctly
that is the annoying part
it's the
the idea that
respecting a trans person
means just coddling them
or like giving them
if they're trying hard
then you throw them a bone
and you gender them correctly
but other than that
they don't really like
like it's
it speaks to like
a general
like not
what's the way to phrase it
not agreeing with the terms
but just doing it because it's a nice thing
to do not because it's like correct
the implicit assumption
the implicit assumption there is that
the implicit assumption there
is that you
the other person
you get to choose
you get to pick it for another person
and oh if you
and if someone like
if they please you
if you decide okay this person is cool
I'll do them the favor
I'll respect their pronouns
because I like them
but if I don't like them for whatever reason
obviously then I'm not gonna do it
they don't deserve it
they don't deserve to get that from me
because I
am the chooser
I get to decide if they deserve it or not
and I'm gonna choose not to give it to them
because they haven't earned it
you gotta work for it, you gotta earn it
it's terrible, it's awful
it makes me really mad
fuck you
fuck you penny packer
get fucked
next voicemail
is called
my accidental meeting with ben saint
at mice
uh
this must be about
because if you remember I went to
I tabled at
it was not a proper mice
which is the massachusetts independent comics expo
they didn't have a normal mice this year
they had a mini mice
that was an outdoor thing
uh
and it was smaller than usual
but I was there one of the two days
so let's hear
it, okay, 3, 2, 1, go
hahahaha
no
well that last part is completely wrong
ben saint would never part with bitcoin
I would never
I would never sodle
uh the
no, you should know from last
episode that I converted all my bitcoin
to ethereum so that I can pay the gas prices
to get my usdt and usdc out
duh
but what about your usdc
no, you don't gotta check
wait, I gotta check gas prices
no
ethereum gas price
are we up
wait, okay, ethereum average gas price
are we up or are we down
oh, we're down, we're down to only 78
hey, that's the lowest it's been
since october
that usdt is
ah, it's gonna be so good
wait, okay, we gotta check the price of bitcoin
no
we gotta check the price of bitcoin
nah, shut up, nah, we do
the people expected
they come to us for financial advice
no, well, they shouldn't
I encourage that behavior
bitcoin is, oh, no, it went up
no, it went up a bit, it's over 50
oh, no, it's over 50
bros, what do we do?
it's over 50
what are you gonna do, cry about it?
lie down and run
I'm gonna livestream tears
I'm gonna get a bucket
and they're gonna have the camera webcam on the bucket
and see how many tears fall
a lot
well, bummer
I was hoping it wouldn't go back up over 50
but it did
oh well
next voicemail
is called
wisdom potato
sorry, I'm finding it here
there and everywhere
okay, wisdom
wisdom potato
3, 2, 1, go
I hate the procrastinator's podcast
I fucking hate it
I can't get through a single point without
literally every single host
constantly, like vultures
try and jump on me
and cannibalize my point
to the point where it's unrecognizable
Gladys, I didn't know
you were on the procrastinator's podcast
I'm very sorry for trampling
all over your potato point
um
whatever
next one is called
join the F-A-G
parentheses
stomp out the red pill
what is this?
okay, okay
let's go
3, 2, 1, go
hey PCP, thank you so much
for all of these episodes, tons of
entertainment, keep them coming
um, you know, you've already given so much
but I'm just asking one more thing
um, you know, I understand
that this is a, you know, it went from the
most red pill podcast on the planet
to now probably the most blue pill podcast
on the planet, and I need your help
if you couldn't tell by my voice
I am a high schooler
probably one of the last high school HPCP
fans left, but that's neither here nor there
what happened is
the turning point USA
alt-right group
they're definitely redpilled as fuck
and they're putting up posters
all over my school because they started
their own fucking club
and it is angering
so what I've been doing is I've been working on
my own grassroots opposition
um, to them
and what I request from you guys
is um, we have an Instagram account
it's at fagpenrid
F-A-G-E-N-N-R-I-D-G-E
it's the fellowship of atheist gamers
and we're trying to
at least overtake them
and followers, we're at like
20 I think right now and they have
like 124 so it's not going to be
hard, but I think once we get
to that level I'm going to be able to
you know, I'm going to have a lot more firepower
you know, um, right, like I have
there's already a lot of infographics up there
they're just kind of parodies of the posters that they already have
hanging up, um, you know, I don't want to
toot my own horn, but I think they're pretty good
anyways, um, thanks for
your time
um, okay, funny cause
a bit of an edgy name, but
it's not so bad I guess
a bit of an edgy name
fuck turning point, they're cringe
I mean, yeah, fuck turning point
I think Munchie told me that like
at his school they're also like
turning point just kind of like shows up
oh no, and just kind of
they don't really like advertise it
they sort of like
will show up under like the guise of something else
but then like when you go and like talk to them
they'll be like, hey have you heard about turning point USA
uh, have you heard about
that the Democrats
you know, I'm looking at this
Instagram, I don't know if
the
the F slur angle
is going to be that useful
I feel like
like progressive types would be
pushed away, they're not going to be pulled
to turning point like
who are you, who are you
trying to get a reach with this
as a
as a dunk
like as a dunk against
turning point
because you know, it's F-A-G-G-O-T
a fellow Atheist
gamer's grassroots opposition to
turning point, I guess it's kind of funny
I do think it's a bit
is it a play on turning point, does turning point
have a similar acronym
uh, no
you should have taken
parody
it's not like a parody of turning point
it's funny, but like it's kind of like pointless
in why it's like that
pointless even
hmm
turning point less
okay, who was President Ronald Reagan
President Ronald
Ronald Redpilled Reagan was the 40th president
of the United States of America
uh, and the 16th
overall
Republican president, his most important act for the country
was his president for his work as an actor
bedtime for Bonzo is, without a doubt
the best and arguably most genre-defining
monkey movie of the 20th century
with a 5.4 out of 10 on IMDB
it takes the peak of presidential cinema
but enough about monkeys, let's talk about
those monkeys
from those African countries
damn them, they're still uncomfortable wearing shoes
yep, he said that
should have known better to trust Richard Nixon
in a private conversation, amazing right
who would have thought that an 80s era conservative
was racist
I thought I would talk about Reagan
well I guess
he's saying that Nixon like
leaked the con-
maybe Nixon wrote it down
and like that's how they know
Nixon had their seats for that beef
I think so, yeah
that sounds right
what I know turning point for
is the
fucking women's conference they did
which I saw a live stream
when Vosh like reviewed it
and these people
are actually insane
for the first like hour
actually no, if it was an hour or not
you mean turning point?
yeah, returning point women's conference
for the first hour I have this conservative woman up on stage
who's like, oh my god, cute servitives
you're so cool, we're gonna go out there
we're gonna be girl bosses
we're gonna get jobs and be business women
and it's gonna be so cool
and then Charlie Kirk goes on stage
looks at all the women and says
yeah, if you pursue a career
you're not gonna be happy
you need to stay in the home and not have a job
you're worthless and you will never be a man
and you can never be on the same foot as a man
and you suck and then all the women
cream their pants
it was funny
that's what they wanted, the first one is there to set them up
to set the pins up so Charlie could
just bowl them over and knock them all down
be like, yes
it was a
a false flag
a red herring
I think I support F.A.G
they're definitely
they're definitely better than the alternative
I like what they're doing
I support it, I support the name
I'm in a gay relationship, I can say it
it's a great idea
I think I would encourage people to
I think it would be pretty funny
if the fellowship of atheists gamers
were to defeat turning point
USA
at Penridge High School
I think I would call that a W
oh, okay
they say the F.A.G
is
a parody of
Penridge
turning point USA and F.C.A
which is the fellowship of Christian athletes
so I guess that's what
they're going to do
wait
I think I'm on board
yeah, if I used Instagram
I would give a follow
if only, if only I could use Instagram
I do
actually, I do have an old
Instagram that I have not logged into in years
so I don't know, maybe later
I'll try and hop on and see if I still remember
my password
Instagram
at F.A.G Penridge
with two ends
give them a like
give them a boost
I support it
next voicemail
is called
x8
here we go
in three, two, one
go
he is
coming
Santa Claus
to town
is x
is x8 like
an edgier version of
Nate
is it like the nobody
is it like Nate's nobody
oh shit, it is
it's gotta be
maybe
I can't think of what else to think
like they all have an X in their name
like Luxus and Zaynart
so Zate is the name
yeah
maybe
what would Nate's
nobody, would it be like
Texan
Exant
I think Exant is pretty good
Texan
yeah
Tenza
Zenat, I don't know, I'm just typing random shit
Zenat
is probably closest to what it could be
I don't know the name of the convention
I don't like that one
because it has the nat
it's not different enough
you're right
you're so right
one of those other ones I said was probably pretty good
I'm so right
next voicemail
is called
let me find it
a message about one piece being political
oh no
oh yeah
here we go
3, 2, 1
this is from Berserk Chip
3, 2, 1, go
so I'm out of the loop
I'm behind a couple episodes
it's been busy
so I don't know what the deal is with calling one piece political
I don't know if we're trolling conservatives or something
but
you said at one point
the show is clearly political
because the world government
are the bad guys
Ben
it's a show about pirates
of course
law enforcement and government bodies
are gonna pose an antagonistic force
when it's a show about pirates
it's like saying the show Dexter is anti-cop
because the cops get in his way sometimes
when he's trying to serial kill people
I'm cringing
now I'm not saying one piece isn't political
but like if you're gonna say that
if that's the meme
you gotta have a better argument
like
one piece is political because
Luffy only ever cares about himself
and his tightly knit family
and that's like a staunchly conservative mindset
if you're gonna say it's political
I would go with something closer to that
anyway
I love you and I was
dumb
this is really dumb
you're right
that obviously
it's a story about outlaws
the government is the antagonists
to our protagonist
yes obviously that's true
but like
think about how the world government is
portrayed
do you think
do they seem good
are they portrayed as though they're doing
what's right and they just happen to be
at odds with the protagonist
no
they're evil and it's because they have all this
systemic power that they abuse
it's so obvious
it's so obviously about
the government is bad, the police are bad
here are the ways that they're bad
and that's reflected in
one piece, it's obviously true
give me a fucking break
the thing with like
cops and robbers
the show chooses to show the robbers
the pirates in a good light
and to show them the protagonist
the main character
good-hearted monkey Luffy
as like a pirate
clearly implying
then a political message
that not all people determine
like Daned as criminals
are bad and the world government
is the one who decides who is a criminal who isn't
all Luffy wants to do is explore the ocean
he's not like actually a bad person
it's not like
you make a show
and it's about this
raper and he loves raping
you wouldn't show him as like the protagonist
as a good character
and then the police are
like
choosing who
is the good guy
is itself like a political statement
are you saying that rape man
my favorite anime is political?
it's very reductive
it's very reductive to be like
the show's about a pirate
so of course the bad
the police are the good guys
or are they
like there's no
nuance in that read
it doesn't take into account
what a pirate is
a lot of people don't know what it means
for something to be political
I think a lot of right-wingers
or otherwise
centrists would assume
that thing being called
political means
it's like
a character similar to how
drug PSAs happened in cartoons
in the 80s where the main character
of a popular TV show would
turn to the camera and say
hey kids, stay in school, don't do drugs
political messaging from your government
the America
that's not what being political means
being political is just having
an opinion on the way anything works
to be honest
I'll be honest
you could definitely take
a right-wing or libertarian message
away from one piece if you wanted
there's a really easy argument there
to be like
the government is incompetent
we need to reduce the size of government
everybody
we need to form tightly knit
clans and look out for our own
and that's what Luffy does
with the straw hats
he gets a clan together
and they look out for their own
and they live in this world
of the strongest
whatever
they live in a meritocracy
they have to prove themselves
in the marketplace of ideas
that is the grand line
and the competition for who will find
Raftel or whatever
you could totally make that argument
example of
an anime that has
an outlaw as the
protagonist and law enforcement
as the antagonist
that I would say probably is apolitical
and that one
the main character is a thief
and his opponent is
Inspector Zenigata
but like
neither one of them is portrayed as particularly
good and Lupin
he's pretty amoral but he's just doing
what he wants but he's likable
whereas Zenigata
is not really representative of
law enforcement as a whole
he's just one bumbling idiot
who is kind of acting on his own
right?
that doesn't really say anything about
the role of the police
or the government in society
one piece definitely does
way more than the other
I mean the Tenryubito
literally living at the top of the world
breathing different air
the Tenryubito and the Goro say
and they're completely protected
from all of the bad things they do
by the world government who they basically own
it's so clear that there's
there's
class inequality in one piece
in the world of one piece there's inequality
there are bad people
and good people
it's super obvious that systemic inequality
is such a huge fucking
theme in one piece I don't understand
how you can fancy
the whole fishman arc
the whole fucking fishman arc is about it
everyone can see that and they'll be like
that's a thing in one piece
some people don't understand
that's political for some reason
I don't know what they're imagining
exactly political meaning
maybe they're just getting caught up
in like twitter argument things
they assume
I don't know
political means when a character says
trans rights out loud or
something super explicit
that guy
who started that argument on twitter
I think his name was like
black D gamer
what was his name
his take was like
he would say stuff like yeah
like there is racism
yeah there is racism against
fishman in one piece
but like it's not about that
and it doesn't like say anything about it
it's just background
it's just background texture
for the story to happen
against
it doesn't say anything
it doesn't even say that it's bad
none of the characters react in any way
to the fact that slavery is there
they don't even get sad
they're all just like well I guess
we'll just have a fight with someone
not about that
but just in front of it
adjacent to it
I don't know
I don't
have any political interpretation of one piece
but there's also nowadays
this conflict
between the young pirates
these old fashion pirates
which is basically
a reality of
Japanese politics nowadays
like it's time to
the young ones
to step up and the lizards
to just go sleep
because Japan is still
ruled by a lot of old
fashion rules and politics
that they don't work
they don't work
Shin Godzilla
that movie
it's all about that
this is the only message of that movie
so you could also
it's about big lizard go boom
if you look at
the arc of
Wano itself
Wano being the Japan allegory
because it's the Japanese island in the world of one piece
there's so many parallels
to historical events
relating to Japan being closed off
from the rest of the world
which is why
they were
held back technologically
they don't have guns in Wano
they don't have like
dendin mushes and stuff
and the world government
sort of an allegory for America and western civilization
is like trying to get in
they're trying to open the country
there's like so many like
things in one piece
that seem just like
cool plot points in world building
I don't expect people to
understand the political
messaging of
it's clearly all there
to say with confidence
that there's nothing political about anything in one piece
is so weird
the people that I was arguing with
who get mad if you suggest that there's any
meaning to it at all
are like
they think that when you say
there's a political message
or there's a political meaning to it
you're saying that like
you're saying that
that's all it is
and there and like
in their mind that makes it like
that's like to call it
like not a real story
or something you're devaluing it
by saying that
when literally all I think
is just that like
the things that happened in the story
and the choices that Oda made in how he constructed it
say something
and illustrate
some ideas
that's literally it
but I don't know some people
are upset
I mean I know that like
there's like
there are
YouTubers who will talk and complain
about like woke things
in other cartoons
or media where it's like
they're pushing the transgender that oh
there's a gay wedding in Steven Universe
is like some aspect of like
it's political
quote unquote is to be
doing something
that's like
when there's a gay wedding that's political
but when like you know
a class of people that exist at the top
of society you know oppress
everyone underneath them
in order to you know maintain
the social hierarchy that's not political
that's just like that's just texture
I think like
I don't know exactly what these people believe
but I get a sense
there's at least some
people who see videos like that
think of the word political
meaning progressive
and then when they say one piece is political
they think well I don't believe
in this
this woke agenda so it's not political
actually and they just shut down
things are only political if they're being
done for the culture war
when Rebecca Sugar had a gay wedding
in her show she didn't do it because
she like liked the idea
or because she just wanted it to happen
or one of those characters to be together
she did it to put a middle finger
to the conservatives to be like
haha I'm brainwashing your kids that's why she did it
that's how they see things
I mean true and good for them
good for Rebecca
oh god
I guess a right
wing person would probably look at
the Tenryubito
and I don't know I'm just guessing here but my
assumption is they would assume that what
the Tenryubito
the real world analog of the Tenryubito
would be like the billionaire
pedophile elites
that are like
which is like
I guess you could maybe
make that parallel but like it doesn't make as much
sense because the Tenryubito
is a
common thing it's not like
it's not like a
you know buy your way in
you know
so it doesn't make as much sense to me but I guess
maybe you could
try and claim something like that
everybody loves one piece because the idea
of being the little man
I would respect that more than just be like
no it doesn't mean anything
no no it's an adventure story it's for kids it doesn't mean anything
there's no ideas
there are no ideas in this story
you just think about like
when Luffy punches a guy who told
it like haha I treat my
subordinates bad and I'm an asshole
and then Luffy punches him it's like yeah I
feel so good that that guy got beat
I love Luffy because
he cares about his Nakama and it's like
so there's no meaning to any of that
you know you think there's nothing there
of course there's something there everybody knows
there's something there that's why one piece is so
popular everybody loves
being you know rooting for the guy
oppressed by
you know ah my boss
the fucking government ah big thing
that is like hard to
comprehend that is controlling my life
I want freedom I want
me to be the one who punches people
everyone loves that everyone knows what
that feels like and that's why one piece is so
successful and it's just
it's just sad
to see that like I feel it makes me really mad
makes me really upset
people who get upset and argue about this stuff
really a lot of common ground there anyway
they're just not thinking about it right
and it's it's
upsetting a little bit
for sure for sure
um alright so that okay
then there's another one it's called an addendum
to the message about one piece
the beat I know
I know I know
sorry
but it's shorter it's shorter
there you go
okay three two
one let's jam
um okay so I
wrote the script for that voicemail
that I just sent about the one piece thing
and then I sent it
and then like five minutes later I was like
oh shit that kind of makes me sound like a conservative
so just to work clear I'm not a conservative
I don't like conservatives
they're mean to me in the YouTube comment section
I don't like them I just couldn't think of a liberal
way to say that one piece is
political if
I'll keep thinking about it
maybe I'll find it for you
then I promise I'll try
you mean isn't you mean isn't political
right
this guy they were saying
can't even keep his story straight
I don't even
what's even the point
I whatever
noted you are whatever
chip you're fucking
dead I see
if I see you out on the grand line
I'm fucking I'm fucking pillaging you
I'm reading you
something like Luffy just
cares about himself or his crew
that's it
have you ever read
one piece have you actually read
one piece have you read
alabasta or skypea
Luffy feels very strongly
for helping
people who are nice
and who he thinks
deserve to be helped
yeah
I think so
it's very simple
he acts selfishly
he acts selfish sometimes
well he acts selfish but it's like
for things that are not really that important
when somebody is getting hurt
like he doesn't just sit back and let it happen
he doesn't like that
he's the first one to act
okay so next voicemail
is called job offer
accepted
posting it there
we have like we have like four more
after this I think so we're getting down there
okay job offer
job offer accepted three two one
go
I'm like a weekly with this voicemail
but you were looking through voice gel and voice grill
and you were saying that somebody should be taking
keeping track of that shit
and Ben just said oh well we already have a marron pan
doing minecraft blah blah
just get him to do it and you know what
that sounds hilarious that's really funny
I proudly accept the title
of warden of maximum security
voice gel slash grail
and the funnier thing
is that I literally
fucking did it
I made it
the maximum security voice gel
and grail in the procrastinator's
minecraft server that's right
you audience member
if you're looking for something to get that
very special somebody this holiday season
get in the
procrastinator's minecraft server
become a patron $5
just talk to me
don't worry about it
patreon.com slash the procrastinators
dabbington municipality
dabbington go there
and you'll see it
and you'll see all the funny people that left all the voice
alright that's an I think I got the message across
thank you but I love you
there's so much in that server
we'll do another one
I probably won't want to do another
stream
until
phantom's revenge is done
which hopefully will be soon
but after that we should do another one
where is the
voice grail voice gel
thingy
where is it in the video description
of the pcp
there is a link to it in the video description
I need to check
if something has been rectified
it might not be
up to date
there may have been errors
in the accounting
I love those errors
results not guaranteed
yeah clusterpunk kitchen still hasn't been added
to the grail
what a shame
are you sure because we did release a bunch of people
no
to the grail
they were never added
after keto delito
after everyone unanimously
ages ago
yeah definitely should have been
added
are you sure they didn't sacrifice themselves
to release someone else
from the jail
okay
if you're sure I believe you
alright next voicemail
is called irish man gives you
a w
there it is
3 2 1 go
alright
take your w
I guess you deserve it for that
there take
which one
I think it's just an old purpose
old time use like
if you need a w
this irish man
can give you one
that's pretty nice of him
I appreciate it
sounds like a subscriber
like oh a new subscriber
a new donation
the jig
the jig starts playing
next one is called
irish man reacts to ben saint
3 2 1 go
the toy on the next service
tithe me at patreon.com
slash ben saint lol
cool
okay the next one
is called um
irish man reacts to gib
so let's uh
3 2 1 go
of the sucker
while pugging every other day
what a bastard
true
to do something so evil
while pugging
such a such an insult
yeah
that wasn't even like
it was hardly even about you
just reminded him
of some other bad thing that happens
okay
next voicemail is called
coming on stream
uh oh
here we go
3 2 1 go
according to the bible
one shalt not
wastes one seed in solitude
thereby condemning masturbation
as a mortal sin
but
what if i jerked off and came
live on stream in front of mother mary
in the whole world
that's not a way
man i guess there's only one way to find out
we'll never know
is to do it and then die at some point
yeah and let us know how it goes
okay the next
this is the last voicemail
is one cool dud
3 2 1 go
hey ben
i
stole something from
hobby lobby the other day
nice
was pretty proud of myself
hope you're proud of me too dad
now
i totally absolutely just don't get caught
and if you do get caught
just run
just run for it they can't they can't arrest you and they're not cops
and if there are cops there
don't resist
go quietly
they'll kill you
the pcp supporting acts of terrorism once again
acts of terrorism
stealing something
exactly
these liberals are going crazy
that fucking guy
this was maybe a couple weeks ago on twitter but there was shoplifting discourse
and someone was like
shoplifting is
he called it looting
but what he was actually talking about was shoplifting
but he implied that
people shoplifting
from stores
carries the risk of they coming with guns
and they're gonna hold you up at gunpoint
hold up the cashiers
and hold up the store employees
and it's like
no
that's armed robbery
that's a different crime
than the one you're describing an epidemic of
you fuck
but some people are just like
all crime is the same
any form of theft carries
with it the threat that the thief will
put the object
in a big bag with a money sign on it
and then pull out guns and knives and swords
and threaten you with them
this is just what criminals do
it's all
more ass in my mind
I can't distinguish between anything
that's what happened
that's how it would be on the internet sometimes
hey that was the last voicemail
we're done we did it
are we proud of ourselves
not really
no oh fuck
what would make you
feel proud of yourself
what would improve your self esteem
people should check out your work
if they have not seen it already
if they're a pcp had they probably
have seen your work somewhere around
but uh yeah
check out the page
incoming animation career please
yeah
I've seen one or two
animated pieces that you've made
you did the pumpkin alley up in the car
oh yeah
right right right right
that was really fun
that one was really good
with the shine going through the
going across the sunglasses
that was really fun
kaiju knows
kaiju knows what's up
kaiju knows what he's doing
check him out for sure
send us a voicemail
at speakpipe.com
become a patron hear our bonus episodes
join the minecraft server
all that good stuff at patreon.com
the procrastinators
um
DM me on twitter
if you are a Trixie
patron and you would like me to pay
you money to stop being a Trixie
I might as well
haven't plugged that in a while
that's still a service I offer
I'll never stop offering that service
uh it's true I mean it
I've done it before and I'll do it again
I used to do right then
tell your friends
I've come around
many such cases
my friend
um
I guess that's
what else
buy road to radcon
also DM me to buy more copies of road to radcon
I've still got like 50 copies
will I ever move that product
I've only got one copy I should have more
you got your copy
it got caught in the mail
I had to resend it
I got to include your apartment number
I gotta go like in one second
so
we're basically done
go to all the things
stay tuned for my secret project
the patreon.com
slash give and take
okay
alright peace
goodbye
alright I guess the rest of us are also done
so let's fucking
stop
bye
end of the episode are we done
yeah
bye
see ya
I'll use our take these sounds
and overlay them over like the last minute
so there's just multiple voices just like a coffin do it