Hello everyone and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. We're the reason people are dying
and you're the reason that we exist. No, that's not true.
It skits true. No, it's true.
It's sort of true. It's entirely true.
I'll give it to them. They can take credit for everything we've done.
How's everyone's week been? Another week of no fucking videos on the channel.
Thanks, YouTube. Love you.
Thanks, YouTube.
My favorite, the best. I'm so glad we tethered our existence to this hellscape.
They just keep saying, yeah, we'll work on it. And then, I don't know.
Yeah, for the time being, these are all going to be audio only, but when I hope the channel
is cleansed of stupid shit and we can post things safely again, they'll all come out
at once. Most people will be like, okay, I'll skip them.
Yeah. Most people who end up hearing this will hear it weeks later. Assuming they come
out at all. Assuming that the channel doesn't just get obliterated again.
And we just never return to YouTube. We just spur them for life and like, fuck you.
Why don't we just go full paywall? We don't need to go full paywall. We can have it free
on a website like every other podcast. I know we don't have to go full paywall.
I'm just saying, why not? You know?
You know, when you say it, I suddenly agree. As long as you say it.
Yeah, I did.
I don't know about paywalls, but I do like the word pay. So I'll sign off on it just
for that reason.
That's my logic as well.
Okay, cool.
I want to start off with a follow-up to what I was saying last time about suicide because
I had more ideas.
I've missed the juicy one.
More ideas about how to kill yourself?
No, no, no, no, no. It was about what I said about the idea of guilt, of inconveniencing
other people being the reason you stay alive is a bad thing. You shouldn't feel guilt.
That's bad.
What you could interpret from that is that time to, you know, like if you're not worrying
about inconveniencing yourself, you may as well just go and do it.
No, no, no, no. It's not what I mean. The idea was you're alive and you're really sad,
so you want to die. But you think about where you're going to die, like jumping off a bridge
or that ruins loads of people's day. Like your parents are going to be upset. Everyone's
going to be sad. It's like, oh, I don't want to feel, I don't want to make people upset.
That's not what, you know.
Sorry, I couldn't hear you for a minute there. Could you recap what you were just saying?
I'm just recapping what I was saying last time about guilt being a reason you stay alive.
And I think the reason guilt is a bad thing as a reason to stay alive is because it allows
you to not do anything. It is like a coward's way out in a strange way, because if you are
really sad with your life and everything sucks.
It's the coward's way out of the coward's way out.
Yeah, it is a way for you to say, well, I'm really sad and I want to die, but I can't
because of this, because I can't make people upset. And it sort of prevents you from forcing
yourself to ask the question of why live. And usually the solution to why live is happiness
or something like that. But the point I'm getting at is that if you're forced to ask
that question, you are going to be more proactive in making the solution, i.e. improving your
life to a point where you aren't sad anymore. And if you rely on the whole guilt thing to
keep you tethered to this mortal coil, you'll just be sad and be alive instead of trying
to improve yourself. That's my big suicide thought for the day.
So why live, hippo? Tell me. What's it all for?
Anime. Yeah. That's all I needed to hear.
Fuck. So I just watched Premiere last night. It was pretty cool. It definitely gave me a
reason to live. Oh yeah? Anime is pretty based, yeah.
That's pretty cool. That's pretty cool. I almost watched Isoken, but then I was like,
that sounds boring. No, cool. It's so good.
You stupid shit. That's like the back of man of anime.
Okay. I was just, I was like, that's a back of man of creativity.
I was like, Ben, you know how you read bakuman? You're like, this is so fucking cool. But
at the same time, it's not me like, like this is really cool to see how like my favorite
manga is made. But like, I would never work like this. I would never be in this industry
because I'm not Japanese and I'm also not a professional. Like I just don't.
Isoken is like, oh, this is my brain autism. Like this is, this is how I think. It's just
like a random girl who's just like, I have big dreams and I'm going to make them happen.
And it's very much like exactly how us kind of people think. A small grassroots idea of
wanting to make something sick and just like being totally lost in their own head and then
like an actual smart, intelligent person with like business acumen, like slapping some sense
into that creative retardedness and being like, okay, we got to aim this in this direction
and make something actually happen. It's genius. It's brilliant. It's perfect.
It's okay from from bakuman who's like always depressed and says, oh, I can't do it. And
he has that one guy, his producer or whatever, who says, do it idiot. It's that.
Oh, he's my favorite. Yeah. Yeah.
Okay, that's all fine. Does it take place in high school?
No, it takes place in. It does take place in high school, but it is a like a very cool
like location. It's like made up.
But are they high schoolers?
They're in school, but like it's it's a silly school. It's like this.
You're a fucking silly school.
It's like it takes place in school just because they're young.
It has nothing to do with school at all.
Oh, that's okay. I hate that.
But all right.
They're going into the career world. That's part of the whole thing.
They're abusing and utilizing the advantages of being in school to get to kick a career.
Ben, Ben, the first the first big thing of this show is like how the school system is
hampering them and is keeping them down and is bad.
Yeah.
Okay, I just hate young people.
You know, that's fair.
I just hate them, but like that's just anime.
You know, they don't act like young people, though.
That's that's really the thing is that the characters anyone can relate to from any age.
I get it. I get it.
I get it.
This ageism is not very progressive.
I was I was just like it was I was just like maybe I should watch something and I was like
what's something people have told me is good.
Oh, I heard Isaac is pretty good.
But am I really willing to commit to watching a show?
No.
And that was my and that was what happened is a bit is a big ask.
It is a big ask.
I can't do it.
Guys, guys.
I have flowers to take care of.
I have a much smaller time commitment.
I haven't played Animal Crossing in like weeks.
I might I'm sure that I'm sure that Yaki Tori Island has gone to complete shit.
I hate art, guys.
I hate it.
It's it's bad.
It's all bad.
I mean, you're wrong.
What is the fucking point of it?
There is no point.
Yeah, exercise and narcissism.
It's just a fucking it's just a distraction.
It's just a waste of time.
It's all bullshit.
It's all it's all vanity.
You know, then it comes and steam rolls it anyway.
So what's the point?
Yeah.
I don't like it.
It's annoying.
It asks things of me when I see content.
I'm like, God, the absolute gall, the gall that this person has to expect me to to consume
this thing that they made.
Despicable.
I'm insulted.
See, I have been on a kick of completely the opposite mentality recently.
I guess this is Gibbs being a stupid fucking idiot corner.
So play that funny thing again.
Hit it.
This is the stupid idiot corner.
Hi, stupid idiot.
Because of the the manga stuff, the Clarissa, the the struggles, I've been like,
I don't have anything in my brain.
I don't know how to make anything.
I just I figured out the solution or I was told the solution.
I don't remember whether it was my idea or not.
But I've been binging cool movies that I've been told about and I've been researching
and I've been looking up directors names and what that influenced them and going back in
time to like the 1920s.
And I've just been it's just so fun to watch films with the intent of gaining a bit of
knowledge from them as to how to be cool and make my own cool art.
And I've basically been watching a bunch of Westerns.
I started with the good, the bad and the ugly because that's like the big one that I've
heard of.
And I've been going from that backwards to Akira Kurosawa with Seven Samurai and all
his like Western inspired samurai films that inspired Sergio Leone.
And then you go back from Akira Kurosawa to John Ford and things like Stagecoach and
and High Noon and all these old shit, black and white, even silent films.
It's great.
I love art.
I love seeing how things have inspired people and what is like considered a classic master
piece.
And I'm like looking at it.
I love art so much.
Anything made like today sucks.
Anything made like a year ago sucks.
Everything that is not old is bad.
Old good new bad.
Yeah.
Old good.
Like it's old.
And I've heard of it.
It's old and good because I've heard of it and it's old.
That's true.
Okay.
I mean, that's pretty persuasive argument, I guess.
So like Akira Kurosawa, the Seven Samurai, heard of that a lot.
Yeah.
It's really good.
It's my favorite anime.
The Kikucho, or whoever you say it, Kikucho, Kikucho.
They say it real quick in Japanese.
Those guys, they speak real quick.
Okay.
But he is like my favorite character archetype.
Which one?
The like wandering guy?
The sort of crazy guy with the biggest sword and the scowling and the jumping and the screaming.
Yeah.
I think that's like my favorite.
I think that's the only Kurosawa I've seen.
I think I've seen any.
But M.Dot talks about Seven Samurai all the time.
How is a huge influence on like, maybe I should watch that.
And it's been like 15 years and I still haven't done it yet.
Yeah.
You can find it pretty easily.
I googled things.
I found like a whole free version on a like a criterion collection archive website thing.
Dude, archive.org has like tons of shit.
Like, I've just been like watching all the Godzilla movies again.
You just go on archive.org and they have 1080p uploads of like every Godzilla movie ever.
I'm like, oh my God.
Why would I ever buy things ever?
This is so stupid.
Yeah.
It's all just right.
That's the other cool thing about all of shit is that it's free.
You can just have it.
Nobody cares.
It is pretty good.
Yeah.
All right.
We're coming around.
I was coming.
I was going in these old like Westerns and I was like, oh, inspired by a novel.
You know what?
The next step for my like research, my artistic smart boy research is like, imagine me in a
library reading.
So I'm going to read books based on like the inspired these Western films from the 1920s.
And they're just all free on online.
They're just PDFs, like links upon links of free PDFs of books and e-books.
I just have them.
I just have them now.
It's so easy.
Too much power.
Why get an audible account?
Why?
Why would you ever pay money for anything when all of this free shit exists?
That's the whole thing.
You just get sucked into that.
Oh, it's so easy.
I can just pay Amazon more money and make Jeff Bezos even richer and get access to all these
books.
But it's just like, no, it's all here.
It's all here to be stolen.
And that's the way it should be.
I guess I was going to, I guess I'm sort of supposed to read debt again for the, for
Munchies book club.
I said I would do it, but I haven't done it yet.
I keep getting notifications from that.
And I'm just like, hmm, no, I've got other things to do.
I'm going to stay uncultured and safe.
Yeah.
Stupid.
Stupid ass.
That's me.
I've been on, I've been, so I hate art now.
This coincides with me actually starting to make some again.
You know, it's bad.
Like all art is bad.
But I keep, I keep doing it.
I've, I've actually guys, I've actually made progress on fucking slime and punishment
finale.
It's actually getting done again.
Holy shit.
I know.
I will be so fucking relieved.
I'll be so fucking relieved to have that done.
I'll be relieved when I get my fucking Vapors book.
Vapors book.
Munchie.
Munchie or a Kazi is done with her, her thing.
Oh yeah, I saw.
Munchie is almost, wait, you saw hers?
Where?
I saw her say that she finished.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Munchie is like getting close to being done and then Jade, I don't know where Jade is.
I'm going to have to, I'm going to have to pick on her some more.
That's fair.
Yeah.
But it's getting there.
It's getting, it's getting there.
Things, things by, by, by waiting long enough, I made it happen.
Things are looking up.
You know,
Excellent.
It only took months of inaction for something to happen.
That's sometimes that's what it takes.
Yeah.
Speaking of months of inaction, I wanted to announce before I forget that when, when you
have five listeners who ventured away from the YouTube plantation to find us on the outskirts
of Google podcasts or iTunes or wherever.
So I want to let you know that as of you're listening to this, all of the radcon for rewards
will be in transit to you.
No.
They're shit.
They are packed.
They are done.
The only things that are not taken care of yet are those large posters because those have
to be packed separately.
They're at Digi's.
She refuses to send them to me.
I don't know when that will be resolved, but everything else is packed.
Everything in my possession that I had control over directly with my responsible boy powers
has been created, packed, labeled, assembled and shipped.
It will be in transit.
People are already getting them.
You can see on Twitter people are already getting their packages.
I saw somebody go to a pin.
Did you also do the calendar?
I did.
The calendars are done.
Oh, shit.
I have extras.
So if you guys want to frame our debauchery all the time, how do they look?
Oh, no, no, no.
I don't want a calendar.
They look pretty damn good.
I like that.
The print quality is better than I was anticipating.
We got a really good deal on them.
I haggled them down.
It was pretty good.
Oh, shit.
I just realized one of those calendars coming to my house because my brother pledged.
Yep.
I packed that up.
I saw that.
Oh, no.
He's going to have.
Oh, I cut him.
Think about it.
All of next year, you go into his room.
It's going to be there mocking you.
Well, only on some of them months, hopefully.
I want to see.
I want to see post a picture of the calendar for me so I can.
I can go grab one and take a picture of my phone.
I mean, I guess there's no hurry.
If you care that much.
And I said, I don't care that much.
I'll see you eventually.
Der.
What?
What are the rewards were there?
There was the pin.
There was the shirt.
There was the calendar.
The pin is the pin.
There was the small poster, which and then there's the larger poster, which is signed.
And I remember if there was anything else.
That's pretty much it.
It was not a whole lot in terms of physical items.
What about PC pennies?
Meetup only.
Oh, meetup only.
Okay, that's right.
That's right.
Collect his items.
Do you want to talk about like progress that's been made on the other things that were funded?
Is there much to even talk about yet?
I feel like we're still kind of.
Well, I was going to.
I didn't ask in the chat earlier, but I was I was going to ask about the the the OVA.
I mean, like we were doing.
There was progress there.
There was progress.
Yeah.
And I haven't heard anything about it a little while.
Okay.
I need to follow up on that.
It's the, I don't know how much to say, but like the OP is like an animation OP.
That's that's the thing we're currently working on.
Yeah, I'm talking to people about it.
And it's just because it took a while to get sorted.
The people who we had have like other work.
Oh, no.
So like they're just being slower, but it's it'll happen.
Don't worry about it.
Okay.
I did post some.
I did.
I did leak a little bit.
I did leak a little bit on my on my on my Patreon.
Just just a little just a little smidge just a little smidgen of my own shit.
It's fine.
Nobody owns me.
No one can tell me what to do.
Damn destroyed.
You're not nobody.
You're not cops.
Don't be a cop.
But I'm really stoked about that.
I was looking.
Well, I you say you say it's like they've got other work and it's slowed down.
That's that's gay.
It was looking pretty cool.
Last night.
Yeah.
I don't think we've talked anything about this publicly yet.
I really should.
Should we not?
Should I not have brought it up?
It's fine.
It's whatever.
Everybody knows it's coming.
Like they played.
We did.
We did promise it.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, I'll speak.
We don't we don't we don't we don't have to go.
We don't have to go into like any specifics about what it is.
No, no, no.
Yeah.
Because I don't want to make it seem worse than it is at the moment.
We have been getting like character designs like us as anime characters.
Designed based on what we look like in in our silly like OVA designs.
Oh, it's those have been worked on those are looking pretty great and they're basically
done after that.
The next phase is to start the the storyboard and animation and it shouldn't take too long
once we get started.
It's just that the character designer is the person who has got other work while they
were waiting for us to to like give feedback on the tweaks of like, oh, this character
needs this more of this and that.
And then we've been there's been a back and forth process.
Yeah.
But once the character designs are finalized, we can go to the animator and then we get
over what I've done.
That's why I made I made tweaks to mine.
And that was the last I ever heard of it.
I never saw them.
I never saw my my my very important changes implemented.
Yes, that's the one I'm weighing on.
I follow up on my guys.
I'll say what my my notes were like a bigger tits have the tits bulging out of the top
please have them fucking sloshing around and fucking jutting out and just exploding out
of this thing.
Have them be disgustingly big, but not big enough.
This is an embarrassment.
Fix it right now.
Also make the eyes purple.
Purple's better.
But the bigger tits mostly.
Thank you very much.
Good night.
I relayed all of I relayed all of your notes.
Good, good.
And it was just like pages of that just typed in a Word document.
I can't wait for the OVA to finally be finished and Ben finally gets it in his inbox.
He's just like, I can't be bothered to watch art and just doesn't look at it.
Yeah, I won't.
I won't fucking watch it.
I can't be fucking bothered, but it's going to be it'll be a waste of my like how long
is going to be like a minute.
I can't I can't spare it.
One whole minute.
No.
I have to spend that minute making.
I have to spend them in doing the Simon punishment finale.
My dudes, it's coming.
It's coming.
It looks really good.
I've got I've gotten I'm getting fancy.
I'm doing some fancy cinema.
I'm doing I'm doing cuts.
I'm doing swipes and fades.
Yeah.
Timing.
Oh man.
Timing is really fun timing things to to happen again and just like you change a few frames
and you're like, oh, it works so much better.
Yeah, I like that.
Yeah, yeah.
I have it all.
I don't have the music yet.
I'm just kind of like putting it all together and like it's all like it can all be I'm going
to have to go back and like change the timing on everything.
So like make it fit to like the beat or whatever.
Yeah.
I don't know about that.
I guess it depends on how much animation you're doing what do you mean when I was doing when I was doing belgap finale
I couldn't imagine animating or storyboarding anything before I knew what the song wasn't how long it was gonna be I
Had I had to have it finished and then I didn't want to wait too long for the song to be finished or like
Be good. Yeah, that's why it sucks
I
Had well, I made the storyboard first and then um cuz um I was talking to I was talking to
Sixon six and was gonna do a little little music for it
And I gave him the the storyboard and I guess he was gonna fuck around with a make a little make a little tune for it or whatever
But so like the beats are already there and it's just a matter of like how long each one lasts
I've sort of been
I've sort of just kind of been putting everything together
With the assumption that like every like major like cut or event happens on every like four seconds or so
So everything is kind of like in a regular pattern
and um
I don't know. I'll just have to like fiddle with it when it's done
uh, or maybe if something needs to go on a little longer, I can just get like a
A
Little piece of the song to like just play a little longer or a little shorter or something or whatever. Yeah
I'll figure it out. I'm gonna figure it out as I go
Um looks really nice. It looks very it's very homestuck. It's very uh, it's very, um
It's a big kind of sure it's gonna be really cool. Thank you
It's it looks really cool. There's there's there's big it has a really good sense of scale
I think is what I've tried to capture
with it and I think I think it
It's got some nice little transition. I don't know. This is all stupid. This is all stupid to talk about this
Uh, if you'd like if you hadn't if you don't know what it looks like
It doesn't mean anything for me to say. Oh, yeah
Some really nice work. I did on those. Yeah, you know what guys? I'm just so cool. You know that? Yeah
Yeah, when this finally comes out someone will sync up the footage to this part of the podcast
And it's like we'll finally understand
I'll make sense now. Ben is an idiot. Ben doesn't know what he's talking about. I get it
Uh, hell
I feel like I've been I've been stressing a little bit on on making this uh, Tezuka manga thing
The goodest it could possibly be. I don't want anyone to think I'm bad in any way and I'm constantly improving and
Oh, they couldn't possibly be a dud. It couldn't possibly be like all this effort wasted
No, it has to be the best thing ever. I have to win the contest. In fact, I
I'll kill myself if I don't win. That's what I've been saying every day every night before I go to bed
I say I'm gonna die. That's what I say
Uh, I think that's a healthy outlook. Yeah, that sounds really healthy. Definitely keep doing that. What have you been
doing to make it
Like what like give me give me a practical example
Of like how you've been handling it
Well, uh, as I as it was saying
um
Watching a lot of films to get inspiration
uh
So
I'm getting a lot of western have you tried smoking weed?
No, no, no, no. It's much easier
Uh, then making art. Yes. I'm I'm sure it is watching movies
You can do both at the same time. I guess I guess
Yeah, I don't know where to find weed
I go out into the to the park and I cut like grass bits and roll it up into a thing
The answer is and then I smoke and it was not weed at all
It was I throw it down to in disgust go to the nearest college campus and look for any guy in a tie-dye shirt
And ask him
That's how you do it. Oh wait coronavirus never mind
Whoops, okay
All right, look for a guy in a tie-dye
Uh face mask
Tell tell tell me more you've been you've been stressing about the tessica thing
I've been stressing about it being good. Yeah, um
and I've been
Uh, first off I I spent a while a few like a week or so just thinking about ideas
scribbling down on bits of paper opening and closing notepad documents and google documents just
Trying to come up with ideas. I came up with some good things some bad things
And then I was like, okay, if I'm gonna be like punctual I need to
like move on
Before I get too bogged down
And so I tried to start sketching it and then I realized I don't know what any of the west looks like
um
and uh
I think something some complication happened in the middle of june
I got depressed and I didn't do anything now. I've been watching films to get like
understanding of what the west is
Because I I I haven't seen that many western films even though I know that I like it and it's really cool
um
So I've been like gathering a
input so that I can output
Things so I can output art. I need to input what art looks like
You know, you can't you can't be a great artist unless you see great art. So
Um, I'm at this. I'm at the stage where I think I've seen enough films and I'm going to
really try
to
Make a a script that is better than the one I made before
and then sketch
and then
Oh, I hope it's good
Okay
I I don't know whether I answered your question or not. No
No
Not really not really. I don't know. I feel like june was like a weird month for me as well because like I
Had I started I started june with a contest, right? I had a contest on twitter my character design contest
Uh for an izumi project. I'm working on I got a bunch of people who submitted ideas. They were great
I think I'm actually going to rewrite the part of the script
I was going to have they had these characters in it because the designs were so good
And I want them to have a bigger role because it was a very small role before
uh
but
In the middle of working on this in june, I was like, oh god, I'm like so bad. I'm so bad. Everything sucks. This is bad
My ideas cannot be expressed properly with my baby's tier skills. So I just kind of stopped working on that project
I'm just been like consuming
Courses I have like my cg cookie subscription. I'm just like I got to learn everything
I got to learn all this stuff and get better and smarter and gooder
And I just kind of like dropped off the face of the planet
And I'm just trying to learn edge flow and topology
And I started learning 3d sculpting and I feel like I've become more powerful but not enough to actually
Coalesce the power into something usable. It's just like a sun exploding in my face
And I don't know how to control it and it's been very frustrating
But also kind of cool at the same time to be exposed all these new ideas and new ways of working that
At some point when I get dope enough will allow me to transcend
Time and space but until then I just stare in awe into the abyss beyond my comprehension that
That's what's been fucking me up is this
This obsession with gathering skill before making anything
Because it's like I feel like I'm going on that at the moment like when I did a few sketches
I had at one scene pretty firmly in my mind and I tried to draw it
um some of the things like how
It starts I wasn't sure about but I knew one moment in that scene
It's very clearly in my mind and I sketched it out and I drew a really really good panel
Like a really really good sequence of panels. It was like the best panel layout
Individual images and it was a sketch and I just magically did it and I was like damn if I can do that
Everything has to be that good. I can't possibly like live with myself if
Like page one is not as good as this page all the pages have to be this good
And so everything that happens in page one. I have to fine-tune so that is like a perfectly realized
thing and I
I don't have the skills yet to make that work
I need to look at panel layouts and mangas and look at things and films and see like
How they how they block a scene and
Oh, no, everything. Oh, no
No, everything else just has to like get
Everything else just has to get you to the the the important part that you drew the good that you drew good
It's true. It doesn't all have to be good. It can all be bad. I don't know
I like this is not like my preferred work method. It is just what I am noticing
I'm doing is like obsessing over
gaining
power before I like make my move even though
It'll never it'll never just run out of time. It'll never be enough. Yeah
Yeah, I mean also that I like spent you can't live you can't live like this
I spent the first week of june like tweaking my zumi model to make it better
And I was like, all right sick
I like re-rigged it and I changed some of the the design and stuff and it looks really good
And then like a week later. It's like, I'm throwing this whole thing out. It sucks
I got to remake it from scratch now that I learned better. So it's just like I'm sure as soon as this is done
I'm gonna learn something else. I'm like, oh, this is garbage. I gotta do it again
It just never ends. It's always a constant
struggle
But like to go back to what you were saying give I think something it's like interesting because I was I noticed this while watching primary yesterday
Is that like they have these like ridiculously over-the-top choreographed action sequences that are just like full of like 3d and like camera rotation and dynamic perspective
And all this like ridiculous insane shit and I'm just sitting there like how did they fucking think of this?
but then like the dialogue stuff to get you in between those scenes it's like
static shots
Just what you need to get the point across and like a lot of the times the characters will animate in like two frames
Just for the sake of efficiency to like get us from point A to point B
And I think like all art does that right like you got to put your time
In the most important part. So if you have like a really cool scene that's like really well choreographed and like like
I've one or two pages of really intense shit
Like there's almost like a sense of flow where if you're firing on all cylinders the entire time
It's gonna loot that scene's gonna lose its impact. So if you have something more simple
Like adjacent to it
It makes that sudden dynamism hit way harder and that scene actually gets better by the stuff preceding it being
less
I don't want to say creative but like less dynamic almost
So yeah, it's not so much dynamic as in good. It's just sort of
When I do the sketches
One thing I know is that they need to be
Um
They need to be realized enough so that when I'm doing the line
I don't need to think I can just copy the lines
You can just draw what is there
and uh
This often happens with backgrounds where I don't care about what's in the background
Um, it's a character moving from one part of something to another part and I need a panel to show that they're doing that
um
And I draw the panel like a sketch like just a cuboid takes this much space out of the page
Sure, then the next panel's here
Um, and when I sketch it, I'm like, I don't know if I can what where to put the character
Here, I guess it's just sort of like
The panel exists and it's not very well
Realized in my mind as to what it should look like
and I've been
I don't know
It's it's hard to go over panels that I don't care about and try to make them
Have a purpose
Uh, I don't really know how to explain it
I think it's just
There are parts of the story that are just there as transition
As opposed to like you're super invested in because like there's always parts of a story
You're more excited to tell than other parts. There are parts that like kind of have to be there
Then they're like the parts you're really excited about
um
I don't know. I guess I guess I just I dislike in in background specifically having
Oh the cuboid building with the square
Um holes in it that are windows. It is just a cuboid. It has no features is nothing
Um, I look at that and I'm like, oh, I suck. Why why is this building not a real building?
and so I sort of
Maybe I don't know if I overcompensate or
Slightly overcompensate, but I try to think what what is this building?
What is its use in this town?
Oh
Why is it in this location? What is next to it? Why is that next to it? How do this town come to be?
Why, you know, where's the water where they get the water from where they get the food from?
Uh, what are the what are the the natural barriers to entry?
Is there like a mountain range like I think of all these things and I feel like I can't depict anything until I know everything
I need to like plot out the entire area
And that's such a daunting task. I'm like, I don't want to plot out the entire area
Just so I can know what this building is supposed to look like you just you just got a you just got a
Just make shit up whatever you need there to be a mountain. Oh, yeah, there's a mountain
There's always been a mountain
We just never saw the the landscape from the right angle before but it was I mean one of the I always I I feel like I
need to make it
make um
Consistent sense like if you see a mountain from one window from one side of a building out the window
When you go out the building it should be on that same side of the building
I mean, I think that's that's not a bad thing for like your own mind to like keep the space consistent
But I don't I think a I don't think most people will even notice those kinds of things
Um, which is not to say that it's not important to have spatial awareness of where your setting is
Um, but I just think sweating it too much might be more trouble than it's worth
But also like you're making a manga like a black and white manga
So like
99 of the time the panels won't even have backgrounds
You know because like a good a good question to ask yourself is like is this background serving a purpose, right?
Because like if you have a really detailed background like if you
Go and design your entire location and you know where every building is in every point the character is standing at and you go
And render out those buildings in exquisite detail
You're almost detracting from the center
Like point of the panel which is probably to show a character doing something
And you're you could risk adding too much visual clutter to the panel
So I think a lot of the times when manga chooses to not have a background and just have it be white
Like not only is that a time saving technique because they have like seven days to turn around like 20 pages
But it also keeps the focus of the reader on the character and any dialogue that might be spoken
And prevents their eyes from wandering around getting lost in extraneous details that might not serve the story
So just just be a vague right like any okay
Anything anything that's relevant to like the immediate story at hand that's happening right now
You should show in the panel
And anything that isn't relevant you like don't have to show so like
It doesn't it doesn't matter if like if like later on you decide like oh there was a uh that you had this this this
Place is in a it's in a volcano. This is in this is in a this is in a cave or whatever. I don't know
Uh, you just you just don't
You just don't you don't have to do anything with it
It can it can remain like just just just kind of outside of one's awareness until
They're they're like there'd be no reason to have to include details
Until they become relevant anyway. You know what I mean?
Hmm stupid I did a terrible job
No, I I get it. It's I I guess I just sort of have like a fear or like um
Not a fear but like a the the prospect of like
Crafting a story and then telling the story
Non linearly it's like oh my god. I can't imagine
Can't imagine a story growing as I draw it as I write it
I I need to know everything that happens and then I just need to draw it. That's what that's how you do things
That's not necessarily always the right way to do it. Is that how is that how you always do things?
Um for the load of ghosts. I I made it. I made up what it would be
plot-wise
Entirely before and then I made up
Uh, how it looked as I went
Um for bail jpe. I made up everything as I went and I didn't give a shit
I was gonna say bail jpe was not you didn't have you didn't know how bail jpe was gonna end when you started it, right?
Yeah, I had no idea I would even have like a like anything like I thought it would just be like a tiny little joke
And instead it's a real big joke
Yeah
By the way, you asked you asked sorry
Sorry to change the subject. I don't mean to but since you mentioned bail jpe
You asked you asked how much like animation there is in uh slime and punishment finale
Like very little there's like
It's almost all just like static objects like moving and trend like trend like scene transitions
There's like there's one scene
There's like one or two little shots where people will probably have a little like two frames of like
They like go from one pose to another
And that's like yeah, that's that's that's yeah
That's the homestuck thing. Yes, it is that so much of it is like um scale and rotate and
Shake and flash
Yeah, that's efficient. You can get a lot of you can get a lot of mileage you get a lot of mileage out of just
Having like static images move around a screen
I should have done that why did I
It's too late. I've already spent the time it's cool now. Yeah
Yeah
No, dude
I won't I I I I'm I'm I'm resisting the urge to talk more about that
I don't want to say anything about what what goes on in it until it's out
Yeah, the I I guess this whole bit has been give being a stupid fucking idiot. Yeah, play the jingle again
Play the jingle like every five minutes play the jingle
I don't even know there's a jingle I've missed a lot apparently I well
There's only been the last episode that I coined the term I haven't even listened to the jingle
I just know it exists. I don't is there I don't know if ellie is are actually added a jingle or not
He made one I'm posted there. I just didn't play it. Okay, and I I didn't see what it sounded like before the episode was edited
Yeah
But I'm sure it's cool
Yeah, I I need
To I need to stop thinking
But it's hard
You can't just draw. What are you insane? You put a pen to a paper
You just draw a line and it becomes something that's how it works. That would be really cringe
If your art doesn't be creative on the fly, it's pretty cringe. I watched
I watched another there was a new a new mon ben someone on twitter
Uh outrider sake on twitter added me to let me know ben somebody uploaded a new mon ben
on daily motion
the one the one where
The one where urisawa nowki
Like talks to manga people and films them working and stuff. Right, uh, it was
When I watch mon ben I get I get a sense like it's cool
it's cool to see
Artists like working so hard on like making their shit
But I also
Have a strange feeling of like why
Are they even bothering like this is cringe like why are they doing like it's stupid. What are they established or something?
Yeah, it's like what what's what's the purpose what purpose does this serve?
And then and then they're gonna eat and then them and nowki will be like, oh, yeah
Uh art really is you know the artist's expression really is like a pure expression of fetishism
You know, it's like, yeah
Uh, uh, it's the the part, you know the kai I've always had a really intense emotional
Experience with like the human clavicle and that and everyone says that like that's why I draw it so good and like, oh, yeah
I like I you know, I want to express my fucking my fucking anxiety through a through a
Something or other and there was this highfalutin
Shit, and I'm like cringe
Just fucking just just just just quit
If they if they were good at explaining why they do what they do they wouldn't do what they do
They'd be explaining other people things. That's true. It's it's I don't know they always
Nowki always, um
He talks a lot about fetishism
But like all he means by it every time he says it he just means like
Liking something it's just like something you're interested in like liking to draw shoulders
Do you think it's just a translation thing? Do you think they're just saying fetishism in the translation when it could be something more literal?
I think maybe the word I think they say it in English like they use the English word and I think just maybe it has a different connotation
Oh something that's interesting
I I I'm talking about it like I'm
This probably makes it sound like I hate the show and I don't even like it anymore
But I do I just feel I just feel weird
About art in general art is so cringe because it becomes base and you want to be that cringe so you can be that base
But you can't bridge the gap yet
Yeah, it's like they'll be like oh so-and-so has been working for like 14 years writing a
It's a it's a manga about a
A girl from a from a tribe that has to like fight against like an
Ineval empire or something and like free her and I'm like I hear that and I'm like, okay. I get it
Like all right got got it
What's what's the point? I mean, that's just the synopsis
Nobody goes around reading synopsises
But I feel like I feel like I don't know maybe this is dumb
But I feel like I feel like the synopsis is all I need
And I don't I don't like I don't know
It's very uncharitable and it's probably stupid, but like I'm like, I mean maybe you're just tired of like
Narratives that get repeated
Right, but all narratives get repeated. That's why all art is bad
Or art can only be good when it's new and there hasn't been any new art ever
So no art can only be good when it's old old good
Well, it was
It was it was new
It was new when it was old though. That's why it was good because it was it was new at the time
Now everything now everything is old because the old stuff was new
First wait, I think I think you mixed up a word there or two. No, I don't I think I got it exactly right
The idea was fresh new ideas are not fresh because the old ideas were fresh
When they came out
We just got to wait
We just got to wait until we're old and then the things that are coming out today will be good
Because they'll be old. No, they won't they won't I promise it'll never happen anything old people are the most based thing
You could be you go, oh, and you're like, I can't walk anymore and you're like, I can't wait until like
2050 when there's like fucking like 65 year old men like oh, yeah, I remember back when
Movies were good. Remember iron man. Ah, it was a classic. Remember remember the first iron man. Yeah, that was that was that was it
Everything it's all been downhill from there
We went into that cave and he made an iron man suit out of scrap. How do you do that?
How do you do that? He's so smart
I
Fucking hate movies
It's unbearable
Imagine imagine sitting down to watch a sequence of images played at a high frame rate to create the illusion of motion
So embarrassing
Uh, why don't you look in the mirror?
No, and then move around. This is the like the highest frame rate possible
Yeah, I guess so
You go you go down looking at the the the like a body of water and you're like that sure sucks
It does
um
I'm I'm I'm
I'm like
I'm like I'm working on I'm doing the finale
I'm working on the scenes and I'm like, uh, this is cringe, but you know, I gotta do it
You know, I know what it's supposed to be. I know how to make it be that
Do I do I think that this
Or anything else is good or worthwhile? No, but it's no worse than anything else
That anyone else in the has ever done, you know, it's it's it's equally cringe
As everything else that that someone could be paying attention to
Instead so whatever
Just just fucking do it
That's all art is quite useless, but you know, what yeah, what else can I do? It's very true. That's right. That's why we
Do it anyways just because it makes us kind of happy even though it's also makes us sad
Yeah, I guess so
I guess I I guess I would agree my my biggest goal dream in the world
Is to have a character that gets a
Shit ton of porn drawn of it just by random people. Yeah, that's how you know you've made it
I want to be I want to be the toby fox but only in that one way
um
Pretty cool pretty cool. Yeah, pretty hot. Yeah
It's both cool. You know what else is pretty fucking hot my
Fucking hot and on my 3d printer. I bought it's printing something right now
Oh my god, really you're you're making 3d models and I haven't done that yet because I haven't I don't have a model that's like
Quality enough to print but I've been doing a bunch of test prints. I'm printing some model
I got offline right now like a little question block cart for mario
And it'll it'll hold switch cartridges, which is kind of cool. I just want to do that try and test like a geometric print dude
But uh, it's the fucking best make a
Make that's awesome
Make a fucking a zoomie
A mebo and and I'll buy that's the idea. I want to make stuff like that. It's gonna be fucking sick
I just I printed this yesterday to test out like characters
So I printed a bust that I found online
I'm putting in the chat
Of handsome squidward and it came out great
And it's fucking sick
I've been given power. Oh my god. That is too
It's too much. It's too much. I
The possibilities are endless. Uh, that is one of those
That's uh, one of those
Like you can see the the the lines on it still, but you know, it's pretty epic
Do you could would you like sand those you can sand those down?
There's another right now. I'm using a plastic called pla
Because there's different like plastic types you can use for this pla is like the easiest to use
But there's another one I've been reading about called abs and abs. What you can do with that is it prints out like this
but then if you
Do a
Acetone vapor chamber thing with it like the acetone will like smooth it out
So it'll look it'll get rid of those lines
So I'm thinking I might try doing some abs printing to make some sculptures and stuff, but like
It's fucking dope. And it was like it was not expensive at all
I got this like pretty decently large printer for like 250 bucks and it prints great and it's dope
Oh
Oh man
Oh, that's so cool. Okay
Uh, hmm
I wonder if I could do something with such a thing. I bet I bet you could
Hmm you could print gummy worms. Oh
I wonder I wonder if there's like one you could there's like an edible like an edible
Substrate you could use to like print food. I don't know if there's edible. There's flexible so you can make like springy things and stuff
Which I have not tried yet, but it's pretty fucking sick
And between this and learning sculpting. I'm gonna become ultra powerful and
Make all the cool things
It's pretty dope
Okay, dude. I'm impressed. I like how 3d printing has has become
Cheaper and and you can just get a thing. It's like pretty cool because like it's kind of changed the way I think about a lot of stuff
Because like now
Instead of like, oh, I got to go on amazon and buy something stupid
It's like, oh, I want to like get like a dock for my phone on my desk. I'll just print one
I don't have to go buy it. I'll just print it. Whatever. It's fine. You just go on on the internet get like google pixel
Stand and you just print it out and now you have one
You didn't have to do anything and like you've become a better person
How how long do you think before it pays for itself? Um, I mean nothing I'm doing right now really
is
Worth money. I guess like the phone thing probably would have been like 15 20 bucks, but
If I start making like sculptures and art with it and sell those like I'm sure probably within like
One or two prints that probably start like getting close to paying for itself
I don't know
Fascinating
Fascinating. It's pretty fucking dope. Very good
Damn, damn. That's neat as hell. Yeah, man
Trying to think what would I do with one? I feel like
Dilda dilda dilda. I could make a gun. Have you considered 3d printing a gun?
Uh, you can do that, you know, you can do that. I'm pretty sure it's illegal
Uh, but yeah, but you can do it anyways
Yeah, you know, just get a real gun and 3d print the bullets. That's not illegal when this when the civil war starts
I'll be ready
Okay, uh
Remember, um
The oh fuck what's that thing mark said something about the right to
Arms and ammunition party should not be infringed or whatever. Uh, no wait, that's the second amendment
But mark said the same thing. It's fine marky mark. Yeah
He said he said
Under no pretext should arms and ammunition be surrendered any attempt to disarm the workers must be frustrated by force if necessary
So stick stick with it. Stick with it. Yeah
Uh, cool
Uh, we got to decentralize, uh guns and ammunition. We can make them
They're just you can just free to print yours at home. Amazing
Uh
Do you think
That maybe
3d printing
Would be something that like just everyone should have do you think the world would be a better place if just like everyone had a 3d printer?
um
I think I mean it I'm trying to think of like the the uses of a 3d printer
aside from
like, um
I mean obviously you can get like very intricate
specific plastic parts for moving machines or whatever like if you're building something but like
Uh, I mean you can't 3d print fabric. You can't 3d print
like
Certain that you can't 3d print food
Seems like it's it's it's like decorative almost it's mostly useful mostly useful for useless knickknacks
Which is fine. I like useless knickknacks. It depends. I mean there are people who make like functional parts and stuff
um, I think a 3d printer would be useful in a utilitarian sense if you
Also learn how to make your own stuff
Because like you can get like fusion 360 and like model like basic
Uh
Parts and things like that like for example, like I was thinking of maybe using fusion 360 to model something to
better adhere
The uh stand to my desk that holds my second monitor
Uh, because right now it's kind of wobbly and like that's something that like I could buy
Or I could just make it and print it and like it'd be cheaper and probably quicker
Because it'll take like x amount of days to ship where I could probably do it in less than a day myself
But that requires like knowledge. So like if you're like not lazy
Yeah, you'd probably benefit from a 3d printer because like it'll also it also incentivizes you to like
solve problems that
You can do by yourself that maybe a
You would be able to buy a solution to like something very like specific that you need
Um, so I don't know it really depends on the person
I don't think everybody should have one. I think most people are lazy and dumb
But like if you're interested
I think you can find uses for it
Yeah, 250 bucks is just it's not that much. It's not a very high barrier to entry
You can get one for like 180. It's even cheaper. It's just a lot smaller
Jesus Jesus
Okay, cool
I feel because I'm I'm like
Slightly knowledgeable about 3d modeling. I've done it before
I've also forgotten everything and I tried again and I forgot it all again
um
So I don't I don't think I would ever like model my own things
I wouldn't like if I needed like a
Some like I don't know
System like some some small objects to help around
With my stuff like a a weird shaped thing that needs to wedge in somewhere
I would probably more
Go down the the the route of learning how to do carpentry and building things with wood and nails and stuff
Because I'm already
A little more knowledgeable in that department and I just find it cool to hold wood and to smash it with a hammer
Oh
Oh, did I did I ever mention
uh, my brother
Uh
Yeah, I did I last time I was saying I was gonna help my brother with stuff
Um, yeah, his legs been fucked up. Yeah, I have
Uh, since that podcast came out I went to him. I asked him if he needed help and
we got together because
Henry Henry's been um
Getting into upholstery
as like a skill
He went for like making couches
like making chairs and like traditional sort of upholstery so using like
proper
old-fashioned real materials like
Stuff and things and horse hair like padding. Okay. Um
And uh, he's had these two chairs
It was he's had like three or four chairs that he's been like half finished
But because of his leg he hasn't been able to work on them. I came in I helped him
and
it is it's got to a point where we are
We are building chairs and my presence in
In his room helping with like one of the chairs while he works on another chair
has got him
Motivated and made him feel better and it's bass as fuck
But also it's bass as fuck for me because I'm building a chair like a real chair would like
with
Layers to it. I don't know any of the terms, but there's this
That there's a thing called a harpoon needle
um that used to to to sew like threads all the way through the top and bottom of the chair
um, and then there's like these curves needles to
like the
uh
Really curve like if you get a mug and a needle goes all the way around the mug like a semicircle
that's sort of
A video game
Where you play there are games like this, but a video game where you play as a mouse
But you're like a warrior mouse and you have you have an rpg of swords
But they're all little needles
And like you you you get like different kinds of needles, right?
Like you buy oh like like I found a harpoon needle like this one's like god gives me gives me more strength
The smaller defense or something. Okay. Yeah, sorry. Yeah. Yeah, mouse guard everybody. It's fucking sick
Mouse guard. Yeah, that's like literally what you're talking about
I feel like I'm I mean there's I have seen games where that might literally be
Exactly game that I follow that's doing that you might have I've retweeted
It's like a it's like a pixel art one. It's like behind
Yeah, it's like a sort of like a big like switch blade kind of thing
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, that's it. That's the one
Yeah, it's not a needle though. Not a needle, but that's fine. They use needles in mouse guard though, which is why I said that
Okay, but I think what's really cool about that give what you're talking about is like when when something that seems kind of like
Almost magical gets disambiguated and you understand how it's made, you know, like a chair
It's something that just kind of appears like you go to a store and it's there and you bring it home
But then like oh, this is how it's made like it's not like a magical thing
Like there are steps there's a process and now I know with the process
So when I look at chairs
This thing that kind of like had no context now
It has context and it like kind of makes you think about like everything around you
It's like there's a process behind all of this and like things that I don't know
It's like really fucking cool to like be in on the secret almost
It's it's really interesting because it's it's specifically old fashioned chair making techniques
The sort of chairs that last for hundreds of years before they break down as opposed to modern chairs
Which is just like a lump of foam and it breaks down after like two years
Like modern things in general just don't aren't built to last right so like building a chair in with this method
With like there's this layer of like
coarse
Like black coconut hair
That you're you're supposed to like scrunch like from an actual coconut
Yes gross I think
And it's like you you scrunch it around and you use like special like a
Um, I forget the name of it
It's like a a neat a thing you stab into the chair to push
The the the stuff around to like smooth it out and then there's like specific stitches to like hold parts in place
um
So that when you sit on the chair
It's like the stuffing doesn't
It it can't move from one side of the chair to the other like over time
So it's all it's in its individual little
Part compartments and then on top of that there's a horsehair thing and then there's a calico layer
And you you do half you get these little tacks these little black nails
And you half tack it all the way around and then you pull it really tight
And and then you're supposed to like while holding pulling the calico or pulling the the fabric with one hand
You get this special hammer that has a magnet on one side and you're supposed to like put the nail the tack on the hammer
Hold the the the material really tight and then like whack the nail into the fabric into the wood
and then uh
Then it holds it because it's really sharp
And it's like all these little processes to go to make a chair that just uh, you see and you're like, oh, it's a chair
It's got a it's got padding
You see like all these things that go on in these old chairs is really interesting
uh
Learn making making gummies has has not demestified demystified it at all. It has remystified it
I am continually surprised and terrified
by how
they come out
So different every time like I made some the other day and they came out. They were completely solid
They were they just came out as completely solid like hard
Hard candy, which is not what I wanted. It was inedible
Uh, uh, it sucked and and then I used the same recipe the next day and they didn't
Uh, I think the difference is that I just I cooked the first one longer like I cooked more of the water out of it or something
um
It's like yeah, there's so many fucking variables and I can't
Cooking I've been trying I've been introducing new ingredients like I've I've I've switched from using
I pretty much figured out how to do it with beef gelatin, but I don't want to use that anymore
I want to try using pectin and agar agar and uh and carrageenan
Um and rice flour, but I keep I don't know. I'll fucking throw these things all together and it'll it'll it always comes out weird
But a different kind of weird
It's always wrong, but in like it's it's wrong in new and novel ways every time
Baking is a mystery
It's it's neat I guess
Uh, I like the ones that are passion fruit flavor passion fruit's the best flavor. I make them blue usually
uh
That's a fact jack
I've tried making keto brownies three times now and each time they've come out completely different despite me doing
The exact same thing and I don't understand
Is very damn it's are you doing keto tom? Um, yeah, I usually have one off day a week
Uh, yeah, most part i'm sticking to it
And uh, yeah, I found this like keto brownie recipe. That's just like
almond flour
uh
Sweetener cocoa and protein powder and then like a can of diet coke and it makes brownies really. Yeah, it's it's like diet coke
That's very weird. It's very strange, but it works
I just can't get it to be consistent despite doing the exact same thing. Uh, that's baking for you
Yeah, that's that's yeah some things
I mean, that's why the factories have like such uh rigorously controlled environments if the humidity or the temperature is different
Everything could change
With some with certain recipes
So like they keep it exactly the same and then they just production line makes the same thing every time
You should need a factory bench need to buy a factory. I I would love I would love to I would love to do that. Um
I've been thinking they'd be really funny if you know
When uh when covet is gone lamal and we do another uh rowdy fuckers con killers
if um
If I just made a big like bucket of keto slime
And I was like hey and like we just could just like ladle it out to people. It's like put it on a plate
I could do it. It'd be easy
Uh, just be it would just make like a make a big a big bowl of what I would turn into gummy worms
But then just not put it in the molds
and uh
That could just be what everyone eats the whole time. You're not allowed to eat anything else actually
Uh forced keto. Yes. Yes
Uh, I just think that would be funny and it would taste good. I would make it I would make it like mango flavor or something
Sour apple flavor
You know, I have an apple. I have an apple flavoring and I don't like it
I don't like the apple and I don't like the pear which is weird because usually I really like both of those
But this brand or whatever
This company that I guess I've been buying my flavorings from they just don't do it good. They don't have
Good apple pear. They suck. They're bad
But their mango and passion fruit is very good. Mwah
Delightful. I made uh, I made some orange
I tried to make some orange yesterday and I used the pectin
And I used carrageenan and I used rice flour and it came out so stiff that I could not put it into molds
So I just spread it on a piece of like
aluminum foil
Uh and put it in the aluminum foil in the fridge and now I just have like sort of a brick
Of this orange paste that is now completely hardened. It sort of has a consistency like fruit leather
um
And next to that is a little jar full of it's actually the same gummies that I I posted a picture of them on twitter
And I guess it started a little bit of an insurrection in rfck. I guess the killers are revolting against me now
Uh, there's some, you know, there's some there's some some pretty uh, uh, what's the word?
There's some propaganda going around. There's a little bit of a revolutionary overtones. That's fine
Uh, but I still have those but they're in a jar, but like they've hardened
So much they're like candles. They're like they're like they're like wax now
um, and and I
They weren't like that before but I guess you should use them like candles
I wonder
Addable addable candles. That's that's where this is going. That's where this journey ends
Edible slime candles slime candles that have a green flame at the end
Those ones didn't even come out that good. Those were apple flavored
I tried to make them green apple, but they didn't flavor them enough and the apple's not very good anyway
and uh
They're they're they're really hard and waxy and I don't know. I don't know man. I don't know
That's it's uh, it's a mystery
It's complete complete chaos
In the ben saint kitchen these days
Uh, yeah
So I got to say about that we're at an hour, uh, if you guys are
One we could go on to voicemails unless there's anything else you want to talk about
I got one last thing. Yeah, um, wouldn't be very long. I just want to ask you two because you're old than me whether this happened to you
um
It's my birthday in two days as of the recording of this
Yeah, and uh, I
I don't remember if I'm already 27 or if I'm gonna be 28 or 29
I don't I don't remember
I thought you were like I thought you were like 25
No, no, no, I'm at least 26, but I don't remember further than that. I I've completely lost track
I could easily add up the numbers, but it's like yeah, like late 20s
I stopped caring, but when I when I was about to hit 30
I was deathly aware and I felt very terrible and now every year past 30. I've just like
Oh god, I'm not even I don't even like why even be alive anymore. It doesn't even matter. Nothing I do
Is is worth anything?
No, I I'm with you because I'm actually I think I'm 32
But I might be 31
Uh
Wait, no, hold wait, you'll be turning 32 right because you're only a couple months older me. I'll be 32 in november. So
You're wait, you're turning 32 in november correct then I would have then I would have turned wait no
I was born in 90. I was born in 88 and it's 2020 now
So so like I was I turned zero in in in 88 and I turned two
When's your birthday? When's your birthday? I turned. Oh, no, no, no, it's a april april seventh
Okay, been your 30. So no, I am I am 32. Okay
Right, it's right because april because I turned two because I turned two I turned two in 1990
So I'll be I'll be 32 in 2020. Yeah, okay
It's just like funny because I'd like up to this point. I had pretty be like, yeah, I know what age I am
I don't know what age I am anymore
Uh, I am with you. Yes. Yes. Yes. It happened changed. Yeah, I mean it means less and less
What's what's even the difference?
What's even the difference between like 25 and like 40?
15 years
Anyway, I gotta go to the hospital now
Yeah, what is old age?
Ah man, oh man
I we could go to questions. I guess, you know, we got nothing else. It's a little bit of it's a little bit of a relief
Honestly, it was a little bit of a relief to have quarantine happening when I had my birthday this year
Because it meant we didn't have to do anything
which is just kind of like
cool
like, yeah, I don't
Don't care that much. I don't care about celebrating my birthday too much
I think I think we did like all hang out or what are like some people in my house all did a thing
but we didn't like
You know ordinarily, maybe I would have like
Had people over or something and I didn't have to do any of that
You know, like I like doing stuff, but I don't like doing
birthday stuff
It's annoying
Happy birthday to you
Me to you
Wow, this video is copyright claim. Oh wait, it's not even on youtube lamau. We don't have to worry about that anymore
I love dude. I can say sponge bob square pants now. I can say that
No character
Let me you know, let me complain. Let me complain about something
Uh
What do you guys think? I think
That jenna marbles was not cancelled and anyone that thinks she's been cancelled is fucking stupid
I know nothing about this
All right, well, I know that on twitter cancel culture
Is is is all the rage these days everyone's complaining about it and I guess it's it's almost entirely on twitter only
I don't know if it has any effect
Okay. Well, jenna. Well, well jenna marbles got quote unquote cancelled
Which basically just means that somebody was like, hey guys jenna marbles did blackface once jenna marbles was like, oh
It's true. I did I shouldn't have done that. I'm sorry
Everyone was like, wow, what a gracious apology. You know, she's really handling this the way more people we more people should
And then jenna was like, hey guys, I have decided of my own volition
to not
Uh upload more videos to youtube and everyone said, oh my god
jenna marbles was cancelled the cancel mob got her
And like they fucking didn't I don't know it makes me really mad
It makes me really mad that someone could see that and be like, oh
How could that how could this have happened? She's such she's been victimized by uh by an irrational mob mentality
That is just cancelling people left and right. She's the latest victim
Like no, she had a pr kerfuffle
And then this is how she chose to handle it. Like that's
Like what what what do you want? Like what what else what should have happened?
That's what I don't understand. I don't understand the mentality here
She should have doubled down and just done more blackface. I mean that's the obvious she should have said it was representation
Yeah, obviously
She should have become completely blackface from then on
Ah
Let's talk about
net netflix pulls netflix pulls the episode of community where the chinese guy
Uh, uh
Where is black makeup because he's played he's a drow in d&d
Uh stupid uh brand stupid
Uh, uh, uh simpsons is like we're not gonna have white people play black people anymore. Uh, whatever nobody cares
Uh, I hate I hate everything
Uh, I hate
I hate culture. I hate society. I hate living in a society. I have become joker-fied
um
I don't know that's that's my june
There you go
Yeah
Well, yeah, I I've I've been I've been
Not paying attention to twitter because I blocked it on based in the same way. I block youtube
I may have mentioned that already uh last time but
um
Blocking it in the same way that I can only look at it during the weekend
Which is right now, but I also haven't felt the need to because like
Like I check twitter every day. I used to check twitter every day
I check what people I'm following and then I check a bunch of people that I like assume would have something they're talking about
um
Like just by searching their name
And I look at what they're saying and I'm like I go on twitter and I feel worse than I was when I first got on there
Yeah
And it's like just it's it's like it's the same thing every time
um, but by reducing the amount of times I do it
I just care less I'm like like if I do it every day or every five minutes
I'm gonna care a lot, but if I do it once a week. I I don't know
I've been seriously considering just like
Becoming a new person online and just scrubbing everything
Just why don't it's it's I I like the idea, but I also
Feel like it's so
Impossible what what what would be the point? I don't I don't really even know what the point would be
It's just it's just a temptation that
Lacks any sort of like cohesive reasoning. I just feel like I want to go away sometimes
uh
Yeah, sometimes I feel like
By by having
Information out there at any point
Um, I'm now like damaged goods and I can't now exist as a new mysterious person anywhere
Unless I hide my
voice or face
Like eventually people will connect the dogs and find everything that I've ever said and it's like well, I'm whatever
Can't do anything about it. I guess
yeah
If you went away for like years and then you came back and did something like completely unrelated to what you're doing now
Even if people discover like oh, this guy used to be on a podcast or whatever this guy used to have another youtube channel
uh, uh, uh, I feel like
I feel like it is possible to create like
enough distance between like your current self and your past self and it's like oh, well, that's like
Sure, that's like technically the same person, but like it's not like you know part of the same
like like, um
I don't know
It's funny. I just remembered that there have been people who
Like watched t-bap and both yours and Nate's content and had no idea you two were those guys
That's so funny
Like who like didn't even know like, uh
Uh, if I can jesse
Uh, endless jess was also my japanese anime. They thought it was they were two different people. I was like how
That's so that's so wild
Yeah, I always just assume that anyone who's seen
My stuff like found it through
My other stuff
right
I don't I don't imagine like
A new
Like I don't imagine the stuff that I put online like reaching a new audience
I kind of just always assume that it's just going to be seen by all the same people who've seen everything else
I've ever put there
Uh, Lamal
I guess it's not always true. Sometimes it leaks out into the wider world a little bit
Everybody everybody finds you
Through a different thing
Hmm. Hmm. Very wise very wise
Uh
I don't know
Very is really funny that uh
I'm imagine imagine having watched tbap and then watching like stumbling across the pcp
And not knowing that it's the same guy. That's so wild
I don't know
You guys there or what? Yeah. Yeah. Sorry. Okay. Okay. Nothing to say about it. Well. Yeah, please. You're leaving me hanging
I'm dying here. I mean, yeah, you know, I agree. I agree. Let's go to voicemails. Let's go to fucking voicemails. Yeah, no more of this
Okay, so
voice
males
Where?
Okay. Okay. So first one is from
Keyblade spirit. This is Keyblade spirits pride month special
three two one go
This is an open letter to the lgbt q i a plus community
Please
I'm begging all of you. Please
Iron you goddamn pride flags
Well, what do we think gentlemen, uh, is he right or is he right?
I don't know. I haven't seen a flag in my life
Uh, I've never seen one flag
Uh
I feel like that's solid advice regardless of the context keep your flags presentable if you want to raise them high and let them be seen
Have some pride in your pride flag
Listen, listen, I'm I'm not a cop. I'm not gonna tell you that you can't wave around
That you that you can't wave around a dirty ragged, you know crumpled up pride flag if if you want to
But you know
Can consider consider how best to spread your intended message. It's not illegal, but it's not really ethical either
Is it not ethical to I think it's it's it's the better choice to
Have it be presentable. You can do it just because you can doesn't mean you should
The I mean, you know when when a flag touches the ground, you're supposed to burn it
So I so I propose gentlemen
That in a display of solidarity to our lgbt qia plus allies, we all take to the streets and burn pride flags
In a demonstration to show just how seriously we take I feel I feel as if you might have missed the mark a bit on that one
No, no, no, no. No, this is good. It's good. That's called patriotism
We are the true patriots. You're more educated on this than me. So I'll defer to your expertise. That's right
That's correct. This is not a pride flags. This is flag pride
Uh, wait, did you say fag?
That's what I heard. That's what I heard. I'm sorry
I heard it. I heard it. You know what you want to hear. I think
No, no, no, no. Shut up. Shut up. Shut up. Um, all right. Let's move on to the next one. Let's move on
No, no more of this. Okay. This is from
Trapped in my room and there is a youtube link attached
three two one go
I missed the old rad con the comic gold rad con the bread stole rad con and now there's no rad con
I hate the new rad con since Nate's screwed with rad con his channel's got hacked and now he's ruined rad con
I missed the fans rad con the 30 grand rad con people might even say i'm better than rad con
So you had to grow with rad con. I made my own rad con since impossible now to even be shown rad con
I used to love rad con. I used to love rad con. I even made my own lecture
I thought I was rad con what if a fan who once was a slave to rad con
Stole a Kanye song just to promote his own channel so he can save rad con
That's all it was rad con. We still love rad con. They stole you like brad stole brad con
Uh
Cool, so this good good good flow good beats
um
This guy so this this link that he he has here goes to
a a lecture
Kanye it's called Kanye name one genius that ain't crazy a pcp inspired lecture
I
I feel like maybe
Okay, I think recently someone added the pcp on twitter
With a lecture and I think maybe this was the same one
Uh, so this is another we've got I guess this is only like the second
Like like pcp style lecture i've seen i've seen tectonic improv's one about linkara and I guess this one now which is about Kanye
Uh, I don't know. I'll I'll give it a watch
Lincoln Lincoln the doobly-doo
Uh, let's go check out, uh
Yeah, he's trapped in my room on on youtube. He's got a fucking it's two hours two and a half hours
Every time someone says doobly-doo. I get a little bit closer to going on a mass shooting. Sorry, dude
I say it ironically. I promise. Oh, no, no, no, no, you don't I promise no, no, no, no, no, no
You say it ironically one more time it will become unironic
Oh, I've only got one left
Yeah, and I better make I better make a count every time
Oliver on philosophy tubes says doobly-doo. I'm like, please never do that again
Philosophy tube. Yeah, does he say that? He does. I think it's uh, I think it's a uh, uh, a vlogbrothers thing
It did originate from vlogbrothers. Yeah, it was like I've started
I was he started he was saying it on his older videos
I'm like, oh, this is like his older videos before like he realized it was a retarded thing to say
But some of his newer videos he still says it. I'm like
Oh, you know brand recognition old habits old habits diehard. I guess I just it just
What if you copyrighted hey guys
Oh
No, there's an idea. There's an idea. You know, we got a copyright. Sorry. We got a copyright. Sorry. I haven't made a video in a while
That's where the real money is can we do we do we sell a shirt that says that we don't we should
Yeah, we absolutely
Wait, it's in the the front. No the front of the shirt should say hey guys and the back should say sorry
I haven't made a video in a while. Yeah. Yeah, I don't I don't see why not
Uh, okay. Well, that's that's next
On the pipeline. Uh, next one next voicemail
Uh persona this one is called persona five is too difficult on normal
By the way, I have not curated any of these
So we're just we're just going in completely raw. So this one's two two voicemails along so three two one go
Finally fucking did the persona. I beat the the the the thing that I was talking about and I killed the penis head monster
Uh, the game is finally good again
yippie
Have you guys played persona?
Never
No, okay neither of us not even I don't even care
Yeah, you're right. Actually, uh, the next one is called persona five. I did it. Uh
Maybe he did it. Okay. I guess he did it. Congratulations, sir
Uh, great. Uh, all right the next one. Uh, the next voicemail is titled your white
And not you are why you are your why you are white
So, uh, let's fucking get it
gentlemen
All right, three two one go
Hello, Nate. This is, uh
Well, you already know who this is
Um, I've heard I listened to the last podcast episode and I did not read or
Played
Still want to hear my voicemail to be played. Um, Nate. What's your opinion about the BLM?
BLM movement
And I want to actually if you don't mind be on the show discuss why
Dispree with a lot of your opinions and how it's contradictory that you want a star trek future, but you do not advocate for the
Uplifting of any other ethnic community
Um, so that's kind of weird
So and your alter in your belief system of doing the most good
Is contradictory of your actions. So again, just just want to know
Nate like if I want to see if you actually uphold the standards or you're just putting on errors, dude
All right, so all right
Yeah, again, this is
Oh, this is uh, you're white. That's that's why I put in the last title or whatever. So again
I want to hear your opinion and thoughts about it. Okay. Bye. I don't remember this guy's previous voicemail
Do you guys remember I didn't I remember I think you were by yourself when you did that
Uh, I don't or maybe not. I don't know
Did I not I don't know okay doesn't ring a bell whatever I don't know Nate's not even here
Uh, I agree the Nate is cringe. I don't know any of Nate's opinions on this and I don't want to
Uh, Nate just doesn't talk about it, which is cringe. Very cringe. I see. I see. He doesn't want to talk politics
I don't want to talk politics. Uh, you gotta be gotta be neutral on everything. That's how that's how you do the most good
In with stuff. Okay, whatever
Uh, thanks for your call your white. Mr. Mr. White
um
Shall we next one is from
PAP endorses mining at night
Uh
Three two one go
Hey, pcp. I have a very spicy one for you guys. So the procrastinator's anonymous
Fully endorses mining at night. Now. I know what you're thinking. It's a very controversial take, but
It's actually better
I mean, hey, you want the least amount of mobs to spawn as possible to interrupt your mining. Am I not correct?
Thus you do need to mine at night because more mobs will spawn on the surface
And less will spawn in the caves where you will do your mining
I don't know whether that's true
I guess it depends on if you're close enough to the surface that they can spawn up there or if you're on a multiplayer server
He's okay. So he's saying that because mob spawn in the darkness and there's a limited number of mob spawns
If you're mining at night, they'll be spawning on the surface and that'll reduce the spawns you
Yeah, okay
It makes sense
It might be true. I don't know
I don't play minecraft. Well, to see the thing is
Uh, it's it's not don't mine at night because it's better to not mine night
It's we're just telling you to do that. You have to do it if you don't if you disobey you will be
um
Scoot, yeah, it's it's not. Yeah, it's not it's not worse because anything in the game
It's worse because we'll kill you we'll destroy you you dare. Yeah. Yeah, how you dare
He does the the the the the pro the procrastinating the the pro and on cast
Is that what they're called? What are they called the procrastinator's anonymous cat pro and on?
Yeah, one of those pro and on they they all right they endorse this dangerous ideology
It's cringe. Uh, uh, it does not it does not reduce harm
Uh, it is it is uh, it needs to be canceled get on twitter
A hashtag cancel the path. Uh, that's that's that's that's what's up
All right, third next one
Next one
Is titled with a a bitly link and the link is to his discord screenshot of michelle
Saying oh wait, shan. Are you the voicemail god?
uh, okay
But here we go. Well three two one now
Ellie is our please link this in the show notes. This is that feel when you're late to the joke
Okay, terrible
Voice jail
We didn't we didn't successfully abolish voice jail. No, we still have an iron grip on a few people
Fuck yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it's still there. You know the terror the terror continues
So, uh, you know watch yourself. All right next one is from vox populi
Uh three two one go
Since this is apparently some sort of art help podcast. How the fuck do I finish long projects short project get inspired do thing
Finish thing long project get inspired do thing have issue no inspiration to get over issue never finish thing
What the fuck can you even do?
Uh, yeah, long project is just small project, but uh, but many of them in a long in a long line
Yeah
Yeah, break it break it down. You just gotta into manageable chunks. You gotta not rely on the inspiration
You have to discipline yourself and not be a bitch
Uh, I had that's also true. I had a fucking twitter post where I I made this really long image of
me explaining
The two methods of of creation
Uh, I don't want to get into it because it's really long-winded, but
I could link that because that it was like it was good. I remember that
yeah the thing with
Doing things and then creating things
Two sides of the brain two different methods if you're if you're liking inspiration
Um, it's because you don't have a plan of what to do and for that I would say so the solution is just to experience things you like
That's what I'm doing. It's working. I'm what if you don't but what if you don't like anything?
Then look at things people say is good and just be optimistic about it
Ugh
No, just like assume that you are correctly stupid and you don't know anything is like go to people say
What do I do? What do I what's good?
And they say a big big list because they always have a big list everyone has a big list of things that you should watch read and
Listen to and you're like, okay. I'll do that. I'll do that. You put one into your vhs
And you watch it
And you're like, okay. I don't know if I gained anything but I I did it
And you do that over and over again, eventually you'll become smart like me
This is like kind of sad almost but something that like does inspire me is like watching bad things
Uh, because a lot of the times I'll get down on myself back. Oh my god
This is the worst thing ever made by human and then I'll watch like an episode of best of the worst
I'll be like, oh my god. I'm fine. I'm totally fine. Oh, definitely. It could be it could be so much worse
Oh, I'm I'm a fucking genius. I'm and then I feel better have I mentioned the Tezuka awards
Submission page has like a thing where you can look at all of the submissions
And there are so many of them already and they are awful. I mean
These are the ones that I'm I'm talking about. I were posted like days after the contest was announced
So they could not have been a lot of effort put in
um
They are the worst things I've ever seen. They are extremely cringe. I look at them and I'm like, wow
I'll be fine. Wait
These are like other entries other entries into the contest. Yes
Where can I find them? I want to see um, I'll get a link
In a yeah
I want to see the cringe. Are they all
How many of the entries are from japanese people? I don't know
Hmm
There's a there's a there's a place to see it
Uh
Guys, I just got a message
from munchy
Jay trump telling me that the vaporette is done. Oh, that's good. Five. That's five unless he's lying unless this is a prank
That's five out of six
So there we go. Oh, this is happening live. This is happening live on the air
unscripted
So we all have to bully jade morrow now. Is that what you're saying? We all have to bully jade morrow. That's right
jade
I think she might I think she might be on like a trip or something
I think she she said she was going somewhere and I'm not sure if she's back yet
That's still her fault for going on a trip
That's true. No, it's true. She was getting off the bus and I held my leg out and says have a nice trip when she fell
And she's still falling. She's been falling for ages
Take a picture of the last longer
Cool
Um
Can you show me these man show me the manga. I posted the link. Show me the manga
Where is the manga? There's definitely some some more good ones that have been submitted since I last looked
But there's there's definitely the
There's definitely the ones I mean
There was one that was like popular for a while called two piece, which was just
Like a terribly drunk number two piece
Yeah, that's
And uh, oh, yeah, some of these are like real bad
Yeah, I mean, no, it's it's a it's a very exciting process. Yeah, I do
Tails gets trolled is on here. Wait, no
No, it's on page two
What there are pages at the bottom
Oh, okay
Tails gets trolled by chris pool. Is that his name?
What the fuck it could be his name
No, it can't be
This can't be this has to be some kind of like troll entry
It has to be right
I mean, I hope it's the real deal if if he thinks he could he could like submit tails gets trolled as a comic
To the is a troll. It would be a troll move to submit tails gets trolled
Yeah, it would
Oh, these are like not even very long. This one's only this one's only 10 pages. There's two piece
This one is
Oh, no, it's not it's not by lezabot. It just says please go support lezabot. Fuck you, dude
Post this on his behalf. You're probably
That sucks. What if it wins, huh? What are you gonna do then?
um
what about
How wait, how oh, okay, this one's 54 pages
I was gonna say like these all seem really short, but some of them are long some of them. Um, it's
What one of these days? How long is yours gonna be? No idea. I'm thinking between 30 and 50 pages
It's respectable
healthy
Because like, um
The wanted by it sure odor was 30 pages
I was looking at some other ones the the won the tesaka awards
They're more closer to 50 55 pages and the limit is 55
So I'm thinking somewhere in that ballpark is like the the the right amount for it to be
concise
Yet contain a lot of stuff and have it
And I'll have it all work
so
Are these all the submissions? I
Oh, you can change by language. Let's there's not actually that many
These are the english ones if the at the top
Right, so you can I guess you can't see the japanese ones. You can see the korean ones
There's only a few of those
Spanish why can't I why can't I see the japanese ones because those are the best ones
Those are the ones that are actually going to win
There's a lot of spanish ones
and they they seem to be
Generally better overall like i'm seeing a pretty few actually good-looking ones
But then also, yeah
There are exactly five there are five korean ones
It is funny till I mean we still got two whole months before the deadline
I'm sure there's going to be a huge spike near the end if you had two more months to work on this
Why would you submit it like I would be like busting my ass like it's it's cuz people
I mean these ones they don't look
Either they were already drawn or they're very fast at drawing or
Like the the ones that look bad. They don't realize that
You need to spend more time on a drawing to make it good
And they just wanted it to be done like I I got school
I should I should I got like a few minutes after school. Maybe this is like an advertising thing
They're not trying to win the contest
They just know that they're going to be on the front page of something a lot of people are going on
And they're hoping to pick up traffic that way
I mean there is like a voting system people can like things and view things
So it's true
Some of these things that look not so good have got a couple thousand looks
Do you think do you think do you think jump regrets their decision yet of opening this up to everybody?
I I
I don't know
I don't think so because
There's got to be lots of of young japanese kids who are like
Generally japanese people seem to be better at drawing
That's not that's that cannot be like all people in japan are better at drawing
There's got to be a few that just don't get it don't know how to do it don't unskilled don't want to work
But they want to win anyway, so they're gonna submit so I don't think this is like unusual
That's fair
What if I like went and just like submitted the champion to this like even though it's old
You could do that. Yeah
You couldn't put the you couldn't put the game in there, but uh, how am I how many pages is the first chapter?
Uh
I I forget hold on let me find out
Uh maximum page limit is 55. I I guess for it to be like a good entry
It would need to be a contained story that has a beginning and an end
It's 60. It's 67 pages. Ah fail lull. It's there's an epic fail
Lot of ghosts is nearly 100 pages, so I couldn't submit that I'll just cut out like I'll just cut out like some some bad ones
Cut out the the first page second page
Who needs them?
Uh
Oh, yeah, I can cut out the well if I cut out the cover
Maybe yeah, I don't know whatever who cares
Uh, all right, what were we talking about? We were talking about laughing at people who are not good in order to feel better about ourselves, which I do
um
It's not for me. It's not so even so much laughing. It's just like
Because like so much of the time you look at it's a relief and you see great artists and you're like, oh god
I'm nowhere near that but then you like it's the other side of the spectrum be like, okay. It's not it's not as bad
It's there are no there are no great artists every time I see art. I think man. This this is shit
This is embarrassing. That's not me at all
But I guess that means I shouldn't be embarrassed because even the good stuff sucks
Like the the thing yeah, it's not laughter. I don't I'm not laughing at these people. It's it's more of a
a relief and like a
That that people who have nowhere near the level of skill even I have
Are confident enough in themselves to submit
Their work and I'm like wow. Why am I being a coward when these people
Are able to step up to the plate and present something to the world
So it's like it's it's a relief that I don't have to worry so much
Yeah
Yeah, I feel you I feel you on that being an artist is embarrassing
Being an artist is just like embarrassing yourself
For money. It's it's cringe and based at the same time. It's one of those. Yeah. Yeah, pretty much
I guess I guess so
Uh, do you want to do the last voicemail?
Yeah
Okay, this last one is from
We got one from this person last time. This is from margar. So three two one go
Hey, the pcp
I've just been listening to the latest episode and I can't help but wonder why there are so few you
Showing up. It seems like lately. It's really just been ben
uh, hippo and
Nate but
Isn't there a financial incentive for more people to show up?
I mean, it just doesn't really make sense to me like
What else could you guys all be doing that more people can't show up for the episodes?
I'll listen to them either way. I think this just seems a little weird to me
I said the same thing. I also don't understand it. There is
There is an incentive. Yeah. I mean, that's how you get paid is if you show up to episodes
Well, I can explain why I haven't been here
Yeah, I mean I've been busy with like studying and stuff
But the the real reason is that I have the covet unemployment thing
and yeah, uh
If I am on all four
Episodes a month and then I get paid from Nate
I am not qualified to collect unemployment and I make double the amount of money
For unemployment than I do being on the podcast
So it is actually my financial incentive now is to not be on the show because I make 500 extra dollars
Can't you just thanks covet? Thanks covet. Can't you just like split up the amount like
Between weeks and then you're still under the limit. I'm splitting up my patreon right now
Between the weeks
But I don't know because like if you if I go over 267 dollars in one of those weeks
You get kicked and I don't get anything
So I I'd have to crunch the numbers and like figure it out because even if you make like 250 something dollars
You still get like 20 percent docked from the mouth. So yeah, it's yeah
It's a it's a financial juggling. It's a lot of math. I don't like math
So the easiest way is like I can spend that three hours doing more studying which I want to do anyways
And I know I make more money. So I I also I do I do get money docked off my
My unemployment for for like making income at all, which is funny
uh, but
But people got to be on the podcast
Yeah, somebody's got to be on the after you guys a bone this week. I was like, I fuck it. I'm right here
Yeah, sure. Yeah, sure
um
I mean
You can always just ask Nate to like hold off on paying you, right? I suppose
Yeah, um, I mean it ends like in like three or four weeks. Anyways, so it won't be an issue after that
It uh, they might extend it but like less like it might go from like the like 600
Bonus to like they might like cut it a half down to like a 300 bonus or something. Well, I'm okay. It's not
It's not it's not clear what they're gonna what's gonna happen
I'm gaining back all the savings I lost when I was fucking pre-surgery. So I'm about it
The state is uh, helping me out right now and I'm I'm all I'm all for it
Yeah, that's good to hear
Yeah, the thing is get some of that that sweet money back from those those all that tax
They take for me every year for being self-employed and they double tax me. I'm finally getting a little bit of it back
Are you ready to get taxed on your unemployment money though? No, I'm not
Well
Get ready
That's coming
Um, it's only it's only the base though like the covet part is not taxable from what I understand
It's only the base $267 of unemployment that will be taxed wait
Really? I'm pretty sure the 600
Is is not taxable income
Oh boy. Oh, I should look into that. I'm pretty sure don't quote me on it
But I was watching some videos on the unemployment stuff and I'm pretty sure part of the decision was that that $600 is not taxable income
I know that the trump bucks are not taxable income
But unemployment is but like the 600 dollar like cares act bonus is a separate thing
So I could believe that maybe that doesn't count. I'll look fascinating. That's great. That's that's very I hope that's true
Uh, okay, cool. Cool. Cool. Cool
Uh
Dur
A dur
Uh, well
As to as to where everyone else is uh, I don't know
Yeah, I don't I I don't know why Nate's not around. I don't know. I guess I guess digi is
Doing other stuff. I don't fuck well digi digi is um extremely busy with
Like backed up projects and also gender well stuff and I can I can I can understand digi
Digi's digi's very busy with her gender right now
Yeah, loma. I guess I guess. Um, I'm backed up projects. I've got fucking. I've got backed up projects out the wazoo
Well, they're they're backed up projects like patreon reward things
That's that's what I've heard like I can understand that taking president
It is still only like a couple hours a week. It's it's like two hours. It's like two hours a week
That's like, uh, I don't know. I don't blame anybody for not feeling like coming on because sometimes no
It's it's it's a two hour podcast, but like you don't always want a podcast. You don't always have anything to say
you don't always
Feel like
Spilling your soul out to a bunch of people who will go lol fail
It is very strange to have Nate not showing up because like
Nate is Nate's on like every I'm on like almost every episode
I think Nate's the only one who's been on more episodes than I have
So he's always here
but now
It's all gone. It's all come tumbling down. No, no, it's fine. It's fine and it's good
Sure
Sure it is
I say this so that the patreons don't leave and then I can get all the money when I'm the only one left
The patreon the patrons will be like they'll hear this and they'll say oh no
We're on a sinking ship. They're gonna take me down with them. You gotta bail right now
If you're if you're on if you are a patron when the pcp crashes and burns when we all get cancelled
You are all liable for our crimes
I want you to know. Yeah, so uh, you
We're we're all in this together
Uh, if we fail you you go down as well
We'll make sure of it
That's right, that's right, okay. Uh, well shit guys, that's all the fucking voicemails
That's the end of the podcast
That's the end of the podcast send us a voicemail at the procrastinators mail at gmail.com. No
That's that speak pipe
Oh, what did I what did I say you said the the patreon? Oh
lol
Okay, well, yeah tpcrastinators
Uh become a patron and so we can take you down with us at
Is it is it tpcrastinators?
What's our fucking patreon patreon.com slash the pro procrastinators speak pipe.com slash pcp voicemail
That's pcp voicemail. Oh, okay
Okay, good
Also on twitter at pcp. That's tpcrastinators. That's the one tpcrastinators
Hey get in the discord for one dollar bonus episodes for five dollars on the patreon
If you're listening there's like a hundred thousand million bonus episodes right now. That's that's the thing
If you're listening to this you probably already know but we do have a website. It's the it's the procrastinators
Dot-com or the procrastinators podcast dot-com. I believe it's the procrastinators podcast
Let me see the
procrastin
Yeah, the procrastinators podcast dot-com
All our episodes are there all our shit is there. I guess that's our I guess that's our hub
Uh or whatever as it should have been the whole time. It really should have been the whole time. Yeah everything every
Damn, oh damn. It's okay. It's okay. It's gonna be fun
Uh, we will probably
I'm I'm
I feel like
We are probably gonna get the videos back
And then we will
I would if you if you made me guess right now, I would say probably yes
Probably they will eventually come back and then we got to fucking back them up
Maybe on the website or with that library thing you were talking about tom. I will as soon as they come back. I will be doing that
I personally went through and saved
Everything that was not a bonus in a pcp a pcp episode
I saved it to my personal hard drive of the stuff that is currently there and has not been
Deleted as of right now just because I was just because I was afraid they're like, oh, what if they terminate us again?
Like what if what if they just
What if they're reviewing the content and they're like, no never mind cancelled again out of here? Yeah
Uh, okay. All right. We're out almost two hours. We did it guys. We recorded a full podcast
We made we fulfilled our obligations to the audience and fulfill your obligation and give us money
That's right. That's right
All right. Well, let's let's fucking get out of here
Bye