Look at the stars. Look how they shine for you. And everything you do. Yeah, they were all yellow.
I came along. I wrote a song for you. And all the things you do. And it was called yellow.
So then I took my turn. Oh, what a thing to have done. And it was all yellow. Your skin.
Oh yeah, your skin and bones turned into something beautiful. And you know I love you so. You know I love you so.
Digibro. Pro Crastinators. 2016, y'all. Let's do this shit.
Rolled up at Coldplay in 08. Songs were great but the stage play made an impression. I'm guessing the old white folds to the show never give the solicit, but here's my position. I need some invention.
Not iteration, not the basics of emotion, but basic reaction. Some action, suburb of the verse. Suburb of the curses you spit.
Not a clean up, clean cut show, but it's a burp and I dance with the kids. I need some legit.
It's that time that you know what they act with the real stuff, the text that this is.
A little bit of it, but shadowing that hell to come. It's a totally complete piece of shit.
So sit back, motherfucker, get lit, cause the podcast is always fucked. You definitely want it quit.
Hello and welcome to another episode of the Pro Crastinators podcast. Here back again with all your favorite internet people.
It's not yellow!
Oh fucking god, you're a host.
All right, let's settle it down. I'm your host, the best guy ever, bestie boy.
Fuck you, I ruined the podcast.
Here with all my internet friends, we've got patreon.com.bensaint.
Former internet friends.
Yes, that's right. The DeVoo Collective.
Yo.
21st century digital boy.
See, the fact is that we can't ever escape each other cause we're all a part of the DeVoo Collective.
That's exactly right.
There's no fucking breaking out of this hell.
Hip-O-Crit.
It is yellow.
Thank you.
Endless, endless jessicles.
Who's ready to argue about Homestuck for an hour, guys.
Yeah, feels that way.
And me, the best guy of all.
So, today is a couple of times before we've taken suggestions on what the topics been from comments and stuff,
but today is a suggestion from a friend of ours, our buddy Nino.
Or, like, Nino90 or something?
Nino. You can Google him Nino. We'll put a link to his shit in the bottom.
And, by the way, Quick Plug, he made the coolest song ever, just today we heard it,
called Jacoshie on his SoundCloud.
I'm gonna put a link to that and this shit, too, cause it was so dope, everyone in the world should listen to it.
So, everybody go listen to it.
And his topic suggestion was things you just can't get into.
Things you can't get into.
And so, there's no urban dictionary for that shit, we're just gonna have to feel it out ourselves.
So, anyone have anything to say on the topic of things you can't get into?
Cause I've just got a bunch of examples, personally.
Well, I generally think it's annoying when an internet person, like, talks about it and then says it too many times.
And they're like, oh yeah, I can't get into this and I can't get into that.
When I don't get the sense that they're really even trying in the first place.
I feel that something that you just can't get into should be a really special status for a thing.
Is that the definition we're gonna use?
For example, someone's doing a crunchyroll plug and they're like, I tried watching this anime but I just couldn't get into it.
It's like, nigga, you don't even care about fucking crunchyroll, you care about anime.
That kind of shit pisses me off.
People that, I have a friend who I tried to get to play Undertale and he was like, oh, I just can't get into reading things.
I just can't get into reading the text.
I was like that, well, yeah.
I agree with DeVoo, but mostly in the context.
I don't mind if it's like, hey, I'm on this guy's vlogging channel and he listed 10 different shows that people asked him about.
I can't get into that one, I can't get into that.
But when someone writes a whole review of a movie and they're like, I just couldn't get into it, I'm sorry, guys.
And I'm like, why'd you fucking make a video about it?
No one cares that you couldn't get into it.
That's the least interesting sense.
When they let all these things that they just can't get into be part of their mythos.
As everyone knows, I'm not the kind of person who can get into this or the person who can get into that.
That's so stupid.
I think to some extent, Yahtzee is kind of annoying about that.
He has all these things.
He probably can't get into JRPGs at all, right?
Proudly wearing their inability to appreciate something on their sleeve is a really obnoxious character trait.
I can't get into rap or something. I don't listen to any.
I'm not proud of that. I'm kind of ashamed that I don't understand this art form.
Just five minutes ago, before we started the podcast, you were saying, what?
This rap was done using a beat that wasn't made by the same guy who did the rap. That's terrible.
No, no, no, no. I thought it was something else.
He was misinterpreted.
I appreciate that Yahtzee.
I don't expect everybody to get into everything.
I think with something like games, people group them all together.
It's all video games, but they're really so different that it's understandable to have ones you can't get into.
I'm glad that Yahtzee at some point said, I'm not going to cover JRPGs and fighting games anymore.
He cut them out of his life and of his reviews.
He's annoying because of his attitude. His attitude is the double-edged sword that makes him who he is.
The approach I'm going to take in this podcast is, for me, anything I can't get into, like Ben said,
I'm disappointed in myself. I'm on a constant quest to get into everything.
Stuff that I just can't get into is like a major failing.
By the way, let's just clarify, not being able to get into something is very different from disliking something that you experience.
Totally different.
They can be the same thing.
It could be the same, but it doesn't have to be.
If you watch something and it leaves no impression on you, that's more...
You seem to have a well-figured outlist and stuff, so why don't you lead the charge here and show us all what we're looking for?
Yeah, I put some thought into this. Mine are a little bit less specific pieces of media or anything I couldn't get into.
There were sort of more things over the years that I've been interested in and just never really found a comfortable place in my life for them.
Let me see. I've got three bigger examples here.
Here's my favorite one.
Back in college, me and my buddies...
What is it?
It's like playing video games with other people.
Unless it's like a fighting game, obviously that is built for that.
But being able to play any kind of game while other people are in the room has always been a big problem for me.
It was particularly an issue when in college, me and my buddies did nothing but sit around and play video games all day.
When we played Smash Bros. Brawl, it was great. We all had a fantastic time.
But then my buddies would play their favorite RPGs because we all played that kind of shit.
One of them recommended... I enjoyed being in the area while other people were playing a game. That was great.
Eventually, someone would recommend... I played Tales of Symphonia. That was a game recommended to me at the time.
I played it and my friend, quote-unquote Mike, as he's known, was there.
That's just his name.
He's just Mike in quotations. That's his name, yeah.
Wait, hang on. I thought he was your quote-unquote friend, Mike.
The term has become interchangeable. He goes by quote.
My quote-unquote friend, quote-unquote Mike.
I don't really know anything about him.
Everything I know about him is by implication only.
He recommended that I play Tales of Symphonia, and I did.
He, quote-unquote, recommended it.
He, quote-unquote, played this game, and so I, quote-unquote, did.
It was a good game. I liked it a lot, and I beat it.
But the thing was, that game has a Final Fantasy IX kind of multiplayer aspect.
We're in battles.
Oh, god, you played it multiplayer?
Of course we did, because he wanted to play too.
That's how we played Secret of Mana back in the day.
That's very different.
Secret of Mana.
And back when we were totally uncritical children, it was fine.
I gotta tell you guys.
As adults, I'm sure it would be infuriating.
That's the thing. Back in the day, me and Ben played all the...
I would sit right next to Ben, watch him play video games.
We played Secret of Mana together.
It was, I remember those days so fondly. It was fantastic.
But when I got older, playing...
Let me real quickly to clarify the difference between Secret of Mana and Tales of Symphonia.
In Tales of Symphonia, first player does everything,
and then once you get into one of the random battles,
then second player gets control of one of your characters
who would ordinarily be controlled by the AI fighting with you.
But the camera still follows player one.
So you're basically a glorified NPC in this game.
Once the battle's over, then player two just sits down as controller
and fucking player one does everything else.
It's not fun, really.
At the very least, you're going to have such small...
Because it's a fucking JRPG. It's all fucking talking all day,
and then there's a couple cool fights, and then you're out of random battles.
It's a little sister multiplayer, where it's like,
if you're like 15 and you've got a five-year-old sister or brother,
and they are like, I want to play video games, you're like here.
Secret of Mana is so much better for that,
because unless there's pretty few hardcore cutscenes in that game,
you're always able to just run around and do whatever as player two.
It's a great game.
But the point is just, when I got older,
I was 17 at the time playing this game with all my friends around.
The thing is, we all wanted to talk, because that's what we always did.
We would sit around, we would talk, and I would get so angry
when people would talk over voiced cutscenes,
and there's a million of those in that fucking game,
including little dialogue pop-ups that happened,
and it infuriating me.
And their presence made the experience horrible for me,
and my need to hear everything.
They'd be talking to me like, guys, shut up.
I'm trying to hear the story. I can't hear what they're saying.
Made it horrible for them.
It was terrible for everyone.
People talking during movies.
I mean, it's a similar issue.
I was going to say movies are the same.
Watching movies with people, I just...
Oh my God. Watching movies with a fucking woman.
They never shut their goddamn yaps.
And then, 20 minutes into the movie,
I don't know what's happening, because you're fucking shut up.
Oh my God, why aren't you paying attention, you dumb bitch?
Oh my God.
I would actually rather shoot myself in the head with a gun
than watch a movie with a woman.
The time I remember that most strongly was...
Ben might remember this. We were at like a family...
I want to say a family reunion.
I think at Uncle Andy's house.
And they were playing The Big Lebowski in the basement.
And I had always wanted to see The Big Lebowski.
I was fairly young at the time, maybe like 18.
And I was excited to see this movie.
And then my fucking cousins and the adults...
At this point in my life, I hated alcohol and it terrified me.
Everyone piled into the basement to hit up the fucking bar.
And they just kept talking.
And they kept talking. And they got louder.
And they got louder. And more people came down.
And they got drunker. And then they were like, hey Nate, what are you doing?
Why are you all by yourself over here, Nate?
Trying to watch this movie?
What are you doing, Nate? Why would you be here?
We're trying to have a party here.
It's not like you people put on the fucking movie.
And I just chose to sit down and watch it.
You're getting away from the topic.
That's true.
And even the original thing you're saying
sounds a little bit more like a gripe
that it does a thing you can't get into.
No, no. I don't know.
Let me just clarify it.
My two-player tells us of Podia.
That's definitely the horrible esoteric topic
that makes no sense in that.
Alright, we can move on.
As soon as I finish my point, which is just that
we would play other games.
And whenever I wasn't the one
who was playing the game, if I just came in
to do whatever,
it would always be a great time.
My friend was playing...
Fuck, what was it? I can't remember.
It doesn't matter. Jesus.
The point is, I've always hated that experience
and I'd like to be able to do it
because I know lots of people have fun doing it.
Alright, that's my first example,
but we can move on to somebody else's shit.
Hit those.
Okay.
There's a forest near my house
and there's this big old tree
and it's got a thing underneath it
and I just can't get into it anymore.
I used to be able to...
But I'm too big now.
And it makes me really sad.
Every time!
I know that feeling.
I got fat and...
Hit but I'm surprised you can't fit in there, honestly.
Well, it's a very small...
You got the big bones. It's his hair.
I do actually have...
I do actually have a thing.
Okay.
Now what? I forgot it.
I forget it.
Alright, Ben.
We need more PCPs like you.
Oh, the points gone?
No, no.
Right.
It was about the idea that
considering what everybody said about
getting into something
and not trying,
I'm very much the person who doesn't try.
I can get into anything.
It's just the actually
opening it up and looking at it.
And it set the tree.
But if somebody really pushes
something to be like...
If something is considered among everybody
to be really, really good, then I'll look at it
like Ava or something.
But sometimes the fact that they're pushing it
makes it less appealing.
That's how I feel about Game of Thrones.
I don't want to get into Game of Thrones
because everyone's constantly talking about it.
But it's not that I can't get into it.
I'm sorry I won't be able to.
Yeah, I'm kind of the same.
I'm pretty hesitant to pick up a new thing.
It's just like...
Everything sucks.
So when you pick up a new thing, odds are it's going to suck.
I never pick up a new thing
unless it's been recommended to me by
multiple trusted sources.
Yeah.
I don't trust any sources.
So I pick up absolutely everything.
If Nate recommends me an anime
and then independently some other person
is like, hey, have you heard about this anime?
I'll be like, oh shit, that's twice.
Maybe there's something to it.
Yeah.
I've never, ever in my life had someone
whose taste correlated
with mine enough
that they could recommend me something
and I would be like, oh yeah,
that obviously is going to be something I'll like.
Well yeah, okay, but you can figure out
why they like it and then figure out
how that relates to what you like.
I guess, but like I said, my method is
just to literally watch everything.
I won't be able to trust anyone until I try it.
Like with Game of Thrones,
there's nobody who could tell me
that it was good
in a way that I wanted to watch it.
And then finally, the only reason I did
is because it was like, it was so
fucking universal that I was like, I gotta at least
let's just fucking, I sat down with Victor
and I had seen like a few scenes
here and there that I thought were kind of cool.
You know, I'd seen the red wedding on TV
and I was like, oh alright, that's kind of cool.
So then I watched it,
but no one can ever like just talk me
into watching something. I have to
just check out everything.
Except the seasonal anime charts.
Alright, who else has got it?
I guess, I guess Steven Universe though.
We all kind of talked each other into that one.
I got recommended because all you guys
are watching it, so yeah.
Alright, alright, so my first
item of things I can't get into
is something that I used to be very into.
And that is Dungeons & Dragons
and or Tabletop
role-playing games in general.
Now, as a
youngen, I was very taken
with my self-image as a
quote-unquote nerdy kid
as a, you know, as an
intellectual, little fucking smart
nerd guy. And the image of that
on TV portrayed these people
as playing Dungeons & Dragons.
So I was like, oh I gotta get into Dungeons & Dragons
and I found some stuff, I figured it out.
I invited all my friends and we all played
Dungeons & Dragons all the time.
And it was a fine and dandy way to hang out.
But that's all it really was.
Agreed.
The thing about D&D is
like, yeah, ostensibly
the point of it is to tell
a story. Like the point of D&D
is that a story unfolds.
But like everything about
the game itself stands in
the way of good storytelling.
It is all based on fucking...
I mean, a great Dungeon Master can pull
a great story out of even the stupidest
scenario. That's fine.
But like, it's all based on random chance.
It's all couched in these
stupid fucking combat mechanics.
Every time I play D&D and there's a fight,
every fight takes like hours
and they're boring because nothing
narratively interesting happens during a fight.
It's all just fucking dy-
And it's like everyone having to wait for everyone else to go. It's the worst.
I did a pen and paper role play with
my friends. We just sort of invented our own
rules. We did something really basic.
That's the way to go. Make your own rules.
Whenever we wanted to do something that was fun
or dialogue focused, I would just
simplify the rules. It was basically
like one of the new Paper Mario games.
We're just like, okay, just one hit
will kill this enemy, but like five hits
will kill you. Alright, how about that? No more health points
today. You know, Ben,
looking back on it, I think there were exactly
two times I had a good time doing RPG stuff.
The first was our like
Homestuck one that you ran. Yes.
Which was awesome. Spurg. I talk about it
in my interview. Oh, yes.
I was. Yeah, Nate was in that.
I was Luke something,
the guy. I don't remember what I was.
You were the heir of life. Oh, yeah, it was awesome.
I brought life.
Your power set was about animating
objects. It was super
dope. And the other time was
do you remember, Ben, back at College
Academy, that guy Kevin
the DM. That was like the first time I
played DM and he fucking killed that
shit. Me and Nate
both did the summer program as
kids where we went to
the point is it was like a thing for smart kids.
And we were in the Mentos Trio
of the Mentos. Holy shit.
The Mentos Trio is life.
We gotta go back. We gotta save
the Mentos Trio for another day. Okay.
But yeah, they had
a class at this thing that was basically just playing
Dungeons and Dragons and the kid who
the guy, well, not a kid, a guy who ran it
was this dude Kevin Powers. Yes.
Who had, he was like as tall,
extremely white, extremely skinny
nerd. But he was
with the voice of Barry White. He was really into jazz
music and he had the deepest
baritone voice I've ever
heard in my life. Fuck yeah, Kevin.
And he would
he would roll the dice and be like, uh
I, is there a, I attack the monster
and he'd be like, mmm, the kobold
reels back from the savage
blow of your mighty war hammer.
He was such a badass. Roll for damage.
That was the best
that was the best possible experience
of D&D playing that. You guys
you know, I've noticed an issue with all
of your things so far is
I can't, one thing I can't
get into is such and such. Except for that one
time I totally got into it.
It's kind of going against the spirit of the thing.
You know what, Ben admitted that he used to be into it.
Let me, let me bring it, let me bring it
to, let me bring it to why I can't stand
it now. One, the rules
are cumbersome and there's too many of
them. Two,
playing it with people is a nightmare because
when you get together everyone has their own idea
for how to have fun playing it and
combat takes for fucking ever and
everyone else's turn is the most boring
thing in the world. Only your own turn is interesting
and it is a minority of the experience.
You just fucking sit around
and do nothing and just fucking
deal with all this rule-y bullshit and I fucking
hate it. I hate it so much.
It's not like inherent.
The inherent format isn't a problem
for you. It's just like the, it's
about the way it's always done. No, it is the format.
Some people like it. No, no, no.
There are better games
than D&D that have less crunchy
rules and are less annoying about it.
I still think they kind of end up being
annoying because of the social aspect.
D&D itself
I think is a particularly bad game.
I think for me, because
I'm piggybacking on yours, I also can't
get into tabletop games and just like
you it was a thing that I grew up thinking
looked cool and like obviously
it was like what all the big kids did instead
of like, you know, like it's
like a bit better than video games
because it's real and tactile and you're making
it up yourself. Hold on, dude.
I remember specifically in your old Q&A
you said that like you could just play Arkham Horror
for two weeks if the power went out and you'd
have a great time because you had done that
before when the power went out one time.
Oh, shit. Yeah, we did do that
and Arkham Horror is not really a role-play
game so much as like Arkham Horror.
I had no idea what it was. I had no idea
what it was. I thought maybe it's a prequel
to one of the Batman games, the board game
edition. I don't know. Yeah, that's what it is.
It's a HP Lovecraft inspired board game
that's so intricately
intricate in the way you play it.
Yeah, by the way, David, they're both inspired
by Arkham from Lovecraft.
So, but yeah, like that's
sort of a different thing, but like with pen and paper
which I'm not that into board games either
at all, just because
they take so fucking long to set up and do everything.
Sam, I used to be into board games and now
I just think... Oh, that's why
that's like the best part in the board game series
when he has this one board game
that he's gonna play and like it's like five minutes
of him explaining how to set it up and
Motherfucker Mike is like, okay, when you're
gonna be finished setting it up and he's like,
well, you see, you also have to get these stats
in the right way and you gotta do this and you gotta do that.
And it's like this huge montage of saying everything
up and then at the end he's like, alright,
I'm all ready to go and Mike is bored and leaves.
Like, I'm gonna go now and I just like, oh man,
that's totally agreed
and relate to that, man. That's also
the Dungeons and Dragons experience because
every player's turn
lasts too fucking long
and nobody else is
like, unless you guys are like really
tightly packed as a group
into whatever event you're doing,
if everyone's doing something even slightly different
it's not relevant to anyone else.
So the second one guy gets his turn, everyone
else gets on their phones and starts fucking
texting other people and just wants to be anywhere
else because they don't care about what's going on in your fucking
story, especially if you're fighting something.
Like, nobody cares and then like in order
to make the story at all interesting or to
accommodate anybody's creativity,
then our DM would just like, you know,
basically say fuck most of the rules.
Like he would just be like, alright, well whatever.
And then eventually it got to a point
where we're like, well the story's not going anywhere
because it was just all of us
we're not fucking story
writers, we have no sense of narrative
progression, we're just digging around.
There's too many conflicting ideas going on.
My brother is great with that. We were in the final battle
of one of our game
and like the boss was about
to like unleash their ultimate attack
and I don't want any of the characters to
die, so like the final attack
is like heading towards my brother's character
and he's like, okay what do you do? And he's like
I slice it with my sword
and he rolls a two
and that's like a failure. I hit it
with the...
He got a two so he did it twice.
I hit it with the butt of my sword, he rolled a one.
I hit it with my left butt cheek, he rolled a one.
I tried to like fart in its general direction
and it rolled a two. He just kept getting further
and further into like abstract ways of
attacking until finally he rolled a four
and it succeeded.
And he's great.
That does not sound like any kind
of Dungeons and Dragons I have.
That's basically who my brother is like.
Because like I was physically moving
the attack towards his character so he kept
running out of time and had to come up with it
like in the span of a few seconds and it was glorious.
And so that's how...
I think I'm just
a lot less interested in the creativity
of my friends than I am in the creativity
of anyone who is trained
as an artist.
Related point,
my interest in
Dungeons and Dragons and board games pretty much
completely died
exactly at the moment that I became
interested in drawing and making my own
shit.
It's such a waste of time compared to that.
Sure is.
It's a creative endeavor only you don't get anything
out of it.
You're doing it with a bunch of people who aren't
creatives and have no stake
in becoming creative people because
they're not trying to do that
as a passion in your career.
You can see that by the way.
On your first session of D&D every time
it's everyone making their character.
Nobody knows how to fucking make their character.
It was like an entire fucking game.
So I guess what I would do in the future
is just you roll a six-sided die
and six means super successful.
Five means very successful.
And then one means a huge failure.
So you just decide what you're going to try to do
and you roll for the success level.
Let's see, there's a problem
even with that because the fact that your actions
are controlled by a random chance
means that the narrative that you want to
happen is not guaranteed to.
Going into trying to have a narrative
is not the way to go man.
Yeah, I mean
part of the idea of it is that
an interesting story is crafted.
Part of the idea is that an interesting
story can emerge through random chance.
That's absolutely right.
The story that me and my friends did
was interesting to us because...
But it won't because people aren't able to handle it.
Because what happened was one of my friends...
Do you want to take that risk
hundreds of hours, I don't know, dozens of hours
on a campaign that might be shit?
I think it's pretty much inevitably going to be interesting
with the right people because what happened was
my friend kept...
We had all the characters lined up on a grid
and stuff and one of my friends
kept happening to
move in just the right spaces
to constantly be in a circumstance
where she would probably trip
in the universe and so it became
a completely accidental running gag
that her character gets knocked over
or trips or falls.
It was totally organic and at one point
another character trips
into one of the NPCs and just the way
the dialogue ended up happening
he became one of the main characters
and I ended up having to play a character
coming. It was so cool.
And then there was one side character
exhibiting very suspicious behavior
just because I couldn't come up with
what the secrets were.
The point is I had to come up with a whole
secret special twist
on the go as I was going
and it turned out to be an incredible twist
that I wouldn't be able to explain here.
But yeah, a lot of really interesting...
I came up with a whole lore about...
Is this the D&D cost or what?
Yeah, I know.
I remember wanting to do it
with all the cool things that he did
with his friends doing D&D.
The thing is...
The point is Ben can't get into it, right?
That's all we're saying.
Fun things can happen and like
it can be really interesting and entertaining
and also a good way to hang out with friends
and all that stuff is cool.
I just think that it's way more pain than pleasure
and that the amount of bullshit you have to deal with
to get those benefits
are not worth it.
Alright, and the case has been made
and it has been contested and that's fine.
Let's move on to the next one.
Jesse, you got something you can't get into here?
Yeah.
There's a...
There's this webcomic.
This...
It's pretty popular.
It's like kind of a webcomic
but I guess it's also kind of like a shitty video game.
I don't know.
The art style is really gay.
The characters...
What's it called? Something about homos.
Something about homos and suck.
Ah, my god.
Is it...
Is it Homestar Runner?
Is that what you're talking about?
I like Homestar Runner personally.
Ringback Homestar.
Here's the thing with Jesse is that
if something is introduced to him in a contentious way
that he'll never be able to like...
God damn it!
Don't even fucking start because
you're not going to goad me into a fight.
Okay?
Because I thought about this long and hard.
No one here is going to say some stupid shit
or infer some far out bullshit
about me that's going
to fucking get my blood pressure up.
I'm not going to have it. I'm not going to allow it
because I have constructed
the perfect
argument proof
example of why I can't
get into Homestuck.
We're all going to sit down.
We're going to sit in a circle.
We're going to have a calm, familial discussion.
We're going to have a Thanksgiving turkey.
I can do that if you can.
We're going to sip hot tea.
We're going to fucking play some oriental music
on like some strings.
We're just going to go to a fucking Chinese restaurant
and we're going to turn on some yellow lights
to light everything.
I don't know what those are.
I don't think that yellow lights
are actually a thing that exists.
They do it in a Chinese restaurant.
All the lights they put up are yellow lights.
I'm making a racial joke.
Okay, go on.
And what a joke it was.
Okay.
Homestuck.
It's fucking gay.
There it is!
It was all worth it.
I don't even
disagree that it's gay.
It's pretty gay.
It is both ways.
It's homosexual
and it's gay as well.
I figured out the mental block
for real.
If something is
really long
but grabs me immediately
I can give it a chance.
If something doesn't
grab me immediately
but it's short and manageable
I can give it a chance.
Homestuck is both really long
and doesn't immediately grab me.
So that's just the two factors
right at once.
I know there's
some people say that it's
boring at the beginning and it only gets interesting
later when the trolls
or the time travel shit comes in.
I'm not saying that's what you think Jesse.
I don't think that's you.
A lot of people do say that.
For one totally disagree
I think Homestuck is
maybe not on the first page
but definitely within the first act.
It's really interesting.
I was also one of the people who
heard that
Victor read it before I did
and I just saw him reading it
and I'd never fucking heard of it at all.
So I saw him reading it
and
he was in Act 3
and he didn't really start enjoying it
until late into Act 3
and he was like I don't know
it doesn't really get good for a long time
and I was like I'll just read 5 pages
and if I'm not into it I'm not going to read it
because it's fucking long.
I read page 1 and I was like
this is the funniest thing I've ever read in my life
I'm going to read all of this.
It's funny right off the bat.
I don't know what people don't.
It's got its own sense of humor
that you have to adjust to a little bit.
It's funny but there's also a lot of these
long dialogue
that you have to scale.
Yeah but that's where the jokes are.
The way I got into Homestuck
is that I saw...
Jess is the only one of us who
reads books.
He's way more than all of us.
That's true.
What were you saying?
He was saying that.
I got into Homestuck because of
Sweet Bro and Hella Jeff.
Me too!
I saw that and I thought
the guy who made this was hilarious.
I got to read the main thing.
Dude, encourage me.
Shut up Nate!
Remember before the podcast started
when Nate was like I'm going to really try
not to cut anybody off.
I make tactical insertions
where I think people are going to stop.
The way that the rest of us do it
is someone starts talking
and we just wait for them to finish their point.
I can't afford to take that risk.
Sorry, go on Gib.
I forgot now.
You were saying you got into it through
Hella Jeff and Bro.
I didn't find
the very first act to be that as funny
but I kind of got it.
I feel like I would have
stuck through it anyway but
I don't know.
Me and my buddies
in college
we didn't even know Homestuck existed
but we read
all of Sweet Bro and Hella Jeff
thought it was the best thing ever
and had no idea about Homestuck.
I think until Ben showed me that Homestuck existed
and was a thing
and frankly I yearned for those days
before I knew.
I had seen Sweet Bro and Hella Jeff
I didn't really know.
I got into Sweet Bro through Homestuck
but the existence of Sweet Bro
and Hella Jeff is one of the best things
about Homestuck.
In the universe
there is this fucking
comic that exists
that one of the characters makes
and most of the
best memes in Homestuck
are not external memes
but are memes that were generated by the author
within this in-universe continuity
of Sweet Bro and Hella Jeff.
Reading the end recently
when Caliborn gets ripped
it was fantastic.
We've got Tom joining us.
Tom are you recording?
I am recording.
So
should we see Test right now?
I don't want to go too much into Homestuck
on account of
we I think will have a Homestuck
podcast at some point
once everyone finishes the story.
In all honesty
I'm so fucking tired of fighting
with you shitwits
so fucking I was fighting with these
dumb motherfuckers for like an hour
because they okay
you know what let's just get into this
I'm sick of holding it inside
We should get into this now because Jesse
isn't invited to the real Homestuck podcast
so this is the time to air his grievances
No this isn't about that he's about to talk about
lights about yellow
Oh fuck nevermind okay
These fucking guys they all fucking ganged up on me
it was like the people versus endless Jess
It wasn't ganging up on you
No no
No oh you were being aggressively wrong
every single one of you stupid idiots
objectively aggressively wrong
saying that my fucking video
looked yellow it does not look
yellow and you know what Jesse
I'm gonna post those fucking pictures
in the chat
I hope you do
You post those videos
and don't even say anything
don't say who did what and just say which one looks better
I dare you
Wait is the question which one looks better
or is it yellow
Okay well that too
Well nobody's
contesting which one looks better
I mean Nate might be because he has a personal opinion
There you go
I have also my own illustration that I put together
where I compare the individual
like pieces of Jesse's face
in almost all of his videos
like where it's got the um
the lighting that he has in almost all of his videos
versus
did we explain what the issue was
Jesse's videos he has a certain style of
lighting that all of us identify has
yellow lighting
but Jesse disagrees that it's yellow
lighting
even though I officially
I'm done
I thought we were gonna try to make these enraged Jesse less
It's just called incandescent lighting
I have an illustration of a visual
a graph that compares
like the actual colors
of his face and his beard
in that one scene
in one of his horseshoe reviews where he goes outside
and it's a totally different
less yellow color
I would even say that
Jesse's argument that
the color is normal
is also true
it is normal to live
in an incandescently
lit room because
most people have those type of light bulbs
it's just that the type of light that that is
is called yellow light
I don't disagree necessarily
that the lighting in that one
shot that I used of you being outside
is worse that might be true
you know because you just grabbed
the camera and talked out
I thought the outside shot looked way better
the outside shot looks like shit you're objectively
longer
the real issue is that
these people do not know what
yellow looks like they don't they literally
do not know what the color is
you don't fucking DeVoo proved that it's yellow
DeVoo proved himself wrong
these guys
they made images to try and
show me how wrong I was
and the images proved them wrong
and they can't accept it
in the video of you being outside
your face looks like pinkish grey
Jesse what the
that's not an argument you're just making
retarded noises
in the basement
your face looks like pitch yellow
what's up everybody did you bro here
feeling uh
existential having a smoke
drunk after the end of that
podcast thinking about
my philosophical take on the color yellow
you know this shirt is obviously
yellow the light
being cast on me is actually from a fluorescent
light from inside of the
from inside of the
garage here
I feel like my face
tone is pretty close to my shirt tone
and yet this is definitely blue
light but you can tell that's blue the sky
is definitely blue and I
look over here see now that looks white
the you can tell that the white
the light is white or blue
rather which is what white light
is considered yet when it's
shining on me
I don't really look
I don't really look white I look more
yellowy but I look over
here and behind me
I can see
what are clearly
more clearly off camera
than on yellow lights
in the distance you can't even see me now probably
because it's quite dark out
but I'm thinking about the street lights right
and how
like I would always think of a street light
as yellow
but what is yellow
as a concept like
I think we'd all agree this
the light on my cigarette is yellow
but does yellow
mean a color that an object
is
or can lighting be
yellow
we can agree that
a monitor represents things in colors
a camera captures
things in colors but does light
actually
emit
colors
a different thing
is the sky blue
is my shirt
my shirt is definitely yellow
but if I have a yellow light on me
am I
yellow
what does yellow mean
I don't know what yellow means anymore
I have lost track
of the meaning of yellow
I
I guess yellow
like most things means what we want it to mean
I don't know what the fuck I'm talking about
character with yellow skin
like that's what your face looks like
do you people at home
do you hear how these morons are ganging up on me
they're so fucking insecure about how wrong they are
they just can't accept it
do you think people are supposed to look like
I want to clarify
simpsons characters are not what real humans look like
we're not actually yellow in real life
you're saying my video looks like a simpsons character
you're that fucking stupid
you have to understand where I'm coming from
at least
three years of watching your videos
and in most of them being yellow
I think some of them are lit by other means
but most of your videos have been
yellow for all this time
and you know like
here's how dumb these people are
digi goes
look jesse I'll show you a picture from one of my videos
that also looks yellow
he shows me a picture
it also doesn't look yellow at all
so it's yellow lighting
it's what it's called
I don't care what it's called if it's wrong digi
it's objectively not yellow
by the way we've been having this argument for three fucking years
just so everyone knows
this is not the first time the yellowness
of jesse's videos has come into question
I don't know if you've been around for the last one
but this is like an ongoing battle
for all time longer than the homestuck
first of all you're mischaracterizing
this is not about the yellowness of my videos
plural because not all my videos
are professionally lighted and professionally made
most of my videos are like vlogs
I don't care about the lighting
any time that I put effort into the lighting
it looks beautiful it looks perfect
I think great if you don't disagree
with those two statements
I disagree
I don't think any jesse video has beautiful visuals
or lighting
that may be the true
but let's not even get into it
we can't get into jesse's yellow
lighting or at least ben can't
in fact we shouldn't even be on this topic
at all because it has nothing to do with the
topic of the podcast so let's just
move on alright no it does because
I can't get into the insane frame of
mind that you people are in
that you see yellow where there was no fucking yellow
I can't get into it
to format where you could talk about literally anything
to clarify what I just said
I only mean that I don't think that
you know like good like high quality
visuals are one of the things people come
to a jesse video like that's not something I would
say that like the jesse channel
no matter what you say jesse is not going to listen
it's not going to matter I'm not talking to jesse
oh my god and let's talk about that okay
because they can't handle that he's wrong so he could
sound this high horse about oh jesse just never listens
to criticism he can't handle he can't
handle my hardcore criticism
my construction I'm just saying that you get
angry when people criticize your shit
no no no I get angry when people criticize
it wrong I get angry with wrong
criticism because your criticism is objectively
not true I don't care if gibbons
playing guitar you can play your guitar
you can sing your little gay boy songs all you want
it's not going to stop me it's not going
to quell this fire it's not going to
put the fire out gibbons you can play all night
I don't care
it's not yellow it's not
it's not yellow
what's something you can't get into
I don't even understand
what are you protecting enough
oh this is my hill to die on
what are you people saying
it's not yellow
it is not
this isn't even like this has nothing to do
this is not me going like oh my videos
are great don't critique my videos
this has nothing to do with whether I think it looks good
or not
this is not black
it's not yellow they just
are yellow
we feel the same way
towards you about this issue like how can you
not see it
you guys are seeing that isn't there
you don't know what yellow is
I can show you a picture of the color yellow
and you look at it and go yep that's yellow
and then I show you my video
perfect the fact that it is not
like hashtag
FF0069
good job
it's not the issue
is that actually the yellow
is it
do you think it looks good
you said it like this
I wanted to make a shirt called
it's pitch white and the text is
I'm hashtag
fucking white
because that's the code
I get it
what's the bottom line is that I made a video
that looked fucking natural
and beautiful and Nate's like
oh I'll show you how yellow it is
and he like color corrected and makes an image
this looks so much worse
ok so this room
looks one way right
and this room looks another way
cause this room
is lit
with fluorescent light
no this one is incandescent light
and this one is fluorescent light
incandescent light
is referred to as
yellow or warm light
whereas
fluorescent light is referred to as
blue or white
light
so
this this room
it looks normal
this is what a normal room looks like
and
you could say
that it's technically not
like nothing in the room is yellow
the room is not yellow and even the light
isn't
technically yellow it's just that
it has more yellow values
like the values
in what is being presented through the monitor
I'm like look at my hand right now
like
yeah it is skin colored
my hand is skin colored
but it does look
different
in this light
it is still skin colored
but the lighting looks different
and the way that that lighting
is represented
by a computer monitor
is to use more
yellow values
whereas in here it's more white values
this is more white
this is more yellow values
this is more white values or blue
blue values rather is what I mean to say
yellow light
both are normal
both I would describe
as normal light
a lot of people think this kind of light
looks cleaner
and I do think this kind of light
is very appropriate for the videos of someone
like MKBHD where he's talking about technology
because it's a very pristine
look to it you can see more
detail in
in white light it's easier
to pick out every individual
you know
in yellow light
it's more of this homie
nostalgic feel
when you think yellow light
you think I am in a house
and I think that if the
concept of your video
is that I am in
a house
then yellow light is appropriate
because whenever I see white light
like I said it makes sense in an MKBHD video
because he's talking about technology
but I always feel like it doesn't look like a real place
it doesn't look like his room
it doesn't look like a place where a person lives
because no one lives in this
I would not be able to live in a room
that looked like this
so to me having a room be
oh god my food's done
you know what I'm saying
it doesn't matter if it looks worse
the point is it looks less yellow
which it does
my videos does not look yellow in the first place
so no it does not look less yellow
it just looks like a different color
because it's yellow
it's gotta be one color
which other color is it
I can't fucking believe
that you guys are all seeing yellow
there's no I'm fucking
my wig is blown off
which color is it if it isn't yellow
I'm losing my fucking mind here
it's not a color
you know what I just realized that I still have my flux on
so maybe that's why
I'm seeing all this yellow
I just have to turn off flux
what's the thing that you can't get into
um
I have a couple things
one of them I said is I can't get into going to concerts
oh
okay that's a good one
I agree with you but I'm still fucking pissed off
I feel the same Tom
could you give us any anecdotes
I mean I haven't even really gone
to like any like big concerts
but even just like small ones that I've gone with like friends
and shit
I enjoy listening to music
just and like kind of getting lost
in it and I feel like when I'm at a concert
there's like a bunch of fucking people that I hate
because I hate people
they're all around me and like people are like
fucking just like crowded together
and I mean it's fucking good
because like you're like fucking far away from a stage
and I don't know
the appeal of like oh it's the band
playing the music live I'm like I don't give a shit about the band
I give a shit about the music
so I
I'm the last concert I went to
was last year's BronyCon
I think that's the last time
and I mean that was cool and all
because it was a thing
but like now when I think about going to a concert
I think I would have to physically travel there
which is annoying I would have to buy a ticket
which is really annoying
and it would take
like my whole day or like my whole evening
which is like I just can't bear
I can't bear the bottom
let's call it what it is
what you're getting out of that
is these famous people
and you're going to you know socialize
and that's fine that's what you want to do
but that's what you're paying for really
and to hear songs that you may or may not like
when I go to concerts
it's usually because like my parents have taken me
or friends have taken me so I didn't have to pay
so in that way I'm just experiencing
it's the experience of like being in a huge
it's being in a huge stadium
the appeal that I find
is not necessarily that the music
is there because I can listen to it whenever
it's that it's just
being in a stadium is really cool
because it's all echoing really loud
and it is heard afterwards
the best concert I ever went to was
on my birthday
my buddy
Rich came up from New Jersey
is this relevant to the topic of not being able
to get into concerts at all
it is because I got into this girl
who I finger banged on the dance floor
you told the story already actually
did I?
I was able to get into it
Jesse why aren't you able to get into concerts
I want to hear everybody before I chime in
Jesse you still there
he killed himself he did
man that was a great joke that I could have made
oh there's this this girl
you know I'm just walking around
and there's so many things that are yellow
and none of them look like my video
I was waiting for it
no yellow thing
looks like my video
do you understand color?
it's not yellow it's a yellow tint sir
it's not even a tint
let's just categorically redefine
what yellow is so we can say the video
that's what you guys have been doing this whole time
Jesse if your lighting is yellow
there wouldn't everything in your room
be yellow by necessity
that's it that's it he can't see
yellow because he's been saturated
what the fuck
I told you there's so much thing
it's yellow lighting
there's a problem
in thinking about light in the way I'm describing
it's mostly philosophical
do we want to say
that light can be yellow
or do we want to say that this is what yellow is
I think if you were in defense
of yellow as a color
if you wanted to be a purist about what yellow is
then we shouldn't refer to yellow light
we should refer to incandescent
or fluorescent light
each of which does have its own meaning
and looks different however
not necessarily
a color
I don't know man
is it an insult to say that somebody's
video looks yellow
what world do we live in
what universe am I in
where the fuck am I
that we can even talk about this
why is this happening
why is this the world
does he notice the difference
or he would think it looks better when he has flux on
or I don't know
shut up I am not the crazy one here
you stupid motherfuckers
I am sick of being vilified
and treated like I'm the guy who's crazy here
I am not the one who's crazy
you are all crazy
when everyone else
everyone else in the world
is crazy
Jesse it's all
yes I am the only sane man
in a mad mad mad mad world
as we've clearly established multiple times
you have the history of this podcast
Jesse would you like to weigh in
to why you can't get into live shows
concerts
we have to make a yellow video
so that you can all see what a yellow video actually looks like
if that was gonna happen
who's got a thing a digi
I was gonna go in the opposite direction
I love concerts
I go to them all the time
for me it's
I guess because I grew up with them
my parents are big like metal heads and stuff
so I went to lots of metal shows in my teens
and it was always just about fucking destroying myself
and going ape shit
you know it's like
cause it's the loudest
that you could possibly listen to this music
and there's a bunch of other people
who are all into it too
and you're all just like
it's like an additional layer of
loud is better
isn't that like worse at a certain point
well yeah I mean
I think I definitely
I've been to a lot of shows
and there's definitely a huge gradient
of how much I enjoyed them
a lot of the time sound mixing is fucking terrible at shows
especially if you go to like a big
like a stadium type thing
usually there's
just not the best mixing of the audio
and wherever you're standing or sitting
you know
and the worst thing that can happen
is when you have a crowd who doesn't get the music
like going to
cause I know
Tom you're a big opeth fan
I've been to two opeth shows
and those guys
they perform perfectly
they sound exactly as good
live as they do on the album
they have perfect sound
and they'll play shows
but like the people who go to them
they have a crowd
and those people
are fucking wasted cause they're at a show
and so they'll be playing
like the heavy part of a song
for those who don't know opeth transitions
like frequently between heavy and calm parts in their songs
so they'll be playing a heavy part
and everyone's like yeah and they're all going crazy
and mashing and shit
but then they'll be like two minutes of soft
finger picked guitar
cause the average opeth songs like 10 to 15 minutes
so like transition back and forth
just kind of like doesn't really know what to do
cause they're all drunk and ready to fucking throw down
in a metal show and a lot of them are people who aren't necessarily
opeth fans just people who are dragged
by their friends and so
there'll always be a bunch of people talking
or people on their fucking like phones
and shit and it's like it's miserable
like it's such a good
performance that the band is putting on
but the crowd is so terrible at opeth shows
that it's like almost not worth it
you get a bunch of inflatable beds
and inflatable couches and just like
give everyone a bunch of weed
in the middle of each song
it seems like it really is important
that reminds me of my next thing
I can't get into
but the best shows I've been to
was it Lady Gaga
Lady Gaga was a fucking awesome show
and the best shows are the ones where the people
get it
and like everyone in the crowd seems to
like Lady Gaga the crowd is almost all gay people
and like almost all of them
cause I was down in the pit
it's all gay people who go to Lady Gaga
yeah
well no other than me and Victor were the only
straight guys there
we did not expect
that it was like I didn't know
what kind of crowd Lady Gaga pulls
so when I was there I was just like oh my god
it's all gay people and we're in the
the pit and everything and it slowly dawned on me
and then I looked down to myself and said
it's all gay people
well it slowly dawned on me
that everyone there
Lady Gaga really meant something to them
there's a part where
she had people throw
cause I guess she had some kind of fan club
and like a bunch of people took stuffed
animals and threw them on
stage at one point like I guess it was
something they knew was supposed to happen at this part in the show
and she like lays down on a couch and they throw
all these stuffed animals and they have letters attached
to them and she's like reading out these
letters from her fans about
the deep emotional connection how they
saved her from fucking
she saved them from suicide and all this shit
and she's like reading these letters and stuff
and I was like whoa this is like such a big deal
to the people at this show
but the best one I've ever been to cause I'm not
the biggest Lady Gaga fan it was a really
cool show but there's this band
Boris we talked about this in the
sleep podcast the band Boris with their
album flood they were doing
a tour where they were just playing flood
so like cause they have a lot of different
sounds they play stuff in all these different styles
but like it was touring for
that album which is a 15 year old
album and they were like we're doing a flood tour
so everyone who was there
knew exactly what they were in for it was
like a small dive bar in DC
everyone was a huge Boris
fan and we just fucking stood there
and like zoned out
to this like epic fucking
post rock song and I was
like just sitting there like with my eyes close
and I felt like literally like the ocean was
washing over me imagine
imagine if somehow it was in a
crowd where no one got it no one knew the song
it would be the worst performance ever
in terms of audience retention
why has it been ten minutes of
doom-boodly-dum-boom
oh no they didn't do that part
what's the point in that's the part
where you're supposed to fall asleep
to challenge yourself
there's like a lot of
they played a bunch of other songs
that weren't just flood
hold on here
for like two years I've known about
this concert you went to
you did a vlog about it when you first did it
and this whole time you said
Boris performs flood
and they just played flood
and now all of a sudden
more than two years afterwards you're saying
oh they didn't just play flood they didn't play all of flood
well my life is a lie
they cut off the first like ten minutes
and the last like
five to ten minutes of flood
so it's only about 45 minutes long
right so they cut off a lot of
the end in the beginning and so it was like
a 40 minute version of flood
and then they had played like five or six
of their dronier songs before that
okay that's cool but
Ben's got a thing to say right Ben
oh yes
D'Vu mentioned smoking weed
giving the crowd a bunch of weed and smoking weed
is something that I just cannot get into
hey you know by the way I was
asked did you ask me about what I thought about
concerts and then Jesse interrupted and I
never got back to what you think of concerts
and what sucks is that I had a really funny
line about how I've never been to a concert
because I live in a culturalist void
of humanity and it was going to be funny
but you've never been to like a country
christian no no just everyone around
is uncultured fucks
and it's ridiculous oh man yeah so
it's really weird I've performed a concert
in a church believe me D'Vu I know
what it's like to be surrounded by uncultured
fucks
anyways yeah alright Ben talk about
weed that dank 420
meme yeah yeah
can you get into the meme Ben can you
get into the meme at least
I hate the meme I've smoked it
I've smoked it a handful of times
you've smoked a handful of it
the sensation I've gotten from
a handful of times
and the sensation I've gotten from it has
been better or worse like sometimes I've
gotten weird and anxious and tingly and
felt really bad other times it's been
like relaxed and I've gotten in a very meditative
state and it's been okay fine
fair enough but like
God when the people around me
smoke it these days
these days I just have no patience for like
altered states of mind I want to be
focused all the time
any time I'm honestly any time
I'm not sitting on my computer either
working on drawing or
like trying to get myself to work on
drawing I'm in physical pain
because I should be doing I should not be doing
anything else nothing else is of any value
so when when someone is like
hey I'm gonna smoke weed
then they smoke weed and I try to be cool
about it but I'm just like I'm looking
at them like you sad motherfucker
this is what you want to spend your time doing
this is how you want your life
this is how you want this evening to go for you
and someone offers it to me I'm like haha
no thanks but in my mind I'm like
you mother for how do you know what Ben I
you're trying to say fucking I know
exactly how you feel because
every fucking party at some point someone
pulls out the doobie
and they all start and
just like you said I'm like
I'm like no thanks I don't want any
like I'm polite about it
but in my head I'm going I want
all of you to fucking die
how why don't you just hand me a gun
and say hey would you like to shoot yourself
with it I mean we know
what happens we know it goes down
I mean I mean I'm not saying it's
gonna kill you or anything I'm just saying that
like it's not a good thing to do
you know I mean I don't
I mean you gain pretty much nothing
I mean maybe stress relief I guess
you know I guess it's just
it's just a fucking juvenile thing for people
who have no fucking creativity
or no fucking ability
to entertain themselves and have an
actual conversation here's the line
thank you Jesse it's juvenile is fun
well think about this think about it this way
you know one of the best defenses people have for weeds
is that it helps soothe the pain
you have a terrible disease well what's your disease
well that's the second disease that you have
my disease is being
a man in the 21st century
I mean I mean
in this matri whatever
I don't want to go too hard
against it because like
I could make the same argument against any
recreational activity oh why are you
watching that movie that doesn't accomplish anything
you know that's stupid that's juvenile
like I get it you know if you enjoy
it fair enough but for me it's like
Jesse do you think you're going to have a good time
speaking and once you do it like
you're trapped in it like once you're high you're trapped
you have to be high for a while I hate that
yeah that's the scariest part by the way did I
ever tell you guys about the time I was physically
trapped like I got really high with
a couple people I barely knew and had one of them
had given me a ride that was
fallen to a bear trap
were you suing it for me did they stuff you
in the trunk of their car and drive you to a cliff
well okay really quick so me and
some friends I had met when I was working at Best Buy
a couple years ago I met this guy Aaron
he was okay we were hanging out one time and like
when I go over to his house to hang out the first time
he's like we're going to go drive to my
other friend's house he's like the coolest
guy in the world and so we go and we
drive out to that house oh my god this was
this was a terrible yeah it's this story it was
a terrible idea oh my god
so we go tell this alright we go all
the way out to his house which was like fucking
half an hour away and so now I'm trapped
he gave me the ride I can't
leave until he you know takes me away
so you know I'd smoked weed a couple
times before this just had a little bit
of experience and it had been hit or miss
up to this point so I meet this guy
you know I fuck it I'll go all out I'll
tell you all the details so we pull up to this guy's house
please please don't tell us all the details
please condense yeah all right I'm already
sick of this story you're like how old
for me the pooh you know what you know what
fuck it I mean you guys don't deserve to hear
this fucking story the point is okay good
I'm gonna I gotta think
I gotta sing no it's a good story you just
suck at telling it is I want to hear story
wait let's have Ben tell the story
Ben can't tell this fucking story doesn't
know anything I don't remember
all the details I mean you were there
and you did you get hired to just they
get okay the point is the guy that we
went to meet turned out he was he hyped
him up like this god among men and he
was a complete disgusting piece of shit
who this guy was obviously blind to like
a certain person I know can't see a
certain color this guy can't see how
shitty he is in real life you know sort of
like that like it what did this guy say
was cool about him well okay they had a
YouTube channel and I hadn't seen any
other content but at this point having a
YouTube channel was really impressive to
me and like I don't know he was just a
cool guy and he kept telling me how amazing
this guy was with a creative genius he was
and you know things of this nature but
anyway I meet him he's like I walk into
his room he's this fat fucking stoner
wearing no pants just like smoking from
a fucking he had like a vape bag sort of
thing and was just like he's just like
what's up guys and like his walls were
plastered with like heavy metal posters
that were just like covered in shit this
room was disgusting and the point is
there was nothing like what I'd been led
to expect and the point is we sit down
there's nothing to do so we all just get
high and I and once I get high I
immediately realize I go into panic mode
that oh my god I'm trapped here there's no
fucking escape what am I going to do so
eventually I just they started showing me
their videos was a fucking nightmare I
just eventually call I text everyone I
know in my phone but what were the videos
like um were they yellow remember I've
looked where they to know why are you
making him give more detail in the
story I don't know that was an
interesting point he described to me one
time and like they were really embarrassed
we had to watch these videos they were so
yellow I couldn't take it all right
the videos were in fact like because of
the context where I've been hyped up
that they've done all this awesome shit
and they were such amazing creative
individuals when they showed me the
videos it was a fucking nightmare it was
like and I was super high by this point
and I did like when I was I don't I what
I did was I looked around I looked at
these people who had nothing going on
their lives this is what they do with
their life and I think to myself this
is how I'm spending my life right now
hanging out with these people and I'm
trapped here I feel with everybody yeah
it's on this fucking planet right so the
point is I panic especially on this
podcast I texted literally everyone in
my phone like please call me immediately
that's what I texted to everyone in all
caps yeah like I start getting calls
from all my contacts on my phone because
my plan was I'll have someone call me
pretend there's an emergency and then
like force him to take me home
immediately as to get out here without
you know like saying anything weird so
like I keep getting calls and like I'm
pretending I'm on the phone with my mom
right now while I get another call
because I wasn't actually on the phone
because I just hung up on people because
I didn't actually want to talk to any of
them I was high as fuck dude I was high as
fuck it was a total cluster fuck and so
like I'm like guys I have to go my
sister like needs a ride to the airport
I have to leave now something like that
and the guys like oh dude we're we're
pretty fucked up though like we should
probably chill out for a little while
I was like okay I can survive and yeah
I survived for the half an hour we went
home got the fuck out of there it was the
worst experience in my life the point is
the weed made me super terrified super
paranoid was horrible don't do it yeah
man don't do it it has given me very
anxiety yeah that the anxiety is the word
it sometimes makes me feel really bad
I don't do it give go okay I have a
really good give boo
tangentially related to weed is alcohol
and that is a thing that I can't get into
sure because yeah everything I said
we just now also applies to out yeah
there's specifically getting wasted I've
been wasted like three times the first
time I was sick the second time it was
pretty cool but the third time I was so
sick so hungover that I I swore I would
never drink again I have drinking again
none of you guys have never gotten that
drink I've had my ups and downs with booze
but these days I've sort of settled into
a comfortable sort of I'll drink rarely
just to I don't know because I have a
silo every so often yeah and maybe a
glass of wine but I don't want to get
cups deep into my box wine right now
since we started the podcast I've met
three cups of wine I've like tried but
I just I don't like having my senses
dulled because I yeah yeah just
because I'm just I'm naturally anxious
so when I like oh my god everything
spinning oh yeah and then I'm just like
what the fuck like well I kind of like
being buzzed I'm just like it's hard to
get into drinking when there's not a
reason to it it feels good to be a
little bit buzz and to be a little bit
drunk like it is like relaxing and it
kind of can be fun but yeah before I get
there the thought of getting there makes
me anxious and I'm like I don't want to
I don't want to dull my senses I don't
think I'd ever get into alcohol as much as
digi well yeah I mean it's really like
like a it's like a practice thing for
comfort like I mean if you know how much
alcohol you can handle you can pretty
easily make sure you don't get to the
point where you're gonna fucking lose
your faculties and throw up yeah I know
exactly how many cups of wine I can have
before like I know how many it'll take
before it's a I feel like I can't drive
and then I know how many more it'll take
before I feel like I can do anything in
the world and that's where I need to stop
and if I go any further that it gets into
the I'm gonna feel this all fucking night
and I'm not gonna be able to do anything
so at Baronecon that last night where
we were all drinking for the show I
didn't really drink that much because I
didn't want to get sick you know in another
country smart but at the at the same time
I felt bad because I wasn't as crazy as
everyone else I was just sort of normal
I think I was like another thing you know
from everybody I was having had one drink
that night so we were wasted I remember
getting I really hate every part of like
the getting drunk process mm-hmm like I
hate the taste I hate putting it inside
me I hate fucking getting there I hate
being drunk I hate feeling the beginning
hungover I don't usually get hungover but
I hate it when it happens enough to make
up for all the times I don't but like the
only time that I actually drink a lot is
when I specifically want to turn into a
monster mm-hmm it's it's like it's like
the Mr. Hyde it's your doctor I was just
gonna say Dr. Jerry Mr. Hyde like I got
to let this monster out somehow or else
it's gonna eat me up from the inside
something has to happen tonight you know
my least favorite part of the whole
process is definitely the morning after
because oftentimes specifically when I
was in Japan me and my buddy Garoff would
go to the red light district and just
fucking party all night and get super
wasted beforehand and just be fucking
monsters and then the next day it would
just completely destroy my next day
because of how much I drank and how
irresponsibly we did it and I didn't
know anything about how to do it right at
the time you know well hangovers are a
well-documented phenomenon I know you know
it's funny to mitigate it though as did
you can tell you funny because the last
time that I got drunk
I got I drank an entire bottle of rum
I recorded a whole album that will never
see the light of day because it needs to
be destroyed it must never be seen or
heard by anyone I thought it was good
though you said it was good it's good
no it's but the world's not ready for
this kind of good yeah yeah exactly the
world isn't ready for it I have it can
you just give it to me and I'll just like
keep it around you can listen to it but
I'm not ready for the world to hear it
yeah okay but I just I feel like I want
it for myself because I hyped myself
after the podcast over it yeah the
name the album yellow the world's not
ready oh shit the world's not ready
yeah the album art is actually yellow
it's sure because you know it's funny
that uh you know you want to dwell on that
even though the conversation is over and
I've won the debate I guess you just
so insecure about how thoroughly I've
trounced you in this objective fucking
debate you can't handle the fact that I
am objectively smarter than everyone in
this chat combined that's so you're
bringing it up again out of thin air for
no reason you just want to keep harping
on it because you can't take it you can't
handle people are fucking colorblind
that you see colors that are not there
you see yellow but you know I was going
to tell a funny story about the color
yellow I'm not going to tell it now I'm
just going to let it go we lost out on the yellow story
that'd be in the case because you want to
talk about made-up yellow stories I mean
his yellow story is probably not going to
be very good anyway so oh shit yeah it
was I got a I got I haven't done one of
these things right right yeah I've been
letting you guys the point is I was
puking up stomach acid and it was yellow
oh holy shit that does sound like a great
story um is did you the last one that
hasn't I think yes we've gone through
some of you twice I haven't done any
is that true I have a third one oh David
you haven't done one hey I have plenty I
got a whole list baby I've got a list too
yeah I think this is one that probably
was obvious because I'm sure I've
mentioned it before and do you will
definitely know I've talked about this
but country music and also I'm going in
classical music both of them I see I
have heard well yeah well the thing
about country music and I talked about
this on an old podcast that like this
for me to enjoy something that's like
country ish like country influenced like
it becomes enjoyable to me at exactly
the moment it stops being country like
there's a lot of artists who are like
folk who are like country folk who I
like or like maybe you know have some
country aspects but as soon as it's like
country I can't take the voices I can't
take the southern accents like the and
the the mixing where it's usually like
very prominent vocals with these thick
southern accents going like honka-tonk
won't it don't fair you know like
because I mean I was my mom like
despises country music to an extent
that if she hears it for 10 seconds she'll
like flip shit and so like I grew up with
it like very ingrained in my mind that
country was the devil like never listen
to it it's the worst thing in the world
you know so like I have like this knee
jerk reaction to like a country accent
that's immediately like nope you know I
have that yeah for like just because
it's a terrible voice like the way that
they not the country accent but the
country music voice that y'all doing on
the same on the fall on the planet
well I mean I get I get that for people
who come up in a place where people talk
like that I guarantee you I would be
annoyed by it if I had a country accent
more than I do I would hate it I grew up
in Yankee country in Massachusetts and
there's a little bit of and I wasn't
really supposed to much of this at all
growing up but over the years I found a
couple of things that I'm into like like
like mr. Conway twitty I see the
sparkling little diamond in your hand
now he's great he's great you know this
when you guys watch Pokemon does Pikachu
just blend into the background for you
since everything you know you look up at
the sky do you see blue is there any
other colors up there I want to finish
this fucking country point of this you
know there's certain songs like everybody
loves Johnny Cash right he's like the
he's like the hips like if you're a
music hipster guy everyone says no
country but Johnny Cash yeah yeah he's
a country guy who's very acceptable to
like you know there's been a the needle
drops on a classic album review of one
of his things he's a you know he's popular
in the circuits of people who like music
people who ordinarily wouldn't like
country at all yeah and I've heard some
Johnny Cash songs I thought were kind of
okay I think he has a cool voice I like
his cover of Hurt by Nine Inch Nails
but like I can't get into even Johnny
Cash like I can't listen to a whole album
of his stuff because it's just like it's
just too country you know it's not that
country anyway like he's more even he
is more like blues folk rock pop fusion
like I mean that's what country there's
a large infusion of retardation and
very incestuous country yeah I've heard
some outlaw country where sometimes the
music's not that bad but I just can't
deal with the voice I've heard my ex
girlfriend was a huge country music
person like she grew up with it and all
she listened to was country and country
rock and shit and and well not only but
well did you the thingy terrible taste
in music but she played me this this
this album those like the soundtrack to
this show Nashville which is like a show
about musicians and like I actually
thought a lot of the songs on that
soundtrack were pretty okay but they were
all like folk country like they weren't
really country songs and the ones that
were country songs were terrible and it's
like this is this is really what I feel
is like the heart of what I wish this
podcast were and it isn't quite it's
because Ben will say something like I
can't get into this except when I can and
even like hippo is like I can't get into
drinking except that one time where I did
like it you see the point you made it
back in that very old podcast was that
as soon as a country song becomes good
to you it's also become something beyond
just country the definition of country
like what makes country its own thing
that makes it unique from everything
else is something that you do not like
like it like it is something that is
inherently shitty to you and for me that
is the ultimate in of an example of
something you just can't get into right
yeah I mean there's I don't want no
hand out living I don't want a part
anything they're giving I'm proud
even I got a song even trying to do a
country voice like immediately makes me
feel like the song must be bad you know
and I said a few things and I'll admit it
if you want to get ahead you got a hump
and get it I'm a white boy looking for
a place to do my thing
I won't say that I've never heard a
country song that I liked at all but
I've never heard one that I was like
returning to regularly you know it's
it's a hard genre and then also I really
I really resonate with I'm a white boy
by Merle Haggard
I also want to throw in classical because
I can't get into that either and like
classical at least I can appreciate the
compositions and be like yeah that's
that I mean I understand the emotions
that that's supposed to evoke but I don't
like the sound of classical instruments
it's soundtrack music so of course you
know it's like it's not necessarily
something you can get into as much and
we're not talking like a song that plays
in a movie we're talking the background
music that's going on during a scene and
it's like you'll have a scene of a guy
not classical classical like Mozart wasn't
a backing track you're thinking of
orchestral it's different than yeah
no is it most classical music like set to
certain plays no I'm pretty sure about
that they wrote them to be stories in and
of themselves yeah Beethoven and Mozart
and fucking what's this fuck are none of
them are well you know I don't think
anybody actually listens to classical
music everyone just says they do
wait a second how many of you know I know
some of the dais like half that movie is
like people playing classical music and
there's a play going on to it and he's
posing it for the play what's going on if
I've been lied to I'm a dais is the
greatest musical I mean movie of all
time some things yeah well a lot of it is
like that like whether or not it's
not about whether or not it's soundtrack
music I just don't like the sound of the
instruments I don't like classical
instruments I don't like orchestral
music at all that's right I know
orchestral music that's way too broad a
category all of the people I know who are
into that kind of stuff are like only
into that stuff like it's all people who
like play classical instruments and are
only into those that kind of me know I
don't like any orchestral music with that
is very few exceptions I don't believe
a couple of anime soundtracks I think are
pretty yellow is the best classical sound
but it's a rock and roll sort of guy
thing what yellow electric like
electric light or orchestra oh yeah
okay but they're like a electronic
they're got like no that they're
electronic slash classical right but as
soon as you put electronic elements in
there it's no longer just or well you
said you didn't like the sound of the
instruments well I mean I don't like them
like I love the violin I think the
violin sounds great in the background
of a rock or pop song like I don't want
to just listen to a violin unless it's
like a like one exception being like the
opening song on Agilosh do you like
you're lying April did you go well
first of all I dropped that show after
one episode there you go garbage
you didn't get to the music okay just
checking yeah um no I I mean I watched
all of or most of no dime a cantabile
and like I appreciate the musical
performances they're well directed and
they're good they are good pieces of
music I would never listen to them of my
own accord like I've tried countless
times to put on like you know everyone
loves Moonlight Sonata right that's
everybody's intro to classical song and
I put it on I feel nothing you know it's
okay I'm like I don't think yeah
whatever all right fine I accept that
you don't like it fair enough I just
want to say that the idea that like a
lot of the things we're saying like we
we can't get into them except that one
time I think that's mainly because like
we're all basically quite open-minded
and that we can enjoy we can get into a
lot of things in a small way yeah I
object to your objection to do that makes
perfect sense it wasn't an objection it
was just like an observation that we're
all talking about things that we like
once but most of the time not I mean like
I don't come I don't hate everything
about Dungeons and Dragons like there
are parts of it that I think are fun and
cool it's just that I think on the whole
the experience of it is generally well
as long as we're clarifying previous
things we've said and as long as we're
airing our grievances I want to go back
to the yellow thing for justice just a
minute I'd rather you go back to the
hope stuff because now what are we
going to do
you muting me doesn't have anything to
do how do you how does you muting Jesse
doesn't really help
go on Jesse
I still hear Jesse
someone for yourself I didn't know that's how that worked
yeah you dumbass you fucking
idiot
wait a minute wait a minute wait a minute
no don't finish your point I want to hear what
makes you think that you have authority over
who mutes Jesse anyway first of all
that you think that you can do that is stupid
and that you think the perfectly rational reason
for thinking that alright there's two reasons
first of all when I muted you for a second
ago there was a mute symbol next to you
that's identical to what it looks like
if someone mutes themself second of all
I gave everyone
I gave everyone here like absolute moderator
admin powers and I'm the one who owns
the chat oh I never accepted
them okay stop trying to
we're talking about yellow here let me defend myself
you ripped on me for not knowing
why I can delete anyone's
comments we can all delete one another's sentences
just fucking sit down
shut up Jesse I'm going to tell you
I can delete anyone's messages
and anyone can so I thought it seemed
very likely that I can use someone else
okay Davoo you make that
Davoo we weren't bashing on you for
Jesse was
it's the fact that you thought
that you were allowed to do that
the light blue is quite uniform
it's orange
it's not quite yellow
it is kind of yellow
okay I just wanted to clarify
for everybody because I said before
that the issue was not
whether or not my video looks
good the issue is that whether or not it looks
yellow see there's actually two issues
there they're both separately on their own
they're both very valid issues that I
that I take grievance with
first of all it doesn't look yellow it's not yellow at all
but I didn't mean to imply
that the other issue is not important
the video absolutely looks beautiful
that fucking Christmas video
it looks gorgeous it looks beautiful
I don't know what the hell you think
there is no Jesse video I would describe
as gorgeous I don't know what you think
gorgeous is then I don't know what you think
gorgeous is then because my videos
you know I'm the best fucking director
I'm the best at fucking framing a scene
setting up a shot hey if you want to see something
gorgeous why don't you head on over to
saintcomics.com and have a look at some of my
fucking bullshit my camera is HD
okay you're all giving me shit like my camera quality
now you know once I beat you in one
subject you jump ship to the next subject
and try to start a whole new thing
my camera quality is great
that's not true Tom and I both brought it up
okay so I was
right about the yellow it's not yellow I was right about
how beautiful my videos look they are beautiful
I was right about the camera quality
my camera is great so you guys are just fucking wrong
about everything and every time I catch you
in the act of being wrong you jump ship
to something else
just to clarify what you're doing right now
is you're just grabbing other arguments and attaching
them to your main one as to give it more
validity no no these are all separate arguments
that I'm right each one by themselves
alright well Jesse you're right about everything
DeVue what the fuck
no no no no see see see that's another
that's another sick tactic that you people use
okay you try to brush me off
there's no way out there's no way out of this conversation
what answer would you like
Jesse I would like you all to do
what answer could you possibly want
sorry, I catch this
there's no exit
Rollin, rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollin rollink saja
DeVue what the fuck
raisins I've never been able to
Okay, look, here it is. Here's the thing about raisins, right?
I think the taste of raisins...
I think the taste of raisins is all right.
Do you like grapes? Do you like grapes?
This just shut up, Nate.
First of all, Nate, I know what you said about grapes.
I can also like...
I know what you said about grapes.
I also like orange juice,
but I don't like rotten orange juice
that's been out in the sun for five days.
So here's the thing about raisins, right?
The taste is so-so.
I suppose orange juice is yellow, too, right?
Sometimes.
Is that why it's called fucking yellow juice?
I'm...
I'm starting to get on board with this banning Jesse idea.
Like, raisins are like...
Good! I hope you ban me!
I hope you all ban me! This is my hill to die on!
Go on, DeVoe.
Keep power through. I'll never let this go.
All right.
I kicked him out of the call, so...
Oh, you... you don't like...
He said he's never gonna give up,
and we have to finish the podcast.
Uh...
I care more about his hilarious argument
than I do about your taste of raisins.
That was a little bit... much.
Is he not even in this chat anymore?
Oh, man. You really stepped over the fucking line.
What did you do?
I thought I was just gonna kick him out of the call.
I didn't kick him out of the group.
You clearly don't know anything about the rules
in the fucking thing.
I'm not the one who derailed this podcast five times.
You are the one who completely...
Dude?
No, I'm honestly glad that he's gone,
but I still wouldn't kick him.
I have to figure out how to get him back in here now.
Oh, my God.
This is not good.
Uh, fuck.
These fucking raisins are tearing us apart!
Like, okay, we're gonna need to get
constantly shouting,
where the fuck is the end right now?
Stop talking about this.
I take action to solve that problem,
and everyone thinks it's weird.
Our friendship is shriveling under the hot yellow sun.
Yeah, well, here's...
Does anyone have an invite link for this shit?
I got it. I got the link. I'm trying to find...
Yeah, I have...
You should still be friends with him,
or if you go to, like, the top direct messages.
But now all we're gonna be talking about
is how I kicked him out.
And again, I thought I was just kicking him out of the call.
We can cut it, dude. We can cut it. It's not a big deal.
No, we can't. It's funny.
This is pretty funny, honestly.
I want him to be able to listen to this.
Oh, man.
Jesse, if you're listening to this, I'm sorry, dude.
As soon as he enters the call,
all he's gonna talk about is me kicking him.
Here's my...
I think that Jesse was going way too hard
on this yellow thing, but I also think
that this is like...
Yeah, I wouldn't... I mean, I don't know.
I'm a centrist.
Sure, fine.
You realize...
Jesse, I didn't realize I was gonna kick you out of the chat.
Right? You realize the mistake
that you just made.
You have just made this fire
so much worse
than you ever could have imagined.
When you beat Jesse to low on HP,
he only comes back stronger.
Yeah, it's like final fantasy 8.
You realize...
that it is now my mission to derail
every podcast with the subject
until the end of time.
All you had to do, DeVoo, was just move Jesse
to the other voice channel.
It would have had the same effect.
You guys just aren't happy
with any actual executive action
taking to fix this problem.
Because this crusade is over...
Because this is all a funny act thing.
It's hilarious that we're
derailing the podcast and arguing about yellow.
It's the funniest thing in the world.
Now, if we don't...
Where do you draw the line here?
I was getting pretty tired, honestly.
Kicking him was hilarious,
but it's also hilarious because it was incompetent.
It's not yet begun to become tired, Ben.
It's not yet begun
to become tired.
You people are going to
beg me for mercy by the time
this is done.
I will keep this going for months.
I'll keep this going for years
if I have to. By the time I'm through
with you, you will
beg. You will weep.
You will...
You will beg me to accept
that it's not yellow.
Do you understand?
You will be like Theon Greyjoy.
Please cut my finger off.
Please cut it off, Ramsay.
Like Theon fucking Greyjoy.
Just cut it off.
I'm mostly...
At this point, I'm also mostly laughing
at the thought that DeVu
was so
campaigning to make Jesse be quiet.
It kicked him out so that he could talk about
racism.
It's not true.
You guys were constantly telling him
to shut up.
You just created your own monster, DeVu.
You just created a nightmare.
Turn into a mural on the Sistine Chapel.
This event, you know, should be immortalized.
I was going to do it regardless of who needed to talk at the moment.
It was like the fourth time we derailed it.
It wasn't because of me at all.
Do you know what it feels like
to be betrayed, to be abandoned
by your friends, to be kicked out to the curb?
To DeVu.
Do you know
the rage
that you were exhuming a man?
Oh no!
You're finally free.
You know what it's like to leave the Bork, don't you?
That's a death sentence right there.
Yeah, no, Jesse finally had sweet escape
and as soon as I gave him a
leash back in, he immediately jumped on it.
He was like,
put me back in for another round.
For what it's worth,
I kind of want to hear why DeVu can't get into me too.
Me too. Me too?
We have this ten minute delay between me actually explaining it.
The texture is gross.
It feels like I'm eating a bug. That's it!
That's all I had to say.
I like raisins,
they're sweet, and that's it.
I don't like them in muffins, they're annoying.
They taste like candy.
I don't like candy, I just like
the majority of candy my entire life.
I guess I should have said that.
Why didn't you bring that up?
You know what I was thinking,
this whole podcast, I know that
all the things I can't get into
for real, I'm not even going to be able to think about them
because I just haven't even
thought about them in so long.
But yeah, candy, as a kid,
and I like slightly more candy
as an adult than as a kid.
Just almost all of them.
I can only think of some candy I can tolerate
with a laughing taffy.
Do you like sweet food in general?
Yeah, totally, just candy is disgusting.
I have friends who just don't like sweet food,
so I was just wondering.
What do you mean when you say candy?
Candy is very specific.
Like anything you'd buy at a candy store.
Because we call them sweets in general.
Candy is a specific thing.
Like a Reese's or a chocolate bar,
or like a...
Well here, to go into like
anything sweet,
I can kind of like.
The fact that it is candy is the biggest detriment
against liking it, you see.
For example, one candy bar I do kind of like
is Take Five. I don't even know if that's still in production.
It's called Take Five.
It's got stuff in it that I like.
But the fact that it's this tiny
really processed
with tons of preservatives thing
makes it vastly inferior
to just getting some pretzels and chocolate
and peanut butter and layering that
and putting that in an oven. That would be vastly preferable.
The opposite. I like everything
more when it's processed.
I've come to realize, I can't home make any snacks
that don't taste good.
To make it, you should experiment with the cooking.
It's the best. Feels great, tastes great.
You're trying to recreate candy bars
at home. It never works.
That's true.
How would you recreate a chocolate bar?
Chocolate melts in general.
And then you unmelt it.
Hershey's chocolate.
Hershey's chocolate just tastes like it came out of a can.
Hershey's chocolate is pretty gross.
I've heard of Hershey's just
in like
Hershey's
chocolate kisses are just like disgusting
for some reason.
M&M's
are hell on earth.
I just can't stand M&M's or the grossest thing
because they also feel like I'm eating a bug
because they got that shell that feels like
the exterior of a bug.
I love M&M's.
That's all this conversation is doing for me right now.
Well see
here's the depressing part for me.
I grew up loving candy
especially Reese's
and as I grew older
taste wise I could
eat more candies.
The stuff I didn't like when I was a kid
like almonds or stuff like that, I don't care.
Any candy, it tastes good.
But I take one
fucking bite of candy
and not only do all of my teeth hurt
but I can't drink anything afterwards
and my mouth tastes like sugar
and it just ruins my whole fucking throat.
As soon as I take a bite of candy
I want to die immediately.
You should get some work done on those teeth dude.
Every once in a while
I'll go to the supermarket
and buy an entire box of
gushes and then open a pack
and just scoop the entire pack
and scoop the whole pack of gushes into my mouth.
And then do the same thing
and then do the same thing with every other pack
in the box.
Pack a box of gushes in my mouth
and just let the gooey juice
just squeeze so much.
Did you guys ever turn
fruit by the foot into just a jawbreaker?
Hell yeah!
Dude, I would squeeze it into a thing.
Any of those fruit by the foot or like the
fruit roll-ups I would just mash them into a ball
and take little junk bites out of it.
I eat them and that's tasty
but I just feels wrong
after I ate it.
Well they are wrong, I love it.
As a kid as well.
Why did I eat that?
That wasn't like a satisfying experience
overall.
For me it's not about satisfaction
it's about physical pain.
All of my teeth will scream at me.
I have a filling in every tooth in my mouth
and they don't take kindly to that shit.
It's sad.
It's really sad because
as an adult I can afford as much candy as I want.
I can go to the store and just buy all of them
if I wanted to and it will mean nothing to me.
I kind of get the same thing.
For some reason lately
chocolate has been making my teeth.
I think I probably just have a cavity.
There is a way to get
chocolate that I enjoy
which is bags of chocolate chips
and you just do something with that.
That's just a Hershey kiss but smaller!
The thing though, the thing about that
is that that's
literally not true at all.
It's a completely different taste.
When I think of chocolate
the taste of chocolate chips is exactly what
even if it's Hershey's
chocolate chips is not as milky.
It's a totally different taste.
It's way better of course.
I don't know how this works
but if you put chocolate chips into cookies
and then you bake the cookies so the chocolate chips are melted
but then they get unmelted because the cookies
cool off
the chocolate tastes a million times better
now that it's been infused with the cookie.
I do like sweet things and bakery and stuff
but anything that comes out of a wrapper
is just inherently gross.
That's interesting.
Now you can get into that.
If that's wrapped it up
I wait
I have one more thing
I don't know if I should bring it up.
I was planning to wrap the whole podcast.
I just want to move on to the next one.
I have like one other thing.
I have a book for like three hours
I have so many topics left over
since I was
since I was on ceremony
Let me do mine.
I really hope that this is not off base
for the tone of the podcast
but the thing that I cannot get into
is the gender non-binary.
Okay.
And when I say that
it probably sounds like I'm antsy.
You can't get into it because you
tried on the dress
and it just wasn't working for you.
When I say that I can't get into that
it probably sounds like I'm transphobic
or something. I'm not.
I respect people's right
to be treated the way they want
and to express themselves the way they want
and I wouldn't tell anyone that they can't do
I'm transphobic. I hate trans people.
I hate them all.
But there is this idea
that some people have
in like that community
and like when they try to express what it is
about being like non-cis or trans
they'll say like
I am a woman on the inside
like spiritually I am a woman
like I am biologically
a man but I feel like a woman
and I don't know what that means
and I don't think they know
either because I don't think
there is any specific feeling
like being a man or being a woman
I think that is
what they probably mean is that I want
to look and act this way
and I think that's fair but when they kind of put this
weird sort of almost mystical twist on it
like it's what it is inside me
I have to be like that doesn't mean
well hang on Ben let me ask one
I really think that the whole issue
honestly comes down to
definitions and words
I really think in my heart of heart
that it is at its core a semantical issue
of how you define the word gender
possible
and therefore because it is a semantic issue
I find the whole thing kind of boring
and pointless
hang on I've got a really important thing to ask about that
because I have heard something that might
be an issue with that now I'm pretty much with you
on all that but I have heard when I've been
you know reading about this stuff
I have heard that there is an argument
that there is a real biological difference
between the male and female brain
and some people contend that they have
the wrong brain for what
their you know like their body is
now I have not really looked into it but I've heard
that it's legit a little bit maybe
I think that that claim
I mean I don't know the studies
I haven't read the studies but I think that on an
individual basis that claim
I have the wrong brain is impossible
to back up
what I think is that even if it were the case
even is even your brain
the definition like imagine if someone had
imagine if a white guy had like
the kind of nose that
black people tend to have a little bit more often
would you say I have a black nose or would you just say
that
necessarily the black nose
you would have to research what if there was a difference between
necessarily the female brain
if one male person can have the same patterns
as that female brain
then is it necessarily the female brain
you know that's what it is
what it is
what it is about the brain
thing is that it's
the average so the male average
brain acts in a certain way
okay I'm with you on that
there's actually three genders
Pinky Elmira and the brain
okay
okay hold on
I've got one thing to say about this first
the last thing you said was an important thing
what's this one now
get it all out at once
okay because Ben said that such a thing is
unquantifiable but because it is
unquantifiable I say it is impossible to back up
on an individual if that's the case
then don't we kind of have to take their word for it
when they say that
I didn't say we shouldn't
no look okay
but let me say my thing I think you would do
because I'm
part way with you on this but for me
I am not into
labels at all
I think the problem is
I think the problem is people making a big deal
out of being male or female
or any gender just be you
you guys know about gloom gender
just be whatever you are
and it doesn't need a name
it doesn't need a title you don't have to make it
a thing just be you
and if you want to act
a way that does not
match up with what your genitals are
then just act that way
there is a strange
dichotomy in the thinking
of trans allies
and the lgdb community
which I cannot wrap my head around
and the duality is that on the one hand
they say that gender
is merely performative
they define gender to be merely performative
and a social construct fair enough
on the other hand they then
you know they have
you know they want to they choose one
or the other like I am this
I identify as this but if it is a social construct
and a performative thing
why must you then
why must you then slot into one
that is an excellent point Ben I have yet to hear a defense of that
my whole thing
with definitions and names and boundaries
of where the words begin and end is
what's the most useful
because like I understand
it doesn't matter what's useful or not
people will come up with whatever they want
when you think about stuff like
gay, straight, bi or asexual
I feel like
which sexuality you have
you can sort of at least round it up
it's a better example to make my point
that you can round it up
or round it down into one of those four
and those terms are useful
if say you are at a party
or a bar or whatever and someone wants to know
whether or not they can hit on you or something like that
fuck that
just tell them individually
I am or am not attracted to you
it doesn't have to be I'm bi
or I'm gay or I'm straight
I don't like you get the fuck away from me
that could be more useful but
there are plenty of other
circumstances where you need
words to shorten down
what you are, like digi is the
otaku ganzo journalist
those are three labels right there
Jesse is the old school fool
those are different terms
I came up with a new name for you
you are the home school fool
with that home school cool
Tom what were you trying to say
actually what Nate just said is great
because people say home school
but there is such a huge grade
and good old Ben he is that home stuck fuck
with that home stuck suck
I will gladly
I will gladly take off
what Nate brought up with home schooling
because there are so many different kinds
it really doesn't necessarily say anything
about how that person was raised
but here is the thing
the term home school does mean
that you were taught by your parents
probably at home as a term
and there is no concrete definition to it
but that term is useful
I can't just begin
but who cares about the fact that you were home school
other than you just feeling like
well for example when we need to talk
about it like in the last podcast
and what if I began
my talking about it
my commentary by saying
by like trying to like in three paragraphs
describe exactly what my situation was
that would have been perfect
hold on did he not at all
because this is how I used to communicate
I would like try to explain all the details
before like explaining what the overall
reality was
you don't have to do it before or you can do it later
no I did it that way and you complain
that whenever I begin talking about something
you don't know what I'm talking about until I'm
toward the end of my point so I'm like oh
this is what we need words for
I don't think home school counts as a label
I don't think that's the same thing as what I'm describing
you say home school people think of certain things
but they'll probably be inaccurate
but it does mean
like you weren't schooled in a building
you were probably schooled by your parents
it means certain things
necessarily even though everyone is on some sort of weird
gradient
I began my commentary on the last podcast
I was home schooled that lets people get
some context into what I'm talking about
and then I can elaborate later but not everyone
can know exactly what you mean
let Tom say his thing
I think the reason though
that people get hung up
on the label with
trends and all that kind of stuff is because
it's not it's because they want to feel
part of a community
because
that whole kind of like there's this huge kind of
collectivist ideology
deep in the root of social justice
whatever you want to identify that as
it's very much a collectivist ideology
so they don't really
did you you're making a great point I agree with you
because I'm an individualist but they're not individualist
like they classify themselves
isn't individualist a label
and that's one of the problems I have
I think with the whole
kind of like trans movement
I guess is that because what they do
is they'll say like I want to be a woman
or I want to be a man but then they make
a big deal about the trans label so now we
have male female trans male and trans
now we have four things instead of trying to
just transition from one to the other
so you that
plus for identity is making it more
more complicated instead of just simplifying
it because by putting so much emphasis
on that
that's true the social
the social and community aspect must
complicate the issue
this also comes down to because I
made this exact same argument on an episode of Digi Bros
before the one I was making earlier
and you know some of the responses were saying
well you know
in the name of getting people to
understand what the fuck
this thing is having labels
is helpful and I get that
it's just that
DeVu has accused me of this before
that I always seem to go right for the biggest
possible picture as opposed to
what is individually relevant right now
because in my mind I'm wanting
everyone to not care about labels
anymore forever
just all people all over the world
and I was going to say like if you never
if you're one of these people who's you know
got their own fractured you know gender identity
or whatever like you're like do we just need
to make labels for everybody because there's always
going to be somebody who doesn't fit isn't
it better to just shoot for we all kind of just
you know we live in our own shit
that's the real solution
was themselves and everyone else
didn't question it and just accepted it
but obviously
we're not in that world and it's
it's going to take a while and like you know
a lot of people won't get what you're doing
if you're like acting one gender
that is not the one that you seem to be
you know people won't get that so I get
I get why the labels exist I'm just saying that
as an idealist
who wants to live in a world where everyone's
just a fucking weirdo that's my dream of the
perfect reality is that everyone
is totally fucking weird
that's my perfect world
is that every person I see
and I'm like what the fuck is that guy
that's awesome
what is that
guy is not a gendered term
yeah guy is just a name for the coolest guy
I'm a dude, he's a dude, she's a dude
we're all dudes yeah
the same applies for guy
but you can't even do this example
without saying he and she
like you can't even like make any progress
they're just entrenched in our language
whatever did this podcast become
I like the better one you were arguing about
yellow
I sure didn't
and I just want to close out my point by saying
that again it's not about
what anyone does or chooses to do
I think everyone should be free to do whatever they want
it's only some of the reasoning
behind it that when
explained I think when someone says
I am actually a woman
or I'm a woman on the inside
I don't think that necessarily means anything
I think that there's a thing
I close out I guess
I've always kind of thought
it's kind of insolvable with this kind of mentality
maybe just no one's explained it to me good enough
is that you have people saying
I'm a woman on the inside because
there's differences between men and women
and I'm a woman trapped in a man's body
but those same people also say
all the time
it's arbitrary
it's socially defined
gender norms are bullshit
so if there's differences
then you're either saying
I just kind of made that point
I think while you were standing up
he did
I can totally get
relating to and identifying more strongly
with a traditionally feminine
societal role
that makes sense to me
being a woman on the inside
feeling like a woman on the inside
does not make sense to me
I think you have a very funny definition of the phrase
things I can't get into
just to close out people
everybody go watch
are we closing out or do we not have more
do you guys want to do more
I didn't get to say anything in this podcast
we will do more but let me just say
because I wanted to just say digi
I have a beautiful vision of what you were saying
would look like and what is Imaishi's current show
that's going on with the alien girl
Luluko
Space Patrol Luluko is the perfect ideal of this
I gotta talk
Matthew Matosis into cutting this
one ten minute chunk out of his four hour live stream
at E3 where he was just on this
like epic rant about
how space should be fucking chaos
he was like
everytime I play a game about space
I can't do his accent
everytime he plays a game about space
it's always just like normal
it's always human stuff
it's always humans fighting humans
if I go out into space everything should be fucking crazy
I just want to walk up to somebody and be like
oh my god what the fuck is that
and he just went on this long rant about it
that was awesome
it was the best thing I ever heard
Jesse you were agreeing with him
oh ok I get it I'm with you
Matthew Matosis
tell me your sins boy
oh father
father Matosis
your sins
he's definitely
I can't get into Matthew Matosis guys
Jesse what's the thing you can't get into
that's not true I can
old comics
comics
yeah like silver age
bronze age
shut up
yeah
iron age
shut the fuck up god damn it
he's getting steamed now folks
I'm gonna
I'm gonna ban you
I'm just gonna talk to myself
that's the ideal scenario
I'm really interested in this though
because I've always been curious about whether
comic fans like old comics
I figured Jesse would be into the golden age
because of what got
ok
shut the fuck up
alright Jesse go on
I don't know what you were getting at with that
so in the 1980s
Frank Miller
Alan Moore
and Grant Morrison all got together
and said what if comics were good
and they made
and they wrote Arkham Asylum
they wrote The Killing Joke and Watchmen
they wrote Daredevil and Wolverine
and all those great comics
and suddenly comics were good forever for all time
it was the greatest medium
in the history of art
but before that
every comic was trash
all of them from the golden age
silver age and bronze age
I tried to
anything pre 1980s and even some comics
from the 1980s
I tried to read them
I'm like I want to read these old stories
and I just fucking
I see the art
and I see the giant retarded word balloons
and it's just like
Jesse are you telling me that Stan Lee
is not the greatest creative genius who ever lived
I don't think Stan Lee actually
created anything
I think he's kind of a con man
kind of
except that one time he cosplayed his liquid ocelot
that was pretty dope
he's great it's not his fault
it's just
his time was an era
bereft of talent
the paradigm was
to make bad comics
I've always wondered about
it's all about the generational evolution
where the kids grow up on something that sucks
but they can appreciate
what is the potential about it
and they spend all their time wanting to make it better
and they become adults and they take it to the next level
that's what happened with film
I'm gonna piggyback on Jesse's thing
and say I can't get into old
anything
as soon as it's passed a certain threshold of age
it's just
I think that what Jesse just described
with the comic creators getting together
and saying what if comics were good
I think that has happened in every
medium where
with movies like the oldest movies I really
can get into are like the 70s
which is when the movie brat
generation came around
when Kane did you
I don't think they actually
had a meeting and said that
I made that story up
I don't think the movie brats did either
but my point is that
there was a period in the 70s
where a bunch of people who were like these
big time film buffs
who were big fans of film
who were educated in film specifically
as opposed to
this was just what Nino was talking about
in his fucking Miyazaki video
in the 70s and the 60s
anime creators
were all people who were like
doctors and stuff
people who had come from other fields
referencing a Nino video
it's a new world we're in now
Nino was talking about how
these creators
of the older anime were not
like anime fans
they were influenced by other works of art
but then when
you got Gainax coming into the fold
and stuff like that
they were inspired specifically by anime
not exclusively
Anno has made a huge point
about how the fact that he thinks everyone is just influenced
by anime these days and it's a problem
but
I think that those are the people who
Miyazaki or does Anno say that too
Anno says it too
but I think that
there's certain periods where people who are
into a medium
and who clearly care deeply about it
can sort of recognize what's good about it
like better than
perhaps the people who actually made the stuff
right? because everyone's just kind of
like if you're making something
new that's never existed before
then it's more about
how to make it cost effective
how to make it something that is
capable of being done
like how do we even make
an anime happen
and then the people who come later
look at all those anime and they go like
this this and this were the best episodes of
Astro Boy so what if we copied those
elements and made a show like that
as opposed to throwing
100 episodes worth of ideas
at a wall only some of which will stick
and so I think that every
medium
inherently gets better over time because people can
look at the old stuff and say
they can cut out the stuff that didn't work
and they can put in new stuff that does work
here's my counter
wait you don't say that about video games
here's my
I would say that about video games
video games from the fucking 70s were garbage
you want to fucking play Pong?
I totally disagree with that
Digi because in my humble opinion
anything that is old
or recycled or reincorporated
is automatically a lesser version
of the original
well I completely disagree
I like Quentin Tarantino more than any of the directorcy copies
the fact that
new movies might take something
an old movie did and do it
quote unquote better
but the fact that they're not the first one to do it
makes it less valuable
I totally and completely disagree
I think being the first one actually makes
is a sad weakness
like you were the first one
you're a fool bro
those people deserve all the respect
in the world
they just have by the sad fact of being
first have made the worst product
this is getting like way beyond
what I originally was talking about
I just think that specifically
with old comics
you're right we were talking about comics
I totally co-opted
Jesse's problem
I look at old comics
and the artwork looks derpy
it all looks like this weird
homogenized 60s style
I think everyone knows what I'm talking about when I talk about old comic book art
and the stories
are always so wordy
the characters are describing everything they're doing
and they're just a pain in the ass to read
they're just not well written
or well conceived even
and not even just
like that the stories themselves are bad
most of them are pretty far out
and weird and wacky
but not necessarily bad it's just
like they didn't have anything
they didn't know what good was yet
it's like
well they were for kids back then
yeah like nowadays
like those three guys that I said
Frank Miller and Alan Moore and Grant Morrison
every comic ever
nowadays is influenced so heavily
by the books they wrote in the 80s
that they kind of
made comics something completely different
than they originally were so it's almost like
a whole different thing that I'm talking about
when I'm talking about old comics
and I feel the same way
about like TV anime
with Ava were like
and all the anime that was good
in like the 80s was either like
the world masterpiece theater show
which meant it was based on an old novel
or it was like directed by
these very few certain directors
who were doing like good stuff
but none of it was anything close to what
Ava did and like Ava created
the idea of original TV anime
and the directing
was so much better
in my opinion I mean there's plenty of people
who will actually kill me
for saying that
Anno is better than Osamu Dazaki
or something but like I watch those old shows
and what I see is an 80s anime
and when I watch Evangelion
I do not see 1995
I see
like the best anime I've ever seen
you know
yeah but I mean okay
we've made new anime since Ava so it's obviously
not the best anymore you know
there you go
in that one specific instance it might have been done
like way better but in general
it's not better just because it was done again
I just think that I think
when you take something
when you take something old
and you subtract all the shitty parts
and just tighten up the good parts
and then enhance it
with your own extra creative edge
it's a better product
it depends on what like that's so vague
it's totally vague it's all about the artistic
it's the individual artistic product
you can judge it by whether or not it's better or not
if they didn't enhance it then it's not going to be a better product
it depends on what these so called shitty parts
if something is good
then I like it
if something is good then I like it
what the fuck
it doesn't matter how old it is
I like old things
I like new things I like
Ben what if there's a movie
where like the whole
thing is amazing
but there's this one part where they left in
like this like just
lame ass ten minute
like two characters taking
a poop or something like except not
that hilarious
something dumb
that happens in the middle of the movie
and then someone later
like if in Citizen Kane they just two characters
started doing battle shits in the middle of it
for like yeah
I'm trying to think of an example that wouldn't
make the movie better
let's put it this way
what if you took Citizen Kane and made
the same concept but now it has battle
shits in it it's a better movie
fucking Kane
Kane and his wife
are sitting across the long table in the
Xanadu fucking farting at each other
you can't just add
bullshit to an old thing and then it's like
apparently a better artistic piece
God fucking damn it
I want you to prove yourself here
because I want you to like list off
all your favorite stuff at some point
figure out if it's clearly all new stuff
I will list off my favorite
things at some point when we do
the people versus Ben St
like isn't like
isn't Homestuck like your favorite thing of all time
that's super new and it's super built on the
backs of like every other art medium
ever created if video games
hadn't existed you couldn't have that
everything's built on the back of something
but everything that's great about Homestuck
is the way that it fucking innovated
and did things that no one had ever done before
do you think that the video game
parts of Homestuck are inherently
not as good as Pong
because they weren't the first video game
is that what you're saying
okay look let me
counter that if there had never been
a video game ever if video games
did not exist and then you were
reading Homestuck and you hit
that next button and suddenly you were having
an interactive experience
let's discuss the reality
let's discuss the reality we live in
Ben
let's discuss the actual reality we live in
where things are constantly getting iterated
making a fucking thought experiment
digi
like of course that would be the case
but that's not the case
so
Ben you need to understand the difference between
the point is that newness is valuable and precious
you're talking about stuff that is
impressive like the amount of
wow that is so much more
new it's not the same as being
better
I think newness
there is definitely inherent
like an inherent goodness
to newness
but I don't think that that
goodness exceeds the goodness of
being better
but you're judging better by
doing it again with other shit
like there has to be
which is what everything is
everything after the original
is just doing the same thing
but better
I like things that are
good
much better
a vastly superior thought experiment
imagine Pong came out today
you'd be like oh
I can't get into Pong honestly
I just can't
it beeps and it boops
Pong is just
tennis
that proves my point too
because if it came out today
it wouldn't be good but back when it was new
because it was the first fucking video game
it was good
and now it sucks
do you want to play Pong?
is Pong your favorite video game?
no no one gives a fuck about Pong
it's not good anymore
I give a fuck about Pong
on the PS1 version
the remake
it had value
and was impressive
and people wanted it
it was
it's not even was
as we know
and it continues to be noteworthy
no no no worthy yes
it is very noteworthy
it deserves
all the respect in the world
doesn't make it the best video game
this all came out of my topic somehow
I'm so sorry
here is why Ben is wrong
than anyone even gives him credit for
as we know from that PlayStation 3 commercial
our grandmothers
played by having
a hoop with a stick
and kicking that around
grandmothers played by getting raped
they got raped in the back of a Cadillac
after prom
people were bored as shit
all the time
people had very little stimulus
to go on compared to what we have now
and now those people are old
and they just sit in their houses
doing nothing
forever when we are old
it's not going to be like that
when we are in our 80s
we're just going to be marathoning shows and videos
and playing video games all the time
I like to think I'll still be drawing right up until I'm in the ground
but you'll also be doing this other shit
we are into so much more stuff
like in 1997
a kid playing Final Fantasy 7
is enjoying himself
way more
on average probably
than most of the biggest, most fanatic
fans of pawn
we are having more fun
relative
but there's also a time
relativity here
life is objectively better
today than it was in the 1800s
but happiness is not up
because of your happiness
overall is compared to everything else around you
the medical technology we have today
gives you
you should read
there's a fantastic chapter of One Piece
during the Marine Corps
I thought you were going to recommend a self-help book
if that's pretty much what it is
in which
this is my favorite podcast
we've ever done by the way
in which
Don Quixote, Do Flamingo
does this grand young speech
what does Don Quixote have to do with this
Jesse, I'm talking about One Piece
in which this guy who's a really powerful pirate
makes up grand speech during this war
in which the fate of the world is at stake
about
when you're poor
like little things
become much more valuable to you
and if you're rich and entitled
then losing even the small thing
is a proportionally much bigger deal
and that our happiness
is contextual on our experiences in life
well thank god One Piece exists
to give us that philosophical truth
imagine if Nate were
a marriage counselor
we just keep fighting all the time
what should we do
well I've seen chapter 375
of One Piece
one piece taught me how to be a real human being
I'm imagining
Nate in a church
he's in a big church and there's stained glass windows
and they've all got the crew members
of the going
Mary on them and he pulls out
he's like today we'll be reading from
chapter 537
One Piece is my bible dude
page 15, panel 7
and Frankie said
SUPER
we sing that shit
we have all the medical advances we have today
where our bodies on average get to feel
a whole lot less pain
and misery than we did before
but your happiness overall might be
the same as it was in the 1800s
but here's the thing
the amount of pain you have in your body
is a different variable to evaluate your standard of living
and your happiness is a totally separate variable
so like a kid from the 70s
could go out and have the same amount of
time of fun playing
Pong as a kid from the 90s
would go out and play Pong like it's the same
amount of fun it's just that the kid
in the 70s has so
few alternatives to go to
beyond Pong whereas a kid from today
playing Pong could enjoy it just as much
but we'll choose to do it
less because there's better alternatives
so they'll walk away
from playing Pong going it wasn't
really worth it because I could just play
Final Fantasy 7 and have a much better time
whereas from the 70s kid he'd be like
oh it was a great time there's nothing better to do
so that is why
even at the time it wasn't worth it
you just didn't have the ability to feel
how much better it is now
putting aside the whole issue of like whether or not
you know like audio-visual
stimulus is necessarily better than like real life stuff
I agree I agree
alright who else has a
thing to think into
I've got one that's an extension
of one that you of yours
Digi what was that
Country Song
and this is it's just
music all music
music in general I can't get into it
and I'll tell you why
I'm kinda with you
it's not that I don't like music
because when I listen to music often times I enjoy
it immensely and you've recommended a lot of stuff
that I really liked
I always thought you were a lot more into music
I know Ben isn't into like
anything he's mentioned
Ben's less so than me
yeah see that's the thing
I like music when I get to it
the problem is I don't have a place in my life
for music
and that's really what I'm talking about
there's no point in my life
when I have a place where I can just put on music
like you Jesse, I mean you Digi
you just listen to music like all the time
is what you've always said
it's just always playing in the background
I like when I'm editing
I don't want to be listening to music
because I need to hear the audio stuff
I have to edit in silence
you know there's a
you just open up your music player
you start playing an album
with no vocals
and you turn the volume down on the music player
to like 20%
that's not gonna be good enough
it's gotta be quieter than the music of your video
and it will not interrupt anything
I promise you
I don't want to just put music on the background
I actually am enjoying listening to it
see well that there's your problem
because I have recently found a place
for music in my life
which is I put on some like
soothing vapor wave
chill wave, simpsons wave
vapor wave is like a seal wave
and you put and I put it on
and it has to be of a particularly low tempo
sort
and I put it on and it's just atmospheric
and I leave it on and if the music is
non-distracting enough then I can just sit
and like either write
or sketch or ink
or tone or whatever
while I have it on
just because yours doesn't involve audio at all
but my work does so you know it's
I don't think it interrupts
my work involves audio too
you're gonna tell me what interrupts my work
you're gonna tell me how I should be editing
I'm just saying you haven't tried it
I haven't tried it with like super chill music
I mean I think if you're just syncing up like
the key is to use
to go and find the music to play
I have to download it, I have to put it on loop
I have to see if I like it
just listen to everything on YouTube
everything's on there
what I do is like
all the music I listen to is contextual
it's like if I feel
I always say that I love my beautiful
dark twisted fantasy but I can only listen to it
if I'm drunk and depressed
that's the situation where that album is perfect
if I'm editing videos
it's like one of a few
instrumental calming
electronic albums
or if I'm trying to
get myself hyped for editing it's on a monoguchi
if it's like
if I'm in a mood where I just want to thrash stuff
I put on some metal
if I'm in a mood where I just want to chill I put on some chill music
you know what this is
I don't view or use music that way
I like view an album as like an art piece
I need to sit there for an hour and study
and appreciate it
it is like the first time you listen to it
the first 25 times you listen to it
but I listen to albums hundreds of times
I don't got the space to listen to it for the first time
you know I'm not trying to like
tell anyone I'm just telling you what my life is
and like why
let me break in with a brief anecdote
the other day I was finishing up my high work submission
and I was
inking in some sketches of the characters
from my new comic
and I was thinking about
what the story is
what the main themes of the story are
and I realized
as I was drawing this I hadn't even realized it before
I realized that what the series is actually about
in my mind
is the quest to be happy
and how to be happy
and I was inking in
that character, that really cool looking character
that I didn't show anyone else but I posted in the thing
and on my playlist
Pharrell's happy came on
and I was so struck
by like drawing that character
while listening to that song
I felt like
not like I was emotional
like I was crying, I was just so like
amped up, I was so like in the moment
it's so hard for me to imagine
this feels so right
it's so hard for me to imagine you who's like the biggest hipster I know
getting all emotional over like
the biggest song of the last five years
I'm sorry
no
here's a terrible thing about me Digi
I hate popular media
and when things are popular
it makes me hate them and yet I really
I often find myself
really really responsive to like
huge hits and things that are massively popular
like I fucking love
I think it's an amazing song
and I can't, I wish I didn't
I wish I hated that
it was a feel good hit of the summer
and I was just sitting there
just like twitching
it's all
coming together, it all feels
like it's all in place
Nate I will say, I will agree with you
that like if I was editing or
if I was even writing a script
I would by no means listen to music
that I haven't heard before
that is not the right, unless it was
unless it was like
if you're hearing it for the first time
you can very easily go on YouTube
and type like
chill wave mix
and it'll just be like a two hour mix
of like a bunch of shitty electronic music
that's really generic
is like perfect
listen to any trance mix
they all sound exactly the same
let's go to YouTube and search for funk
and just jam the fuck out for a while
I've been listening to some great chill wave mixes
that are by some guy named
I think Epicuros
and they start off with a scene
from Blade Runner where he gives the
the what's it test to Rachel
and uh
I don't know
that's how I feel about all vaporwave
other than like Blank Banshee
which I legitimately love
most vaporwave to me is extremely
disposable and not memorable
and not interesting
there are some
upbeat energetic
vaporwave songs that actually get me kind of pumped
I've heard the, cause there was that
sailor wave, that hour long mix
that Nate had posted
and the whole thing is like
one hour long funk song
it's like the same song over and over again
and you can get the point within
20 seconds and that's the
entire thing and I just put it on
for an hour and I didn't pay any attention to it
I was doing work and doing other shit but like
it fit well you know
it's not something I would ever listen to
as like a let's sit down and listen to
sailor wave for an hour
whereas I would do that for like
like a Kendrick Lamar album
like that's not music you can have on in the background
you really have to sit and listen to
to Pimpa Butterfly if you want to get
that album you know
I have two vaporwave mixes that I
listen to a lot one is called Neo Batavia
and the other is called
Squad Goals
and they both, they both
have like a couple of songs on there that are like
Squad Goals is the one I was talking about actually
not Sailor Wave
Oh yeah, the one that plays
when like the looping gif of the
Doraemon characters walking
Squad Goals is the mix with like the
tons of anime shit in it right
it's like a heavy
the video is like a heavily processed
thing of like an old anime
it looks all the videos
it's really cool because I know all those shows
and for me like my favorite thing about
vaporwave is all these 80s
anime that no one's heard of suddenly
like surfacing in media and I'm like
oh my god people are making videos about fucking
Cobra and shit like this is the best
there's a there's a YouTube channel called
Artsy Music and there is a
like ARTZie
and there's one
there's a song by Lord Son and the name
is in Japanese but like
it's this looping gif of I forget
her name the character from Gun Buster
Oh yeah that's Noriko
Yeah Noriko from Gun Buster
I know the video you're talking about
Dude, yeah that bit of animation where like
she's well it's not just
the tip bounce like she stands up and like
she like she has her mouth open
and then she closes her mouth and blinks twice
and as she's doing it she closes her fists
and like twists her arms inwards into
like a triumphant pose I have
watched that loop and I
watched that animation like like for
10 minutes straight and I would just like
try to blink at different moments in it
to like pick out the different frames
and like until I had like
developed like a feel for every
individual frame in that like several
second animation you know what you gotta do now
you have to watch because that that
specific cut is
in daikon 4 and it's in otaku
no video like it's a cut that they kept
reusing in uh in gynax so
like because it was a
act according to your definition band
that makes Gun Buster worse
well it's all the same guy it's all
Toshio Kata wrote all of those
Recycled idea
No it makes the other things that it was
recycled into worse
Well it was originally
It was first daikon 4
and then Gun Buster and then
otaku no video
well it's still a beautiful animation
regardless yes it's very cool
it's in like right in the middle of daikon 4
you should watch it it's only 4 minutes long and it's the best anime ever
I have seen daikon 4
I can't get into
Steven Seagal I hate him he's a fat
shit old movie
executive action is the greatest
movie of our generation
fucking you know what I love
that's right because I was all the wrong
generation I identify as an 80s kid
you know I love action movies
the cornier the better
you know I love
everything by Stallone and Schwarzenegger
I love Jean Claude Van Damme
but something about Steven Seagal
I just look at him and I want to puke
he doesn't look like he can do any of the things he's doing in his movies
he doesn't look like he can beat anyone up
he looks like just a fat dad
he's got some major dad bond going on
he's the worst action star in the history of action cinema
he belongs in
he belongs in like Uncle Buck
he's like a John Candy actor who was
cast into an action hero
I've seen like
a compilation of like oh really cheesy
hilarious Steven Seagal moments and I'm like
this would be funnier if anyone other than
Steven Seagal would make money in this scene
some executives were like
this is Steven Seagal we made him
a bad action hero as a joke
and that's just his whole career is just based on that
but then they forgot it
how do you feel about like Charles Bronson
he's the greatest actor of all time
yeah he's great Charles Bronson is great
he's good of course he's the fucking man
I love all of them they're all great except
he's the only one Steven Seagal is the only guy I hate
he sucks
you said Charles Bronson but I thought of
Charles Barclay, Bronson, Marle
Marle and Brandon
Jesse you made me think of one thing
that I pretty much can never get into
is the so bad it's good principle
because most things that are so bad
they're good are like
really sparse with things that are so bad it's good
which is why like Garzy's doing
the Digi introduced me to and that one's really great
at least the first episode because that one is
so dense with interestingly hilarious
bad stuff but most
so bad it's good things
same as I feel about like the guilty pleasure label
like if it's so bad it's good then it's just good
yeah
it depends on how you're looking at it
but Davoo you really should watch the room
because the room has gone so far
beyond ironic enjoyment for me
that I just love every single bit of it
yeah Nate I did watch the room
I didn't get a whole lot more out of it than just
like to be honest when I watched the nostalgic critics review
because he just showed all the funny parts
give it another try
hold on I already
watched the room and it wasn't like that
good like because you know whenever you watch
a review even if it's one of those really
long that guy with the glasses style ones
which basically just shows the movie
it doesn't quite capture
what the actual experience of the movie is
so it's not quite spoiling
the room has all these
really long scenes that aren't
that full of like really funny stuff
what are you talking about man
every second of that movie is funny
it's true it's all like every line
Tommy says is instant gold
it's fucking amazing
but I just want to say that I too
got into it via the nostalgic critic review
and I watched that video like a bunch of times
then I got into the movie so I'm just saying
Davoo I don't know
how many times you've seen it
something about the room is that I can see how you
would think that on like a first viewing
okay I know you said you saw
the nostalgic critic review so maybe this is
not you maybe you're not a naive viewer
like I'm gonna describe but someone who
watched the room one time probably
wouldn't he would there would be some funny bits
they laughed at but I think it
takes like several watches and like I
think you kind of have to discuss it and like digest it
to really understand the depth and the
density and complexity
it's such a social movie
you kind of slightly different
I want to change my terms
I'm never going to be able to appreciate
movies the way that James
Rolfe does even remotely
and the way that he can appreciate movies
like horror movies
and they're like really terrible and
like I don't know what he gets out of it
and that's definitely something I can't get into before
and cheesy and a cheesy horror
it's just like
I just feel like people can really get into
movies because they're movies
and the craft of
film itself is
captivating to them but see that's exactly what
makes the room cool because the deviations
from what you'd expect a good movie to be
are done so hilariously
in that movie that is
I can't look at the room
even as a bad movie
like to me it has a place
that no other film in history has
and it fits exactly for the room
I didn't know you were such a fan
you're a kinder experience
I've been down to clown with the room
since time immemorial
have you been to the live shows
where they play in theaters and throw the spoons
and shit? I've seen it
in theaters and stuff
that's what I was saying
so much has been what makes the room
enjoyable
and it was like the best thing I've ever been to
it was so much fun
so much of what makes it enjoyable
is the social aspect of it
is having a bunch of guys in a room
and everyone knows the lines
and moves in their minds and everything
that did make it better but I just want to clarify
I've already loved it intensely before going to that
I know Jesse was also a big Rocky Horror fan
so it's kind of the same
same thing
I'm with DeVoo
because I don't get like
because I don't think that's quite what we're describing
the room is more
I think of the room as being just like Garzi's wing
where it's so
there's so much to appreciate
and so much of it's outright memes
and with the room there's stuff that you can quote
every day of your life
I think DeVoo is talking more like just like
old timey effects and corny dialogue
there's a lot of those
kind of more like the cinemasticist
how he can get so into some of those old
schlock movies
and it's not a cultural thing
it's not him joking with his friends
it's just him watching these movies
and enjoying them by himself
are you familiar with this one James Rawl video
the top 40
shitty shark movies
he and his wife watch them more
than 40 shark movies
and like Sharknada was coming out
as he was making the list so we put it at number 5
at the last second
he had the mental ability
to watch all of those
I'm with you dude
I can only barely stand to watch one good video
I could
see the thing is that like what you were saying
about like being so enamored with the
craft of film I could definitely
do that with anime
I don't think I would enjoy all those shitty anime
necessarily
but I could easily watch any
shit anime just because it's anime
because I'm so enamored with knowing
everything about it and knowing every single
possible thing
I think it really is more than just appreciating
to appreciate something like these
it's not about really judging it by itself
it's about having a larger context
of what the work is
and how it deviates from that and why that's
so cool but I do think that like
with stuff like the room in Garzi's wing
that's like a different story
because it's not just that it's so bad it's good
it's so bad it's like amazing
like legitimately the funniest
movie ever
it's got green light with these things
it's like the fact that people like check the box
like okay ship this is just like
holy shit it's amazing
I mean a lot of what
makes bad things
really bad things good and interesting
is the way that it sort of
forms a narrative about the person
exactly the things you learn about Tommy
by watching that movie are
yeah you learn about Tommy when you watch
the room you learn about what's his name
I just want to bring this up briefly
that I've recently become fascinated as of
the latest YMS video where he talked about
the three movies by that one fucking weird guy
those look so good
they look pretty fucking hilarious
and it suddenly dawned on me
that like all these guys
obviously these directors are fucking weird
right they're definitely weird people
and like their movies always have like
suicide like strong themes
of suicide and depression and death
and it's like these are like
tormented people
like these are obviously people who
are trying to express themselves because
they've probably lived a whole
life of being fucking weird and nobody gets them
and so they try to make a movie so people
can get them and people get them even less
and they get it all wrong and that's why they want
to fucking kill themselves
there's no way to win
I bet the guy from that new YMS review
he had like a laptop back in the 90s
when he was nerdy and kids made fun of him
and broke his laptops and now all he can do
in his movies is break more laptops
and all of his movies to vent his frustration
about laptops
and yeah so like did you I totally
I'm like that with video games
like right now I'm on Moby games
I click random game and without exception
I'm at least a little bit interested
because the fact
that video games exist
is always the most mind blowing
incredible fact that I can
ever think no matter how many times I do it
that's how I feel about anime
and yeah and a lot of people seem
to be that way with film like they just
can't believe that this film is
happening and it never gets old to them
dude you have no idea how many times
I like I sit back on my bed
and I'm like because I know enough about
anime to know that this is like
like I always think
of it as like 40 people making all
anime right like that's a gross
exaggeration but anime is so incestuous
that it's like
it really is compared to anything like
compared to the world at large
tiny handful of people
on this far away archipelago
in the middle of fucking nowhere
in the middle of the Pacific Ocean
who are sitting there like
creating this it is
an archipelago it's a bunch of islands
totally an archipelago
you know
it's just
a bunch of
this handful of people on this island
somewhere far away who have been doing
this thing for so long
that there's this whole culture around it
this whole like
it's own trajectory of development all these
things and like 45 shows coming out
of season and yet
it's so insular
that it doesn't make sense to anyone else
like how the fuck does anime exist
how are they still making it
how is that fuck how is it not died
like it it just keeps getting
more insular it never gets
bigger and broader and more appealing to the rest
of the world like every once in a while it does
at least netflix is helping
and attack on titan people watch
that shit but then a show will come out
that like I feel like 12 people
can possibly appreciate it
and I'm like how are these 12 people
gonna fund this show that only 12 people
made
each one of them buys 12
even in the age of light novels did you
do you still feel that way or do you just feel
that way about some shows light novels are the most
insular those are the ones that are like
yeah but they haven't established audience already
right but that's the thing
there it is
for the most part in japanese anime
it's just
it's crazy that
there's a whole market
that is so small
and so like plays to itself
and has
it doesn't seem to be trying to get any
bigger for the most part
and yet it somehow
can generate more content
than like any other medium
like what other medium has 45
news things coming out every
fucking three months that is
an insane amount of content
video games but I guess there's way less people
45 video games
going steam probably
I mean in indie games
I guess so but in indie games also like
one guy making it where an anime is like
a team of 100 people
that's fair that's fair
you don't know just how many games
there are on steam I remember on a digi bros
you were saying eventually you've seen
all the steam games no eventually
you've seen all the steam games that are linked
to by other steam games and recommended
pages if you go to
like list all games by most
recent multiple games come out every
day yeah yeah
well whatever that's cool all right we get
the point it is sweet it is sweet
let's do another one
hold on I want to figure out how to do that
before we move on
from the subject I know that the subject
evolved a little bit but it was originally
things that are so bad it's good and before
we move on I can't help but mention
Christian Weston Changlin
the electric hedgehog pokemon
which um wait
have you hippos read it
Nate has read it
digi de vu jesse have you guys read
I have not oh man
you guys should do it
okay I have read the entire
thing multiple times
I was way into the whole
thing in like college and a little
after and um
the thing about sonichu is
the the comic itself
I mean it looks terrible obviously you can tell
just by looking at it that the art is bad
the story is
very often extremely boring
and usually completely
incomprehensible
but the challenge and the
satisfaction of reading sonichu
comes from understanding
Christian Weston Changlin himself
understanding his mindset
and understanding what was happening in his life
when he was drawing these things
and fucking figuring out
how to parse what it is he's trying to say
and often it is extremely obvious what's going on
but sometimes it's brutally difficult
like
like there's a scene
there's a scene where
uh like
he beats up a bunch of cops
at a bowling alley
in the comic yeah jerk cops
and he says like they I'm not the
weak person I was I'm much saltier now
and like
what does that mean right
well if you dig enough
you find out that um
Christian Weston Chandler went to like some
bacon in like 2005
at which he met the voice actors
that played Hayat in excel saga
and excel saga contains
a joke where in excel
says ah I'm not the sweet
person she thinks I am I'm much saltier
wait did Christian start
the salt thing like
is that how salt became a thing that people
know okay no no
he means he means that he's tough
um yeah so he it was it's
actually a stolen joke
from excel saga with its
context removed and butchered to the point
which he stole a lot from including his own
inclusion in the story as a character
there's dozens
and dozens yeah excel saga
is like an unsung an unsung
hero of like not know that
at all yeah it's big it's big
it's yeah it's even the reason I haven't read
sonnet you like all of his plagiarized
the reason I haven't read sonnet you is
I've always been under the impression that one
day you were going to just tell me the
entire CW
story that's what he did with me that's what he did with me back
years ago I've been I've been waiting for the day
that we can sit down and you can just describe
the whole I just like to propose
for radcon let's just have the sonnet you
sit down
appreciate the whole day yeah
but sit down by the fire and then
pulls out the tome it's dusty
he blows the pages all the dust comes
off the tome by the way
is uh is
oolulila's book yeah you should bring
that too
legend of the legend of the ten
elemental masters which I also own
oh but yeah I don't think I've ever
mentioned this on the show but I have a piece of
original Christian art I have a comic
page that I commissioned from him
that shows the secret fate of the
brown-shirted imposter that was never shown
in the comic I was like please liquid
Chris $50 you know draw draw me
yeah liquid Chris draw me
what happened to liquid Chris and I
have it on my wall and I will show it
to him probably on my twitter put that up
and I want to see it yeah
again um
I was gonna say something
about um
yeah it's like it's the whole
sonnet you saga is like this weird puzzle
that you gotta unpack but once you do
it's like it's it's dense
with meaning in the in the same kind of way
the room is by the way there's
I did I did link you to the way to
list all new games on steam
well you actually comes out every day this
week your your uh your
list doesn't have as many listed as the
one I had already found but I'm seeing
not that many games well yeah I narrowed
it I narrowed out uh I narrowed out
software and downloadable content and that stuff
okay well just full games who
gives a shit let's move on
I have another one
thing I can't get into and I need to
you know preclude I need to
disclaim this you know I'm gonna sound
like a nerd he's gonna talk about economics
here it comes
something I can't get into
I'm gonna sound like a jerk
so I want to so as soon as I say this
I'm gonna have to clarify why immediately
mm-hmm I can't I was
the same with the gender binary I can't
get into sports
because not because of like athleticism
fine with that you expect to be argued with
by anyone in this call like none of us
fucking yeah I think our audience is gonna
be mostly who the hell was gonna make you sound
like even though I know I do like
football and I watch football occasionally but
even though I know most people will agree with me I just
know there's some subconscious judgment of
like because you know you don't have
any athletic ability that's why right
well you know that might be part of it
but the real reason is
is that there's no level
design I you know
exactly
one level design there is exactly
that's not because I think about this
Final Fantasy 13 is the worst
game ever but because for one simple
reason it's all a hallway right okay but
imagine this what about a Final Fantasy 7
you can change your character I'm at 13
I'm at Final Fantasy 13 okay
yeah I actually
I didn't even hear you say so
okay I'm sorry but
but here's the difference is that
every time you play Final Fantasy 13 in this
example your characters are all different
and it's a different team comp and you get to
have a different team that you're fighting
you know what's funny to me about this
argument is that one of
my favorite video games
of all time is Mario
Power Tennis which has no
level design and it's one of the best
games ever and
I also like watching Tennis on TV
so I don't like watching Tennis at all
boring why don't you fucking
why don't you fucking get some
DFW David Foster Wall
essays and go read Infinite Jest you fucking
you fucking
by the way David David
Foster Wall yeah it is about tennis
oh god nobody knew that
I've got the audio book I can
listen to it and watch tennis
at the same time you know what I totally
I totally don't agree oh my god
I can play Mario Power Tennis and listen to Infinite Jest
oh my god
I have to buy the new Mario Tennis game
for the Wii U this is the
greatest realization of my life
I might be drunk now by the way
I actually don't agree with what I said
before about the you can't get into it
I think actually the definition is
can you really get into it
and become a fan of it not just have
isolated moments of enjoyment
let me tell you it's like I turn on
no shut up I turn on tennis
and I'm like hmm that's kind of cool
that's kind of and then I'm done I'm done
I'm bored I'm that's it that's it
I'm not like into tennis
because there's because it's the same
thing every time and I know it's all about
the staff and people but that's not enough for me
the reason people enjoy it is because
all the players they know the ins and the outs
they know the staff they have expectations for what's going to happen
the majority of the appeal of sports
to sports fans is the narrative
it's all about
but there's just not a narrative
there's not like a world that they're inhabiting
it's the same location every time
and I you know I would
dislike the world they're inhabiting is our world
the location is
no they're not
it's the same court every time
it's not there's four different types of courts
you've got the clay court the grass court
the fucking the super bouncy one
that's not enough
the players as characters exist
in the real world that's where the stakes are
you've got that world
you've got that one court where the
physical tangible way
you've got the one court where sometimes the tiles
there's like water underneath
and you fall into piranha plants and stuff
what about snakes and ladders
shoots and ladders god damn it
but Davoo more than
just the game is relevant to the game
with a ladder
we at hippo were both trying to make a reverent jokes
while you guys were talking
if it were the other way around
let's say like football
just think about how much cooler football would be
if it took place on a mountain
yeah it wouldn't be even anymore
but it would be the coolest thing
wasn't that what homestuck art was about
the one that hussy
went through so much effort to get
it's not homestuck
the football player on the mountain
fighting like a dragon
that football player fighting against
an evil unicorn with an
erupting mountain
imagine if soccer
took place in a marsh
and they had to get around
there's an interesting thing
back when
in England football
used to be played
between towns
and they would kick the ball from one town to the other
through forests and over rivers
that's so cool
that would be what you would want to see
this is exactly
what hippo wants all football to look like
that's pretty great
I'll link that in the description
I'm the one editing this
two of you have said you were going to link something in the description
forgetting that I added
interview digi you said you were going to link that fan art
that I made and you didn't link it
I had to wait for a commenter to point it out
and I had to go in and put it in
okay let's
Jesse do you have another thing you can't get into
oh yeah
okay new fighting games
can't do it
okay
so I can't get into fighting games in general
I used to
really like street fighter
but that was when I was young and naive
I used to play street fighter 2 on our SNES
yeah when we had the Super Nintendo
and it was just casually
it was great
any fighting game
that I grew up with
and have a fondness for
is street fighter, Mortal Kombat
Smash Brothers, whatever
I have my character
I have my guy
I know all the moves, I know how to play it
I can be reasonably competent at it for the rest of my life
but any
game that's just coming out
I don't have anybody around to play with
so I don't have a fucking
there's no social aspect to it
I don't have the ability
I don't like you getting everybody's names confused
I fucking shwasted making it as ass to yourself
on the internet
everybody shut the fuck up for a second
god damn it let Jesse continue
I don't have the ability to like
learn a new character
shut the fuck up
shit
oh christ
you got me to that point
it took you two and a half hours but you did it
Davoo kicked me out of the podcast
that didn't do it, you started yelling at me about yell
that didn't do it
but you finally pushed me
right over the edge
I'm sorry
okay go on
I'm listening
I don't know
that's fucking it
I fucking would have had more if you'd let me talk the first time
alright
I have a really easy time
getting into new fighting games
cause all my friends are fighting game addicts
all they do is talk about fighting games
play fighting games
I don't have the time nor the patience
nor the ability nor the incentive
to learn a new character in a new game
that's my whole point that's all I wanted to say
move on to the next one
the last fighting game
I was able to get into
I guess I kinda got into smash at some point
but I got into
I just like the aesthetic of guilty gear so much
and I thought that Kai looked so cool
I thought he was such a cool looking dude
that I managed to sit down
for long enough to learn how to sort of play
Kai in guilty gear
I have this real burning desire
I have a lot of weird plans for when
we all eventually live near each other
and one of them is that
Jesse is always describing
guilty gear as like the coolest game
that he's never gotten into or never played
and like I have this
dream of having Jesse around
and I can be like Jesse
let's play guilty gear and I can
I can be the one who finally gets
Jesse into guilty gear
cause I fucking love guilty gear
How do you feel about that Jesse? Are you into that?
I'm all into that
Oh so you are open to it
I thought that you weren't interested in new games
Well if you had been listening Nate you would have heard
I'm sorry
Wow Nate I'm actually shocked
that you actually didn't get his point
Oh right cause there's no one to play with
Okay right I'm with you
I'll play
guilty gear with you fucks
Yeah it's a fun game, we used to play with you
Playing video games online is miserable and shit
even when it's with people you know
I have no interest in playing games online
Oh man that's funny cause like
I can't definitely cannot get into
playing online games randomly
It's not an appealing idea
This is relevant I gotta tell you
Hey Tom be back
Tom you love guilty gear, how do you feel about playing it
online?
I don't play guilty gear online
Interesting
Well let me tell you guys cause playing online sucks
I played League of Legends for years online
and it was only so that I would have
an excuse to hang out with my friends
because they live far away in other states
I agree
Overwatch now and shit
I played Halo 2 back in the day all the time
but I've never played it online
with my friends
We all like, you know, schedule it together
we'd all play, I've never played solo by myself
Same thing after college when I played Black Ops
when I played with some of my friends
but I hate playing online by myself
Me too
because I'm being social in general
so just a bunch of people yelling fag in my ear
playing a game that's really boring
so I hate that
I used to play a single player game that's constructed around
having experience
If only they made a single player game
about guys yelling fag in your ear
I'm into that
I used to play Halo and Gears of War online
but that was because you could have
a split screen with you and your friend
but you were in the same match together
online so that was always fucking cool
I did that with Halo 2 a lot too
I'd go to my friend Mike's house and we'd just fucking
get the Xbox going
When you have a friend next to you
they're all yelling at you like
what the fuck man
don't use the fucking sniper that you and your friend
can just be like listen to this fucking idiot
When it's just you hearing that voice
it wears on your soul after a while
You're like does this guy really
feel this strongly about this video game
I'm sorry I used the sniper rifle
please
please forgive me
I get it
you seem to care a lot more than I do
so I'll just back out of this match
and go back to other things
I immediately muted the chat
and overwatch once I got there
There's only
three multiplayer online games
that I can stand
it's Hearthstone, World of Warcraft
and Team Fortress 2
Hearthstone and Team Fortress 2
is okay because when I lose
it doesn't feel so bad and in World of Warcraft
I can just beat by myself
but in every other game
I've ever played online
including Mario Kart Wii
and fucking
anything
it makes me so infuriated that I
break things and I hate everyone
It's the worst
There's one game that I did play online
by myself and I didn't have a ton of fun
with it but it was
the Mass Effect 3 multiplayer
I had to do it because you had to
for the story you had to get your
readiness up by playing
which is a crock of shit
it was like horde mode
so that was a bit more
because it wasn't like people screaming at you
that you're a fag
people working together or trying to
or at least doing their own thing
it was more palatable
Relevant to that
most people
when they characterize online gaming
it's people yelling at you
but those times when you get someone
who compliments you and stuff
I always feel like that's the most heartwarming
in the world to realize that some random
stranger is a halfway decent person
is always really nice
I think the idea of online gaming would be
fucking great if people didn't suck so much ball
I will say
that I am a big fan of
MMORPGs like Terra
and Black Desert but I play them totally
solo and talk to nobody
so I just play them because I like the mechanics
World of Warcraft is my favorite
single player
I'm surprised
actually that is a great transition
because I was going to bring this up
as one of the things I can't get into
which is like
playing
online games in particular
and just generally any game that's
not about beating it in like
a sitting
I love single player games
where I can sit down for 2 or 3 days
and beat the whole game
and be done with it for as long as I want
Dark Souls 3
beat it in 18 hours
played a little bit more
just because I like the game so much
and then fucking forgot about Doom
beat the main campaign, went back a little bit
alright I'm fucking tired of Doom let's move on with my life
any game that's like
you play it regularly or you come back to it
or there's not an easy out
for me what's always made me paranoid
about playing online games
is the idea that if I leave
I fuck somebody over
oh yeah that's a trap right there
they're setting for you
yeah in a lot of those games and I could not even imagine
like one like League of Legends
where the matches are like 45 minutes long
it's a nightmare dude
you know first person shooter games is not too bad
it's like somewhat because
I like to be able to just get up at any time
when I'm playing a game I like to just go like
I literally in Dark Souls sometimes
I smack an enemy and he's dead
and then I realize I'm hungry and I put the controller down
and I go eat or you know
someone calls me to go do something
like I really value that
and when I can't do that
when it's like oh shit I have to finish this match
before I can go eat dinner
you know that it's like
unbelievable stress for me
and I cannot handle it
not to co-op the point
but yeah lol and mobas
are something that I cannot get into
and that I honestly fucking hate
I can't get into any point and click games
I cannot stand point and click
controls in video games
no no
some friends of mine tried to get
I played League of Legends for a while with some friends
and they tried to ease me
into it but they could not
help themselves but to get mad at me
it's because you depend on everyone to carry
the weight of a team it's brutal you know
yeah I know right like they were counting
on me but like I'm a noob I couldn't
you can't play with friends like that
and it fucking sucked and I played
enough I had a couple of good
kills I had some fun occasionally
it wasn't just like D&D it wasn't
all bad there were good there were highlight moments
but then I sort of got
okay with warwick like I sort of
figured out how to play warwick decently
and I was like oh cool now I'm starting to
have a little bit of fun and they were like
okay now stop playing warwick
pick up a new character learn the first out of like
a hundred god damn champs you need to learn
and then repeat for every
and then repeat for every character
until you know them all because that's the
only way you can fucking be good at this game
I was like no I don't understand
how anyone I cannot
understand how anyone has any fun
with these fucking games unless they're at like
a super high competitive level
that takes thousands of hours to get to
and who the fuck would want to do
because the thing is I only did it because
my friends played you know I think the
people who I think the people who get really
into those kind of games are ones who like
don't really do anything else
Oh absolutely my brother
shade gets really into like
like right now he's really into overwatch
and it's like overwatch came out
and now that is what he does
that would be awesome
apparently all my friends are playing it now
but shade is definitely going to be the one
who's the highest skilled in playing the most
because he gets into a game and he'll just
like not stop for months
it's all he does
he's actually editing a
overwatch video just comparing
all the running speeds of all the characters
like proving which ones are the fastest
and slowest like just because he fucking
felt like it you know
well he's I don't know it's not like a
narrated video it's like just
footage and music it's just remember
when the fucking he said it to his own
music to which is cool remember when the
Game Grumps dude made that like clapping thing
of all the smash oh yeah that was great
just reminds me of that but before we
compare the running speeds first we
have to talk about we'll have to talk about
parallel universes
yeah oh if only the best
meme ever
all right uh Tom now that you're back
do you have another thing you can't get into
um let's see
I don't know what was said while it was gone
yo I can't get into yo girl knowing I'm saying
dog I've been trying I've been trying man
suck at it dude
that's a that's a weird
that's a burn on you that's like
I failed to have sex with your girlfriend
it's really boned me out right now
damn oh damn
hahahaha
all right Tom what's your
all right I don't think I can follow that up
no um one of the things I've written here
is sports slash reality tv
I think spucking retarded
we did cover sports but not reality
we did sports we did not do I want to talk
about reality well let Tom start
yeah yeah yeah I don't know I just
my mother is obsessed with reality tv
so I see it all the time
because all she does is watch tv when she's not
at work
and I've just seen like the depravity that
she's been watching it ever since like the first survivor
like so oh yeah
so I've just I've I've
watched it evolve
via proxy and it's just the most
disgusting vapid boring
shit ever and I don't yeah I mean
I can understand why people like it
but I just can't believe people are so stupid
that they like it there's one
reality tv show that I do like
is called I'm a celebrity get me out of here
I don't know whether you guys have I don't know
but it's um a bunch of celebrities
trapped in an Australian jungle
and they have to do challenges in order to get
food and you're just
you're just seeing them go insane over
like a course of a week or two
it's pretty good
all right I too I'm not really
into reality tv show hold on
wait before you start I want to ask Hippo
I want to
I want to say that if it's celebrities
I don't think it entirely counts
because at that point
it's basically like a panel show with a
broader concept right
like celebrities are famous for the
fact that they have a personality
and are interesting people
on some level as opposed to reality
shows like what makes it reality
is that it's just real people
supposedly well the thing about these celebrities
is that they're washed up and nobody know right
nobody actually know we have a few like
they've been in a tv show we have a bunch of shows
like that we had the the surreal
life which was like the like
basically a bunch of d-list celebrities
doing the like a regular
reality show but I don't know
I feel like there's something slightly different because to me the whole point
of it being reality is that it's
supposed to be just like well a window
into the life of some well you are seeing them
like literally stop and go in
it's hilarious there's a reality
there for sure okay that's why I
that's why I'm hesitant to get to see the reality show
because it sounds too good
all right anyway Ben was saying something
okay
yeah I don't really make a habit of watching
reality shows I haven't seen that many but there are
some that I have really really
enjoyed I want to tell you
the first one the first one was
penny arcade strip search
which was not on tv it was a web series
and I should preface this by saying that I
don't really like penny arcade the comic
or find it funny at all and yet
I fucking love everything that
Gabe and Tycho do I think
like every interview with them and every
like I listen to their podcast
and I think that as dudes
they're just fucking awesome I love the shit
out of them and they decided
that hey we've got this fucking comic empire
and all this money let's just do
something and they decided to have a
reality show where they invited
all of these cartoonists all these bait
you know more or less unknown cartoonists
into a house
and they had them do challenges
and and fucking compete
to win like a spot like
basically like working in the penny arcade
office and like being like an official
penny arcade partner and
the thing about this show was
that Gabe and Tycho set out to make it
as like as
bog standard a reality
show as possible they wanted to direct
everything so that the artist would hate
each other and want to kill each other
and foster bitter rivalry
and drama but
they couldn't because they're weak
because Gabe and Tycho are weak bitches
and they did not have the fucking
emotional stones to carry through
with this plan of theirs
so what ended up happening is they all became
best friends and they all like loved each
other and like they all cried when they
left because they loved each other so much
and they couldn't bear to leave one another behind
it was that sounds like
a deconstruction of the whole
concept of reality shows
yes it was an unintentional
deconstruction of the whole concept
and it was fucking awesome
some of the challenges are really stupid
and some episodes are better than others
but like some of the
people in there were really great
and like a couple of them formed
beautiful friendships that continue to this day
I gotta tell you a bunch of
watching that show with you
a couple of more fucking
assholes though one or two of them were shitty
but just like watching some of these
kind of shittier people
make great comics and like bloom
it was like awesome it felt so good
to watch people be like
forced to get their shit together
and they did and then they won
oh man it was awesome like Maki
Maki was so cool
Maki wasn't my favorite
he's the first guy I thought of
thought of my head
Katie Rice was the best by the way
Katie Rice for life
alright you guys are getting too specific
I'm sorry
I've seen hundreds of
reality shows I know this
because I made a list of every TV show I've ever seen recently
and I was deeply disturbed
by a lot of the shows I had to include
on my list as having seen
the worst one
this was the absolute bottom of
the barrel show on my entire list
the one that I was the most ashamed to have seen one episode of
and Jesse
I feel like you've I think you've made
reference to this show before
rock of love with Brett Michaels
oh jeez
I don't know
if that's the spin off of Flavor of Love
or if it's the other way around
it was a spin off of Flavor of Love
yeah
well they all come from each other
like Brett and Michael's show came from Flavor of Flavishow
which came from the surreal life season 3
they all spin out of each other
it's a night tequila tequila one
a self perpetuating night tear
night tequila's from that too
I love New York
there
I've seen a lot of these fucking shows
because my mom has always been
really into just all of it
she'll watch all of it and the thing is
I think that the reason that reality shows are so popular
because I cannot
I cannot
tolerate them
every second of it is pain for me
and the reason is that they are
edited so fucking awkwardly
where like
you can just hear
they try to make it look real
but the more you know about filmmaking
the more you can't believe any of it
the thing that really gets me every time
is like how fucking obviously
they're manipulating your emotions
like if these things happen in real life it'd be like
oh he said this to me
even on like a production level
it's like you see all these people
and sometimes you're like
how can they have audio that good from where they are
like there's parts in Survivor
where they'll be out in the water
right and then they'll be talking to each other
but they'll film it from an angle where you can't see
their faces and they'll have
a conversation that
I know as someone who knows
how to make film you can't
have that conversation with that audio
because the only way to do it would be
if they had lapel mics and those wouldn't
survive in the water
the way that they're in the water
and the reason they're not filming them from the front
is because they're ADR'ing those lines in
they're adding in later
there's so much stuff that's falsified
or fake or it's edited weirdly
where they'll have someone giving like a speech
and you can hear where each part of the
sentence that they're saying is not one
sentence but you can tell that it's stitched together
I hear you dude I just have to defend
because the best one
the other example I know Ben was going to give
was the pickup artist
which is
that is the other one I was going to say
me and Ben were into that for a time back in the day
and this show was so
it was so important to me to see
it was powerfully emotional
it was the story of a bunch of
scared, helpless men
trying to make their
carve out a little piece of happiness for
themselves in the world and watching their growth
over the course of this series and them
becoming real fucking human beings
was beautiful and it was completely
real and the emotions that
mystery felt when they had to leave
it was like when they had to kick a guy out
it was like they're casting about
lonely men these were lonely men in need
of help but like the rules of the competition
dictated it one of them had to be
like it was hosted by mystery
mystery was like sad and emotional
when he had to kick some of them off
there's a huge gradient in quality between them
not all of them are equally terrible
I've always heard that RuPaul's Drag Race
is kind of like what you guys just described
where it's like a way more emotional and like
legit feeling show
it's just that so much of reality TV
is
like creating the same kind of
narratives that you could get anyways
like from a well made
show but trying to
make it well made god damn it
the idea the idea is
hey hey it's just as good
a narrative as a regular TV show
but it's real so that makes it better
except it feels even less real
because I can see the seams
so easily like every little thing
there's no seams in the pickup artist god damn it
look look okay I hear what you're saying and let's say that that's
true but the thing is though these
men were actually helped
by this show real good
was done to the world
I don't doubt that some of them are more real than others
and I will say that if we're doing
net shows my favorite one is
Thumbs Up which is a series
about these two Korean guys
who like um
stick their thumbs up and show their butts is that what it's about
no it's a pretty low budget
it's like a low budget internet
show where it was about these two guys hitchhiking
across the US and they did like
three seasons of it were like the first season
is they had to make it from
like from like Vegas
all the way to Florida only
hitchhiking or only taking free rides like they would
they would train hop a lot and do all this
like a like sleeping weird
fucking like run down places
in the middle of nowhere and like but their camera
man would travel like individually
like he would film them sometimes
on the road and then he would like drive to
stuff like that
and then they did one season where they went from
Texas to Alaska
and then the last like the third season
they crossed China all the way through hitchhiking
alone and I don't know if they ever did more
but like I don't know if that counts as
reality TV but it was definitely in the
vein of it but it was
show is probably don't count just cause like
I was talking about like the
shit that's on like network TV
like my mom watches like fucking
matchmaker which is fucking garbage
you know maybe we got a little way from Thomas
it's yeah well
I think it's worth mentioning those other shows
just because of the fact that
those like that shows how like
cause they're obviously inspired by reality TV
these internet shows that are much better
internet shows I just my internet cut out
everyone stop what's been said in the last
minute I didn't my internet died
taboo dude just
just calm down it's just nothing's
been said I
I thought it was a real thing of any
important thing I can't get into so
so yeah
I was gonna
wait until there was a good time I'm a big fan of
naked and afraid I want to talk about
how great that show is
from like a something about
it you know from a concept is amazing from
a philosophical standpoint it just touches
something primal deep inside me I mean
like this the whole concept of the
you take a man a woman they get naked
in the jungle they have to survive you know there's nothing sexual about it but then they
get to that point where it's at night and they got
a cuddle and they got a spoon and that's just
profoundly beautiful you know
that's what it's all about
that's what I've always wanted to watch
that's like my ideal vision for what the world should be
I think we should all be naked and afraid together
as opposed to
clothed and depressed alone
when the third impact
when the third impact comes
all this left are naked
Jesse and Fluttershy they will comfort
each other in each other's arms
or hooves and it will be beautiful
you know right taboo what was the thing you can't get into
yeah well I was thinking of
extreme makeover home addition
and that reminded me of something I can't get into
oh like house flipping shows
that one is all about like hey we need
there's this really tragic story
of this family and they have a shitty house and everyone
the entire universe comes together
to build them an amazing house
that show is literally like
everything every single element
of emotional manipulation you can
possibly imagine packed into one show
but there's two things about it
that really really get under
my skin about is the fact that
they have these kids in the show you know the kids
who were part of the family and they always
build them a room
that looks exactly like everything that
they want at that exact moment
which not only will they be embarrassed
to have when they're an adult
they'll be embarrassed to have next year
I hear you dude I hear you on this but that's just one
that always bothered me but then after watching
the show more I realized oh wait
wait hold on for a second here
these are people who are dirt broke
they can't afford this giant house
how is this happening
and I remember seeing like news stories
don't they like give it to them
well like how can they afford the bills
is the thing and I remember seeing
like I remember my mom saying there's like a news
story of like oh yeah one year later
this totally broke family is even more
broke having to pay property taxes
on this three-story house
oh dude and so one of the what here's what I
think one of the best things you can do is look
up the follow-ups of all reality show
people yeah nightmares there's a whole
website dedicated to what happened
to every kitchen nightmares
right they all become famous
yeah so this is what I can't get into
charity imagine the idea
of giving someone something I just think is
so imprecise so hard to figure out
the idea of giving
anything it's just like if someone gives
me something I'm like I can't more hardcore
you know I can't like if someone
gives me something I'm like I don't I wish you
give me this like it would have been better for everyone
if I feel the total opposite
I want everyone to give me everything
all the time please go to
patreon.com
everyone
I don't think I ever
everyone except for DeVoo because
we want money or not
I want absolutely everything
that anyone wants to give me I will
absolutely accept
a Lannister takes
what is that a thing they say
or takes what is
given I'm pretty sure
there's a good reason to give
but when I'm talking
about stuff like Christmas did you an elephant
never forgets that's not
I said pays his debts god damn it
the elephant family lives
in the southern islands
they're not from up
I'm 90% sure
and said a Lannister takes what is you know that's
interesting DeVoo I feel differently
I like the idea of charity
I just will never do it because I don't give a fuck
about anyone besides me
I'll definitely take you know
with Christmas
there's definitely an element of that to it Nate
but I'm also very distrustful
of the people that take charity
like I don't I do not trust
let's get to the heart of the matter
even if they offer me
even if they offer me statistics claiming
everyone without fail operates
in self interest whether they admit it or not
and every charity is there to make
at the very least to make you feel good about
doing it that is an unquestionable fact
if you want to give to a charity
do you want to feel about it
just put like a hundred dollars in your pocket
and walk around Chicago for an hour
and dole it out to bums
yeah the poor community will have that money
at least Lynn
at least you know that it's going to someone
like yeah
even if it's someone who's panhandling
who's like not a real bum
you know it's going to him
he earned it to have that money disappear out of your
wallet like that
it's not going to be an entrepreneur
something the way by the Susan G. Coleman foundation
to pay for their pink helmets and their stupid wrist bands
it's not even that like okay look
Patreon that's like
I mean that's it kind of belongs
in the same realm as like
your friends with someone and you go to dinner
and you pay the tab sometimes and sometimes they do
there's this there's like this
unwritten exchange
of benefit to one another
that you give that's what Patreon is
well that's why
the idea behind
charity is that
there is also
an unspoken thing which is that you
elevate someone's life and then
they no longer are fighting
and squalor to eat
and then maybe they turn out to be a great
artist because they can finally pursue their passions
but why don't they just fucking deal with it
like fuck them I don't care
I don't care about anything
well it's just it's like to me the
whole idea of
uplifting the lower
members of our society is that
it might benefit me in the long run
you're absolutely right and if I could
better everyone immediately however
I am not willing to lose even a single
cent of my own money to do so
I mean I don't blame you I don't
think it's necessarily true that
you're automatically like
I don't think that
the only means to the end of
people being better is giving them money
sometimes it means to that end
by the way I think no place on being a good person
I can't become a fan of
it's like something the idea of giving
something is like it's just one
of many great things to do
but it's not something that I ever think of
as something that's good in itself
and I think that the whole idea of like Christmas gifts
to adults doesn't work at least
for me there's just nothing
that anyone can find me
oh my god Christmas
Christmas gifts is such a
fucking like flash
here's what it is here's my theory about Christmas gifts
stupid waste of everybody
the whole tradition of giving people
gifts on Christmas was invented back in
like you know the 1800s
back when everyone made everything by hand
so that made a lot of sense
today everyone just buys stuff
so it doesn't make it doesn't make a difference
but I just want to say I like
I kind of like the idea of giving gifts on some
level just because oftentimes
you like will under no other
circumstances will you ever give the people you care about
anything I know that's true of me
I never give anyone anything
I'm forced to do nice things
for people I really do I really do
I feel like you would give gifts more
if there weren't obligations
to do so maybe maybe
I don't think I would
I would never give anyone anything
I had a fun moment
when I like once I was old enough
to have my own money and then Christmas
rolled around it was like exciting because it's like
an expression of the fact that I'm an adult
with his own income now that I can buy things
for people sure yeah
the person here just likes being nice
sometimes yes you're the only one
yeah probably
I just gave Hippo 116
dollars for his playing ticket
but Tom you're really doing it for yourself though aren't you
just to feel good about doing it
I'm not criticizing you
I think there's an element of both
in there
I'm going to visit my friend this week
and I'm giving her a computer
she doesn't have one so I'm giving her one
you're giving her one what
so you're going to smash that press right
I assume that's what's going on
I don't think of giving stuff to your friends
as being in the same realm as charity
because when you're giving stuff to your friends
it's deepening your bond
you're all sucking each other's dicks
and getting a good heart blowing
if you just give money to some kid
it's not going to suck your dick
what the hell kids suck my dick already
he got hit in explosion
and he doesn't have lips anymore
I bet even if he sucked my dick he wouldn't be good at it
personally though I just have an obligation
because my name is Digi Bro
and like the first time I did something
nice for someone after changing my name to that
they said like man he really
earned the bro in his name
and ever since then I feel like I have to do something
really nice for somebody every couple of months
so that I live up to Digi Bro
just so that more people will say that
Digi Bro give me some of that sweet Patreon
yeah
like I said I gave some to Hippo
but that was a sweet crunchy roll box
actually
4 or 5 months from now don't worry about it
everybody needs to get your plane tickets
by the way Hippo and DeVoo already have this
wait have we made a total announcement
about Radcon 2016
should we need to?
we don't need to
let's leave it a mystery for now
that's going to be too much of a mystery
you guys are just all going to
hey everybody we're going to have a
you're going to have a conference at my house
in September
by the way it's not a convention
it's not a real convention
none of you people listening are invited
don't get the wrong idea
it's Radconference
I'm considering a conference or a summit
but not a convention
in case anyone doesn't get the joke
Radcon Conrad
is a Digi's house
that's brilliant isn't it
someone still doesn't get it
who the fuck is Conrad
I feel like you're explaining it
made it way worse
anybody have anything else
we've been going for 3 hours
10 minutes
all I brought up was country
and classical music
and I guess old things
everyone in this chat is very mad
let's hear it
as soon as you said things that I didn't like
this was the first thing that came to mind
and I knew if I said it I'd get a mystery for it
oh boy
I want to hear it
it's punishingly difficult video games in the vein of Dark Souls
I fucking hate it
well that's an oxymoronic statement right there
Dark Souls is not punishing
how have you not heard the 5 million videos
that people have come out with saying Dark Souls
isn't punishingly difficult
this is a misunderstanding
how have you not heard that 5 times yet
yeah how
you fucking geek
well there you go
that's not how you do it
why are you even living if you're not playing Dark Souls
nothing in life is ever giving me joy
except for Dark Souls
punishingly difficult that's such a hacky phrase
I'm so sick of
punishing like what does it mean to be punished
does it literally spank you after you lose
there's no such thing as punishingly difficult
I hate that term by the way
wait wait hold on
you are fucking wrong
there is such thing as punishing
if you have ever played Banjo fucking Kazooie
when you die in that game
you lose every collectible you picked up in the whole level
and you have to start over
and if you lose 5 lives you have to start
from the fucking starting area of the game
it's way over punishingly difficult
I just hate it when Tom says it
I mean
it's such a hack
the best game ever
there's Crash Bandicoot
there's games like I wanna be the guy
which are deliberately punishingly difficult
so obviously punishingly difficult
IT is a thing but that's a Dark Souls
doesn't like that
the best game ever
is Banjo
Tui
I just don't think there's that many consequences
for dying in Dark Souls
the worst thing that happens
is you have to fight through the last
one minute again
it's fun because the combat is fun
so like I never feel like
I have to do something I don't wanna do
it's like oh boy
oh no I died and now I have to fight
the funnest level of all time
again
when you do it the 20th time it starts to get annoying though
well you shouldn't be that fucking shit
that takes you 20 tries
I'm the best gamer of all time
what makes Dark Souls hard to get into
way more than its difficulty
is just the steepness of its learning curve
the opaqueness of its UI and its systems
the fact that it doesn't explain how to play
that is definitely the hardest thing about Dark Souls
and I am pretty confident that Tom is at that point
and once you know how to play it it's fucking easy
welcome to the Dark Souls commentary
I have created a faith build
called Father Matosis
you can all tell me your sins
alright advice to the whole audience
if you want to be good at Dark Souls
put all of your levels into
vitality or not vitality
if it's Dark Souls 3 but vigor
and strength
just put all of it into your life and your strength
and then if you have a lot of life
then no matter how many times you get hit
it doesn't matter because you have a million life
and the enemies won't do anything to you
and if you have a lot of strength you kill them all in one hit
so then you just run through every level
with a huge sword
upgrade your weapons by the way
that's the other thing
upgrade your weapons and you're done
that's it
it's gay and so is home stuck
it's all bad
the only game that's good is the color yellow
Tom did you have more to say about that subject
before we all snapped on you
I mean
I guess to just move away from Dark Souls
and just like punishing the difficult games
quote unquote however you want to take that in general
I just
I don't like games
I mean
I play games to de-stress
not to get stressed
like there's a threshold where
I stop having fun that starts becoming a chore
and any game that goes too far
past that line
I feel like I'm just like not getting anything
I'm completely in agreement with you now
I absolutely despise punishing games
I just don't think of Dark Souls as
and I did before that's why it took so long
for me to play it but once I figured out how
it works then it was easy as fuck
I played Contra
DS and that game fucking sucked
cause it was just like it's impossible
no one can fucking beat Contra
you get hit once and you're dead
I tried playing Mega Man Zero
I played all of them and I loved them
and they were brutally difficult
but I beat them all just cause they were so fun
like
oh Mega Man Zero
I mentioned it in passing earlier
when everyone was yelling over each other
but like I legit quit Banjo-Kazooie
specifically I enjoyed
the game
but the way that it punishes you when you die
is so unbelievably severe
because of the fact
because you have to collect like for certain
jiggies and stuff it'll be like collect every music note
in the level and if you lose a life
you have to collect everything
over again like it gets rid of everything
you've collected and then if you lose 5 lives
it just arbitrarily
puts you in the very beginning
of the game like you just have to
walk back to where you were and it takes like
a long time so
anytime like there's certain like
pretty big steep difficulty curve
in the game where it gets pretty hard later on
and it's like it's not that the challenges
weren't fun but
it is an early N64 game
and sometimes you die to the camera
sometimes you die to the
you know like you attacked slightly off
from the enemy and then they hit you like there's a lot
of deaths that would be
forgivable if you were
instantly respawning and not losing everything
if we're defining punishing as just like
shittily designed and like
unreasonably
like a camera dad is punishing
well I think what Tom was talking about is
no reason
what I really mean is games
games that I've not having fun with
anymore games well I agree with that
I hate not fun games
really insightful Tom
I think what Tom was meaning is like
something harsh
here's the thing
that I feel about video games
is I have like an ungodly
amount of patience
I can sometimes
summon infinite patience
it must have been the way we came up
because I feel the same way Ben
okay okay like
like Newgrounds games that are like
you know the games where like you fire yourself out of a cannon
and like how far you go gets you more money
and then you use that money to buy upgrades to your
cannon I can spend like
entire days like
upgrading games like that
and like some
and like if I put in a significant amount of
effort collecting all those music notes in Banjo
Kazooie and I die you better
fucking believe I'm gonna do it all again
I don't care right now Ben is trying to get
the hundredth and final crystal and grow home
something that seems completely ridiculous to
the rest of us but he's
he's chugging away it's like it's a matter of
except for this last one it wasn't even
that hard okay the last like five or so
we're pretty fucking hard I think I love
hard games but only when it's
like every moment of it is fun
anyways I was just gonna say like for Ben
getting like the last five out of these hundred
like it's the bell curve of fun
has curved down so you're getting so little
fun for a time invested
on the one hand yes it's
true even if it's not fun anymore I
continue to do it I can't stop
on the other hand grow home is such a great
fucking game it's fun even it's fun to
just glide around and just being in the
game is enjoyable so that's still fun
because like there's like
the original Ninja Gaiden for the
original Xbox yeah you can't say the
original without meaning any
yes you have to say like the semi original
well he said for Xbox god damn it
he fakes me out for a second
yeah okay fine
why don't we just talk about every fucking
video game ever made
why don't we just make this an eight hour podcast
how about that why don't we just sit here
whatever Jesse do you fucking
you know you can you can dip out
and stop your recording if you watch
that's true holding you a gun no because
I wanted to make my final point I want
to make I want to I need to tell
say my final thoughts right well let us
get out of the way Tom hasn't been here
the whole time yeah trying to blow off
some stress from work every god fucking
princess Jesse over here
wait I want to hear about
I I I didn't know you guys
could hear me I was just muttering under
my I was
trying to
anybody no I uh
Tom I am curious
about this because of the fact that I know
you're a huge fan of like Ninja Gaiden
and Metal Gear Rising Revengeance
which by my metric are unbelievably
fucking hard games so
this is definitely not about hard games
Ninja Gaiden is definitely pretty difficult
yeah never like people were bitching
like when Devil May Cry 3 came out that it was super fucking
hard and I didn't think it was hard at all
like oh yeah destroyed that game
and everyone's like this is hard
so it it's
but like there are other games that I'll find
fucking really difficult so it's weird
and I want to like Dark Souls
because everybody here likes Dark Souls but
every time I play it I'm just not enjoying
the gameplay at all Tom with Tom if you played Bloodborne
yet are you are you leveling up
are you upgrading your weapons I've only played it
for a little bit but even just like the way
the game moves away your character moves the way
heavy heavy it takes time to get used to it
I don't have a ps4 anymore
oh yeah well I think
you would enjoy Bloodborne a lot more than
the other games because of the fact that
I think you might enjoy way faster
Dark Souls 3 because that's a lot faster as well
well Bloodborne in particular has
like a more aggressive like
Metal Gear Rising or
or like
Devil May Cry-esque feel to it
I don't know if anyone's going to disagree
with me on that I had this very long
argument in the past about
how I think Bloodborne is
after watching that video of Matthew Matosis
analyzing the first Devil May Cry it looks
a lot like Bloodborne in the sort of
yeah it has the same like I
yeah like the attack animations
I definitely see where you're coming from
like even though it plays like Dark Souls
it's a lot faster and it's
less punishing on your health where enemies just
do less damage and it's
more about regaining health because like
in that game every time an enemy hits you
if you hit them back within a certain
amount of time then you regain all the health
that they took from you which is a great
mechanic yeah which is a lot like Metal Gear Rising
where if you
kill enemies in a certain way you regain your health
so it's got some of that
spectacle fighter aspect to it while
still being the free form
open world RPG that Dark Souls is
and I think that
Bloodborne in spite of being
I don't think it's easier than the other games
but I think it's so much easier
to get the point and be like oh yeah
this is fun which is why
Aaron Hansen got into the Souls series
through that game because he totally
didn't get the point until that one and then it was like
oh now it all makes sense and then went back
and played all the others and that's how I
experienced it too so
maybe Bloodborne would be a good entry point
for you if you ever find a chance to play it
I need to get a PS4 again at some point
because now there's actually games coming out again
Did you like sell it to Nate or something?
I sold it to Nate because you wanted to get the new Kingdom Hearts
because you were hyped for Kingdom Hearts
Oh like that's gonna happen
you're gonna need the PS4K by the time that fucking
game comes out
possible possible
specifically because I remember going out
I believe I got the PS4 from you
specifically because Bloodborne was coming out
and I wanted to be there
Hey Nate remember that time you bought the PS3 for Kingdom Hearts
I do remember that
I remember buying, I have a purge in my life
three PS3's with the intention of playing
Kingdom Hearts 3
oh god just fucking kill me
Why did you betray me Square Enix
Why would you do this to me
Shit in the fucking head
Yeah, yeah I'm rolling in my fucking grave right now
Jesus Christ
Alright Jesse
I got, yeah
Okay
Well, well guys
It sure has been a great podcast
but it's time for my final thoughts
It's time to nuke this baby
It's been great being friends with you all
but it's time for my final thoughts
on yellow
Yeah, okay
I don't have the energy
I don't have the energy to talk to you anymore
This is the greatest podcast I've ever been a part of
Guys
This is the most I've ever enjoyed a podcast
Digi, you have to give this video another
Yeah
I'm going to make the opening song
It's going to be Coldplay
I promise you
All the people out there in the world listen to this
All the, you know, impressionable youngsters
who may hear these people's bullshit
and believe it because you don't know any better
I just want to set you straight
I just want to let you know
yellow is actually
my favorite color
This is true, you know
I actually knew that
You know, I love
Starboard bow is yellow
Yes, right
I love Fluttershy
I love Oscar's yellow dress
Episode 8 of Neon Genesis
Who doesn't
I love bananas
I love all the yellow things
Yellow, such as myself
Yellow is 30
That's a fallacy
No, shut up
You don't know
Guys
I've been
I've been down with yellow for a long time
If my videos
If I had a video that was yellow
It would be because I purposely made it
yellow and seeing as how I did not
purposely make a video yellow
could not have been yellow
Did you feel when he claims that
I just say that I get video games more
than everyone else because I am the best at them
Yeah
That doesn't, you know
Tasting your own medicine
I think we all do it
I think we're all fucking terrible people
It's true
I'm just saying that since we've established
that I am the best guy
at determining what is yellow
and what is not the best guy at finding it
Yeah
If your victory for this argument
is that we have to accept that you
decide what is yellow, I'm down
I'm honestly down
I will accept that we're all going to change
the definition of yellow to fit Jesse's
definition of yellow
Yellow's
Yellos are formative
You know
Patreon one
Yes, Jesse
You know, that's one way to put it didgy
but you know, the more accurate way would be
to say that you should all be done
changing the definition of yellow
and you should go back to what it actually is
which is and has always been my definition
of yellow, which is the actual color yellow
not the color of my video
It's a simple formula, kids
It's a simple fact of the world
So what color are your videos
The color is normal, right?
Normal color
My videos are definitely normal
You know, and you know
And that Christmas video
in particular, you know
It was really looking normal in that one for sure
You know, I'm going to have to
I'm going to have to download
Dude, I just smoked some weed
I got to go into my color packs
on my computer and download normal
like a font pack and throw it in there
So I can make stuff in Jesse's
style if I ever need to
It's funny that you're trying to make
my argument sound so
go out there by claiming
that normal is like some color
that I'm saying something so crazy
when I just say that the video looks normal
It looks how the human eye actually detects
what the world looks like
I'm not talking to rocket science
in rooms with fluorescent light
It does look like what a podcast has been
I see such a fucking gauntlet
I can't believe it's still happening
Why to you
Is it yellow?
Is my question
Is it just because it's not actually
full yellow? There is a delta
in the yellow value of the image
Right there, he said it people
You heard it right from the horse's mouth
Just because it's not yellow doesn't mean
it's not yellow You don't understand how color works
in fucking video goddammit
There's a gulf between the yellowness
These guys are saying it's something
These guys argument that because it's not
ROY G BIF
There it is, we all live in our own realities
We all have our own
ideas about the world
And if one of us thinks
that one thing is yellow
and everyone else thinks it's something else
We can't tell that person they're wrong
Really, I mean we can say that they don't
agree with the general consensus
But it's no different than saying that something
is good
Good is in the eye of the beholder
Yellow is in the eye
of the beholder of yellow
We can't tell a man what is or isn't yellow
We can only tell him what we perceive
And just as some people might say
well there's a god
And therefore morality is determined
by what my god says
The next guy who doesn't believe in that god
will say you're wrong
And neither one you can really
say is right
I mean you can have scientific observations
to back your claims
But who's to say that science is correct
So there's really no way of disproving
that the beholder isn't yellow
by each individual person's standards
Roy G Biv
Introduce yourself to my buddy Roy G Biv
Jesse, I was going to teach you a thing or two
You ever played Smash Bros
when you're winning with Roy and the Kraus
by devolving into chaos
But what they don't realize is that I am prepared
to do this all day
Jesse, I will make a ten hour podcast
The Endless Podcast
Okay, Jesse, I have a question
that can be answered with yes, no, or
no
Okay, I'll give you the question, alright
In that visualization
that I showed you where I compared the colors
of your face and your beard and your eye
from a natural lighting shot
to a fluorescent lighting shot
and you see the individual colors
and there's the color on the left
is the color in your basement
Are those colors
more yellow, yes, less
yellow or the same amount of yellow
Does he even have that image?
The same amount of yellow to view, which is none
None yellow, okay
That's objectively
incorrect, yeah
You realize that light is made out of a combinate
There's one thing that really
I feel like we have a different opinion on what is a color
We need to get to the root
of this whole thing
Here's the problem though
I want to be able to
tell Jesse that there's a spectrum of light
by saying that light
Oh, there's a spectrum, alright, and he's on it
But the only problem, the reason why
that argument isn't going to work
is that the light spectrum is red, green, and blue
so it doesn't involve yellow
so he's going to not even accept that
as an argument
Don't computer monitors use like
blue, purple
monitors only use
monitors is RGB
It's cyan, yellow, magenta
spectrum
We've experienced the entire spectrum
in this podcast for sure
That's what happens when we all come together
It's true
Maybe all of our different perceptions of colors
is determined by our different levels of autism
Maybe that's why we don't all see it
Yeah, exactly
I have no autism
and so I
I don't see any yellow because I'm not autistic
unlike the rest of you
That's exactly right, did you
That picture that you made
Yes, obviously
the colors in the two pictures were different
but neither of them were yellow
in any way
Jesse, so are you saying that the other one looks blue to you?
No, what the fuck?
Because if something is less yellow
it's more blue
I had a feeling we were going to get to this
at some point and it was going to make it even worse
Light comes in two forms, yellow and blue light
Those are the two kinds of light
No, you idiot
Light comes in one form
White or else it's dark
No, there's a rainbow
of color
There's a rainbow, but the thing is
when light is normal, light is really shy
the colors are really shy
You need a prism which excites them
and makes them feel emboldened in their actions
It's like alcohol for people
This is like teaching
kindergartners
You guys are trying
to use alcohol as an example
Jesse, do you think that
just because that image
captured by your camera
is what it looked like in real life
does that to you mean that it isn't yellow?
No, Ben
What makes it not look like yellow is the fact
that it does not look like yellow
I'm looking at my room right now
I don't know why this is so complicated
for you people to grasp
I don't know how anyone can be this retarded
that you people just can't understand
that it simply does not look like yellow
This is not rocket science
This is not open heart surgery
It does not
I repeat, does not
look like yellow
I just don't believe in this idea that there is a
normal look
like everything is affected by the light source
that is on it
Jesse, I'm gonna fucking take this picture
Jesse, I'm gonna print this picture out
and take it around
and fucking Steve Harvey game shows
Ben, that's pointless
and go around to 100 people
on the screen and be like
what fucking color does this look like
and 99 out of 100
will look like you're a crazy person
because it doesn't look like a color
it looks like a fucking picture of a guy
What the hell man?
Pictures don't have colors
Dude
What?
You see, I think that most people believe this
I'm going to red sweater
I've got frost on my face
The video itself is not happy
You guys are out of your fucking minds
There is no way to prove or disprove
someone else's reality as
I am less real than you
So it's always an argument that everyone's
perceiving a reality as a fight
and there's no victory
There's no way to convince someone else that
they're seeing something wrong
Yeah
So I don't think there's such thing
as an objective truth about what's yellow
Like I said, yellow is
And it's one or the other
Neither is helping your case
A cacophony
It's a cacophony of sound, that's true
But we do it, it's a cacophony
Yeah
You know, the burden of proof is on you guys
I'm proving it
This is more evidence
I'm taking the color of your face
in the basement videos
and then I have a list of shades of yellow
and there's one shade of yellow in particular
that's pretty ding...
I know but it's pretty ding similar
out of only like 30 that are listed
Here's what I'm going to do
I'm going to take the picture
I'm going to put it in fucking manga studio
I'm going to blend the entire picture
into a single solid hue
and then I'm going to post that hue and you guys are going to look at it
and tell me what color does it fucking look like
I'm going to fucking see that
It's almost like if you change the picture
it'll be something different
It's not going to work, Jesse won't believe it
because you altered the picture, it's not real
I'm only going to use the blur tool
and nothing more
and I don't care if Jesse doesn't find that valid
It's not valid
I think everyone's desperation to win this
is really fucking hilarious
What's your response to this?
I want your rebuttal of this
This is a shade of yellow that looks very similar
to your skin in your basement videos
No, that's a shade of skin
that looks similar to my skin
You dumb fuck
Hey guys, guess what, Jesse
You're promoting racism because skin used to be a name of a color
for Crayola crowns
Skin, which is white people skin
that was racist
so they got rid of it
You're saying that yellow looks normal
because your skin is tangy
Your logic is getting pretty out there
How else am I supposed to rebut, Jesse
You're not supposed to rebut it
because there is no rebuttal
Jesse doesn't think it's yellow
Nothing is going to change that
We're all insane for arguing with him
but I find it so funny
that I can't stop
and I've also wasted
and I just love this podcast
I'm shocked, I'm shocked and appalled
by your guys insistence
on trying to rationalize your insane belief
that this fucking picture of me
is yellow
It's not in comparison
It has a yellow
hue tint to it
There's an overture of yellow
It's not even playing songs related to this argument anymore
He's just playing She's So Heavy by The Beatles
This conversation is fucking heavy
It's weighing on my soul like a fucking anchor
Does anybody have anything else that they can't get into?
Are we wrapping this up?
I hope this conversation haunts you all
for days to come
I hope you see my face in your nightmares
and I hope my face in your nightmares looks yellow
Motherfucker, because that's the only place
it's ever going to look yellow
is in your own sick imaginations
just like in your imaginations right now
You know what this video should mean?
I know how we can end this
I was just talking with Idol Yo-Kai
about this argument
and she says
that Jessi's videos look yellow
Oh, there you go
Why does that matter?
I'm just going to fade out this podcast
Why does that matter, Tom?
We had to sync with Tom
It's a funny thing that you mentioned Idol Yo-Kai
and I'll tell you exactly why
and I want everyone to gather around
and listen to this little tidbit
because Idol Yo-Kai is currently
drawing a picture for me
and I said to her
and this is a true story
I said I want my sunglasses
to be yellow
and guess what
Oh boy, I'm on board
She gave me her picture
and the sunglasses were wrong
the sunglasses were black
so she doesn't know what yellow is
Okay?
So I win!
That's it! Thank you!
Thank you for proving my point
The opening for this podcast should be
I win!
Guys, we need to sync with Tom
You've drawn your hat into the ring
with fools
Tom, on the count of three
we all say shit breaks
One, two, three
shit breaks
You know, what's really crazy is
one, two, three
shit breaks
You know what else we haven't even brought up
We just amplify this even more
Wait, everybody, everybody, everybody
Say goodbye
Bye
Yeah
I'm supposed to
be working
right now
But I'm not working
I'm doing nothing
My dick, I'm jerking
Myself, I'm sucking
I am an asshole
I am a stupid
I've got a deadline
Don't want to do it
I am an asshole
I am a stupid
I've got a deadline
Don't want to do it
What the hell is wrong with me?
I'm supposed to
be making money
be creating
funny
Think that the people
gladly will pay
for artistic
genius
That's what they came for
Instead, I'm tweeting
hashtag repeating
That's why
there's no heat
and holes in the ceiling
Yeah
It's quite the burden
It's a hard knock life
Being
a genius