Hello everyone, and welcome back to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
TPC, PCP, that is what I want for me, and welcome back. I'm the best guy ever, and we're joined by Hippocrit.
Hey, the SleepTight Bandcamp is up, and you can get the Gay for a Day album right now over on sleeptight.bandcamp.com. Link in the description.
I listened to it. It was a heck of a time.
We got Munchy. It sounds better than the live one. True.
You know, guys, I was having like a really good day today. Like, you know, like I woke up in my bed, just to further clarify, my race car bed.
And like, I just looked around my beautiful room full of posters of bitches, all legs spread.
And I came up the starting gate knowing it was going to be another great day being straight.
But what's this I see in my Discord? Oh, it's the PCP? Oh, I'm feeling a little bit gay, guys.
I'm a little bit like, homosexual right now. Oh, God, I think I might be turning gay for a day right now in this Discord call.
Major cringe, my dude. Major cringe. We've got Tom Oliver.
Look, as somebody who's gay every day, I'm offended by the fact that you're taking my identity and leveraging it for fame and musical shenanigans.
Unbelievable fame.
I suspect you're a gay trender, Munchy. A mere gay trender.
I know. It's fashionable to be gay right now, so I'm doing it. I mean, if it were fashionable to wear the color red, you would do so.
I do want to give it a deep look. I'm red for a day.
You're going to be sleeping tight in your grave when I'm through.
Oh, dude, I'm red for a day. I say turn into bin sain, except I never become not bin sain.
There he is, Ben.
Oh, yes. And hey, guess what? If you're listening right now, the next episode of Grimp is out. I'll link that in the description.
Go listen to Grimp, too.
What does Grimp mean? Is there a meaning behind that?
Wouldn't you like to know?
Oh, I dearly would, but I never will.
Yeah, that's right.
If I listen, will I find out?
You'll just have to listen and find out whether you'll find out.
I guess that's true.
Damn, that's double-layer marketing.
I also have a thing to say, so it's not out yet, but okay, here's a larger subject.
So it's just that, no, this is all good, and you'll be probably happy slash excited to hear it.
It's just that I am currently working on a project with one, my work is done.
I have a not nearly as much work as he does.
Best anime ever goes in the shell? Yeah, we know. You've been working on it for like five years.
No, no, no, not that. I'm working on something with one Nexus Mania artist, professional human being.
He makes his living being a human being.
If you haven't read them, they're comics by Nexus Mania and they're fucking good.
Yes, he is very talented. He does animation stuff.
He did a couple of things for, like, he did the Weagua opening animation I used at one point.
I know him for the cork-cursed background.
Very true, very true. He does the art for the podcast most of the time.
Now, I was very explicit. We've been talking about a project of his for a long time,
and I clarified what I'm allowed to say because a lot of it's secret, but I am doing voice acting.
This is an actual voice acting gig. I will be receiving money for this work, which is very exciting.
And my part's all done. There's other bits left to be done. It's a pretty big animation project.
It is an animation that Nexus is doing. I'm extremely excited about it.
I think it's going to be dope as hell. Script is pretty sick, pretty tight, and it's got me as the only people who matter.
Can we have a hint as to what the nature of this animation is?
I don't think I'm supposed to say even any details as to what the story is about or who's involved with it.
Is it like an anime OP? Is it like a music video or is it like a show?
It's like its own little contained story of Nexus's that he wrote and he's been working on.
It's its own thing, but it's very funny, it's very meta, it's very cool,
and I have no doubt that the animation will be stellar when it's complete.
It's pretty short, probably only going to be like, I don't know, less than maybe like five minutes long.
But for an animation, that's pretty sizable.
I know this probably isn't it, but being a huge fan of Bunny Wave, I kind of wish it was the date that's going to happen in the arc of Bunny Wave
and you were voicing Max, the fucking cringelord guy who tries to be really cocky and popular at school,
but he's actually super insecure, which is basically you anyways.
Bunny also kind of shares that, but yeah, true, but I won't even say if it's that or not,
but it's something and it's coming in by the end of August, I think it's the deadline.
By the end of August sometime, that'll be out and I could not be more excited about it.
Love you Nexus, keep up the good work, thanks for the money.
Well, as we all know, anything that's talked about in the PCP by Nate doesn't come out, so...
That's like six weeks away.
I know, I know, he's got a lot of work ahead.
Alright, well Grimp is out now, and guess what?
The topic, yeah, so what's two in the hand, one in the bush, whatever.
And the topic is, should we, aka Grimp, talk about politics?
So there you go.
We can keep it contained, yeah, we can keep it quarantined.
A discussion about if you even should discuss politics.
Yes, the question is should we.
I find that a relevant and interesting discussion.
Actually, that's a discussion I am interested in having in general.
Find out, find out what we conclude right now.
Unlike this fucking animation that will never happen.
Six weeks, the fucking world will have ended by then.
You know Nexus talks sometimes.
Climate change!
Yeah, oh fuck.
When I was talking to Nexus, he was just like, yeah, you know, just doing my work for, he does like...
I think it's called Dragon Ball R&R, which I shamefully have never actually checked out,
but apparently is good.
Nexus works on it, so I assume it is.
But he was just like, yeah, I just didn't sleep last night, just like worked all night.
I was like, oh, is that your life?
Sorry about that.
Maybe change, maybe do something differently.
That's a life of every artist who tries.
If you want to get anywhere in the world, you just have to give up.
You have to give up on having any life at all.
There's nothing in this world I hate more than staying up all night.
I hate it so much.
It's not that bad.
It's honestly not that bad.
No, that's just your youth buff.
I need to wear it out in about five years.
I need to hashtag sleep tight, if you know what I'm saying.
I have no idea what you're saying, in fact.
Listen, I've developed ever since...
I relate to you all the story of this war, ARG, that I worked tirelessly on throughout the nights.
And ever since then, my life...
The only thing that curbed this was Hippo, but before then, I was just staying up for a day,
then going up for another day.
So I would just be awake for 24 hours, if not more.
Sleep for 12 hours, 36 hours, 36 hours, just over and over and over again.
And that just was my life.
And you know what, honestly?
Pretty good. I liked it. It was pretty good.
It had a lot of fun.
I think staying up all night might be human core.
Yeah.
No.
And I think it's something that I'm guilty of.
Is that like post-human core?
Because you're deviating from our natural biological urges?
I think it's something that...
Well, I mean...
There was some discussion on Twitter about what is...
Being human core means you can deviate from what you're literally naturally inclined to do.
I mean, human core pertains to society, pertains to civilization.
Because the whole point of being a human is that you're not following animal instincts.
I would say staying up is human core.
Sleeping normal eight hours is animal core.
Okay, there was a debate between I'll die of I'll die corp and Dax tier on Twitter.
And Dax tier said human core is following your base instincts.
And I'll die said human core is what separates a human from the animal.
So it's the exact opposite of that.
Yeah.
And I'm more inclined to think that it is about base instincts.
But that's not all it is.
Because like tradition, following traditions and like culture,
like traditional culture is human core.
Like going to church is human core.
Is there like a social human core and a biological human core?
And agriculture is human core.
The way I use human core, and I speak as an authority as the most human core person on Earth,
I use human core as a distinctress from the animals.
You should buy my human core shirt available at teespring.com slash human core.
Which is why I say the two things that you have to do to become a human are
is own a dog and eat bed.
And also buy my shirt.
Also buy his shirt.
What if I eat rice instead of bread?
What if I'm an ass bread?
I think that's difficult.
Okay.
That's just another bread.
My onigiri and I'll chow down.
Rice is just lots of little loaves of bread.
Yeah.
Natural bread.
Oh, you know what?
Oh my God.
Okay, actually that launches me directly into the other thing I wanted to talk about today.
And you will love this.
Guys, be ready to salivate.
Be ready to jerk your own dick.
You know what?
Honestly, I don't think I will.
I do that every episode.
It's that.
Okay, so Michelle got like an Amazon prepared meal box dish.
A cured one from the ether.
And I personally 100% cooked that meal from start to finish.
And this was.
This was sale.
Is this just...
Yeah, go on.
So fresh for Amazon.
I was just gonna say, is this just Hello Fresh by another name?
That's exactly what this is.
Okay, then I won't explain my feelings about it because you are...
We know.
We have made them perfectly clear in the past.
All right.
But why is it an Amazon version of why not just go with Hello Fresh?
Well, I mean, because she got this for free.
This was free.
So like she just got it.
Because Amazon, having more money than anyone else, can corner every market and therefore
do everything cheaper than everyone else and therefore kill all competition.
Absolutely true.
That's what we call the free market.
That is one way that it operates, which is suboptimal.
Totally agree.
But the point being, so it's basically Hello Fresh, just whatever.
Amazon variant.
It was like a sweet and spicy shrimp over, I think it was like...
What was the word?
Marbled couscous.
Something like that.
It wasn't marbled.
It was like...
No, it was called fucking...
Oh, purled.
It was called over like seasoned purled couscous.
That's the word that they used.
What is purled?
It's like more spherical couscous.
I think it's made of rice couscous and it's like round...
No, it's basically just a rice.
Just think of it as rice.
Yeah, it's like the same thing.
Is it literally made from rice?
Is that accurate?
I don't think so.
It's functionally the same as rice.
Was it purled or pearl couscous?
I believe it said purled with a D, purled adjective.
Okay.
And okay, I don't know why, but okay.
This required me, your boy, BGE Nate,
literally the most human corpsman on the planet now.
Now that I've done this.
Okay, yes, sure.
I have...
You prepare two separate things.
On the one, you prepare this delicious multi-stage shrimp ragu
where you, individually, you grill the shrimp.
Nothing like a good ragu.
Oh, yeah, tell me about it.
You prepare the shrimp, you grill it, you move it aside,
then you put in all the vegetables,
you grill your onions, you grill your peppers,
you grill your various other things that were with that.
You pour on your seasonings and shit.
You cook all that, you marble it up real nice.
Then you pour in the tomato paste or whatever it is,
and then you stir all that together.
You make your ragu slop.
Then you re-add the fucking shrimp back into it,
which has already been cooked to perfection
and browned into a golden, crispy dream.
You warm that all up.
You put the shrimp back in, you warm it back up.
That's your ragu.
On the other side, you're preparing your couscous,
which is you put in a pot, you don't use water.
You use what was referred to as, I think it was called clam moisture.
No, no, it was like clam water or something like that.
What the fuck?
It was like clam juice or something like that.
It's the equivalent of using like a chicken stock or something.
Yeah, there I am.
Exactly.
There I am.
Fucking some Islander ride, some native Islander.
Yeah.
Plying my national trade, I dive deep into the coastal coral reefs
and I go down and I pick up clams and I bring them to the top
and I crack them open into a bucket
and I find the pearls within and I throw them in the garbage
and I squeeze out that sweet, sweet clam moisture.
That's where the money's at.
That's basically what happened.
So you pour in that stock or whatever,
you pour in the couscous, you just cook that
and that cooks down and absorbs all the water.
You just have this delicious little marbles of couscous.
And then I think what makes it, what did I say?
A pearl.
Is that you just pour in, like you just put butter,
like a little thing of butter that comes in there
and then you sprinkle like it's oregano.
I think it was oregano.
You just stir that and oh my god,
that was the most delicious looking, shiny little marbles of couscous
I've ever seen with the oregano all over it.
And then once those two separate things are cooked,
then you combine them in the bowls that you are serving with.
You put your couscous on the bottom,
10 out of 10 looks incredible,
and then you pour your shrimp ragu.
In the middle of two, it was, it was an absolutely
incredibly delicious meal.
But I would have traded it all away
for another 45 minutes of precious Minecraft playtime.
I could have gotten so many diamonds
instead of preparing this fucking meal.
I regret it so intensely.
I don't give a shit about food.
I want my Minecraft stats back.
I want, I could have been building a tower.
I could have been building sky towers
and connective shit, it's connective tissue
to make my world more optimal to optimize towards Starfleet.
What a fucking waste it was making this fucking meal,
even though it was like the best meal I've had
in the last six months or so.
So that was great.
The best meal you've had in six months.
Well, I went to like the best restaurant sincey,
that was better.
But like the best one I've had like at home,
and it was incredible.
It was delicious.
You've been pulling what you accused Digi of last episode,
which is just saying like the most basic things
of all time and then sounding like you've found out
like the secrets of the universe.
Like an unbrewable revolution about what's happening.
I describe in such glowing terms cooking,
and then I counter that by saying,
I wish I'd played Minecraft.
That's the joke.
And you, sir, are not recognizing the joke.
I understood that you wasted your time
because you don't know how to cook effectively,
because you're following this.
Well, I did cook effectively.
I did exactly what the recipe said.
This is this bullshit Amazon fucking
what are you talking about?
Fisher price, goddamn recipe.
This was the most efficient cooking process of all time.
Munchie, have you come over to my side
on the Hello Fresh issue?
No, well, okay, what I'm trying,
Ben, what I've said a thousand times is that I agree with you.
All I've ever said is that there is a reason
why some people would want to use Hello Fresh.
All I ever said, all you ever said,
don't tell me you don't have like your stock.
You don't have, you're not speculating in stock
in Hello Fresh right this second.
I, listen, I used to be a Hello Fresh person.
Convert all your Bitcoin to Hello Fresh stock.
And then I haven't needed Hello Fresh
in like six months, like Hello Fresh is dead to me.
I have no more use for it.
Okay, all right, good.
Hey guys, ready for this gem?
This was just commented.
Wait, wait, I want to say a little cooking story
because like, I'm not like, I don't do my research.
I don't study recipes.
I know how to cook very basic things.
I don't know things, I don't understand stuff
and I don't comprehend how I like it.
And I've been like, just sort of like,
passively being interested in cooking
because Munchie is also interested in it
and it's sort of like rubbing off of me.
Really?
Ooh, that's really nice to hear.
Yeah, just like through the past few months.
I mean, I know your guys would do it too.
Oh yeah, well the thing is dad cooks so much
that it's never really an issue for me to need to cook.
But I wanted to like learn how to just cook rice well.
And I try to make like,
this brand new invention called rice
with a fried egg on the top of it.
Oh, nice.
And I made a thing of rice and I had the rice
and I fried an egg and I fried it bad
and the yellow, the yolk cracked and then I just put it on top.
I think they call that recipe sunrise
over the sunrise kingdom.
That's like rice to pan, you know?
I'm pretty sure that is actually
like a real Japanese dish, fried egg on top of rice.
I think that's called moon over Miami.
Oh no, I've seen it in anime
and I've also eaten a bowl of rice and stuff
with an egg on top.
You know, when I was in college,
I just cracked a raw egg into a thing of rice.
It was like the most disgusting thing I've ever eaten,
but I've seen it in anime.
Because I saw it in anime and I was like, that makes sense.
If the rice is hot, then the egg will cook.
This did not cook.
Right, well, yeah, there's definitely a technique to it.
Yeah, I mean, if egg fried rice was easy to make,
I would make that. Oh, I love that.
That's good.
That's not even hard, dude.
It's not hard, but it requires like more
than just a frying pan and nothing else.
Well, I mean a bowl, but like, that was my cooking story.
I just made a rice and put egg on it
and I didn't have the runny yolk,
so it was kind of lame and boring and I ate all of it.
But, you know, it didn't take very long
and I got some, you know, some energy from it.
So I don't even think it was that bad.
Dude, think about how many diamonds
you could have gotten instead of doing that.
I want to circle back to Nate here,
because I mean, I believe that everyone
can benefit from cooking in some way.
And then I think that what you're doing
is not the way that cooking can benefit you, Nate,
because it's not about, there's no one way to cook, right?
There's no one benefit you get from it.
And so the idea of being able to, you know,
perfectly make the exact, you know, fancy meal
and take all fucking day to do,
that's not what would appeal to you or benefit you in any way.
Well, you could see that would benefit you,
is there are recipes and there are ways to cook
and just make food that are far faster, far cheaper,
and also able to be far more healthy
than getting alternatives, like ordering in,
or, you know, or getting delivery.
I'll stop you right there, Munch,
because you're absolutely right.
And my boy Scooby, fitness God,
has an extensive series about him
who can barely cook at all,
but he has tons of like fitness-oriented meals
that they take like five minutes to make
and they are delicious
and eating out is a waste of money and mostly money,
and you shouldn't do it pretty much ever.
So I couldn't agree more,
and that's the kind of shit that,
when I was at my physical peak,
I was cooking myself those kind of meals,
like, I mean, every single day,
I made my own food and stuff.
That's a great segue.
I just want to do it too.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay, sorry.
Then wait your turn.
I was just going to say like the whole rice thing.
I feel like I'm going on like a very slow,
like inefficiently slow journey of discovery,
because a few weeks ago,
I did a bowl of rice with some baked beans in it,
and the baked bean juice was really nice.
Earlier than that, I did just a bowl of rice,
and I was like, there's not enough flavor.
So I've been adding, you know, one thing at a time,
learning how to do like very basic baby shit,
but each time it's still a whole bowl of rice,
and that's like very filling.
So if you want to like cook without a lot of like prep
or like hassle, you know, you like beans,
just do a beans and rice thing,
and learn how to make it really efficiently,
and then maybe make it in bulk,
and then just reheat it.
Make it in bulk.
Oh, dude, okay, speaking of making it in bulk here,
hippo, I've got your next big target here.
I've got like a bounty for you,
putting down a wanted for risotto.
If you're being like a rice god,
if that's the new way that you're taking your life,
make a risotto because it is delicious,
and it is risotto.
It is an Italian dish that you probably have heard of.
I've heard of it.
And it is delicious.
Dude, risotto, just like in the movies.
Literally.
Me and a guy, me and a guy, I used to know,
we had a little running joke between us,
and the running joke was simply that when we saw Pepsi,
we would say, wow, Pepsi, just like in the movie.
That's a pretty good joke.
Those are rich folks in their Pepsi in the movies.
Dude, yeah.
Okay, speaking of bulk,
and also being at your physical peak,
I'm lifting again for real.
I've heard all about it.
I'm squatting and deadlifting and going nuts,
and I think I've done like three workouts so far,
and that's enough to establish a pattern.
Three is a pattern.
I'm so fucking jealous of you.
I was doing so good with my fucking working out
before my spine broke into pieces.
That's understandable.
I was doing so bad with it.
I feel...
Until Tom's spine broke, and then you got inspired.
You're still my juju, you bastard.
Yeah, yeah.
I was, you know, well, haha.
There could only be one fit person.
I have to break this guy's spine.
What about Nate?
Yes, you had more to gain from killing Nate than killing me.
Nate just like looks at it.
Nate lives further away, therefore.
I'm a cream puff.
I'm all flash, no substance.
Nate's the final boss.
You have to like...
Ben's like Goku.
He wants to fight Frieza at his highest power,
so he has to let Nate stay strong.
Yes.
We're going to get the fat Nate song.
That's what I'm waiting for.
It's never going to happen.
I dream of the day.
I got lads.
I've been tracking my calories like a hawk
the last two weeks.
I'm down roughly four pounds or so,
and it's just smooth sailing down to my...
I will look like a god when I'm at my 170th target.
I'm just the perpetual flab fag at this point.
I just can't fix it.
You will lower your calories, I guess, Starve?
Just, okay.
Let me just clarify.
If you actually have a calorie target people out there
that think it's so hard to not eat right,
let the...
Calories is the big, the cheap way.
Just like eat your calories.
It's all you got to do.
Just track what you eat in one day.
You will instantly in one day be like,
wow, I'm sure fucking up, and then it's so easy.
Once you understand what you're dealing with,
you'll be like, oh, I can easily not eat that.
I'll just eat this instead.
Once you do that, that's why the whatever diet
is so powerful.
It just makes you aware.
Being conscious is the most important thing.
I have a general question about that.
Just don't eat bulk grains.
Even if you're not keto, right?
I mean, I like keto, but even if you don't want to go
full keto, stop eating bulk grains.
Stop eating bread, stop eating rice.
I'm never doing this again,
pretty much for the rest of my life.
I would just be like, hey, I'm hungry.
Oh, a loaf of bread.
I could, one of the things I'll do,
I'll just eat pieces raw.
I'll just do that for a while.
I'll make bread or toast.
That's a great snack, right?
It's so easy to just eat an infinite amount
of cereal or bread or stuff like that.
Carbs are my bane, absolutely.
Bread was the peasant food,
and the bourgeois created it to keep the peasants down,
keep them weak, keep them fat, keep them dying.
Let them eat cake, let them eat bread,
basically the same thing.
Swear to God, it's true.
I've said it before, grains are not the thing
that humans evolve to eat.
Grains are a thing that were invented later
after the onset of large civilizations
because they are not the most nutritious thing,
but they are the most effective way
to feed a large population,
but they're not the healthiest thing
on an individual level.
Seems reasonable.
A question about tracking calories.
Yeah.
Say you eat a sandwich.
Do you have to count how many slices of ham
or gauge how much butter you put on
and then check the packaging
and then divide it by a certain amount?
Because that seems like it's gonna be difficult.
Can you count?
Then it's not that hard.
No, no, no, look, look, look.
We live in a civilized age.
We don't need to fucking do math manually anymore.
If you just get my fitness pounds, an app,
you just type in ham sandwich,
it has a ham sandwich there,
and it gives you the baseline of what it would be,
and you can ballpark it pretty reasonably
just by saying, oh, I have a ham sandwich,
it's just there, you click it,
it tells you what's in it, and you're good.
The thing that always gets me about the idea of that,
because I've never tried,
is just like you eat one sweet thing
out of a packet of sweet things,
and you have to check the packet
and then divide by the number
of the maximum sweet things in there.
Well, what's cool with my fitness pow is that you can,
let's say you get like a thing of Swedish fish
or something, like in this example,
you can use your phone,
scan the barcode of the box of Swedish fish,
and it'll bring up the information,
and then you can pick the serving size.
If you had one fish, one serving, or one container,
and then it'll do the math for you.
I didn't know about that, that's cool.
See, knowing that would make it much easier
for me to start if I were to need to do that.
Yet, my fitness pow, there's a reason
Jack's Blade has been logged in
for like 2,000 days in a row.
Fan?
Oh my God, that's incredible.
I'm in a streak of probably maybe two weeks,
maybe a little bit more right now.
It's about the same.
I'm just saying, I'm doing pretty good.
That's all, Bunchy.
I'm not trying to fight you, but now I am.
Oh man.
Ah, cheese guy, cheese.
Well, you know, things are going well for me.
I'm doing good.
I haven't been working out as much as I need to,
but I'm getting better every day.
I believe in myself.
And I'm gonna do it.
This is nice.
There's a fitness air in the air.
There's a miasma of health.
Just sort of permeating around.
This is a fact.
If you live in a place where people
are health conscious in general,
you just will gravitate towards like the mean
of what that lifestyle is like.
Like if you live in California,
I guarantee you are in 10 times better shape
than if you just live in Ohio.
I mean, like I've said before,
the Ohio staple of diet is chili with cheese equivalent
to the amount of chili underneath it,
at least in terms of volume.
Cheese is fucked up.
Yeah, it is fucked up.
I think I just had a heart attack listening to that sentence.
It's piled with cheese in this fucking city.
It's fucked up.
Dude.
Shouldn't be that way.
It's keto, man.
I, yeah, it's keto.
I bought, yesterday I bought a no joke,
like seven pounds of cheese.
And I ate it all right then.
Well, okay, there you go.
There you go.
Cheese is fired on keto,
but if you're not burning the fat
and just storing it, you're fucked.
But you should be exercising.
I was traveling out of state,
I forget where I was, I think it was in Nevada somewhere.
And I ordered just like a side of broccoli
because I wasn't very hungry.
I didn't want to partake in whatever fried shit was happening.
So I ordered broccoli and it came back
just covered in like cheeses.
Broccoli and cheese, yeah.
But like the reason I eat broccoli
is because it makes my body feel good.
When I eat cheese, it doesn't make me feel,
like what's the point of this then?
There is no problem.
I don't understand, what's wrong with cheese?
There's nothing wrong, I love cheese.
It's just that-
Well, much is probably getting enough calories already.
He's trying to eat a low calorie thing, I assume.
Well, I mean, it's exactly-
Cheese is good on keto, but if you're not on keto
and you're not in ketosis and you're not burning fat,
you're just-
Then you're fucking up.
Then you're making a mistake.
But in this Pacific scenario,
of course the cheese is a bad thing.
I used to be like that.
I used to be in the dark.
Oh, I'm like that again.
And then I used to be in the dark,
watching the shadows, watching shadow puppets on the wall
until someone brought me out into the light
and I saw the sun.
And now I'm coming back into that cave
to drag you all out to show you truth.
People including me have such a thought in their head
when you're not on the wagon,
as to how incredibly hard any of this stuff is,
like losing weight and again,
I might fuck up and I'm tempted constantly by things.
Not every day has been perfect.
I go over my calorie count every once in a while.
But like, if you just put a little bit of effort in it,
this is just tracking your calories.
I understand, a lot of people are so,
as we've learned in this call,
pathetically ignorant about calorie counting
and how to manage-
Wait, who are you talking about?
You, Ben, you.
What?
What do you mean?
I thought I thought you were talking about me.
Not actually you.
You just didn't know something
about my fitness pal that's totally understandable.
But like, people don't know.
That's such a cool feature.
As was evidenced in this call,
that like, if you look at the nutrition facts
on the back of like, for example, a loaf of bread,
people think like, oh, it's so hard to track.
But on that nutrition label, it says,
like what it does is it divvies it up by serving
and it tells you what a serving is,
like one piece of bread.
If you eat a sandwich, that's two pieces of bread.
You just know that's two servings of like 100 calories.
It's so easy to track.
I have developed a sense.
I have developed like a pretty good sense of like,
like I can judge a tablespoon of butter by eye
for example, stuff like that.
I just kind of know.
I just know which things have carbs in them and which don't.
I don't have to look at the label.
The hardest part though, by far, is getting started.
That's where 99% of people have their issues.
It's that 80-20 rule.
You're gonna get, you get the most benefit
out of that first 20%.
You just like a little, even a little effort
in anything, in this, like in anything else,
goes a long way.
And like, I don't know, like the keto work for you,
that's fantastic.
But for me, just counting my calories,
I've lost like four pounds in about two weeks.
And you know, I'm sure it's not perfect.
These things fluctuate, but it really works.
And I'm gonna keep doing it for the next couple of months
until I'm perfect and then I'll focus on like bulking,
to gain more muscle and stuff.
It's honestly really fucking easy.
If you just are, get my fitness pal.
If you care about this, do that.
Try tracking your calories for one day, for one day.
It's not hard.
It has all the tools you need.
And track your progress.
Arm yourself with knowledge, friends.
Indeed, indeed.
Okay, that's it.
While I was in England, I just kind of reflexively
checked the calories of whatever I'm eating,
and just, I don't even, just even fun, honestly,
just to see what's going on.
And the European like dietary thing on the back,
the nutritional facts, are like a maze.
Like I can't ascertain what's happening.
Like in America, it just is like
in giant, bold calories, whatever.
Even on like a zero calorie drink, which I had,
I just couldn't even find where it actually said
zero calories, besides the actual label.
Because we have such an epidemic over here,
of fatties, they gotta make it really clear.
That's true.
As a further selling point for my fitness pal,
I can't speak to losers or the other ones,
but like just so everyone know, it's so easy.
Here's what you do.
You measure, you get a scale.
A scale is important.
You say what you are right now.
Whatever your goal is, gain weight, lose weight, that's fine.
On the thing, you can set your goal.
If your goal is to lose weight,
you put in your target weight,
and then you set how fast you wanna lose it.
It just tells you how many calories
you need to eat per day, and you just have to fit that.
So it's, it gives you all the tools.
And what's sick is if you're under your calorie weight,
or your calorie count, and you end the day like that,
it'll give you a projection.
Like if you eat like this for another six weeks,
you will be at your target weight.
And it's just like, oh.
Exactly.
I can be the person I wanna be in six weeks,
in time for BronyCon.
Oh my God.
Exactly.
I feel like, I don't think it can really
calculate that accurately though.
Nothing, sure.
I kind of feel like if you're using that,
and you're like, oh, I'll weigh this much
at such and such time.
It's just for motivation.
You're setting yourself up for deployment,
because it's not actually gonna match up.
Well, you should never expect an exact result.
But like, if you follow the trend,
and you should track your progress
you should weigh yourself literally every day
at the same time per day,
I do it right when I wake up.
So that, like what matters is not the numbers,
because the numbers can fluctuate,
it's never perfectly accurate.
What matters is the trend line.
If the trend line's going the way you want it to go,
you know you're doing something right.
If it's not, then some good.
Imagine if there was an app to weigh yourself.
If you don't have a scale,
you just stand on your phone and it tells you.
That'd be nice.
Okay, okay.
Buy a scale, invest.
My roommate, my roommate has a,
he got a new scale, like a fancy scale, right?
And I've been weighing myself on it.
I find out after like several weeks
that this scale is connected to an app on his phone.
And every time I weigh myself,
he gets a report about how much I weigh.
Oh!
So he's, so like what time he's like,
hey Ben, I saw you lost a couple more pounds.
Congratulations.
I'm like, what the fuck, what the fuck do you know?
Dude, that's fucked up.
I know.
Just noticing you're a little more cut, Ben.
The guts getting smaller, I'm proud of you.
I didn't realize it was attached to his,
it was fucking connected by wifi or whatever it is.
I would love that function, but that is fucked up.
Now here's the million dollar question.
Did you ask permission to use a scale
or did you just start it?
Yeah, yes.
Hoping.
No, he told, no, he said, no, he said,
like, yeah, I got a new scale and I'm like,
and I'm like, cool, right?
It was, but you know, I can't,
I can't tell it like, hey, scale.
Don't count this one.
It's me, Ben.
Please no bully.
It's me, yeah, it's me, Ben.
It's not that other guy, it's this other guy.
You know that famous clip of the fat lady
hitting the scale?
It's only, it's Ben, he's like,
you will not report me to the authorities.
You will not tattle on me about my progress.
Wait, which clip?
There's a clip of like a fat lady,
not to, I'm not trying to be mean, but she is fat,
where she's like, she's saying like,
this scale has affected the self-esteem of women
like for generations and we're fighting back.
So she takes a hammer and she smashes the scale.
This is for, you know, hurting my feelings and whatnot.
Oh, is that a scale?
Yeah, it's a scale, it's a scale.
I thought she was using like,
I thought she was like smashing an American flag.
Um, I think that's-
They look exactly the same,
because I understand the confusion.
I've only seen that clip with like other things edited
over the thing.
Yeah, it does get me.
I just assumed it was an American,
God, okay, smashing the scale, all right.
Ben would see the American flag one
and use that as the reference point.
I just seemed like it was a political thing,
like the way she's talking.
Only the way it's been edited, not originally.
That would feel be like a very inefficient way
to destroy a flag with a hammer.
True.
You know, well that's true.
You know, someone brought the hammer,
the other one brought the sickle,
it was a, you know, they were trying to send a message.
Yeah, that's true, that's true.
Good times, good times.
Speaking of keeping apps with keeping going for days on end.
Yeah.
I have been continuing my Duolingo journey
into languages.
They added Arabic, didn't they, on Arabic?
They have added Arabic since the last time I mentioned this,
and I have been going,
overall, I've been going for 42 days straight,
so that's pretty cool.
Hell yeah, nice.
Here's a review of Arabic, the language,
and also the lessons on Duolingo.
Arabic, very squiggly, very funny.
Very strange in that like a letter will,
depending on where it is in the word,
will have a completely different shape,
but like parts of the shape will be recognizable.
So like the oo sound looks like a G.
And when you have a consonant followed by an oo sound,
a tiny version of that oo like G
will be like above the consonant.
But if it's at the end, it will just be by itself.
And then a consonants can like change shape,
depending on whether they're at the beginning
or the end of the sentence.
And it's very confusing until you just,
you know, you know what they are.
It's gonna internalize that weird shit.
And there was a moment,
I just remember when I was learning Japanese,
at the first, it looks like all squiggles.
There's just one point where it's like,
oh, I actually understand there's like actual meaning
attached to these squiggles.
And that's a really great moment to get to.
It's really satisfying.
You jump into like a new lesson
and there's a bunch of new squiggles
that they're introducing you to
and you don't know what they mean.
And you get them wrong a few times,
but then you realize like,
oh, one dot above this thing means an S sound,
but three dots above it means a sure sound.
So like you piece together the puzzle
and then when you see three dots,
you immediately know what it is.
And it's like, wow, I'm figuring it out.
I'm learning Arabic.
And I don't know any words
because Duolingo, the app, the Arabic course,
seems to be mostly introducing you
to the way these squiggles sound when you say them
and not into like explaining
what these squiggles can be turned into words.
I was just gonna ask
if you could say something for us in Arabic.
I suppose you gotta start with that though, right?
Yeah, well, the other ones that I've been trying
like Hebrew and Chinese and stuff,
they quite quickly go into things like,
oh, a hospital is these characters
or a doctor or words that you can use in things
like, hello, goodbye, thank you.
Arabic, I've really only learned that America
and English and Scotland,
it's like, they just say the same thing in English,
but it's slightly different
because they didn't invent the words,
so it sounds the same.
And they've been giving me like names like Zaid
and Rosa and Otto,
and I've been figuring out like by looking at the squiggles
what sounds they would make
and figuring out the names.
But I mean, it's satisfying in that,
but I'm really wondering when I'm gonna get to a point
because I've done quite a lot of these lessons.
I haven't really got to a point
when I'm learning words yet,
but if I see an Arabic sign, I would be able to say it,
I just wouldn't know what I was saying.
That's interesting.
You know, I would think like as a professional
Japanese educator,
which I have made one video on on my channel,
you'd think that what you do is you like teach
a couple characters and then you immediately try
to make as many words as possible
with the limited characters you've taught
to help them like latch on to real meanings
for those things.
Like when Japanese, you'll start with the vowels,
and then you like the first ones are ah and e,
a and i in English.
And ie literally is a word that means love in Japanese.
So like boom, your first two letters,
you have a word instantly,
like now meanings are beginning to be associated.
Isn't that cool?
I wonder why the Arabic's different.
Maybe just because it's new.
I think it might be new.
Also, it might be that there's just a lot of squiggles.
By the way, I said the three dots was a sh,
and a single dot was s.
May not actually be true.
I think I may be mixing that up with t and th,
just make it sure if anybody is also learning Arabic
or knows Arabic.
Don't kill me.
Hello.
But yeah, I really, there's this really funny one,
which is.
I look forward to the give PCPU lecture on Arabic,
and perhaps Arabic history.
I mean, you know what, I'll do it.
PCP, PCP, PCP lecture on the Israeli,
Palestinian conflict, please.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, I'll learn Hebrew, I'll learn Arabic,
and then I'll fucking understand,
I'll be super enlightened,
and I'll be like, guys, I got it.
Oh my God, you can finally end the conflict.
I'll make a PCP lecture on how to,
by the way, there's this w,
it looks like a three turn sideways.
If you put that w, a tiny little w,
over the top of a consonant,
that just makes the consonant longer.
So say if you have shu as a word,
if you put that there on the s, it'll be shu,
and they distinct, they have like words
that are distinctly different based on how long
certain consonants and vowels are held,
and it's cool.
And also I'm learning the ch sounds,
the ih ch, all those,
there's multiple different types of those.
Oh my God.
So, pretty complex,
I don't know whether I'll ever be proficient in it,
but I'm just gonna keep going,
because it is very fun to figure it out.
It's got the bleeps, the sweeps, and the creeps.
My favorite things.
I've always thought it's very romantic
to learn a new language,
but they're known if there was a language
that would actually like benefit me,
obviously they're Spanish,
and it's universal, if you live in America,
you should also learn Spanish,
because that will just open a lot of opportunities for you.
But like, I don't know, I don't have to speak Spanish.
But also like hashtag build the wall,
if you know what I'm saying.
Yeah, well I think I mentioned this last time,
but like, I don't know how important this app would be
if you need to learn, if you like need to learn a language.
Like for work or something?
Yeah, I mean if you can,
because some of these they work better with learning
how to read and write the things
rather than how to speak it,
because they have voice clips for every thing,
and sometimes it gives you a voice,
and you have to try and put letters
or like, figure it out through that.
But sometimes they don't,
and a lot of the time, at least in Hebrew,
I couldn't really make out what the hell they were saying,
but I could figure out the letters.
So I'd be able to read,
but if I were actually to go to Israel,
or to go to some of these countries for these languages,
I wouldn't really know how to talk to the people,
unless I was in that country,
and I just sort of learned it through osmosis.
Well you know, that's actually pretty cool,
because I know a couple of people,
like for example, Michelle's dad
like had to learn Korean when he was in the military,
and like, so he's actually, he's Japanese,
but he was forced to learn Korean,
he like doesn't speak Japanese very much,
which is pretty funny.
But like, it's just because he had to work
with like Korean people, he just like just on the job,
he was an American, didn't speak the language,
just like had to learn it for his job.
And I've always like,
I mean, I do things related to Japanese,
I hope to kind of through osmosis,
just like pick up more,
but I'm aware I'll have to like force myself,
or spend a lot of time around like,
exclusively speaking Japanese people probably,
to learn any of it.
I want to not have to do any work,
I want the environment around me to just teach me things.
And that's what I want, that would be great,
that would be excellent if that could happen.
But I don't know, I've always thought it was pretty cool
how people will like learn new languages
just for their jobs.
I always thought that was neat.
Like if you're like, hey, oh, Johnson,
we're transferring you to the Mumbai account,
I'm trying to think of some like Indian city.
Go learn, they got like a million languages in India,
but go learn whatever they speak over there.
Hindi, yeah, Hindi, go learn that, Johnson.
Yes, sir, off I go.
And then he does somehow.
I was, by the way, here's my invite link to Duolingo.
If you use this link to get on,
I get a free week of Duolingo Plus,
which has no benefits really at all,
except that it has no ads.
No, that's a plus, that's a plus.
I was, I was thinking about this earlier,
because I was getting pizza with Sixton,
who is over here staying at my house, famous,
Ronnie Cooker's Con Killers.
Oh yeah, famous, right?
For his Con Killers, Pop Idol,
and musician behind the Izumi game.
So, oh yeah, cool, God tier, God tier musician.
Anyway, he's here at my house,
and we were hanging out, we were getting pizza.
And I thought about how, isn't funny,
how you can go to like Italian restaurant or something,
or like an Indian restaurant, or a Mexican restaurant,
and it will be made up of staff who is that ethnicity.
And it makes sense, obviously, you know,
they may know how to make the meals better
than anyone else would.
But imagining from like the initial perspective
of like, imagine if I were to like immigrate to France,
and then I'm like, well, I'm American,
might as well like push this angle a lot,
and then I went to like a McDonald's,
or I went to like a burger place to start like that.
Oh, this is my life now, you know?
I was born American, so this is what I'm gonna do
with my life.
That's not exactly what's going on here though.
I'm just gonna push my angle.
Well, what do you mean?
I mean, they're doing what they know.
They probably like were a cook, I assume, you know,
either with their family,
or if they like came from another country,
that's like, you know, that's their specialty.
So they're offering, that's what they have to offer
in a business sense.
They're like a specialist in this kind of cooking
or something.
Sure, but I'm trying to think about the amount of times
that I see another like, for instance, in Italian.
When do I see an Italian outside an Italian restaurant?
Like, never.
I mean, it's probably family run though, right?
Like a Chinese restaurant, right?
Like what we think of as American Chinese food
is not like, you know, to Chinese food staples,
crab rangoon, not Chinese, invented in California.
I think, oh God, was it, is it,
I think General So's chicken is what you're saying.
These are like, these are staples of Chinese food restaurants
and they're not thing,
I mean, they'd probably have them in China,
but it's not like traditional Chinese food.
But when you go to like your American Chinese one,
when you go to your American Chinese restaurant though,
you see like, it's generally speaking,
Chinese people run in the place.
I know, but I'm saying that like they still have to learn.
You know, it's not like they just like show up in America
and they're like, well, I'm just gonna,
I'm gonna take all the things that mama taught me
how to make and that's gonna be my restaurant.
And then, and then they just,
that's what ends up on the menu.
I think there is gotta be a little bit of like,
I'm Chinese, time to start a Chinese restaurant.
Because if I didn't, the customer would experience,
there would be ludonarrative dissonance
when you eat in my restaurant
and everyone would, and everyone would be freaked out
and be like, this doesn't, ah, this doesn't taste authentic.
Pig slob, bad review on y'all.
What's the pose though?
Exactly that.
Sixth one's relaying me about how his friend,
who was white, wanted to work at like a,
I believe it was a Thai place.
And they're like, if you aren't Thai, you can't work here.
Like they said, don't call back.
You at least gotta look Thai.
Yeah.
You can be, you can be like,
you can be like, you can be some other Asian,
just keep your mouth shut.
Yeah.
I would really like to see a Chinese-run Italian restaurant
because they would make the spaghetti all different.
I mean, you know, walk, spaghetti and walk.
You know, is that, is that, I mean, I personally,
I have no problem with a restaurant doing that
if they want to.
Like they can hire whoever they want.
That's their business.
But like, is that actually like a crime
to like discriminate in that way
based on like the race of the people applying?
Well, out of Sweden, maybe.
Well, I think, I think generally the reasons for hiring,
you can't like, you're not like forced by the government
to hire people just because.
But you are, you are barred by the government
from not hiring people because of some specific criteria.
I would imagine, I don't know.
I would imagine that when you go to like a Chinese restaurant
and everyone there working there is Chinese,
it is like primarily because the place is owned by a family
and like a lot of the people working there
are in the family or friends of the family or whatever.
Probably.
Also like, like Ben in Chinatown,
I was wondering, not very seriously,
like, you know, what if I got a job,
like it's somewhere around here just over the summer,
well, well, I'm going to college.
But like, you know, I couldn't because I don't speak Mandarin
and I'm not Chinese, which Mandarin is more of like
a skill set, which makes sense.
Well, that's the real issue.
If like the whole restaurant is run by people
who like really speak Chinese
and maybe their English isn't necessarily great,
then like they're probably going to want to hire people
who, you know, share that language.
Yeah, that's a legit reason.
Maybe this is a stupid question,
but is racism illegal or is it just like very largely
maligned as a thing to speak?
Racism is basically illegal as far as like,
it feels like it's pretty new.
Well, I mean, you are, you are not allowed to like
bar someone from employee on the basis of race.
Yeah.
So it's like, you know, you're not allowed to do that
specifically and things like that.
Like certain, certain, certain like racist reasons,
things are illegal like that, but like,
you're not like arrested just for being a racist.
It's illegal, but like, or well, yeah.
No, no, no, it's not illegal on paper at all.
You can feel whatever you want, which is what's illegal.
He means hiring, so like, like making a hiring decision.
Yeah, that's what I mean.
That's all right.
I didn't know that.
I just thought of that idea.
There are, there are laws like that in America.
I suspect that with this like,
China, if for whatever reason,
somebody wanted to be like, they're like, I don't know,
wait, and they want to work at a Chinese restaurant.
I suspect if you like, filed a lawsuit and kept going,
you'd probably win.
And then they'd have to give some other reason.
Wait, couldn't they just, I don't know.
Couldn't they just like, lie about it?
Say, are you not the right guy for the job?
Well, I think that's why they would like,
that's why you would sue and do an investigation.
Here's what I think.
I think the reason is probably, it's not like,
I bet that they'd never have any positions open
because if they did, they would immediately just fill them
like, through like, friend of the family,
like, who do I know?
Right?
Probably, probably.
There's been hiring signs in Shintown before.
Yeah.
If they were putting out, if they put out a sign
that says like, hiring and you showed up and you applied
and like, you spoke the language that the boss speaks.
Yeah.
You probably, they probably can sue you.
Because at that point, like, they're out of people.
They're out of like, in-group people that they know.
Like, they're looking for outsiders.
I imagine this is probably, jobs happen.
I'm sure you could get a job like that.
Yeah.
But I just think it generally doesn't come to that
because probably these kinds of establishments
tend to hire in, like, inside the family
or their community.
I don't know, man.
I've seen now hiring signs before in Shintown.
I know I've seen like, for example,
you see a lot of like, you know,
whatever, Latin America or whatever people.
I've seen them working in like,
Chinese food kitchens in the past.
I assume because, you know, it's the kind of work
that maybe people who are fresh to the country
can get relatively easily and learn the,
maybe they're a chef of some kind
and, you know, looking for a job in the meantime.
Eh, I don't know.
I have a feeling, I have a feeling
that probably relatively few people working at restaurants
like that are like, professional chefs from the old country.
Well, yeah.
And it's probably just more like, I showed up here.
Chef was the wrong word, probably.
I don't know anyone.
I've never cooked a day in my life,
but like my uncle's, like my uncle's like wife's son
just opened a fucking restaurant or whatever.
And I guess I got an in there.
So I'll go do that, you know.
When Tony Montana came into America
at the beginning of Scarface,
he was able to get a job at like some shitty restaurant
that's open like 24 hours or whatever, washing dishes
and making like shitty sandwiches
for like dock workers in Miami or whatever.
And I imagine that's relatively the experience.
You get like a low, low level job.
But then you just become, or rather you continue
your active campaign as an assassin from the third world
and you just move up the ranks like hotcakes.
You move to pushing cocaine,
you move to doing bigger and bigger dope deals,
you commit assassinations for your political friends
and bing bong bing, you got yourself a mansion.
I'm just saying, nepotism is a fact of life
and they're definitely, this is definitely
just because they're hiring the people they already know.
They're hiring friends of friends, right?
That's it, solved.
I solved the issue, no more.
It's the end.
The reason why is obvious, but it's interesting
that we just kind of assume that, you know,
if you are from ethnicity,
you may know how to cook the ethnicity as food.
And like- It's more likely, right?
And we are like, you know, like it would be sort of like,
you know, it may not be like bad or weird,
but if you were like at a Chinese restaurant
and some like white dude were to serve you,
you'd be like, oh, huh, interesting.
I'd puke instantly.
I'd fucking shoot out my goo from all orifices.
But it's funny that we say that because yeah, you're right.
I guess it is more likely,
but I think very small of an increase
because I wouldn't assume that anyone just walking
down the street would be able to cook
like at like a traditional American meal.
I wouldn't assume that everyone's a cook
that would know how to do it effectively.
What even is a traditional American meal,
burger and fries?
It's like a pie or something, like an apple pie?
Is that even American?
They say apple pie is American and shit,
but is that even a fact?
You understand what I mean.
I do, I do.
So it's interesting that we're just like, oh yeah.
Listen, you know, Irish, oh, you can make a fucking pastrami.
You can whip me up a Guinness, can't you?
Yeah, yeah, you can whip me up a fucking corned beef.
Just get in there, buddy, just go behind the grill.
I pelt wheat.
Oh, wait, wait, what do they make Guinness out of?
Wheat, I assume, because it's beer, is that?
They make it out of beer.
Oh, pups, pups, pups, Jesus Christ.
Oh, oh, you know what, Munchy,
talk about the time you drank three beers.
Yes, yes, yes, I'm saying the Guinness is a perfect segue
because last we spoke, that was my knockoff record rel
from that one guide code commercial impression.
Last we spoke, I had drank in one apple cider,
and that was like insane, like I couldn't even believe
what had just happened, and I broke all the sacred vows.
Do you mean like, do you mean a hard apple cider,
like in My Little Pony?
Yes, literally exactly.
Applejack came up to me in Victoria Square,
she said, hey, y'all, and I slapped her
and I drank her fucking cider.
And in your traditional British accent,
she said, howdy, y'all.
Yeah, exactly, and that was it.
I had cursed my family and I was dishonored forever,
but it felt pretty good.
And then later, due to yaya yada circumstances,
me, Hepo, his father, and a bunch of his fucking rowdy,
like English coworkers, went out to a pub, a proper pub,
with dim lighting, with brown on the walls,
and a bunch of weird knickknacks everywhere,
an actual literal cartoon I stepped inside of.
Like from the movies?
Yeah, like from the movies, wow.
Literally, I mean, I don't think of it as much
because I've seen these sorts of pubs
semi-regularly all my life,
but I guess it is sort of like the cartoony,
prototypical stereotype of a English pub
with the dark oak seats and the dark and the green
sort of cushions and dim lighting
and the curtains and everything.
I literally long jumped into the TV that day
and I appeared inside a pub.
And I was kind of just ready to get like a water.
Yeah, holy.
Literally, I would,
ha, bu, bu, bu, bu, bu, bu, bu, bu, bu, bu, bu, bu, bu,
wee!
And I was kind of just ready to get like a water,
like I was kind of just prepared
to not really do anything
because that was my last day in England.
And the plan was to drink until the pain's over,
but worse, worse, the pain or the hangover.
Hangover, yeah.
And I was just gonna stay up
and I was gonna sleep on the plane,
which I will get into the aftermath of that later
because that's a whole story into itself,
but I was gonna stay up on it.
So I didn't wanna just, you know, get fucked up and die.
But the sweet old man who ran Hippo's dad's,
like I don't know, the scout thing going on,
whatever, it doesn't matter.
Well, he didn't run.
He hasn't run it for a while,
but he used to be in charge.
Well, the point is that there was a sweet old man there
who offered me a drink and who was I to decline.
And so he got me an actual beer.
So the age of drinking is 18?
Yes, yes, yes, that's why, yeah.
And he got me a lager, a lager, is it called?
Oh, yeah.
Ooh, I've heard of those.
To be honest with you, I hadn't.
So he got me that.
And then halfway through drinking that slowly,
because it tasted just like fermented dirt
is what it tastes like.
I was halfway through and I thought, this sucks.
I'll just go to the end and then I'll stop.
And then Hippo's dad,
the hero slash villain question mark that he is,
just gave me another one,
just placed down in my sights,
in my sniper reticule, a second version of my drink.
So I was like, oh, so what am I gonna say?
Am I gonna splash in his fucking face and say no?
No, I'm just gonna have to deal with this.
This is just my life now.
I'm halfway through drinking that one, two beers,
and then again, another drink up here before me.
Oh my God, he's brits.
And they're just fucking loading it up
to do whatever saw to me
they could possibly want to do to me.
He's fucking limies, yeah.
They're setting you up for a fall, friend.
Yeah, and you know what?
It's weird, because I finally, beer snapped in my mind,
as did many brain cells.
And I finally understood why,
because why people drink beer
is because after the first drink,
beer tastes like nothing because your body is destroyed.
And so it doesn't taste bad anymore after the first drink.
It just tastes like...
All it tastes like is you go to pick up your drink,
then you've put down your drink
because you've over-drinked it,
and then your mind's confused
because you just lagged out for a second.
Yeah, that's right.
And anyway, it was a great time
because of the previously mentioned rowdy coworkers
who were speaking in their foreign tongues,
calling me Donald,
and talking to me about MPs.
No, no, no, that's my father.
I'm Munchie J from...
Yeah, no, no, no, literally.
Okay, one...
Yeah, yeah, the moment with the phone.
Yeah, do you want to say it?
My dad, well, you can tell the story,
but I just want to tell you
that my dad was really impressed by that
and has mentioned the story like three times already.
That American guy, that Munchie guy,
is really great, really witty.
He'll do great things.
It's like, yeah.
What? Oh my God!
Yeah, he really likes you.
Both of my parents really like you.
Andrew, an old man, mentioned you again.
You really hit it off with everyone.
Oh my God!
That's great!
Oh, my heart's a flutter, be still!
I can't believe this.
Oh, I'm doing that thing that girls do
when they put like one leg up behind them
while they're kissing someone.
Obulate, obulate.
Yeah, yeah, obulate.
Anyway, one of the coworkers,
like they're fucking like,
it was like a family-run business,
like the Chinese do as a business,
as pulled back the current on
and called it for what it is.
I just said what we were all thinking,
that Ben St. Guy.
He's gonna get like a point.
Yeah, yeah.
And one of their brothers called,
and they were like passing around the phone
to everyone to play a prank on him.
When they got to me,
I was already like, I'm a lightweight,
so like the three were, it was able to get to me,
and I was able to do it.
Which is surprising considering your size,
but you're a young undrink or so,
that'll do it, yeah, yeah.
And I remember, I just answered the phone,
it was passed to me, it was some dude,
I'd never met before.
And I said, Nigel, I gotta say,
I love what you've done for the family,
and I can't wait to meet you in person.
I love what you've done.
Oh my God, my chair just broke,
my chair just broke, my chair just broke,
my chair just broke.
It's completely broken.
I wasn't sure if this was part of the story
or something that actually just happened.
Did you hear the snap?
I did hear the snap.
The fucking Thanos snap of your chair.
Okay, all right, hold on.
I'm just gonna keep speaking
while I take a picture of my now,
completely and utterly broken chair.
Okay, I can't hear you for one second.
There's the photo.
Anyway, the point is, is that he called me Donald.
Show notes, please.
I said that Donald's my father, please call me Baron.
And then we just, we just talked about Boris Johnson,
we talked about who's gonna be the new prime minister.
And it was great, and it was literally an iconic evening
that I will not forget for the rest of my life.
Because it was literally a cartoon, literally a cartoon.
I've never been to England.
I wanna go there and meet Gibbs' wacky family
and his kooky characters.
Oh, they're so wacky.
Like, I just love like, hey, like, hey hippos,
dad, dance for me, you stupid fucking bitch.
And then you can do it over and over and over again.
That's what your people are known for, as I understand it.
All right, you taught them how to long jump back to something.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I remember after, after,
okay, look at my fucking chair.
Look at the mangled mess that this is.
Whoa.
Oh no, so the arm just snapped off?
Yeah, the arm snapped, we're just right off.
Dope.
Yeah, this is great.
This is literally fantastic.
Anyway, I remember after, after, like,
I stood up for the first time after drinking the three,
the three loggers. Oh boy, yeah, there you go.
And my brain just was like, oh God, everything's hard now.
And I stumbled to the bathroom.
The bathroom was like a weird like pig trough
where there was no like urinals.
It just was like a wall that you piss on.
And it was terrifying.
I didn't know if I was just...
Yeah, it was a pretty gritty bathroom.
I couldn't tell if I was just like pissing on the wall
or if I wasn't supposed to be doing what I was doing,
but I did anyway because I didn't fear
the ramifications at that point.
Yeah.
I came back and then after we were all said and done
about talking about our glorious God Boris Johnson,
we went back to Hippo's house.
Hippo's dad gave me a shot of whiskey
and I drank it and it like blew my mind off.
It felt like a shotgun blast
at the root of my fucking mouth and it was terrible.
And we just crushed Crash Bandicoot 3.
That's all we fucking did.
We went up to Hippo's room
and I was so excited to play Crash Bandicoot 3.
I got like one level in it, fucking sucked.
I gave it to Hippo and they just watched him
destroy Crash Bandicoot 3.
Like literally the hardest any gamer has ever gameed.
Crash Bandicoot 3 was like vanquished
from the face of the earth.
I'd be surprised if you could literally even locate
a copy of it after what we did last night.
So what are your updated thoughts on alcohol
after this experience?
My updated thoughts on alcohol
are actually somewhat devilish.
They're actually somewhat upsetting.
I know this is like a real heel turn.
I know this is like against everything
that like Munchie stands for as a human being
and that I may be kicked from like several different
friend groups or just like podcasts or anything.
And maybe like option society.
I didn't hate it.
I didn't think it was the worst thing on earth.
Now what about the hangover though?
What about the hangover afterward?
I didn't get a hangover.
You what the fuck?
It must be your size.
That's the only explanation.
You just somehow tanked it in your body.
I can't believe it.
We defeated Britain, broke away from America
all those years ago, but vengeance finally came back
and they took Munchie from us.
Those goddamn British.
Did you by the way, did you drink much water
while you were doing this?
Cause they always say drinking water
is the way to offset a hangover.
You did not.
Okay, you just carry enough ambient water with you.
He had, I mean, I don't know whether he drunk water
when we got home, but he did stay up all night
playing with, playing some.
I've heard that helps.
I've heard that helps too.
After we were gonna play Crash Bandicoot
and a hippo went to bed like a fucking pussy piece of shit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
What did you stay up to?
True, true, true, true, true, true.
Not even hiding from it.
Me and HDB guy just stayed up all night
talking about like real shit
and like diving into our psyches.
And then watching the English television version
of the Chronicles of Narnia,
which is really like bizarrely whimsical
and also ridiculous.
Like on his old fucking CRT.
Now, yeah, I really wish I'd stayed up
cause that does sound great.
I was just destroyed from various things.
And I woke up the next day with a sickness.
But anyway, that's my final kiss.
That's my parting gift.
I'm still sick from that.
But anyway, Munchy, before you get onto your plane ride
that you want to talk about, rate my family.
What do you think?
What do you think about my family?
What's the tier list?
Yeah, I will go by family member by family member.
What you guys have to understand
is that hippos, brothers, they are like a comedy troupe.
They are like a constructed set of characters.
They're like, if you go on Tumblr and like,
hey guys, this is my OC, Tee-hee-hee.
You will just see a picture of him and his brothers.
Like they are just like a constructed version
of what you think English people are like.
The different character archetypes
that there can be for British humor,
there they are in real life.
Hippos, like the Venn diagram of both of them
and Henry HGB guy is like total unhinged madness.
Like full internet neat dweller,
like madman insane psychopath, literal serial killer.
Most twisted psychopath you will ever meet.
And then Charlie is like this like normie,
like chill, like cool Chad normie,
who like works at construction yard
and just sort of like soft spoken.
He's like, he's the guy who like will kill people,
will get a lot of kills and then say something like,
huh, it was easy.
And then we load his clip.
So they are both Kino and I love them.
They're both literally 10 out of 10
and it was great hanging out with,
it was great hanging with Henry
because he threw up, he threw up on the train
and that was great.
And just hanging out with him was a hoot.
And then Charlie was like a down to earth nice guy
who was fun just walking around coal drop parks.
I believe it was coal drop park.
London is so fucking cool.
London is like better than like any American city
except like not at all,
Boston's way better half fuck you Limies,
but it is cool because it's so walking around pedestrian.
And there's just like the sight lines,
literally Disneyland, but a city
because Walt Disney himself planned out London
so that the sight lines,
we were in some like just nice little hill
and we were able to like watch an outdoor fucking movie
on a big screen on this beautiful river
with like a river boat that was like a turn into a library
and behind us there was like a chic coal plant
turning into like nice boutique restaurant
and shopping center.
And I couldn't even see a side scraper in sight.
And we were like in the heart of London,
literally perfect best city ever made,
but it fucking sucks because I got sick and fuck you.
Your mom's really nice.
You hippo look just like your mom and dad put together.
It's funny how those sort of things work out.
Literally just like copy and pasted.
You have your dad's face and your mom's hair.
Perfect.
Literally perfect.
And your mom's really nice.
She helped me with my coat and with my cold.
She nursed me back to health.
She was like there.
And then your dad got me drunk
and it was cool when we played Crash Bandicoot 3,
the best game ever made.
So your whole family gets a 10 out of 10,
munchie, a seal of approval.
I'm coming back right now.
I'm turning the boat around.
I'm sailing back on the Mayflower.
I'm gonna ram it right into the fucking Big Ben
and he's gonna fall down.
So I gotta twist my ears like in half.
I gotta like pick up my ears
and have to put them back on
like a fucking Mr. Potato Head.
I'm back now.
You know, just quick question slash point.
When I was in Japan,
I turned 21 while I was in Japan
but the drinking age there is 20.
So I too was able to drink just willy nilly
when I first got there.
And similarly, you know, in Britain,
the drinking age is 18, that's cool.
You know, that's the three years difference
versus what is in America.
My question is, so you're not facing any legal repercussions
of having underage drunk in another country.
My question is, why is it such a big deal
when I fly to the Philippines
to fuck the 12 year old lady boys?
Same logic applies, what's the issue?
Literally, what's the problem?
Well, I think the answer is, is there isn't.
I think you've just asked for a rhetorical question
to give people a good point. Okay, great.
Which is the most reasonable point on earth.
Great, great, okay.
Listen, I'm saying that we should legalize grooming children
if the children are also into it.
That's my official statement.
Hard to agree.
Well, so what else, what else is on people's minds here?
Wait, wait, wait, what's much you're gonna do
is talk about his flight back.
Was there anything to say about that?
Yeah, there's not much of a story.
It just was the worst experience of my life.
Yeah, okay.
Which I'd stayed up the entire night previous,
which was fine and good.
And me and Henry rode to the airport together.
But when we were at the airport,
I checked in and I said my goodbye and I got in,
but I had an aisle seat.
An aisle seat while I was like as sick and like sniveling
and like coughing up a fucking storm,
I had an aisle seat.
And so I squeezed in between these two fucking fat people,
just you know, three pigs in a blanket, you could say.
And I was coughing and I was trying to lean my chair back,
but my chair specifically was broken.
So I couldn't lean my chair back specifically.
Wait, wait, when you said aisle seat,
do you mean you're in the,
are you saying like the aisle or the middle seat?
Yeah, no, no, no, no, no, I'm retarded, yes.
I'm in middle seat.
Okay, that's what I thought.
I'm in middle seat, yeah.
And I couldn't sleep the entire night for 12 hours.
I was just waking up.
I had like a weird like headache,
I think because I sleep deprivation or something.
And I had to keep getting up
because one of the people on the window seat
kept wanting to go to the bathroom.
So I had to keep getting up for them.
Like every 20 fucking minutes, it was a literal nightmare.
I got to Canada and Canada is like a weird,
like I'm almost there, it looks like America,
but it's just wrong enough.
I just want to go home.
Why is everything so hard?
Why do they speak English?
Except they're so different and I hate them all.
And I was cursing the entire continent of Europe
and the entire continent of North America,
Sands America.
And I got through and it was a nightmare
and it was the worst experience in my life.
And I was sick and it sucked.
And that's all I want to say.
Fuck planes, fuck Air Canada.
Oh, oh, I went to the bathroom.
Cause I fucking, cause I was doing a big bathroom
cause I was going to explode and die.
And then someone caught me in line.
There was like a little, there's like a little like,
like bathroom offset that you could do.
And it was like a very like a small,
like not really formed line that was happening.
And I just got like a quick, quick,
tiny wash in my hands and in the bathroom.
And then someone cut cut in front of me
and I had to go back of the line.
I had to go behind like 50 fucking people.
And it was a nightmare and fuck you.
If someone cuts you in line for the next five minutes,
wash and not apply to you and should be able to retaliate
in any way you want.
I agree.
Anyway, that's done.
Munch of podcast over.
I'll take the thousands of dollars
that I receive per, per appearance, 50 K a verse.
I'm going to call it hers.
But Ben was going to say something stupid.
Probably how the fuck you been?
Probably.
Yeah.
I was just mad, just mad.
Looking at Twitter, seeing Trump,
just saw a Trump tweet and it got really upset.
Well, it's almost as uninteresting
as someone's vacation story.
You know, he's just saying that, you know,
Democrat, Congress, women of color
ought to go back to the shit hole countries they come from.
I mean, it's pretty cool.
Harsh but fair.
Tough love is.
How do you, yeah.
Facts and logic.
Don't care about feeling.
That's all I had to say.
Well, I guess I'll just mention that I have become sick
from Munchie being sick at the time he was at my house.
No, no, no, no, no judging because that that just happens.
Well, you'll be happy to know that I got six and six.
So I'm just nice.
Six and then he's going to go home with his family
and his family's going to get sick.
And then the family's going to go home to Sweden.
This cold is literally having like the longest life.
You're a real plague doctor.
And only instead of curing the plague,
you're creating the plague.
You're spreading the play.
It's like it's like it's like a real good combo
in a fighting game.
This this this one virus is going around doing combo moves,
not dying, continuing to spread.
Very cool.
Anyway, the sickness is not the story.
The story I have is just what is it has caused me to think about.
Because, you know, when you're sick, you're sluggish, you're hurdy.
You don't want to do things.
You see how he gets a hurdy.
Yeah, I see how we.
And I have been like not considering working.
And I've been just sitting around watching YouTube videos
and playing games, and I feel like that's fine because I'm sick.
And I've just started playing games that have been in my steam library
for millions of years, hundreds of thousands of years.
I've had these games and I've never even opened them.
And I'm just sort of going through them and like having opinions that the reason
I I never really wanted to do this before, I think was because I wanted to go full
Digi Bro and have a spreadsheet and like, you know, give it a score
so that I could maybe make a video on it later or something.
But because that's sort of like out of my mind
and I'm just sort of brainaddled through sickness, I'm just sort of playing games.
And I'm like, wow, is this what people do with video games as hobby?
What the fuck is pretty fun?
You just got you just open up a little thing and it's just a nice little time
and you just stop when you feel like it.
Dude, I feel the same way, but about like shows like I like this was the thing
that I declared I was going to do has become the media munchie.
I was become the oh, yeah, that's right, actually consume art again.
And I've been doing so.
I've been I've been I've been watching like HBO shows and it's like great.
Like, has anyone ever thought of this before?
Has anyone realized you can like watch art instead of making it?
It's like insane.
It's like actually crazy and I can't believe it.
It's like it's like actually fun.
Like it brings me joy in my in my life.
Yon sounds lame.
It does. It does.
Hey, I can't enjoy things anymore.
I also have been like just getting into dumb reading some comics.
I went on the quick draw discord and I asked for comic recommendations
and I have a big list and one of the big ones was Astro Boy never read that.
But I have, you know, I have some knowledge of it.
I've watched a show of it once when I was young.
Astro Boy is like what I would make.
It feels like Ali youp the comic because of how like it's just
Astro Boy is such a cute character, such a cute design.
And the way Osama Bin Laden draws
like Astro's feet and stuff.
It's just sort of like like gloop feet, like the sort of just
I don't know how to describe it, but it's so free and so like
free of like rigid structure and like body proportions
in like the in the art school sort of like life drawing way.
It all makes sense in its way, but it looks like you could just scribble it
and I guess that's why he's so such a genius
because it looks so palatable and appetizing.
I just want to eat it.
But I don't want to eat it.
I want to eat it with my eyes and I want to read it.
But it's it's clearly like I haven't tried like emulating the style.
But that is that is very good.
I like Astro Boy.
Also, it's strange how I guess just because it's an old thing.
But the story like the very first story in Astro Boy, the first like chapter,
the volume was like surprisingly in depth and dark and like
twisted and like, whoa, dude, that's fucked up.
I couldn't imagine such a cute character going through such weird shit.
It's the same sort of feeling as seeing like those old Betty Boop cartoons
where there's like some really, you know, before cartoons were quote unquote,
four children. Yeah.
There was a lot of adultish themes in Betty Boop cartoons
and a lot of like almost grotesque imagery just thrown in there.
Betty Boop, the original anime character, unironically.
Yeah. And Astro Boy has that same feeling
where there's like political tensions and like themes of, you know,
all sorts of injustice.
There's this dog in this first one who Astro Boy goes to save.
But it turns out the dog has been killed and his brain has been implanted
into a cyborg robot.
And a lot of the the character of this dog
is that he has to try and get over his programming that he is a cyborg
and he has to kill Astro Boy. Oh, my God.
And sort of struggling with this like existential sort of crisis
that he wants to be a dog again, but he can't.
It's not it doesn't like end with him just being a dog.
I think it does.
Yeah, like it's a goof.
It's goofy as fuck because certain things is like all the other
like cyborgs are also have dog brains.
So he has to when he's in like a kerfuffle, but he knows he's a dog.
So he goes, oh, and he gets all the cyborgs on his side.
And like there was a bit where the word sit will force the cyborgs to stop.
And, you know, the evil villains like, well, what is my henchmen doing?
They're sitting when people say sit.
That's not how they're supposed to work is that you use dog brains, you idiot.
Yeah, it's it's it's great.
Go read Astro Boy.
I think there's a there's lots of places you can read it.
You know, did you just made a video?
Oh, yeah, did you just made a video?
I forget what it's his video.
Don't skip the classics.
And I enjoy that video very much.
And it was basically about how there's a new anime out.
I can't remember and it's not in the description.
So I fucking forget what anime it is.
But it's an Osamu Tezuka.
I don't know what the fucking name of the thing is.
So they just made an anime adaptation of it and did you watched it?
And he had like read the original and like you can see in the thumbnail
like the difference between the two.
And he was like, yeah, like the new anime is like, it's fine.
It's OK, but the original has such like an interesting style
that was of its time and is like, you know, it's fucking Betty Boop.
It's Osamu Tezuka, like from his from his heyday.
And the new one is like that only like they shear away all the like
classical trappings like of that era and a lot of that stuff.
And they just they put it in the context of like our current
understanding of like how anime like quote should be made with modern
stands or whatever.
But in that process, so much is lost.
And like if you just look just that thumbnail shows the difference
in style between the two and you can see it is not even close to looking
like what the original looked like.
And he talks about like a bunch of the he just shows like art from the original.
And he's like, wouldn't it be great if like imagine if they made this?
They adapted this anime.
But they are like one of the primary goals was to adapt the style of that time
to like keep it looking like that rather than trying to fit it into our,
you know, current understanding of how things should look.
And even that even that other show that was made that anime
about the the what is it like the sex tuplets or whatever the the boys.
It's like a comedy adapted action that was like adapted for their modern style.
And the art style like kind of resembled the original.
But even that was changed a lot.
But like to really keep to the original art style is is something that I mean,
you'd have to go way out of your way and would be probably very challenging to do,
which is why they don't do that.
It's you know, it's a lot of work and it's like the stylization of like red line.
Now that has to be on that level or anything.
But I mean, yeah, obviously classic stuff.
First of all, not only is it not necessarily bad.
People have been writing stories for thousands of years.
They're pretty good at it.
It's not like we magically got so much better in the last, you know,
fifty hundred years or whatever.
We though our standards are set based on what we've consumed in that time.
But yeah, there's just a lot to be gained from, I don't know,
recognizing the value and the specific qualities of art from its time.
And that's that's pretty neat.
That's that's a lot of why I'm not too into just like, you know,
this kind of remake stuff and they're called classics for a reason.
They've withstood the test of time.
You know, I've read almost no Tezuka,
but I've always wanted to read Phoenix and Astro Boy.
I should get in on that shit.
Oh, I'm a big Blackjack fan,
but I've actually watched the like anime adaptations of more recent years
from like the nineties and shit of Blackjack.
So that shit's good.
Well, I mean, we went to the British Museum and there was exhibit,
a whole exhibit on manga that we saw.
It was really, really great.
It was a really fantastic exhibit.
And in it, we were just there was just a bunch of like there was a section
like the main section was just there's manga for everyone.
And there was just it was just showcasing the best of each genre that there was.
There was like a sports section.
There was like adventure and there's stuff like that.
And one piece was one of them.
And I was just looking at one piece in like just just I was just reading
a little bit of one piece that just had a page.
And it clicked in my mind that I didn't really consider it all
because I don't I didn't really just even really think of one piece.
But like one piece looks like perfect, like it visually looks like everything
that I've always wanted my art to look like.
And it like looks perfect.
Like like like it resonates with me so much.
And I had never even like considered like, oh, maybe I should read one piece.
Yeah, maybe it's easy to get lost and forget about that.
Yeah, it's just like for all this shit we talk about like the podcast,
like the political situation, the specific interaction of the characters and what not.
But like, frankly, that's all good.
And I enjoy it very much.
But like just the classic going to a new world, like seeing just that double
wide double page spread of like this new land and just I mean, Oda loves doing that shit.
I remember the shout of like when they first saw Fishman Island after the time skip.
And that was like it's like this crazy like underwater bubble world where they went through this
like they've been they traveling through this underwater current.
And like it was dark and spooky.
They're all these monsters, but they get to this one place where there's
like a magical light beaming down from above.
And it's just this it's just like, oh, my God, there's so much adventure
that awaits us in this new world.
And people have various thoughts about Fishman Island.
But like that's oh, I love that stuff.
That's that's the best they had like a lot of originals for of
Manga panels and stuff from from Tezuka and Kira Toriyama
and one piece and all that Naruto.
They had a bit of Jojo in there.
I took some pictures.
If you go to my Instagram.
Oh, yeah. A few put a link to that.
The original original pages from like Dragon Ball and stuff.
And you're able to see like the sketch layers on these original pages.
And it was and you were able to see how they colored in the black.
You're able to see the unevenness of some of the like the colored in black
black blotches.
It was incredible.
It was incredible because you always just think, oh, like when you read
a manga, like everything's so even and black and everything.
So it looks like it was it was chiseled by a God.
But but seeing that like, no, a human made this a human made mistakes in some ways.
And there's like a sketch layer underneath.
So it was guiding him.
This is why, dude, this is why I one of the many reasons why I
prefer manga so much to animate, generally speaking.
It yeah, it's it has exactly that human core feel of like a man
slaved over this and worked to convey his emotions through pictures.
And yeah, it like you feel his presence like in every panel of a manga drawn,
whereas like the anime adaptation, it's like, no, no, no, like someone shit this
out because it was like their monthly quota and they like had to get these
frames animated and they don't even look that good because they're in-betweens.
No, not not much love was put into any individual moment of this
outside like the key frames sometimes.
But I feel the love so much more strongly in manga.
That's why it's my I mean, I haven't seen any like
manga pages in real life, like the actual like versions.
But like in college, we went to a comic exhibit and we saw Dave Sim's work on
Cerebus, like the originals, like there's just one awesome cover for the
Cerebus volume.
I think it's three church and state volume one.
And it's just as huge because like in that volume, like Cerebus basically becomes
the pope and it's like a huge breakdown of like religion and stuff.
So there's this big picture of him, like on top of this building preaching
to like hundreds of people in like a crowd.
And that's like the cover of the book.
And I always thought it was super cool.
And they had the original.
You could see like the like like Zipotone stickers like up cut and
applied on this page.
And the page was huge compared to what it is on the book.
You could see all the details and like I came everywhere because it was the
best moment of my life.
You're just a small point on this.
It's just that when I when I prepare the podcast thumbnails, I do a lot of work
like cutting out the white and like pasting the images on there.
So I've I've actually spent a lot of time like actually
there's even actually even in the in the very last podcast thumbnail, there's
if you look on the on the most right side of it, in fact, let me get a link to it.
There's there's the guy's hat of the Kappa Kawamatsu, the Kappa who was revealed in that.
His hat was cut off on the edge.
So what I did was like, oh, that doesn't look good.
I actually I redrew just that does not exist the edge of his hat.
So like so that's just the kind of thing.
And I've done actually done that a lot making these thumbnails over the years
of like redrawing.
So I've actually almost done some like actual redrawing work the way that
like scan laders do when they're turning this into English and whatnot.
So I feel like I pretty intimately am down with with the manga pages.
And when you zoom in real close, when you're like cutting out white or you're
trying to crop out things, you can see like those little splotches,
those like little tiny details that you never see as you're burning through
trying to get like, oh, what devil fruits revealed?
Like what what are the big character interactions?
But when you zoom in, you hone in, that's that's what I really mean.
It's like, oh, that's splotch.
He probably didn't even put that there intentionally.
But this is just like from the pen, from his ink of like drawing
the outline of this character.
There's like a little detail there that I don't know.
It's a little silly, but it's like, I feel like like, oh, this is like me,
like really communicating intimately with the guy who made this.
Like I'm seeing details that most people don't see when they're
just skimming through this and I feel a real close connection.
And I love it sometimes draw things that are missing.
Or like covered by text or speech bubbles in poddika thumbnails.
And it's really cool.
Like, except for armadillos thumbnails.
Yeah, just adding the little adding the little bit in and be like,
you know what, it pretty much looks like it fits.
That's cool.
Maybe I could do a drawing one of these days.
Maybe, maybe.
Also, they had Man Ben playing on a little TV in that exhibition, which is cool.
What? What's that?
What?
Mine then.
In the wild.
And yeah, on the TV in the manga exhibition with subtitles.
And I was like, oh, you could watch a little episode of that.
I wonder if any more episodes have been translated.
Probably not because like one comes out every six months.
What's Mon Ben again?
It's that show where the guy puts the camera in another manga artist's
studio and films him for a week.
And then at the end of the week, they like watch the footage and like talk
about it and discuss shit.
That's related to the craft.
Big quotation marks.
Man, you guys know about Facebook ad auto-generated shirts?
I don't think so.
Yeah, unfortunately, you know, my brother, my brother showed me this.
I don't know whether it's the same thing, but like a shitpost
generated t-shirt design thing where you can actually buy the shitpost
generated shirts.
I just saw, I just saw a retweet of a picture of one in the wild
that says, I'm the lucky one.
This is this is the whole shirt.
I'm the lucky one.
I have a crazy boyfriend who happens to cuss a lot.
He was born in August.
He has tattoos and he has anger issues and serious dislike for stupid people.
You hurt me and they'll never find your body.
Yes, he bought me this shirt.
Oh, OK, that's totally just like I'm the proud son of a mom.
Yes, you bought me this shirt. It's literally my shirt.
I'll post it in the in the channel.
There you go.
There have been a lot of shirts like that where it's it's like a very
hyper specific, like like SoundCloud, like there's there's another one.
I see another one that's about a grand like thinking thinking I'm just a spoiled
child was your first mistake.
I'm a spoiled grandson of a crazy grandma.
She is also a grumpy old woman who has anger issues and a serious dislike
for stupid people.
You hurt me and they'll never find your body.
Yes, she bought me this shirt.
So like there's like there's like chunks of that get like recycled and
yeah, yeah, and matched up.
Fascinating. What is great is Facebook is terrifying over there.
They got the algorithms.
It's a book with every every face in the face.
If you have a face, they know it's like it's like that guy from Avatar,
the Last Ambender, who steals the faces.
Oh, yeah, that's a great way in the in the in the Facebook headquarters.
There is an entire room like floor that is just is a field of wheat.
Yeah. Yeah.
And is this true?
Yeah, no, this is true.
And in the middle, in the middle of the offices,
Mark Zuckerberg has an office in the exact middle of Facebook HQ.
And in his office is a giant glass cube that you can see inside of his
office at all times.
I'm not Google search it right now.
I'm not fucking with you.
Maybe this is a safety mechanism to make sure he never touches his dick
and he can't be caught.
He'll never be tempted because everyone's watching.
This this is the best shirt.
This is this is the best shirt.
That's a best shirt.
I'm not just a father to an amazing daughter.
I'm also a veteran who did four tours in Iraq and I have chronic diarrhea.
I think that's a baby tanks flanking veteran really bring the whole design together.
Yeah, it does look quite small.
Isn't that like a woman's t-shirt?
It looks like a baby.
I don't know about that.
Maybe it's a woman's tea.
Yeah, I'm looking for this glass cube.
I can't I can't see it.
Oh, I should mark Mark Zuckerberg glass office cube.
I'm OK.
I don't know how these are generated.
But I wonder if like it's there, though.
Trust me, do they will it like will Facebook here?
No, we'll Facebook like look at will Facebook like look at your profile,
like take your information and then like generate a shirt to show you specifically
based on like the things you've maybe or post.
That's my guess or whatever.
Like was like was this generated by Facebook for someone who has a dad
who did four tours in Iraq and has like liked posts.
I don't think he's generated by Facebook.
I would assume that this is like an algorithm by some company
or some like, you know, reseller t-shirt company buying Facebook ads.
Because I know like this is like an evolution.
Like the basic Pokemon version of this that I was aware of was you just
you get shirts that have like people's names on them and have like cute little
like dumb, normie core phrases around someone's name.
Like I'm Ben, I'm the coolest.
And then you run a Facebook ad that's like if the person's name is Ben,
run this ad and then the Ben like dumb Ben is like, I'm Ben and then they buy the shirt.
There is a relatively simple explanation.
Finally, a shirt just for me.
I mean, I've seen many shirts like this, frankly, in like the Asian world
where people who just don't speak English that well, they buy shirts in English
because like it's supposed to be kind of cool or whatever.
I've seen many of those.
No, this is not the work of someone who doesn't speak English.
This is this is the work.
Well, OK, well, maybe.
And I'm just one and I'm just wondering what who is running the algorithm
and where is it getting the data and how Facebook ad lecture literally went.
Like, like are these are these generated from an individual's data
and then advertised to them and like like generated
or are they or or well, I mean, that or are they simply like a complete mishmash
of concepts that are just sort of sprayed out onto the Internet
and like advertised at random in the hopes that one will just perfectly
describe somebody who can say, I just don't know.
We got to wait for the Vsauce video to explain it all.
That's very true.
So so it's like this.
Is it time for voicemails?
Is it is a time now?
I feel like it is.
I think it might be. Sure.
Yeah, sure.
Now, OK, before we go to proper voicemails,
there's there's like an update from some individuals.
So let's let's just play this.
This this doesn't count.
This isn't a real voicemail.
But this is from Mark it did.
Mark it did. OK. Commence.
Hello and welcome to market.
How do they market at market doing how the market do fuck?
Sorry, we haven't promoted our dating seminar a while,
but that is going to change right the fuck now.
We promise the thing and we will deliver.
We will birth the Sprovian bottle and biographical bitch, baby,
right onto your lap as you stare and disgust and confusion.
And then, well, we'll see what happens then.
I guess what I'm trying to say is follow at PCP
dating on Twitter to motherfucking stay informed,
stay vigilant, stay updated.
This is a signing out.
OK, there you go. Update.
Follow. What was it happening?
PCP dating, Sam, or is a PCP dating?
Whatever he said, that's the one.
It's at it's at PCP.
Dating is the official one, the full right. OK, OK.
And last last update was some new Tommy.
Indeed. Oh, I saw that on July 12th.
It's pretty, pretty great.
I can't believe this is two days ago from from today's.
Well, I'm glad I'm glad that's I mean, I'm glad they're still going to.
I expect it instantly.
Oh, by the way, so in contrast to that, that was fine.
The dating sim's cool.
I have to give a verbal lambasting to one I'll die of the I'll die
corporation, your voicemail.
OK, look, we've been we've been softballing you for a while.
I'll die because they, you know, they were fine.
The Robo voice thing was cool.
The voicemail was you sent this time.
It was fine. It was fine.
But the problem was it was a fucking like the topic that you said
and you talk about with your Robo for a while was fine.
I know this was sent by an algorithm and you're not to blame,
but it just turns into a fucking ad to like follow you on Twitter at the end.
Like what the fuck was that?
It was like just some please follow me.
Like it was a tease, like the subject for like this project they're working on.
And I just like, oh, my God, there's nothing that makes me want to puke
more than these like just advertising their own project, like in a voicemail.
So I'm tempted to go PCP voice jail for that one.
You you you you've played you've played voicemails that do exactly.
When they're entertaining, that's fine.
As long as it's entertaining, anything is fine.
But this was, I mean, mediocre.
And also like if you'd listen to it, it was just an ad.
It just go go to the speak pipe and listen to it.
Just not great.
Just very reprehensible and rethink your your life.
Please, please, that's it.
Maybe I'm wrong.
You guys can correct me, but I just thought it was simply terrible.
So and follow and follow.
I'll die for that.
I'll die three, one, four on Twitter.
Indeed, I thought it was particularly egregious.
But OK, so that's that.
That's out of the way.
Let's get some quality content.
We've got the that's all that I'll die three, one, four on.
OK, analog signal audio demon is calling in.
So let's see what he has to say and go.
I am the audio demons.
I am a demon that can curse your audio to make it sound like shit.
Oh, no, I don't need it.
I will need you all to state your age.
Twenty nine, twenty nine.
Eighteen, huh?
Which one of you is the eldest?
I think it's Ben.
Yeah, it's me.
It's me for the next 30 seconds.
You will be cursed with flanger starting now.
Oh, no, Ben, you sound so fucked up.
What? Oh, no.
Well, well, well, well, well, well.
Say something Ben, say it would say.
I can't think of anything that I would say.
Say something about communism.
It's too horrendous.
OK, I think the time's over.
There you go. Am I cursed? Am I cursed now?
You fucking wasted that, Ben, man.
I'm angry at you.
You wasted that so fucking hard.
You didn't say literally anything.
What? I'm sorry.
Yeah, you fucking should be.
This guy cursed you under the trouble of cursing you,
trying to locate who the eldest person was.
He came in here with the intent to put a magic spell on you.
And only because we were like, oh, what do I say?
Yeah, pretty, pretty bad.
Literally anything.
Pretty terrible.
But can we put Ben the voice jail?
It's not, it's not.
Michael, this fucking dumb spell didn't work.
Well, maybe maybe with a little editing magic.
Blame the blame the player, not the game or something.
Well, OK, Ben's dead.
Let's move on.
We've got a voicemail.
OK, this is from one doopity schmoople.
You know him, you love him.
My first. Let's see what he has to say.
Let's see what he has to say and go.
Hey, guys, you're here.
Yeah, I'm just calling in to ask for advice,
because apparently that's what the show is for.
They always say that.
Basically, stop saying that.
I'm almost 18, getting ready to move out.
And I don't know what to do.
Not sure if I want to go to college or not.
Not sure if I don't.
If you don't know, don't want to.
I don't even have a job, so I don't know
if I'm going to pay myself.
Don't know if I should stay here for a couple more years or what.
Wait, that's.
I do I want to be in this,
but I haven't really drawn anything.
So do I want to be in this?
OK, I got it. I got it.
Yeah. I don't know.
Just asking.
OK, you've given us zero information.
Yeah, like what do you do?
What does he mean that I'm getting ready to move out?
But I don't know if I'm going to college.
I don't have a job.
I don't know if maybe I should just stay here.
Yeah, don't you have a plan for, I mean, moving out requires finances.
I mean, obviously, don't move out until you know where you're going.
I think that's what he was saying at the end,
like maybe I'll just stay here.
So I assume that's not set in stone yet.
OK, hold on.
I as as Jupiter's father, who he would be moving from in this area.
Right, right.
I had no idea that you were leaving the rough house, but you know, that's fine.
We all got to spread our rings somehow.
Got to spread our O-ring sometime.
First of all, if you want to become an artist, but you haven't drawn before,
put that I'm not going to say on the backburn and since it like,
don't try and do it.
But in the sense that like, don't be like, oh, you know,
like I'll make a living being an artist.
I'll just get around to drawing someday.
Like, no, you have to start drawing today.
Today, I'll make my Patreon and post like something today.
And then tomorrow, it'll be a job.
Yeah, yeah.
OK, so that's a possibility for tomorrow's dupity.
You have to start today, drawing so that you can be ready
to make a living off it in five years.
So yeah, you should have been doing this your entire.
I don't even know, like, surely there's another way that you could be doing this.
I can't believe that you would think that you can just like start doing it
and we'll be fine.
Not everyone's been saying and been saying was doing it.
But like, it's not even true.
It's like a lie. It's not even real.
He had drawn before it.
Fuck you. Yeah. Not a lie.
I mean, I was I mean, I was way older than Duke when I started like drawing much.
Yeah. I mean, I never drawn a day in my life before that.
You put in years of work before we ever started, like, you know, fine.
Yeah. But less. Yeah.
But less work than a normal human.
Less years than a normal human. Sure.
Sure. But he's put in zero years.
Yeah. Yeah.
You can't work with zero.
Also, if you don't want to go to college, literally don't go to college.
If you do not have an express reason to go to college, you shouldn't go to college.
College is good and it is a useful tool.
And if you come up with a reason to go to college and if you come up with a valid
good reason to go, then of course you should go.
But right now you shouldn't go just for fun or that it's like all the thing to do.
Unless you have a reason to go, don't go. That's obvious.
I mean, college is a tool like any other.
Why would you like, hey, hey, guys, should I pick up a jackhammer?
Just like, I don't like it.
My parents just think that I should.
Should I like just like a pick it up and like, you know, use it on the ground?
Is that the sound it makes?
Yeah, I have a suggestion.
Moving out is a good thing for almost anyone because like staying with your
parents will keep you with the mind of a child.
And like, that's fine.
It just it keeps you from developing like life ownership skills,
which I think are very good to have, frankly, relatively as early as possible.
And like, what's the word I'm looking for?
Like commitment and responsibility.
That's the word I'm looking for.
So I would say like stay with your parents until you can get a job and save up
some money and I would recommend moving out.
But I mean, you've got so little details to what you want to do.
So my suggestion is like work on trying to figure out what you want to do.
And in that, like if you want to be an artist, great.
So practice that in your spare time, but get a job and move out so you can
support yourself, doesn't have to be an amazing job and like get an apartment
somewhere to do that.
You don't know what your life passion is.
Your passion is to try as many things as possible until something collects.
I build up some savings.
You need.
I just want to phrase it in the way that like if you don't have any plan
for what you're doing and you have no job, then don't even think about moving
out because you just will fucking immediately die.
If you have literally how is it going to buy the apartment too early?
It's too early to even think about that right now.
You're obviously not in the position to do that.
I mean, you got to you got to start.
This is like a Maslow's hierarchy.
You have to start with the foundation.
OK, like what do I want with my life?
I want to like live on my own, presumably.
OK, what's required for that money?
OK, what do I need for money?
A job. So OK, got to start with the job, then get the money, then get the apartment.
Yeah, things of this nature to try to think approach things that way.
Let us know. Let us know how it goes.
OK, on to the next one.
Call from Italian boy.
Let's see what he has to say.
OK, go. Hello.
It's Italian boy. Nice.
He's listening.
Thank you for giving us your sweet, sweet cash.
And I just wanted to congratulate you guys for reaching 20,000 subscribers.
Hey, but you don't give a fuck.
And it doesn't matter, but I also don't matter.
So yeah. All right.
Thanks, buddy. What a voice.
OK, what a voice mail.
Why did you play that?
Because he congratulated us and said nice things.
Who reached 3,000?
No, we reached 20,000.
The BCP. Wow.
That's some accent you got there.
OK, I'm going to add
a Italian boy to the PCP Munchy Concerts.
So he is the first PCP Munchy Concerts Italian boy.
Look at you. You're such a European.
Yeah, Italian boy is now my right hand man.
He's my first son in this timeline.
Oh, wow. OK.
Congratulations. All right.
Dupe de disown.
Well, no, no, no, it's a different timeline, it's a different time.
They're separate but equal, separate but equal.
That's that's universe one, five, five.
This is the PCP as opposed to the Sliver.
OK, let's let's kick up the quality with another voicemail from one dumb fuck.
Here we go. I didn't realize I called him. Go listen.
I need some advice on how to be not such a like bumbling retard.
Because every time I listen to my voicemails that I record, I have like a million like,
uh, uh, uh, like a million, like every other word is uh, and then the words that aren't
uh, are like, and I don't know.
It just sounds retarded and really bad, and I need help speaking like a person who speaks
English.
This is a terrible question.
Okay.
He just keeps rambling about this.
The obvious answer is to talk more.
I mean, I was definitely like that before.
No.
I'm still kind of like that, uh, but through talking a lot, I've just gotten better at
not doing it.
Just record it again, and this time don't say those things.
I mean, yeah.
You gotta do a few dry runs first.
I could tell he was trying not to say like an um, in that particular recording, so I guess
he did that.
I know, I know.
This is, I thought this was a good question, because this, I thought it's not even just
for him, but for everybody.
No, this question sucks.
The answer is self-evident.
Well, yeah, it is, but like, here, here's some tangible advice for anybody who feels
this way, because I'm, a lot of your voicemails get weeded out, because you sound like shit.
So if you want to just get to the point, uh, here's what you do.
This is super easy.
You have a computer, get audacity, record your voicemail ahead of time, like just say the
words into audacity, and you will hear back how you sound.
And if you got too many likes and ums, you're like, oh, should I gotta work on that?
Do it again, and try to suppress it.
You'll hear if you succeed or fail, and just keep doing that until you sound good.
And then you're improving your, your speaking overall.
And I feel this, because I do this too much myself when I talk, and I, I haven't done
that.
If you, if you don't have a microphone, and you're using like your discord, your phone,
there's recording apps to say this, yeah, just get a free recording app and just do
the same.
Just listen to yourself until you know what is gross, and then you can feel ashamed about
it and change it.
This isn't showcased on the PCP whatsoever, because PCP is possibly the most highest stake
scenario that one person can talk to, and they're like in all of society, like it has
the most like, like negative consequences for speaking and not as fast as humanly possible.
But what I do in normal life is, this is, this is a life hack for you.
When you want to say um or like, just don't say anything.
Just take a small little pause.
No one will really notice.
You sound smart.
Yeah, and you sound smart.
That's true.
That's like an actual speaking tip.
And it's not a big deal.
You sound considered.
Yeah.
Uh, okay.
On to the next one.
Uh, Munchy, we have a voicemail from one, the only fly away now has called in with a
voicemail.
Yes.
The man himself.
Uh, let's, let's hear.
Go, go, go, go.
The name's a fly away now.
The same guy who has internet clout for some reason, because I was hammering into a presumed
mentally ill future United States Marine for a few years until it was a, I can't discover
it to all be a ruse named Park Road, do 91.
I've been listening to the PCP for a good half a year, even though I heard first heard
of Munchy's lecture on Diggle Nation years before that.
I didn't even watch it fully until the last six months because I wasn't big into a podcast
like things until I realized you guys were angry.
Actually quality.
Oh, thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'm not quirky or trying to be a manic pixie.
No.
Half the other underage liberals sending you stuff, but I actually appreciate the podcast
with all my heart after I watched all the lectures and realized, oh, hey, they talk
weekly, they do it consistently and their degeneracy is personable, even to normies
like me.
So you have, which is far more than any of us deserve.
And when Andrew Yang gets elected, I'll give my monthly bag with a PCP Patreon.
Thank you.
I don't know how you handle guests and whatnot.
I wouldn't mind hopping on for a bit to give you some insight on Lollacows from my perspective
or really just anything, just so I can get Ben to shut the fuck up about politics for
one second.
Dude, this guy's Yang, no, this guy's Yang Yang.
Oh yeah.
Big time.
Only, only on the condition that we only talk about Andrew Yang.
Only on the condition that we all vote for Andrew Yang.
Yeah, yeah.
Like live stream.
Oh, dude, Ben, you should totally live stream voting, but anyway, that was, that was lovely.
That was a real human being voicemail.
I just forgot.
Remind me.
What was the flyaways now status?
He was involved with Parkour Dude.
What was his?
He, he, he was, he was affiliated with Team Gamer Food and he was one of the many Islamic
trolls.
I believe, I believe he, he was one of the, he was during, he was present during the
trial of Jace and I can't remember if it was Flyaway Now that pressed Jace on being way
too racist even for trolls or for someone else.
But he was definitely present and he, he, he was part of that crowd.
He was part of the opposition to Jace, the conservative party, to Jace liberal party.
Fantastic.
So, so he was one of the people that, that, that ringed the, the juicy, juicy nectar
of Jace's mouth.
Well, an important, an important job.
An important job.
Yeah.
Part of the reason, part of the reason why I made that lecture, because if it wasn't
for people like him, then Jace would have just kind of wallowed in relevancy.
It wasn't for people purposely trying to provoke him to get him to, if it wasn't for people
engaging with the ARG that Yon had made, then I wouldn't have mattered at all.
It's small world.
Such a small fucking world.
I can't believe it.
I know.
I was looking at that video, 120K views for that, for that little story.
I can't believe it.
I really can.
I love the fucking lectures, man.
They love them.
They guzzle them.
Like water.
Like Chikus.
Well, well, I gotta start preparing for Chris Chan, too, electric Google it.
Oh, are you doing that?
Is that the word?
Oh, yeah.
Everyone agrees that I need to make an update version on everything that happened with Chris
afterwards.
Good idea.
I need to brush up on it myself, because there's a lot.
I mean, a lot has happened, and I only know the broadstrips of it.
Are you going to get first-hand account from BronyCon, since Chris will be there?
I forgot.
Chris Chan is at BronyCon.
He's going to BronyCon.
We will be there.
She's going to BronyCon.
Am I allowed to not take her seriously on this, because she's so unserious in all other
ways?
No, you can't.
You look like a big asshole if you do that, so you can make your own decisions.
But why do I take her word for it, because she seems so confused on all other things
in life?
Well, you really don't want to look like a fucking asshole, and that's the reason.
You're not giving me any actual reason.
That's not much of a point.
You're just saying that it's bad to do it.
Why is it bad?
It's a bad take and a bad look.
Should I also take seriously these claims of the dimensional merge that is happening
like any day now that Chris makes over and over again?
The point of it is that she believes that she is, so if she believes that she is a different
gender, then you've got to respect it.
Obviously, he doesn't respect her in any way.
Just the way I need to respect the dimensional merge claim is I don't understand the distinction.
Shut the fuck up.
Let's talk about something else.
All right.
Anyway, I want to go back to Fly Away Now and just say that I would like to know more about
how you circled back.
Did you just have nothing to do and then watch the lecture to completion and then just six
months ago or something and then you got into it?
I'm surprised.
I'm always surprised that there are people who get into the PCP now and just haven't been
following along for literal years and are just like leftovers from when we actually made
good videos.
It is good to see.
I'm always surprised and you know what, top of the morning to you, as Jeff Septekai would
say.
We poo-poo a lot.
I mean, I certainly do.
This notion that people would even get into the show at all, but I guess it's possible.
I guess it can be done through some mechanisms.
It is a little strange due to the fact that the people on the show vary and the quality
of the shows vary a lot in quality and topic.
The idea of people just seeing one and then seeing another one and finding that there
is not really a link between them necessarily and then continuing to watch them is unexpected
at least.
Too true.
Once you get in the third one, then you're along for the ride, I think.
That makes sense.
You're therefore like the personalities rather than what they're saying or how smartly they're
saying it.
Three's a pattern.
Yeah, you're in the pattern at that point.
And according to this guy, though I doubt his claim that he's actually a normie, but
we even have the normie reach according to him.
Would a normie be one of the people provoking Jayce to...
Yeah.
I'm just saying.
That's kind of as hard to believe.
But maybe.
I mean, there are degrees of going there.
I'll take that at face value due to the fact that he just left a voicemail.
It was not like a voice comedy routine.
That's true.
There's degrees of being normie.
It was refreshing to see just like a normal fucking human speak to me.
Imagine.
It wasn't this drawn out like voice recording that was fucked to hell in audacity.
Well, speaking, speaking of...
Oh, yeah.
I was really refreshing.
I mean, you can't wait to see it.
That brief respite is over.
Our next voicemail is went on a date with a milf.
And let's hear how that goes.
Damn.
No.
Guys.
That's quality women's, dude.
Hello.
Guys, I just got back from a date with a milf, dude.
Nice.
Oh, my fucking...
I'm in a Cougar Life account because I've always been in older women because they're
much more mature and fucking stable.
Like yourself.
Most women my age.
Most women our age.
Ben St. listen to this shit.
She was amazing.
She was amazing, dude.
She was 50.
She was a career woman.
She's a lawyer.
She writes grants.
She's amazing.
She's fucking amazing.
She's beautiful.
And I just went on a fucking date with her and I thought Cougar Life was a scam, dude.
Every fucking account was like fake accounts and then all of a sudden she was like two
and a half hours away.
She drove like two hours here because apparently she commutes all the time, dude.
She's fucking amazing.
She's amazing.
And we're going to fucking bang, dude, on the second or third date, I think we're going
to bang.
She was going to get a hotel down here and she was going to stay there because she was
going to go to the beach the next morning.
But oh my God, she's so fucking sexy.
Change your batteries.
Change your smoke detector.
She has a shit ton of money.
She travels everywhere.
She's so mature.
Ben St., man.
I'm telling you, you're a broke ass nigga.
You've got to find yourself a fucking milf, man.
They're amazing.
They're fucking amazing.
They could be your sugar mamas, man.
My God.
She's amazing.
I'm going to keep you guys updated if I bang her.
Thanks.
I'll call back.
Yeah, dude.
I'm drunk out of my fucking mind right now.
Dude, call in while banging.
It was a surreal night.
Yeah, good idea.
I can't believe she was even real.
And we fucking met up.
Holy shit.
Is this real?
What do we think, guys?
Is this real or what?
I think that...
The story doesn't sound too unbelievable.
100% real.
I think he met someone who was 50.
That seems within the realm of possibility.
But like everything...
Well, I mean...
I mean, he was drunk at the time.
Is this a glowing...
Or should we necessarily take all this as like a possible, like we should follow this
life advice?
I mean, probably not.
I'm sure it's...
I've never dated a cougar who was 50 or even close.
And they're on cougarlife.com.
So, I mean, it's one way to go.
Ben, I mean, I know that you're a mill flover and that's your license plate number.
Are you going to follow this?
Yeah.
That's right.
Yeah, you know what?
You're...
Yeah.
This is actually...
You got me.
I'm on cougarlife right now, signing up for an account.
It's the right thing to do.
Me and quality women, we're going to converse.
We're going to...
Well, we'll trade notes.
All right?
DM me.
Sounds good.
Excellent.
Good luck.
Man, guys, quality women has really just grown out of a shell, you know?
He's gone from being stereotypical.
You know what?
He's been stereotypical.
He was so...
He was so conflicted and now he's found peace.
Yeah.
He's been stereotypical like, oh, my girlfriend's so fucking crazy.
What a bitch.
He's just, you know, banging milks a day and day on cougarlife with their hands full.
What a...
What an arc.
What an arc we've been privy to.
Just...
I mean, imagine.
Just imagine you meet someone online and then the entire time you're talking and you're
just thinking, oh, women, we have sex, women, we only have sex.
That's the mark of a real genius.
Isn't that how every online interaction goes?
I thought that was just normal.
Most of them.
Okay, let's move on.
We've got a short...
Great job.
Well, actually...
Before we move on, I just want to say that I was looking at...
I was just checking the comments of the deletion lecture and then I started to absentmindedly
just scrolling through the PCP.
And I just...
Just a small little point here on Chewbacca's Osamonga Dio.
It says that the location where you filmed it in is the Gardens of Vatican City.
You can click here and it will be above the title.
We were recording the Chewbacca's in the Gardens of Vatican City, according to...
That's a lot.
Yeah, yeah.
Very nice.
Cool.
Fantastic.
Okay.
Let's move on.
We've got...
Okay.
Now, this is one of these things I don't normally do, but this is good enough.
It's Anifred's application for the Teen CP.
So I think Anifred is literally 13, right?
So he's just barely...
Yeah, no, he really is, yeah.
Okay.
All right.
Let's set him up.
We have no involvement as the PCP, but Teen CP, listen up.
Let's see if he's got what you need.
Oh, he's an Anifred.
It's about time we've got some English blood on the Teen CP.
Chewboy, Anifred.
Let's go.
It's Chewboy, Anifred.
We've had a gun and I'll shoot you dead in your dungeon with dead mom.
It was red.
If we steal your dad, because I'm a hardcore lad, I'll make you a fucking chad.
Talk about pride.
What are you proud for?
You've got an anime vid in a lanky hall, kick down the door, so I'm calling.
If you're a woman, then don't join.
You can chew on my pork loin.
Now watch for your zoom.
Crack that soul, Anifred.
Boy, I get it all.
I'm ready for a brawl at your Teen CP.
You know what to call.
Don't stall.
Yeah.
Yay.
Anifred, you know.
Another masterpiece.
Anifred keeps knocking out of the part with his regimen.
He just keeps delivering the hits.
Someone put together an album.
Set that to a beat.
Yeah, help that boy out.
Yeah, please.
Do a remix.
Okay, great.
Let's move on.
Who Wants to Be a PCP Millionaire?
Here we go.
Another episode of everyone's favorite show.
Let's see how it goes this week.
Here we go.
Here we go again.
And go.
Welcome back to Who Wants to Be a PCP Millionaire?
Oh, so you're truly my man.
Last week left, Johnny, you pulled the PCP to see what they wanted from the voicemails.
How you got your answer yet?
Oh, yeah.
You bet you did, man.
I want to see the last voicemail.
Just got to give a last voicemail.
And I got to tell you, this answer is all kinds of right, like a fine woman.
Okay, Johnny.
Right.
The question is, what do the PCP want from the voicemails?
Is it, A, violent relationships, B, piano solos, C, interrogation, or D, ramblin'?
I'm going to go C, interrogation, violent answer.
Correct.
Next question.
Yeah, there you go.
What did Munchy request the real-ass Batman sing on the PCP?
Is it, A, the PCP theme song, B, one-two oatmeal, C, you guys suck your cocks, or D, the alphabet
song?
Oh baby.
I'm going to pay more attention than the voicemails.
I'm going to go with one, two, oatmeal, fight B, violent answer.
It's like, well, Johnny, you are...
Correct.
Yeah.
You know, real-ass Batman, I didn't know you could sing.
I can't, but Munchy, Munchy take, requested that I try.
Speaking of which, Nate, you would be so kind, please play the voicemail.
Next one.
Okay, ready, go.
Here we are.
One, two, three, go.
Perfect.
One, two, oatmeal, Kirby is a pink guy.
One, two, oatmeal, because Kirby's very cute.
Is this the real song?
Yep.
One, two, oatmeal, Kirby is a pink guy.
One, two, oatmeal, because Kirby's very cute.
Kirby inhales his enemies and makes it later.
Kirby's so happy there's something he can because he's such a pink guy.
He inhales his enemies and makes it later.
One, two, oatmeal, Kirby is a pink guy.
One, two, oatmeal, because Kirby's very cute.
Here comes Kirby tonight to make it to protect because he's attacked by King Dedede.
Man, I swings his sword, King Dedede.
Here comes Kirby tonight to protect King Dedede.
Who protect King Dedede?
Man, I swings his sword.
How is this so fucking long?
Oh my God.
Oh, he hit the time limit.
He hit the time limit.
It ended.
Finally.
What a triumph is now.
Literally what a triumph is that.
Wow.
A great one.
I'll tell you that.
Yeah.
What a triumph is that?
A great one.
Thank you.
Everyone look at one, two, oatmeal.
Someone speed up, set that to the song.
I actually don't because you just listened to it just now.
That's all you need to know.
Yeah, that's how it sounds.
Okay, let's move on.
This is our last voicemail.
First, we've got Lost Tape Archive 5A.
Davoo?
Question mark?
Let's hear what we have.
Go.
I've been sitting on the shore for nearly two months.
Searching for answers.
Searching the ooze.
This smooths.
And for what?
I haven't found any tape.
All I got was this circular disc.
A CD, if you will.
What am I supposed to do with this?
I can't play a CD.
I don't have a Walkman.
But that's when it occurred to me.
This isn't just any old goo.
It's the goo.
Davoo.
I choose you.
I am the goo.
I will play this CD for you.
Holy shit, that worked.
Okay, part two. Here we go. Go.
It's Davoo. He's back.
I like to pretend that my girlfriend is a retard.
Because it makes me hang out with her whenever work permits.
I make out with her when she's taking a shit.
Oh no.
But my girlfriend is a child.
Makes my dad go wild.
They would leave you for me if they could.
To take a pic under my hood.
When I save peanut butter sandwich.
Do I put the image on the P?
Or on the E?
I sure hurt nobody notices.
But my insight into editing is beginning to tear baby shit.
I'm not as smart as you think I am.
My dick has two legs.
Two arms to clamp on your clam.
And stab my C-man on your womb.
Bixby, a bixby, a bixby.
Oh god.
Oh my god.
This is horrific.
Ben?
Munchy.
Executive decision?
Yeah.
Ban anyone from entering the Slime Sea with a CD.
Ban them.
Just outright ban them from ever doing it again.
They were a mistake.
We'll kill them on site.
If you're seen on the fair with a CD,
you will have to answer to us.
I've seen a lot of people playing a lot of Smash Bros. brawl
farming CDs in the subspace emissary.
And they're just piling up.
I think that was a war crime.
I've never heard such a savage takedown
of a poor sweet boy.
Poor Davoo.
Well, Davoo, even though he left the chat,
he's still with us in spirit.
God, I hope not.
I don't want him to hear these things.
Yeah, he should rest in peace.
Oh my god.
Well, Lost Tape Archive does his work again.
Thanks for unearthing that, Relic.
Classic.
Who has Lost Tape Archive done yet?
He's done a lot of us.
I think like half or most of us at this point,
not all of us yet,
someone should put that information together.
It should be like a playlist of some kind.
Because these are incredible.
Yeah, the audio editing is off the charts.
That beat was pretty fire.
That was pretty fire, I must say.
If Lost Tape Archive isn't already in the voice grail,
I think he deserves to be there.
Just for the sheer effort he's putting in there.
He deserves to be there for his past crimes.
So this crime, he's putting straight into voice jail.
What do you think?
Can he exist in a superposition of jail and...
Voice Azkaban.
Yeah, I think he exists in both simultaneously.
Torn between two worlds.
Voice Limbo.
Okay, so it shall be.
He exists in both simultaneously,
like Schrodinger's Cat or whatever the deal is.
There you go.
Schrodinger's Cat Clues.
Click on the link in the description to watch Gay for a Day.
On our bandcamp, it's in high quality.
High quality rips way better than the live version.
The highest of quality.
It could not have been more high quality.
Let me just say about Gay for a Day.
By the way, that had seven tracks, right?
I didn't miss it.
Seven tracks, and I believe four bonus tracks
that you get if you download it.
They're not connected to the story.
They are their own standalone songs.
Oh, okay, I didn't listen to those.
By the way, I listened to Gay for a Day,
and I just want to say I loved it.
There were only a couple of times I skipped ahead.
I just, as someone who's on the record,
pushing hard for Gay for a Day to be real,
I'm glad that you finally delivered.
I'm glad that my faith in the project's completion
was not in vain.
Indeed.
Tom was the carrot, and I was the stick
lashing from behind, or the opposite of that.
I don't know, whatever it is.
It exists. Go listen to it.
It is a jolly good time.
I had a great time listening to it.
And now,
if you come in
and give your covers a Gay for a Day song,
we will, of course, play on the voicemails
every single time.
Every single time.
Let's put a quality floor on that real quick
before we...
Munchie and Gibbs said that someone in their band
said that they wanted to do a cover of the album.
God, I hope you stick to it, you coward,
and actually deliver that.
I want to hear it.
Heavy metal covers.
It could use a little bit.
I'll, for keeping the quality of the original,
you know, I hate remakes,
but a reimagining is something else
that I could get behind, you know.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like on the link in the description
to listen to Grimp, too,
should we discuss politics.
And speaking of not
discussing politics, Nate,
I don't want to talk about this right now,
but I think you should watch...
You ever watch ContraPoints?
I've seen ContraPoints a few times, yeah.
ContraPoints' newest video is called
TransTrenders,
and I would recommend you give it a watch
for some things...
Based on our previous discussion in this very episode.
Yes, for some...
things to mull over and chew on.
Look, my only point will be
that I've got no problem, trans people exist.
They seem perfectly real to me, got no issue.
Shut up, I don't care.
But Chris Chan is a different case.
He's not, but anyway.
She's not, fuck!
No! It's spreading.
Alright, anyway.
Watch TransTrenders, it's good.
I'll consider it.
Hey guys, Nate from The Future here.
Listen, I would never do anything like
misgender someone to their face
when they so clearly want to be addressed
in a certain way. That's not my bag.
And of course, this extends to Chris as well.
But this is a comedy discussion
podcast, and we're just
here to discuss ideas,
and I don't think gender or anything else
is a sacred cow.
I don't think it's crazy to have certain
thoughts that some people may be more
or less sincere. We know that
TransTrenders exist to some degree.
Some degree.
And to maybe think about some people that
perhaps they could be in that category,
I don't think is unreasonable.
And I think most people would agree with that point.
But I'm never going to be rude to someone in real life
when they want to be referred to in a certain way.
So I just wanted to make that perfectly clear.
Okay, I think we're all on the same page.
After finishing this conversation,
I actually did go and watch
part of that ContraPoints video.
Her videos are not my favorite stylistically,
but I do think I got the general
thesis out of it that she was trying to convey,
which seemed to be an argument of,
as opposed to arguing about who's male,
who's female, you know, whatever position on the spectrum, whatever,
instead, why not put empathy
and compassion for how people
may feel or identify over
any kind of logical proof or categorization
as to gender? Because is it even that
important? To which I say
that's not a crazy argument
and I can see where people are coming from
to make those kind of points. So does Chris's
gender really matter? Is it my
business to even judge? No,
not really. My only rebuttal to that would be
that, firstly, I do think that gender
has some real use in the real world,
so I don't think it's useful to just throw it
out as a total concept right now.
But also, there's guys like me
and I think a lot of people in a similar position
who are just very
hearingly minded, I guess I'd say,
where we try to categorize things
and put them into boxes and whatnot, and I would
just ask people to have patience
with those of us who don't necessarily put
empathy as our prime, overarching,
most important ideal,
but naturally do think in this kind of
organizing way. I don't think it's
evil or bad, it's just a different
way of approaching the world. Because I think
we all know it is not my prime
virtue. I'm more of a problem
solver. Anyway, thanks for listening,
and I'll talk to you later.
We can use to determine who is or is not
really trans, who does or does not
meet the criteria to be
referred to as the gender of their choosing.
Gender is not as
simple as a question of XX
versus XY, this kind of scientific
interrogation will not yield
us a robust definition
of what is male and what is female.
Therefore, there is no objective
metric that we can use to determine
who does and does not
get to decide their own gender identity.
We must accept that everybody gets to
do that. It's the only logically
consistent position. And accepting
some people's ability to do that while denying
others or doing it sometimes
only in public and only not
in private or whatever solves no
problems and accomplishes nothing.
So in the case where someone
has made it abundantly clear what
their preferred gender is as
Christine has, I think the only thing
to do is to accept what
they wish to be referred to.
And I'm committed to doing that for Christine
and I'm committed to doing that for
everyone. For a question
that has no rigorous logical answer
I think that empathy is the only
thing that we can fall back on
to answer it. Thank you and
get fucked.
Oh hey by the way, right now
after this episode I'm going to be speaking to music
I'm going to be recording a live concert
in Uzgarans. It will have been a week ago
by the time you hear it. But just go back
and I think there will probably be a stream on RFCK
literally a
real live concert with all the
RFCK musicians playing in a voice call
in RFCK an in-game concert
it will have happened. Good job. Fantastic
how exciting.
Is that right after this? Yes. We're recording
okay I'll hop over. Sick.
Alright I guess we're done then.
patreon.com slash the procrastiners people
one dollar get in the
discord five dollars get the bonus episodes
there's like 27 28
I stole water and it's only
one dollar. Dude are we
going to hear that? Is that like in a month?
Yeah no. Oh my god you're right
I forgot about that.
Oh how exciting we got out we got out
that boy. Can you believe they didn't give us a fucking panel
can you believe that? You know what I very much
can believe that because we are not
brony people at all we have no credentials
been out for years
I very much can believe it.
I can't believe this. I'm just going to flex my privilege
here because I'm friends with Saber Sparky got me on
a panel on a free badge so
Saber Sparky is also not a pony
man nor has he been for years so what's
his credentials? Yeah exactly
Nate do you understand there's given that
to anyone who asks. I mean
everybody in that clique does have a panel
despite not being mostly pony people
at all anymore.
Damn. I mean they were like
much bigger than we were at the time
Saber Spark is big
Saber Spark is the
Saber Spark is the worst
He has 800,000 subs
Saber Spark is the worst lowest common denominator
content most toxic shit
I've ever seen on YouTube. Saber Spark?
Yeah his videos are the worst
I mean I never really watched the live but
I hate them. He just rips on shitty fucking
animated videos
They're very milk toast
like unique nemesaurus
tier. Well I think they're worse
than that. They're normie content
but they're not bad normie content
I think they are bad normie content
The voice over is
hilarious
There you go there's some feedback for you
Don't tell him I said that though
You can tell him yourself when you see him in
BronyCon. It's a secret
I can't wait for the
brony brawl while everybody kills each other
Oh won't that be fun. That's the last day
that's Sunday night. It all ends
Because there's no bronycon anymore
we have to die. What's the point
of even being alive?
You're right. You're right
At TP Crasneers on Twitter
Check it out people
And that's gonna do it. Don't forget to give us your money, Patreon
and what not. But okay we're out of here
Another episode in the can. Thanks for being
on our CNX week people.
Bonus episode one of these days. Bye!
Bye!
I'm doing nothing
My dick I'm jerking
Myself I'm sucking
I am an asshole
I am a stupid
I've got a deadline
Don't want to do it