1, 2, 3, sync.
I feel like that was a big delay on that one. Let's try that again.
One more time.
1, 2, 3, sync.
Alright.
Well, I felt like we were all in time with that. Maybe Ben you're hearing us all later.
Maybe the first time.
No, I think it was okay.
I have an awful syncing method, but it works.
What's that?
Hey Ben, how you doing?
I'm cool.
Hey Gibb, how you doing?
I'm alright. No, wait, we're not going to do the whole thing of it.
Go, keep going, keep going.
Hey Oblivion, how you doing?
I'm doing, ah, oh my god, this month is a fucking clusterfuck. I don't know if I can, I don't want to take up the time to explain everything right now.
Just make a noise.
Hey Tick, how you doing?
I'm doing alright.
No, that's not what he said.
Tom, that was done right before.
Maybe there is a flaw in this method.
You have to be able to recognize your name.
Hey Tom, how you doing a second time?
I'm okay, I can't hear what's going on apparently.
Oh god, I just kind of, and then I just line it up because everyone will be in between.
Your mic sounds pretty rough Tom, are you on like your phone or something?
Does it really sound terrible?
Well I mean it doesn't sound great.
It sounds fine, it sounds okay on my end a little bit longer.
Your microphone's pretty rough Tom, are you recording through a dog or something?
Is that better?
Yes, that is better actually, much better.
You catch.
I knew it.
Alright, so are we ready to start?
I like changing my microphone and now everyone sounds like an alien, that's weird.
Oh really?
Do you have to fix something?
Tom, what?
No!
The microphone ate all of his bandwidth somehow.
Genuinely?
When he said we all sounded like aliens, he was ignoring the actual aliens that were right.
Is that any better now?
Yes.
You sounded okay before, but you also sound good now.
Okay, fine.
Do we sound okay?
You've found not terrifying anymore, so I'll take it.
Should we just use the whole thing and not even cut the pre-syncing part?
I like disasters.
Welcome to the Procrestinatus podcast.
Welcome to the PCP, again.
It's me, Ben St.
Gib is here, Gib and Take.
Hello everybody.
Tom Oliver's here, back in fighting shape.
I would go that far, but I am back.
Okay, we've got a lineup today.
Guesting for the first time is Tessnaker.
Hello.
And returning are our friends of the show, Oblivionfall.
And Tectonic Improv.
I think this is a record amount of guests for Oblivionfall, me, Tessnaker and Tom Oliver, all guesting on the PCP.
You're forgetting the infamous Oops, All Guests episode.
We had like 70 guests.
I wasn't there.
We could beat that every day.
We could beat that.
We could beat that if we try.
Do just invite them snakes on.
You'll have like 27,000 guests at that point.
Oh yeah, technically true.
On a technicality.
So we've returned to the olden days of two years ago.
And we've returned to the olden days of too many people on a podcast to understand what is happening.
So I guess, how's everyone doing?
How's life?
Playing bad video game all day.
Actually, it's not bad.
I don't know what it is yet.
I'm figuring that out.
My life is currently an absolute clusterfuck.
You don't want to know.
I know that feel.
Yeah.
I just moved into an apartment.
Congratulations.
I guess unless it sucks.
No, it's a pretty nice one.
Oh, it's considered.
You know, it's, I'm still moving everything in.
I got, I still, I have a fucking, I have a ridiculous record collection.
So it's been a pain in the ass bringing all those over.
I had like a bunch of milk crates, but the milk crates are too small for the records.
I want to fucking blow my brains out, but it'll all get done.
It's all right so far.
And think about it.
When you put that final record up, you'll be able to say to yourself, oh, finally.
Yeah, finally.
Exactly.
Amazing.
Good job.
I've still got.
Gamers Tavern is back on the show.
Is that Gamers Tavern?
I've still got a big stack of boxes in the corner of my room from when I moved in
because I'm not willing to get rid of them.
I know I'll need them soon.
For the winter.
Very soon.
For the yet.
When I'm evicted and I need to live inside something, though, that's what I'm going to use.
Yeah, probably.
Yeah.
When my fucking slumlord decides to evict me for, I don't know, nothing, whatever.
You can never be too careful.
Who's got a video playing in the background?
Do I?
Okay.
No.
I heard something.
I heard someone yelling.
I need to work.
That's another guest.
That's five guests.
I live next to a football stadium.
If it was on today, we could have had.
We could have had triple digits.
Oh my God.
We could have.
We could have live.
Sold the microphone up.
No, it is the Arsenal stadium.
So it would have been booing.
Oh, because, you know, Arsenal hates the PCP famously.
Yeah.
What is Arsenal?
Arsenal is a thing where you store ammunition or guns or weapons.
You know, that's what an Arsenal is.
Thing about Arsenal.
True.
That's kind of why the football team is so controversial, because they just get red-carded when they blow the other team away.
Yeah.
People give them a stern look.
They bring their rifles and muskets and stuff onto the pitch, but they can't really do anything until they start murdering.
Every time that happens here in America, just be like, hmm, thoughts and prayers, and that would just be it.
In America, the controversies are all over teams being named racist stuff.
But in the UK, it's like, ooh, that team's name has guns in it?
We don't like, we don't have guns over here.
Oh no, you do not know about English football fan racism.
They are some of the most inventive racists in the world.
I'm saying, yeah, they keep the racism.
Keep the racism, lose the guns.
That's the United Kingdom, I guess.
I just, okay, this is a weird story to bring up about one of my six, seven uncles.
I have too many of them.
I also have like tons and tons of extended family members, but so I understand.
All right, let's hear it.
When the cricket was on last year, I went downstairs, my uncle was visiting family and it was all just...
And I was just going to get a drink of whiskey.
And my uncle just casually just says, hey, Patrick.
And I was like, yeah, are you a racist?
And he asked it in the most casual tone.
I think I've ever been asked the question.
And what was your answer?
Um, no.
You just said no.
I just said no.
I just said no and bought my whiskey.
And I got upstairs and it wasn't always upstairs.
I realized how absurd that question was given the framing.
Did he ask it like he was hoping you were so he could...
Did your answer satisfy him?
He just went, huh, like it was just a very casually interested...
Weird.
Wow.
And kids these days.
I went back down in my house, how bizarre.
I went back down and I had to ask, I just asked, why'd you ask if I was a racist?
And he just said, he just kind of looked at the telly because we were playing.
It was either Pakistan or India.
And he said, well, you know, when the sport's on,
they're saying about us as well.
He was just checking to see if he could say something racist.
I was about to dunk on them, but I'm sure I have the all clear.
Is that what it was?
He wanted...
I don't think that's...
I don't know if that's what it was because he's not...
Of my uncles, he's one of the...
He's one of the less racist.
There's a scale, as they call him.
He's challenging you.
There's my uncle that's like the elder racist, even though he's not the oldest brother.
And then there's, you know, it goes downscale until one is maybe just a little bit of a little Englander.
And...
Well, that was nice of him to ask for consent to be racist before...
I suppose so.
I'm sure it's okay.
It's better than the conversation I had with another uncle where I've left a passport in a caravan,
which we used to go on holiday and he just said,
you'll want to get that back, you know, then foreigners.
And she's like, I'm just...
I literally just said, I'm walking away from the phone, mate.
I can't be bothered.
It really is.
Especially in sports in the UK, there's just sort of like a...
It's okay to call players of color a racial slur,
but that's just banter.
That's just, you know, lads having fun.
It's just lads having fun.
They just have no understanding.
If they didn't want that, they shouldn't have played for the other guy.
That's pretty much it.
The fun I had with my family...
My family are all big football fans, and it's not even...
It's not just exactly the racism, because my immediate family is just the extended family,
which I find very fucking lucky.
Everybody's got those racist uncles.
Yeah.
But it's funny that every time, you know, penalty on one side,
and my family's just blowing their lids,
and then penalty on the other side, and it's like, no, that was...
That come on with it.
And it's like...
I don't know.
The legitimacy of a penalty is decided on which team it is.
Not by how broken the man's leg is.
That sounds about right.
Yeah.
I watched some good old fashioned American gridiron football
over Thanksgiving the other week.
Go Pats.
Nothing...
It was...
Who was it?
It was the Raiders versus...
The Bills.
The Pats were not playing that day.
Yeah, there might have been the Bills.
Yeah, I think so.
Oh, that was a good game.
That one was like...
That one like went into like overtime.
It was like...
That was actually a great game.
It was really tense, and then the Raiders like barely eked it out,
and we were rooting for them.
So...
Yeah, fuck the Bills.
They're not a sports guy or anything, but I've said before,
I will partake if it's on, and if the season is right,
and the season was right, and a good time was had by all.
Good, good...
Really, really neck and neck.
Real nail biter.
It doesn't get much better than that.
I haven't actually...
It's funny because when I go to America, I do really want to catch
like a baseball game.
If I ever visit America, I'm more like a...
I don't know.
The Simpsons has taught me that it is mostly an excuse to drink,
and it actually is really boring.
I mean, the excuse to drink is fine by me.
I just want to feel like an American for an afternoon or an evening.
I'd go with someone who was excited to go to a game.
Oh yeah, I wouldn't go by myself.
I'd need the company.
That's not me.
I went to a baseball game or two when I was a kid,
and then I've never been to a football game,
but I did work as a beer hawker at a stadium very briefly.
I was really bad at it.
So I've seen a football game or two that way,
but I wasn't paying attention.
I don't know.
Getting a ticket and going and spending the whole day
and getting in the seats and waiting in lines and driving,
it's like too much effort for my blood.
Yeah.
I think it's like I just kind of want to get in on that experience at least once.
I think of that one out for myself.
Great Iron Football is a better sport.
Great Iron Football is a better sport than baseball, though.
I like the experience merely of being in a gigantic crowd of people yelling,
which I can get by going to like a music concert,
so I usually prefer those.
But now, COVID, you could never ever do that ever again.
I don't like concerts either.
I was packing in my bag.
No, concerts aren't for me.
I've got shitty whacked hearing,
so I don't want to risk that any further than I already pushed it.
I hurt my hearing really bad once at a concert.
Thankfully, the ringing went away,
but I never go to a concert without...
Your plugs?
Your plugs.
Yeah, smart boy.
I usually just stick my fingers in my ears if it gets too loud,
but it really doesn't most of the time.
I think I like...
Well, when I get like tickets, I try to get cheap ones,
and they're usually near the back, but of course it's loud,
so it doesn't really matter too much.
If you want to get close,
you're just going to be able to see the people's faces a bit better.
I don't know.
I saw Snacky Puppy once. That was fucking cool.
Oh, I did see...
I did see Zen Huxtable play in a band in a show one time.
This was like a few months ago.
I saw his band, and they were actually really good.
That was a concert that I actually did enjoy quite a bit.
They were playing at some kind of weekly festival
or a little tent set up with a beer stand.
It was like every week this tent place would set up.
They would sell beer.
You could hang out during the day for a block party,
and then they would have a lineup of local bands at night.
And they were the headliner.
Wow.
Apparently he had been conscripted
as a temporary assistant to...
Because they needed more people to perform more tracks on stage with them.
He wasn't an official member of the band,
but I think he got promoted to an official member later,
because he was really good on the keyboard.
That's the plot of that thing you do that Tom Hanks made.
Is it?
The drummer breaks his arm or something,
and the main character fills in form and pretty much takes his spot.
Sorry, movie.
They were...
I don't know.
Anyway, it was a great show.
A lot of fun.
Small crowd.
I think that was better.
And it outdoors probably makes it easier on the ears too.
It's the indoor venues you gotta really be careful about.
True.
It was at... Have you ever been to the Paradise Rock Club, Ben?
That's where I hurt my ears.
I don't think...
It's somewhere in Boston.
It's near the Raising Canes.
No, I've never been.
Damn, man.
I feel like a small cramped room would be...
Not a small, tiny, but a reasonably sized,
but still very much enclosed space would be much worse than stadiums concerts,
which are much louder, but they're usually open on the top.
Those are nice.
Music.
What was that band you saw again?
What a concept.
Where are we going with it?
What's the apex?
That band that you were talking about, Gib.
What's the point?
Snarky Puppy.
They're like a jazz fusion band.
They've got some really popular songs on YouTube.
Lingus is one where it's got this...
Oh, you linked Cory Henry.
Maybe his guy is once before.
Yeah, they're really proficient jazz,
like a super big group of bunch of people who go to jazz music,
and no singing, it's just music.
It's just real music.
No singing.
Singing's not real music.
It's painted by the human voice, which I agree with.
When I hear...
I got my headphones in and I'm jamming and I'm hearing the beep, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop.
And then I hear a little...
And then someone goes...
And I go, no.
No, and I throw my headphones on the ground and I'm like, they ruined it.
It was pure.
It was pure, and now it's tainted.
It's not like singing. It's just that like when music can fill a stadium
With no like big-name artist singer, you know, it's it's because the music is incredible and it was
Sure, sure. It's an hour eight fair. That's how you know. It's serious real music
Real music not a track under five minutes two drummers. They had like three fucking
brass section
If the lyrics and everyone had a song, then it's real music. That's true. Yeah, lyrics
That's when you uh, that's the only time they're valid, right?
Yes, during the final boss during the final boss when the when like the the opening theme song of the game
Plays, but they add a vocal track
Operatic music. This is the one time humans are allowed to sing
Feel the sunshine
Yeah, I think that's the first song ever sung by a caveman as they like beat something to death with a stick
Caveman was mass destruction from persona free. Yeah, we haven't stopped since
Did you say lotus juice? Oh god, he doesn't know
Is that not the name lotus is is the name of the of the artist who wraps the the songs in persona three
That's his like a stage name. Oh
Yeah, no, I did not know that I thought it was I thought it was like a colloquial British expression or something
Like man, that was so that we needed we needed some lotus juice to get that done like that took some real elbow grease
That took some serious birds milk. That took some real lotus juice
Yeah, we came up with a term lotus juice when we were just absolutely
Defiling China with opium. I don't know if I I mean, you know lotus eaters right from the Odyssey
I don't know it could mean something it could go a bunch of different ways. I'm just do it
I'm just doing free association here. I'm like, you know, it's like John Cleese said you guys are all in the active mode
You guys have all you have your creativity switched off. I am in the playful mode
I'm in the creative mode. I'm I'm just there are no bad ideas, right?
I just I just tied lotus juice
So the opium was you saying I'm not on that's the worst joke
I'm gonna make on this podcast unless I really dive deep never say never alright. We still have three more hours
Joy join me snake in the creative in the creative clouds
No, I'm already paying for adobe. Oh
What if
Lotus juice seems like a weird like like a vape flavor
Oh, it will be one day. It sounds good. If lotus juice isn't selling lotus juice. He is not one brand
No idea what it would taste you have a hole in the market. It's time to capitalize on it
You got to start making I context of that changes then if a guy called lotus juice is selling juice with his name
I have to wonder where the juice comes from and then well, you know
You know, he could do like the Lil Nas X thing and he could sell shoes with his blood in them
And he could say like this shoe contains the lotus juice
It's already got blood so we're just gonna have to like he's gonna have to have his glands squeezed and
We can go lower we can we can yet do worse
We can drill I
Think I think they did fill the niche in the vape market that I was waiting for I think someone finally did make caffeinated vape juice
Which is a godsend does that work? I don't know I wish I said I wish I still vape
I wish I still vape so I could try it
I hear I hear from my friend that they don't know they don't make vape juice without like nicotine in it anymore
Is that true? You've got to be able to find some without nicotine
I mean, I haven't really looked
You used to be able to find it. It would be it would be really fucked up
It would be really fucked up if they did like a crackdown on it and the result was not that like you can't buy the flavored
Kind anymore because it appeals to kids
It's that you can't buy the non nicotine that you can still buy the flavors the kids like but you have to get it with nicotine
They cracked down on the nicotine free because the kids were getting into it. That would be fucked the most
That's exactly what they would do. I've got the dumbest feeling on vapes and cigarettes
I don't smoke. I've never smoked. I'm
Thankfully way too cheap to ever take up smoking if I want yeah, but that's a that's a big
When I'm walking behind someone and they blow a big plume or something and it smells like vanilla instead of cigarette smoke
I'm like that's wrong
Fill my own fill my lungs with cigarette smoke, please
I'm gonna kill you stop wait wait wait you're saying that you would prefer it to be cigarette smoke
Yes, I asked smoke is fucking granted die. No, I love that smell
I know
The smell I also like the smell when I was is nostalgic
But I definitely don't like reading it in because I was scared to death by like videos of like
Here's what a fucking lung looks like if you smoke and it's like like a like a creepypasta scary monster
And I'm like, oh, no, I don't want that to happen
And then when I every time I see a person smoking I hold my breath
I don't I was a little kid when I was a little kid
The only person who I ever spent much time around who smoked was my grandpa
And when I went to his house his house smelled like cigarettes and I liked my grandpa and I liked that smell and I thought it smelled nice
There are times when I think
Like when I when I used to smoke I would catch myself smelling like cigarettes and I'd be like this is disgusting
This is horrible. This is a nightmare. My breath is gross. Why am I why live, right?
But but occasionally I will catch someone else smoking and I will get a whiff and be like
Kind of nice though. I kind of like that though kind of want that. I should ignore that feeling
I should point out just for clarity's sake. I'm not saying that I've taken the smart opinion on this
Just that that's the way my brain has been foiled. I disagree. I
Don't I don't understand I don't understand I like the smell of cigarettes
But I like the smell of vapes better like I like a good a good smell of smell of like like menthol watermelon
It's like delightful
men fall water to me. It's just it's me. It's like
Some weird Senate. It's not even synesthesia. What am I talking about this feels like reality isn't quite adding up
They're cheating snake. They're they're gonna smoke. Oh, yeah smoke the good shit. They got a guy
Commitment to the bit when I when I light it when I light a scented candle like I just it's such an uncanny
It's like why does it smell like like bananas and walnuts like my reality is fizz collapsing
Mankind was not meant to live like this
You're taking me on one here. You're moving me a step beyond what I mean
I'm talking about when I'm walking down the high street and it's grotty and horrible and I'm in London
So it's just human misery all around me if someone isn't smoking to die
I want it to smell miserable. Yeah, I want I want the app most to be perfect. I want to breathe in and go
Yeah, this is my town
All right, okay, that's not quiet. I take it back. You can live that's funny
If if they can live as long as I'm allowed to with this air quality
It needs to be in like a hipster trendy part of London if it's like a sweet weird smelling vape
Oh, yeah, yeah, I feel you on that is this closer to the set
There's like a bubble tea shop and like stuff like that then the vapes can the vapes can be like different colors
They can be coming out as pink and green. Yeah, someone is you know, just blowing out a plume of that or someone else is choking on a tapioca
They should have like themed vapes for different parts of cities like in Italian districts
You could have like olive oil a pizza a pizza flavor. Yeah
Oh my god, I'm just thinking of London tourist vapes and I'm getting disgusted
You have you have corned beef
Like a baby like the tower London
Well, it's like jelly. Do you remember a like Willy Wonka Willy Wonka had those like pills that were like an entire
Three-course meal. Why not vape? Oh first? I vape my mashed potatoes
Then I vape my my turkey and and and cranberry sauce then finally I vape my pumpkin pie. Ah, it's a whole Thanksgiving meal
The dystopic food pill into the dystopic vape wait, what if we could vape on the blockchain
No
So like so like you get you mine coins by I don't know
I don't know what I mean by that
What you do is you suck in from an e-pen or an e-sig or whatever is then you put your mouth to a hard drive and you just blow it in
That creates
You just have the pen the vape pens wirelessly connected to your phone or your computer and like every time you inhale
It can calculate how much you're inhaling and the more you inhale you get rewarded with vape coin
So like if you just like keep vape the more you vape the more vape coin you mine
And then you can trade it for a theory or something and buy your your vape NFTs
You know and then they'd they'd have like like like mass-produce vape mining operations where people sitting in a room
Like 16 vape pens in their mouth sort of time like an opioid den
But just a bunch of people vape a bunch of crypto bros just vaping for the dear life
I've got all the crypto bros that have popcorn lung and Bitcoin just like disappears
There's a supervisor walking around saying if you're good today, you get the vanilla flavor
I'm so sick of the olive oil flavor man, please
We can convert we can convert like our smoggy our smoggy like industrial cities billowing out plumes of smoke
No from now on it's gonna be big clouds of like yeah of like a blueberry muffin
scented
Diacetyl of vapor just into the clouds surrounding the atmosphere
Filling filling up filling up the ozone layer
But it'll smell nicer the plumes coming off of like a nuclear power plant would be
Centered and it would make the whole area around taste great when it rains all the time cup out and you can catch the juice
And it will be great
She's like mommy mommy the rain tastes like a taste like menthol the rain tastes like
Grapes grape menthol. That's my favorite by the way. My favorite flavor was always the fruit menthol combos. That was
I love it. That's so that's what I keep going back to
What what is the taste of menthol? I can only think of methamphetamine. I know that's not what it is, right?
Well, have you ever yeah, it's like mint. Have you ever had like a menthol cough drop?
Yeah, it's like a like a mint. Okay. I know what really weird because I
When I'm recording, I'll get like Fisherman's friends, which are menthol flavored and it just tastes
Cold wait you the Fisherman's. Yeah
What's that? Does that help with recording using like cough drops or something?
It helps with sore throat and it
It basically if you're talking too much and you're not talking properly, which I'm very very bad at narration
After 10 years, I was hoping I'd get better, but I just I don't know
I guess if you think it's as long as you so
I
Just I use those which they're like a menthol sweet which soothes the throat and just kind of helps
Yeah, if you've ever had like if you've ever had like a menthol cough drop like a cherry menthol
Like it tastes like cherry, but it's just kind of got like a little like a sort of like cool minty icy
Mentholiness to it
Like like like icicles are growing on the back of you the throat sort of
Pretty much like a very extreme delightful
delightful
Man, well, I don't even know what we're talking about anymore. How did how did this happen?
Where I was very weird chain from racist uncles in sport to the blockchain, which by the way
Crypto just crashed the other day
Oh
That's one of the items on my list. That's one of the items on my topic list was the crypto crash
I'm so sorry. I just had some I'm sorry. I had to mention no
I mean, I'm excited. It was a pretty big one. It dropped like 20% in like one day. Yeah, it was pretty brutal
Did something like a bit what caused it? I bought the dip. Did you buy the dip then?
Did you actually buy the dip? I did I bought two hundred dollars with Ethereum on the dip
Uh, no, I did not no, I did not buy the dip
I'm not convinced that it will not continue to crash
It probably will go through like I someone would mentioned because I've been knee-deep in those research for this fucking video
That like it's gonna crash during the holidays as people cash out to like buy holiday gifts and stuff
Are you making a crypto video for like?
I have like a 12-page video right now on NFTs and why they're bad and it's a deep
It's a deep dive. My brain is permanently infected with garbage the common section for that video is gonna be great. Oh, okay
But I mean the the avatars of that comment section
Clicks ready boys, we're gonna have to take them all is
Do we know what caused the the big crash the other day because I have no idea
It was because of all those fainting beat. They stopped being able to vape. They yeah
Yeah
I actually want to know okay, but does anybody know why these things happen? Like I said like like I
Sometimes there are like sometimes some country who passes some legislation and there's like oh as a market response
Well, like I said, I'd heard I'd heard that like it tends to crash a little bit
Around the holidays as people like cash out to like use them their gains to like buy stuff for Christmas and shit
I don't know if that was the entirety of it
But I expect it probably to kind of be rather low for the rest of the year as people continue to do that. I
Didn't buy any dip
But what I did do was I complained before about how a bunch of I had a bunch of stable coins that I got from some app
That like some tax youtuber may it recommended me to try and I tried it and now I have a bunch of like
USDT and USDC
So and then I I said this before
STD
We call them STIs now actually
The the anyway, yeah, I had them in this app and I tried to transfer them out and they ended up in
Not my not my coinbase wallet, but my wallet in my coinbase wallet app
So my coinbase wallet wallet so they're in my coinbase wallet wallet
But I can't transfer them to my coinbase wallet without paying gas and the gas was outrageous
They wanted me to pay more in gas than I even have in the account
That's cuz coinbase coinbase the app and coinbase wallet are two different things. I
Know that now
Guess so I guess so I've been so I've been waiting for so I had a little bit of Bitcoin
I had like $80 worth of Bitcoin. I had a little bit of USDT USDC
So I sent my I converted my Bitcoin to
Ethereum and I'm gonna send the Ethereum I sent the Ethereum to the Bitcoin wallet wallet
And now I'm waiting for gas fees to go down low enough that I can use that Ethereum that was Bitcoin to pay
The gas the ether gas fee to transfer my USDT and USDC for my coinbase wallet wallet to my coinbase wallet
And then cash them out and that's the plan and this is all to get like a hundred and fifty dollars
This has been like a month's long process
Arturning is much better. Carturning is awesome. I got a new one the other day
The American Express blue business card doesn't count towards my 520 limit 524 limit
Fuck yeah, I'm excited. I'm back on the churn, baby
Back in the chain. Yeah, I'm gonna make a hundred dollars during this podcast by finishing a commission. That's what I do
What are you well? Oh, that's multi-tasking. I
Think I've mentioned this before but I used to be in the my little pony community shocking
Terrible, are you making more are you making more vectors? Yeah, I am
I did a lot of animation and I made rigs
Very similar to the ones for used on the show. In fact, I have the rigs from the show
There are like animation files that were leaked from the show years ago, but I had access to before anyone else
So I've like studied how I do things. I built these animation rigs and
You know, you know how you know your youtubers who have their little like character in the corner
It's just a bunch of PNGs that they swap out similar
Who would do such a thing the arm crosses who would do such a thing or pony analysis channels
I mean my god, who are they we've moved into the third dimension now
We use fully fully modeled 3d rigs to do our to emote for our youtubers. It's true
I am being outclassed slowly, but I basically used my animation rig to make a hundred and fifty poses in
flash and each pose is just a keyframe in the program and
So son will commission me a hundred bucks for a hundred images or a hundred and fifty images for, you know
120 bucks of their character and all I have to do is just draw the hair once slap it in and it's done
Hmm, and I go I was gonna have to vector hair and recolor and that's it. That sounds kind of smart not hard
I guess yeah, definitely up your rates
I
Everyone I think my rates are good because something a lot of especially when they accept easy designs
I can do it in like an hour. Yeah, ours
No reason not
Yeah, I've hit the sweet spot for what people are willing to pay people don't want to pay more than that
So okay, okay, I think I'm the market started to start accepting a theorem then that's when you'll really fucking. Oh
No
Tom stop
You know I should
At some point I really do think at some point the the crypto bubble is gonna pop and I just it is
And I just don't want and I just don't want to be holding the bag
I just don't want to be holding the bag when that happens. We don't have you want to get in and get out
The easiest thing to do is to not grab the bag at all. I
Try to get in and get out
I tried to get in and get out during the last big rally and I ended up I waited too long and I cashed out and I lost like a
Little bit. I've mostly broke even and so I'm like, what's the point? I can't time the market. I don't know what shit's gonna
Do, what's the fucking man exactly?
It's genuinely all just gambling by another name
They're totally gonna we totally have the resources and energy to do that
Totally, I'm sure NFTs are gonna replace emojis. Just you wait. I want to hear what they're gonna do
I I just wanted to like point out my own stupidity and why I will not I ever expect anyone to but just never take
Financial advice from me because I own thirty nine thousand shares in Napster
No, that's funny
Wait, whoa, when did you buy them for thirty nine cents? They are thirty nine cents now
So I've lost
But so here's the thing about so I I got into stocks trading the whole GME thing happened
I thought I'm too late to get onto GME, but I've been
I lost I lost a couple hundred dollars on me. I didn't go on GME. It just kind of reminded me
Hey, I've been being start doing stocks for a while. Let's let's take a punt on it
I've got a bit of money spare and this does go against what I said earlier about me being too cheap to smoke
But I am perfectly willing I set aside a hundred
But not too cheap to buy Napster shares. It's never too late
But here's okay
Not that this excuses my later decision-making, but
What I started as was when I was just looking around for companies to invest and I saw on as alone
It was a company called Melody VR and its whole its whole modus operandi. Whatever fuck was
That we do 360 degree
Videos of concerts and my brain just I'm very simplistic on it
I was just like hey, maybe when covid's over and there are concerts again
That sounds like a cool venture and like headsets are becoming more common
That sounds like something people might like and I threw in a few quid
Turns out Melody VR is the company that acquired and bought Napster
Um years ago and then at some point just decided hey, we're gonna start trading under the name Napster again
So it was like they just pulled the cloak off and like we're Napster actually
We
And then it just kept going lower and lower and at this point. I don't expect to make money on it
I just kind of want to know how many fucking Napster stocks can I have
Can I eventually trip Elon Musk into boosting it?
Can I make it a revenge thing against Grimes? I don't actually believe those last two steps, but you know
Can you why would they change their name to a thing that is associated with like an old
outdated here's the messed up thing I since learned which is Napster is still functional and has a music storefront
Just no one cares or knows not even I own stock in it and I don't care or no. I just have spot of
I think I think I remember hearing that they um
They tried bringing back Napster like a few years ago
Oh, like there's report. There's multiple reports. They say we're bringing it back in 2023. I'm sure sure you're fucking up
It's it's the equivalent of like owning the name myspace and trying to make a comeback when everybody is associated
Myspace with like oh that one that failed and facebook won
Like nobody would get interested in a new myspace. I mean, I guess I mean a lot of these old companies
They still keep puttering around doing
God knows what um, but like they continue to exist and have some sort of
Presence like I don't know who uses them, but like maybe somebody does and that's we're still pulling in
uh
about like
Several million a year enough to remain technically functional
But you know, they're never really good. They're never going to be in the public zeitgeist again
Yeah, like like they've had their fame and they've scuppered it. They need a new name because otherwise
Nobody will yeah exactly
Like I I wasn't even on the internet when Napster was
Influential I didn't get internet
till 2003 when and I only heard about Napster in retrospect
My generation was using limewire to nice to steal everything. Yeah
I was limewire and memories of limewire. Yeah
My knowledge never saw limewire
My Napster knowledge pretty much begins and ends the episode of Futurama
Where they oh, yeah, where they make like robots of celebrities or something
Oh, was it kidnapped? Yeah, they're kidnapped. Yes. Oh, yeah
I feel really bad with Futurama because I think when I was a teenager
I knew near enough every episode word for word and it's all gone now
I want to get back into it. I haven't watched it. I never I never watched the uh, the re the reboot
I
I I watched a couple episodes and yeah, it's not on it
The average quality is not as good as the original fox run, but there are still some gems in there
The original
Futurama writing team seasons one to five were it was a room full of phd's
Yeah, we're just making whatever joke entertain them
Well, it was that wasn't a family guy writers and it's it loses some some of that
Wasn't the team originally like a bunch of like the best talent from the simpsons team got like put like sort of
Yeah, it was it was led by it was led by david x cohen formally david s cohen
Yeah, and he just grabbed some of the smartest people he knew and just let them loose on making the most obscure gags
They could while just being funny along the way
Yeah, and that's kind of how you get futurama. It's this weird flash in a pan
Honestly, I believe something that shouldn't have happened, but
It did
Yeah, glad it did
It's it's funny how like 50%
Like 50% of number file videos I watch there'll be like a segment where they're like, yeah, futurama reference fist
Like it always happens
lol
I thought I thought you were making a joke like like 50% of number
File and then you were gonna make up some like
Weird statistic like you're gonna like be like, oh, yeah
Actually, according to number like the number file numbers followed like the fibonacci sequence
If you spiral it out or something if you take the square root, I don't know it didn't happen
I don't know never mind. Well the reason all I don't know mathematics jokes is impossible
It is impossible. You need to know numbers. I and that just doesn't add up
I make jokes
Fucking numbers
We already talked about this words are bad. You has to be instrumentals only if you can you have to make me laugh at your instruments
I've been getting yes. I love the sound of a trumpet
It really makes it really gets me going
I've been getting the most I've ever gotten out of my physics degree
As I mentioned during the pre show I have been
Uh, I've been making I've been doing my programming shit
I've been making making codes and shit and I use numbers
All the time they said they said they I said I'd never learn I'd never need to know about how
Oh, what is the the acceleration is equal to the square root of the the mass of the times of gravity?
Well, guess what I'm doing it. I'm I'm I'm making animations and stuff. It's gonna be it's gonna be
I am a dang I'm I think I gotta be a nerd I'm I'm getting like
I don't think I could have kept at the greek the game grind this long if I wasn't a dang nerd
And I get
I'm a jock game reviewer
Chad chad virgin game developer the chad game reviewer
Yeah, that's that's telling me about mario jumping in a parabola
I have I could not have stuck with it if I did not get a perverse
Uh, a nerd pleasure out of when I when I type in yeah when I when I make a little formula and then like
Oh, here's he's gonna move according to this formula and then I boot up the game
And I see him and he moves in the in the correct arc and I go
Aha, like oh, I'll I'll define I'll define such and such to go according to this formula and then I see it and I'm like
Yep, that's that's the waveform. It tickles that like residual gone god complex
All of us nerds have for being fucking bullied and having no control growing up. It's like now they all listen
Absolutely
Absolutely, that's why I named all of the characters in my game off my childhood bullies. So I could
Yeah, exactly. No. No. No. No. Hey. Hey. Hey, this is my
I made I made a little game called hatred and have you ever heard of it? But yeah, that was that was how I work
Oh, that was you the trauma. Yeah. Mm-hmm. And yeah, this
This brings me to okay. This brings me to another topic one of the topics on my list that I wanted to bring up
I have I have a conundrum
Where I'm getting close to be able to release this I already talked told
I think give and tom and probably tech also. I mentioned this too
Uh, I I'm getting closer to be able to release it
And I want to put it on steam. Oh, yes
and I am
Cons and I am and I'm wondering
Are they gonna be mad if it has like music from an old SNES game in it? Yes. Yes, they will. Yes, really
Is something is something actually gonna happen because I yeah, I find I find it
I find it kind of hard to believe that anyone would even notice
I
I think
Them not noticing is likely, but like there will be consequences for you and your game if it gets caught
You are absolutely playing with fire. Just the context of one the one bit of history
I have with this and it's not quite SNES music
Okay
Um, you know the yeek devs
Their previous games and brothers that had bitcrushed shadow of the colossus music in it and you can't you can't buy that game anymore
And that is one bit of flak that's going to follow them around forever
So I'd say I mean and this is just my perspective on it
Here's even if you think you can get away with it
You probably can't and you would be taking the reputation hit
Just what I'm saying. Hold on. Hold on. I hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. This is okay
I'm not saying I'm not intending to pass off it as my own work
Like I was intending to be like credit in the credits like this music is I took this music from this game, right?
Like that's what I wasn't I wasn't gonna plagiarize. I was gonna be like, yeah, it's credited. This is not my music
I don't think that matters
Because you need the licensing rights or that just lets everybody know that you knew exactly what you did and did it anyway
I don't yeah, because you're gonna sound like stealing something from someone admitting you did it but like
But it's okay. Hold on. It's not plagiarism. Okay. It might be no. We're not saying it's plagiarism anymore
We're saying it's yeah, it's intellectual. It's violating copyright
Stealing from who though from square square doesn't even exist anymore. There's square enix now the game was never even localized
You're trying to they still own the fucking trademark. Just convince yourself. This is okay. Yes. Tell me what I want to hear
Right now
There's so many people. This one we're involved. You gotta you gotta go back to doing musicians. You have access to musicians find someone from the piece
I don't want to. You could release it on itch. I feel like you could release it on itch and be fine
I'll say all right. It could still be a bad look but you could do it
But I wouldn't put it on steam. I'll fucking kill you. I'll fucking end you. It will not be a bad look
It's not a fucking bad look. What's wrong with you? What's wrong with everyone to be like? Then why are you asking the question?
Why are you asking the question? Let me say this in a way that
You're admitted to violating copyright law. It'll get I don't think it's a bad look
I don't think it unless I charge for it. If I charged for it. Maybe it would be a bad look if I wasn't
I still think you then just distribute the game via napster, then you'll be on brand
Just put it on just put it on napster and have everyone to be able to download it from there and then you'll be on
39 shares will finally go up in value. You know everybody everybody wins
Yeah, when I'm a millionaire, I'll be able to say the pcp got me here
I'm going to put it on itch no matter I was gonna put it on itch for free
But then I was like hey, I could technically put it on steam if I wanted to I did not know that you were gonna just make it free
Yeah, I still think it's a problem. I guess I guess it makes sense because it follows on from a comic
But I assume since it's on steam you you'd probably want it to to get paid for
The game is already a nightmare of like stolen intellectual property. It's already that then I wouldn't put it on steam
That's the point god. Okay. I feel like it's it's funnier that way. Well, I mean if you like you just pull one out
Hey, I got this legal action. That's funny. Then go for it
What's that what you're saying snake? I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I was talking over you
It's just I feel like you just pulled the hell of a fucking joke on us with
Oh, yeah, it's got this one SNES track in it and then we zoom out and then there's all these intellectual characters
No, no, no, what I mean what I mean is that like in terms of inter I'll tell you the exact specs in terms of like assets
There is music from uh front mission gun hazard
There are a few sprites and sound effects from secretive mana
and uh mario rpg
I'm pretty sure those release the us
Those released in the us, but okay, but the music but the music did not release in the us
All right, but I mean the the game is the game is based on a comic, which is I mean it's
It's it's it the main character is a my little pony fan character and it's about his uh, it's it's it's it's also involves a
sonichu, which is also, you know, uh
Has its own intellectual property that definitely falls under parody. That's definitely fine
Well, maybe my use of uh the front mission gun hazard song is also
I was making a comment. It's a commentary on the original and how good of music it is
It's very much. I like it and want to put it in a video game
I thought we threw the gameplay just have a character say damn this tune is rocking and it's like we did it boys
We defeated
I got so excited my headphones fell out for a second
I might might be right but now it's for now. It's for the purposes of review and critique
That's how I get exactly
Actually, that's how
Get away with everything
You should have a character say wow this this you should have phantom horn do a a t-bap on that song
And then it would be fine
It would be a review
Okay, well, fuck you guys. You didn't tell me you didn't give me the answer. I wanted so how is that not the answer?
You wanted that's a great idea. It's funny. You do it
Oh, okay. Thank you. It's the one my my guy my guy livid now you can make the final boss of your game us
Shutting down your Ben. Here's what you could do. Here's what you could do
Yeah, I
You could probably do something
I know like a lot of like porn games on steam do something similar to this where they release like a
censored version of the game on steam and then they point to a like a
A way to patch the game with like the the porn scenes in it
What you could do is you could release the game on steam without the music and then like
Like subtly nudge to to a patch that patches in the the front mission gun hazard music. There you go
That might work with the porn game example rather than all the yakuza mods that
patch back in
No, I of course I think of the porn games before yakuza. No, I mean that's my my game has more has a more direct lineage to
To porn to porn visual novels those mass three games. Yeah
Yeah
Okay, that's an idea that's uh
I will continue to uh, I will continue to mull this this conundrum over
Uh in my spare time
You should put it on the epic game store instead
That'll be
Supposed to exclusively we love phantom horn ben we want your game
Fans of big big t-bap fans speak speaking of big t-bap fans. This is crazy. My sister called me the other day
My sister is a tattoo is a tattoo artist. She was famously on the podcast one time when she said you're a dog
You're you're a dog and i'm sick of it
um
And and she called me the other day to tell me that one of her customers like a guy who had come to get a tattoo from her
they were chatting and she brought up her brothers who had a
A my little pony youtube channel and the guy was like what's their channel called and she told him and he knew
He he okay. She's she specifically asked wait is ben saint your brother. He didn't ask about keg standard
He asked is ben saint your brother
Uh, he knew t-bap. This was I know
Crazy shit. So so my sister just got a lifelong customer out of that
Uh
Some guy walked in was like, yeah, I want a tattoo a tattoo every week comes in just like what's ben saint up to
What kind of debauchery is he getting into this week? I I want a I would like a tramp stamp
Please on the back so that it looks like when I'm wearing pants so that it looks like uh phantom horn
Is coming out of of the right side of my pants and and keg standard is sticking out of the left side
Shouldn't be the other way around
No phantom horn was on the right. Oh, okay
He's right like separated by the arse. He moves slowly left over time
Anyway, I thought that was very funny that that is very small world
Small world small world
Uh, all right. So that's that's two
That's two of my items. That was both of my two items off my topics list. I'm done
I've said all I have to say about this week
I
I've got a thing to say
It's pikmin bloom. Oh god. I love pikmin bloom and I'm gonna say it again
I want to ask people in in in the call
Have you played pikmin bloom and do you know how cool it is? I have not I've seen it. I'm sorry
I thought it was like pokemon go thing, but different probably. Yes. It's it's different from pokemon go. It's just it's just good
I've just never I've never played pokemon go ever in my life
Pikmin is about tiny little people who come out of the ground and then they help you do things
Yeah, um
And that's that's that's what they do sick. So you it's a you grow slaves. What?
You you grow a little? No, they like slaves
Yeah, just like just like pokemon
It sounds like just like pokemon. They like it. It sounds like justification to me. It's different. I swear
But I mean we got we got nintendo's classic franchises, you know
Like cock fighting with pokemon and slavery with pikmin. It's just like fun for all ages
No, he's like, you know, Miyamoto said that, you know zelda was like the forest he explored and pokemon was the bug catching
Now it's just taking it back to when his family had the plantation
Miyamoto Miyamoto made he made pikmin to remind him of all the good times he had as a child uh helming the slave ships from africa
and
That's why that's why the ships legs sprout in a triangle. It's to represent the transit
Yeah, captain olamar. I cut myself off. I cut myself captain olamar is actually based off of uh, uncle remiss
his uh, his old friend from
I want to cut through the irony for a split moment just say pikmin one and two are very good
I never played three. Yes. I never played them because I was not a game cube guy
They're cool
I'm really
They make me really anxious because I always feel terrible when like any pikmin dies and like you're not going to make it
Do that game without losing a couple of them. Oh, no, I
Have tried for a zero death
I've I've very gotten I've gotten very close as like the second boss was the first time one of them died
I was very angry reset the game like it's fire and bloom
Yeah, anyway, anyway pikmin bloom
um, you have your little pikmin
And you pick them up out of the ground you you grow them by walking with steps
So it counts your steps and the thing that I've learned
Aside from the fact that it's like it's not as stressful as pokemon go is with like
There's billions of pokemon and you just have to once you've found all of the common ones
You're just sort of waiting and there's nothing to do until you see. Oh, there's a cool one nearby and then you go
um, it counts your steps and it records um
You can plant flowers as you walk to increase
The chance of you finding an expedition which is sort of like a little mission
You can send your pikmin on together like a grape or something
Um, and then you can bring it back and make nectar which you can use to make more flower petals
But the flower petals are server side
Um, and everybody can see them so you can see like frequently warped paths
And that's cool. Yeah, but the thing I like about it
Is that in pokemon go
the high
Like amount of pokemon like a lot of pokemon spawn in like densely populated areas
So you always have to go to the major cities in order to get loads of pokemon and loads of poker stops
Which kind of defeats the purpose of exploring
You just sort of go to a place where there's like 10 poker stops in walking distance
You walk around the block and then you go home to your probably less in the middle of the city
You know place and it's like there's nothing to do especially out in the country. There's nothing to do
But with pikmin it counts your steps and everything is about just how far you can walk
So it's completely the opposite you are it encouraged to go on long walks
To rack up the steps so that you can grow more pikmin more quickly
Plant flowers everywhere and then go and find
You know expeditions for your pikmin to go on
And I really like that because going on walks was the whole reason I sort of
Got into not the whole reason but part of the reason I liked pokemon go as a game
And then once I realized that I would never go for a walk unless there was a rare pokemon that I needed
Um, I realized it was terrible for walks
And but pikmin is pikmin bloom is great. Do you want to get some exercise?
I do need to get more cardio
But it's fucking cold now
Why couldn't they release in the spring?
I can actually I just got a new phone my phone has been has been unusably bad for like a year now
And I finally just got another one in the mail. I got to activate it. Dude download pikmin bloom right now
Maybe I fucking will maybe I don't know
It's funny because you had the countryside
And where you didn't have much to do and I have london
And I had a somewhat different experience with it, which is just walking around london
Can kind of be shit
Especially when it's like a pokemon will be somewhere. It's like that's kind of a dodgy neighborhood. I don't yeah
Yeah, I don't want to do that. Do I want to stick my neck out of that?
And it's like it's never it's not that bad, but there are moments where it's like
Mmm, don't don't like that area. Do I want to go there for that?
Do I want to have a walk in sheffield for a snorlax? Not quite not today, I would say
You know I grab I grab my handgun and I'm like right we're going to we're going to peck them
Let's uh
Take a chance is yeah, and the chancey folks whether
Dead or alive pickpocket alleyway. I had to break out the squad and we had to infiltrate to
Liberate a pokemon
That's what that's a new to in buckingham palace. You just have to storm it
I mean, I'd say hello to the queen on the way out challenger to a duel
I'll think of all the cool pokemon get blown away by the palace guard
I don't know if the queen has a smartphone. I've always wondered that and I've never seen her with one anymore. She's dead, dude
Oh, yeah, she's done. I know she's in the hospital. She's got to have like some some like like a nintendo switch
She's gonna be reborn the only nintendo switch she has she's like hooked up to and it's somehow her consciousness is being uploaded to it
It's keeping her alive
She's in a cocoon. She's gonna turn into a bead drill or a butterfly. We don't know which one
Please don't switch off her life support
You know what they're doing they're they're minting her they're minting her on the blockchain
Save the queen
Ah, it's the only way to keep her alive is to put her in the in the in the god's right place to queen
You're right clicking the queen right click saving the queen is a punishable by death offense
So you will be found
But I thought you're supposed to god save the queen only is god the only one allowed to right click save
You're supposed to god
All right, I was confused by that
I you know i'm just gonna nick and eddie is odd bit and say why do we have to ask god to save the queen?
She's got an army and men with guns
Like god could have a go now the blockchain might be all right
That's just god. God's got guns. She's doing all right
This whole time we thought they were talking about god, but god's actually an acronym for gamers on demand
Like she has her gamer army to rise up
Oh god, we didn't think about they've all been waiting
For her to snap her fingers and the gamers will rise up and uh
What will they do? I don't know they were raised playing the getaways so they'd probably drive really badly
They'd rise up and bring all of their playstation 2 memory cards and they will save the queen
Oh, yeah
Save the queen memory card thing and you have a little queen head in there
That'd be cool. I just think a little 3d model just slowly rotating. Yeah, and then I delete her to just clear room for more metal giz solid photos
Yeah, sorry. Yes, right priorities. Yes queen. Hmm. Do you want to do you want to overwrite this file?
Yes queen
That's the day when we're we have voice voice controlled computers and it's really gotten out of hand
Well, they're looking for the commands. Yes queen. Yeah, we're not we can't we can't say yes, please we have to say that
I pushed into it
Snake yeah, I wanted to ask you a question
I wanted to ask you at some point on this podcast about how you found the pcp
Sure, because I saw because I saw um, I didn't know
I saw you you pledged to the patreon and I was like
Is that the to snaker and then I looked at your and it was it was linked to your page. I was like it is
It's the guy same guy. I know this guy. Love this guy got to get that guy got him
That's where I am. So here he is
So, yeah, how'd you how'd you find this? So it's a long and winding road?
I'm a little bit trepidious and it's kind of spotty, but there's when I was a okay
um, I didn't start watching anime until I was
21 22
God you're so pure so long. I was so pure so long and it fucks you up if you get if you if you hook them too early
It's funny as well because I have a problem with watching films and watching as well
I don't watch them that much and I just thought I'm gonna really see about getting into anime
So I watched 100 shows in a fucking year, which and then I didn't watch much afterwards
I just catch I just catch one or two things a year maybe it was it was the year of anime
Yeah, and that was also I was in university at the time and I was also doing the youtube
I was doing the youtube and I was looking at what other creators were doing and because I just got into anime it was
I watched I watched Trixie and
It's funny because I talked to a lot of people in the essay. I'm not gonna put them thing
I had more respect for what she's doing than most of what most of them
Just wait you cut out for a second. Sorry. It was basically I I
Started watching Trixie just kind of see I looked into any tubers. Oh, sure
I kind of wanted to know what was going on and I've been and you know
I I talked to other game essay creators and I have made to all do game essays and I think
I think even back then I had the highest opinion of
Stuff but it's like I thought it was okay. It was fine. Um, it was like stuff
I could watch and then I
I found the pcp through that essentially because I also needed a lot of podcasts because I was doing
I was doing a practical filmmaking course at university
Which is a lot of a lot of your credits where you literally had to
Go and get work you had to go and approach people and do that and a lot of your
grade in the third year and a lot of it in the second year was influenced by
how many credits did you have and
The minimum was five you had to have five
Rolls it could either be like five rolls on one project if you were mad or like one roll on so many
I ended that year with like 25 credits
Saw a lot of credits
I was I was kind of sneaky about it because I was literally the only person in my class doing
Audio engineering. No one else wanted to do audio engineering. Everyone there wanted to be a director
They wanted to be a writer. Of course
Classic
I was the only person in there who like spent my kind of
University grant on a sound kit on like a boom mic and all that
So I was on trains a lot and I needed a lot of podcasts and yeah, I kind of
I listened to a bit of ps uh pcp and it didn't stick with me then
My most of my memory of it then came years later when I was bloody doing
The evil the evil genius video. I was I kind of got bored of listening to the sound of that game
It's got a great soundtrack. I was just like I need to this is a podcast game now
and yeah, it was it was basically via Trixie and
This is gonna sound really weird and like a lot worse than it is. It wasn't actually until a few months ago
I started actually looking into everyone else in the pcp because like because I don't listen fine
I don't listen to I didn't watch Trixie stuff that much anyway. It was like her stuff was
fine, but it was
How do I put this?
Because I don't want to be doing something with it
It's the perfect stuff that I can listen to it when I'm working because it's just mentally engaging enough
Sure, yeah
If I listen to something way too interesting, it's like I have to stop and pay attention
If it's not interesting enough that part of my brain isn't shut up that demands to be entertained and fed
So yeah, it's kind of like I've bounced I've bounced in and out over the years essentially
Well, I uh, I found I think I found your
Evo video because I had played that game and like I didn't know anyone else who I just I saw it recommended one day
Uh, and I just thought that was needs. I was like, oh
There's I played that game like a once and nobody ever talks about it
Yeah, so I checked that out
And then I think a later on I think after I saw
The running shine yick video your yick video got recommended and I was like, oh, it's that guy. It's the same. Oh, it's the same guy
Let me check out his other videos and I've watched a lot of your videos even though I don't play
any of the games you talk about I get that a lot because
My mission statement has changed a lot over the years and at one point and I do still kind of hold to it
Is I want to do these kind of long form deep dives on games that would otherwise
Probably not get this treatment
I break out something big occasionally
Because really I just kind of at heart of it. It's just pursuing what I find interesting
but
Stuff that's got less eyes on it. I'm just kind of drawn to that
But ding ding
What was that? I oh
Oh, that was my computer for some reason that notification didn't go through my headphones. It's just
Okay
I just got I thought I just got cinema sins dinged for something. Yeah
Oh my god, no, that's the mac text message sound
Tom's nft is just minted. It was oh, you know, I've been working on it hard
You know, I figured if I'm gonna make a big video dunking on nft
The best thing to do would be to immediately launch one of my own
It's like it's like it's like ironic, you know satire. Yeah. Yeah. I want to ironically get like 10 ethereum. It'll be good
Yeah, um
It was funny actually the year I did evo and yeek because that was in the same year
A lot of games I did that year. I was picking as excuses to
Again, there it is again. Tom. You're a madman. I can't stop it. I can't stop it every every time snake lies
it goes ding
No, come on. It hasn't been enough for that
Okay, I'm good. Um, it's
That year I was like I did the video on um, we the revolution I did that
I was just kind of picking games that gave me an excuse to research external stuff
Oh god, tom, please. I'm trying to mute it. I'm trying. I can't do it
How could you not mute? I I don't know
I don't know what angels you use
I can't put the spoon. You got to flip it turnways
You got to tip the take the volumes the volume knob and you got to flip it turnways
Or not we could just keep dinging. Yeah, I'm fine with that. Yeah, we'll just pretend citizens is joining us
I'm so sorry for that
All right, I'm turning off playing sound effects. I don't know how to actually switch the fucking thing over
Hey, that's my name in my series
Huh playing. I don't know why I settled on that name. I think it was a real friday afternoon decision
Hey, it works. It's not taken. Yeah
Playing a game
Playing a game and I feel it it was kind of like um, it gave it a sort of relaxed vibe because it's the kind of
Even my try and go as deep as I want to on them
I think it's it's meant to be something like a guided tour of whatever I'm playing and you know
What what experience did I have along the way? What did I learn? What did I find out and what can I pick into with it?
And that was with evo was fun because I like genuinely in the course of making the video
I discovered the other one existed and yeah, I got it gave me an excuse to read up on you know
Ancient creatures and all that and I have a friend who's really into paleons paleontology
So that was fun
I got to speak to her a lot about that and she gave me to yeah
And I learned enough to make a bunch of really bad puns at least about creatures
I I guess I won't specify
Because I guess it's sort of I don't know I don't know if you can spoil like a like a review
If you want to it depends I don't mind it being spoiled because I spoil
I won't I won't I won't because that I like that video and the way the way that the other game ends is really
Cool and it's like makes for like a cool the the ending of that game makes for a cool ending to the video as well
Yeah, I I do think um a lot of my videos
I feel very blessed in terms of um, what's the word for happy coincidences serendipity? I feel
A lot of my videos just kind of come along
There's a I'm always making a video and there is a point where I will learn something or a friend will say something
and then it's just very serendipitous and it all kind of pans out and with the
With the uh evo video there were two of those which was discovering the original game existed and it just
Even though it's the earlier game it ramps up in such a nice way that I could put it second and just have a lot of fun
with the better ending and comparing it back
And uh working backwards to peppering jokes and like call forwards
And it was also me and a friend are just the same friend who really likes paleontology and that
We just finished the table. Tom. I got I got I got it. I gotta stop you. Tom
Your typing is he's mincing. He's mincing so loud. Why?
I hate everything. I don't I don't know if there's any way that you can we maybe get this this typing situation under control
Can we brain it? I'll just type on my phone then
Okay, I have I have a real life thing happening right now. It's okay. It's okay. I'm gonna multitask
I'm rocking up. I'm rocking up. Eleazar cut this all out
No, Eleazar keep it all in make me feel like an idiot duplicate it Eleazar just whatever you think
Base boost his typing
Whatever you think makes for the best listening if it like syncs up cool to like the the the the speech then do that
Otherwise, you know have fun have fun, buddy
It's like a it's like a drum drum roll for the speech but
The second bit of serendipity was I was I think I was part way through recording
Or I maybe hadn't just started. I can't remember these like Dave. I just finished
I was probably through recording the second game and me and a friend had just finished a tabletop session
And she said to me
Hey, have you ever heard of spirit science?
Yeah
And
Showed me we used to have a video about that on our channel. I didn't see I didn't see munchies pcp lecture until afterwards
It's gone now
Although it is still around it's still around on the internet in places, but we saw far channel
But okay, and just anyway. Yeah, so so so we so we know about spirit science is what i'm saying
Yeah, I don't I probably do not know as much as you I like watch that video
And I I studied bits and I studied bits and pieces and just saw the correlations and
I I'm it was a fun coincidence. I may have like with a year of reflection of thing
It's the motifs of spirit science are repeated in a lot of
new age shams
um, yeah
It was a fun coincidence to be able to kind of dig into and just peppering that little bit of the video
I mean, it's it's it's more it's even though like a lot of that stuff is not unique to spirit science
It's more fun to talk about spirit science in specific because everyone knows it and it's this
particularly wacky yeah like a iteration of that sort of new agey
Uh belief system. It's the potpourri
Soup mix grind ground up everything's in here
Yeah
Yes, and also the fact that it's presented through a fucking extra credit squeaky guy youtube animated puppet man
That is the most surreal part of it is that yeah, it's like why is this the form that?
Yeah, putting a weirdly innocent squeaky face on it
I don't know very very strange decision for like how you want to spread the word of your weird
I do think it's kind of like the people who you know the the alt-right pipe line of people who do like friend like that creepy
cutesy like we're friend is like
just
It could be like just making it
You know defanging it out the gate to make it more presentable to some people. I don't know that's just like my
my way of like it's I mean it sounds like like sinister or is it just
Well, there is there is a question. There is a little bit of anti-semitism mixed in there as the
It's it's it's a bit like it's that video is definitely
Like those youtube videos are definitely meant to put like a friendly approachable face on like whatever the fuck this is
They don't they don't say anything
They don't in those videos. Yeah, they don't say anything bad about the Hebrews
But the Hebrews are singled out as a particular group of aliens that has a
That has an outsized like influence on like the course of
Of human history. So like the door is open for something
My thought is is is like i'm not sure whether it was
like
The the the the presentation was made cutesy for reasons of covering up
What would be otherwise sinister language? I feel like the person who made that just likes that
It could be they saw extra credits once and I was like, oh, I want to do that
But with my thing it's tricky to it's tricky to discern intent
Because essentially well, here's the thing. You know why like Nigerian email scams are poorly written
It's essentially that they know they're poorly written. They don't want anyone who can suss that out
They want the people they don't care if it's a smaller sample base. They want the people who will fall for the fall for the thing
That's why they're very upfront with you know being poorly written because they don't want anyone who I just I'm just repeating myself
You know the uh, you you might you might as well. You might as well
You might as well filter out the people who are going to be like suspicious
Essentially, yes, so you make yourself look as stupid as possible so that you'll only get the punters who are easily fooled by it
That's a funny that's a funny way to think about it
Like they just made it just made it down on purpose
I heard that on like a scam baiting channel, but it makes a degree of sense and that
Yeah, why wouldn't you want to filter out the people who are going to be difficult?
Yes, yeah, I think so. I think so
um
It is a
I think I watched that entire video. It's like many hours long right the spirit science one
Isn't it like six hours like the like the full human history one is like huge
Yeah, I think the one I watched was only about an hour and a half
I get a series right I got the easy right it is part of a series and I
I jumped and I bounced between them trying to
I was trying to grasp a
Uh, I was trying to grasp what could be the
The synopses of this and it's
Hard to pin down especially with you know the person who who made it and it's a
It's a blurry road backwards
God, I'm trying to remember the name of the guy because it because it was inspired by some old grifter in the 70s who
Kicked it off with some something by another name
It's been it's been a couple years in the video and my specific deals. Yeah, that's the tragedy of
Like the year I made those videos was as an excuse to learn a bunch of stuff and then my own
Confounded memory made me forget a lot of it
I am finding it funny though because now I'm thinking about the fact that I did the weed a revolution video
And munchy also did the french revolution which I did catch and was very right
That's right
I think it's a real that's a really interesting game
Yeah, it was fascinating
It's I feel bad for I have I have seen that one. I feel bad for a friend of mine because the first time I played
I had a mate round and
I think this is old let's play a brain of just I regret not recording us playing that game
Because we had like some it would have been good banter. Yeah, and then I felt weirdly cynical about that afterwards
The the you you review games that I've like never even heard of and I never would hear of
Ever I think tech like when when be on on as it flame chase ma
flesh flesh
Chasmer, yeah, or chase chase ma as I like to call it
Oh, yeah
Well, that's that's just one I I've never heard of like neuro or whatever
Yeah, that one I got from youtube pms when they existed. I did not find one by myself
Uh, what's what's uh, I don't know. I guess like what's uh, what what's in a game that makes you want to
Be like I want to talk about this game like what is it about the games you pick that are like this is like
Why do you pick the games you pick? I guess when I figure that one out? I'll tell you
Okay
It really is just
I I said before we started recording proper that because we kind of briefly touched on it, but I'm
This is the first time in
Years that I've had anything approaching a planned ahead schedule and it's just four videos
But usually yeah, I will finish the video and I'll just kind of look around and I'll just think
What do I want to do right now?
And sometimes it'll sneak up on me sometimes
I will just kind of pick something at random and then decide I'm gonna make this interesting
It's gonna be it's like a challenge myself
Sometimes another category that the well is drying but narc the one I'm doing next is one of those games
What's the game that I played as a child and it's just kind of in the recesses of my memory
but I never finished it because
When I was a kid I had fucking weird taste and I would buy the strangest things and then just
Never finished them and I'd come back to them years later because
I bought I wound up buying a lot of russian jank as a kid because those games were always trying
Because I wanted games that promised a lot of freedom and a lot of mechanics
Even when in the early 2000s
The the the trade for that was going to be the mechanics are going to be a little bit
Not half baked just kind of not all the way there. I guess that's a distinction about difference
But you know, but that just kind of led me into I'd see a game like boiling point in the back of the box thing
Was look how big this world is and you can drive anywhere and do immersive stuff and it's like
That sounded cool as hell to me. I like the freedom of it
Or like gangline manager on gang and things like that. It's like, okay. Yeah, I I need to own this
Gangland is a weird one. Yeah
Watch watching you play that one in that video. I'm just I'm looking at that. I'm like
I don't know who would make a game like this. I don't I don't I don't get it medium monsters would
um, I guess so I I am kind of sad genuinely that the
The italian crime family the mafia crime family
Genre isn't as big as it could be
It's
It could be a really fun simulation. I think but I guess it's really tricky because there are a lot of things
You'd have to account for account for and it's a very different rhythm
But the last game that we got in that vein was um, empire of sin, which was
made by George Romero and his wife
John Romero, right?
John Romero. Yeah, that bad. Yeah, John. George Romero is the horror. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Whereas John Romero is the uh
Is the guy who's made you his bitch
Yeah, right. Yeah, I think he just did now because of that slip-up. I think he
Being beaten down right now
Um, right
But and that game
I want to love it because I I kind of want games like this even though I
As a kid I wasn't too big into gang stuff
But now it's like I'd love a good simulation hat, but it's just very boring
It's very artfully put together. It pays a lot of homage to the gangsters of the time
It has the rope-iest Irish accent. I've ever heard in a game. I can't ropey
I see. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
But it's uh, it's not doing it. It's it's just not there. I don't know
Do they just they just haven't done the genre justice yet? I guess
It's the problem is trying to figure out the fun in running a crime family because it's
I guess on the surface of it. It'd be very slow very meticulous. There'd be a lot of rules of respects
What is ometta?
Not the game the literal code of honor, but you know, you know, how do you finally game by that?
That episode of the simpsons
I don't even remember what episode it is, but there's a little joke where martin prince
He's playing he got a new video game, but it's the uh, it's the like game version of uh,
My dinner with andre. Oh, yeah
He's playing that in the arcade. Tell me more. Yeah, the the the three the three. Yeah, tell me more bon mort
Like bon appetit
That's good. Yeah, I think it would be really hard to find the fun on that and
How much of a big audience would you have of people who really want an in-depth?
Mafia simulation where yeah, you might have to go to a meet and pay respects and work your way up
If I can surgeon simulate the physics trying to spin the spaghetti around your fork
Oh, yeah, bring that to your mouth. Don't let any of it get on you or you just lose respect
Don't don't let any don't let any source splash on the eye of your of your business partner
Because then you'll get mad and you'll get a gun out. There's a soprano's uh video game for ps2, right?
Is that any yeah road to respect it takes place between between seasons three and four or two and three and was based on a
Storyline that got dropped from the show
I wouldn't have that has anyone played that one. How does that one play? Is it just like a generic?
I think only cybershell has played that game. Oh really cybershell the biggest soprano's man. He's a soprano's guy
Um, I'm working my way through sopranos and I did I was on a stream the other day where I realized and I've still never seen it
I was on a I was on a stream the other day where I realized and joked I should play that game when it's canonically accurate to the
To the series
It's like oh, well that was a great season. Just boot up your playstation too
Just oh god. Oh, I really took a dive here. I need Tony's full story
I like ps2 tie-in games to media franchises because it's like the the the area where they're just about getting
photorealistic faces, but not like good
They're just being able to like put a png of an actor's face onto a model
And you just like okay, I can recognize who that is
But it looks like shit
Um, but that's the fun exactly ever there's like a 24 game. I played where it's like jack bowell's face
But the gameplay was godawful. Have you just flying all over the place and getting shot
It's like when you play the funniest one is uh the lord of the rings game
Like the two towers or ps2 where they'd like shift from the movie and then try and recreate the frame in ps2
And like back in the day is like whoa now you look at it. It's like
Oh
The I mean you could tell there was a difference back in the day, but it really just was oh my god
I'm used to playstation one exactly so incredible and uh, I think I think tech's trying to access something
It's it's it's okay. It's okay. I just don't want to talk over people. You know it is uh, no you got you got a battle for dominance
Is how I know there's a it is that's how we do it. Have you ever played have any of you ever played enter the matrix?
Yes, yes
That game multiple times as a kid xbox. All right. So yeah, I'm playing through it right now for reps to gog, right?
And um, yes
So the thing is the thing with enter the matrix is that it's a tie-in game to the movies, right?
But it's it's 100 canon and they got like act they filmed actual footage
Of the actors from the movies for the game. So there's like there's live action cutscenes for the games
I'll really fucking dark by the way
And then it'll switch it'll switch to the in-game models that look like shit, but um
It's it's like the apex predator of of movie tie-in games because it gives you like crucial plot information that you won't get in the
Yeah, it's reloaded. Like I was watching the it's like it's like the kingdom hearts chain
Is it like the kingdom hearts chain of memories of uh, of uh, yeah, it's it's like that
It's like that like level of crackheadedness, but for like a matrix video game
And it's like 45 minutes of new film scenes or something crazy like like
It's like you don't play as like nioh or whatever, but they got like kary and moss and shit
For for like yeah, it's like the two side characters that like briefly appear in yeah ghost may have to play on both because they have
slightly different stories
Yeah, I was I was trying to see if I could get away with just playing as ghosts
But I think I'm gonna have to I'm gonna play as nao. We just uh
Just to say I did it wouldn't be it wouldn't be right. I thought fucking having the uh, this
Rise of Skywalker event in fortnight was bad back in the day
We had 45 minutes of an entire movie in a shitty video game
Yeah, I mean you you'd be watching uh, the matrix reloaded and you wouldn't know you wouldn't know how uh, naobie got the uh
Got the oh my god. What the fuck was the name of that stupid ship from uh, that like
Nebuchadnezzar not the nebuchadnezzar or the logo so the the ship that gets like destroyed in one of the animatrix, uh
Movies that is basically delivering
Was it was it was it called the was it called the sargon of a cod?
You know, it should be it should bend that joke
Wait, I wait no, do I have like a foggy memory that like there is a ship called that it's somewhere in the I don't think
It's within the theme. Yeah, it would it would there would be okay. It makes sense. But yeah, there's like a
They like get they get like some message like a distress signal or whatever from a ship that's supposed to alert zion
That the machines are have found their location. They're attacking them
And that's like the whole impetus of like the matrix revolutions
But they don't tell you any of that in the movie the only reason I figured that out was because I happened to watch the animatrix
Another tie-in that is tech that is cannon
Oh, man, it's cool
I think I watched the animatrix and I don't remember anything. It's really good at all
I remember the one like main story that goes through it of like how actually the machines got kind of fucked and humans
So I was like, you know what that's some really second renaissance
Yeah, my 13 year old brain is down with this shit
Mmm
It's like society. It's genuinely cool. Even if um, that's a dangerous word even if reloaded and revolutions like kind of suck but
Uh, the world and like the the lore and the the world building and stuff are like really really
Uh, interesting in the matrix
I'm not I'm not gonna spoil it. But um, who here has played uh, path of neo
I've not played that I want to I heard it like when it came out
I heard it was like actually pretty good and everyone's like, oh, this is way better than enter the matrix actually
That's what I heard too. I'm looking forward to it
What is path of neo?
It's like I think it's a game that just follows the movie story
It's like and you play as neo and you fucking beat the shit out of dudes, right?
Oh, yeah, it's the whole trilogy that kind of condensed into a video game and it's a decently fun, uh, brawler
And I was gonna and I don't know if I'm not gonna spoil but now I'm not even gonna do my very light
Nudge and wink spoiler if I now I know someone wants to play
Yeah, I
It goes places. I was gonna see how much that game costs on ebay for xbox right now
Uh, it I got it. I got it on ps2. I like a local game store for like 15 bucks. It's not
Uh, that expensive. Oh, sorry. They're 14 dollars. I got it for 14 bucks
14 dollars for xbox. That's not bad
Maybe I'll buy one
I will say my one weird bit of matrix game trivia that is like not really a spoiler
But also just kind of viscs. It's funny. There was a matrix mmo that was also canon and orpheus dies in it
Yep, there was a matrix mmo. It was it was
It's you know what you know what?
That's pretty cool. Actually. It's like, yeah a matrix mmo would be canon
Uh, and matrix was an mmo. Yeah, like movie. Yeah, that seems really thematically like and good
I have a disc copy of it. You can't play it anymore, but I I had the matrix online
Um
Awesome. I didn't play many. Awesome kid. I had I had that one
You know what better than wow? I said
Let's go
Uh, hmm, I I bounced off of final fantasy 11
After a while and that was about it. I uh, it's all about final fantasy 14 now
I had star wars galaxies, which was way too complex for me. You know who messaged me
You know who DM'd me on twitter the other day?
After after getting embroiled in another argument with one of these weirdos who insists that there's nothing political about the plot of one piece
In which the literal final bed the literal ultimate antagonist is the government
um
one of
None other than maryweather
Popped into to weigh in a little bit on that and then he he DM'd me
Afterwards to tell me that I should really play final fantasy 14
Because it's cool and good and it's got a free trial up to level 60, but that's what he said
He all he he didn't say the exact copypasta, but he I mean he delivered all the all the basic information
Contained there and I have my husband is playing final fantasy 14 literally right now in the other rooms. Oh, they managed to
sound
I yeah, they've been able to do it
I uh, I had my group's tabletop session cancelled this week because of ff 14. So I hate that damn game
No
Bullshit, it's bullshit. That's un that's unacceptable. We have to hold no
It's your fault. It's your fault for not joining them in final fantasy 14. I tried. Okay. This is the pettiest damn thing
I'll ever say I'm just not an mmo guy, but I played it for half an hour
And I stopped and I'm gonna admit this is on me. This is just me being a dumbass
I just said I'm sorry mate. I can't do this. I hate how everyone is dressed in this game
That sounds that sounds like uh like one of those
Iroly things that like whenever someone says that the designs in final fantasy 10 are dumb. I just get mad
You know, I like how people are you talking about the npcs? Are you talking about the uh the player character?
I hated everyone
I walked into a room and a lot of fells started getting sassy with me and I'm like
I don't feel like this
It was entirely petty I was not an mmo guy
Yeah, it wasn't not my jam. So but I've been taking the piss out of a friend for liking ff 14
Just for the sake of it for years and you know what that was ammo
Good my stupidity and pettiness is ammo. I mean it's it's not that petty because like i'm an mmo
You play for hours if you don't like the look of your character
The hell's the point in being there? I suppose but no, it's just i'm just saying you know my dislike of it is
Serious, it's just an ongoing bit for years that has become steadily more internalized
People make fun of me for liking water warcraft
Uh because of the giant shoulder pads and no other. Well, I like the giant shoulder pads
I want them to be even bigger actually. No, it's silly. They think they're so cool
Just like dragon balls you with all the spiky hair. They're dumb
They're not cooler than me think of think of all the storage you could put in those giant shoulder pads
Why why the why isn't it there like five stuff where containers where they're organs built into each one?
Where are the pockets? I
Look seeing a world of warcraft guy with huge shoulders oof her poor bag
I'm just thinking does that guy have any cartilage left in his knees. That's too heavy. No
No, he's just very strong. He's so fucking strong
Look, I don't play video games. I don't he's got a sword the size of the earth
I've just been sitting here. I've just been sitting here gathering gathering of stuff for my topic
Yeah, because I've had since since the month started 1st of december
Shit happened and every day there's been some crazy shit happening to me most of it bad
Um, so to start with I don't have it. I lost my job
And it's not like
Oh, I don't get to go to McDonald's anymore like go whatever the fuck no
My job was working for pencil mation one of the largest animation channels. I was gonna ask if that's the job you were talking about
Yeah, what happens they have
All right, so for people who don't know pencil mation
Is like a animation series about a stick man who walks around on a piece of paper and there's a pencil that draws things
And he interacts with it. Wait, wait, sorry, uh, is my is my cameo still gonna make it in
Yes, I was gonna get to that
So I I watched the first episode of pencil mation
In 2007 I was a little boy and I made a fan of your job. I just wanted to see my face in the show
I'll get to it. You gotta be patient then I can't I can't I have tell you this story
I'll kill you wait. I said I have a lot of patience before so I gotta I gotta do that
Okay, well anyways in 2007 I saw it and I was a fan of it and I made like a little fan animation
Back fan that I still have and I forgot about it for years
And then in 2016, you know, like or no 2017 2018 like 11 years later
I got a message from tr or y the famous my little pony porn animator
I'm saying that they wanted to hire him as a director, but he didn't feel like it
So he was just telling other people he knew like who did animation if I'd be interested and I said, oh sure
And then I realized I got the job and I realized afterwards it was a thing. I was a fan of as a kid and that was cool
um
Well, the reason I got laid off is because a lot of people got laid off a lot of people
Um, are they downsizing?
Yeah, okay, so kind of funny. Um, I looked up pencil mation so I could grab screenshots of all the cameos I've put in for pcp things
Because now what I'm no longer working there. I no longer care if people know what I did that. I used to be very secretive about it
Funny thing is I looked them up and the two results I see are at the end of pencil mation and a graph going down
Basically, what's happened is the youtube for kids
designation has completely screwed them over
Instead of getting like 10 to 20 to 30 million views per video putting out free videos a week
They are now getting like 50k views
Whoa, okay, because of an out an algorithm change
Well, okay, so
You as four kids it was the four kids destroys your ads and fuss your search ability
Right
It's it's a bit more complex than that. So originally, um, only like one or two videos were getting flagged like every couple months
They weren't getting flagged that much
And they managed to avoid the four kids thing by saying no animations for everyone, you know
It's not just a baby thing even though
There to be fair it was mostly kids watching their stuff
But like they were trying to like avoid it because they didn't want their ad revenue getting cut down to like 10 20% of what it was
The problem is is because most of our audience were genuinely kids and the episodes were not appearing on the kids app
Where it was getting used more and more. Um, their viewership
Um was starting to go down. Um instead of getting like regularly like 20 million views a video
They were getting like one or two million which is still good
But like for how big the team was they they were like just scraping by
so
They noticed on a couple of the videos that had been automatically flipped to four kids
They had a resurgence in views shortly afterwards like we're they're getting 10 20 times the viewer count
So even with the loss in it like ad revenue like, you know percentage
The added views were going to add up to more money
So they thought maybe we just need to bite the bullet and switch everything
And they did about a month or two ago
And it worked for a while as in flagging it for kids
Yeah, they they intentionally flagged for stuff for kids. If you do it intentionally you can switch it back anytime
It's only when youtube does it that it's permanent
So if I get it did that as an experiment it worked for a bit and then
Suddenly like a flitch a flitch a switch was a flitch a flitch swept. Yeah
Like internally somewhere at pencil mation, um at youtube. Sorry and just overnight it just went to nothing
And I've seen this happen before it happened to my old channel nightfall studios
Why did that happen though?
According to
Ross who again, he has like fucking crazy. You mean you mean of game brumps?
No, no of uh chris farms. No ross ballinger
Of pencil mation. He's a cool guy. Oh, okay. He was he was gonna fucking just two russes in animation. I can't believe it
Impossible impossible. He's not even made of rubber. What the fuck how did that happen? But
According to him the algorithm
Oh, I got it. No, I got it. I got it
Rip rip to the podcast
It's uh, I'm sorry
What he's what he's heard from his deep state connections at youtube is the algorithm has like a good video switch and a bad video switch
Or maybe a good channel switch and a bad channel switch
It'll just decide channel bad and just fuck them over this happened to one of my old channels
I don't use it anymore. Um, but we had a video on there that was yeah nightfall studios
We had a video called a cult classic. It was a my little pony animation. I did
um
Which is probably one of the probably the best video I made it used to get about 20 000 views a day consistently for years
And then like instantly in a single day a day pretty much
um
And then instantly it dropped to like
50 views a day like
Like instantaneously because youtube said video bad flip the switch
I think apparently internally apparently that's how it works at the time
I didn't know what it was. I thought like they just decided to blacklist it or something
It's a thing that can just happen to channel sometimes
And it happened to them and so they had to
They they were just like fuck we we have to scale back and so pretty much everyone was like go
I I'm not I'm not worried. I got good severance pay. I'm gonna be fine. Like we have
Enough in savings to coast by for like a year. So I'm just gonna be working on my patreon and stuff
Um, and I'll probably end up making a lot more money by the end of next year. So it'll I honestly with
It's good. I'm kind of glad it happened. That's what Trixie said and look what happened there
I was oh, yeah, but I'm I'm smart of in Trixie though. It'll be I'll be fine
I'm privating all of my porn drawings in three weeks
Save me now
Now's the time for me to make my porn drawings even more public because I don't have to worry about it being associated with me
You're working for a channel that does kids entertainment
Um, anyways, so I'm gonna I'm gonna show some of the cameos I've done
Uh, this episode, uh on on this frame. There's like there's a give and take drop face. It's very hard to see
It's at like one percent opacity
I have a dark inversion. You can sort of make it out. It's like
Oh, yeah, it's big if I have to like lean my head way back and I can sort of see it
Yeah, um, there's another one in this episode for one frame and uh, there was like a cloud smoke cloud
I put one in the corner
I put a number one on a painting at the end of this episode
They're all in the background
Dude, I fucking love the bra. I fucking love the bra
When when Gib drop that video years ago, I thought it was the best video ever and like all the comments were
Oh my god, you you lazy. Why are you making such a lazy review of my little pony?
With like jesse
No, no, no, this is when I was starting to be like, uh, jeez making a video every week sucks. I don't like it's boring
I'm just talking about pony show every time. So I started to fuck things up. I I decided to draw my pony
uh, like
avatar really really badly in ms paint
And bruhp was just one of the drawings, but there was a bunch of them. Oh, yeah
Explain the plot and I talked in a silly voice
That was a good video. I remember that it was episode with the I don't remember it was the one of rarity getting the green
evil thing whatever the hook
The evil the evil jewel or whatever
She got like the the evil
Book that gave her like green magic and she was doing a bad thing. I don't know. I love that video
I love I thought it was the funniest thing and everyone was like hating on it at the time
So I and I always like fuck you bruhp is good. You guys are shit. So I have a I have an emotional connection to it
Um, but I didn't do any cameos for a while because I was working too hard. Um, the workload got crazy in 2019
You'll notice in the first two videos. It's just like very simple. No backgrounds. It's just a blank
Paper texture and then in the next one. It's like a full-on painted background with a million characters
Yeah, that was during 2019
They started making the episodes way too fucking ambitious and it was like really hard to keep up
And this episode the one with the Ben st. Cameo where you're shoplifting in a market
Oh, my god, you can look at it's not I don't think the episode's out yet
There he is. I animated that it's just barely it's just barely me
yeah
so
That episode took two years over two years to complete when other episodes take just a few months
Yeah, 2019 like we were way too ambitious when we scaled back
On how complex the episodes were but yeah, that was one of those but yeah in total
97 episodes that are out. I've like directed either entirely or I directed part of them and it's like another
13 or so episodes that are unreleased that'll be finished by the remainder of the team at some point
So like 110 episodes total pretty cool
um
I'm I'm proud of what I've done there and I'm glad to be moving out
But yeah, those those are some of the pzp references. It's possible. There are more that I've forgotten
But I'll let you know if that ever if I ever find them
Literally epic. I was gonna say it's epic. It's not there's no other word for it
Uh, I mean, how many views did you get on the you haven't like millions of views on the uh?
Is it the cum zone video not the one with the with the pcp logo?
Yeah, the cum zone video has like welcome to the cum zone
Yeah, the first one has like 11 million views
Pretty good. Um, the the cuphead animation has like 90 million views that I put all the pcp stuff in
Hold on
All I have to do is search cupheads sort by most popular and it's like the second result on youtube
Spare some views sir, please
91 million views. Yeah
with the
This little hypocrite. Why not a hundred? Yeah
Um, it'll get there. It still gets views pretty quickly
My videos my my lectures, uh, they took a dip. They've been taking a dip by the dip views recently
No, I can't
But they're down. Yeah, they they they are getting less views than they have in like in like years
These past couple months, you know, we had the big bump with the uh when I released sonichi 102
And I thought that would give my channel a boost and for a while it did but no, it's down lower than ever
I'm a bit down. I'm a bit. I'm a bit cheesed about it. It's not good. But that is cheese
I was um, I need to
Animation youtube gets more screwed than anyone else unlike when youtube changes something or other
Yeah, yeah, the only reason pencilmation was able to succeed is because they did reruns
Um, when they uploaded a video like the first five minutes would be a new episode
And then it would be 40 minutes of reruns of old episodes. That's how they got the watch time up
right
That was the only way they were able to succeed which is technically like breaking youtube's rules for like, um
what's it called like
Uploading like re-uploading like the same content over and over
But I guess they were just skirting by on like a technicality. It's technically different content. So they were fine
Oh, yeah gives youtube any respect. They don't respect the people who actually play post there. Yeah, no
I mean, I mean if they were getting away with it
Last time I calculated I I went through and manually added up the view counts of every pencilmation episode
I've done and it was close to a billion views like two years ago. Nice if I'd um
If I included the fact that my episodes appear on reruns
And I have like almost a hundred episodes pretty much every rerun would have something of mine
So I'd be multiple billions of views at this point if I could fucking calculate it somehow
Incalculably high
Yeah, I need I need I need like a tool that I can like just input like a hundred like youtube links and it can just
Spit out the total view count for all of them because he's doing it manually fucking sucks
subconsciously suggested to potential billions
Yeah, and yeah the pvp. Yeah
It's we have to how are we got to flip the switch?
We've got to say the code word to like flip the switch to activate them
in the minds of the masses
Oh a little the little all hail plankton helmet that's being strapped into their head except it's been sainte
Maybe it's me, but does anyone have a feeling like get get get in is getting a step closer to an insanity every video
He makes I mean I still like them, but man
What a shift started as an assembly of different opinions on a particular episode
Then moved into a sort of not so serious review then stuff and now we're here man the pony
The pony youtube
Comments the kind of people who were leaving comments on pony youtube videos were
They were a different they were a different breed simply build
They're the they're the they're the people who analyze the analyzers
That over
Massacre show. So I'm not in I'm not in on brony stuff. I in a brony. I don't know about it, but
This is a fucking thing. I thought it was a joke for the first three years. It was happening. I thought it was an ironic bit
Yeah, definitely started is that right?
It I assumed I assumed it was until until I started finding some of the fan stuff and being like, oh, no
No, this is this is sincere appreciation. I'm seeing okay. All right. It was a weird
What I first thought but I was thinking like
This show I saw was like a youtube poop of it. It was like there's no way this they like this show
I thought it was an ironic thing and also a porn some clips of it
Some clips of it. I was just like, oh, that's cute. Maybe I'll look at it. Maybe I'll see for myself
Biggest mistake in my life. Absolutely. Look look where it's led you here. This cursive play
This is not coming ironically
Huh, if you'd ever what if you I don't want to repeat came on ironic
Well, hey oblivion fall sorry to hear yo that you got fired
Oh gross for gross misconduct
Gross for sex for sexual harassment. I'm sorry here. You got fired for sexual harassment. Anyway moving on to the next
topic of discussion
Yeah, no, that's no, that's a bummer
But the next the next topic is plagiarism. Oh, all right
This guy
I want to I want to talk about something else. Um, that's been happening to my friend recently. She's an artist
She has a she has a character that she uses to represent herself. It's like a hold on. I
Wait, I had a fucking no, I closed the folder. I had it all open a second ago
This situation is really funny. It's not just like, oh, you know, just artist dramas, but it's the fact that
like
People are defending something that is so obviously stupid that I can't wrap my head around so like
Hold on. That's loading up an image
So that's like some drawings like of my friend's character that they did over the years
They're like a black cat
like
spooky monster thing
And they've drawn like probably like close to a hundred images of them
It's like an overcat
Yeah, she's like a cat wolf thing and sort of like hybrid. It's hard. I don't exactly know what she is
It reminds me of uh, that uh, that thing in the um,
This is gonna sound bad the thing in the wall review
Lucy lace maker
Little white rat the nostalgia critic
Fills me with the urge to decapitate
That creature
I'm sorry to think and I will let you go back to I just want to bring up that
The other day because I heard about from me. I watched the nostalgia critic sailor moon review
Which has an extended aside on age of consent laws in japan, which oh, I know
It's true though. Wait, is that a new video or is it?
No, it's a few years old. It's old. It's old. He's like at this age
You can have a blow job, but you can't touch a vagina at this age
You can like he's like he's just going into the technicality for like 10 minutes and I'm like
It's like he's stuck on it and he says one sense and I knew it was coming because like we've been told about me
Everyone was like, okay, doc. You said the thing you can move on now
And then he just keeps fucking going for multiple minutes
okay
And he's like genuinely just like elaborating like the legal system
He's trying to make a genuine point about and then at the end the funniest part the punchline of all this is kind of
It ends on
And that's why when I put sailor moon whatever on my sexiest character's list. I didn't know
It's like, okay, dug that is genuinely the funniest joke you've ever written and you did not mean it that way
Yeah
I'm really sorry twins were up. So he got flak for that back when he made whatever that that list
Oh the sexiest characters. I'm sorry twins right like an actual topic with that
Was he like was he like thinking about this for years like oh god
I've got to have to I'm gonna have to address this somehow. He probably I bet he was I bet he was yeah
It was yeah, no the uh an airing of the grievances was the primary motivator
I guess behind the nostalgia critic sailor moon review because
The rest it was even worse than a usual nostalgia critic review in terms of just airiness and emptiness
Yeah
I mean it sounds like it was worth it though. That's oh, yeah, no we were me and I've watched through every
nostalgia critic film more than once with different friend groups because
Oh film. I thought you were gonna say every review. No, no every review. I'm not like I've watched every nostalgia critic review
No, just the films just just the films and they are I've actually never seen a single one of the films
Uh, they're they're a good drunken with mates watch if you're all in on the bit of how weird and bad nostalgia critic is
I've I've heard a lot about them
But I never watched like I'd never watched uh like uh
Like that guy with the glasses content in its heyday. So I'm not like I wasn't invested in the characters
I just know about them now as like. Oh, yeah that weird
diaspora of people that that all came from
Guy with the glasses like linkara and and uh, Todd in the shadows and Lindsay Ellis and all these people
Every time they're all just mingling every single time juwari always on screen. It's harrowing
You just kind of got to think about it
Like damn there he is. Okay. He he's the guy he committed suicide, but did he also have some like sexual assault
Sexual assault allegations come out after the fact. Yeah
Yeah, I don't know exactly the extent of it, but uh
everyone was
Everyone was like they at first
Suicide obviously everyone was very sad. Yes, and then they learn about that later and they're like, uh
I've got to delete all of my sad things. I said
They couldn't because I love all my loving all my loving tributes to juwario
Yeah, that's why I love lull
lull
Anyway, what were we talking about something? We're talking about the plagiarism thing. I was gonna get into that
Yes
Yeah, so anyway, they've had this character. They've had this character for like a couple years
Um, and one of their artist friends who was a much bigger artist really liked the character
They they were simping they were simping hard. Oh my god. She's so cute. I want to cuddle. I want to sex. She's so great
And my friend, you know told him well
It's too bad. My character is a lesbian lamal and he oh no cry emoji that does make that is very upsetting
It is very upsetting Frank. I don't know what I would do in that situation. Lose lose my mind. I assume this fictional character is a lesbian
Yeah, yeah, so he drew um a lot of fan art
Initially and because he really liked the character and he was really into it
So he drew a bunch of fan art that was really good. He's a really good artist. I think um
And he drew that for like for out 2020 for about a year. He was drawing fan art and that's the images on the left
And all of a sudden he had a new o.c
That he started drawing afterwards
That he claimed. Oh, no, this character is different. This is completely different. This isn't the same character or they look nothing like
And it's they look pretty so they look pretty
On the right. Wait a minute. That's the other one. Wait. Wait. Okay. The one of she's peeking out the wall
That's the same drawing
Yeah, that is the same drawing well spotted then he was literally the same drawing
That that drawing that drawing that's not the same drawing one of them has a speech bubble
Yeah, yeah, you're right. You know, she has a picture
See he insists. Well, well like her personality is different. See my version. She's straight
She's not as tall, you know with all the all these images or there's no background. You can totally tell how tall she is
um
Okay, and like and he insists that there's a bunch of differences
But they're all differences you can't fucking see because they're things that aren't being drawn at the time
Um, and yeah that one image that is identical. He sent that to my friend in 2019
Like as as like a piece of fan art he was working on two months later
Someone wrote a fanfic based on his fan art
where they like
Made them straight and stuff and then the remainder of his art was of
The character from the fanfic of the fan art that he was now
drawing
Fan art of a fanfic of his fan art of my friend's character
And saying it was no longer the same character even though the design was identical
Okay, and he then
A year later
It's confusing
Just just really to get around that lesbian roadblock by any means necessary it seems the any means necessary
He added he basically just yeah, he added a speech bubble to the image post
Posted to his twitter a year later and said it was his character
And so like we tried working things out with him like in dms like saying hey, maybe you could change the design
Maybe you could put stripes in her hair. Maybe give him a hand
Okay, okay, okay. So so the is the is the problem just like
He's basically using the character. He's using the design
But calling it his own character is the idea like
I don't want you using that design because it is so
Like it much it'll be confused for mine
Yeah, and also the fact that he was like using the character for like straight things and my
Friend is lesbian and was uncomfortable with it because it's like a character that represents her
And also they were just friends and she told him like that's an extra degree of discomfort. Yeah, yeah
Maybe I'm being like and for like a year she was asking him to change the design and he was like, oh, yeah
I'll get to it soon. I'll get to it soon. Um, actually, can you like drop it?
Um, uh, like I thought I thought like those just like those damn plebe and the wee blu rays. Oh, I'll get to it soon
Oh, when are we gonna go? Yeah. Oh, I did nobody bought me a burner burner though
You should try sending this guy a blu ray burner. See if that helps any
Yeah, so
Eventually it went dark for four months. Wait. Wait. Was it was snake?
Yeah, it wasn't like a thing. It was like I'm being maybe I'm being maybe a little naive about this
But it was just like
Really love the character and maybe I'm just not key to it on how much it's they're gonna share this thing
But why didn't he just do this for himself?
the character
I don't
I don't really get it. It seems it seems like the motivation on like
Like you can make the odd just why spread it around at that point artists are vain
This can confirm can confirm. Okay, right. Yeah. I'm not in on yeah
I'm just being I'm naively asking. I just it seems like to me if you wanted to like keep this
Going the simplest solution would have been to just be like, you know
Do what the porn artists do and be like your sexual orientation is whatever I feel like in my art and just go hand my
My feeling
Okay, I I'm getting the feeling that this is like what this is really about
Is like a like weird control thing like I want this part like it feels like it's just like crossing the boundary
into like
This is about the artists
If it's because it's because it's because it's because it's because it's her character
If I don't really consider this character, I like effectively becomes what I want it to be because I control this narrative now
I I just I could see that being like a thing because like maybe
They go to this artist. This is maybe they know it's the
representation the artist draws of themselves
And then he says oh, I want to cuddle that or I want to like is it that like
Yeah, it's like a maximally of like
The affection for the creator
Because that that takes it to a level of
Mm-hmm. It definitely that is definitely a bit of a weird thing
I I would not like make an argument based on that, but it is a no
Not accusing just speculating
Yeah, I know I know I'm aware
Allegedly
Yeah, like we've been we were trying to work this out for for like a year and he just stopped responding for four months straight at a
Certain point, so he made a call-out post which anytime someone brought it up on his twitter. He would just hide the reply
Um for like a week
And he just wasn't talking about it. So then they filed a dmca on a couple of images to like just get his attention and also because
We think it we read up on like how dmca works and like if you think you have a copyright claim
Which we think is valid you can do that and then he like came out and was like, oh, well
Well, the characters are obviously different. They look nothing alike
And also you don't even know your own character because
In in 2019 you said they were this tall and a couple years later you said they were like a few inches taller
So clearly you're dumb and don't know what your character is. He was like trying so hard to like
He was just trying so hard to like deflect everything and his I saw yeah
Yeah, he's right
And it was I saw your post where he tries to argue that they're not the same character based on and I like the really flimsy stuff
Like the different like foot anatomy when like even when he even when he draws the the original character
He draws them with that same foot. It's not like a character thing. It's just like the way he draws feet
Yeah, exactly
Like I have received a lot of fan art of my character and everyone draws the horns differently
On on my character. She's like a demon girl people draw the horns differently all the time and probably because like
um the way they
Look at the reference. Maybe they misunderstood the reference images I have or maybe if they just like drawing horns a certain way
Um, it doesn't mean it's a new character all of a sudden that's theirs that they can claim as their own
um
Let me stop unless I'm a bit maybe though like but what if I want your character to be
Is your character by?
My character will fuck everything. Are they gay? Okay. What if I want them to be I wanted to make them an insult
Yeah, I want to make them an insult
My character is literally unfuckable. I there's cannot be fucked under no circumstances
But it looks exactly like what's what's her name? What's the character's name?
Let it did something not lydia. What's her name?
Lydia from breaking bad literally unfuckable. No, not no
Oh my god, dude. She's so hot oblivion fall. What's her name? What's your character's name?
stevia
Are you can you hear me? Yeah, are you are you asking me a question? Yes. Yes. Oh, no, no, no my character's name is
Is is fallia. Sorry. Oh fallia fallia. Okay. Well, my fallia. This is my fallia is is just
Is just gross is ugly looks the same but mine is ugly and nobody likes her mine is infallible
And you can't have a copyright claim because uh, you've drawn her with differently sized boobs in the past
Sometimes you draw them really big and sometimes you draw them
Even bigger than that
Yeah
So clearly you have no consistency and you can't have a copyright claim. Yeah, it's basically
It's obviously different. Yeah
It's it's it's spelled the same but mine is pronounced failure and failure
Is a is a fake fail failure is a z z z cup and fallia is only a y y y
Failure is what I am. Oh why?
Uh, okay. Anyway
failure
That's my yeah, that's mine. She can't get laid
Amazing dark dark mirror
whole version
so
Yeah, this guy seems like he wants
To have his fucking way with it. He wants to have his way with this cat girl
We just if that's if that's if that's the goal though, why not just be like
Fuck what you want. I'm gonna just draw her
Regardless of whether you accept it or not
Because like
Isn't that what she's doing?
Well, no, no, no, I mean it's just keep doing fan art however you want, you know
Like regardless of what the intention of the original creator is
It seems like I feel like this might have been done to try and mitigate controversy, but this only
Is worse. It's worse because you're not just like you're taking a character on top
Putting it in this situation the artist doesn't like you're like doing two things instead of just one
Uh, it seems like a very poorly thought out plan
I I guess it's like I guess maybe he just he's just so compelled by this character
But it's like, but I would write I would make this character different though
But isn't it strange that if you're compelled for the character you're you're now arguing that the character is different
So like by your own definition, you've kind of like moved your own goalpost
It's like having enough shame to not just make a carbon copy of that character that is just named differently, but not having
It's having too much shame to god. I'm getting this backwards there. Let me work on this. Give me give me five minutes
Too much too. No, you're right too too much shame to just admit it. Yeah
You have enough shame to have started and gone this path
Right, right like a weird level weird in between of shame
Yeah, I feel I feel like you could have just gotten away with saying. Yeah, I I I draw your character and I made them straight
Yeah, I you wouldn't really need to say that you can just commit to the bit
And then and just say just say in your own in your own art like people go to your page
I see your art and then you say fan art of this oc
Then people will there's nothing to worry about people go to the actual artist to you know, you know, you know what?
You know what? I'm gonna go to bat a little bit and say that in this scenario
I think that would be fucked because this guy is a bigger artist
I think it would be a little fucked for a bigger artist to take the oc of a smaller artist and make like fan art of them
That is like well, correct. There's there's no good move here. I think what you're talking about like the less
This thing is kind of what matters because just a kind of thing on it
I don't know how much of your friend has put in their character, but
If any of themselves is in that character that still is kind of fucked up to do to someone
That's that's definitely the most fucked up part. True. Yeah, I
I really think okay. I really think that like yeah what you're saying tom
Like just like just draw fan art and have it be whoever you want
I would say yes
If it were a small artist doing that to the character of a bigger artist
But for a bigger artist to take the character of a smaller artist and draw art of them doing things that contradict
The power dynamic like what the creator thinks about them
I don't like my my brain and I think that's my brain is going to like people doing like fan art of tracer
Like fucking dudes, even though she's like canonically a lesbian, but like obviously the scale is much different in terms of like creative
But who cares who cares what blizzard right?
Yeah, yeah, I'm just I'm just surprised like this guy didn't just take that
Avenue, you know like it's still wrong, but I'm just surprised going this extra step and causing extra controversy
It seems extra stupid and correctly to just make the same character again and just say yeah, I do
Actually, this is mine
All right, I'll say it to the artist who is definitely listening. Um, you're not actually you're not actually banging the character you want
It's it's not that one
Please
Please stop edging right now
Just
This is like this is like that episode of the future drama. This is like kid Napster
Oh god is yeah, hell yeah
It all comes back
The episode's come full circle
If he he should he should he should put the character on the blockchain. He should mint it as an nft
Oh, no, no, no
Why why not why not there's no rules to get my legal fund made up
ready to go
Gonna sell nfts for that to fight that dmca claim
Oh, I can't say the hairstyle of a character is based on my friend's real hair. That's definitely one thing
Based indeed
That's what we like to call in the business weird champ
My friend told him if he changed the hairstyle like like months ago
My friend told him like maybe he could just change the hairstyle and put like a stripe in it
And yeah, it would be and he didn't do it you could you could you could totally
You could totally just change the hair and like most things could stay pretty much the same
You would only need to make minimal changes. I mean not not to shit on the character design
But it's like not generic, but like it's non-descript enough that a small deviation like that is all the plausible deniability
You'd need I do actually genuinely like I said give him a hand. It's just a power thing of just not even
Not even conceiving something that yeah
It's it can't it's gotta be it's about the fact it's about like this
It's about where the character comes from. It's not about the design. It's about like this is this character specifically
He spent a year drawing
He spent a year drawing fan art of the design and then a switch flipped and he
Spent another year drawing it as his own character
Like the timeline is just switched
He's put in the work. He deserves this character. I think you're right. You know what it changed my mind. I changed my mind
He earned it
Oh, no, I think I think
10 grand 10 grand or so. You know transition of power
You know his money where his mouth is
Actually, maybe your artist should make an nft of this character and then have this guy buy it make that joke. Oh, no
I'm sorry. I'm sorry the blockchain is a revolutionary technology
For just such now now we can settle disputes like this before it was all he said she said now
We can just we can just refer to the blockchain and understand ownership
You don't own this character
You just own a receipt that says you own the character and that's the best you can really do
If you have a receipt the beepers at the store don't go off and you can leave
Hmm
Oh like shoplifting. Oh like shoplifting like I did
in that one video
That oblivion followed me and then that I did it in pencil mates. It all comes back together
It's all tied together. It's all true in a spirograph of meaning
Uh
It all wraps around. Yeah, it's a spiral. We've all we've all we've wrapped all the way around. We've come 360
I guess anyone got any more uh shit. They want to bring up
My topic feels or wait. Are we are we done on are we are we have we said all we can have to say about uh
Missy I feel like we could head into voicemails soon ish. I uh if anyone
Huh, I'm just glad my topic was so shit and I'm glad we can avoid it
I know wait
Say it. Did you know it? Oh wait? I would oh wait. You didn't say it yet. No, um, but we we skin
We like we have to cross it. We surfed over it basically
Oh, we got it. We got to dig deep. We got to dig deep on the start. Okay. I'm sorry. I didn't realize
I was gonna my intro to it was basically you know how
When you when you kind of mentioned, you know, you can bring whatever topic you want and I
I was working on watch dogs legion video
So I like barely had time to think and then I I finished it. I was like, okay, I gotta get back to then
I said to the message and then I apologetically say I've got um, I've got a topic
But it's shit and you say I'll out be on brand and I'm like, well
Yeah, yeah
You said well, I'm dead like it was you said it was shit and I'm sure and I'm sure it's been talked about before
And I was like that's that's completely on brand fresh and I was like, well shit now. I better not think of another topic
I better just commit. I'll be sure to I'll be sure to go in saying it shit
And my topic was just gonna be and also at the time I thought it would be like
Even keel 50 percent american 50 percent british
But now we're massively outnumbered because it was
Because it was being it was being british on the internet. It was
The perception of being a british person and then I thought about that because I was playing not so good these days
I was just thinking like being british on the internet is a weird mixed bag
Because it's because we get if you're doing youtube videos
You just get a leg up because the accent makes people think you're clever no matter what yeah
Yeah, that's the weird thing with me though is like people can't tell that I have an english
I don't know what accent I have. It's definitely informed a little bit by
Americans talking on video. Yeah, and I've sort of adopted some mannerism. So people think I'm not british
You got to lean into it more. That's that's the power you you don't know if that's true
You and snake in my opinion and everyone can disagree if they want but in my opinion like
Neither of you have what I would consider to be like a very like
Like stereotypically or like very like obviously british accent. I'm like a stereotype is like a posh
Wanker
From the victorian era
You sound exactly like what I think of in my head when I think of a british accent. It's funny because when I
This is gonna sound really weird. It's like
I used to have sorry
I used to have a weirdly set dislike of other british people on the internet
Especially when they leaned into it for points or they like I am the british game rubber
It's like fucking have a personality
It's just don't yeah gaming brit and and uh total biscuit had like the the cynical brit
I've actually met the guy in real life. I like both of those guys
I mean, I guess it sort of makes sense because on the internet your voice is so important
So like if you're obviously british, I guess maybe you got to lean into it
a little bit maybe
The thing I didn't like about those is that I think it's just sort of a
If you wave the flag and you're like
I'm proud of my country
That's sort of like an american thing to wave the flag constantly and to be like hey look at what my nationality is everybody
That's sort of like a thing that
You don't do all the time. You do that when you you know as a special occasion. Oh the queen's getting another divorce
I don't know
In my mind like even british patriotism has a an angle of shame about it from what I've seen
Yeah, as it's there's always like a I love my country, but we're a bit shit and that's
I something fun. I'm always I don't think that people who exploit being british on the internet really do
I saw something I saw like a tweet or something that was like, uh, like yeah, like amer- american nationalism is like
We love guns and god and we love our greatest country in the world and and british nationalism is like
Yeah, it's shit here and that's just how we like it
That was that was like a lot of the humor when I was growing up was like every comedian
The most pro british thing would just be a love of how shit we are as a doing things. Yeah
There'll be observational stand-up comedy about like
Uh, I know all those other countries. They're doing all this and we're over here and it's shit and oh
We're standing in queues. Why do we like queuing as a nation? That's stupid. Ha ha ha
That's what it's like being british. I have heard I've heard a few different places
And I think this is really funny that apparently there is a certain uh attitude
In canadian politics. There is a particular, uh, what's the word? Um
Fixation or phobia of like not appearing to american
Like if you say if you say anything that sounds like too american, it's kind of cringe. It's like
Like there is a lot of like there's a lot of very like similar
Like nationalist and like like uh pro like trump. It basically trumpism sort of attitudes
Like they have it in canada as well, but they can't
Like say it that way
Because if you phrase it if you phrase it as like a pro trump way
That's like american and like you don't want to be seen as like being a big america stan
He's it's it's it's it's look down upon in canada. They really
They really want to have their own identity like we're definitely we're not america. We're not just america's hat guys
We're we're we got our own thing going on. We we're under the queen over here, right?
Yeah, they uh, now i'm imagining blackface over there. Yeah
Trump would never do that. Come on trump get the blackface out. Show us what you're all about
He could he could he he just he just runs he just puts on blackface makeup and runs in canada and replaces trudeau
Because they just love it so much
That's our prime minister right there. He's like pretends he gets he he loses 2020 so in 2024
He decides no i'm not gonna run against joe. No i'm not gonna run against kamala. No the kamala p tickets too strong
No one can beat it. Hey, I'll run it. I'll run in canada. I'll run it. It's unstoppable
It's an unstoppable combo. You can't you can't beat it. Uh, so i'll run in canada instead
I I could do I could do blackface like it worked for that other guy
You know what they say black is the new orange
Oh my god
It's all downhill from here. We can't we can't stop that
Can't keep getting away with it
uh, the
Oh, you were gonna say you smashed into something
I I smashed into boris johnson. No, I nearly smashed into boris johnson ones and like like in your car took him out
No, uh on foot. Oh, okay
Like I almost ran over. I was gonna say if it was your car like you should have gone for it
I mean I was on foot and I should have gone for it
Ruck be tackled in fair enough
I I used to volunteer with a group called, um
Good gym and it was
It was this weird mix of like
Exercise jogging and charity work. You would like jog to a place and like volunteer there for an hour
And then you'd jog back and you'd do that every week in different places
And over christmas we had um we had a thing a homeless shelter
And fucking boris johnson was there with his press team and he was just like pretending to look like he was getting involved
Like they'd film a shot of him, you know at the counter or just in the kitchens doing something
While we did do all the actual work like we had been jogging for an hour at this point like we had
I had done two tasks that day one of them was like carry like jogging with a backpack full of fucking tinned food
Like two kilometers across london to move it somewhere else
And then we had to jog there and then we got split into groups and I decided i'll go to the homeless shelter
That was something outside
And then we were told hey boris johnson is here and we're all getting roped into being in a fucking advert for him
So you were you were just there as like you were just there on your own
Uh as a group good gym was a group thing. There was about 10 15 20 of us. Okay
And like we were we were there to just actually volunteer
I'm kind of annoyed for several reasons which the primary one not just politically is just that
We were actually there to try and help and we were on a limited time
So why are we being roped into being a background shot for this cunt? Yeah, like
But but we were and I just let's just figure out. Fuck it. I'll be on I'll be on tv
I guess I didn't really put together at the time be on tv for this guy
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, and the the shot they wanted planned was hey, how about we tie it in with good gym?
We have boris standing in this lobby. It wasn't actually a lobby. It was a kind of
Subterranean area
Uh while all you guys come running in through the door and you run past him like you coming in twos one of you runs left
One of you runs, right?
It's the problem. This is so fucked up. They just like hey you guys you got to be in a you got to be in a commercial for the president
What the what the fuck he wasn't he wasn't uh prime him at the time prime in oh right he was
Um, you know, he was pre prime in but he's he's there now
and
Uh, so here's the problem
Well, there's many problems, but here's my physical problem was the
The area outside the door was actually just this tiny little alleyway because it wasn't really a an entrance exit
It just led out into this little subterranean area beside the building
You could barely stand shoulder to shoulder, but we had to jog do a 90
45 my under bad angles. We had to do a hard turn into the building
and then
Go up a step then jog in and jog to the side of him
I did not quite have the grace of foot to do all those motions. Was he jogging or was he just standing there?
He was just standing there while we all jogged past him. I get in missed the step. I'm like stumbling and they made you exercise too
I'm about to take a hard step
And this was actually when I was more fit. I've been out of it for a while
This is when I was like jogging all the time and
Actually taking care of myself
And like I stumble and I'm about to like I'm about to eat shit really bad
And then I I reach my arm out to grab something and I feel I feel something and my
You have almost moments in life where the world goes into slow motion
and you think
What oh, I know who that is. I know what I'm about to do. I'm on camera and I just
Using everything just right myself
Run past the thing
Probably looked really clumsy. I've never looked at the footage. I've never so you were so you were about to trip and fall
And collide with Boris Johnson
But you yes
But I wrongly saved myself
The one time to not trip and hit Boris Johnson
Yeah, I should have gone all in. I should have bought the first gave him a little donkey punch. I don't know
You should have pinned him to the ground
I'm like you should have tripped and like accidentally grabbed his like boom like oh my gosh. Oh, no
He's like
You should have had a you should have had a piece of toast in your mouth while you were running
Oh, yeah, it's to have a lovely romantic one. They call him senpai
The you know this reminds me what is the prime minister or not the old joe san can't be this cute
Oh god
What's up oblivion I was just saying this reminds me of a time that I had an encounter with the prime minister of new zealand
um
You guys you guys have a prime minister. What the fuck? I never see the president
All right, so in in 2005 prime minister helen clark came down to otago university for some of that otago university
No otago
Enroll me, okay
Okay, my dad my dad was doing his phd at the university. I was I think I was home school at the time
So I was just they just took me to university with them and it was cool. Um
I it was fun. But yeah, the prime minister was coming down my parents, um
You know weren't politically aligned with her. They were part of a peaceful protest
Against something. I don't know. I was too young to like really know what it was about. I was like 10
um liberal or something
I don't know. Um
My my parents are like
Right leaning
For new zealand standards, which is like dad centrist for by american standards. I don't know like a bernie sanders type
Yeah, yeah, maybe
Yeah, um, but but but anyways, um one of my parents friends, um
Glenn had a printout of the prime minister with like horns like
Talking and like nerd speaker some shit and I I had one of these and I she walked past
I held it up to her and I was like screaming
And she just waved and smiled at me and walked by
And then later that day, um
Like she was on camera talking to press my mom was in the background holing up a speeding sign because um
uh prime minister helen clark had recently like been caught speeding like
Driving way over the fucking limit and she was like, oh, I'm gonna go see a rugby game or some shit. Um, and my parents
I guess they just thought that was really funny. So they made like a fake speeding sign
And it's made out of like paper like not like your regular printer paper, but that really like flimsy packing paper
Um, they just yeah, okay
Cabinet minister pete hogson like grabbed my mom and like pulled the sign out of her hand and threw it to the ground and like
yelled at her and it was caught on camera
And then how fucking funny if i'm if america was like a tiny little island and like sometimes you would go to like
You would go to one of these things and like, I don't know fucking, uh, uh, uh, who is the who is the like mike
Pence just like tackles you say
Hey, yeah, what are you doing here? Get out of here
No, the police got involved
My mom was on the fucking channel free news to talk about it
I think that was um
Like a year ago when I mentioned that my parents would be on the news
I think this was one of the incidents that was about where bite
They sent an interviewer to a house to pre-record the interview
But then they played the videos of my mom's pre-recorded interview and pretended it was a live thing
Um, yo, yeah, yeah
Yeah
Yeah, I think that was related to that but
I just remember that that happened
um, I I generally don't remember much about
The political ramifications ramifications of anything back then that my parents were involved in sure, but um
Funny stuff
Uh, guys, I need to go. There's a prior engagement. I I forgot about
But uh, I thought it was a good episode
Hell yeah, the snake where it was nice to meet you. It was very nice to speak to you
And uh, yes, goodbye everybody. Goodbye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. See you and bye
She said that she had a thing to do in the morning and she was going to be back
For the evening and that's why we moved the time later
I wonder if it ended up changing so that she had to do it later and maybe we should have done two things to do
Maybe there were two. Maybe there were just two things too. Yeah
Hard hard to imagine
But I guess yeah, two things in one day two things in one day
Can you that's that's too much? I don't know. I'll be some people have all the luck
I'm up here trying to scrape up one dang thing to do in a week
geez louise
uh
Things to do as I go you got it. You got to make your own fun
I uh, all right. All right, so we have been going for two two. We're a 240
Uh, I feel like there's 240p. What shut up
um
Is there anything else? I like any other urgent matters to discuss before we move on to uh
To uh, all right that that talk about being british went on longer than I thought it would I thought I had like one thing
And it was just a bit a thing of I stopped playing up being british online. It's really annoying
You're making us look even worse. We can bring any topic of every last little bit of gold that's there. It's we're good at that
Had a hundred and ninety something episode two hundred and ninety something episode wherever the fuck we're at. I don't even know
We've been at it a while the
Nations nations will fall and uh history will turn the winds will grind
The sand the desert sands will grind the the the mountains down
To to flat planes and and and and the and british people will still be playing up how british they are on the internet
Uh for cloud besides anything else. I'm half irish, so
Hey, i'm a quarter. Hey, i'm a i'm a quarter irish. Nice to meet you brother
Fellow mick
Well, you can I guess you can say it
My dad used to I don't know if my dad would slap me. Maybe maybe not
All right tv show called
The the mick uh, it was on uh, I think it was on fx or something. Hmm
Was it about is it not is it not as bad of a word as I thought it was?
I i'm gonna be honest. I don't actually fully understand how bad it is. I just feel
I kind of thought I kind of thought it was a pretty nasty, but I don't know. I mean I imagine it's been defined
I don't think it's a reclaimed word or anything. I mean i i'm i'm just i'm just fucking plastic you can
You can call I mean you can call nalleners kiwi, and that's fine, right
Right
Uh, you love it. You love it. Yeah, I do. You're stroking yeah
Yeah, good, okay.
I've got a quarter, I've got a quarter of Scott in me,
but I don't just flippantly use jock.
So I think I've put the arbitrary cut off
at being half something.
Jock, is that a Scottish thing?
Yeah, that's a derogatory term for a Scott as a jock.
Oh, I know that.
What?
I've never, no.
Yeah.
It's not just like the football chat and the music.
You literally called yourself a jock earlier,
but you were talking about in like the sense of-
I was talking about a different kind of jock.
Yeah.
Not the Scottish jock.
Interesting.
The language is fun.
Yeah, this is why music should only,
you should never have lyrics
because words are fucking terrible.
Second full circle.
That's a Venn diagram, baby, voicemails.
Beautiful.
You said you've got a quarter of Scott in you.
And I thought you-
No, no, no, it's probably not even that.
And I thought you said you've got a quarter of Scott in you.
I was like, wow, we progressed from that one beer from before.
Actually, I had that and a wine,
which you all not meant to mix,
but it was already there.
Opshaw.
Who says, doctors, what do they know?
Genuinely, one of the biggest pieces of advice
my dad gave me was don't mix grape and grain.
That's the one bit of advice I remember.
Grape and grain?
Grape?
You know, what?
Grape and grain.
It's basically don't mix wine with other kinds of alcohol.
That's so silly.
That's so funny.
I mean, that's how you get the-
Mixing alcohol is how you get the worst.
They both start with the G.R.A.
They're made for each other.
Grape and grain, I've never-
Yeah, beer before liquor is the-
Beer before liquor never been sicker
is the one that I know.
And what's beer-
Liquor before beer, you're in the clear.
You're in the clear, that's right.
That's how it goes.
There's a lot of advice about how you should drink.
I suppose the best advice is-
Probably don't.
Have fun.
Just have fun with it.
Yeah, definitely.
Have fun and be yourself.
Yeah.
Anyway.
So we've learned even more now.
I think we should start voicemails
if you guys are up for it.
Hell yeah.
I mean, I never am, but I do them anyway.
Okay, well, here we go.
I'm gonna post them in the general.
Let me find, okay.
Did I, oh, shit.
Did I save these in the wrong order?
Did I save these?
We're gonna get through all of them anyway,
so it doesn't matter what the order is.
I, well, I need to know, yeah, okay.
All right, this, okay, I found it, all right.
First one, the first one is called when,
and here it is.
It's called when question mark.
So if you guys are ready,
in three, two, one, play.
All right, week three, me asking,
the who, what, when, where, why, of Radgon?
When will Radgon be?
You asked this already.
Do you guys think this will be a soon future endeavor?
No.
Or later, and when do you want it to be?
And when do you realistically think it'll be?
I don't know, there's only so many ways I can phrase when.
It won't be for a while.
Snake, do you know what Radgon is?
Yeah, I've watched the PCP lectures.
Actually, I forgot to say that, yeah,
that was actually a big part of what I did listen to
that got me into the PCP.
I forgot you mentioned a...
You mentioned the lectures.
I have watched most all of them, so, yeah.
Do you have a favorite one, Snake?
Yeah.
My favorite one, god.
Give me a fucking minute on that.
I think it is actually, I think it is
either the Son of Chew or the Bloody Son of Chew
or the Tales Gets Told lecture,
because they were just topics that I'm more
intimately familiar with.
And it's like, it's always being broken down.
Yeah.
The JDR and the Animorphs one are probably my favorites.
I really enjoy, I do really enjoy Munchie's ones.
I only recently learned that he's a lot calmer.
And that was actually very pleasant to learn.
In real life, he's much more,
he's still very loud.
He has a very loud voice, but he's much more,
he's much more low-key in real life.
If I had to pick, yeah, among the ones that are not mine,
I would probably say Animorph,
maybe Animorphs and Kingdom Hearts
are probably my two favorites.
Aside from mine.
I enjoy Nates.
Kingdom Hearts is pretty good.
I like the kind of raw enthusiasm he kind of brings to him.
Yeah, yeah, he does.
Because I love Jeff, he's my favorite.
I love Jeff.
We need to have him at Redcon 4.0.
Where's Jeff's lecture?
Yeah, if we ever did anything else like that in the future,
I mean, it wouldn't be...
Jeff would be there.
We haven't even thought about it,
and like, we're still thinking about getting all the final stuff
from Last Redcon out and produce and release, so...
You're gonna clear that.
Not even start thinking about the next one.
So it wouldn't...
It couldn't be that soon, even if we wanted it to.
I don't know.
Okay, the next one is called
In This Voice Mail I Nate So Hard.
There it is.
3, 2, 1, go.
No Nate November.
More like, Nate never makes anything.
Wait, what's this?
New Gamer Zone episode.
Featuring Giggit.
Hold up, I think I just lost this challenge.
Gross.
Fallen Soldier.
Amazing.
He will never be allowed into the Nate fucker ranks.
He's not worthy.
What a shame.
He's Nazi in heaven.
Next Voice Mail is an image.
Let's post it.
The fuck is this?
What is this?
I'm not familiar with this format.
Well, this is me mining cryptocurrency
at Redcon 3, I think.
Probably.
Who is you getting assimilated into the blockchain?
This is me mining for Slimecoin.
I'm getting slimy in here.
I am having a good time.
I like this.
This one's going in the Favorites file.
Okay, next one is called I'm So Fucked Up.
So Fucked Up.
Wait, it's loading.
Come on.
Okay, there it goes.
3, 2, 1, go.
Why, when you really got a P,
it's like, ooh, that sucks.
But then you P and it's like, ah, so rude.
Tell me about it.
When you got a shit, when you really got a shit,
it's like orders of magnitude worse than really having a P.
It's like torture.
It sucks so bad.
And then sometimes when you do shit,
it just feels like you still got a shit
and you just wait until your bowels calm the fuck down.
What the hell?
What the fuck?
So fucked up.
That's called the gape.
You're experiencing the gape, my friend.
You have to wait for your body to un-gape.
I feel like if you don't shit for long enough,
your asshole will just close,
but we're just constantly damaging it just enough
to maintain equilibrium.
I learned this.
If you don't shit,
like if you hold it in,
you can prevent yourself from shitting for a while,
but if you don't shit,
it feels bad.
Your body, like,
moisture absorbs out of the poop
through your large intestine.
And the longer it spends in your large intestine,
the drier it becomes.
And so when you do eventually shit it,
it will be harder and drier
because you absorb the moisture out of it.
Because it spent more time in there.
I don't know.
What should you do with this information?
I'm not a doctor.
It's as small as poop fast.
Or take the dry shit challenge.
I would say yes.
You should probably shit...
Don't hold it in.
Guys, listen.
Viewers, please.
Don't hold...
Don't hold it in.
Listen, everybody.
Please take part in dry shit December.
It's the heaviest product going.
Dry it!
Dump this in there!
No!
We did it.
Let us know how it goes.
Hold it in for a whole month and see how dry it is.
Send it in.
Don't...
It's not to hear somewhere.
Send it to somewhere and they'll...
Obviously.
They'll get back to you.
Better than doing an advent calendar, I guess.
Well, if you hold it out long enough,
it can be part of next year's advent calendar.
The next voicemail is called
a fried vocalist.
There it is.
It's loading.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
I have bipolar.
I have to sort over there.
Sounds like someone has already started
dry something December.
D-D-D-D.
They've already started D-3.
Actually, they're already struggling
on the first day of December, it says.
When you successfully complete
Dry Dump December,
you get crowned King D-D-D.
That's the lore.
That's the Kirby lore every YouTuber tells me about.
Because Kirby's all about eating,
his antagonist, King D-D-D,
he's all about shitting.
It's the end of the day.
Boss, end of the expert.
Can you start Keto diet help on Dry Dump December?
Keto can sometimes give you diarrhea.
Sometimes.
Oh, okay, never mind.
It's spotty.
Sometimes when you start Keto,
you can get a little bit diarrhea-y,
but not always, and it's just temporary.
I don't know.
All I know is it dries you out,
but I don't know.
Well, I'm very serious about staying hydrated.
Okay.
I think it might dry some people out, but not me.
I'm built different.
Next one is called...
What is this?
It's called Oh No, I Failed NNN.
Well, you got DDD to look forward to.
Three, two, one, go.
You know, in listening to the latest
Gamer Zone episode,
and Nate's streams and shit,
I realized the reason Nate's not on the current PCP
is that he is a relic.
He's a fixture of the past.
He still does all the edgy jokes,
all the...
all the racy stuff,
all the sexist stuff,
and it's always funny,
but it doesn't fit with the current PCP anymore.
I don't know.
He just saw himself growing obsolete,
took himself back into the back of the fucking barn.
The shed and popped a cap in his own ass.
But, okay.
I love that you specified that it's still funny.
Oh, man.
If you think Nate is...
So why are you here not watching the Gamer Zone?
I don't understand.
Okay.
If you think his humor is dated and makes him a relic,
that's okay, but if you then say,
and it's funny,
that means you're a relic too, my dude.
You're right there with him.
It's either not a relic or you are also a relic.
I need a joke about the opium wars
and called Ben St. Amick earlier this episode.
You're getting canceled.
We're canceling Snake on this one.
Well, catch me on the Gamer Zone next month.
No, he would.
Nate would poach you like that.
He did it to Cyber Shell.
He'll do it to you.
I don't know.
I've never spoken to the guy.
A bunch of my patrons want you to go on the Gamer Zone,
and I'm just like, I don't know, man.
It seems a little too high tier for me.
I saw it enough.
Well, that's a bit too high concept.
What if Nate got Saber Spark and not you?
I mean, I would understand.
Why would you want someone with no following
when you have someone who has a huge following?
It's the stratification of podcasts.
You've got the Gamer Zone.
I'm the one who writes all Saber Spanger videos now,
but that's okay.
He can get all the credit.
Has he been gaining subscribers?
I feel like he was at 150.
Saber's at 1.5 mil.
No, no, no, Nate.
But is he still gaining?
Oh, Nate?
I have no idea what Nate's at.
He was at 150.
Nate has been up.
But now it's 114.
I think at the time, we even mentioned,
because before Nate hit 100K,
we had noticed the phenomenon on YouTube.
Once you hit 100K, you get accelerated in the algorithm,
and people hit 200K really quick.
And then it didn't happen to Nate.
It didn't happen.
It's like he's an anomaly.
I don't understand.
I'm going to press it at 100.
I think it's actually, maybe I'm thinking,
if you're hitting 100 fast, it's momentum.
I don't think you get a boost off.
I could be wrong.
There was, I mean,
there was something that was actually done.
That was like the common thing at the time.
At least the confusion.
I haven't a lot.
I didn't get the boost,
but I also haven't posted since I hit 100K.
Well, I guess that would help.
Yeah, it would help.
I'm still surpassing him though.
I'm still growing like 1,000 a month fish.
Damn.
I'm growing 1,000 a month,
and I don't think I'm going to get the boost
when I hit 100,000 if it does exist.
You're at like 90, right?
Oh, wow.
I thought you were bigger than me.
No, but I've been at this for a thing,
and I've just had very slow,
but steady growth throughout.
So for the last few years,
the ramp-ups have been very steady.
And honestly, I'm okay with the slower growth,
because I don't really care to get too big too fast.
I don't really care bigness,
as long as I just have a good base to work from.
That's the most important term.
I'm always thinking about,
I should really be doing something with my channel.
I'm not doing anything with it at the moment.
I should do something.
I mean, I'm doing my game right now.
It's really difficult to do weekly videos
on top of bigger creative projects.
Yeah, I wouldn't want to do that.
It sucks.
I don't know what I would...
I know I should be doing something with my channel
and trying to grow my channel,
but I don't know what I would want to do with it.
So I have no ideas.
I'm stupid.
That's the curse you expect.
I'm not going to tell you to do something
you don't want to do,
but maybe devlogs or just breakdowns
on what you're doing,
tie it into other projects,
but then you're just creating more work
on projects we're already doing.
It's always a balancing act of,
am I having fun with this?
Am I enjoying it?
Is this awful or painful?
I started doing devlogs for Patreon
just because I needed more bonus content
to throw on my Patreon,
and even that takes a lot of time away
from just actually doing work.
Yeah, that is the tricky part,
because I have that with my Patreon videos,
where it's like, I do enjoy doing them
and it gives people a chance to interact,
but it's like, it takes three or four days,
and it's like, this is three or four days
off the thing that your technically came from.
I'm so upset that Clubhouse didn't take off
and become a thing.
I was really hoping that the Zeitgeist
would shift to audio,
because just shitting out audio stuff
as we're doing right now
is the easiest thing on God's Earth,
and if that just became the de facto standard,
God, I could destroy the world.
Video is just such a fucking grind,
and it sucks, and I hate it.
What's Clubhouse?
Yeah, I don't like enough failure.
Clubhouse was an app,
but you know how Twitter has spaces
where people can just jump into live audio calls?
Yeah.
Wait, what?
They stole that from an app called Clubhouse,
which is just the same thing.
I saw one or two spaces.
Didn't they kill spaces, or are they still around?
No, they killed fleets.
They're pushing spaces hard now.
They killed fleets.
Oh, thank God fleets are gone.
That was stupid.
Yeah, that died.
I never even saw a single fleet.
I still don't know what fleets were.
They were Instagram stories on Twitter.
Oh, yeah, I don't use it on Google.
Because nobody can have an original idea anymore.
Voicemails.
Oh, yeah, let's look at those voicemails.
Finally.
Shit.
Which episode?
Okay, the next one is called...
Full circle.
Oh, the next one is called Who Made the New Intro?
And the answer to that is I think Eleazar did, right?
That blessed that guy, that son of a bitch.
I think...
It was either that or there was a voicemailer.
No, it was a voicemailer.
Yeah, a voicemailer made it.
And I don't know who it was.
I don't know who made the new intro.
If you made the new intro, shout out to the comments.
I have a musical...
A PCP musical thing I've been doing for like a year,
but it's not done because it's been too busy.
We do?
Did you just let that rip?
You'll see it.
When I finish my current project,
I'm going to actually take time to finish it.
Wow.
Based.
Okay, sounds good.
Let's do the next voicemail.
It is called...
Horoscope.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben, you come off as earnest and considerate,
emotionally honest and wise enough to laugh at one's own.
Wise.
Your soft-spokenness and fiery virtuosity
paint you as compassionate and well-compassed.
I agree.
You're both guided by strong moral principles
and emotional intelligence.
You attract people who act in kind.
Do you agree with your horoscope?
No.
Was that me and Giz?
That was correct.
Well, Giz's not here.
Mine, what did they say?
I was like, compassionate.
All lies.
Something about like,
bleeding with emotional intelligence
and attracting people who are the same thing.
You're anti-sigma male.
They're saying you're like a sheep of Inu coin?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, Elon Musk's a tweet about me
and I'm going to go to the moon.
Wait, wait.
Ernest, considerate,
emotionally honest,
wise enough to laugh at myself.
Ernest, considerate, emotionally honest,
I would, okay.
Ernest, considerate, emotionally honest.
Unironically, I agree with all those things
and I think they're all true of me.
I don't care how that sounds.
You know, emotionally honest in the sense that
I don't know if you're wise enough to laugh at yourself.
I feel like you just didn't have a choice.
You had to save face.
You're honest in that you'll tell someone
that they're fucking stupid
without hesitation because you believe it.
Exactly, exactly.
That is definitely true.
I don't mean to sound conceited.
I'm just giving you my Ernest opinion.
I'm just,
my honest,
my emotionally honest response to this
is to say that, yeah, I think it's all true.
I guess we've learned today that horoscopes are real.
Yeah, that's right.
Shit.
A lesson I learned over and over again,
but I always fail to internalize.
People say that
crypto is horoscopes for men
and so are horoscopes.
Crypto is essential oils for men.
And NFTs are
multi-level marketing schemes for men.
And
Sigma Male Grants sets over
horoscopes.
Tesla stock is
horoscopes for men
and
the
blockchain is
makeup?
I don't know.
How do the Grants sets fit in though?
That's gotta be one of the things.
I would have said that was horoscopes
because it's all about your personality, man.
You're not an asshole.
You're just really smart
and people don't understand you.
You're too smart to care about people's feelings.
You're special.
You're not an asshole.
You're just so intelligent and no one understands you.
That's correct. Thank you.
You're right. What's your point?
Sigma.
What's your point in saying these things about me?
Okay.
Next voicemail.
The next voicemail
is another image.
So let's see it.
Tech had to go do some shit,
but maybe he'll be back.
Oh, Bencore.
Oh boy.
Yeah.
These are all things that you've talked about in one way or another.
Wait, what is...
I wouldn't go so far as to say that
Golden Girls is Bencore.
Gold Ghost is great.
What are you fucking...
I just mean you're old, Ben. That's all it means.
Yeah.
It's just a coincidence that the picture is from Golden Girls.
Correct.
They were just pictures of an old person at doctor with health problems.
So this is great.
Maybe it's not Golden Girls.
Maybe it's more specifically Be Offer.
I don't know.
No, I was talking last episode about...
Or maybe two episodes ago about the Golden Girls.
But I like that
their Simpsons is also
the old people.
So there's a message here.
I don't know if these are Bencore.
So much as these are just things that I like.
I mean, Homestuck is pretty Bencore.
I would maybe say J.D.
I'm trying to work out...
Some of these are Bencore.
Do you know what the one in the middle right is?
Yeah, Oolulia.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Elemental Masters, yeah.
I've not read Elemental Masters,
but I know it's very granular.
It's magic system.
I was...
I was talking...
I wanted to get Nick to let me do
the audiobook version and let us upload
an audiobook to Audible.
And he was down.
He said he would let me do it.
But then when it came time for him to
just fill out the form,
giving them permission to sell his book,
just put in his
payment information
to be a person who uses Audible.
He just wouldn't do it.
He was just like...
I don't know if he was just lazy,
or if he was like, phobic of
anything that Google owns.
That might have been it, actually,
because he said he would not
look at Facebook, because it was like...
No, wait, Facebook is not owned by Google.
He's phobic
of Google stuff, though, so...
Alright.
Amazon owns Audible.
He doesn't like alphabet
or operation.
Maybe it was...
I don't know. Maybe he was just lazy.
The point is we could have made some money,
and we didn't do it.
And it's his fault.
What?
If we
cracked Jeff Bezos' head
like an egg yolk would come out.
Yeah.
I think it's only one way to find out.
I think like a chick would come out.
We'll take an axe to it.
We'll find him.
Long story short, as you were denied
the rank of Elemental Master.
I was.
I was so...
I was so hyped for it. I honestly was really hyped for it.
And then he...
He betrayed me.
He hurt me.
I was owed. I was owed this.
And he robbed it from me.
And now I'm out for revenge.
After I destroy Trixie...
Oh, Lillia's next.
Oh.
Okay.
The next voicemail is this image.
This Lynchian Alignment chart.
An academic definition of Lynchian
might be that the term refers to a particular
kind of irony with a very macabre and very mundane
combined in such a way as to reveal
the former's perpetual containment
within the latter.
Hmm.
Okay.
Only film TV.
Okay, form can be any art.
Form, rebel, anything. Okay, that's simple enough.
Content purist.
The mundane refers to regular plain Americana
and the macabre refers
to strange psychosexual violence.
Content centrist. The mundane refers
to any sense of normalcy and the macabre
anything creepy.
Content, rebel. Okay, it doesn't have to be
that normal or that creepy.
So play...
Pizza...
Pizza bait, papa?
I don't even know what that is.
So it's an idea that there is a certain
sinister undertone even in
very mundane
concepts.
What is pizza bait, papa?
Or pizza. I'm just trying to work out how...
Is it just a pizza with a chicken on it?
I'm just trying to work out how...
I mean, I guess that isn't normal
or creepy.
I guess it kind of fits the content rebel definition.
I would say a pizza is relatively normal.
There's something abnormal about the pizza.
I would say
by these definitions where form rebel means
the medium can be anything
and content rebel means it doesn't really
even need to be normal or creepy.
Yeah, literally anything is lynchian
by that definition.
So sure, maybe it's just a pizza.
Maybe.
Yeah, I'm just thinking by this term
the universe itself is macabre
and there's an irony
within the mundanity by which we experience
and get used to it.
I mean,
DFW's definition up here
is referring to...
He's referring to something that is
evoked in media
where you bring these two ideas together
to suggest something
but you're suggesting something
about the real world.
So it seems a bit
off base to point to something
that really exists.
Which yes, of course the macabre
is contained within the mundane.
That's why the lynchian
paradigm is compelling
because that's how real life is.
So just point to something in real life
and be like, oh, it's lynchian.
It's like, well, no.
Lynchian things just refer
to the same phenomenon.
They just evoke the phenomenon that exists
in reality, in media.
So you've gone off base.
You've lost your mind.
Where does dry dump December
fit on the lynchian
line?
When someone's taking a dump,
you know how you see stars
sometimes if you push really hard?
Those stars will start dancing
and there'll be some nice
jazz music playing.
I would say, okay.
Do you know the context behind this picture
of David Lynch and the Woody Woodpecker dolls?
Yeah, he rescued them.
Yes, dude.
Oh, no.
In the lynchian line, this black and white photo,
he's sitting on a sofa with like
five Woody Woodpecker dolls.
There's a video. I'm linking the video.
This is one of my favorite videos ever.
Okay.
And Snake knows it.
Is it as good as
David Lynch cooks quinoa?
Ben, it's better.
No way.
See, here's the thing.
I think there's nothing macabre about it.
It's potentially macabre,
but the macabre has been denied.
Well, here's the thing, Snake,
is that there's a follow-up to this video
where he talks about
this video in an interview he did once,
where he
ends talking
about these Woody Woodpecker dolls
with, they're not in my life anymore.
Oh, okay.
I forgot about, yeah,
I said it just very vaguely in an interview.
They're not in my life anymore.
With no elucidation.
Like, what did they do to him?
Oh, I love, I love
any chance
I get to link this fucking
David Lynch Woody Woodpecker video.
Yeah, the pin drop,
the shoe, the other shoe.
Something, something macabre,
something, something.
Dried up, dried up December.
Okay, my question is,
if he is
participating in an event like dried up December,
no November, is that a form of art,
that participation?
Or does that count as anything?
I am of the games or art crowd,
I think art is a very
broad thing where if it's meant to
star an emotion in you,
then it can qualify.
Something being bad doesn't mean it's not art,
it means it's bad art.
I agree. Yeah, and
that's your argument that
dried up December is art.
It's not just art, it's a movement.
A bowel movement, if you will.
I'm gonna disagree, because
I think that the creation
of dried up December
obviously was inspired
and is a work of art.
Dried up December as a concept is a work of art.
Merely participating in dried up December,
merely
executing upon
the ideas contained within,
I don't think I would call that art.
I would call that
performance art.
I think that's contributing to
the, I mean, I guess that's the
separation between art and artist, right?
You're not an artist
when you play a video game.
You're an artist when you make a video game.
I don't know, I've never seen my videos.
When you design the game.
You participate
in the game that you play,
but you don't
make art by playing a video game.
You participate in art that someone else made.
I don't know.
I think dried up December
is a distinct and new
from these
terms.
If you make
a let's play, that could be
considered art.
If you're doing dried up December, you have to
catalog the process.
If you publicly perform it and you
catalog it, then of course.
I do just want to actually say
for sake of
let's plays as art.
If you've ever seen Sonic 2 Special Edition,
that is art.
That's some old, something awful.
Sonic 2 Special Edition.
Is this text LP shit?
It's not text LP.
It's an absolutely hilarious
let's play that kind of builds on
the old jokes about just how much cut content
there was in Sonic 2.
It just kind of builds on that
into an absurdist joke where the game just
gradually breaks down
and the edits get more and more absurdist.
At one point, a level
just is played like memento
essentially.
Is it this?
I believe so.
I watched it on the LP archive
years and years ago.
I'll give this a watch. This looks right.
Yeah.
I'm trying to remember the name
of the guy who made it. I still follow him on Twitter.
He's still around. He just doesn't do LP stuff anymore.
Doc Future?
Doc Future. Yes. This is the guy.
Yeah.
Interesting. Alright. I'll give this a watch.
This sounds cool.
Yeah. It's a fun old LP
and kind of something awful.
I think that's actually where I got a lot of my
old weird internet
sensibilities that have steadily dropped away.
Is this where I count?
Yup. There'd be Doc Future.
Interesting.
Fascinating.
I really like really
something awful LP's where people would get
really
creative with it.
Put them on blue.
Oh yeah.
I have enjoyed your video series.
Thank you.
This isn't...
Is this the guy?
Oh wait. This is the guy behind Petscop?
No. No. The guy
who uploaded the video did a
or like he was basically
describing the series.
Because this is a reupload. He said,
think a more comedic version of Petscop.
I misspoke.
I thought I recognized the name
and I thought maybe...
I made Petscop his name as
Tony.
I think it's just Twitter app.
This is just for me
and maybe tech, but I've just noticed
the uploader's name is Mike Dawson
and now I'm wondering if this is a
Retsuit Pre-reference
the uploader of Sonic 2.
Is that the name of...
Mike Dawson is the guy from
Darkseed.
While I'm just going off
of weird trivia, the guy who wrote
Sonic 2, Benson also
wrote the Metal Gear Solid 1
novelization, which is awful.
That's insane.
That's the one that canonizes
Snake as a dog musher.
Yeah.
What?
Is it actually bad?
No. I actually can't say with 100%
certainty whether that's the case.
I think Metal Gear Solid 1 itself
does allude to the fact that Snake
was taking part in the idea of a rod.
Yeah.
A dog musher. I actually don't know
if that's the correct term. Basically
he retired
from the military
or whatever and he went to Alaska
to
mush dogs.
Slay dogs.
Thank you.
When you crack the whip and you go
mush, mush.
Oh yeah, right.
The briefing mission.
The fucking dogs.
I forgot Roy.
You bastard.
I didn't watch that when I first
played the game. I watched it later
and I was like, holy shit. Roy sucks.
I get that it's
desperate, but still.
That's a pretty crazy first impression.
Metal Gear Solid is great.
Metal Gear Solid series.
A lot of fun.
A lot of fun, guy friends to kill dogs.
I've only played
the first one and I didn't even beat it
because I'm a fucking noob.
Well, you at least
watched the Mathematosis reviews, right?
Of course.
I'll watch anything he puts out.
I'll play his fucking game too
whenever it's done.
Just to say I did.
I'll pay $10 for it
on Steam, but no more.
Next voicemail
is called
Voice Grail
3, 2, 1
Go.
Hello, it is me.
The golden bitch, Trixie.
Also known as Dark Gazers.
And since we're retroactively
voice grailing people,
I would like to nominate
Tommy J. for voice grail.
Thank you.
I really thought he was
going to nominate himself.
I didn't go where I was expecting.
I think, you know what?
You know what?
If the illustrious Doid Gazers
makes Trixie the golden bitch.
If he makes Trixie the golden bitch.
I was going to say we'll do it
if he wants us to, but no, you're right.
No, he's going to sing for us.
Sing for us.
Dance slave.
Snake is BRB.
We can
listen to the next one.
Well, he's gone. It is called
Your Gay.
LeMau.
As in the letters, U-R-G-A-Y.
Here we go.
3, 2, 1, Go.
You guys are
shitting on crypto and bitcoin all the time.
And it's
getting infuriating.
I mean, just think about this.
If you would put $500
bitcoin one month ago,
today you'd have $300.
Think about that.
True.
He's going to love this one.
On a long enough timeline,
on a long enough timeline,
the value of every investment
is zero.
Think about it.
Really think about it.
Really mull it over.
Buy gold.
Buy gold. It's the only truly safe asset.
No, you want to buy silver.
It's going to go up.
Don't worry.
Actually, you want to buy copper?
Actually, because it's
like silver, but it's heavier,
so it's harder for them to steal
your value.
And it'll always be valuable.
Yeah.
Steal other people's copper.
How about that?
Steal would be a pretty good asset.
Maybe we can get our hands on some of that.
It's pretty valuable in Dwarf Fortress.
It's like the most valuable metal.
Aside from Adamantium, obviously.
Obviously.
All right.
Next voicemail
is called
I'll be a little embarrassed if we get to the end of these
and we end the episode.
Snake is still gone.
We have to sheepishly explain.
Episode ended while you were away.
Sorry.
Yeah, next time.
Okay, this one is called
Penny Packer.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Sup, guys.
I was just watching VTubers
and my friend told me to leave a message.
I haven't watched this
or listened to this podcast
for like two years.
I just want to say
Ben is gay.
Hippo used to be pretty cool.
He's just a little cool now.
And Nate
Well, Nate doesn't even exist.
See ya.
That was a great voicemail.
Damn. 10 out of 10.
That was...
That was appreciate the misgendering.
I can't believe I've been gaslit by Nate.
Yeah.
Well, not by Nate.
Everyone's been gaslit by Nate.
Oh.
Everyone was gaslit
when he said he was going to make
Best Anime Ever
Ghost in the Shell
And then he gaslit us all
with that video about the movie.
And then he said,
No, you're crazy.
That's the video, guys.
He said, why?
Why?
Okay.
So, that's...
Uh...
Nate fans?
I don't know. I don't trust them.
I don't trust them.
They don't trust themselves.
Yeah.
It looks like I'm missing the next voicemail
for some reason, but I will get it
really quick.
Why is it not in my...
What does it mean to be the best anime ever?
What does it mean to be that?
I mean, the deal with Nate Stick,
you know, it was sort of self-consciously
like, uh, you know.
He makes a Best Anime Ever video
about multiple different
animes. You can have multiple different
Best Anime Ever.
It's just whatever you feel.
There's no rules.
What does it mean to me?
This isn't a question for anyone else.
This is me putting my thoughts out.
I want your 5 paragraph essay
on what makes the Best Anime Ever
to you on my desk by next Thursday.
We famously discussed
the question of the best game ever
on the very first episode
of this podcast, and we came to the irrefutable
conclusion that Undertale
is, in fact, the best game ever.
Ah, yes. The most beloved 7 out of 10
ever made.
Uh-oh.
Savage.
Cruel.
The most beloved 7 out of 10 ever made
is definitely Dark Cloud
for...
I've got to admit some of my own
uh...
Not cagey-ness.
I've made that joke about Dark Souls,
but I just undercut my own opinions for an easy jab,
and I will do that at a moment's notice.
I believe that about Dark Souls, and ironically,
and we'll stand by that.
No, I actually do.
I don't actually believe in number grades.
I've never finished Dark Souls, because I just always get bored
when I get to Anor Londo,
and I'm like, I've had my fill.
I'm done.
I beat Dark Souls, but I did get bored
partway through number two.
Two is terrible.
I got to the Royal Rat Authority
and was like, I'm done with this fucking game.
I did beat the Royal Rat Authority.
And it's like, these controls
are unbearably bad,
even compared to the first time I went out.
I really tried to stick with it.
I really gave it a shot.
Um...
I don't know, I just never got the satisfaction
I felt other people were really, like,
clamoring from it.
Same.
It really makes me sad,
because the reason I powered through Dark Souls one
is I wanted to have that epiphany
and come out on the other side getting it,
and I just never did.
There's kind of...
This is a kind of okay
hack and slash with
sort of grim setting,
and it's like, I don't know, this stuff has existed
for years already.
I think part of the appeal
of something like a Dark Souls
or a Demon Souls is that,
like, while
from software it was making it,
it was very obvious that they knew
or that they didn't think it was going to be
this huge fucking phenomenon,
it just feels like a pretty
niche game that somehow
managed to come out.
There's nothing about it that stands out as
like, oh, this is a revolution in gaming,
clearly.
It's just really good.
I suppose I should really balance the elements.
I suppose I should walk back a little
just so I'm not just being
contrarian, because that's not what I'm trying to do.
I think it's just, it came out when
there was a big discussion on
AAA games that are too easy
and it
right place at the right time.
That's very true.
Definitely, definitely.
And it's like, right place at the right time, it was refreshing
for that, but I've been
like, oh, this is going to sound really arrogant,
and I apologize to anyone who takes it.
I've been playing weird jank PC games my whole life,
and it was, I don't know,
it was
interesting from the outside
in that regard.
Discussing difficulties always going to be kind of hard.
It's tricky, because
it's a tricky debate, because
everyone is at a different skill level.
There's no perfect baseline to
judge it from.
And I don't even think like, difficulty is
the interesting, well, people are
key to it nowadays, but it's like, difficulty
is being part of Dark Souls.
It's the tone and atmosphere.
If there wasn't like a hook
to push you through the difficulty, no one would
beat the game, you know?
It's like a nice oppressive
atmosphere, which I am, okay, just
tonally for myself, I'm not into like
really oppressive shit.
It's not really my jam, I guess.
You're a berserk snake.
I've tried, I want to,
I feel bad that I can't get into berserk.
Yeah, that's it.
Not even like the
first arc?
Oh, no. I'm really bad about
reading manga, like really bad.
And I kind of don't just want to watch the anime.
That is one I feel like
I've got to actually read this.
I finished two manga in my
I finished two manga in my life, and I can only remember one
of them, and it was Anna Satsushin,
which was a digestible read.
Unfortunately, none of us are ever going to finish berserk,
because Mira's dead, and it really
fucking sucks.
I don't read that much, but I did
manage to read all through the
like the first bit,
the first part of
berserk that everybody knows.
I mean, I have been saying that I'm
going to catch up on one piece for like three years
now, and I haven't done it.
The last chapter was really cool there.
You got so close at Radcon 4, and then you just fell off
the bandwagon again. Yeah, yeah.
Now I'll never fulfill the prophecy
of appearing on an episode, the podcast.
I
I did read
I read all of Death Note, I read all of
Bakuman.
Those are really good.
I read
You read Chainsaw Man?
I have not, but I
I kind of want it.
I've heard good things. I just don't
know anything about it other than that it's fucking dope.
It's a show, it's shown in action,
so if you like that,
I think it's probably one of the best
shows in action stories I've
read.
I kind of troll about
on the two best friends
subreddit a lot. It's actually a decent
place, and they love
Chainsaw Man, and they're like, okay, I gotta
read that at some point.
I read one chapter
while I was on my
break at work, and when I got home, I just
like I bingeed the entire run.
It's technically not done yet.
I was told it was done,
but it's just like only the first arc
is over, and it's just sound like hey,
this for now.
But what's out right now is
it's a complete story.
And it's
really good. It's like 90-something chapters.
Cool.
That's definitely dope.
Okay, stupid question.
Mob Psycho 100
was not a manga, right? It was just an anime.
No, it was
by the one punch man guy.
It was a webcomic? Yes.
No, wait.
And then it got mangled by
or is there only one punch man getting mangled by the guy you
did? I assume.
I know that happened to one punch man.
But I feel like
Mob Psycho
Sorry.
One punch man got really big,
but
I feel like
it was a direct to anime.
No.
I know the answer to this.
So one punch man was a webcomic first,
then it got redone as a manga
by a really good artist, then it got an anime adaptation.
By the time Mob Psycho
was started, the webcomic artist had gotten
a lot better, and they were able to just
do the manga themselves.
And then it also got an anime adaptation.
That's why the art style looks
a lot more like the webcomic style for one punch man.
I've not watched all of anime in recent years.
I fell a thing, but I am going to definitely
come back for Mob Psycho
Season 3.
I need to watch Mob Psycho.
I adore Mob Psycho.
I read a bunch of one punch man.
I
have not read or seen
Mob Psycho, but I saw
Alec Robbins, the Mr. Boot Guy.
I guess he just finished Mob Psycho,
and he said he loved it. He was gushing on Twitter.
He said it was amazing.
If he likes it, maybe I should read it.
I adore it because
it takes a similar theme
from one punch man of, you know,
this is the one person with these powers, but it puts it in a more
kind of juvenile finding oneself
perspective and not putting all
of your stock in powers you have, and
more the thing you want over the natural gifts
you've been given, and it's very heart
warming and very nice, and I really like it.
Let's see.
Yeah, that's...
I guess I've recently moved that onto
my shortlist.
You know what? I gotta admit
I'm not really sure what you're saying.
The other day,
everyone was telling me to watch OddTaxi,
and I said, no, fuck you.
But then the other day
at Friends Giving, I was at Munchie's
house, and somebody put on OddTaxi,
and I watched one episode of it, and I was like,
oh, I'm kind of intrigued.
Maybe I should watch three of those.
I watched one...
The one episode, I think it was the first episode,
and it seemed pretty good, so...
And I was immediately
like, okay, you know what? Everyone that said
this is a Ben sort of thing,
they were absolutely right. This is exactly
the kind of thing that I would like.
So...
That's not a guarantee that I'll actually watch it,
because I'm lazy about watching things, even things that I like.
But we'll see.
Yeah.
LaMau.
Next one?
That was a good episode of GamerZone, we just did.
Was that an episode of GamerZone?
We talked about games and anime.
I'm assuming that's what GamerZone is.
Oh.
Sure, sure.
We should call this podcast the GamerZone.
The Gaming Zone.
Gaming.
Next voicemail.
No!
Shut up!
You can't...
The Bone Zone is the Undertale podcast.
That's our Undertale side story.
Oh, goddammit.
GamerZone only. NSFW.
Next voicemail.
No!
Next voicemail is called...
Wait, no, that's the wrong one.
I think you posted this one.
I think this is the wrong one.
What the fuck?
Why are these all out of order?
This man does not have his voicemails together.
The show's over, we did it.
This man doesn't...
Show me a man, I will show you someone
who doesn't have his voicemails.
Here's the real one, sorry.
This one is called Clarification.
3, 2, 1, go.
I have...
Bipolar...
This is so hard.
This is the same one as last time.
Wait, we've heard this.
Yeah.
You already posted this one, Ben.
Yeah, this was the file you posted just a second ago.
Yeah.
You really rattled today.
Okay, sorry, sorry.
Okay, no, this is it.
This one is called Clarification.
3, 2, 1, go.
I just wanted to clear this up.
When I say you guys in a voicemail,
I am speaking to Ben
and presumably a guest
and or Tom if he's there.
I am in fact not referring to Gib
because I do not speak to women.
Yes!
Excellent!
You've got his priority straight.
Good man.
The American people are tired of women.
Tired of women.
Women!
Good for you.
You can never misgender
if you don't acknowledge
their existence
ever.
That's a lesson in that.
Just the facts.
Just the facts, sir, just the facts.
And by sir,
there's no one here.
All assembled.
Next one,
and this is the real...
I swear I'm going to do it right this time.
Next one is called Timmy's Big USA Adventure.
3, 2, 1, go.
Oh my lord!
I do have to say
hearing Ben talk about the creator's satisfaction
he finds in creating Phantom Worms
revenge really warms my heart.
Thanks man.
When you work really brings
all the themes and emotional beach
out in mind to fruition
it's a beautiful thing.
Now, just to by road
to Radcon straight from his doorstep
to fulfill my parasocial fantasy.
Let me see here.
By road to Radcon.
Hey sir, is this bus coming
anytime soon?
No?
Why do they keep around these boards
to leave bus times?
It's hard enough to find a stop.
Well,
let me just take a subway then.
Wait.
An isekai to meet Ben Saint
in Rhapsody.
You mean in America they close perfectly good subway lines?
Just to force people to take the car?
Damn you city planners!
Just admit it!
How far do the car companies have their hands
off your ass?
How many fingers are they sticking up?
Fuck this!
I'm going back to Europe!
At least stock and give can be done by public transport.
I don't want to encourage shawking.
I do like the point that yes,
our public transport infrastructure
is just bangin'.
Like that pride I can take in that.
The whole country is shit
but we can get anywhere in it.
If your country wasn't such a
piddly little
such a miserable tiny little island
then
you say it's piddly and little
I say it's focused.
We would have high speed rail
all over our country if we were tiny.
That's all I'm saying.
There's nowhere to even go.
Maybe you shouldn't have settled
on such a big lion mess.
It was our destiny
and we were manifesting it.
Thank you and good night.
The only thing tiny about America
is our consideration for the working class
and we're damn proud of it.
Come on, don't pretend English.
I thought you were going to mention
my penis.
I figured we all knew that by now.
It seemed redundant.
So there's two things. Two things tiny
about America.
Ben, you're a traitor to America.
You don't count anymore.
Someone in America has to have the little dick.
It's just a law of nature.
Somebody. It's me.
I'm somebody.
I'm the burden for everybody else.
Somebody
in the earth has to do
the Christ-like sacrifice
of having the smallest dick in the world
so that everyone else can feel
better about themselves in comparison.
It's me. You're welcome.
I provide a public service.
This reminds me,
it was an interesting bit.
You guys watched Noah Caldwell-Gervais?
You know him? I love
Noah Caldwell-Gervais.
Did you see his new Forza video?
Yeah, I have watched that.
It's great. I'm not even a car guy.
No, me either.
And I know he's a car guy,
but he mentions
the bit about how
he has seen a lot of anti-car
sentiment grow.
He's a car guy, and I'm an anti-car guy.
And he said
it's been interesting watching anti-car
sentiment grow up around him in recent years.
And he kind of agrees with a lot of it.
But he's still a car guy.
He just loves cars.
And I don't know.
I guess I thought that was interesting.
I just thought that was interesting.
Maybe we'll get another watch.
I don't think it's quite cognitive dissonance
to just kind of understand the
ramifications of Caldwell.
But also just know
it's undeniably fun
to go fast in a car
and to enjoy the
engineering thing.
I hate that.
In that bit, he describes
the American dream
and how the car is
intertwined with the American dream
and the open road and the freedom to go anywhere.
In a country
that's as big and spread out as America,
car ownership is
the freedom to go
whenever you want.
That's fine. That's cool.
I do understand the appeal of that.
So like it's
I just think no is a cool guy.
I just thought that was interesting.
I would like to present
your statement that buses suck.
Maybe in America they do.
But America has shit public transport.
So not surprising.
Buses in New Zealand are fucking great.
They're clean. They're shiny.
They're modern and they're comfortable.
I would say this.
I won't say all buses are clean,
but I would say
the public infrastructure
we have and you find
the funniest, craziest people on the bus.
So got that going.
I don't like that.
Boston is basically
good.
Boston is one of the places
in America that does have
a workable public transit system.
So feeling blessed.
Feeling blessed.
Speaking of crazy people on the bus,
I went to high school and I took the bus
during the last couple of years of high school.
There was just this guy probably in his 30s
who was always on the bus.
He looked like he was permanently cracked out on meth.
He had the face of a rat.
His eyes were perfectly circular bulging out of his face.
Or was he messed out on crack?
He was one of those things.
Nobody knows.
He was one or both.
His eyes were red
and he had like a hook nose.
He looked like an NPC
in some medieval setting
who was like...
He hunched over with a hunch bank.
Yeah, please, sir, give me a fucking coin.
Was this an old man?
No, he was probably
like early 30s.
He just had that face.
He had that build.
He looked like a goblin of a man.
And he was on the bus
every single time in the same spot.
Wow.
But a couple of the kids
would be friendly with him
because they would just chat with him.
I say kids because I was
mid to late teens
and the kids were probably 11 or 12
but they were just friendly with him for whatever reason.
I was always concerned.
I'm like, no, maybe he's just a nice guy.
Why wouldn't you want to befriend the local goblin?
In New Zealand,
do you get
the school kids on the back of a bus
who are blasting tinny music out of their phones?
No.
Okay, that's a
a phenomena for England.
People have their headphones
in the middle school.
If you played music,
the bus driver would turn around and be like, oh, I stop it.
Oh, no, it wouldn't happen.
We have the double deck as it'd be upstairs
and just blasting
some kind of music.
It does not that it happens that often
but when it does happen that someone's
blasting music out of their phone,
it's not school kids that usually do it
or buses that I see.
It's usually just like some guy
or just some person.
Over here, it's always like a gaggle of secondary kids
which is
I mean, I guess they got to ride the bus home.
Gotta do something to entertain yourself.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm always surprised.
I'm always surprised to see a gang of school kids
get on the bus
because I rode the bus to school
but we had school buses.
They were like, oh yeah, in a city,
I guess you could just
sometimes just take the regular bus.
Why would they have new buses?
School buses aren't really a thing
in London unless...
They're not a thing either in New Zealand.
It's just for regular buses but we have them everywhere
running all the time,
every 30 to 15 minutes for the bus
at every stop all day around pretty much.
There will be a bus for
special needs kids
but besides that,
yeah, that makes sense.
Okay,
well, love
public transport, obviously.
It's good, that's great.
This is the last voicemail
is the next one, I think.
It's called, I know.
Not that many this week
in the grand scheme of things.
This one is called, Why Nate Still Loves Ben?
Three, two, one, go.
Well, yeah, you're right.
But I wasn't even talking about Ben.
Oh, I mean Ben, you know.
Ben would not
hold back his hand
when a woman's talking smack
and that's why I love him.
That's why he's still my brother.
Was this on the...
Any idea what this is from?
It sounds like it's from a stream.
I can hear like Pokemon music in the background
or something.
Ben would not hold back his hand
if it was...
That's why I love my brother.
That's kind of sweet, actually.
That's sweet in his relic-y way.
Into the dirt is what keeps us
related.
In his relic-y way, I appreciate it.
Honestly, that does warm my heart
a little bit.
What a sweetheart.
I mean, if it was serious...
If we're talking about serious smack,
then, you know,
like if a woman were to call me
say, a knife
or say that I had
Arger or Rargi
or some other form of dishonor like that,
then, if you watch...
If you listen to the Fun Fact Challenge
bonus episode, then you'll know
that Nate is correct.
You know what I would do to a woman
that said such a thing
as what anyone would do
or to anyone to protect my...
to protect my honor.
To protect the world from devastation.
Yes, yes.
Snake, do you know
what to do if someone
calls you a gay wizard?
What would you do in that fucked up situation?
Pray the gay away?
Which is don't pray.
An admirable effort,
but I'm afraid it wouldn't be enough.
I'm afraid it wouldn't be enough to save you.
I'm sorry.
I mean, yeah, I was wrong from the start.
It would be like a paladin thing.
A wizard wouldn't do pray.
You just got to accept the compliment
and move on with your day.
That's not the...
That's not the Nordic way.
Ben, they can actually say
what to do if you're called a gay wizard.
Otherwise, then there'd be no point
to subscribe to the Patreon
and listen to the Fun Fact Challenge.
Exactly! Guys, thank you so much
for playing along with the bit where you pretend
not to know what I'm talking about.
Yes.
I totally know.
I was just reaching into my D&D lore
which is how I understand history.
I know, I know.
I mean, those are my textbook.
That'll be the death of you.
The only history I need is right here.
I'd say patting my
second edition monsters manual.
Yeah.
One time, a long time ago,
I wanted to buy
my copy of the second edition
Rules Cyclopedia.
He was going to buy it from me for $200.
What?
And then I just forgot to get back to him.
You should message him right now
and be like, yeah, still got it
if you're interested.
I have a set of the
three years ago.
The D&D first edition
player's handbook,
Dungeon Masters' Guide in a Monster Manual.
It's like $20 from a friend.
I don't know what edition...
I'm not sure what edition the Rules Cyclopedia
is from.
Rules Cyclopedia...
I've been a...
not a D&D, I've been a tabletop guy
for about 10 years now
and I have genuinely never actually played D&D itself
just because I find it.
I don't...
Oh, you've played other games.
I've played games that focus more on the actual...
I prefer games that are lighter
and just focus more on the actual role-playing
and combat.
You would like 5e, then. 5e is definitely
Rules Light.
I haven't played that one yet.
I'm a Dungeon World guy.
Snake, have you done that one?
I bought the book for Dungeon World. I haven't played it yet.
It's a lot of fun.
There's a ton of custom classes for it, though.
The base ones are like fine.
Only meld them in if you're not getting enough
out of those base classes.
I just need friends so I can actually play
with people.
That's the big missing component right now.
Have you ever played Powered by the Apocalypse?
Snake?
Dungeon World is Powered by the Apocalypse.
Oh, right, right, right.
I have played Apocalypse World, which was the origin
of it, and I've played
Spirit of 77, which is a
7e's buddy cop show
kind of take on it, which is really fun.
It sounds very funny.
I played the tabletop game once.
I only did it one time, but it was fun.
It was Powered by the Apocalypse. It was
Monster of the Week, where it was basically
like...Gib would like this.
It's basically like Buffy,
where you solve
mysteries and fight monsters and stuff.
It's really...
I don't want to say low stakes, but it's not
very combat heavy because it's very easy
to get yourself killed.
Yeah, it's more about the investigation
and working out what the
Paranole thing is. I played one game of
Monster of the Week. It was really fun.
The leader
of the party, I say in quotes because it's just
thing, we did a gag party
where the guy leading it was basically
playing Ghost from True Capitalist Radio
if he was a Paranormal Investigator.
That's good.
He was just really pissed off and mad,
and I was his driver and bodyguard.
Oh, you were the engineer?
No, I wasn't engineer. I was Scott
Shelby from Heavy Rain, but even
Dumber. I was just like a fat
lumbering guy, just following him around.
And that was a really fun
session.
Yeah,
D&D is fun and all.
I made a video about
the piece of channel. I actually remember you bringing it up on an episode
of things you can't get into.
The classic.
Yeah, I'm very...
I always chafe and feel irritated
by all the
minutiae and the nitty-gritty of the rules
and stuff.
That's why I like Dungeon World because it gets out
of the way and it's very interpretive.
And also, I genuinely think
it's a problem of having the right group of people
who... and kind of knowing what
your rule there for what you want.
Because a good GM will like, if something's more fun,
the rules can maybe take a backseat.
The point of dice
roles are, you're just playing make-believe
if there isn't some skeleton to
like, oh, am I going to be able to
do this? Am I going to be able to...
That's the stakes of it.
It's about having the right
group and all knowing what you're there for.
There's a rules-light
RPG game that I found
and I thought it was really interesting
and I always wanted to DM a game of it
with the PCP.
I always wanted to do at a Radcon.
We could do a game of it and we never did.
The game is called Rises
and you have only one stat
and it's just your class.
But your class can be something
like vague.
It's like a...
This is like a fiction trope, something like
Damsel in Distress
or like
Viking Berserker or something.
It's just something...
And basically, anytime you want to do
something that someone of
your class might theoretically be able
to do, like if you're a Viking, maybe
barge down a door, or flip
a table, or chop
a tree down,
you can make a Viking check where Damsel in Distress
would be like, climb a rope down the
side of a castle, or
convince a noble of something
or something like that.
That's the only stat you check against
is the number of this class
but it's a nebulously defined class.
And I thought that was really neat
and I never got to play it.
But on the other side...
I have played
D&D before.
I played in regular D&D
like a third...
I played in third, fourth, and fifth edition.
Actually, when I was a kid, I played in second
edition too.
I'm looking at the character sheet for Rysus
and this is very interesting.
I thought it
sounded really neat and I never got to play it.
I would love to someday.
On the other hand...
I was...
I think I was just googling around for like rules, light
systems, and this was
the rules, lightest system I could find.
This was the most minimal one.
But on the other hand, there's another system
that I thought was really cool once upon a time.
I tried to run a game and it was very short lived.
Mutants & Masterminds
is the exact...
I don't know if you've ever tried to play it
but it's the exact opposite. Mutants & Masterminds
it's very free form
in that you can basically be whatever you want.
It's a super RPG where you can codify your own powers
and you can get very crazy with it.
Yes.
You can basically have whatever power...
What?
I've not played that one itself
but I do know the system because I...
I think a few years ago that one was on my brain
a bunch.
The interesting thing about it
is the way that it makes you able to do
basically anything you want. Your character can have
whatever power you want. The way that it controls
for that is it doesn't...
it's not focused on like what exactly
your powers are or what their themes are
or why you can do them. The only rules in the game
are about like the parameters
and they literally will have like a table
where like your power can...
you can have a power
that like... at like a level 5 power
can push
you know maybe a thousand
pounds but it can only push it...
but if it pushes that much
it's only at a certain speed
right? So it can only push...
if it's more it can push it slower
but if it's less it can push it faster
and then if you take a hit to the overall
power balance of those two things
you can also make it modular
whereby you can like do a sliding
scale where like okay well I want to push
more slower or less faster and I can control
for it. It's like...
it's granular like that. It's like
mathematically defined
in a way that allows...
that means that it can aesthetically be
sort of whatever you want it to be.
I used that system
to run... I tried to run a one piece
campaign and I thought that system
was good for like thinking up care
because one piece is so loosely defined
and like I don't know everybody just kind of
you know there's fruit powers
but none of them are consistent in how they work
and like other people are just basically
have superpowers just like for no reason
like Zoro...
can just cut steel... he's a hockey
I don't know whatever
some people are just hypnotists
and have mind powers just because
you know...
We made a friend we found a system
that meant for running JoJo RPGs
and a lot of the mechanics were
interesting. It's very funny.
It was funny because
essentially that the system was
it had momentum where you're kind of
standing and pacing a battle can change to try
and emulate the idea of when you have
all the leverage in a fight you can expend
it to do that one big move or whatever
and it was a cool idea
but it had the same thing of the powers are
very nebulous like it just says
write in your power and let
the GM determine what the point cost
of it should be
and then choose your deficiencies
and I think that was a cool idea but
me and a friend were like we started
co-engineering an idea where
I would run one heart I would run
one run campaign and they would run another
and
my campaign was
like JoJo part 4 it was very low stakes
the powers were kind of
lighthearted and silly and not too lethal
and
meanwhile so I made that campaign
while they made characters for it and then vice
versa and we were going to get more people in
and when we compared all of mine
was just like joke characters
they were like all the battles were weird
puzzles but you wouldn't really die
and it was a murder mystery investigation
hers was
everyone had like part
5 bullshit death powers
it would like could like
instant kill you
meanwhile all the characters I made to tackle it
were my brand of joke characters
and all the characters she made for my
campaign had absurd power levels
it was like shit we've got a bit of an imbalance
you could easily annihilate
there's a mismatch here
you could annihilate any of my people
while I would die
instantly in your universe unless
I was way cleverer than I actually
am
I think one of hers
one of hers
it's like
you're in a video game and you wandered into
the area that you're not leveled up enough
for yet it's like oops
fuck
my bloody villain
his stan
the only thing I'm proud of it was because I really liked
the stan name I picked for the main villain was
heaven helps the man and it was just
is that a song reference
it's gotta be
heaven helps the man
I'm not familiar
yeah it's a good song
and I'm why am I struggling
to tell you
Kenny Loggins
oh really
wait, okay
that's really funny actually
like
usually I would think of like a more
like heavy
or like a more like musicians
Kenny Loggins is like some fucking
80 soundtracks bullshit
it's really funny to have
a good stan named after a Kenny Loggins song
from Footloose
danger zone would be a good stan name if it isn't already
it would be
I prefer heaven helps the man it was also just
his aspect was like
gravity powered he had like a bunch of
his stan was actually just tattoos over his body
and he just basically exuded
push
and I had a very convoluted murder mystery
the players had to work out
around why this guy had stan powers and shit
meanwhile hers was there's a dying old
man who wants to learn the secrets
of immortality was like so he's got
intergalactic race through space
to find something
and there's going to be a bunch
of people murdering each other on the way
one stand was which was called snow
halation by the way had poisoned the whole
planet like it was just a planetary
scale you die here
it was yeah that was
her campaign that was her campaign
did the stories
regret that we never played it if only because I kind of wanted
to get the full
experience of it
I don't know
I have tainted this for jojo
but yeah I don't know anything about Kenny
logins other than that he's dangerous
what
I heard you mentioning his name and it just gave me
PTSD
I put it in general
let's have a gander
does he have a song called read minds
oh no this is
from like an obscure like blog from
like 2010
no I know what this blog is
wait what
Kenny logins ruined Christmas
I think
there was like a
I think there was a mad TV bit
with Kenny logins where he like constantly
pisses his pants
I have no idea why
but for some reason I can remember
that very vividly
yeah like okay
time there's a different time
I believe he's a fictional character
that was invented
yeah
but
maybe I should have given him
Sam Powers
what was that
I should have given him the power to read minds
if he was gonna
have a Kenny logins song
that would have been
it would have stopped
all the other players in their tracks like Ben
right now
I always wondered actually
how should it be to just like
say yeah
the enemy in this tabletop RPG has mind control
has like mind reading powers
so just tell us what your character is thinking
right now
even better oh my NPC has
mind control powers so actually your character
doesn't do that thing that would be
inconvenient for me if you did
actually he has this other thing
I had an evening
just binge reading
RPG horror stories
just like terrible GM
oh as in games like games gone wrong
yeah yeah
there is a subreddit for it called RPG
horror stories which is just
some of them are really painful
like there was
I haven't been able to find the story again
but there was one which just sent me a fucking
on edge which was
they found out that they had been playing online
they found out that for months one guy
had been without them knowing streaming
their game and had been getting an audience
so violated
the only reason
they were able to like start suspecting him
was they realized he started like getting
more and more like twitch
streamer-y and acting things up
and trying to take the lead in situations
he like
accidentally said to smash that like button
like in casual conversation
nothing
shit hooker thanks for the sub
anyway my character attached
hey he's been streaming us for months
it's like yeah
the advice in the friend was
you need to sue the shit out of this guy
he just
trueman showed all of you
it's like you show up to the game
and someone brought quiz nose
and he's handed them out
and when somebody else goes
hey thanks for the sub and the guy just starts sweating
he's like
that's why in this day and age
where you never know if you're being recorded
you just say that to everyone and just see
see if it picks them
a little bit
you never know if you're talking to a live streamer
I heard a um
I read a story or something
about like a kid
I think maybe this some kids
maybe it was just one kid I don't know but like
this kid watched youtube all the time
and he started saying like
like comment subscribe as like
he would say that like instead of goodbye
cause he like all the youtube channels he watched
would end their videos with like comment subscribe
so the kid started saying like comment subscribe
it was when his parents tucked him into bed
at night he would say that yeah
yeah he said like comment subscribe
that really makes you think about
anthropology
that's humanical right there
really makes you think about
I'm gonna have like comment subscribe
on my headstone
and my sub count
not even the day I lived and died
just the sub count
that's all that's gonna matter
in the future anyway
subscribe
I'll have a little uh
one of those um
those like code those bar code
that you can scan
that will give you a
yeah QR code
to scan if you want to send
bitcoin to my estate
in the future
please thank you
this is the worst thought I've had
but I had had it so let's throw it out there
there is on the youtube
the youtube wikia there is like
a page that is the list of deceased youtubers
and I swear
it's like right my sub counts
what the fuck
I gotta see if I'm right
let me double check myself
that's so cool
wait wait what
how many did you achieve
while you were still alive what was your high score
I mean that's okay
it's literally ranked
that was my fault I've linked
that was like my that was my fault
it is ranked it is ranked
okay well this is
this is wikitubio
actually wikipedia
the fact is someone
went this right
and I have a question
and this is a ghoulish question
should the count stop
once you're dead
is that you
that's the cut off that's like
it's your high score
I think it should because
if you're gone
then you can't make anymore videos
you're not on the grind anymore
yeah you're not on the grind anymore
so the project as ray william johnson
once said this project
this project has discontinued
so it should stay at the sub count
when they died
okay I disagree I think
they should just track both because
I think it would be interesting
if people's channels like got a big influx
of subs after they died
and I think that probably in some cases
would happen and I think it's worth
having both numbers
I think that count should be segregated
so that's your post def momentum
the word suicide appears
on this page 107 times
if someone
died
if someone died with like a million subs
and then after they died
their work was discovered
they get 50 million people
sub and like
I guess
no but why would you sub
there won't be any more updates
I mean you're looking at
in purely rational terms
rather than like emotional ones
or someone not knowing
oh yeah
I know it's a bit of a weird gesture
but you know
I mean including the sub count
is pretty gauche either way
yeah no
that was when I read this
it was really fucked up
and then a part of my brain did go
they really all stop counting once they're dead right
the duality
they should publish
obituaries in the newspaper
and say like how many people showed up
to your funeral and like rank them
that week
who was the highest scoring death this week
okay I'm scrolling through this
I'm just looking through them I'm seeing like
Total Biscuit, Christina Grimmie
was on Steph and Carl okay
David Bowie is not a YouTuber
I don't care if he has a YouTube channel
you don't get the put them on this list
oh that
he doesn't deserve the cloud
he didn't even break a million subs
no free cloud David
yeah come on David
social climbers man
member of the prodigy you can't
like guys
Prince Philip
wait
is that what killed him
is that his reason for death
yeah not released to the public
this is so stupid
this list is really funny
it includes people with like
700 subs in the bottom
smaller than I expected
that even put on here
I know who hardly any of these people are
Joe Strummer
wait yeah there's people
Joe Strummer died before YouTube came out
what is this
there's people on this list with 500 subs
like these aren't YouTubers
they're just people who had one channel
I don't know
they make me wonder how they found those
random people who had an account with no
with like barely any followers but like
ugh
that's like what is the point of this list
that's like kind of worse because they're definitely not public figures
and they don't
you don't need that shit
and they are ranked below a bunch of people
I don't like this
what the
God we really could have ended this episode
on a high note with that Nate joke
but instead we sent down this rabbit hole
and now we're here
I am so proud I remembered this
and I can just drag us down
into the depths
no wasted content Tom
you know that's fair
I just you know I shouldn't have brought it back
I shouldn't have brought this up I could have saved this if I ever came back
it could have been a topic of discussion
but I guess it is now
you can click
you can click on
oh my god I can go
I can go to bad wolf gaming's
youtube channel with his
4.92k subs
and I can just watch his videos
they're just there
6 years ago
no do you know what's fucked up about this list actually
oh my god
what's really fucked up is
this list has gotten so much
more than the last time
can control f for prank
one of these people did die in a
ghost prank they dressed up as a ghost
and got shot fuck off
you're lying
they became the prank
you can do it
control f prank you'll find it
oh no his last
oh my god
guys bad wolf gaming's last
video he looks visibly
emaciated his last video
it's called I've got some bad news
and he's saying like they found
like a tumor in his abdomen
and it's like
he's literally saying he's sick and might die
and that's his last video and it happened
oh my god
this is macabre but just
the way it's worded is fucking
you know
you know what
you know what though I would describe
I would describe this list
of deceased youtubers ranked
according to sub count as rather
lynchian I really would
I would say
that this juxtaposes
I would say that this juxtaposes
the mundane with the macabre in a way
that calls the attention to the
containment of one inside of the other
I really would
where's the electricity
oh no
wow you did it
you made it so cool
it's like the fourth circle
oh I'm noticing at the top
that there is some standards
please note channels need to have at least
500 subscribers to be added
what
alright pro tip to anyone
listening get a youtube channel
never go above 499
you'll live forever you're fucking
sorted
won't die
there's one I've got to bring up which
it's not funny that a guy died
but good god the fucking wording
on this
yeah lung cancer the lung cancer was
caused by his excessive indulgence
in tobacco huh okay
fucking
was he like a tobacco review channel
I imagine by
okay this one this one is the one I
always remember Asia McGowan
just because there's a certain
indignity in this
McGowan was shot dead
at Henry Ford college by Tony
who is also on this list
no
dedicated to the memory by the way
I look I'm looking up the
RJ the smoker he's got like
RJ's guide to the intriguing
design of tobacco pipes part 3
he literally
his last videos are
he's vlogging his cancer treatments
it sucks
we should cut the whole episode
cut everything wait wait
thank you for listening to the PCP
wait wait
so so
the one
okay the one youtuber killed the other
and then also died
did suicide
committed suicide afterwards
his youtube channel was deleted
bummer
that's bummer
my research into crypto was
going to be the most dystopian shit
that I found this month but no
here we are this is this is even worse
I'm sorry Tom
I'm I'm sorry I'm sorry Tom
oh my god
who are you
imagine reviewing cigarettes on youtube
that's so bizarre
his last video
RJ the smoker's last video
uh
okay the last video is called farewell
somebody else must have uploaded for him
and it's basically just an announcement video
this guy died
ugh
did no one die from PCP that's what I need to know
oh god we're all going to be on this list
we are the reason people are dying
oh wait all of us have 500 subs
we're all going to be on this list
holy shit
this is our this is our graveyard
oh god
this is where we go
don't forget
we're digi destined for this
for this list
I don't even know what that means
oh shit
digital dreams are going to be on that list too one day
oh no I'm uploading myself to the cloud
I'm sorry
I'm uploading myself to the cloud I ain't never going to be on this list
I'm going on xbox game pass
later guys everyone unsubscribe
499 subscribers
we gotta get on the blockchain
the blockchain will save us
imagine digital immortality
being on the blockchain
subscribe like comment subscribe
patreon.com
if you don't
ever want to join the
list of deceased youtubers
no no
so
what do we think
I know a lot of stuff on the internet
a lot of it horrible
I should know less
good shit
I'm having a blast
get me out of here
alright
are we ending the episode are we done
I got nothing left
we're on the uplifting notes
we're almost at 420
that's good
actually if we include the pre-show we'll be over 420
so
media episode this week
alright I guess that's it
final
final warning
leave us a voicemail if you want
whatever
patroness please
and that's it
bye
yeah later yeah fuck it
cheese
texanikidpro.com