Ok, here we go. Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of the PCP. I'm the best guy
ever, your host today, and we're joined by all our lovable companions, Hippocrit for
example. Hello. Ben Saint is here. Heyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy
yyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy
yccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccg
Okay, well here was the problem that I ran into it was like put in your tax information
I put in all my tax shit, but then like it said like it auto-completed my name to Ben sain
But then down in the name category
It was like okay type your first name and last name and I did and it was like name must match
And I said but but that's not my name. That's not my real name
So eventually so I was typing my real name and it said it does it has to match
That's not okay, and finally I was like okay fine fuck it, and I just typed my name as Ben sain, and you know what it said
Said Nate it said name has to match
Even though I did no I made it match, and it's still didn't I don't I don't understand any of this shit
Can I just say as the last issue here? I've the problem. I've been facing maybe someone else can help
This is a desperate attempt to get someone to fucking help out in the audience
Bouncy now that
Yeah, I will give you I will give you money out of my pocket if you can help me solve this problem my personal money
I will do it this has been a headache for years literally years
One of the problems I've been facing is this whole thing where you can't have more than one account guys like
Munky are easily are able to tie you know all their different channels to get their AdSense money to like their main account
Like that's not a problem because they're all attached to one Google account the problem is I have had to make multiple Google accounts
You know things that involve different people myself and then procrastinators without everybody
So if you know how to fix this please for the love of God help me
And that's it
My rant wasn't over that was oh
That's all like relevant. That's all the sort of stuff like okay. That's what I was going through but it was it's like
For you and and all that stuff. That's like important money. That's like PCP money
That's AdSense for your channel and PCP
That's like big amounts of money for for people that people need to have I mean I've been I've been going through yeah
It's it's bigger. It's bigger than it's bigger than the literal zero dollars
I would make off Twitch which is this is my point like that the fact that like I would have been fine
Never making money on Twitch, but the fact that they said I could potentially get money
Right, let me on this part of this two-day past still hasn't been fixed
I have to now wait for 24 hours for this account to get re
Like you know reset itself so that I can input my number again, and maybe it will work
I don't think it will but maybe it will I don't know but it's just like agony like it just eats away at me like just
Thinking about the fact that I could be making like a dollar every two years on this twitch account
The fact that there's a revenue stream that is
From you gotta open up really just open up those passive revenue streams
It just makes it it just really makes me think it's like I I do this twitch stream for the passion and now that there's money
It's really makes me annoyed that it doesn't work
And now everything is fucked, and I'm really angry and I want to kill everyone and myself included and I fucking
I hate that money has done this to me, and it's it's shit
You know that's a perfect segue to some of the definitions of money over on Urban Dictionary
Oh, thank God. Thank God for this segment before you do that. I just wanted I just wanted to end with a twitch TV slash give and take
Do you want to go?
Everyone go watch I'm on there sometimes we play Minecraft or is that munchies? I can't remember no it's yours, and it's super fun
I I love it. I we should do that more we didn't do it yesterday, and I'll hate you forever for it
anyway
That that's true
I rather I sat there all night with my arms crossed to my brow frode staring at the screen
Why are they inviting me to play Minecraft? Why stay with fucking inviting me to play that's that's me every day
And there's there's a whole bunch of definitions by the way for money over on Urban Dictionary
So I'm going to cherry pick the ones I like
So definition four of money is the root of all evil
Where's another one number three here?
We go paper and coinage that can be used to exchange for goods and services more of it equals power and chicks
And and number two is a good one a money that which allows lazy people to do stupid things without painful consequences
Thus keeping them forever stupid. I know devu would not appreciate these definitions
He might appreciate the second one that was that I thought that was pretty fair pretty pretty even-handed
Let's go with that one. Let's go with that one that works
So, uh, I guess let's just get into our thoughts on on I mean we're all creators here, right?
We're all art kind of guys. So there's always a struggle going on. Well, not bad
Yeah, I mean, you know everybody I have I have the rest of us have artistic integrity of the story. Yeah
And so, uh, there's there's always the struggle of trying to
Decide what's appropriate to to you know make for what you do like avenue revenues
Fucking avenues for revenues is what I was trying to say and I mean guys like me
I'm really trying to do it. Can everyone hear the fucking tractor out my window
No
Well, maybe it's fine here. I'm I'll just kill myself. Thanks. Okay. Thanks. I'll sort that out
I know not everybody thinks of like doing their art
professionally like to support themselves like like mage for example
At least it doesn't look like you're making, you know, particularly strident moves to try to like support yourself entirely with your art
She did start. She did start a patreon at patreon.com slash lethal aurora mage
Tragically underfunded at the moment
What's what's your goal with that mage? Let me just ask you what would you hope to get out of uh, your your patreon?
I just some extra spending money just as to get as compensation or you look into, you know
Be professionally and support yourself entirely. Oh not not with just patreon, but in general all all your stuff all your own gosh
And complicated question. Um
Let me let me quickly think about it. Well, um, I've been debating on getting patreon for like
A while I actually made the patreon account like several years ago back when I was doing phony stuff
but I never got around to actually
Implementing it because I kind of felt bad for charging people for like the shit I do. Oh, let's talk about that
Let's talk about uh that later charge feeling bad about charging people for stuff willingly, but okay, we'll get into that
Yeah, so, uh, but right now I kind of need the extra spending money just on like better food for myself and
Yeah, sometimes sometimes I mean I might need extra spending money because that's the only
Job I have kind of but I'm not like in particular dire need or anything
Um, I don't know mage. You say that you need the money for better food. That honestly sounds pretty dire
I mean, I I'm still getting food. It's just not very good
Well, maybe if she didn't buy as much pocky and ramune from her local anime shop, she'd be in the fucking green come on
I wish I had an animation
I under you know, I I understand mage
I know that a significant a significant chunk of your income needs to go to patreon.com slash ben sain every month
It has to come out of something
That's right
But yeah, like I'm not I'm not in like super dire needs
So I'm not like advertising like hey guys, please give me all of your months right now or else
I'm gonna die tomorrow. I'll say it everyone give major months, please
No, no, it's okay
Like I I I'm like I'm giving an option for people who do want to support me
And that's you know, that's fine. They don't have to I don't I don't want to pressure people into doing it because then I'll feel
Really responsible about doing content and stuff
Which I really don't want to pressure myself into doing because then I'll just start procrastinating
and hating myself
Yeah, I want to procrastinator hates himself intensely. That's true. I want to talk about that because like
I
This month on my on hypocrite
I haven't made a single video for the channel for for patreon for april
So I'm not charging anybody for april
I haven't really thought about I mean I've thought about the fact that I'm not charging anybody
I'm not making a video
But I'm I'm more concerned about the fact that I'm not putting out a video in april
That the the charging people money is just like a thing that I don't think about as much
Because when I feel bad and procrastinate, it's because I don't want
You know the the video to not be good enough. I don't want but it's not because people are paying for it
It's just because I don't want to make bad videos. I don't want to make like videos that I don't think are good enough
And that's why I don't make anything like
There's like a there's a there's a different thing like I don't know how how the rest of you feel
About whether it's charging the people money for it that makes you feel bad and procrastinate or whether it's the quality of the thing itself
Whether it's probably it's probably both actually. I don't know. I definitely my philosophy on that in general
Yeah, you can come in after this, but like I just want to state my philosophy about patreon in general
I sincerely believe that when it comes to patreon specifically
Any money that you get out of the people willingly?
I mean you can't lie and tell them that you're gonna do something and not do it that that's not good
But whatever content you provide legitimately that people are willing to give you money for I think I would find it
Ridiculous to criticize anyone for doing so. It's not that I like if you make, you know
Like shitty art and people pay for it. It's not like I'm gonna like the art there
I just find absolutely no moral objection to to like you getting any amount of money that people find worth in that
Yeah, like no matter what like no matter what people have have opted into it
Like yeah, people have opted in hardcore to support you on patreon. You can't you can't like swindle someone on patreon
That's right. I don't unless you lie. I don't think you know
Yeah, well like that's the whole thing even if let's say you are releasing a bunch of stuff on patreon
Then you do a hard left and you do something different like people can just say I don't want to pay for that and they don't have to
That's right. They have the option at any time. It is your responsibility as a patron to say, okay, this content is no longer good
I'm not going to support them anymore. That's that's you. That's up to you entirely
Yeah, there is no like what can the creator do to like help with that never change their content
No, I've never I've never heard of a of like a patron being like you fucking cheated me
to anyone
But I have heard other people claim that like others are like cheating people with their patreon. You hear that with like kickstarter all the time
Yeah, I feel like I feel like that's more of a case of like people being new to patreon and not realizing that you know
Yeah, like they do it and then they they get surprised when they they realize they've been charged for stuff that they didn't really care about
and they forgot to like set the cap or
You know like because that was a thing for a while forgetting to set your cap as a thing
But like that's not on the person you're pledging. Yeah. Yeah, it's totally on you right
Yeah, it is on the person
But I think I feel like the the small instances in which patrons have gotten mad at creators is because it was a new thing
And then now people know a bit more about it so that they know
Well, I can just leave so
That's what i'm gonna do. It's it's a bit similar to getting mad at like, you know
Sort of like the owner like I you know, I'm a member at a gym and like when I joined this gym
They it's a it's a fantastic gym. I absolutely love it. Um, and it's got all this wonderful stuff
Um, but like I was very clear because I've had a lot of experience with different gyms to ask like, okay
Tell me about the joining fees the leaving fees like the the the monthly payments like is that ever going to go up?
Like what is the uh, you know, like at what points am I allowed to leave the plan?
It's like I've got a yearly plan
So I cannot leave before that point like you just have to understand the situation you're getting into and know that
You know like what fees you can expect to see and uh, you know
Just make your as a as an aware consumer or customer or supporter
You just have to be savvy about the costs and about like any
Issues that could come up. It's your responsibility
Okay, okay. So like I have people pledging to me. Thank you guys by the way if you're listening and um
so I I made a video and I charged people for it and
If like they said they're only gonna like charge them at the beginning of the month
So
If if they wanted to they could back out
But like, you know, if it was a private video, which is it isn't but if it was a private video
They could have seen it and then back out with and I don't know. I think would they be charged?
No, I think I think if it if the charge doesn't go through it doesn't count as a payment
I think like so, I mean mage what you're asking for is if you had gated content
That was behind like your patreon that people had to be a patron to get
Could someone because it because you get charged at the beginning of the next month could someone come in
Say they're gonna pledge watch the stuff and then bail before the money goes through. Is that the question? Yeah
It can't you can do that. I've had people do that to me before
Um, it's it's dumb the way to get around it the patreon in response to that
They have a new thing now, which I suggest everybody do is when you you can set up your account
You can set it so every new patrons automatically charge as soon as they sign up
So like if they sign up for a $50 pledge instead of
Waiting till the end of the month to charge if they're instantly charged for that as soon as they sign up
So that's the way to do it. If the pcp one isn't like that
It should we should adjust it to be like that immediately
Mine is like set up per video rather than per month though
Right the same thing you just got your own system because because the way patreon works
Even if you're set up per video instead of charging as they come out at the end of the month
They'll collect all of the the content you have to upload four videos
They're gonna charge people four times or attempt to charge people four times at the end of the month and then give it to you a week later
Yeah, so they're gonna charge at the end of the month rather than whenever I post videos
Correct guys. I don't know how much we should go down the rabbit hole of you know, patreon minutia here
I was waiting. I was waiting to say I think we've gotten a bit far afield of the topic of
I was just curious. Sure. Yeah. No, not that I don't think this is talking about it
podcast. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Um, okay, so
Teach me some pies
Do doing it doing it for the money versus doing it for the the love of the game
Um, I I guess I have I guess I have a relevant uh topic to say I've been
um, I've I've been doing like
All right, I've I've been I've been pretty slow
I've been pretty slow with my main content
Recently and I have a couple of reasons for that
One of it is like personal stuff because I've been like getting ready to move and all that
um, and the other is just like
I've been I've just
Just been focusing nice looks. Yeah. Yeah, I've been I've been focusing on that and it's been and it's been terrible
It's been terrible and I can't wait for that nightmare to be over almost done. I'm so close. Oh god
But I have I I took I took a little bit of commission work and it's just I found
I found that it's so hard like drawing. Yeah commissions is so hard
because like
Like no matter what the commission is like even if even if what they're asking for is like fine
Like I don't know when when you're when you're making something yourself and you're drawing yourself you're doing it
You're like I don't know like you're you're doing it in accordance with like what you want to see
But like right right
When it's a commission when you're doing it for someone else for you know when you're doing it for the money
I guess as opposed to for the passion. It's like
Every step of it is like this slog and like I don't know right the more the more
Like I sketched out this image that this person wanted and then you know, I was like, okay that sketch looks pretty good
It's pretty rough whatever it's got most of the stuff and then I started finishing it and and like
Finishing it was such a nightmare because it's like I worked and worked because I had to like
Put in more details and stuff and like this is not how I would design this thing and like right
The more I worked at it like the more it resembled what I had been asked to do
But the less I liked it because I was going against my like natural instincts. It was such an uphill battle
Commissions are just such like a psychologically such an uphill battle and it's just so much less
Good
That's similar to like when I first started my patreon. I had reward tiers some of which were like drawing a thing
For a person and and I found those really difficult as well because
Well mostly because I was lazy, but also because I didn't like having to do something
at all
So I don't do rewards because like it really is exactly doing something for the money
Like I'm doing this because you pledged because there's a reward. I'm not doing this because I would have done it
Yeah, and that's why in my patreon now. There's no rewards at all
Which is probably making me lose a bit of money, but I think it's worth it
I don't like having that hanging over me. I know I know that I know that I owe
I know that I owe like a handful of people some reward art that like I have been sitting on for a while
and that is
Yeah, I'm gonna get I'm gonna get to that like probably after the nuzlocke's end
I like that's like on my plate because I have to do that at some point because I feel terrible
I feel terrible owing people art
I feel like some of them have probably forgotten that I even owe them art in the first place
But I know I do and I have to at least try like I have to at least be like hey, you still you still want this
Let's let's let's get this sorted out so I can feel like a person again
It's really annoying
It's really it's really weird when they forget and then you feel bad about it still so you have to you have to decide
Well, I could just do I could just forget about it, but I feel bad about it
Maybe they don't forget maybe they just don't say anything you want to be nice
Well, there is at least one person who I have explicitly emailed and been like hey
I owe you some art because you you gave to my I think it was for my um
Indy might go fund me like what do you want and they didn't answer and I'm like well
You're in the clear. I think I've done all I can do
And absolutely I did the same thing because when I started my patreon way back in like what 2014
I had a tier where I just did commissions and it was a nightmare because I had like 15 commissions to do all of a sudden overnight
Yeah, and I was like, yeah great
I'm making money, but like I made the money to support the videos I was making at the time
But now I've given myself all of this like basically freelance work on top of the work that I was trying to fund in the first way
So I fucked myself over hardcore it sucks and all these pictures are fucking stupid. I don't want to do them anyway
So it's eventually what I just did is I just like people who weren't responding because it took me forever to get them done
So I was like I just put out a big thing on patreon
I was like these are the people I have left to do if you don't respond within two weeks
I'm knocking you off the list and like half the people didn't respond. I'm like, you know what?
Fuck it
Yeah, when it's when it's something. Yeah, when it's something that someone else wants to see rather than what you want to be drawing
It's just harder like it just makes it harder to do
You know this this feeling you've been described is exactly why I have I offer exactly zero perks on my patreon
Exactly zero all that you get is that you get to feel support
Uh for you know best guy ever and you um like that I actually like that a lot
It is completely ideologically pure the only reason to to to you know
Yeah, the only reason to patron me is because you like the content and you want to support it because I make it very clear in my
In my you know on patreon.com slash best guy ever that the money goes to me being able to do this as a career
That's what that's what my whole life is geared towards. That is the only goal
I have in life being able to leave my job and and do more of this shit as fast as possible
Yeah, and um rewards either because like I don't produce that much content and I feel like if I had rewards
I would spend more time working on the rewards, which which is bad for everybody which is bad for everybody
of speaking of like the goal of like
Doing this as a living I feel right okay get on the subject of like like money versus passion
I'll just I'll just lay out my belief on this subject, which I think everyone is probably going to agree with
I don't think anyone's going to find this too controversial
um
Um, I don't I don't care about money at all except in so far as it lets me live
The way that I want to live so like as long as I'm making enough money
Like I I I I need money up to the point that I have all my shit taken care of and I can and I can do art
And then beyond that it's all it's all superfluous right agreed
Yeah, I think we all agree on that except some of us have standards of lilings that go slightly above
You know eating a discarded pizza hut out of the dumpster from behind the thing
Well, you know some of us buy our own pizza. Well
You know I've had I've had to get closer to that point. I've had to yeah, I've I've lowered my standards of living
I've yeah, I'm not joking like I'm low
Like I've like I've lowered my costs and I've lowered my expectations to like as low as they can possibly go
Because I just want to hit that equilibrium point where I'm making enough money that I can live
And not have to do any other bullshit except make the shit that I want to make
And like anything that I could anything that I could do to scrape more money out of my art or
Lower my fucking cost of living like anything that gets me closer to there is worth doing like
Everything I respect that actually I think that's it's the only thing. It's the only thing that makes sense to me. You know, right?
Yeah, I the way I work is is exactly that like
But the problem that comes with that is that I sort of go in and out of phases of certain things that I want to do
Like um
Like recently this month instead of doing hypocrite videos
I did like a whole series of drawing brisker, which is you know, it's it's I'm going to continue doing that
But I then then I was like, oh, you know what my little pony started
I'm going to do a my little pony podcast with Jesse and I was like that's another thing
And then there's like vlogs and and anything anything and anything that isn't like a main channel video because I have been working on one
But it's sort of like
I have to play the other whole game and take notes and it's taking long
And it it it sort of drains me out. I just want to do other stuff
I I want to make other videos
I could have if I worked on it if I had the the the wherewithal the passion that the drive
To make a couple smaller videos on hypocrite and that would have been great for everyone
but I didn't because I
I do it so much for the passion that if I don't have the the passion then I won't make any money and that's just how it is
Yeah, um, I hate I hate that about myself because I do at least want something at the end of the month
But I don't know devout devout chimes in
Quote life is like a video game and money is like points
I want to achieve fun and interesting goals while also seeing how high I can get my score
People in the stock market and billionaires and shit. I think this is their entire goal
Most of them seem to like making money way more than they like spending money
That's that's accurate. Yeah, he's living living living that living that gamified life. He's living
He's living the gamification dream your passion is making money. I think I would argue that must become addicting at some point
It's oh, oh, absolutely
I'm sure but I was I was gonna say in response to sort of ben's point and you know, everybody gives as well
About you know wanting to achieve the equilibrium of you know, lowering your standards to to just like be able to do what you want
I would argue that. Oh, well, I guess I wouldn't argue anything. I'm just I would put in that. I have an additional
um, like like uh, sort of point in that equation something that I feel should also be addressed
And that is I mean and then here comes Nate's quote. We uh, what is it a weird utilitarianism?
Yeah, I feel like I feel like there there should be some
Like net gain from your life or you know, you should strive to achieve that like there is no fucking such thing as like
There's how you say that how the fuck do you measure that? Uh, well, there's lots of ways. All right
I know I know what you're gonna say is does it close to get us closer to starfleet?
Well, no, I was okay. No, this is how do you fucking know?
You can you can wait wait wait wait wait wait. There's a net gain
By purview of like already by the fact that we didn't exist before and now exist and some people like what we made
Right, that's already a net gain. So you're talking about a big like long-term people would argue that isn't even like a legacy, but yeah
Uh, I yes, I mean, I yes, I am operating from the standard. I fully admit I am operating from a human
Centric utilitarianism standpoint. Yes, that's where I'm coming from
But so is it is it I don't but you're not talking that you want to have a legacy because you
This isn't a but no, it's not about any individual person ego
You're trying to like give back to the community on a more macro scale. I'm rooting for team human here. That's just what I'm doing
There's no there's no like there's no standard of like what is progress and like what is what is a
Hard to quantify that is absolutely untrue. You're absolutely untrue
There's so many ways we can all agree that the world gets better
Is the world better if we create a vaccine that eliminates a specific disease objectively? Yes. Oh my god
Everyone go out and invent a vaccine. I guess what is your bet is your point that I'm wrong because you're just I'm just my point
Is that you're not true? You're fucking literally throwing out some fucking un
Indefensible unfalsifiable like crazy shit like how like we can't
No, we cannot have according to the standards you're laying out because they're incoherent you you are such you're so dense here
All that is is an example showing you
Dude, you'll get your
Ben you are saying that I am objectively wrong across this uniform view and I'm showing one example to show how that's untrue
That's all I'm doing. That's all I'm doing one example is like so specific
And that's exactly that's fine
Guys we're getting off track the the point is Nate. Well, yeah, but you're never gonna go anywhere with that
Like the whole thing is that Nate wants his videos to lead to something greater than his videos in the long term of humanity
And that's that's just he's just thinking he's just thinking way bigger than we are
I don't really particularly that's true. I'm just I think bigger than everybody
I don't think that's like a necessarily better thing to do. I just think that you know, that's what he does
If you're an artist
Yeah, if you're a if you're a doctor then yeah, okay, sure you you can you you're creating vaccines
You're doing cancer research or you're adding to like the sum of human knowledge or something. That's fine
If
Relevant example do our discussion today if you're a fucking artist
How do you measure whether you're fucking shit has has a fucking net gain on society?
Look, I would argue
I would argue that every person intrinsically does it whether they know it or not
They are trying to basically do exactly what i'm saying. They just aren't aware of it
Like why does an artist create, you know, like a big mural of like, you know, martin Luther king or like or like
Inspiring people from their community. They do it because they want okay one time
This is my sound bite for the podcast art is a self-indulgent practice. It is
Absolutely. It is. I I think I think I think
Even if I sit here and say I want to make a piece of art that says something
Relevant the only reason I want to say that thing that's relevant because I believe it and I want people to believe what I believe
So it's entirely a self-indulgent practice. Well, I don't think I will say I will say that um, I've just realized in this that
Nate
Aside from his analysis videos is not an artist per se. He doesn't make stuff
Self-indulgingly in that way. He likes explaining why something is good
He likes explaining art more than he likes making why Nate is right about something and why he is the best guy ever is
Incredibly self-indulgent
Right, but but I I do that because I think that there is something valuable to be gained through that process
Davoo says, why does Nate always come to this? Nate? I also want videos to lead to something great
But I don't need to bring it up every goddamn week
It's
It's it's almost like it's almost like that's kind of the core philosophy to everything else I do
It's almost like that Davoo. Wow. You're such a brilliant guy Davoo. You're so smart always making these
I just want to kill you. I just want to make one more point about this subject like
Nate I think that you're I think that your logic is fuzzy here on two levels because one
I think that everyone is going to disagree about what constitutes progress
I agree and be I think that it's going to be like like even a really
Like it's going to be really like no matter what standard you choose
There's going to be cases where it's going to be hard to determine whether or not progress was actually made
That doesn't mean that we shouldn't try or make an effort to to get that way
What I really want to understand because this is the thing that's that's always like made it seem fuzzy is that I don't know
Quite exactly what your plan is to make like
Specifically what your videos and what your plan is in life to make a change for the better
What do you want to happen due to your involvement in you know the universe?
What what what do you want your impacts to be?
Based on what you're doing now and what you plan to do in the future
Well, I fully admit and there's really no other way that anyone can operate that like I am approaching things from my perspective
As what I think the right way to go is and I have thought about it for a long time
And I legitimately hold these beliefs so things like in the gurren login video
What I'm doing in that video is pointing out how this show is is sort of encapsulating an idea that I think is valuable
And I wish people would consider more as they conduct themselves or in their daily lives
And it's you know, like it's an anime analysis showcasing an idea that I think is really good and explaining why I like the show that you know
Has that bit in it like that's that's what I'm doing and I want so what
So you would say maybe that you're like a preacher using the medium of youtube analysis
I okay. I mean I say this
Yeah, I say this all the time. He's a bard. He's a bard
Yeah, like I I'm all about that thing that hui freeman talked about in that fucking episode of the boondocks where he puts on the christmas plate
Like he had this idea and he wants to explain to people
I don't know whatever it was in his case like the real jesus or something
And why you know everyone's wrong about jesus and like nobody gave a shit until he put like fucking
Uh, I don't know like I don't know who was it like kanye west or like people that are just like famous and just like are cool
And he put like songs and he put sword fights and he put all this flashy shit in order to like
Make a sweet pill that people would swallow to get the medicine that's inside it like the important message to get people talking about it
That's what i'm all about. That's what i'm all about. That's hui's law as i call it all about that blue pill
I'm totally it's not a blue pill
I'm totally sweet pilled. I'm totally sweet pill dog. It's
I get it now that you're just you're just trying to spread uh, good messages good vibes christ consciousness
You know, that's right. All that good stuff. Damn right. That's it. You're just you're just trying to tell people
The cool stuff look ben ben. I really just to go back to this
I really think that there are even if you you think that it's like
Hopeless that there's too many things that people are going to disagree on and we can't get anywhere
I would still I would say that you have to say that there are at least some things that I think that we can form a consensus on
Like like just as an example come vaccines like things like that
But how is that?
Guys because I want to make a statement
Wait, wait, I just let me mage mage. Let me just answer what he just said quick
he's
Go on ben. He said
The like that's such a specific example like that. Yeah, that's who the fuck is gonna be like i said
Who the fuck is making vaccines like like i'm like what i'm doing in my life is not going to lead to the creation of
Giant corporations giant, you know like medical corporations are making vaccines. How does that fucking how does that fucking inform?
How the average person should live their life?
Maybe they should work for that company
About this discussion anymore and it's certainly going to be losing us money if we keep going so mage
What's up? I just wanted to like agree was tell me that when he said earlier about this whole self-indulgent thing
Like, uh, I I do art because it makes me happy
Like i've always been drawing regardless of whether people saw it or not
And even if I wasn't popular or even if people didn't like my art
I would probably still be drawing but the fact that there's a lot of people
Out there that like my art and and they they're happy because the you know, they got to see what i'm doing
Kind of makes me happy and it kind of motivates me to do more
But regardless of that I would still be doing what i'm doing with or without the people
That leads me into the point
I wanted to make about this discussion of money versus passion and how I think
There is another aspect that people operate on that we're totally leaving out of this equation and that's a tension
I think more than even money. I think people do things for attention. I think that's a huge motivator
honor and
Glory they're similar in the sense that you know, like one is sort of economic capital and the other is social capital
And both can be sort of used to gain advantage like social capital for a lot of people is probably more valuable
I think okay. Sure. Sure. That's fine. That's fine
I totally is but I think there's like I think there's so many people who just like shitposts and do like random crap on the internet
Just because they they're looking for attention even though they know it's not going to make them any money
Whereas there are things that could make you a lot of money that people don't do
So I think I think a lot of people operate just under like they want attention
I would start hiding and doing things whenever I would give like a lot of attention because I got scared of being like
Really I line light
I I will say that mage you say you say that you would draw even if no one was watching and
I
Honestly, I'm pretty sure that if I didn't if I didn't think anyone would see it
No, I would never draw anything because what would be the point
I could just imagine the image in my head and then I'd have seen it and I wouldn't need to share it
I wouldn't need to create it to share it with anyone
I feel sort of similarly to Ben and I would say I advocate for sort of like a
Sort of like a benevolent
capitalism on this front
What was the other thing? What was hippo gonna say? Sorry. Yeah. Go ahead. Oh, well, uh,
I don't know. I was gonna say something
about like like like not understanding Nate's position before but now kind of understanding that yeah
He's thinking about that that sort of thing and I think
Art, uh, when you're making it
It's it's it's everybody does it for a different reason some people do it because they want attention
Some people do it because they need money, but also because they kind of like it
Some people just love it so much that they can't not do it
You know, I think we all have like the the reason I make my my reviews of video games is because
I feel good when people reacts positive positively to them. I also like it when I can tell people about
Um, cool video games and have them play and have fun. So I like spreading the the fun and you know on another level
I like understanding understanding in myself why something is good
Which is why there's always a lot of analysis even though I'm mostly a comedy guy
I try to figure out for for real exactly why a game is good so that I can say to myself. Yeah
I figured it out finally and it's it's all those
Little different things the reasons that I like doing what I do
And the money is is a is a much lower on the on the scale really to the point where I probably would still make them
Even if I didn't make that much money that it would always be a hobby of mine to do that
Um, you know, if I got like a real job or something or a different source of revenue and hypocrites
Just sort of the died or it never gained any sort of big popularity
I would still probably just be slowly making them until I'm dead
Is it is it going too far to say that really when it comes to a question of doing it for passion versus doing it for money
Is the heart of that doing it because you want to do it for yourself versus doing it for other people
Is that really what it comes down to?
Well, everything's selfish everything's selfish in the end
You might do it for other people because other people make you feel good about yourself for having made it for them
Go on
Okay, let's hold on to your thought. Don't forget it. Yeah
So for me like, um, it's a little uh, when we talked earlier a bit about the whole, you know
You said, you know, you wouldn't do it because no one would see it like for me
I've like I said, I've always been drawing ever since I was little and not a lot of people saw it
Like the fact that people did see like a few friends, maybe family family not so much friends, I guess
Uh, it it was definitely like a motivator to you know, sort of show off and share it
But I it just I couldn't not draw like even if no one saw it. It's just it's just part of my life for me
um
That's like is that, you know, the people saw see it and they like it
That's definitely like motivating me to make more. However, there is a point where
The attention turns into expectations and that's where I get like really uncomfortable
And then I kind of backpedal and not do anything because I don't like people expecting stuff from me
like um
And and like this is what's bothering me because my most recent video like the animation meme it blew up like a lot more than I
Expected it too and people were like, oh man, this is so good. I'm subscribing like I can't wait for more quality memes
animation memes and I'm just like
How I'm gonna live up to this
I see I see
Like I did this meme like just because I wanted to for the most part like I could have oh my god 152,000 views
Jesus christ and less than a week. Exactly. That's uh, really good. I mean
It took me several days
But I I did it because I really wanted to make it look a little different than the other uh copycat memes
It wasn't like because I wanted it to get a lot of attention or like make a lot of months out of it
Silly boys. Don't look at my meme animations. I hear you mage
No, no, no, no, I mean like yeah, I wanted to put it out there and I wanted people to see it
But it was like I wanted to do this. That was my main motivator. I
This is the meme I want to do and this is how I want to go about it
And I did stress about it sometimes and I did change several things and some things didn't turn out the way
You know, I wanted to and in the end I'm not too happy with it
But kind of proud of it. I'm proud enough to put it up. But then like
You know, it was for me mostly for me
I'd like I like the people did like it and shared it and now that he's getting a lot of attention
I am getting scared
And at the base it was it was just because I wanted to do it not because other people wanted me to do it
Yeah, I think that I think when you when there's like
Reasons to make something everything's on sort of like a slider the more you slide something to one end
You know the other ends like you know a percentage of the reason you want to do it sometimes like gender like gender
You're somewhere along the slider. Yeah, okay. We're on the same page, right? Like like
It's like a percentage thing like or a pie chart. I don't fucking know how to to visualize this but like
That's like
Yeah
There's like, uh, there's uh making it because you want it to exist
That's like every every time I think of something. Oh, wow, that doesn't exist. I want it to exist
And I make it sometimes said something like very similar to this. I'll read this after you're done
But yeah, so there's like making something because you just wanted to exist and you haven't seen it yet
And you just that's the drive the other thing is like making it because uh for attention slash money because like
It's basically the same thing you you want like validation in some form. Um, and then the other one is like
Uh, something I don't fucking know. I I I I ruined my own idea
I'm with you though. I'm with you. Well, well, DeVuz DeVuz comment is I have a Venn diagram
The things I want to make circle is so big and vast that I am left demoralized at the futility of picking one
When I examine the things people will like and things that will turn a profit and
Things that I have the skills for fields and figure out what is contained within all of them
I am presented with a glorious few paths to choose from
Summed it up pretty good. I think I like think I'm into that metaphor or it's not a metaphor
Hey, uh, I'd like to I I'm also acting as the voice piece in this case for monkey who just asked
Where is DeVuz typing this shit? I want to post fun notes. Okay, never mind. No, I owe this to DeVuz
I owe this to DeVuz. I'm I'm being subsumed. Yeah. Well, because he left me his microphone
And he was like, oh, that's right. He was no, he was like, I kind of want to be on this cast
But I kind of don't so I'll just let you use my microphone and in return in return just read my DMs in
In the thing. I was like, well, I guess I can't say no
Yeah, what the hell like we could never ever have a podcast with Ben and and DeVuz on it because
We did last week and I just used my shit mic and it sounded like garbage. You gotta buy one my friend. No, but I don't want to
Yeah
How will I how can I buy a new mic like that's going to come out of the funds I'm saving up for that oculus rift
If anyone yeah, let us know in the comments if you understand what the fuck i'm talking about when I say that
That's that's a deep it should stay a deep a deep hidden. Yeah, deep hidden. Yeah, that's the deep layer
So you know on that on that pcp like depth chart that should be like that's pretty fucking deep
It's maybe not the deepest but it's down there. Um, okay
So about what we're saying about like things you want to make versus what people want to see for for me
Being an artist is all like the satisfaction of being an artist is all about making the thing that you want to make and then
Putting it out there and seeing what other people think about it. So like I'm
Like like I'll do like I'll do commissions or stuff whatever because I need money like like I said like like money
Doesn't motivate me at all except in so far as it lets me do the things I want to do
What really does motivate me is attention and I'm kind of embarrassed to admit that but there you go
I just want people to see my shit. I want I want I want people to see my shit and I just want to see
I want I want to make the thing
I want to make the thing that's in my head and put it out there and see what it is
And I want to make things that are like honest and like represent like my actual self in some way and put them out there
And get like the and see what see what happens, you know
Like there would be no point in doing it. There would be no point in doing it with anything other than like what is really
my
self, you know
Any like I wouldn't like I have I have no interest in like catering my content or something to be more popular because
If it's not if it's not the thing that I want to make then I don't care
If it's not the thing that I want to make then I don't care how what people think about it or how popular it gets because it's not
Really mine if you're just gonna if you're just in it for the money might as well do a job that actually pays more than that
Yeah, exactly like if you're in for the money, there's no reason really being an artist
You're kind of kneecapping your your main desire right there. Yeah. Yeah, what when it when it comes to things that I want to make
I think this is the reason I'm a jack-of-all-trades and I'll never be like really good at any one thing
I'll just make a loads of different things because I have like ideas that you jump cut jack-of-all-trades my favorite character
I'm so glad you're here jump cut jack-of-all-trades. Yes
and and it's like
You know, I want certain things to exist and they don't exist and I don't want to pay for them because I don't have really
I don't really have money for that if I did have money even if I did have money
I would feel weird paying somebody to make certain things like like art or whatever
So like I've considered like writing a book because I want to I want to have like a book
I just I just want it. I I've written like a little thing and I'm gonna I'm gonna make it eventually
And there's like a video game. I want I want playstation 2 style graphics to become the next big thing
I want to bring it back
So I want to work with my brother to make a playstation 2 game just to just because I want that to exist because there isn't one
There isn't one on steam that you can buy in the scooter. There is no playstation 2 game. God damn it
PlayStation 2 has no games in yeah, that meme has been going on
Really annoys me
You know and things like that even like pornography like there's certain pornography
That I I think in my head and I'm like, oh wow, that'll be cool, but it doesn't exist. Nobody draws it and it's it's annoying
I feel like I gotta I gotta get better at drawing anatomy so that I can I can make that for myself just be like, oh, yeah
Yeah, I did it
I did it. I did it. I
It was in my head and now it's on paper and I don't have to think about it anymore
I could just look at it, you know, it's just all these things. I want to do everything
I want to make a rock album or I want to make a rap album or I want to make everything
And it just it kills me because I'm just I just don't focus on any one thing for any
You know a good amount of time to make the things that are in my head because I just
Yeah, I have so many comic ideas that I want to do I don't want to do comics
I don't want to make a game as well
But I don't know like I don't know the first thing about like programming shit
I could do the arts
I'm I'm lucky that I have a brother who is a programmer so I can
I can have him do it. I I wanted help. I have you said you're good at programming
Not uh, yeah, I'm you know, I pretty much stick to my lanes that I use at work and like I like
When I was younger, I was into game design and planned on doing it
But like I've I I basically just do the corporate kind of shit and do not spend my free time doing it
So like I'm not really a game programmer or anything like that kind of show
I I want to expect that I had I had I had a bunch of I had a bunch of champion stuff that I really wanted to do
And like I'll probably still do it
But like like I had I had like the next three chapters planned out and I had like a side chapter
That I was gonna thinking of like maybe paying someone else to draw
It's like a little side story and I thought about making like a little like a game
I thought about like programming like a really simple game that related to it or something and then all it all kind of got
I fucking I started the second nuzlocke and then I fucking
I don't know I put I don't know
I feel like my effort went into that instead and I deeply regret it and I hated and it was the biggest mistake in my life
It wasn't worth it
But like once I started it I had to finish it and well you're almost done
And once that's done you can reassess all your priorities at your leisure and I hope you make
I hope you make choices that will uh support you financially and then once you have more, you know leveraged there
My find it'll be easier to do whatever you want. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, yeah, that's all. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's good
It's gonna be good. It's gonna be good
I feel like I feel like I'm really coming to a point where I can finally just like
Fuck everything else like I'm gonna have time like soon
I'm gonna have the time and like the ability to like just do the shit that I want to do and it'll be fun
Once once I get some stuff out of the way like some commission stuff and
Fucking getting people other rewards because I need to fucking get everyone their rewards before I can feel comfortable with anything
I feel like how did I even get on this fucking tangent? Never mind. It's not important. No one knows. Nobody knows. Nobody cares
What were we talking about?
Money I hate it. We're talking about stuff and it's so hard and I don't like how difficult it is and it's gonna take
40 years before I
Feel good about it. You guys were talking about all this this, uh, you know doing stuff because you want to do it
Let me just put it out there that I don't give a shit about anyone's feelings
The fact that artists want to make what they make could not care less about, you know, people doing what they want to do
I'm only interested in your uh, and you know, like the the the productivity the productivity units that you are, uh,
Putting into the human machine. That is what I'm interested. That's what I see people when I walk around
I just see units of of value and some people have more some people have less
You're crazy, Nate. You're fucking crazy. No. No, Ben. Yeah, Ben. I'm the one who's called the communist
This is something a little communist. Here's the thing here's the thing with this
I'm on Nate's side here because I I understand that his point of view is that and there's no
Owners on me to give a shit about his desires as a person
So if he wants me to like if he doesn't care that I'm doing what I like, right?
I mean that doesn't change anything about what I'm doing. No, I'm doing what I like
That's not what's crazy about it. What's what's like I'm all for not giving a shit about about other people or about what they want
but
Measuring measuring them and here's measuring them in utiles
Like like giving them like a utility using some kind of utility calculus to like objectively determine their marriage is
Nonsense, that's a meme. That's a meme. But what I'm really saying is I am not interested
I like I don't agree with Ben Shapiro on a ton of stuff
But one thing that I do totally agree with him on is that I am totally disinterested with how other people live their life
But I want them to have the total freedom to do whatever they want as long as they contribute in some way to the whole
So this this is a purely capitalistic system
I'm talking about here where I want you to have the freedom to do whatever you want to do
You just have to find a way to make people give a shit about it and and just in addition to that
I would like it
This is where like my personal thing is I would just really like it if everyone had as a priority that like
Okay, I'm gonna find a way to make my way in the world
But I'm going to keep in mind that my overall goal is to like also try to make things better in general in whatever way
I define that as I'm gonna try to make it better and obviously there's gonna be conflicts as to what makes things better
But that's what I want. That's what I want. So say say I make all my art stuff and it's like, you know
It never gets super big but people like it and it's and it is people liking it
It's people being feeling happy about the fact that that I they're watching or listening or reading the thing that I made
That the happiness level has gone up. They've got happiness points. Is that progress? Is that like what you think is a good idea?
I'll tell you exactly what usefulness art and and all that shit has there
There are times when human beings can no longer do the work that makes them valuable members of of society
At those times it is appropriate for them to do things like in consume art or or play video games
Or which is art. I'm not making the distinction there or just like do you know things that make the relax listen to music
Whatever to de-stress so they can wake up the next day and continue to be a slave to the to the human machine
That's what that's what we need them to be. So there's totally a place for that. Here's here. I agree with that
Okay, I just I just don't think of it like that. I just don't think I like to think in cold
Mechanical terms because I don't think of it like benefiting society. I just think oh, you know what? I'm glad that people enjoy myself
I'm glad I'm making a few people's lives a little better every so often
It's really funny. I don't care about making anyone's life better. Like I like I don't I don't care
People Ben is far more amoral than me consider
No, I'm completely amoral, but I just think that
I think the I think that I don't like the tone. I'm using that's all you're no here's what I say
You see I admit to being completely amoral, but you claim that you have some kind of moral compass
And I'm over here highest moral. I'm over here trying to dismantle it and show you that actually
You're not because your moral compass doesn't actually make any sense or point anywhere
Um, the right. That's what you're trying to do. That is what I'm trying to okay. It's spectacularly
Yeah, by okay by saying that like people should keep in mind like the greater good
You're just you're just asking people to go against human nature and it's just pointless like everyone human nature is weak
Human nature can't be trusted. We have to rise above it. Everyone you can't you can't rise above human nature
You just can't do it everyone by nature
That's a great like acts in a way acts in a way that like maximizes their own fucking good and like their own
So there's so much evidence. There's so much evidence that humans can in fact rise above human nature
Take for example the founding of the united states of america. It broke away
It was it was created by the enlightenment as a secular state in
Direct defiance to the old aristocratic systems of europe that shit was garbage
Yeah, they did it because they wanted to and nate. What does that mean?
Of course, they wanted to they were reacting to things they found in just because we have elevated our morality
And we're continually working all the time in philosophy to keep elevating human morality
I'm not I'm not gonna work through that. I'm not gonna work through this whole fucking
Thing i'm just gonna like just viewers at home just try as an extra try as a homework exercise to think about in what way
In what way the creation of the united states of america could have been, you know, what's the word?
Pragmatically motivated like for the Kurds creators like in what way could they have been driven?
Like, you know in in in some way that that serves their own self-interest. I'll bet you could think of a few
I don't throw jefferson and washington and adams under the bus
It's just saying saying saying that people should work for the greater good is just it's just asking the fucking impossible
Because people don't do that people people people act in accordance to maximize their own benefit
And like it just so happens. Well, not it's not entirely an accident
It's like I don't know just the way of things or whatever. It's a way things shake out that like
Generally people acting in their own benefit will will benefit the group at large, but not only it's a group
It's benefiting all the individuals. I will admit I will admit in a second that
No one is not selfish every single act we do is a direct action done in order to make our own lives better
I will happily admit that. Yeah, I just want people to consider the the large-scale ramifications of that
when I said when I said that um
Like where people like be people feeling happy about my stuff
Like that that isn't like a reason that I make anything. That's just a happy little bonus like a little extra
Like every time I get a comment saying man, this is really good. I really like this. I'm like, ah, cool
That's nice. You know and and and I and I I do admit that I sometimes make content because I know that people will like it
But not that's not ever the only reason I do it. It's never money. It's never other people
It's mostly to do with the fact that me wanting it to exist and it just so happens to benefit society
I don't think of it as as a like a thing that in in my head that I'm thinking all the time
Like it's strange that you think about it all the time, but it's fine. It's weird. I don't I don't do art
I don't do art for my own satisfaction because if no one was watching it
I wouldn't do it and I don't do art for other and I don't do art for other people's benefit because I don't care if it
Makes them happy. What I like. I don't know. I guess I do. I guess I do it to get their reaction or something
I guess I do it because I'm interested in people's reaction to it
I guess you get it like I do it because you want people to take you know to to value your opinion and I think that you're cool
I also just want to say that Davoo says that he agrees with Nate on the American Revolution and also with the enlightenment the rise of science
The way we swapped out right. I don't know what I'm already airing for slightly less terrible ideas like multiculturalism
Sometimes me and Davoo are absolutely on the same wavelength. Anyways, go ahead. Okay. Here's here's the thing
I'm not sure where I'm going with this. I'm still kind of sleepy. I'm man. It's been hours. I'm still sleepy. God damn, age wake up
Come on. No, no, no. Listen. Okay. Listen. I have this I have this idea. I don't know where I'm going with this
Okay, so there was this dude in his side to find out he was he was he was like super good at painting right and
Hitler
Yes
Oh
So he was he was really good at painting and he just if he just went with that instead of like trying to benefit
Society because he was a patriot and he wanted to like help the German people initially
So what is this lovey-dovey bullshit? Oh art will fix all the problems of the world. No, that's not that's not how it works
Also is very good at painting. What is your point? There's no way he's good
Nate I have a question to you about your about your mentality and okay
My thing is just listening to this whole time because I haven't really been saying much is that
I can understand you saying that you want people to consider and try and have some sort of motivation when they create things to
for the greater good and
pushing humanity forward but my question is do we as individuals even have the capacity to truly understand the
the grand impact of anything we do
Because like we I
Who knows what's going to happen with our content, you know
Even like 10 years after we're dead or 10 years down the road from now
Like we don't know how it's going to go out there and proliferate into the world
So we can't really see the far-reaching impacts of anything we do. So
Is it
Is it I think outside the scope of human perception to understand the grand impact of anything that we do has in the world and beyond that
I think it's it's it's um
It's it's something that the the fact that Nate is the one that's saying this and he's not an artist
Means he has like the time to think about that like artists. I mean, I'm not a fucking like drawing artist. That's true
I would consider my what I what I what I mean by that is that I think I think for us
Um thinking about the greater good, you know, it's not worth thinking about it's just an extra taxing thing
Like oh, how will this benefit humanity you just you just have to let it happen if it does happen to benefit humanity
That's great. Whatever
Sorry, I would rather let I would rather let Nate think about that and just just just you know
Think about that in in the big grand scale and just let me do my little dinky thing in my in my own little head
Just just going along doing whatever I'm doing and if it just so happens to benefit humanity, that's good
I don't want to have to think about what I'm doing. You can't think about that
You can't think about the greater good with in everything you do because you you never know what the fucking larger
Amifications are going to be you can have some idea, but you'll never really know
It's totally fine. There's no objective standard of what to work for and fucking it's just not even fucking human nature
Like you're if you're a human being you're going to be doing what you think is going to fucking just get you the best outcome
And like yeah for for a lot of people
Yeah, benefiting the whole is going to benefit the individual
But in that case
They're they're going to do what benefits the whole of humanity just naturally because it also benefits them like okay
That's just it's it's all you can do is just kind of go with the flow and follow your fucking human nature
And most of the time just the way that just the way that it happens to shake out
Most of the time if you if you do that most people what they do will benefit the the larger fucking society
Usually and that's the best that's the best we can hope for
I would say I would say that
Largely largely it's a pipe dream to imagine that everybody could be thinking about the greater good all the time
Like if hitler was thinking about the greater good
Maybe he wouldn't have done what he did like maybe he would have like
You know put german resources to to fixing the economy without having to kill a bunch of people
In his mind he was saying the greater good
Well, I mean yeah, but like the the greater good for like the entirety of humanity like like you can't imagine
I can't I can't imagine a world where people
Like all like the majority of people will be working towards the goal of that
You just have to have these few people because like most people they just they're just dumb
We're we're apes we you know, it's pessimistic to say and to think that
Like everybody will not be able to be on the same page of humanity, but I think sometimes you just have to concede that not
You know expecting other people to take on your worldview like that
Um and use it and think about it
Hang on hang on no, I am not I'm not expecting people to adopt my same world
I'm fucking sick of this subject. Fuck you Nate. This sucks. I hate this. How is this my fault?
I just said my opinion and everyone's freaking out about it's not my responsibility. It's funny. It's funny. It's a funny meme
I'm over it. I just want to say all I want to say is just that ben we clearly and I don't think this is totally fine
We clearly have a different view. Yeah of like the capabilities of human beings and all our differences stem from basically the fact that
You know, I sort of think that people can aspire to higher things or like can perceive it and you don't and I believe
There is a level above talented above loyal that a nigger can aspire to
That is a great quote from negi huga. Okay, uh,
I wanted to say that for the most part
I think most of humanity the best they can do is just not get in each other's way
But there are you know, several people that can actually greatly benefit humanity
And you have to sometimes realize which person you are and do that
I'm one of the people that I don't want to
Kindre other people and I'm just gonna do my own thing in my own little corner
Well, that's exactly what I would hope for if you think that you're an obstacle get the fuck out of the way
That's perfect. That's exactly right
I have like an obstacle
Hey, mage called herself an obstacle not man. She's she's our old ball and chain. She's the old ball and chain
Of the whole pcb. Excuse me. I identify as purple
Purple purple ball and chain
Yeah, purple isn't an object purple is a concept. Yes, exactly. I am a concept. Oh, okay a wavelength. She's a wavelength
Yeah, I have a cool cool ending statement for the whole podcast
Before if we get if if nobody has
Yeah, I think we're wrapping up in those part. Are we we've already been going for like an hour
Well, we need to do questions for a while and you know, we can make statements, but yeah
Yeah, I have a good ending statement. I would say that as as we are in the pcp
Um
In general we are more passionate than we are money-grubbing. Yeah when it comes to to our art. Yeah, but
Um, we are all very much procrastinators in making that art. That's true. That's true
We're always just sort of fucking around
Yeah, and that that's the that's the story of the pcp the procrastinators. That's our origin
Yeah
Fade out. Yeah fade out credits roll. Well fade out and then fade back in because we gotta do questions. Yeah, that's right
Okay, let's uh, all right. That feels pretty good. Let's let's just pull these questions here
Uh, let's see what we got I that came on so suddenly I didn't have a time to actually look at them ahead of time
Like I normally like to do so. Okay. Let's see what we got
Okay, here's a filler question while I look for a better one at jen is maku domaro this this guy's always had some questions
Um, that guy that guy helps me with pokemon. Shit. That guy gave me. Yeah, that guy gave me a that guy gave me a
shiny a shiny rallet
Yeah, he gave me a score for my birthday. He gave me a shiny rallet and a name
Guys my birthday is fiftieth of may but this is probably gonna come out after fiftieth of may give me
That's cinco de mal you were born on mexico day
It's sometimes gold goes along with like the fiennion mother's day because mother's day and the fiennion is the first sunday on may
So sometimes we've all done that thing and mage mother of the pcp
Okay, all right. I see what's going on here. My birthday is on easter sometimes
Oh, yeah, uh, ben uh, home. Europe's home a zombie man, right? Just like jesus understood basically
Okay, so, uh, jen is maku tomorrow asks, uh, what would you guys like the next from software game to be?
They're all done with dark souls forever pirate game pirate game pirate game with dark souls physics
I want I want but dark souls but pirates. I want to bet the best. Well, I want it. I want it to be like the
I just want it to be dark souls but on pirate ships. I just want pirate ships. I there's never been a good pirate game
They've all been sort of okay, but never really good. They would be the best people to make a pirate game
I've always held this opinion. I love uh, yeah, they could they could they're great. They can do mech games
They can do you know medieval games
I don't see the connection to like yes, they make good games
But why specifically are they the best ones to make a pirate game?
Is it just because you like pirates and you like from software?
So obviously they're their games going to be the best. They made they made a great
If they made bloodborne if they made bloodborne but with pirates and pirate ships like moving ones then
You know, well, I'm just saying I basically like any any genre like with the dark souls formula applied to it
With the level of craft they put in I would pretty much instantly love because I love playing this game so much
I really want to make demon souls last night. I really want them to make kingsfield 4
Or whatever you played any of the kingsfield though. Yeah, I played one on digi bros that is like months late and hasn't come out yet
I think oh and boy. I think it was kingsfield 1 or 2. It fucking sucked
It was so bad
Well, here's here's another question at monkey away our frequent commenter says uh hitler used meth. Why don't you use meth?
Well, you know relevant solid. I mean just look at the benefits. Just look at the benefits
You got to you know, unite the german people. I know I know why it's because I just I don't have the courage
I don't have the courage that hitler had
I I agree. I feel like that with a lot of hard drugs and just drugs in general
Your cowards your cowards don't even don't even do meth like hitler
You're goddamn right. I have a joke for this bit. Yes
No, I don't
Well, the joke was you the joke was you I guess shout out to hitler for being a special member of this podcast
Yeah, shout out to hitler
Ha
Another guy at
Ladder and at the ladder analyst who's a guy I see commenting on just asked like your favorite adolf hitler quote
What's all the hitler questions?
I guess he is a popular guy monkey jones
Well, no, well, maybe it was because his birthday was only nine days before the recording of this podcast
Really? That's true. Yeah, April 20th shares his birthday with christian weston chandler as a matter of fact
Everyone was born on weed day. Yeah
That's that's great. Oh, and divu divu says that hitler's death day is tomorrow
Really? Oh, wow. What a celebration. Well, he's not actually dead. He's not actually dead. This was not intentional
And I did not know all the days
Also divu's birthday weird. I'm just saying mage. You were you were born in europe, which is basically like being born in germany
It's basically like being hitler. So i'm just saying it's very similar. It's very simple
Hey, here's a here's a super relevant question for today's episode. Uh at tpcrasnators
Uh, what's the name? Oh at jamie step 47 says ever considered getting a sponsor for the podcast
What is that? I'd certainly consider it. What would that even mean?
Like what would that be about us? I would just have like a solid like 10 minutes of hitler references and then someone asked about a sponsor
Oh, our sponsor for today's episode mind comp
Like in the middle of the podcast we take a minute and plug harry's razors or whatever
Yeah, that'd probably be it. I I'd do it man. I'd do it if the product was good. I would do it for the money
Yeah, I would do it for money. Yeah, I would do it for money. I don't care
Like I don't think we're losing a lot of integrity by doing that on this particular show
You know like like splicing that into there's none to lose
The pcb doesn't have much integrity to give up in the first exactly
Something like a like a I don't know like a fancily edited anime analysis video for example
Like there's not I don't see a place for like an ad in that but here
Yeah, I don't see the problem. I'd do it in a heartbeat if there was a good a good offer
Thing that I really like that I haven't bought for myself in a while. There's like these this little box and it has like yes
It's food
But it's like healthy food, but it's also very tasty food and it's and it comes in the box
And I forget what it's called. So I guess that's good because you know, I'll be I'll be kid cuisine
And no, no, no, it's like it's a very cute short name any here
Kid cuisine
It's some sort of insert word box. Uh, I don't know my nerd box. There we go
Get a nerd food delivered straight to your mouth or something like that. I know bento box. Yeah. No, not bento. I'm not
You were just saying you wanted you wanted the anime star
Yeah, because that would be cool anyhow
I'd like a box called get bento
I
Agreed. Oh, that would be good. Yes. It's just a asian bart simpson on the cover
Just just like uh, mr. Sparkle dr. Sparkle. Yeah. Yeah
Mr. Sparkle
Yeah, simpson. Yeah, I would be I would be fine with like, you know being sponsored by dad because I freaking love the thing
And I love the food they have because it's healthy and it's tasty. We should we should email every every corporation
It's a product you believe in. Yes, right
Uh, yeah, maybe we should look into that. Uh, okay
Here's a question that might be my favorite question
We've ever gotten and I know this is just because it pertains to my interest. You guys might not agree
But uh at gregory barry 2 says, uh, at what point do you feel analyzing an artwork crosses the line into conspiracy slash headcanon territory?
immediately
I I mean uh that uh to me that that feels like kind of like ben's pornography test
We're like it's hard. You like you just have to use common sense
You know, there's no like definition of when you're going too far
But you really just have at some point you need to step back and say like this is not what makes the pornography test up
By the way, that's not my invention. Don't be so humble ben. Don't be so well. I won't I would say
I would say it's probably if you ever have to even like
Tangentially reference anything outside that that's not in the text directly. You're probably crossing a line
Says the man who analyzed big horse at great detail
Well
That was total bullshit. I'm yeah, exactly. But it was the best thing ever. I'm not saying it loses value
Yeah, it goes from analysis to something else. That's pretty good
Like that's a pretty good guideline like if if you're referring if you're referring to something else
Like to inform your reading of the text something that is like not actually suggested in the text at all
then yeah, you're probably reaching and
Like unless you have really good reason like like unless like you knew that like the author was like friends with some
Other guy who wrote something and maybe they were tight or something
Unless you can't point to the thing itself and show me
I think yeah, I think yeah, I think it's fine as I think it's fine as long as at the end you say well, it's just a theory
Evangelion yeah that one and because they thought it was cool and whatnot and then
Trying to find meaning and
Reasons and whatever but like yeah, it was just because people thought like the creator side. It was cool
I would say that it's totally fine to have a yeah go ahead. You can go first
That's going into like like uh, are you reading the the the the thing right?
And I think it's it's fun to analyze like oh, what does this mean like thinking about it?
If it's in the thing you can you can ponder it. I don't mind people pondering something. Here's here's the thing. Yeah, okay
No, no you go. Okay. I was just gonna say that I am totally fine with people coming up with whatever cockamamie schemes
They want you know like like some of that game theory shit about like nests being sands like like you can go nuts
Go ahead and do it, but like I feel like the crucial step that is missing ben. Stop vaping stop fucking vaping god damn it
He's vaping for the passion man. You gotta let him do it bad
Yeah, yeah, you think I do you think you think I do this
For the money
It's for the craft it's for the craft for the love of the craft the artisan my artisan my artisan juice
Artisan vapes artisan juice
That I steeped myself in a still in in my in my granny's basement
Oh god, okay, but here's what I was gonna say that what I feel okay
So go ahead and come with ever crazy schemes you want
But I feel like the step that people forget so often is like after you've presented all this stuff
You have to do take the final step and say like okay
Now that we've brought all this information up does this actually seem reasonable in the slightest if the answer is no
You then say okay into the trash it goes. We were reaching on all of that
Please forget it like just you can keep in mind, but it was not true. So just move on it's not do not keep this here
When people reach it's when they reach like that and then pretend that they're not reaching
When they obviously are sure and it's even worse when a video like that like gets really big
And then everyone just starts quoting it as gospel when it's like
Anytime somebody's headcanon becomes popular
Um, that's when people start getting angry that the headcanon is real is not real
You know what that's the only time it's really bad
Yeah, major that whole I can relate to this so bad because the whole like uh, hey meditons ghost was a female shit
It's not it was never stated. It was never proven
But someone headcanon it it became popular people are now
Pronouncing it as the gospel and I have to deal with this cannon for years
I have to deal with this on my on my
Most popular video that has almost one million views and people just chime in it is like oh
The mediton ghost was the female so is he male or female and I have to deal with this every single day
Yeah, mediton is david bow
Okay, but you know what you know what?
I don't blame people sometimes because like things like solar and like people thought he was the son of guin
Like there there was reasons to come up with that conclusion and the thing is like dark souls is deliberately vague
So like I I totally excuse stuff like that like they were just thinking about that and then like when when dark souls 3 comes out
And just proves like no incorrect like that was never the case. Yeah, well, it's always there's only a problem when
That's fine. I love heads too
Yeah, yeah, but that's the thing a lot of people they get a headcanon and then they get upset instead of surprise when it's not real
Like being a woman like the thing about crocodile and one piece being a woman, but yeah, yeah
Come on people. Come on. There's no evidence at all
Like if it ever comes like saying if say hey, are you were you ever born a woman?
Like for some reason this character is talking about that and he says actually no
I was born a man as you can see I'm still a man and then it's like everyone's going. Oh
Oh
Okay, like I it'll be okay. It'll be okay if they just say oh, well, I guess that's not real
But some people will get mad and they'll be like fuck this
Show
Drop like when it comes to like reading into like like theory crafting like I think you can
I think you can read whatever like meaning into the work you want like you can like you can read a thing and
And look at like I don't you you can you can take whatever lesson from it that you want
Or like you can you can look at it and be like uh, like when the when the characters do such and such
They you know, they're they're that's an embody like they're doing what they're doing there is like
Ah, it's typified by the Dunning Kruger effect or something or you can but then like
You can't it's not fair to do you like you do that with your own interpretation of the work
But it crosses the line when you read that into like the author's intentions
And like
Intention versus interpretation
Yeah, it's not you you can't you can't just you can't like put shit on the author if you don't have like real good thing
Like real like real solid like textual or like or like like word of god reasons to think them. It's not fair
The the most pointless arguments people can have is like
Which canon is the correct one? It's like my head canon is the correct one. No, my head canon is the correct one
Well, that's just pure masturbation guys. Did you know that everyone in undertale is a black gay trans woman?
I read human tana dude. I'm a big fan of human tail actually
Wait, is that like an actual comic? I thought it was a tumblr. It was a tumblr. Yeah
What else would it be? Let's be honest when when you uh
Yeah, like when like when so like when someone like game theory comes out with like uh
Is sands and papyrus you see you see sands and papyrus are very
Similar to like the theory of the two halves of the brain to the left brain and the right brain like you can like
You can interpret that if that way you you can look at that and be like
Huh the dichotomy of sands and papyrus kind of reminds me of the left brain right brain dichotomy like that's fine
But and I and I and I don't even think that that game theory is a particularly bad offender at this
Like there are much worse people about this, but then if you go on to be like
Like that was the point then you're retarded like then you're retarded like unless there's textual unless there's textual evidence
Unless unless there's textual or metatextual evidence linking
Like somehow suggesting that some kind of connection with the brain
You're just stupid if you think if you then go on to be like oh, I see this is what it was meant to be
Like I actually I actually quite like game theory because I like to see how he's connecting things
Yeah, I don't actually mind game theory that much. Yeah, I love I love a man perform mental gymnastics for you know
Like 20 minutes at a time. I've never watched game theory and really thought that they were trying I was being sarcastic by the way
I actually really like they're one about the simpsons about finding spring field. It's actually really good
And I like it that that one is good. Yeah, sure. So we're good
I do generally like a game theory or two that the mental gymnastics is fun
Like just to see how far you can connect the dots if you felt like it
But how am I with fucking mental pirouettes? Can I do off this goddamn fucking it's it's it's an exit
It's a brain exercise. It's like yeah, all those things. Yeah, I like but then I like it out there
I like an out there interpretation of things. I think that's valuable. Yeah
Yeah, I never like accepted them as like true for whatever. It's really fun to see how he can you know
All I'm saying is watching games theories like watching ancient aliens
Yeah, all I'm saying is people just just keep that final step where you say, okay, we heard all this
Is this reasonable? If not, you know, treat it just a theory. Yeah, treat it just a theory
Thank you, uh, Gregory Barry for that incredibly juicy question
I'm gonna put that down as my favorite question. We've ever gotten everyone
That's the standard of a question that you should be asking. I'm here. Oh, let's clap it
What was the question how what was the phrasing of it?
The the phrasing was uh by at gregory berry 2 at what point do you feel analyzing and artwork crosses the line into conspiracy slash headcanon territory?
Real solid
But we yeah, yeah
Uh, okay. Let's yeah, I got like two more little ones. Uh at pond pondi dator at pondi dator asks
I have literally no friends or aspirations. What do I do here?
Don't recommend suicide unless you have a simple and easy method to suggest
make some
Yeah, make some friends or some aspirations. You gotta have that's really easy to say though
Okay, well, actually surely you can do one or the other
I think aspire to make a friend. There you go. We solved one of the problems right there
You can't just say that like if he's actually
Like seriously though, I think something to do if you don't have aspirations is to kind of just start like consuming a lot of media
And then kind of start
I think he probably does that looking looking for ins maybe but like doing it in a way that you're kind of like looking
For something to kind of resonate with you beyond the fact of just like i'm sitting here passively consuming something
I think that's like that idea. Yeah, most of my ideas come from the desire to emulate something
I find really impressive although that is a bit skewed towards the idea that this person should have artistic aspirations
Maybe he could start reading. Well, I mean, I mean, you know
Because like if you watch if you watch like an anime or something about basketball
You're just like, man, I want to go fucking shoot some hoops. Like you can do that too basket. Yeah. Yeah, I guess
I think I think the the the thing you should do if you're in a situation like that
You don't know if you have any
Any because I felt like this if you don't know that you have any aspirations any goals any desires to have a skill
In any, you know way
Just think of about what you already do and what you enjoy doing and if you know if it's you know something
You know, you you probably have one thing that you think well, I could never make a career of that
But maybe you could just look into it. I was something like eating
If it's something like I really like
Um eating then maybe I don't know become a chef
Something something just just choose anything that you like already and then work with start doing something you like
Yeah, yeah, even if you think oh, I'm not really good at this or whatever. Uh, don't let that you know
Be
Hold on words. Just good. Yeah. Yeah. Don't don't don't don't let that don't just try to say is don't let your memes be dreams
Get out there and live them. Yeah
Don't let the lack of quality if you might think, you know, you lack of quality discourage you because like your lack of quality
Because honestly a lot of people
Especially artists like to be down on themselves thinking. Oh, they're not good enough for whatever they're doing
And the feeling of not being good enough is probably gonna haunt you and a lot of other people myself included probably until
The days end for me. So
I don't think you'll ever reach the point
At least a lot of people probably will never reach the point where they're satisfied with themselves and their quality of content
No, but it's the journey. Yeah, it's the journey. That's right. That's right seeing yourself improve over time
Sometimes like oh, hey taking like a drawing from two years ago and comparing to a current drawing
Oh, like, hey, I never noticed how much I've improved. That's kind of very satisfying
And like I will say about
About like watching yourself improve. Don't think about that. Don't don't think consciously
Oh, if I do stuff, I'll improve because then you'll you'll you'll you'll see like one week ago
And then you'll find no improvement and you'll feel like nothing is changing and then you'll get
Just just do what you'll do. Yeah, do whatever you enjoy doing and just do it over and over again
And then in a couple years just see what's gonna happen because something will probably happen
Whatever you whatever you feel like doing whatever you want to do take just take it one like mini projects at a time
Just set yourself like one little goal like I'm gonna draw this really small
I'm gonna I'm gonna draw this thing or I'm gonna sing this thing or something and then just do don't worry about anything else
Just do whatever it takes to make it happen. Just just do it make it happen be like, okay. This is how that came out
Um, let me now. Let me try this this next thing. Yeah, just just focus just focus on the task at hand
Yeah, and if it's like some sort of like little something that you put on like on the internet
And like if no one pays attention to it at first or like, you know, you get some discouraging comments
Don't pay mine to those everyone who starts
Like at the beginning has to deal with it
I would say I would say just like just set yourself set yourself
Just set yourself a goal just just set yourself some little goal
Just think of something you can do some attainable goal that you think that you're confident you can reach and then
Do it for yourself do it because you want to and yeah, I would suggest even if you're starting at something
And it is something that's like post-able online. I would say like don't put it online like immediately
I think if you just kind of keep it to yourself for a while like and let your it was an interesting
Kind of metaphor that someone once said that like
Like your creativity when it's young is like kind of like a person when they're young when they're a baby
They have like the fontanella in their head and it's soft and like if it gets hurt it can like kill you
Your creativity is the same way if someone fucking like shoots you down right when you're starting and you're still kind of soft
It could destroy all of your like
Motivation to keep going
But if you just like keep it to yourself and just kind of like take pride in your little steps forward over and over again
In like six months later
Then you start to post things online as someone comes by and is like oh, it's gay
It's like, you know, you've been doing it enough that you've had enough confidence in yourself. It's like, I don't fucking care
You're gay and if you're just and if you're just starting out don't compare to like pros because there's no point
All right, just just compare to yourself just only and compete with yourself
and like
Dad, I want to say I want to say because we've only been talking about skills the the friend thing
I will
It's really it's really important to know to know like if you if you find skills too
Troublesome and you're like, I don't know I just want to I just want to have a friend like if you have one or the other
Here's how you make a friend you either if you if you go to school
You just act like a complete retard and hope somebody notices like go out
Go out expecting to be a laughing stock and nobody likes you because that's how you already feel
You already feel that nobody likes you. So if you just do some loud shit
He hates himself. Good. It's only up from here
Yeah, but you have to you have to make your help yourself be heard because if you're just like a quiet person
You don't talk to anyone don't have any friends
People will just think of you as the person who doesn't want to talk to anybody
If you go out into the world and you like
Display a willingness
To make a fool of yourself and not give a shit
Even if you do in fact make a fool of yourself like you still look like the cool guy
Because because you were willing to do it like making making a fool of yourself is no big deal
But like not giving a shit about making a fool of yourself is is is is the big deal and everyone likes that and also
Also for people who are not in school if you're if you're like not in school
You're you're just living at home. You don't have a job. You don't know what you're doing with your life
You don't know you don't know any people you don't you can't just hang out in a bar or whatever
Uh get a job like go just get a menial job and you will meet a coworker and that will be your friend
You you'll you'll just work through it like that. Oh wait, that's always there's always smaller steps to go to to find
Let me let me get a job is actually great advice. I was gonna say nothing else going on
What I was going to suggest is just like I'm going to assume that you are a uh an able-bodied
You know like like high school or college age person
And and that you're in the situation like that and you have the ability to do these things
So that being the case I would say yeah
Like find first of all you got to find an interest and then just go find the group around that is involved in that interest
Like a club or something
But really the essence here is to put yourself in situations
Where people cannot ignore you where you where you are imposing on people
So they have to deal with you because like it or not those people will become your friends
And they leave them no choice in the matters leave them no choice
I just want to input a caution like don't get too emotionally invested in the first person you make friends with
And like don't get too attached as well
Like even if it's a friend online, especially if it's a friend online don't get too attached with them initially
Even if you're hitting off very well because
Some people are crap and sometimes some people might feel
Like like you're smothering them and they might start, you know backing away from you. So
We should probably have like a whole podcast of friends. Like how to make friends. That's a good one. That's a great idea
Yeah, there's a lot there's a lot to unpack there may just may just really write about that because like you can
You got to get like a starter friend sometimes like a ben saint and work your way up to like the best guy ever
Don't worry ben there is so sometimes you can train your ben saints to be better sometimes you can elevate them too
sometimes
That's such a sick burn. I can't even
Okay, well, I'm not even I'm not even mad. I'm just like
I just want to I just want to close out that question if we're done with that
Okay, that because he said like, you know, I don't know if I'm ever gonna
You know have a passion or have friends, um, especially with passion
But also with friends too, uh, if if it's bothering you that you don't have it
That means that you can because if you had no passion, you wouldn't be worried about it
Yeah, so there is there is a passion there waiting to be unlocked. You just haven't stumbled upon it yet
Also like movies anime and whatever media like to romanticize the whole passion thing
Like love is never like how you know
The movies describe it and same with like friendships and passions like you don't have to be super into it
It doesn't have to consume your whole life and you don't have to tear yourself over it
Like if you're just like, you know happy with what what little you have
That's fine. Don't don't stress yourself like for not caring more or wanting to do more or whatever
Do it in your own pace
And and very very last thing on this subject. I just wanted to say that I have a last thing as well
Okay, I'll say my first last thing you can say your last last thing
Uh, I was just gonna say keep in mind you're I I'm getting I would guess that you're fairly young
Or at the very least like you haven't really established yourself in the world yet
Like the the confidence to you know go out and do things that comes with just like
Doing like having achieved things in your life
Uh really makes the rest of this a lot easier like the rest kind of just falls into place
So I would emphasize achieving some goals like find out what you want to do and work towards that
And even just the act of working towards it will give you inherent confidence to like just get better all this whole life
Shit, you'll be better off right and the last thing I want to say is that if you if you do actually want to kill yourself
Here's a here's a quick
No, no, no, no
Bring that up. Well, yeah, he's like don't recommend suicide unless you have a simple and easy message
Here's the easy way to do it right get all the savings you have
And then buy a one uh one uh one way plane ticket to a third world country a random third world country
And then just uh exist and if and if you're okay if you can if you can survive then
You deserve to to live and then you can do cool things and you'll be like real cool
Uh, that's a cool idea because like if you're about to kill yourself
Like just Jesse was saying this the other day instead just start a new life somewhere else and see how it goes
Using like all your money because like then you're not dead. You get to try again at the very least might work out
I've literally I literally
I I did the I went to google earth and I did uh show me a random place and I clicked on it
I was like, yeah, I could go there. I guess because I was feeling real down at the time
I was thinking I could I could just buy a plane ticket there. I have the money
But then I kept spinning it and then it was like
There's too many
And now i'm looking at that too many to choose and beam in my room real enticingly. That's uh, I don't have any beams in my house
That's why I'm
Oh, thank god for the new code standards. No no exposed beams
Uh, okay. Well, let's go to our last question here by at mr. No name 2001
Asks, what's the worst thing any of you have ever done? The answer is this podcast
That's for a listen everybody
The answer the answer is um
The answer is my little pony analysis and if you want to hear more of my my thoughts on that go listen
Go listen to the latest fucking uh rowdy fuckers cop killers where we dive deep
We dive deep into our innermost feelings on that subject. I actually have a story. I want to say I think that's the worst thing
I was like six or seven years old and there was this girl and she had a lot of like
Little miniature animal things and I was really big into those little miniature animal things
And like she had like I think I saw like all of them and they were really cute
But um one day I was walking around and I saw it was dropped like somewhere on the street
And I knew it was hers because no one else had like this little zebra one
And I picked it up and I was like
You know what if you're not going to take care of it. I might as well keep it and I never gave it back
Give it to a good home. Yeah. Hey, hopefully you took care of it. I I mean that's basically what ash did with charmander
That's true. Hey, okay. You know what I've got one since this reaction down
This is I think this is actually the the evilest thing I've ever done one time when me and ben were kids
We were just kind of like lying on the couch sort of like parallel to each other and then just for absolutely no reason
I just heel dropped ben in the stomach for no reason. I just thought it would be funny
Really funny
It was very funny actually no, I was terrified because I really felt my slip myself slip into sociopathy for a second there
I really just lost all all you know, like companionship with humankind and just decided to hurt someone for fun
No, not okay. Don't don't do it. Very. I'm sorry ben
Yes, I'm not notice. I'm not forgiven notice. I'm not forgiven. No
We'll we'll we'll see about that. I'm gonna hold that one over you for a little longer
Do you remember that ben? Do you actually remember that? I'm just curious not like I remember
I think I remember like the day that it happened. I don't really remember like it was that traumatic it happening
I because it like I didn't see it coming. You know, yeah for no reason. It was yeah
Yeah, it was just like a sudden like oh god. I am in so much pain and I can't breathe
I was such a bad ass back then
Go back. I have to go back. Yeah
to those days
Yeah, I've always stretched this for almost two hours. Oh, all right. Hang on. I I have a I have the worst thing
I ever did. Okay. It's a pretty big one
The when I was a little boy and then the school cafeteria
um
You have like your meal and then you can have like a pudding a dessert thing
And I always chose the crackers because I liked I like savory things
So I chose the crackers there's a little two pack of crackers
You put them on the on your tray you go and eat them
But I I always I always wanted to eat them in the playground afterwards
So I put them in my pocket and I ate them in the playground even though I'm not allowed to
That's the worst thing I've ever done. Wow
And uh, I still feel remorse
Really?
You're such a bad ass dude. Did you did you only do that once? Actually, no
There's actually more to that because I used to do that all the time until
To the point where the lunch lady would search my pockets for it because I wasn't allowed to to eat it in the playground
In no repeat offender in in I know like all throughout like elementary school middle school and high school
um
I like
You could you could buy lunch at school and lunch came with like a roll and you would like take your tray
And you would go through the thing and you would take one item from each thing and like the first station was like rolls
And I would just go and like take rolls all the time
I would start in the line get in the line take a roll and then leave the line and go back to my seat
And like I just did this like my for so long because I love that bread. I fucking love it's great
That bread was so good. It was so like doughy and just like yeah powdery and just like
It's just so succulent and like people would always tell me like ben. You're just stealing you're just stealing there
And I would be like I don't I don't like I don't care
Yeah, like for a while I tried to justify like no the roll is not actually lunch like it's not a part
It's like it's it's like its own thing. It's just like a thing that comes with lunch
I don't have to really buy it
But eventually I was just like lunch is not lunch. Let's be serious
Eventually I was just like I just want it and I don't want to pay for it
So I'm gonna take it because I think I deserve to have the things that I want without paying for them
I think that that is about pirating games. Yeah, I just do it. I don't care. I do not care. Yep
All right, does tom want to share a story. Are you a bad person to tom?
Let's see. I think my story is kind of similar to mage
I think but I don't know is like it's like taking advantage of stupid people really a crime
I don't know
Because what what I did is is that back in the day when pokemon cards were huge you made a patreon
Well, that was a terrible mistake as you can clearly see now now all my passions become about the money
No, so I pokemon cards were a big thing and I didn't have any pokemon cards
But what I did have at the time what's a boy to do
Exactly it was it was a big problem
So I well the only things I had that even slightly resemble pokemon cards
I remember like back when before anyone knew what pokemon was
Kentucky fried chicken had little like kids meals that came with pokemon stuff
And one of them was a deck of playing cards like just like regular deck of cards. I had pokemon on them
I don't know how this worked
But I had the the brilliant idea of writing in sharpie just like fake stats and moves on all these pokemon cards
And then traded them to people for real pokemon cards and it worked. That's their fault. That is their fault
What did you trade them for pokemon cards? It was it was just like from kfc
Like you know, they get like they have like kids meals that come with little toys
It was a deck of like playing cards like ace and five of clubs and shit like that
But I just wrote in marker pokemon moves on them and traded them to people for real pokemon cards
And it worked
Okay, but I went I got advanced later a couple years later
Uh like the third set or something came out and my neighbor at the time who was a dick and we hated him
But we had to hang out with him because he was the only kid in the neighborhood
He had lieutenant surge ritu and I thought it was the coolest shit ever
And I was like I want this fucking card and he wouldn't trade for it
So me and my sister devised the perfect plan to get it from it because because he was an idiot
what we did is we went home we went on my dad's computer and
We looked up an image of the card and I drew it on a piece of paper
And then I drew it
I copied it down as like in like crayon and pencil or whatever and then I we went to his house and we convinced him that
It was the original card that they eventually made copies of and traded him the fake one for the real one and it worked
It was amazing. Oh my god. That's the ultimate. My dad works for a nintendo story. That's the ultimate
That's crazy that that worked. So you have you have a literal history of forgery. I do
Yep
I'm working on drawing my hundred dollar bill right now
Going to go down in the bank. It's going to be great
In crayon, of course. Yeah, exactly. That's working. Awesome. No. No those people all deserved it. They all deserved it
I don't care. Crayons should die. How do why why do we have crayons?
Yeah, good questions. Crayons are great. I want crayons right now. They're good. They're good crayons, but they're not the kind you're
accustomed to, you know, like pastels are technically crayons, I think aren't they?
I'm talking like the like oil pastels. If they're not called crayons, they're not crayons, my friend
Crayon is the brand. Well
Squares are rectangles. Maybe pastels or crayons. I don't know. Squares were rectangles
Okay, well before we go for another three hours on this, uh, you know, this is some deep shit, man
This crayons conundrum. Let's uh, let's wrap this up. So everybody send us more questions at tpcrasnators
We do this on saturday. That's where we'll be posting. We answer those questions. Thanks for listening everybody and we will see you next time
Bye
See you later, everybody
Right now