I'm going to bless that guy that son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch.
One, two...
Leave that in.
One, two, three, sync.
Hello, and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
It's Sunday, the 10?
No, it's Friday.
12.
I'm Ben Saint and Gibbontake is here.
I'm here.
That's true.
What's going on, Gibb?
Well...
What's been going on?
Well, you know, I've been looking up and looking down, and I just haven't seen anything really.
It's sort of like the week sort of flew by and nothing happened at all.
That is so relatable.
I, too, have had my head buried deep in the sand.
You know, Talbart.
Yeah.
I found his Twitter has another Twitter linked that I guess is the guy that runs it.
This guy, Peanards, and I guess he doesn't really tweet that much.
His last tweet was like a year ago.
All right, he tweets like, but he did a couple of funny tweets like a year ago, or no, it
was only like a month or two ago.
Never mind.
One of them was like, here, I'll just read it right now.
I was looking at them and they were really funny.
No, where was it?
I can't find it.
Gibb, I'm just really sorry.
My bit failed.
Yet more mysteries.
Yet more drama.
The drama of the missing tweet.
No, it was a really funny tweet about like role playing as an ostrich and putting your
head in the ground.
No.
Hang on.
I'm going to hit at Peanard.
I'm going to use the Twitter search function ostrich.
Come on.
Here we go.
December 16th, 2022.
All you care about is your stupid ostrich role play bullshit.
I'm not listening.
I'm bent over.
My head buried in six inches of sand, completely dead by suffocation.
One retweet.
32 likes.
This is Talbart.
This is Talbart's material before he started chopping up Ben Shapiro, Joe Rogan.
Well, I've been big mad this week, as you know.
I've been big mad this week about some stuff, about some old PCP stuff, and I'm cooled off
from it.
And I got to say, I was very unhelpful.
It was very pointless.
As usual, it was very pointless and foolish and maybe a little embarrassing to be big
mad on the internet.
It is.
And that's how it goes.
Do you want me to briefly summarize?
Well, it's a blood feud between you and Jesse over, I don't know.
Yeah.
Basically, okay, it boils down to basically nothing.
It was pretty much just me getting mad.
All right.
We were basically done with the Radcon stuff, right?
Everything was done.
Nate, I don't know if we've even said this on the show yet, but Nate actually finished
the OVA.
It's actually done, and we have it.
And it's uploaded, it's just not published yet.
We could literally be watching it right now.
So it was like, wow, we're done.
And then Jesse, at the very last minute, said, hey guys, I got to claim my gas costs.
I paid for gas to get there.
Reimbursed my gas.
Oh, oops, looks like I have to get my girlfriend to get a letter in the mail from her bank
to prove the cost of a hotel stay or something.
And that's going to be, it's going to be another business week before I can get that
to you.
Sorry.
And that, you know, it held it up for a week.
And you know, this did make me really mad, and I do think it's bullshit, but I did kind
of blow up and go ballistic and say, you're lying, there's no, it's all fake.
There are, this is just, this is just a time buying ploy.
This is, this is just a scheme.
This is a, this is a trick that you're pulling.
I did, I did say all that.
It turned out not to be true.
It turned out to be the case.
Yeah.
But you know what, I don't know.
I don't know.
No, you should have said, I wouldn't change a thing.
I wouldn't change a thing.
No, listen.
I wouldn't have, I wouldn't have missed it for the world or some stupid thing like
that.
Wouldn't have missed, the, the, the, I mean, listen, here's the thing, you know, yeah,
I guess it turned out that the receipts weren't fake, but you know, they could have been
and that's what's so scary.
That says a lot about society that it could, it could have been true.
I don't need to, to like you about it.
No.
You seem to understand that what you were doing was a bit silly, but like over the top.
Um, yeah.
In the end, there was nothing to be gained by complaining and definitely nothing to be
gained by, uh, um, throwing, throwing around out allegations.
So you know, whatever, uh, def, did I need to post about it on Twitter?
No, definitely didn't need to do that.
I forgot, I forgot one of Nate, Nate bought me, uh, I think I've mentioned that Nate bought
me George Washington's rules of etiquette.
It's a little red book that has like, it's kind of bullshit.
Actually, cause it's, it's not like he like swore by these rules.
It's just like when he was a kid, when he was like 14, he read a bunch of books about
etiquette and he just like took notes and he wrote down a bunch of rules in like a notebook.
And this is just like those notes that he wrote down.
So he didn't even come up with them.
But um, one of them is like, uh, what, what is it, speak, speak not of, um, speak not
evil of those who are not present for it is unjust.
And uh, you know, the thing about it is even if everything I said, I mean, okay, hang on.
Not to backpedal, but I didn't, I didn't, I didn't lie.
I didn't lie on Twitter.
I didn't, I know that what I was accusing Jesse of turned out not to be true, but I
didn't lie and make false allegations.
All I said was that, was that I was not beat was that, was that there was, there was whatever.
I mean, what you said implied that there was something happening and because people didn't,
people did not have the full context of the conversation.
They read your tweet and I was like, oh, I guess Jesse's the bad guy.
I guess Jesse is like, this is confirmed because you're, you're saying it.
Well, all right.
He wouldn't, he wouldn't, he wouldn't show me the proof.
He said he had proof.
He wouldn't show me the proof.
He did that not because he didn't have the proof.
He did that to make me mad.
And you know what?
It worked.
He got me.
He freaking got me.
I got mad on the internet.
Um, yep.
Anyway, anyway, uh, whatever.
But even, even, even if everything that I said he was doing turned out to be true,
it would still have been a pretty ugly look.
It's a pretty ugly look to go to Twitter about it.
So, you know, I don't know.
Sorry.
Uh, that's all, I guess that's all I have to say.
Did you apologize to Jesse?
No.
Could you do that?
Come on.
No, no.
Do a little, do a little DM.
Do a little, I'm sorry.
I'm, I actually, I actually won't do that.
I actually will not do that.
Thanks for listening to the pro Christmas podcast, everybody.
Uh, I don't, I don't care what Jesse thinks.
I don't, I don't care if he's mad at me or, or if I was unjust.
I'm not, I'm not sorry for his sake.
I'm sorry for my sake.
And, uh, I guess anyone who, uh, was annoyed by me,
that's, yeah, that's it.
I don't, I don't like Jesse.
I have not liked Jesse for years.
I don't care if the bridge is burned a good riddance,
but that's not an excuse to be, to be a punk about it.
So, so that's what I have to say about that.
Um, anyway, just want to get out ahead of that
because there were a bunch of comments being like,
can't wait to hear Ben rage on the next podcast.
And then I'm over it.
I'm over my rage.
Sorry.
If you want to hear me rage, you can go and listen to my
ranting on a Twitch about it, uh, uh, the last couple of streams that I did,
which, um, my stream viewership is up by the way.
My streams were doing pretty well.
It might be, it might be, it might be because I've been ranting and raving about that lately,
or it might also be because I'm playing battle network
and the freaking battle network collection is coming out.
And I guess that's like in the news, it might be boosting my numbers as well.
The last stream I did was like,
it was at like the same viewership as like I used to get back in like 2019
when I was, uh, you know, when I had a little thing going.
So that was cool.
Yeah.
Be nice if that would keep up.
Guess we'll see.
It might be, might also be because I've been very regular about my schedule.
I've been keeping to the Monday, Friday evenings thing.
So people know where to find me.
That's pretty cool.
Uh, yeah, I guess that's pretty cool.
Yeah.
Do you think that's pretty cool?
Would you, would you, I think it's pretty neat.
I mixed out at 12 viewers last stream.
I was getting about like the, the first couple streams I did for a few weeks there,
I was getting maybe like 20.
I was maybe hitting like the mid 20s.
And then the last one I did, I was up at like, uh, I think I almost hit six.
And I think it did briefly hit 60.
I was like, sure, sure.
Nice.
I'm wondering if, if my streams, because I changed, uh, the timing people saying,
oh, it's too early to do a stream.
You've like, I appeared as soon as it was over.
So I did the stream later and I got exactly the same number of people,
but different people, something maybe.
So I guess Saturday is potentially not a good day to do it.
Or nobody cares about a little old cab or fire emblem.
I mean, I can't speak to what people think about fire emblem.
Saturday, I don't know.
Saturday evening seems just as good as Friday evening.
I actually was, I'm not really sure whether I think that like weekdays or weekends
are better.
I think different people watch Twitch on those two different kinds of days for different reasons.
Yeah.
Some people watch a stream because the job is boring and they don't need to work.
So they're just like, ah, fuck it.
I'm just sitting there.
I think a bunch of people have told me like, yeah, I'm watching this at work.
Like, yeah, this is, this is getting me through the work day or whatever.
Maybe I could move it into some part of the week.
I don't know, the viewers aren't at the point, but it's nice to get viewers.
Are you streaming, do you do it once a week?
Just once, yeah.
Yeah.
I think I used to do it once a week, back in 2019 or so.
And I think now, I don't know, I'm doing two a week now, and it seems to be good.
And I'm trying to keep my, I kept the last one to three hours.
I started getting like cramps in my abdomen around three hours.
And I was like, I'm going to take this as a sign from God to cut it at the three hour mark
before my average viewer number dips.
Abdomen?
Like from sitting?
Like in my guts.
I don't, yeah, I just started, I don't know, I started getting like cramps in my guts.
I'm not, I'm not sure why they actually like went away right after I stopped streaming.
So maybe you were tensing that muscle.
When you were looking at Mega Man.
Maybe it was, maybe it was Twitch chats.
It was Twitch chats fault.
Well, I got to the part in Battle Network 2 where you go to the place where the poor and
the minorities live.
So I was probably really on edge because I was going through a bad part of town.
Yeah, I was watching that part.
Yeah, the basically, the, the, the geography is pretty unclear.
I'm pretty sure I am from a town called AC DC in a, which is like a, a suburb of a city
called Denden City, which is in a country called Electopia, which is sort of Japan.
And I have just, and I have traveled to, there's another place called Yumland that I have not
been to yet.
And I don't know what that's like, but I'm in another place, another country now called
Netopia and Netopia is just America.
It's America, but some people have French accents.
So I guess it's just like a general.
It's just, it's the West.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's French people.
There's, there's medieval castles and, and there's, and there's like back alley slums.
So, you know, it's got, it's, it's truly, it's truly got it all.
Well, yeah, I haven't got much to say about the story in Fire Emblem.
It's almost, it's almost non-existent.
It's just sort of like you go from one map to the other and they give you a brief,
like a paragraph or a sentence as to what's going on.
Oh, I missed your stream yesterday, didn't I?
Yeah.
Where were you, huh?
I was, well, I was lifting, but that was like later.
So I was lifting for 24 hours straight.
Yeah, I was, I was, I lifted in the evening.
Ah, yeah.
And I, that was, so those were my evening plans was to lift.
I probably, I probably could have checked in around.
Maybe that's why.
Maybe that's why it was only a few people.
Everyone was lifting.
Yeah.
When she called me scrawny.
Can you fucking believe that shit?
Well, I'm trying to remember what did you lost
when I last saw you?
What were you like?
Because you weren't fat Ben at that point.
I don't know if you'd been lifting for a while.
I, no, I had not.
That was like, that was like about a year ago, right?
The last time that was, yeah, last summer.
No, you were here, no.
2022 summer.
No, I, it was, I thought the last time you were here was when I was prepared.
It was when you got COVID, right?
Yeah.
That was in the summer.
We went to the beach.
What?
Well, I don't know.
I don't think you went to the beach, but like it was hot.
It was hot and we went to the beach.
And we did some beach things.
It was like, like off because Munchie was off uni.
Am I smoking crack?
I thought for sure that when you were, you got COVID
and that prevented me from doing the live Mega Man lecture.
True.
And that, and that was in like, I thought that was in like February.
No, that, I wasn't, it was all, it all happened in, in one big time
because I only got the COVID, I only came over and got COVID once
and that was when I was staying during the summer
because I remember it being really hot some nights.
Needy that, that Erecon going.
And then because I got COVID, I had to stay isolated for about a week
and then I hung out for a little time after that.
That's so funny.
I remember one of the last things that happened was we got like,
we went to that like waffle ice cream.
What was it?
Is there some sort of confectioner?
Yeah, the waffle pop place.
Yeah.
And we got a thing and we were walking.
And we were walking here.
We were walking down the old dusty trail.
I'm so confused.
I really thought that was in like March.
Wow.
Time, time is funny.
All right.
Because then it was like after that, it was, it was, you were trying to figure out how to do
the Mega Man thing by yourself instead of in front of a group.
And that took basically like a few months.
Well, it took, it took a few months to play all the games.
But you got that by that point, right?
You had played all, no, you hadn't played all games.
I was going to deliver the lecture without having played any of the games or most of the games.
And then, but I recorded the lecture at the end of August because I remember that was like,
I moved like literally the next day.
So it was the end of August.
And I thought it took me like three or four months to play through the game.
So August, what's before August, July, June, was it in like May or June?
I fucking maybe, did I, did I, did I blast through every Mega Man game in like two months?
Probably crazy.
I remember, all I remember was it was, it was hot.
It was like a hot time.
Maybe, yeah, you know what, you know, maybe you're right.
Yeah.
Okay.
Damn.
I thought that was longer ago.
That's crazy.
That means I thought it had been a year since then, but it's only been like eight months.
To all 10 months.
Well, no, about like eight, no, like eight months.
That's so weird.
Usually these days when I remember things, they happened much longer ago than I think they happened.
What the fuck?
Explain, explain this shit to me.
Sorry.
Um, okay, well that, well that was a tangent.
Could it have been like really warm in March or something?
Yeah, it might, it might have been unseasonably warm in like May.
I could look, I could look through Discord things to be like,
this is the 10th account about it.
Uh, yeah, whatever.
No, that, that, no, I guess that, that makes sense.
Yeah, it's probably, it was probably like May or June.
Yeah, whatever.
Cool.
Okay.
I believe it.
I'm just fucked up.
I'm just, I'm just so, I'm just, maybe I'm confusing it with when you were there for
New Year's because we're, because you're there for New Year's, right?
And then you were there again that summer.
Was I there for New Year's?
No, I don't think I was.
I think I was invited.
I think, was that like a big group of people?
I think, oh wait, there was a big group of people.
Some people came for New Year's and then you didn't, you didn't come, you didn't
end up coming.
And I think it was because there were, someone rescheduled or something happened to change
the schedule and you were like, you were gonna come, oh, you didn't come because like COVID
restrictions, right?
Yeah, there was a time I was going to come and it was going to be early in the year,
but I couldn't come because somebody in my family got COVID, like they tested positive.
The day, the day that I was supposed to fly.
So it was like, you don't know that you're safe.
So I had to, we all had to isolate and stuff.
So I had to change, I had to cancel that or like reschedule it for
summer of the same year.
And then it was a summer party and I bought that summer hat, which I still have,
which I like, and I'm going to be using soon when the fucking sun comes back.
Well, thank you for, thank you for helping me to reconstruct my shattered memories,
my chain of memories.
Just like Kingdom Hearts.
Yeah.
How did I, oh, anyway, Munchy called me scrawny.
All that's the same.
I would have been, yeah, I don't think I had been lifting basically at all for like almost a year
or at least six months or so the last time you were here.
Uh, now I weigh about the same, but I'm ripped.
It's not true.
I'm only a little bit strong.
That's why I'm scrawny.
So it's larger your muscles, the less time you spend on Twitter.
It's just not no correlation, just sort of like a funny coincidence.
Not to, with the less my muscles, the less on Twitter or the, or is it like,
as one goes up, the other goes down.
As muscles go up, Twitter usage goes down.
Yeah, maybe so.
Maybe that means I got to get huge.
Munchy is, it's funny.
Munchy is like, Munchy's bench press is already, you know, he's done a lot less
lifting than me in life.
So he's, compared to me at it, he's a bit of a noob on his technique and things like that.
Nevertheless, his bench press is already like almost the same as mine.
It's just because he's bigger, which is, you know, that's, that's, that's just life,
I guess.
However, his squat is terrible.
And he has actually like injured himself several times while squatting and had to
like stop squatting because he got like, he like pulled an adductor or something.
So his squat is, is minuscule, but his bench press is threatening.
So, you know,
I think I did some workouts in that, that basement.
On the rack?
Yeah, I used the thing, but I couldn't.
Yeah, the power rack.
I couldn't lift the bar with anything on it.
I could only use the bar and only just.
What lift, were you trying to squat it?
I was, I was, I was just doing what they were doing.
So I was doing a curl and then I did a bench press.
Yeah.
And I don't, I don't think I did a squat yet to put that like
behind your back.
Yeah, on your shoulders, cringe.
That's literally the most important one.
Literally, literally the most important one.
I did that with the smaller weights, with the hand weights.
Oh, hand dumbbells, dumbbell squats, disgusting.
That's, I was, I was doing some, some weightlifting tourism.
I wasn't really interested.
At least you're not one of those perverts that squats with the bar on their back,
but they put the fricking like roll pad on the bar to like, ooh, cushion it.
Ooh, I'll put the little cushion on the bar because I'm such a fucking idiot
that I rested on my fricking.
Cushion.
Wouldn't that just make it slip?
Well, there's, sometimes in the squat rack, you see a little circular,
it's like, it's like a Velcro round little cushion that you can sort of
like Velcro on to the center of the bar to like rest it on the back of your neck.
The thing about that is that.
All I'm thinking of is if it's not perfectly fixed to the bar,
then it would rotate, it would rotate and then it would slide down your back,
wouldn't it?
Well, there's like potential, that's all I'm asking.
Yeah, I see, I see what you mean.
I mean, it really shouldn't do that.
But the thing about it is you really don't need it,
because if you're squatting correctly, the bar is not, you know,
you got the little like, I don't know what it's called,
the little bone bulge on the back of your neck.
It gets it's a vertebra.
A shoulder pad.
No, no, no, on the neck, on the neck.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know bones.
You can feel the vertebra of your, of like the back of your neck.
Like if you're a freaking, yeah, if you're an idiot,
then yeah, it would be really uncomfortable to have the bar rest on your vertebra.
But you're not supposed to do that.
It should be on your shoulders.
It should be resting on your shoulders.
On your shoulder blades, that's the word.
Right, but no, not on the blades.
Like on the, on the, on the, on the divot between the trapezius and the,
whatever the shoulder muscle is called.
Oh, the trapezius.
Yes, the traps.
No, that's why they're called traps.
No relation, no relation.
Okay.
The trap is the big, well here, let's let's examine, let's examine.
Wait, is that, is that why they're called traps?
What, you mean boys?
I mean girls?
No.
Oh.
The, the, the like neck muscles, I've heard them refer to as traps,
like the big neck muscles when like Goku has one big one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, because it's the trapezius.
It's the trapezi, I think it's the trapezius dorsi.
Wow.
Or no, it's just the trapezius.
I never really thought about it that they would have a real name.
If you can believe it, they really do.
Like pecs or pectorals, like duh.
Right, so anyway, what was I talking about?
Here's, here's the view, the deltoid, right?
If you, if you squat correctly, the bar is resting on the divot between the trapezius
and the deltoid.
It's not resting on, on the bones of the neck.
So you really don't need that cushion.
What if you have a fucked up weird neck?
Uh, well, gosh, I mean, I guess if it's, I don't know, I mean, how fucked up are we talking?
Well, I guess I'm thinking of like, like Gamerneck, like it's going forward.
I got a bad case of Gamerneck.
Where it's like going, like leaning forwards a lot.
But that would get it further out of the way.
So it'll be like some sort of anti Gamerneck where you're like, your neck comes back.
I think maybe, maybe if you're really stiff and you have a bad range of motion,
it might be difficult to get it in the proper position resting on the deltoids.
I think a little bit of stretching and a little bit of practice would limber almost
anyone up to the point that it would, uh, that it would rest.
I mean, I mean, proper squat form takes practice.
It's, it's, it's a, it's a fairly, it's a fairly complex, complicated movement to do.
And you sort of just have to practice it and practice it until you get the form right.
So, yeah, but once you figure it out, the point is you don't need that pad if you're
doing it correctly.
But anyway, the reason I bring this all up, I don't know, I've started, I've started cycling
creatine. I've started doing that again in the hopes of, uh, becoming huge once more.
Once upon a time I was huge. It wasn't that huge, but I was dead.
I, I deadlifted 300 a couple of years ago and that's my goal again.
I'd like to deadlift 300.
I'm actually almost there.
I'm at like 275.
So, but I'm sort of installing on my squad.
I've been stalling on my squad at like 220.
So, you know, I'm going to start cycling creatine again and hopefully blast,
blast past the plateau and become my best self.
The strong, I'll be the, I'll be the cutest and the strongest.
That's my goal.
I've completely stopped exercising or moving at all.
Idiot.
It's, I would die.
Uh, you know, I mean, I will.
This is not, this is not, this is not life.
This is gradual death.
That's you.
That's, that's, that's Osho talking to you right now.
Oh, I love Osho.
Waste, waste in a way.
Do you know, do you know what I'm talking about?
I know from, and I learned about it from the red letter media episode where they
do a video of his.
Well, there's, um,
And he's like a, he's a, he's a cult leader.
Um, insane boy.
He's, he's like, I don't know whether he's insane, but he's just like very good at
manipulating people to believe his bullshit.
And he did it.
That's actually the, yeah, that one they're talking about in that one is
actually the same, it's the Rajneesh Purim cult that, uh, there's a down the
rabbit hole about the same, the same thing.
It's the same dudes.
Lamal.
And I guess there's also a documentary.
I think those guys, the red letter media guys knew about it because of a
documentary I know about it because of down the rabbit hole.
Also a documentary.
That honestly, uh, uh, Nuds Frederick Knudsen probably knew about it because of the
documentary.
Yeah, I need to get back into doing anything.
It's just been, when it's, when it's so cold, when it's so chilly, I mean, it's not
so much chilly anymore.
But yeah, all I wanted to do is wrap it in a blanket and sit on my chair.
I'm really happy that, um, the guys over at, um, what I will call Munchie House,
decided to get back into lifting with me.
I don't think I would have the willpower to do it by myself.
Also, it's kind of dangerous to do it by yourself.
Oh yeah.
So I don't know, I was really happy that those guys, I think maybe like, maybe like
four months ago or something, we're like, we want to get back into it.
And I was like, hell yeah, I'm in.
You son of a bitch.
You son of a, and we've been, we've been pretty consistent about it, uh, for a while now.
And that feels really good.
And I'm really, uh, you know, I like that.
If I had, I think they, if they have to move, I'm, there's, I have a basement.
They have a really nice basement that has a lot of room and a lot of like ceiling space.
You've, you've been there.
Yeah.
Um, if they have to move, I might be able to move the rack.
I have space in my basement, but the ceiling is low.
So I think I could fit the rack there.
You know, it would probably be fine.
I would just have to do like sitting overhead presses, which is acceptable.
You have to dig a hole to stand in if you wanted to lift it up.
Well, at my old place at monkey house, uh, I deadlifted so hard that I crushed the concrete
under the, under the bars.
So when I would deadlift, like the, the, the plates would be sitting in like two
like crushed divots of like pulverized concrete.
Like you mean you dropped it afterwards?
Uh, I didn't like full on like drop it like freehand, but I did sort of like,
you know, I would, I would pretty much like hit it.
It would hit the ground pretty hard.
And yeah, eventually I cracked the ground and like it pulverized some of the,
some of the floor, whatever.
It's cheap.
I told, I told the guys I would, uh, I would patch it with like a patching putty.
Never did.
Just moved out.
Left the damage.
Lemau.
Um, moving that rack was such a nightmare.
It was like a whole, it added a whole other step to like the moving process,
but it was worth it because now I'm strong.
What do you, what do you think about that?
I don't know.
I don't need to see it till we believe it.
That's right.
I am for, I look, I look pretty much the same.
Uh, I look pretty much the same.
Maybe I look a little bit more cut.
I don't know.
I haven't like a lot.
I would have to like, I would have to like lose a bunch of weight.
If I like, I might look a little bit good.
If I cut like 20 pounds, I might, you might, I might be a little more noticeably
muscular than maybe I would have been to ever months ago, but like, I'm not going to do that.
I think I want to focus on getting huge for a while more until I start to feel like,
I don't know, until I feel like, wow, I'm actually a little bit ripped.
And maybe then I'll cut, maybe then I'll, I'll focus on cutting fat and becoming,
becoming cut like a diamond, shredded.
That's the goal.
I don't, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not ripped enough yet that I need,
want to be like, all right, time to cut, time to cut the fat and show these gains.
But soon, very soon.
You want to get abs that you could grate cheese with?
I mean, that'd be cool.
At the very least.
You don't even need to buy a grater.
It saves money.
Like to have huge shoulders.
Big, big, big bulgy shoulders are cool.
I have kind of bulgy shoulders.
I have kind of a wide shoulder pads.
I have kind of like a wide frame and like wide shoulders.
So I think it might be, I don't know, I think maybe to enhance my natural physique,
a big, big shoulders would be like, yeah.
Just lean into it.
Just lean into what's, what's already, what you've already got going on.
So, you know, that's the plan.
That's the plan.
Speaking of the plan, the perfect comic party last week.
Yeah.
Oh, I, I spent some time.
I made a little logo, I guess it's basically done.
You showed me the logo and I told you, I don't, I mean, I think I expressed to you
how much I liked it.
Let me just express, I love, I love it.
I love how it looks.
Thank you.
I can't wait to put it.
I want to put it, if you, if you have like a high res version,
I'd like to put it on the website and I, and I'd like to like maybe make it then,
well, maybe not yet, but soon make it the new channel icon.
I'm going to put it on the Patreon and stuff.
The website is live.
I figured it out if you, now, right now, if you go to perfectcomicparty.com,
it redirects you to the procrastinatorspodcast.com.
And the procrastinatorspodcast.com shows the new, the new website, which, I mean, it's not,
you know, and it's got most of the episodes.
It's got a lot of the episodes uploaded for download.
I'm working on getting them all up there.
It does not have, there's a stuff page that has links to the Dojan and Road to Radcon.
That stuff's not actually there yet.
It's just like a blank download link, but it will be there soon.
And I haven't actually looked to the site yet, but yeah, looking at all these text on the gradient.
It's, you know, it's pretty, you know, it's, it's a, it's a website written in HTML.
Yeah, let me, let me, let me look at it.
Let's, let's, let's throw up a screenshot.
I've never seen, I've never seen like a list in text, all of the PCP episodes.
Oh yeah.
Like scrolling through history right now.
It's, I think I want to, somebody in a, in a comment suggested, yeah, when you go to the,
the archive list, you see all the episodes, all, there must be like 400 mp3s on here.
Um, if you go all the way down.
Oh, so it just opens a download link, okay.
Uh, let's, let me, well, well, some of these are not actually here.
If you go to maybe, okay, that one does, and yeah, it, yeah, it just downloads the mp3.
Um, but anyway, what was I saying?
Uh, shit, I was going to make a point about something, but it's gone.
Uh, the new website, it's got text on it.
Oh, I want to put the logo, I want to put the logo up top.
Yes, well, I think, I guess I can, I don't know if I was totally finished or.
Okay, okay, okay.
I think I was though, I, I did like, I did, I added the, I added the,
I can give you the Photoshop or the Clip Studio.
Do you have, do you have Clip Studio?
Well, I use Manga Studio, which is like supposedly the same program.
So it might work.
Okay.
I, otherwise I can send you a Photoshop with all the layers and you can move them around and stuff.
Uh, I, I mean, I do want the layers, but I mean, I, I think either one is fine.
Um, yeah.
So, yeah, if you look at, um, I made a Kofi, I made a PCP Kofi.
Uh, we should put that, we'll link that in places.
Stuff has, yeah, Road to Radcon and the Paradise Dosion and links to my site,
if anyone wants print copies, because they do have print copies of, of those sitting around.
Well, I do, I have a print copy of Paradise.
I have, I have a big box of Road to Radcon that I would like to get rid of if anyone wants one.
They have really the beautiful, the beautiful cover art by Mishi.
I already have my copy.
It's a collect, it's a collector's item.
I think I, I think I have like, I must have at least like 40 of those just sitting in a box.
I'd really like to get rid of them.
Uh, the PCP Dating Sim, the PCP Minecraft server, a link to Endless War and your website, my website.
Uh, I could maybe add anything else to think of.
Um, yeah, so I figured out all the URL fuckery and stuff.
I think I'm probably going to download all the files we had on Bluehost.
I'm probably going to take all the files off there and save them somewhere.
I would like to just cancel Bluehost and I wonder if, is there a way we can just like,
migrate the domain of a Procrastinator's podcast to Dreamhost?
Um, that's, should be possible.
It seems possible.
It's just sometimes hosting and stuff that can be annoying about how to maneuver it around.
Well, we don't really, we don't need to do that right away.
Cause like the website is working now, but like, you know, the Bluehost is now extraneous.
It's just extra hosting costs that we don't really need to pay.
So, uh, you know, I'd like to get rid of it as soon as possible, but it's not like super urgent.
So yeah, the new website and I'm going to, I'm going to, I'll try to like gussy it up a little
bit with like the, those icons you made and maybe I'll make the fonts a little bit.
I mean, this is kind of plain font is like fine.
Yeah. So it's just readable and it is.
But anyway, yeah, if you're, if you're listening to this, you can at the, at the, okay.
People asked for the podcast apps.
Uh, you know, I have not updated the Spotify or Apple podcast or anything like that.
But if what you want is like a downloadable mp3s that you can listen to,
if you want downloadable mp3s of all the episodes, all the past episodes ever,
they're here and they're on the procrastinatorspodcast.com.
And you just go to, yeah, the procrastinators podcast episode archive link.
And there's a whole list of them and they are mostly there.
And if anything is missing, you can let me know in the comments and I will try and get it up there.
Uh, yeah.
So I'm glad to have gotten that sorted out.
I was really, I was really banging my head first against like,
how do I actually put the files on the, the internet?
Like we own the domain.
How do I put the files there?
I had forgotten how to do that.
And then once I did remember it, I was like, okay, okay,
I remember how to put files on the internet.
But now how do I make it so that I've got the, I've got the original website.
I want to one, replace it with a new website and then two,
make a second domain redirect to it.
And figuring out both, I figured those out yesterday.
So I'm glad to have done that.
Yeah.
And, uh, that was like productivity wise.
That's most of what I, that's most of what I got this week.
But it's, but it's, it's not nothing.
So I feel okay about it.
Yeah.
It's not nothing.
You know, it's, you can say it's not nothing.
That's pretty good.
Anytime it's not nothing, you should feel good about that.
It's like my old thermodynamics teacher used to say,
when you solve a physics problem, it's important to feel,
let yourself feel good about it so that you will condition yourself
to want to do more in the future.
If you beat yourself up about it, oh, I didn't do it fast enough.
Oh, I didn't do it good enough.
Then you're going to teach yourself that getting things done
just gives you pain and that's not going to.
I wish I had that advice when I was young.
I just ended up feeling pain constantly.
Well, you know, it's good advice.
It's hard to internalize and live by consistently, but I mean,
I, it's good if you can manage it.
I've been learning that basic lesson with my therapist.
I think I talked about it last time, just sort of noting down
things I've done and like just noting that they have been accomplished.
So I look back on the week and I'm like, oh, yeah,
I guess I did all that stuff because I often forget.
That guy, that guy was like a, that guy was like a Buddhist like
monk or something or he like worked at like a Buddhist temple,
like a couple of towns over.
And he was like an adjunct professor who they had got in to replace.
We had had like a much older, like a very accomplished older guy
who had written like the textbook.
He literally wrote the textbook for the class.
But that guy had like, he was very old and he was going through some health
things and I think he was got, he got too sick.
Like, like literally the year I showed up and was supposed to be taking
this class, they were like, he can't do this anymore.
We got to get it.
We got to get some new guy in.
So we got this fricking Buddhist guy and that guy,
he gave us all these like sage wisdoms and stuff and he was like, hey,
don't worry about it, just feel good about it.
But then he would assign, he would assign like PhD level questions to us.
And like we found where he was getting his homework questions for us
and they were, they were like PhD qualifying level.
So he would assign these unrealistically difficult things
and then he would just grade them like really leniently.
But it sucked because we didn't know that he was going to grade them leniently.
So we all would like get together and spend all night banging our head against
these things and not be able to figure out, turn in like shittily,
like barely solved, like probably wrong answers and then we would get them back
and he'd be like, oh yeah, well this was pretty much wrong,
but I guess you couldn't have known that.
So it'd be plus.
Hey, feel good about it though.
Take a minute and just feel good.
Feel good that you tried or something.
You tried and you accomplished.
You figured some of it out and like that's good enough.
Isn't the point purpose of school to be taught how to figure that out?
Well, that's what the textbook is for.
Not just tested on it.
Well, that's what the, well, I mean, he did give,
all you need to do, all you need to do to get good PhD results
for a baby, you just give them the same, like a series of tests
over and over again and then eventually they'll get it.
Just every day, just click.
Every day, give them a test.
Like, hey, can you, can you walk?
Let's test, let's test your walking.
Oh, you failed today.
Okay.
And then, you know, several hundred tests later, eventually they'll pass
and it's all because you, it's all because of your encouragement.
Yeah, so that was, that was the first thing I did in the week.
Oh, the logos.
Yeah, the logo.
They're so good.
I don't know if we want to like show them.
Do you want to show them or do you want to keep them a surprise?
I mean, let me just screen grab them right now because I've got them open.
Do you think this is at a point where it's like, yeah, this is finished.
We shall, we shall, this shall be what it is.
Because I can, I can, I don't really know what to edit about them.
I think they're pretty good.
I think they look, I would be perfectly, I'm perfectly happy with this
going on the, on the, the book.
Oh, you know what?
I know, I, I know I asked for the, I don't, I don't think I would put the,
on the, on the PDF.
I would want that for like maybe the website.
Yeah, yeah.
That's just the file as it appears currently.
Right.
No, I'm, I'm think this is perfectly good and like no notes.
This, this can go, this can go right on the, the comic or the, the zine or whatever we're calling it.
Yes.
So.
With regards to that,
well, kind of related, not exactly, but I've been making a PDF ready, a print version
ready of Clarissa for a, an Amazon Kindle direct publishing
sort of thing that Amazon can do, which is my next, my next goal.
I had sort of a crisis in this, this week where I was like talking to my therapist.
My therapist was like, well, I mean, don't you want to make money?
Like how, how, how expensive is this comic?
What are you going to set up for?
And I'm like, oh, I'm going to put it up on the internet for free.
Right.
And they're like, but what else would he, what, huh?
What are you stupid?
What are you idiot?
Right.
And I was like, oh no, I am, I am idiot.
Right, right.
I need to monetize.
I need to, I, I, I avoid it because I don't know.
I guess I should have a thing about it.
The thing about like putting a price tag on my work and statements and marketing and, I don't know.
Yeah, for sure.
It's, it's maybe, maybe a more like a, like a focused determination of whether what I've
made is good is whether it makes money.
And I'm like, I don't, I just want to avoid that whole question.
Yeah, I, yeah, I know what you mean.
No, that makes no sense.
But there's no harm in having the ability for people to buy it.
So I've been, I did the PC, the perfect comic party logo.
And then I started trying to figure out how to monetize and I've got a plan.
And I'm going to make, I'm going to make closer chapters one to four into a PDF.
And I'm going to put that on Amazon so you can buy it as a Kindle digital version.
And with the Amazon Direct Publishing, I looked into this.
It's print on demand.
If you type in Amazon print on demand, that's a different service.
This is Amazon Kindle Direct Publishing.
Okay.
Which was confusing for a bit.
But yeah, you make a book as a PDF or some other thing and it will be printable by the
consumer without me having to do any work printing it and sending it.
That's actually, yeah, the fact that you don't have to do the shipping yourself,
that probably saves you like so much money because Amazon can ship stuff so much cheaper
than you can.
They can.
They can obviously print it so much cheaper as well.
And Clarissa Gunsmoke and the Lord of Ghosts, which I will do as well.
I'll do the Lord of Ghosts.
I'll do a Redman version so you could buy a physical Redman thing for people who missed
the Kickstarter.
And it'll be, you know, it's going to be a storefront.
It's going to be, I'm going to sell my work.
I may even make a Bale JAPE hardback little book.
That's actually probably all that stuff together.
It's actually probably like a really good idea.
Yeah.
That's going to take a while to like settle those PDFs up because they're so exact.
They're so specific.
I was like opening all of the many tabs and like learning and relearning about exactly
what a margin is and what bleed means.
And when you, you know, when you set like, they have a system, I think for any print
company, but Amazon explained it as the size, the number of pages determines how big the inner
margin has to be because of, you know, the more pages there are, the less the book can open flat.
So you have to change the margins based on how many pages.
Now, because the spine is thicker?
Yeah.
The spine is thicker.
Therefore, the inner margin should be, it should be thicker to accommodate for readability,
you know that.
Yes.
And the choice of ink, the choice of paper quality changes certain things.
And I figured out all that for Clarissa at least.
Yeah.
I put in all the numbers.
I know the bleed.
I have the file that is the right dimensions in centimeters and inches and pixels or whatever.
And I'm going to put it up there.
I'm going to make it.
That's next week.
It's going to be made.
That rules.
That's really cool.
That's probably that's probably going to do.
That's actually, it actually sounds great.
I'm imagining like imagine if you could just make a book and you didn't have to take orders
and buy envelopes and address the envelopes and bring them and bring them to the post office.
Imagine that's incredible.
I want to check the quality before I like officially answer it.
I should look into it and see like how much am I really saving?
How much am I really saving by doing it myself?
For me personally.
For you it's worse because you're in the UK, I think.
Absolutely.
That's absolutely a major factor.
But also the whole printing and sending and organizing of all that is so much like hard labor
mentally and physically.
But like mostly just to keep track of everything that I should be getting a bigger,
a much bigger paycheck than what I'm actually getting doing it myself.
So the fact that Amazon takes care of all of that and they're such a large company that
they can print this stuff like without, they don't need to buy 100 of them.
Just let Daddy Bezos take care of that for you.
Just leave it up to him.
He'll take care of everything.
Don't worry about the money.
Don't worry about the money, Kip.
Just let Amazon take care of it for you.
Look, look.
It's so easy.
Isn't it just the easy thing to do?
Isn't it just the frictionless way to go about things?
We just make it so easy for you.
They'll have like a thing on the submit your PDF and there's a box checking,
like checked, like a use slave labor, yes or no.
If you click yes, much cheaper.
You get much better returns.
But if you uncheck it, less money, less money for you.
Hey, slaves need jobs too.
Click.
It would be wrong to take that slave's job away.
We're all trying to make it in our little world.
Well, I guess there's no ethical consumption under capitalism anyway.
Yeah.
I mean, most people never think about any of that.
The fact that I think about it is merely just a frustration for me.
The fact that I know that I'm putting some slave into a work camp, at least I acknowledge.
At least I'm aware that that's what I'm doing.
No.
Now I've made a kerfuffle, but it's fine.
I'm also probably going to look into it and just see how much.
I think I'll try with the Clarissa.
I want to see if the quality is good because my initial reservations were,
are they going to be good for image print?
Because maybe it's just good for text.
But they sell children's books that way, which are entirely illustrated.
Obviously, you got your little publishing independent author and they're like,
I want to sell my children's book.
It has to be good enough.
It can't be shit quality.
Otherwise, nobody would ever use it.
But I'm going to check.
I'm going to do the Clarissa chapters one to four.
And then if it's good, I'll do the rest of my books.
And it'll all be available forever.
And if that's not the case, I'll at least make PDFs that you can purchase if you want to support me.
I'll put that on Amazon anyway, but also on Gumroad, I think, for the same price.
Just in case you don't want Amazon getting anything.
I got physical copies of, actually, at almost the same time.
I got the two test copies of Slime and Punishment.
And I got the test copy of the Radcon for Dojin.
And the Dojin looks good, except the margins were a little bit, I was a little bit,
I cut it a little close with the margins.
And it's mostly fine, except some of the page numbers were cut off.
So I adjusted the position of the page numbers.
And I'm probably going to print another test copy.
But other than that, the bleeds all looked OK.
It's pretty nice.
It looks like a little mini-manga.
I guess I could post a picture of it.
Maybe I'll do that.
Let's see.
Where did I?
I'll post the logo that I sent you.
So that's what it looks like, everybody.
Yes.
Oh, it looks so good.
It looks so shiny.
I love it.
Imagine little enamel pins of that.
Oh, I didn't even think of that.
That's what I was thinking.
Oh, it's shiny, just like my favorite thing.
A little enamel pin.
It's got a little raised up thing.
I did not even think about it.
The perfect comic pin.
Yeah, true.
Yeah.
And I'm imagining, I'm just imagining, I don't know.
You can make it different colors, different issues if you want.
Oh, wait.
I had another question.
I had another thing to raise, but I will mention that in a moment.
Let me just look at my PCP folder.
Let me go to my Radcon folder.
Let me go to the Dojin folder.
And let me show you.
Well, while you're doing that, I also have an announcement
for a new version of the Gibbentake.site website.
I'm revamping it.
And it's going to be nice and good.
That's probably also going to happen next week.
Is it live now?
Oh, next week, you said.
Okay.
Yeah, next week.
Yeah, Ben Rodia.
Ben Rodia, the person behind the famous giant punk plush
that he gave me at Radcon floor.
Meetup.
I didn't know it was the same guy.
Yeah, that's the guy.
Oh, that's awesome.
Okay.
And he's just approached.
He wanted to do the PCP website.
Yeah, I know.
I just said.
Ben was like, is more like, better, better as a list.
And I guess, I guess we don't need like a big revamp.
I just said.
Okay.
I mean, I said, yeah, he said he would do it.
And he said he would make it fancy.
And he said he would charge some money to make it fancy.
And I said, well, I can just make it, I can make it cheap
and quick and dirty for free.
And that's what I did.
So I don't know.
Yeah.
We can, we can, I don't know, we can make it fancy if we want to.
Yeah, just mentioning that I can't do it quick and cheap and fancy.
So it's going to look, it's going to be good.
I'm liking how it's look.
There's a triangle.
Do you want, you quick, cheap, fancy, you know, pick two.
I went with quick and cheap.
True.
Yeah.
But yeah, that's, that's a, that's a cool thing.
Currently there's like the punk, the runaway from snakes game.
Being implemented right now.
Do you have any like images of what it's going to look like or?
Mostly I'm excited because it's away from the shitty WordPress thing.
And it's so much more user friendly to upload like new comic pages too.
Did you, was it, was your old website on WordPress?
Yeah, it was a WordPress website because I don't know how to build websites.
And it's so restrictive and so convoluted and terrible and bloated.
And so this new one, I've been given instructions on how to edit
like HTML and, and, you know, add new pages.
Add new pages by simply getting the images and then like naming them correctly,
putting them in a folder that gets uploaded.
And then just editing the data file to say this is a new comic is of this kind.
Like whether it's a long scrolling comic or like a one page at a time,
like one panel at a time, like a bell jpeg comic.
Yeah.
And then like the, the, the image it's referencing,
and it just makes all the pages by itself.
That's, that's very convenient.
Which is going to be very useful for when I have like a billion comics.
Does it, does it make the new web page?
And it makes it so that it like links to the previous page and the next page?
Yeah, there's button stuff.
That's good.
That's really good.
Yeah, I don't know.
It's all, it's all involved.
It's all incorporated.
And the things I would do is like edit like,
like styles of fonts and stuff to taste.
Yeah.
Most of all the functionality is all there and it's, I don't need to touch it and it's great.
That's pretty good.
Yeah. That's a Saint, on Saint comics, when I upload a new page, I have to like
copy paste another page file and just change the like where the links go, you know,
update the new page so that it links to the one before it and the one after it on the next,
on the next links, which is, you know, quite, quite tedious.
So that's, that's a big, that's big.
Yeah. That's, that's cool.
That's cool.
I intend to have like, yeah, all the Clarissa stuff.
And then Bailej2 will go on there and it'll be so simple to upload that it'll make comics
easier as a prospect.
I won't have to think about anything.
I'll just make it and then it's on the website.
It's going to be easier than fucking, I don't know, what, what's the tapas?
I hate that.
Or webtoon or.
I hate tapas.
Microsoft paint, Microsoft paint fan ventures.
If that still exists, probably does.
Yeah, it still exists.
Although I haven't been in a while.
Oh, fuck, I forgot.
I made, I made one of those.
I mean, Beast Pages was one of those.
Do you remember Horstuck?
Oh, vaguely.
Wait, about, about Gib, right?
About like Gib and the horse.
It was Gib.
It was going to be Gib and the horseshoe crew, but in Homestuck, but it didn't get very far in it.
It was just me in my room, fucking around.
There's a few GIFs.
I could put that on there.
That could be like a little secret.
That's, that's your, that's your bard quest.
Yeah, yeah, I've got a multiple bard quest.
I've got, I've got Pocket Boys, the instantly abandoned Nuzlocke comic.
Right, right, right, right.
I didn't even get to like the first gym leader.
I instantly.
I was like, yeah, whatever.
I instantly abandoned a Nuzlocke comic once upon a time.
I mean, a long time ago, like before I ever posted online.
But I did make like one page of one of those stick, like stick figures.
Hope I never, hope I never find that.
Yeah.
So there's Canon Story.
There's fucking Pocket Boys.
There's Red Noir.
There's Red Man.
There's Bell Jape.
Clarissa Gunsmoke.
The Lord of Ghosts.
And what did I, what else did I say?
Something.
I said something else.
I posted the picture of the red.
Oh, and the horse stock.
Horse stock can go on there as well.
Secret, secret horse stock.
I posted the picture of the Radcon for Paradise Dojin.
Yeah.
As you can see there, it's a real thing.
I have one of them now.
And I, and I got, and the margin.
We're going to get, we're going to get splashed by the water.
It's coming.
We're going to get splashed.
I also got, yeah, Slime and Punishment.
I got two copies of it in slightly different colors.
And in two slightly different page weights.
And, you know, I went with the firmer page weight.
And I got to say, it's actually, it's actually really big.
It's really big to the point that it's a little bit floppy.
Because like the pages are just so large.
And because it's, it's cut like, you know, it's cut landscape
instead of a vertical.
So it has a short, it has, the spine is on the short side.
So even at like the, I'm going to, I'm going to ask her like,
what if we went like, what if we used like unusually stiff paper?
I might try to order like a test and see like.
Wait, sorry, for the slime?
Yeah, for Slime and Punishment.
It's, it's, you said it was a hardback, but it's still floppy?
No, no, no, no, it's, it's soft cover.
Okay.
It's, it's soft cut.
It's not like, it's, you know, it's, it's floppy.
Like, you know, like a, it's, it's very similar to, um,
the paper quality is very similar to like the, the, the problem sleuth books.
It's just that it's, it's just that it's like
much bigger, like it's, I don't know, eight, eight and a half by 11
is the size of a piece of paper and that doesn't sound that big,
but like the fact that it's like a 250 page book of that size is actually,
it's like quite large.
I'm almost thinking I overdid it on, on the bigness.
Yeah, like a size, like a sheet of A4.
Um, I think that's A4.
Eight and a half by 11.
Yeah.
Wait, I've got a, I've got a measuring thing.
Normal, I mean, in America, that's normal printer paper.
And I think it's probably the same.
Eight and a half.
Well, that's, that's a little bit bigger than my A4 sheet of paper right here.
I think I've got like eight.
So it's, you've got an extra half inch by 11.
Oh no, this is, yeah, it's more of a square.
Yeah.
Is it?
A little bit more square.
Oh.
I think.
Huh.
Okay.
Well, um.
This is not A4.
It's a U.S. standard.
Hang on, hang on.
A4 size in inches.
Maybe I'm wrong.
I'm just looking at it.
Yeah, this says A4 is eight, it's eight and a quarter by 11.67.
So I mean, it's pretty close.
Yeah.
Um, you know, U.S. is, yeah, a little bit, a little bit wider and a little bit shorter.
You know what the difference is for?
It's actually, um.
Why would they, why would they do such a thing as to have a different standard of normal paper?
That is, that is stupid.
Same, same with like different plugs.
They, I'm actually, I would have, I would have preferred the book to be, you know, less long
and more tall, but just the fact that the panels were like Twitter sized means they're like
relatively quite wide.
So honestly, having the book be like the proportions of the panel would make it like
really long and it would look really weird as a book.
And so I, I, I stretched it out vertically a little bit just to make it a little more square.
And as a result, there's kind of like some, there's like an inch or two of black space
sort of at the top and bottom of most pages.
It's a little bit of wasted space, but I think it just makes the book a more appealing shape.
Uh, I don't know.
I had to, I had to sort of work, uh, you know, just find the best compromise for page size
and all that.
But anyway, yeah, it's really large.
And so I'm gonna, I'm gonna ask for maybe another sample, uh, with like stiffer paper
and see like, I don't know, does that make it better or does that just like turn it into
cardboard and, or does it, does that cost like twice as much in which case it's probably not
worth it?
The one that I got is like, it's pretty, it's, it's, yeah, it's, it's very similar in, in
quality paper quality to, uh, problem sleuth books, except that the paper, the inner pages
are like coated.
The inner pages are like, not laminated, but they're like UV coated, which makes them,
it, it, it crushes the blacks.
Like when they're like the uncoded pages, the black is kind of gray.
The coated pages are like, the blacks are black and like the pages are mostly black,
like it's black pages with the image set on it.
So like it really needed that, uh, even though it costs more, but that's the price.
Each individual page is coated.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
I mean, because it's, because it's, um,
Yeah.
It's full, it's full color.
So much.
Yeah.
You want it to be as dark as possible.
That's where, that's where a lot of the, that's where a lot of the printing cost went
is making like every page full color, uh, like coated, you know.
But it had to, it had to be that way.
Uh, I cut, I'm wondering, looking at it, it's so large.
I'm wondering if maybe I could have got away with making it a little smaller
and maybe that would have saved some money.
Yeah.
I think I started building the PDF for a, a bell jpeg book to be around the same size
as the Homestuck and Problem Sleuth books because they felt, they felt good.
Yeah.
So I'm like, I don't need it to be bigger than that.
Yeah, they're a good size.
I don't know, whatever.
It's kind of, it's kind of cool that it's big also.
It's cool that it's big and because I went with this one printer, the prices are not.
This, this printer is like, the price is decent.
The price is decent for like a hundred copies.
And I'm hoping I can sell at least a hundred copies.
I would be, I would be like, all right, cool.
I accomplished my goal if I sell a hundred at, at a hundred copies.
It's cheap enough that I can sell them for what I think is a reasonable price,
which is going to be around the 30 to $35 range plus a little bit of shipping.
And if I go, if I go higher than that though, if I sell like 200 copies,
the price like drops tremendously.
If I could sell 200 copies, I would like double the profit on every individual copy
because it's just that cheap to print in bulk.
So like, wow.
Yeah, it literally is like, it's, it's barely more expensive to print like
300, it's, it's only like 50% more to print 300 copies as opposed to printing 100.
And then it's like, yeah, to, and then to go to 500 is only like, it only,
it only adds like another like 50% on, on that.
So like, yeah, it's really,
it would be, I have to check with, with, with the Amazon thing and like how,
because they don't do bulk, it's just right when somebody buys one.
That's, that's the, that's where the, that's where the profit margin is.
It's in the bulk printing that gives you like the per copy discount.
That's where you find my skills lie more in like just making the, the, the comics.
Oh, not me.
I'm terrible at that.
But marketing, marketing and production, that's, that's where I make my money.
The comic and afterthought, the content meaning what is garbage.
What I mean is like, I would,
it would take so much more effort for me to do all of that extra stuff.
Yeah.
That I would not end up making that much of a profit
as opposed to going through something, some other thing.
The, the, the, the, the fact of the matter is you gotta,
you only have so much energy and so much time to spend and you do,
there is a choice to be made.
How much time do you want to spend?
Yeah.
Looking into production details and getting the work produced and trying to like squeeze
out a higher profit margin by, you know,
such and such versus how much time do you want to be drawing comics?
And I, and I'm going to have to say that, yeah, I probably,
I probably do spend an above average amount of time
on the one side trying to like find the perfect,
the perfect paper coding and the perfect book size
and the perfect like printing, printing company
with the best shipping costs and all that.
And that's a, and that's a compromise.
You gotta, life is a series of choices.
And I made some.
But I just, I don't know if I just find it so satisfying, I find it so,
I think a lot of people would find that kind of thing really tedious and aggravating
and don't get me wrong.
It's, it's not not that, but it's hugely gratifying to, to like find
what feels like a good solution and be like, yes, it's just right.
It's, it's the perfect paper size.
I found a good deal.
I'm, nothing is being wasted here.
I am getting the, I am getting the best return on my investment I could possibly get.
It's a, it's great.
So, you know, yeah, yeah.
When I was on a roll with the Lord of Ghost comic, it did feel good.
Like, if I like get printing, like I bought like label paper that I could print on to.
So I was printing out the labels and sticking them on the envelopes and putting the things in.
I had already pre-drawn the, the doodles that I needed to do.
And then for the signatures, I would just sign them, put them all in.
And then it'd be like a big, huge wheelbarrow of, of comics to put to the post office.
And it was like, it felt good to get through a lot of that.
But it's just a little, it's, it's, it's really mostly the headaches of items being sent back
or just getting destroyed in customs.
Yeah.
And me not really having a, like a proper, like I'm not a business.
I don't have all those funny numbers they need sometimes.
Yeah.
Oh, what a, what a fuck.
What a whole big thing.
Filling, filling out the customs forms for international shipments was always like,
I would, I would get to the post office and then I would have to go and like find the slips
and then spend like an hour standing there, like filling out slips with like,
because they already have the information written on the envelope, but no, you got to
copy the information from the envelope onto the slip and then you give them the slip
and then they have to look at the slip and manually type in what you wrote on the slip.
That seems pointlessly convoluted.
It really, it really does.
It really does.
Like, like when I went to the post office, I had like the Royal Mail like affiliated like
news agents.
I go in there and I have the, I went to the Royal Mail site and I printed out there like
template for stuff.
And so because that's all there and I typed it all up and it's all fine, I signed it.
They just put it in a bag.
They just take it's like, is this for stuff prepaid?
Yes.
Okay.
They just grab it.
So it's like takes like two seconds.
I went to the star, star, star, star.
Star, star, star, star, star, star.
Star, star, star, star, star.
That's sorry.
That's what I was thinking while you were talking.
While you were talking just now.
I just wasn't listening.
I was thinking of that.
Yeah.
Turtle.
Turtle dreams.
Turtle memes.
Yeah.
You know, yeah, I don't, this is, this is a damn, what I was just saying right there
I know I said it's really satisfying but also it's a little bit depressing to say what I just said
and think of it like, you know, I could spend, I could stand to spend more time actually drawing.
Couldn't I?
I mean, you like what you like.
I think if you, if you enjoy that process, that's not a problem.
It's just, that's just how it is.
Yeah.
I mean, to, I mean, to, I do to a degree.
I do to a degree.
I mean, you know, I don't know.
I feel like, I don't know, I feel like most artists probably spend more time on their actual craft
and, and, and, and find, you know, I don't know.
I feel like a real, a real artist.
I'm just gonna say I'm not a real artist.
I'm a fucking fake.
I'm a fraud.
I'm a phony.
A real artist has like a publisher to like do all that stuff for them because they don't want to think about that.
I would say you're an artist.
You're just not on that Sigma grain set.
You're not gristling in the ground.
I'm not on that Sigma grain set.
I'm off the grind set.
And I mean, me neither, honestly.
I'm not like drawing as much as I really should be if I want to be like
getting enough, throwing enough stuff at the wall to make something stick.
Because I also, like despite like the idea of like self publishing and Amazon and stuff,
it would also be nice if I could go to a publisher and say, here's my thing.
What do you think?
Can this be, can you do it?
Can you put it in your publication?
Yeah.
Oh, you know that.
Oh, I wanted to raise this issue with you.
And I guess there's no reason not to just talk about it on the podcast
about the perfect comic party.
I mean, I think we said that the first issue is just going to be you and me.
But we're going to, after that, we're going to, we're going to make a call for submissions for like
other people to submit stuff.
Yeah.
Right.
Well, I was thinking,
what about, what's, we, I think we need to hammer out and elaborate a like a rights agreement
for that.
Like what rights, what publication rights are we being granted by a someone that submits
and allows their stuff to be print printed and here.
And here, okay.
For instance, for instance, like what if, what if we eventually decide that we want to like
print physical copies of the perfect comic party.
Yeah.
See this, this is what I want to avoid.
Right.
Well, I have some, I have some thoughts.
Like if we were to do that, we would have to do all of that stuff to make it like
sale smoothly and all that.
I was just thinking like, I don't want it to get big.
I don't want to make a whole like thing about it because then you have to do all that stuff.
Fuck you.
What's the point of doing it if it's not going to get big?
I want this to blow up.
I want this to, I want this to change.
Okay.
Now you're right.
You're right.
I just, I just don't like, I just don't like all of that, that, that stuff.
Well here, I don't know if we are going to need to like draft a contract per se.
We might need to, maybe we need to write out some copy and have people just be like
check a box or something.
Uh, I'll look into it.
But here's, here's what I think would be a reasonable, uh, agreement.
I think that it would be, I think that the agreement would be if like, if we publish
your thing in the perfect comic party, we don't take any like of your rights away.
Like, like it's still your content.
You own the comic and you're allowed to publish it in whatever other places you, you choose.
Uh, but you know, by giving us this thing to publish in the perfect comic party,
you do, you know, you give us the right to, you know, it's, you know, it's, it's for,
it's forever a part of this issue of the perfect comic party.
And we do have the right to print that issue, you know, we can reprint that issue,
including the, the comic that you gave to us for it.
And I, and I feel like that's fair.
Uh, yes.
Like, like, like, like we, we can, like you give it to us.
We, we can print it in this collection and we have the right to reprint this collection.
But you still have the right to print your stuff.
Right.
You, you retain rights, all the rights to your stuff and you can print it elsewhere as well.
It's not exclusive, it's not an exclusive agreement.
So you say print, like this is going to be physical.
Oh, well, I'm not, I don't know.
Well, in the option that it is physical, money needs to go into production of it.
So we would sell it.
And then is there like an agreement that they get a cut somehow for that issue?
I don't know.
I was kind of thinking, I was kind of thinking no.
So it's a, it's a, it's a risk.
It's a, it's a, your capital, your, there's a hypothetical capital that you may not get if
you, if you pledge to the, if you put your comic forward for the perfect comic part.
Yeah.
I mean, we're not, we don't have any active plans to do that at the moment.
But I mean, I don't know, what if like, what if it's, what if it's, you know,
enough of a success that we do maybe a dozen of them, and then we want to like print of,
like a, a collected volume of them, right?
Maybe we could print a collected volume that is like, you know, maybe a hundred or so pages of
stuff, 200 pages.
I don't, I don't know.
It's just, it's something we could do.
And I, I would, I would hate to be like a year down the line, I would hate to be like,
hey, this piece, this perfect comic party thing's going pretty well.
We should print it as physical copies.
Oh no, we didn't, we didn't even think about that.
We didn't have any agreement with our artists about like, do we have the right to print
your submissions?
Yeah, that's, that's, it's, it's sensible to get contracts, even if, even if nothing's gonna come
over it, I guess.
I, I think it's a reasonable stipulation to be like, hey, if you give us your comic and you
want us to put it in our publication, okay, we'll do that.
And we, we, you're not handing over any rights of yours, but you do give us the right to,
yeah, to print, to print this stuff.
To print and profit from, yeah.
Okay.
Because I mean, right.
I don't know how these things work normally.
So like, it sounds okay, I guess, as long as they know that that's what it is and they sign it
and they say, yes, I would like that.
I don't mind.
I don't, I don't think it's unfair because like, yeah, if we were to do it print, like, like,
we're responsible for doing all the printing and we're, we're the ones,
and I mean, it's not like it's sold under the pretense that it's our content.
Like it's still your content.
You'll be fully credited for it and all that.
I, I'm not, I don't know, this, I'm not trying to say like,
I mean, the way that it is now, there's no real money on the table for anyone.
You, you're being paid an exposure and so are we because like, we're not selling it.
And if we, if we were to print it later, I don't know, it would be sort of a separate
thing that is like, we're printing, I don't know.
I know, I know what you're saying, like, like, the perfect comic party
is as like a collection, it's, it's more than simply the comics in a line it has,
it will have like, other stuff to it, I guess, like, I don't know how much stuff is not like,
it's going to be like articles and stuff necessarily, yeah, it might be, but like,
like, it's, it's not the exactly the same as the comics individually.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, exactly.
It's a, it's a periodical that features submissions.
Uh, I guess, I guess it's, I guess it's basically like,
I think that any, any potential money from sales is at this point hypothetical,
is probably not a huge amount, even if it were to ever materialize.
And furthermore, I just think it's un, it's impractical.
Here's the thing, it's impractical to the point that I think it would stop us from doing it.
If we were to, if we had to maintain some sort of like individual agreement with every individual
submit, submitter, like, okay, if we ever sell this copy of the podcast, of the comic,
you are entitled to, you know, some percentage of the cut of whatever sales are made and we'll
have to calculate that in the future. If we had to do that for every individual submission,
I think we would simply be like, it's too much trouble and we're just not going to do it.
Yes.
So I think, so I think we, I think we need to stipulate, listen, if you give us this thing to
put in the thing, we might print it in the future and we might sell it and it might,
and it will include the thing you gave it to us and you're just, and you're just going to have
to be okay with that. And I, and I feel like it's not unfair.
Sure. I think comment commenters, let me know what you think about that.
If you feel like it.
I think, yeah, very clear contract. I know how contracts usually look.
They're so weird and annoying. And you just assume it's fine to just say yes.
I just have like a little, little explanation.
Uh, like, you know, what you just said, and then yes, no sign here, please, if you want that.
Right. Right.
But I think that's.
But I think that, yes, as long as that's all, that's all good.
We'll just have to figure out a way to like get like an electronic signature or, or just a check box
or, you know, it's something in writing to confirm like, yes, you know, I give you,
I submit my content under this, under this understanding.
I'll have to look into how to, how to do that.
Yeah, I have no idea.
Yeah, I don't, I don't really either.
I suppose that could be something that's on the website.
Like perfect comic party. You click on that.
You see that things are going to be like, submit your comic and then a link to the email
or something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, under the submission, oh, a submissions page.
Yeah, something like that.
Yeah. Yeah, a submissions page is a good idea.
And on the submissions page, there should be, yeah, like a.
Like, like you type in the information and there would be like a little thing and then
that would create an email to us with, with the, the thing signed and your comic.
Yeah. Yeah, that makes sense. That makes sense.
Oh, what if, what if someone, what if someone like submitted someone else's comic
and pretend and, and impersonated them?
Well, if that was the case, hey, I don't know.
How do you verify that the person putting a thing is the person who
has the rights to sign the thing saying that this thing will be the thing?
I guess if that happened, we would probably have to like,
issue an apology and then like, you know, retract that content from like any future,
like reissues of the, of the, of the files.
I'm talking, I'm talking about printing at this point, but like, we can, we can,
we can do all this under the assumption of like, we can, we don't have to think about that right
now. Yeah, we can, we can, we can make all the same, we can have all the same stipulations
about, yeah, like a digital PDF and it's fine. I'm thinking about the future.
No, it's good. It's good to think about the future.
Empire building, empire building.
I'm building my empire. I'm building my Gibb and take empire with the, the, the comics on
Amazon and the, the new website and potentially like a Fire Emblem video after I finished
playing all those games gets, get some new viewers.
You really think, you really think you might make a video?
I mean, the possibility is there.
That would be, I mean, I, I ask because like, do I even dare to hope for such a thing?
Well, I mean, I, I never stopped the, the possibility of making that dark cloud video.
I just have been, you know, I have been playing it in dark cloud too.
Dark cloud and dark cloud too. I was going to play them, get it and make a lore video about
and all of that. But like, and then the Fire Emblem, I mean, initially it was like
the point of that playing all those games is not to make a video,
but the fact that I'm playing all of those games and I'm also streaming the video.
So I have like an archive of all the footage means that it's not out of the realm of possibility,
not that difficult to put together something if I have something to say by the end,
which I probably will. It might just be like a boring like fire and bloom retrospective,
like I've seen like a billion of those. I never click on them because I'm like,
I haven't played them yet. But how interesting could they possibly be? I have no idea.
I don't know. I don't know either. Yeah, I've got a damn actually earlier when we were talking about
about how your visit was in the summer, not in the winter, like I thought that made me realize
like, oh, I guess, I guess making the Mega Man video didn't take quite as long as maybe it took.
That means that means it didn't take as long as I was thinking it took. That means I,
that just makes me feel like, ooh, I really should have had another video out by now. Like,
ooh, I really should be. You're taking a potential good thing. Like, oh, that video didn't actually
take so long. That was quite quick. No, you took it as an opportunity to feel bad about the fact
you've made another video. Yeah, I mean, I thought it took, I guess it took, I remember it thinking
that it took about five months. But I mean, I guess including editing, editing took a little over a
month. Playing the games took a few months. And then I guess it maybe worked a little bit.
Yeah, like the script and the setting up the board and all that. Yeah, it was probably about
five months. But now, ooh, it's been, it's been almost five, it's been about four months.
It's been almost four months since that video came out. And I have not, yeah.
No way, it's been four months. Well, it's been three and, about three and a half.
Yeah, that video came out on November, November 20th. What?
I know. I know. It's really bad. It's really bad. And I have really not
really started. What even was I, oh, I know what I was doing. I was being depressed in January,
that's all. Lol. La-Mow. I have really not- I got my shit together though. My shit is now together.
So epic. No more of that. The hydraulic shit compressor. Oh, yeah. Yeah. I think that's what
it's called. But right, that just makes me think, ooh, I should be further along in the process
of my next video. Ooh, I should be cringing a little bit that I haven't gotten more done.
But on the upside, that makes me think, well, maybe the next one won't take that long. Maybe I
can get the next one done in only a month if I put my mind to it. You are playing the battle
network games, which are much longer to play. That's true. And that's, yeah, that's for like a
future. That's me working towards an even further in the future, like my next, next lecture.
Like that's like maybe two videos down the line.
So, I mean, I am putting, yeah, I am putting in work towards that, but that's, but that's not
going to pay off immediately. What I really, what I really need is another video out like in the next
not that long. Just, just so that people that like pledged to my Patreon after the first one,
no like, okay, no, Ben is still making more videos. He's not like, he didn't just make the one and
then he quit the internet and my money is going to nothing. So, you know, I gotta, I gotta get on
that, but I told myself I would go to get on that, but after after I'll get on that
after we get the first, we get the first perfect comic party done, get that published.
And then I'd start the slime and punishment Kickstarter. And then when that Kickstarter is
underway, then I'll be like, okay, well now that can go in the background. And now's the time when
like, all right, let's let's actually get down to brass tacks about my next video.
Yeah, which I, which I think I have, I think I have decided is probably going to be at like a
history of the PCP.
LaMau.
LaMau, lol. Okay. LaMau. Well, I guess that's all I really have to
say about anything. Yeah, my here is like blowing directly on me.
Perfect. One's the other way.
Yeah, I've got a similar, like I've, Clarissa Gunsmoke chapter five, I haven't been drawing because of
website and Amazon stuff. Right. And perfect comic party. It was like after chapter four was
finished, I was like, ah, that was a good bunch of progress. But then there's all these little bits,
all these little bits of things that need to get done. And they all sort of are holding each other
up, not exactly holding each other up, but like, all of them are important and all of them need
my attention. Yeah. So I'm like, I can't really spend like all day drawing. I've got to
figure this stuff out instead. But here you are. But soon, soon I'll be back to getting that stuff
done. That'll be fun. I mean, I really let myself, I really let myself get, get thrown off this past
week with all the various things that, that made me, that made me a rage about the, the RADCON
funds and things. So that didn't, that didn't really help. I didn't really help anything. But
you know, that, that too will be over. That, that too will be a thing of the past soon. One hopes.
Uh, I, I, I, you know, I, I was like, I was about to say that like, I have had to deal with that.
The truth is, I didn't have to deal with that. The truth is, I could have simply ignored it.
Which everyone else does or has been doing. And honestly, at the time, I'm like, why is everyone
else ignoring this? Everyone, nobody else cares. I'm the only one that cares. Everyone hates me.
Uh, everyone's against me and my enemy. Um, and you know, in hindsight, I'm like, I should have just,
I should, I should just, I should also. It's better if it's just not, it's better just not
worry about it actually. Everyone else knows that. And I am the only one that doesn't.
It was a little distracting for me when it was all blowing up and you were all getting mad at
people for not saying anything. I'm like, but I don't know. Like the receipts will come when they
come. I mean, I'm, I'm trying to, I'm trying to do stuff. That's true. Yep. That's true. Yep.
Well, I made, I've made a nuisance of myself and uh, anyway, the next topic is uh,
next topic. Oh, oh, nothing. I actually, actually that's everything. I just want to shout out Prince
Isolation. Prince Isolation was in my stream chat and they mentioned they were doing an Aliyup comic.
Oh. An Aliyup from, from Endless War, little, little adventure she's going on. And I, I,
I read it and it was really good. I hope they post it somewhere other than their discord.
I haven't seen that. The, the person that did the Endless War Aliyup comic
messaged me and asked about like putting the Aliyup comic in
the perfect comic party. And I told them, definitely submit it. We just haven't worked out like what
the submission process is going to be yet, but like when we have it, like, yeah, absolutely. Uh,
yeah. Yeah. So I get fricking uh, the Aliyup like guest, guest, guest art, like side, side stories.
I guess. I got to bring Belle Jape back. I was thinking of, of, um,
was that, wait, Aliyup, your Aliyup was from Belle Jape, right? Yeah. Yeah. I forgot.
What did, well, what did you think? Well, I just thought she's just one of my characters.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. No, sorry. I'm sorry. I was thinking of Canon Story. She wasn't,
no, she was not in Canon Story. She was from Belle Jape, which is the Pumped one. Yeah. Sorry.
I was, I was mixing the two up. No, no, no. Yeah. She's from the Pumped Belle Jape. Okay.
Yeah. Um, what was I going to say? I don't know. Oh yeah. Yeah. Belle Jape. Belle Jape 2,
I've had ideas of where it could go because they're floating on lava. Spoilers, they're floating on
lava. Right. And I've had many different ideas of where they could float to or what they could have
happen in the larger world. Like, ooh, when does this take place on the timeline? I feel like
originally Belle Jape was just a bunch of bullshit. I was just making it up. I really,
I think I should not focus so much on like pre-planning something like Belle Jape 2.
I should just get into it when I finish with Clarissa. I think I should just draw. I think I
should just hop on, maybe on a stream like I did before. Just. Is that how you did Belle Jape 1?
Yeah. I just, I was on YouTube streaming and I was like, what if I just made it? I made a comic.
You know, I made Canon Story on YouTube and a few like commenters,
chatters were like, oh, do this, do that. I was like, okay, there's only like three people there,
but like, it was enough to get me to think about what happens next. And I was like, okay, let's do
the same thing, but this time let's do color. Let's do a little more effort. And that's
turned into something really fun and good and everyone likes it. So like, yeah,
well, I don't need to, I don't need to change it. Belle Jape 2 is going to be like Belle Jape.
Maybe I could, maybe that's, oh, I'd have to stream more, but like maybe I could do that with
Biscopades, draw it on stream and maybe that could be that. People have mentioned that. I
saw people mentioning that in your Mega Man stream that you should stream. Well, actually,
I can't remember. It was somewhere. Maybe, I don't remember, but maybe somebody said that. Yeah,
I mean, because like, you know, I think I mentioned that if we're putting it in the
magazine or whatever, then that sort of takes away the like panel by panel, what do you call it,
user suggestion element to a certain degree. But maybe a replacement for that would be,
yeah, I draw it live on stream and people can weigh in on it and be like, I'll do this, do that.
And it's sort of a different kind of, hmm, damn, but I hate Twitch though, but I hate being on stream.
But it makes a lot of sense. Maybe I'll think about that. You don't think about that.
Because yeah, it would be a little, I was thinking it would feel weird to be like drawing it
just like, yeah, kind of the whole idea of it was like that it would be user submitted,
user suggestions. So maybe that's the way I could recapture that, even though it's changing the
format up a little bit. Just realizing that my process for bell shape, I'll have to go,
I kind of want to go back and check. I think I unlisted all of those, but I think I didn't
know what the text was. I think I drew the image or made the GIF and I had the idea in my head,
like, oh, punk do this, punk do that. But then afterwards, I would put it on the website and
then come up with something funny to write underneath. That's a pretty good system, I think.
I'm commenting on something, but I'd have to do it pretty soon after I draw it.
If that's how the first one got made, then yeah, why not do it again? Why not do it the same?
Follow more or less the same strategy. Everyone likes the same stuff.
That's right. With the same methodology. Yeah. I mean, I don't know if it worked the first time.
Imagine if Andrew Hussie finished Homestuck and then tried make Homestuck again.
But this time with green aliens that weren't trolls or chairs. I think he probably
would not do that because like, yeah, Homestuck worked once, but you kind of can't do it again.
Well, the same setting. Yeah. Just sort of like funny little cartoon comic about somebody doing
some wacky shit in a little place. Well, that's, I mean, and then it grows in scope. Oh, it's a
perfect formula. You can't go wrong. Did you read Psycholonials? You did read Psycholonials.
Yeah. Yeah. Are you, I can't tell if you're serious, like he should have just done that.
I mean, I think I would have enjoyed reading whatever he did in a comic style,
in a Homestuck problem-sleuth comic style, just because I like the way he comes up with the
comedy with all the little bits. Yeah. And with Homestuck was a lot of the funny dialogue and
heartfelt character stuff, but Problem Sleuth was like, meat and potatoes sort of,
what if there was a comic and it was like this? It's like, I love that, more please,
but there was no more. So you're saying that you think he should have gone back and made
another Problem Sleuth rather than another Homestuck? Yeah, you don't need to do everything
the same, because like the way Act Six sort of deviated into teen melodrama a little too hard
and a little too verbose and like overly, overly big text all the time, so much text,
and it just really wasn't that useful. It really wasn't that interesting.
SpongeBob yelling at the burger meme, you forgot the funny! Definitely. Yeah. I mean, I think I've
said many times that like, yeah, pound for pound, I do have to say Problem Sleuth is a better work
because it wastes less of your fucking time. It just introduces concepts and then just takes them
to that logical extreme in a big finale, which is completely insane compared to what Star says.
The finale wraps it all up so cleanly. It's like so many like things introduced earlier,
it all comes first full circle and they come back and the scope gets bigger and bigger and
bigger and then it all comes together in the end remarkably, remarkably clean in a way that Homestuck
did not manage, I'm sorry to say, but yeah. You know, I liked Psycholonials. It was definitely
not that. Yeah, it was, I liked it. It was, I thought the ending was a bit dumb, but you know.
Basically what I'm saying is the Beljapes- Moment to moment, I thought it was enjoyable.
Beljapes Problem Sleuth and I'm doing Problem Sleuth now. I'm the one who does it.
Right. Beljapes Problem Sleuth and Clarissa is Homestuck?
Is Whistles the Clown. Right, yeah. What if Andrew Hussey made another Whistles?
What if he continued Whistles? That would be pretty good.
That would be amazing. That would actually be- That would require him to sit down and do something.
Yeah, true. I mean, his comics were really good. Like, the art in Whistles is like really nice.
Yep. So, I think a lot of people would probably really appreciate that.
I mean, a lot of his core fans would probably be like, oh my god, Whistles 3?
That kind of seems like a Hussey thing to do, actually, is just surprise everyone by just
picking up an old idea that everyone thought was completely abandoned and being like,
yeah, I fully committed to it and I finished it while no one was looking.
He says he'll be coy about like, I'm coming back to a thing and everyone think it'll be Whistles,
but then it's BardQuest. Yeah. He'll fully finish BardQuest and everyone will be like, oh, okay.
Okay, cool. Thanks. I appreciate it. That would be a Hussey thing to do.
I was really wondering what the Bard was going to do next. Now I know. Yeah.
This is going to level up. I'll take what I can get.
Fun fact. This is obvious, but I don't know if people even think about it.
Belljape sounds like jailbreak. True. That's why it's like that.
Okay. I know that. I was aware of that.
All the people who minds blown, say so in the comments. Say that your mind was blown if it was.
All right. You finished typing? You finished typing down there? All right. Thank you.
The only other thing I did this week was I made bombed hands, esteemed hands meme.
Yeah. I saw that. I don't know. I think it was just sort of like, it was in the
thralls of all of the bullshit and I just needed something to distract me.
Right. And I thought of the funniest idea. I don't know why this made me buckle over,
on the floor. I lost all of the breath when I made esteemed hands,
but it was lamp oil, rope and bombs where the things being discussed.
Yeah. I watched it and I was like,
it's so basic. This doesn't really, this doesn't really track.
Esteemed lamp oil.
It just, it killed me. I don't know why. Even just thinking about it.
You just love lamp oil and rope and bombs. Just admit that you just like those things.
I don't need to admit it. I say that all the time. It's not a secret.
Okay. Good.
I love, I love, I think something about it. It's a very basic idea. It's like the default
bread, but I haven't seen it before. And something about it being such a basic idea,
taking two memes and putting them together, but like not in a smart way, not in a,
and it's not an effort shitpost. It's truly the laziest little joke.
It just completely destroys me, especially the super bit crushed.
From like 14 years ago, I downloaded the lamp oil, rope and bombs line,
like the original upload. And it's like 240p, 144p sound quality.
Ah, can't go wrong. Can't go wrong with lamp oil.
Gigi, you can't and you didn't. And you know, I watched the video and I just kind of like
had my fingers steepled in front of me and I'm just nodding like mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm,
yep, lamp oil, rope, bombs, got it, got it.
I think as well, the fact that it's not that funny to other people makes it funny.
It took, and it took a while, and it took a while for like the lamp oil, rope and bombs to even
count. So it's like the first minute I'm just kind of like, when's, when's the, when's the joke?
Like the first time he is like, but what if I were to purchase bombs? That's the first time
it happens. Yeah. And then it's just normal for so long. And then he says, oh, that's the steamed
rope. It's just it takes such a long time for the second one.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean, no, I, I,
you're making me, you're, I'm, I'm laughing, I'm laughing at the thought of how much you enjoy
making it. I know. I think I enjoy the fact that I enjoyed making it, which makes it funnier.
It's like multiplicative. Right, right, right. I think I piqued the mic a couple times there.
That's not so good. That's good. That's fine. Uh, LeMau, uh, well. Oh, that I needed that one.
That's what I needed in my life. Uh, how's, uh, how's Runescape? Oh, I'm glad you asked.
Yeah. Runescapes go in great. I have gotten, uh, I've been mining coal and adamantite ore
in just, just, you know, casually while I rewatch on cinema at the cinema again.
Uh, love that series. I talked about that before. I said I may have done, I may,
there's one of the potential lecture subjects that I could have talked about.
Oh, wait. What was it? On cinema at the cinema. Oh, god, I've been meaning to watch that for years.
Yeah. It's the Tim Heidecker, like fake movie review show turned into like, you know, drama,
like, like real drama, like big joke. It's fun. Uh, there's not a good explanation of what it is,
but, uh. I know that like, it involves like, like they had like characters and they would
like tweet in character. They, yeah, Tim Heidecker and Greg Tarkington using their real names play
two movie reviewers, um, who are both have terrible taste in movies. Uh, one of them is a
pretentious snob about how much, despite not knowing that much, and the other one
is an arrogant, uh, egomaniac who thinks that he deserves everything in the world
for his shitty show that's terrible. Um, and they hate each other, but they need each other
and they just continually make this show and they have like the, the highlights are the,
the Oscar specials where they do a live stream. Every Oscars, I guess they'll be doing one,
like this year, but it might be behind a paywall. I think they've paywalled stuff.
That's a, that's a certain, a certain point. They stopped posting like publicly. You gotta
subscribe to a thing to see new episodes. And I'm like, eh, whatever. I'm, I can't be bothered for
that. Um, but the, the, the, the on cinema live specials, live Oscar specials where the Oscars
is happening and they live stream a movie show, like discussing the Oscars and who's gonna win.
And, uh, it's just a big farce. It's an opportunity for Tim to like get drunk or like fake drunk.
He does drink actual booze, I think, but he's like faking being like a real,
like a abusive like guy who like shouts at people and throw stuff and trashes the place.
And it's just great. It's just, it's just really fun. I, and it's, it's really fun, especially
during the live broadcasts, because you can, you can notice moments where like the characters break
and they can't stop laughing. They really try to hold it in. They never like completely break,
but there's like moments where Tim or Greg, they're like, they try and stifle a laugh because
it's so absurd what's happening. I, my friend of mine was telling me about it and he said that
there's like, he said that there's a timeline somewhere. There is. There's a, yeah. It includes
like their, their, like their, cause it includes like out of show stuff, like their tweets and
stuff that are kind of like part of it. Uh, and, and I don't know what else is involved, but it's
like, yeah, they started as a little podcast. I think it was a podcast of like a basic idea of
like, what if two guys have a really half-assed movie review show, whether they don't have anything
to say at all and they would record it on their phone whenever they were together, just as like a
little bit and then people liked it. So they continued it into, until it became a show.
God, how many seasons, season nine, the trial, season 10, season 11, that only goes to 2019,
this timeline. I know they, I know they've done, I'm pretty sure they've done more.
I guess I'll, it's an, it's an outdated timeline.
But yeah, after season 11, they sort of had their own website where they would post episodes
and stuff. And so I guess, because Adult Swim was not backing it as much,
they couldn't, they, they couldn't really keep doing the stuff unless they had the money. So
fan funded from that point, I guess. But they, they, they do it in universe where Tim is like
a grifter, like an Alex Jones type, like trying to get your money.
Selling brain pills, yeah. Yeah, all that sort of stuff. He plays all those sorts of like,
like nasty people roles. And it's fun. Yeah. But anyway, that's what I've been doing.
It sounds, it's all, yeah, it sounds really cool. And I've been meaning to, I've been meaning to
watch it. People told me about it years ago and I was like, oh, that sounds really cool. That
sounds really interesting. Oh, what an avant-garde work of postmodern deconstruction.
Where is it? Can I share the playlist? What a, what a deconstruction of the way that the modern
media is disseminated, popular culture. Right. This is on cinema, Decker, Decker and Decker.
Decker is like a, like a, a James Bond, like a Tim High Decker is James Bond kind of guy.
Well, not James Bond. He would hate that. He's just, he's just so short. They're like two minutes
long. These are the podcasts at the beginning. You can scroll down to the first episode. You
might want to start with those. This is just the playlist that has everything in it.
And yeah, on cinema season one, episode 101, the first few seem to be out of order.
These podcasts are two minutes. I'll just, I'll, why not listen to them as well?
There's like 50 of them, but yeah, you can listen to them, get an idea of it.
I recommend that the time investment. I assume these are in chronological order.
Yeah. There's a few that look like they're out of chronological order,
but they are not. I double checked. Okay. Something about the, the titling was wrong,
but yeah. Right. I'm gonna, this is good. Thanks for the link. I'll probably,
probably watch this or watch this or wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Okay. Hang on. Some of these are dated that they're seven years ago, but maybe they were like
posted seven years ago, but they're actually older than that. They are a bit older than that.
Okay. Okay. I think the, the show started in like 2012.
Yeah. And the podcast was before that. So the podcast was not uploaded to YouTube till later.
It was an iTunes podcast. Little iTunes show. Gotcha.
But yeah, I've been, I've been re-watching this while I play RuneScape. I have now
2,759 adamantite ore, which is what I need for my fletching challenge. So I no longer need
Addy. And now I just need, I need 160,000 more coal. I'm just going to mine some coal for a long
time. Oh, and I've hit level 92 mining. That's a big milestone. Apparently-
Max? No, Max is 99, but the, because of the way, excuse me, because of the way that
the, the experience like escalates, what's the word, over time, it's a-
The progression or-
Exponential. It's an exponential curve. The halfway point from level one to 99 is level
92, apparently. I see, yeah. So I'm halfway there. Gotcha.
I think I will get beyond the experience for 99 getting all of this coal.
Are the benefits also like exponential? Like is it like a, is it a significantly big jump from like
level 92 to level 93? Like in terms of what it actually gives you?
Not really. There's, on the, on the wiki, there's a little graph that shows you the,
the percentage chance to mine a particular rock every tick, every game tick at specific mining
levels. And for the more difficult to mine things, even at level 99, it only gets as high as like
20%. But for some things, you can get to a like 100%, like iron ore at a certain point
is 100%. Like every game tick you click on it, you instantly get it. So it's, it's really not
that useful to get to level 99 for most people, other than like bragging rights and for the
few occasional very, very high skill requirement things. So it's not so much you are good at
mining. It's that you can physically mine certain things that other people can't.
Like amethyst. I can mine amethyst now, but it's, I'm not a member.
But it doesn't make you better at mining the things you could already mine.
It does, but just not, not that much. I see. Okay.
So like getting from level 91 to 92 is like one experience, a one percentage chance increase
for like coal. Right. But it, but it takes like 10 times as much experience to get that extra one
percent. Yeah. Yeah. It's not like a thing you need to do. That's why, that's why RuneScape is
stupid, but I love it. Sure. It's so pointless. I think the best, I mean, the best games are
a little bit like fucked up. If everything, if everything is like perfectly balanced and perfect,
it's like the games, like you can't make a game like that. That's not like kind of boring.
A system that's totally, well, even chess, you know, who goes first, white or black, you know,
it's not perfectly balanced. That's probably not, that's probably not actually true,
but a lot of the time, you know, a game being unbalanced or like weird.
It's not so much that it's unbalanced. It's just that the time sink and the way you get
the experience in old school RuneScape was so, it was just so tedious that most people
wouldn't bother, which kind of made it so much more prestigious of a thing to get to the maximum
skill. Yeah. Because you have to be kind of insane to bother. Yeah. I feel, yeah. I feel, yeah.
Yeah. So it's like, yeah, like no normal person is going to go for 99.
Yeah. And even beyond that, there's loads of people on YouTube who do like extreme
challenge runs of like many different types to like hand cuff themselves in like ridiculous
fashions. Have I talked about Settled before? I think I have. I mentioned his like Mauritania
locked. Oh, yeah, you've mentioned them. Yeah. But there's other ones where like you, there's like a
lot of people who like stick to a chunk and they have to perform some sort of action within that
chunk or every action possible within that chunk before they can unlock a different chunk. And
a chunk is just sort of a loaded like grid square of like a bunch of like at some distance.
You know, like in Minecraft, they have chunks. You mean blocks?
Not blocks, but like biome chunks? Chunks that are like loaded in. So like if you are in one
chunk, it sort of loads one chunk at a time. So if you walk towards something, the whole
chunk will load at once. It's just like an area of 250 something squared grid on the ground.
Gotcha. But anyway, you have like accounts that are built to be stuck in a particular
chunk and have to try and figure out how to either gain enough experience doing the like
really inefficient methods of gaining experience that exist in that chunk to achieve some kind of
goal for themselves. Like people take RuneScape, an already tedious game, and make it far more
tedious and they love it. And I love watching it. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I mean, if you're there to,
if you're there for the tedium, if you're there, if that's if you're there to grind.
It's the grindiest game there ever was. The Sigma grind set. No, it's something
higher. The Ligma grind set. There you go. That's when that's when you love that's when you're
such a hustler that you grind just for the sake of grinding. You're not even getting anything out of
it. You're not even making any money. You're not winning anything. The true grind is just for the sake
of the grind. You love toil. Yes, you love toil so much. We're all house elves over here.
We just love it. We love being enslaved and toiling forever. It's what we want. Please don't give me
the sock. Don't give me the sock or I'll give you the cock. You read Harry Potter, right?
Yeah, it's a little bit of a cultural juggernaut when I was the perfect age to be reading it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I read, I read the first book I read, actually, it was the first book I
could read by myself without parents is the first Harry Potter book. I was reading, I was reading
Animorphs. I was reading Animorphs before Harry Potter. I think, I think, yeah. But I read Dita
Jackson's review of the Hogwarts legacy. And they said, you know, of course, I read the
damn books. Everybody read the damn books. That was my age at that time. And
their, their, their review on polygon was really good. I liked it. I watched Yahtzee's,
I watched a zero punctuation for the first time in a long time. I watched Yahtzee's review of
Hogwarts legacies. Oh, yeah. Also, the long story short, the game is, everybody seems to,
everybody seems to agree on the things that are not that good about the game. And it's just that
it just kind of feels like a very sort of like flat and not really that deep or immersive. It's
an open world, but it's all just kind of like, I don't know, people seem to think it's not that,
it's not that magical. It's all, it's all, it's all just kind of by the numbers.
Yeah. Very, well, what do they say? Gita said like, you know, like in the, in the context,
like they, they, they tried to make legacy as unrolling as possible. They tried to divorce
it as much as they could from like, you know, they put it, they put a trans character in there.
They made, they gave it a bunch. I mean, I saw the trans character and I thought it was like,
I don't know. Well, what was the, what was the name of the trans character? It was like,
yeah, they had some, some, some male sounding name. It was like a mean spirited sort of joke.
Like, well, we'll, we'll give you a trans character like that. I didn't, it didn't feel
right, but I didn't care. Well, I'm not sure. I'm not really sure what the mindset was there,
but I, I don't know. Gita said that it felt like they tried to divorce it from that and they tried
to make it more inclusive. They put more, you know, they put more like people of color. They put
more like, they put, I think there's like Indians or there's like people from Africa and stuff
in, in there. And it's like, okay, cool, I guess, but it kind of just, it kind of just serves to
remind you that the books aren't like this. Like, like it's actually kind of weird that the, that
the game is like so much more like diverse and inclusive when it's set in like 1885. And then
you read the books that are set in like, you know, the nineties or whatever. And it's like,
where did all the minorities go? It just makes you wonder like, what happened?
There were minorities in the books. There's a, there's a hand, there's a handful of them.
There's a handful of them. There's a hand full of them. There's a hand full of them. There's a
hand full of them. There's a hand full of them, Xiao Cheng. There's a, I, there's a handful.
Yeah. That's what you get. That's what you get. When you get Xiao Cheng, there's like,
okay, there's like two black kids. There's a, there's the one who is like,
the, the Gryffindor announcer kid. I forgot his name. Tom B NZ.
No, he has an Irish name.
Sean Finnegan, I thought that was the white boy in the film.
No, that's not Seamus.
Oh, Seamus, yeah.
There's Seamus Finnegan, but that's not who I'm that's not who I'm thinking of.
People of Colored Future and Harry Potter.
What's the he's a Gryffindor kid.
And in the movie, it was Thomas something or like Derek.
Dean Thomas, Dean Thomas.
Yes. Yes.
See, I didn't I didn't even realize he was black reading in the books,
but like he might have been like, you know, fair enough.
There was another there's a there's a there's a Slytherin kid named Blaise
Zabini, who is mentioned completely offhand like once.
And then in like book six, he has like one interaction with Harry.
There's Cho Chang, there's the Patel sisters.
There's Oh, no, it's Lee Jordan.
No, wait, hang on.
OK, Lee Jordan and Dean Thomas are both black in the movies.
And I think maybe only one of them is mentioned to be black in the books.
And I didn't even notice something like that.
Right. But it's literally like a handful of characters.
Did I did I mention those?
Oh, and of course, and who could forget who could forget Kingsley Shacklebolt?
Yes, the weirdest fucking name.
Yeah. And then in the movie, they give him that.
They give him that hat.
I don't know, something something weird about Kingsley Shacklebolt.
Yeah, but he's a bad ass.
But he's kind of a bad looks cool.
And he's a he's a he's a.
I don't know. I think he's fucking stupid.
It looks dumb. It's probably insensitive of me.
But in the but it's not like a traditional African sort of guy.
Yep. Yeah, probably.
Well, that's what that's weird, though.
Isn't that weird that they gave that they made the one black adult?
They gave him this like freak.
They gave him like a freaking African.
It's like they put him in that, you know, that orange, like patterned fabric
that that all the fricking Democratic senators wore when they knelt
on the Senate floor that one time during the BLM thing.
I don't know what that is at all.
Hang on, senators kneeling African cloth.
Here we go. Found it. First result.
Senators kneeling the Kente cloth, the Kente cloth.
And I don't know what it is.
I just know it's an African thing.
I mean, African clothing is like very colorful and cool.
Sure.
It's oh, no.
It's just a bit.
I don't know. It's just a bit weird that there's one black adult
and there's one named black adult and they gave him this like traditional
African garb.
Like, why isn't he just dressed like a wizard, you know?
Maybe he's nobody else.
Where's that hat?
Maybe he's from Africa and they have different ways.
Well, maybe he.
Well, maybe he is.
I mean, it's fine.
It's fine the way he looked.
But it's fine.
Blaze Zabini doesn't wear a hat.
So it's OK, I guess.
I'm talking about the I don't know
if I mentioned on the podcast before, but I remember reading that, you know,
JK Rowling in one of her many moments, I forget which moment she was just
doing some stuff and just getting controversy and controversy and stuff
could have just been general.
But the people, you know, the actors of Harry Potter, they were like,
yeah, we don't like what JK Rowling is saying.
But the ones that defended her saying, this is outrageous.
You can't attack a woman for being a woman or whatever the fuck they said.
Right.
And they're just defending her.
I don't even think they knew too much, but like it was funny to me.
It was amusing that there was the actors for Bellatrix Lestrange
and Lord Voldemort.
Those are the only ones.
The villains.
I think Luna Lovegood, too.
Oh, no.
Yeah, no.
I think I saw Luna Lovegood saying,
hey, she's just she's just defending women's spaces.
She's just speaking up for the right of women to have male free spaces.
What do you want them to be raped?
Stop it.
Yes, leave her alone.
Yes.
Do it.
It's just so I love sexual assault.
Hmm.
As a as a leftist, as a radical leftist, I do love sexual assault.
Clip that. Clip that, everybody.
But yeah, that's been playing the Fire Emblem and the play in the RuneScape.
Oh, and I continued watching Utena, which is good.
And also.
Star Trek, the next generation.
I'm just watching that every so often now.
Put on an episode of Star Trek.
Yeah, the good old that I never watched the entire show before.
I've seen like bits on TV.
So I'm like, fuck it.
Same. I like filling.
I feel I like filling the hours with good stuff instead of crap.
Yeah, I've seen a bunch of episodes that I used to just catch one here and there on
on TV sometimes.
I think I've mentioned that like when I was a little kid and I would see it was
the next generation, usually, I would I would sometimes catch the show when I
stayed up late and I would be like, when are they going to get like where they're going?
Like, is there an episode later where like,
we made it, we made it.
Yeah, we got to Earth or we got to.
I mean, I guess in Voyager, they are literally like trying to get back to Earth.
Or no, no, Deep Space Nine is that one of them is like that.
The Enterprise.
I think it's just called the Enterprise.
I don't know. I don't know Star Trek.
I've never watched Star Trek.
But they the first episode, they're just going.
They're leaving Earth and they they have like Q appears and he's like,
huh, humans, you suck.
And they're like picked hearts like no.
Wait, they're leaving Earth in the first episode.
They're they're yeah, they're leaving Earth and they're going to go out to explore
and see stuff. That's the the idea.
And Q is there saying humans are so war like and monstrous.
I'm here to stop you.
I'm here to tell you to go back or perish and then Picard convinces him with a
speech that actually humans have evolved beyond the war from the past.
And we're good now.
We're Star Trek.
And everyone says Star Trek.
And then Q is like, you will not stand between us and our trek through the stars.
Our Star Trek.
And everyone said, oh, my God, he said it.
Q said, hmm, that would be okay, but I'll be keeping an eye on you, little boy.
And then he disappeared.
And that's the first episode.
And so the idea is beyond that.
I guess they're just going out into the world.
Yes, as an explorer exploratory just seeing seeing what's going on.
He says at the beginning of every episode, what, you know, seek seek out new life
and new new frontiers.
Yeah, yeah, classic classic.
That space is so big, you guys.
So I really what's in there?
I really should have paid attention and maybe I wouldn't have had that expectation then.
But is it the first episode?
I think it's no, I think it's I think it's like most episodes start with
or maybe they end with that narration.
He says that a lot.
I think it does start that before like the song comes in.
It's either.
It's either Deep Space Nine or Voyager that like the premise of the show is
like there's a warp malfunction and they end up stranded somewhere like far from
the Federation and it's like the show is about like them trying to
trying to survive on their way back.
Yeah, I don't I thought Deep Space Nine was like a space station rather than a ship.
Oh, I think so.
They deal with the comings and goings of different people.
Yeah, but they are stationary, generally speaking.
It's probably Voyager.
That's the we have to get back.
Back to the future.
So there's the Star Trek, then there's the next generation, meaning
and we're doing Star Trek again.
I think original Star Trek is just we're just going out and going out.
Fine stuff. Yeah, I'm thinking of the subtitle.
So like
so Star Trek and then Star Trek, the next generation, AKA Star Trek.
But we did it at second time as smarter, smarter this time.
Then Star Trek Deep Space Nine was next,
which is takes place on a deep space, the ninth one.
And then Star Trek Voyagers were voyaging.
Star Trek.
Was that it?
There was another one, wasn't there?
I mean, I think Star Trek Expedition, Star Trek,
Travel Agency and Star.
I mean, I'm I know there's like later ones, like there's that animated one.
And I think there's one.
Well, I'm thinking of the before before it got reinvigorated with like J.J. Abrams
movies and stuff. Wait a fucking second.
There was an animated series between the original series and next generation.
What? What the fuck?
Yeah, I'm animated in what way.
What do they look like? Is it like Thundercats?
I said like kind of.
Yeah, it looks like this.
You know, I've seen these care.
I've seen these drawings before.
Wait, yeah, I've seen I've seen the one where it's like like Spock.
He's like putting his face over his hand.
Or he's like hand over his face like yeah.
OK, well, I forgot about that.
There's the original series, the animated series, the next generation,
Deep Space Nine Voyager Enterprise.
Well, what the remember that just as you were saying what what happens.
Well, OK, there's Enterprise and then like
13 years later, they made Discovery.
And I think that's kind of when the yeah.
What is it? What is Enterprise?
Enterprise, I don't know.
I've just heard of it.
I only know Star Trek through Mike's The Class and Rich Evans.
And they have talked about all the shows a little bit.
Follows the adventure of the first crew of the Starship Enterprise.
Who's the who's who's the captain?
Is it Archer, Jonathan Archer?
Jonathan Archer, yeah, it was a guy.
Voyager was a lady.
I've like literally never seen this guy before.
Played by Scott Bakula. OK.
More like yeah, Voyager is Janeway.
Janeway, and I think I think the people's
impression of Janeway is that she's sort of like a
she's sort of a loose cannon, like she sort of like breaks protocol.
Just when she feels like it.
That's what I've heard people say about her is that she's kind of a renegade.
In a way that like, like, you know,
freaking Picard would be like he would like, you know, he would he would call a
freaking council and be like, let's have a vote on like what the what the
Federation would want us to do in the situation.
And Janeway will just be like, damn, damn the the the the prime director.
We're all going to die. Get out. Fire the torpedoes.
I might be completely.
Shoot everybody you see.
Don't even don't don't wait for my command.
I might don't even wait for my command.
I might be wrong about that.
That's just what I feel like I've picked up through the grapevine.
You have. Yeah, I'm enjoying enterprise.
I really, really like.
Every time I see the next generation,
I'm like, that is the coziest place I've ever seen that that set.
Yeah.
Like the fact that the new shows are so dark.
I'm like, yeah, but like life is dark.
Turn the lights on.
I want to see that that well lit, soft lighting, carpeted space adventure.
It's the sort of thing I can curl up with a mug of cocoa and watch.
Those set, you know, say what you want about Star Trek, the next generation.
But those sets.
Well lit, very professionally lit.
Oh, oh, it's lit.
All right. Oh, it's lit.
I can see every I can see every detail of that blinking control panel.
It's funny.
It's funny how they have the same sets and the same hallways and you can you can.
And it's funny that like you can identify like what part of the ship they're in,
if you know what to look for, because they have all the same sets and all the sets
are like there's there's specific parts of the ship.
So they'll they'll pass through like the same hallway on the way to get to the same
elevator and like the way to the bridge and stuff.
Yeah, like they put I mean, I haven't I've only two episodes in so far.
Oh, yeah. Oh, right, right.
But I've just seen other I've seen bits.
I've seen bits.
I've just not watched the show in its fullness and it's like I've just seen.
I've just seen I've seen I've seen a map and I've seen somewhere I saw an image
that showed like, oh, yeah, if you look at the map, like when they're in this hallway,
like it's it's it's here in the interior map of the of the ship or whatever.
But they don't have them all connected.
Those sets those sets aren't connected in that exact way because like how do they move?
You mean.
Well, they disconnected.
Well, you know, that's that's the magic of television.
You know, you don't actually have to build the ship and like actually travel through.
I know, but like like it's it's I guess extra attention to detail that they would
know what hallway to use, what set to use for a generic walking show.
There's there's probably there's probably bits.
I bet some nerd on some forum in like the year 1992 wrote like a big thing
about like in this scene of they actually walk through the maintenance bay before
they get to the bridge, but like the maintenance bay is actually on the other
side from the the pleasure quarters, so, you know, they wouldn't have had to walk
through that room in this case pleasure quarters.
No, I would the holodeck the holodeck is what I'm talking about.
Have you seen it?
Yeah, you ever watch you ever watch
the real gyms like Simpsons Mysteries?
Yes, I love those videos.
Have you seen the one about the Rumpus room?
Yes, I do.
It's the it's the one that that Homer is sitting in a beanbag chair.
Yeah.
During the episode where they're all fighting over the comic book and he looks
out the window. Yeah, I think so.
When the lightning flashes and he's like, oh, they're fine.
Like that's a little one moment gag.
And then that room just most of the time just doesn't exist.
Yeah, it doesn't exist.
Sometimes it's referenced most of the time it doesn't exist.
When it does exist, its location is kind of inconsistent.
And sometimes the house exterior is shown in a way where like there probably should
be a window that would look out from the Rumpus room, but there is no window there.
But like, you know, in the Simpsons, they do have a general house layout where like
you understand how like the kitchen and the the front hall and the stairway up to
the bedrooms and the living room all fit together.
And sometimes they put a Rumpus room there and sometimes they don't.
And they know what really nobody really knows where the stairway leading to the
basement is, because it never really appears unless it's needed and someone's
going to the basement.
But yeah, in in they put they put the same thought into the the Star Trek where
like there's a general idea that like if they have to go to the med bay,
well, you know, the the engine room is on the way to the med bay.
So they might pass through the engine room while they're walking or whatever.
It's just good.
It's good stuff, continuity, consistency.
You like you like that?
No, no.
I don't really have that much to say about Star Trek,
because I haven't watched that much of it.
I've just I've just seen mostly TNG.
Used to see it as a kid on TV sometimes.
I hope to finish the entire show.
And then I'll be so smart.
You'll be as smart as Peacard.
Peacard, so clever.
Like Pecan.
It's pecan.
It's a pecan pie.
Do you say pecan?
Oh, John, look pecan.
Do you say pecan or pecan?
I actually do say I actually do say pecan.
I think in the south, they say pecan.
Yeah, I don't think I.
Yeah, cringe, cringe.
Pecan just sounds funny anyway.
True.
A pecan pie.
No, I'm sorry, pecan pie.
I'm sorry, P E C A N pecan pecan.
There's no pecan if it were pecan.
Then I don't know, they would.
You would have an age in before the end.
Right, exactly, exactly.
Yeah, I mean, I don't think I have anything else to.
I don't have any other topics.
We could do one piece or we could do voicemails or we could do nothing.
We could do what did we do last time with one piece?
Do we do it after voicemails?
I think we did it before.
OK, let's do it.
All right, let's let me read.
I forgot to I forgot to read it.
You little rascal, even though you told me to.
Is it 1077?
1077, yes.
I it came out during your stream.
So I mentioned it in the stream chat.
Right. And then I said I was going to go read it.
But then instead I rated Nate's stream
and Nate was reading one piece, but I didn't stick around.
That's why I was reminded because I was doing his one piece stream.
Yeah.
Oh, does he have another person in the Talking Pirates?
Were you jealous? You really should be Talking Pirate.
Oh, you're right.
Well, yeah, I'm a Talking Pirate and I'm here to tell you.
I think.
OK, I very funny and true.
I mean, to be pedantic, I think that the implication is that
we're we're talking pirates like we're they're talking about pirates.
Yeah, but it would only become a pun if there were multiple people on the show.
That's true, true and valid.
I thought you're asking like who
is the new girl?
Michelle, she's just silent.
She's like, I hate one piece.
I hate one piece. I hate one piece.
I've never. Oh, but look, she just can't.
Oh, but look at there.
But look at but look at Caesar.
Oh, but look at Caesar, though.
Cold season cold.
Jerma's cold blooded voyage volume 32.
Wait a sec. It's all vega punks fault.
Hmm.
All right. Yes.
I went back because I was lost.
I will recount this cover arc because it might be important.
OK.
So Jerma, right?
The the guys who are at the whole cake arc.
They saved Sanji or they were trying to take Sanji or no,
they were there for the wedding, but then everything went fucked up.
And so they became good guys to help Sanji and everyone escape.
Um,
Caesar was also there and in their escape,
Caesar was like, please take me with you, Jerma.
And so the Jerma siblings, they flew over
and they got onto their castle snail ship thing kingdom.
Right. They're floating kingdom.
I mean, the whole the whole cakes did the big mom people.
No, no, no, Caesar did.
They got away.
They basically Caesar did some really fucked up stuff and they stole.
They stole pudding.
It's a little hard to know because I think Blackbeard has pudding now.
But pudding was stolen in the escape.
Is pudding still evil or is she good now?
She she I think she's good.
She did she like decided she likes Sanji.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's why she she changed her tune.
I was like, I love you Sanji.
It's like actually heartfelt and cute that they like each other.
Yeah.
But yeah, the thing with whole cake, the Jerma were like two of them were captured
and the other siblings came and broke them out and they ran away.
Caesar came with them.
And then I guess he bumped into Judge and then they were like, who's this clown?
They fought for a moment.
But then they remembered that shared past and what we were in the previous
cover art pages were like, Oh, the Mads scientists.
They were remembering that was their thought their thought bubble.
Like, oh, yeah, we were in the Mad Scientist thing together.
And don't you remember that vagabond guy?
He's the reason everything got fucked up.
Is it because he won that?
Is it because he like won that contest with the flower gunpowder?
Yeah, he won the contest and he's the best scientist.
Oh my god, it's just like Dr.
Light was granted funding for his for his improved AI over Dr.
Wiley's gear system, the double gear.
These guys with their double gears
and they fought for a while and they're tired of hunting.
I'll show the world that my green blood technology was was right all along.
Well, I mean, yeah, that's that's mega punk who did that.
Oh, shit, you're right.
So it's the other thing.
It's my smile fruits.
My shitty my shitty smile fruits are better than
Vega Punks good actually work right fruits.
Fuck that guy.
So, yeah, these two seem to have come to an agreement of some kind that they are
like with each other against why were they against each other is important.
Why were they against each other in the first place?
Because they were it was a scientist like competition.
Oh, right. And they were all they were all fighting for second place.
But Vega Punk was the guy who was better than them all.
So in this moment, I guess they're like, wait a minute,
why don't we just kill Vega Punk?
Why don't we kill that guy?
That's in the present, though.
That's not like back in the past.
Now, this is the present that they're thinking.
Yeah, they're saying this is all Vega Punks fault,
which is at least why they stop fighting and I don't know what else it means.
But I guess we'll know next week if this continues.
I guess I forgot that they were fighting in the present.
Yeah, it's like like a bunch of weeks ago.
They started the Thought Bubble,
which opened up with the mad scientists.
Yeah, what?
And then it's finishing.
Why were they fighting?
Did they just like happen to run into each other somewhere?
And they were like, yeah, it's you again.
They ran into each other because Caesar Clown,
who was on whole cake, escaped with the German siblings,
you know, Sanji's brothers and sisters and sister as they came back.
You can see them in like Ichiji and
right, Kujo, I can't remember her name.
Right.
Just sort of hanging out, being like, yeah, they're fighting.
They're still like, they don't give a shit.
And in the in the thing, I went back,
pudding was Kid Matt and if I can cracker was turned poison full.
It looks like the poison from punk has a cracker.
So I thought Caesar did it.
Who's cracker cracker cracker was one of the
the
what do you call them, the commanders of the of the big mom pirates who
Luffy defeated with Gear 4th.
That was the introduction of Gear 4th into the comic.
OK.
And he smashed his crackers that he kept making.
They had a cracker fruit.
He beat the shit out of him.
And then.
Yeah, so.
Pudding was Kid Matt.
But then we later see pudding aboard Blackbeard ship.
Kidnapped like imprisoned with Kobe, I think.
So I don't know who whether Blackbeard was there or whether Caesar gave it,
gave pudding to them or I don't fucking know what's going on.
Yeah, yeah.
But anyway, it's a lot to keep track of for sure.
That's that's a little reminder of what the fuck this cover is about.
Yeah, OK.
So I mean, long story short, Caesar and
Jerma are teaming up and not Jerma.
Wait, is his name Jerma?
Judge, Caesar and judge are teaming up.
Or it seems that way.
Seems that way.
OK, I'm.
Partway through the chapter and OK, so
Shaka says they're talking about King.
They just they just noticed that these guys are Lunarians.
And Shaka says
he talking about King, he said he was called Abler and he was a test subject.
Who escaped punk hazard with Kaido.
So I guess that that's how they got Lunarian DNA was from King.
OK, yeah, make about that.
The thing was the thing was Zorro
seeing like he's the one who knows all the information.
He just took him really far too long to put it together.
He's colorblind.
Hey, it doesn't have depth perception anymore.
Right.
That changes your color.
In that case, pay attention to the flames on their backs.
Right. OK, so the.
So when the flame is on.
They're like they're invincible kind of.
But when the flame is off, they're like super fast or something like that.
Like there's a reason they turn it on and off, right?
Oh, yes, yes.
They do.
They don't fight.
They can't do damage.
I think I can't remember exactly, but I think King only attacked
when his flames were off.
Yeah.
And that's the only time he was vulnerable as well.
So when he's got his flames on, he's not attacking.
Yeah, yeah.
Which means that you've got to attack when they attack.
That's so fucking strong.
Don't do this.
It is very strong.
Mainly Lunarians are the main aliens.
They're not from the moon, though, right?
Despite the name.
Well, we don't know.
OK.
The only thing we know about Lunarians are that King is one of them
and they have these characteristics.
When when Enel went to the moon, there were like some other aliens there that were not.
There were Mole Man on the moon.
And that's considered canon because it was a cover story, I think.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, the moon's pretty big.
Maybe there's Lunarians as well.
I feel like they said someone said that Lunarians like came.
They lived on the red line.
But I mean.
It could be.
Could be a big important thing.
I don't remember that.
I was thinking.
Hey, did we talk about this that like the red line is artificial?
I think I had that as a pretend like an idea.
Yeah, OK, maybe it was built and therefore
cut off the oceans from one another so that they could be more easily controlled.
Definitely. I mean, if that's true, then it wouldn't make any sense for them to like be from there.
Because like it didn't exist for that long.
I guess it could have existed for like a thousand years.
Maybe the devil fruit is like, I got the line line fruit.
Line line.
Yeah, maybe.
I was thinking it was one of the one of the
the ancient weapons that might have created it.
I think I think I think we talked about this already.
I think in fact, I think you probably said that and that's where I got that idea.
Yes. Yeah.
OK, just I'm I'm paying attention.
I am paying attention.
I'm I'm I'm also reading Nami's butt.
There it is.
Let's show that.
Let's make let's make let's make zoom in.
Let's make real sure to show that.
We wouldn't want the listeners to feel like they're missing out.
It's petite.
It's got that thigh gap.
This is important.
True.
So very true.
Jin boy, Jin boy, that's good.
Thunderbolt, Thunderbolt should do double damage
because Jin boy is water elemental.
So lightning should do double and it did.
Yeah, it worked pretty, pretty effective.
Hey.
Oh, he splashes into the floor.
The way is it called the wave wave fruit?
It's so awesome.
Yeah.
The being able to swim through solid.
And that was it was
senior pink. I was going to say Mr.
Yeah, senior pink.
Is Brooke able to like sense
where he is through like soul magic?
Because he like senses that he's swimming through the floor.
No, I think he just saw.
He saw it or he heard the splash.
And so it's like he's under the floor.
Watch out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I think you're right.
But it looked like he fell because he was damaged.
I will decree one.
Anyone who threatens Nami saw him face Kevin.
Decree nine.
Anyone who makes her scream will receive dot, dot, dot.
The numbers used might be a pun as nine and one can be combined to form Kui,
which can imply fishing, seafood in some contexts.
OK.
Yeah, because because Jim Bae is a fish and Sanji cooks fish.
Yes.
Oh, true.
You could you could use knives and cut him.
It's his one weakness, actually.
He's being being cooked, being filleted.
Oh, there's another.
There's Lilith's butt.
Let's let's show it.
Let's let's let's not neglect to show it.
Poo boy.
Bubble gun bubble, something else.
Hey, ho.
Let's go.
You and Nate are exactly the same.
I.
I don't know these these butts are not.
They're not that great.
They're OK. They're fine.
I'm a I'm a boob, the fact that they are being drawn.
I'm a drawn attention to a boob guy.
Yeah, I heard I heard Nate.
I heard Nate saying that it's kind of unusual.
There are like so many butts on display and it's kind of true.
Yeah, Oda Oda doesn't really focus on but I don't know.
I I would have to to go back and like actually count
how many gratuitous butt shots there are.
I don't really remember there being that many.
There's two in this chapter draws your attention to it,
but maybe the ever so often maybe it just happens.
Maybe, maybe, maybe.
After some serious reason, we have to we have to we're going to have to look into
this deeply green.
Oh, here we go.
Bubble gun.
She brushed it off like it was nothing.
Huh. Green blood gives you the pros and cons of having a fruit ability.
And these bubbles were designed to hurt.
OK, so.
Yeah, they're weak too.
They're they're they're weak as same as any fruit user.
OK.
Which is a I'm glad because otherwise there'd be way too upbeat.
It would be. Yeah, if it were like.
If it were like, yeah, actually lumarian blood like means that like now they they
they're fine in water and see some doesn't do anything to them.
And yeah.
Also, I'm I'm yeah, you you read, but I have a comment.
Go ahead.
I think this is the first time we've heard one of these seraphim speak.
Um, yeah.
I didn't realize they had like they could talk.
I think that's and have a personality, but this little Hancock,
she's she's doing I think I saw someone on Twitter say that they thought that young
Hancock might be the only one that can have feelings because it's like
specifically tied to her fruit power is like emotions.
And I don't know if that's true or not.
But I mean, I I have no reason to believe that the others don't have anything to say.
Yeah, but they it could be like that.
I feel like because Zoro said, oh, you're more than a robot.
You're I can sense humanity in you.
Like he could tell that the little mehawk
was not just a robot.
It was a person like he sense something.
So like I feel like that means a little bit.
He just doesn't feel like talking that much, I guess.
OK, I see nor Jim Bay nor Kuma.
They're all quite quiet people.
True. That's true.
I think I think it was tectonic improv in my discord mentioned something about this.
And it seems like yeah, the original boa Hancock uses the mellow mellow fruit
by like if it makes you fall in love with her or something.
This baby one does not do that.
This one this one gets you by making you think that she's cute.
She does a little wink and they go, oh, so that's good.
That's good that it doesn't work the same way.
Uh.
I'm a little unsettled, honestly,
because it's up is he's turned to stone.
He's dead.
So is Frankie, you're you're on and Lilith, too.
You're unsettled by that, that that's a problem for you.
Well, you know, I feel like being made of stone is not so good.
Oh, he's been in he's been in tougher jams than he's gotten himself.
Out of it, you know, it's on the one hand.
On yeah, on the one hand, it's like,
oh, no, if the Seraphim continue to be enemies,
then he's dead.
But this just sort of means that, oh, they'll be friends again.
I guess because she'll undo it.
Is it is the only way to undo it is if they like choose to undo the stone thing?
Is that how it works? I forget.
That's how I understand it.
Yeah.
It's like, like, I remember a time.
Not like long ago, but like not that long ago in the canon of the story,
Hancock and Blackbeard were fighting.
And she she had the ability to unstone a bunch of people on the mirror.
Marines were there also.
Or something, there was something going on.
But she had the she had the bargaining chip of being able to unstone people.
So presumably they would stay like that otherwise.
Yeah.
OK, well, I mean, I guess she'll have to either get her
to help them out or they'll have to figure some other secret trick to unstone
somebody. I'm on the last bit now and I see Shaka has been assassinated.
Oh, my God, this is gruesome.
It's like a pretty gruesome panel.
Yeah. Damn.
Shaka, he's been shot.
What's going on? Who was that?
He's been shooted.
It's nothing I would hope with a single shot.
Shot through these. Who's that you brought with you, huh?
OK, so I mean, seems like it wasn't Shaka.
And and unless this is an elaborate ruse to fake his own death.
Yeah, yeah.
And Vega, I don't know.
Vega Punk seems genuinely surprised by this.
So it doesn't seem like Stella is like now is evil.
I mean, he seems I feel like it's it's pretty clear that Vega Punk is not the one
pulling the strings. Yeah.
It was always a bit weird, the idea that he would be outed as a villain
soon after being agreeing to like go with the Straw Hat Pirates on their journey.
Yeah, you're right.
And being an enemy of the world government.
That'd be like a little weird.
You're right.
But yeah, have his own plans.
Like, I don't know, I don't think it's that outrageous, but yeah.
Yeah, it's a little different than law with having like their pirates.
So ultimately, we know that their alliance will end and it did after Kaido.
So.
But either way, yeah.
So this chapter,
brief recap, everyone's fighting the Seraphim
and some people are doing not so good.
Yeah, true.
Yeah, Sanji seems to be holding his own against Jim Bae for the time being.
I think Nami and Sanji and Brooke will be OK.
Yeah.
I mean, Sanji and Brooke against Zoro and Luffy will be OK.
But Usopp, Lilith and Frankie, they fucking are dead.
Yeah, they're toast. Yeah, it's over.
It's it's freaking over.
And then Shaka gets shot in the head and with a little pistol gun.
I imagine they'll probably end up in the tank with Vega Punk.
Well, maybe.
Well, I mean, yeah, it's someone.
Whoever's whoever's pulling the strings and just shot Shaka and is keeping these CP
nine, these CP agents in here is probably the same person who's controlling the.
The Seraphim, right?
So I mean, I imagine they will take these stone statues and bring them to the tank.
OK, so here is my thought process.
Where's Stussy?
Yeah, where is she right now?
Haven't seen her.
She was with someone.
She was with one of the groups that we just looked at.
And now she's.
Oh, no, wait, she was with Chopper.
Wasn't she wait?
No, she was she was with she was with Sanji.
Stussy, I was thinking of Bonnie.
Stussy Bonnie is also on the on the loose.
And Chopper is as we haven't seen Chopper.
Yeah, Chopper is the assassin.
He learned to learn to shoot.
He did it. Yeah.
He got his little poofs.
He violated his Hippocratic Oath
and became a demon.
He's he's like unlocked blood on his hooves.
He awakened his human, human devil fruit and became the worst thing ever.
A person.
Wait, the worst, monsterful man.
Are his are his new like post time skip forms.
Is this is that his awakened like zone?
Is that what that's about?
No, no, I don't think so.
I think Luchi and Kaku awaken their zones
and that's why they look different now, right?
Yeah, I mean, I think there's
potential for like Chopper to have found a medicinal way of awakening a devil fruit
with his rumble ball, but maybe it's just for him.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm not really sure.
Because like the idea that he can do all of these
different forms, whereas normally a zone can only have three forms,
he can have like seven plus a giant monster.
Maybe for him, it's just him using like medicine to fuck with it.
Just kind of means that like his forms are like a different thing than like
yeah, classical, whatever awakening.
What does it what does awakening even mean?
It just just just level out better.
Yeah, it's just you figure out that you can actually do an even better animal.
You can do it.
You can utilize this power in a way that you thought was not possible before.
You can do more with it, right?
Or whatever.
Well, yeah, so it's interesting with Chopper because like maybe his ability
to do that is like going to be revolutionary,
but nobody really thinks about it because he's a little reindeer and he's a little
cute reindeer and he never gets recognition.
He never gets a good bounty.
He's the most impressive medicinal mind in the world.
It would be it would be pretty funny if he like, yeah,
if he hit with his like five berry bounty, like completely revolutionizes
like fruit technology or something.
And it's like, yeah,
Vega Punk will have a field day with his medicine.
Yeah, that's interesting.
Yeah, anyway, like them to get to talk about science and shit.
That'd be cool.
So the very end of the chapter, Shaka gets shot in the head
and blood has come out of his head and there's blood coming on the thing.
But then there's a few panels.
It says katak, katak, katak, meaning a
footstep that goes one, two, which I'm assuming is like a heel.
So like a high heel, heel, toe, katak, katak.
That's what I'm assuming that might be referencing.
I think I think, though,
that Stussy was wearing the same clothes as everyone else with the big round shoes.
I'm not sure it could be her.
The only reason it could be her is just because she's mysterious.
She's been on the island before.
Do we know that?
Yeah, remember when you phoned up, like we need help.
We need help from that mysterious person.
And it turned out it was Stussy.
OK, OK.
So like she was on the island.
Yeah, that's looking.
And meaning that she knows the island, she knows a bit about stuff and she can go
around places and she's mysterious.
And she's already shown to be a double agent for
the Cypher pole.
And she's she's also a vampire and a clone of a lady
that was on the Rocks Pirates, who is an old lady who is now got the son,
Edward Weevil, a son of Whitebeard going around.
Right.
So she is obviously very important to something.
Why she's killing people, I don't know.
But the fact is she very easily could be.
I think I think she's she's going to walk down there with a kutuk
like high heel and she's going to be like, haha.
Yeah, I'm evil.
I think that sounds pretty dang plausible.
That's that's the best theory I got.
No, you don't got it.
I have it now.
It's now I heard it.
I've internalized it.
It was easy.
I put it in a marketplace of ideas for free and how it's been used and abused.
Exactly. Exactly.
I mean.
Yeah, I think you're probably right.
Fucking I don't know what her.
I mean, you know, she she betrayed the other CP guys as in Kaku and
Luchi. So, you know, this is just a continuation of that trend of betraying the CP.
So, yeah, it all kind of, yeah, it kind of makes a lot of sense.
They're making a lot of sense right now.
Whatever she's doing, I think if she's a clone of a rocks pirates person,
I think that fact might be.
Like indicative of motivation for her.
Yeah, because why else would it?
Why else would you have her be also a clone of a famous pirate from a pirate
crew that was almost reforming when big mom and Kaido said, hey,
let's reform the rocks pirates.
Remember the rocks pirates?
Let's do that again.
I wonder if there's some, I don't know, some kind of like thing that only someone
with like that DNA could could access like a secret room,
like the Paw Paw Fruit information room or something like that.
Yeah, I'm seeing a situation where Bunny is going to be integral to saving everyone.
Yeah, because she's nowhere to be found right now.
Yeah. And Kuma.
Where's Kuma?
Kuma's in he's climbing Red Line to Marijwa, I think.
Yeah.
Yeah, from for a moment there, I thought he was flying towards Egghead.
Although.
Is he on the other side of the red line to Egghead?
I don't think so.
No, no, he's not.
They're in the New World, right?
The the Revolutionary Army HQ is in the New World and so is this.
I think I want to say, yeah, I think he probably is in the New World.
So he would be on the same side.
So it's not like he's climbing the Red Line to jump over it and get to new Egghead.
Probably not.
I wouldn't think I wouldn't following the program.
I wouldn't assume so.
Yeah.
Don't know what he's doing, but I haven't seen him in a while.
Yeah, Bonnie's around.
So Sentomaru is talking about Ohara.
But he didn't really tell us anything we didn't already know.
Yeah, we already knew that the world government is here to destroy the world
of the island because of information they have.
I like the panel where it's like, by the way, this happened like 12 years ago.
Refresher on the Ohara.
It happened 12 years ago in in the comic and in real life.
Yeah, look at that little that little drawing of Aokiji in the bottom right.
He's so.
Yeah.
Mm hmm.
Very cool.
Niko Rubin's got a little like square smile.
She's a little tiny.
She looks silly.
She looks very silly.
Wait, wait, wait.
Let's let's get a let's get a zoom.
I don't know what to do.
The more I look at it, the funnier it gets.
It's just a little like the the the the ink
uses just a little too thick for a mouth.
It didn't quite, but it doesn't matter.
It's fine, whatever. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, print it, print it, send it to the send of the printers.
Hell, yeah.
Um, okay.
Well, I guess I don't really have that much else to say about this chapter.
It was good.
I liked it.
I had fun.
Uh, uh, the Seraphim.
Yeah, I think I think it's probably true
that if a young what's her shit?
The Amazon, um, not Bellatrix Hancock can speak, then probably all of them
have the ability to speak and all that.
But I mean, she only spoke to like do a fricking strategic thing.
She might not not actually like have, I mean,
she's probably like a complete sociopath
who can only like who can only fake emotions.
Yeah, that would be like she can speak if she needs to for some strategic purpose,
but like she doesn't wouldn't do it normally because like she's a killing machine.
Yeah, that bubblegum will be useful.
Right. Yeah, it was pretty good.
I was at the if only if only well, Luffy could get little Hancock
because Luffy doesn't care about women.
He might still think she's cute.
No, no, he probably wouldn't care.
Yes, it's an odd it's odd because it's a different kind of thing.
The idea, the joke before is that Luffy doesn't he's asexual, you know, he doesn't
like, huh, beautiful woman.
What's that? I don't care.
What if what if the fact?
Hey, do you have any meat?
You know, like that's that's his bit.
But like when it's a little cute girl, it's a different kind of thing.
But I haven't seen Luffy do like it.
Oh, it would be kind of funny.
And I would kind of buy it if like, oh, my God,
now Hancock's power works on Luffy because she's not hot.
Now she's cute and that and he's and he's and Luffy's normal enough
that like he cares about that sort of thing.
But I could also see it just being like he doesn't give a fuck about anything.
Yeah, I mean, at this point, I think.
Who in the crew, if not Luffy, could resist the cute rays?
Maybe maybe Zoro.
I was thinking Zoro, yeah.
I don't I don't think Zoro would be particularly moved by a by a cute vulnerable being.
He does have that that Nico, Nico Robin probably would not.
I'm not Tashiki or was it Tashiki?
The person who we know is Tashiki, like the underling to smoker.
But like, what was the name?
Is it Kuina, a Kushin?
Kuina. Yeah, I want to say it's Kuina.
Yes. You know, that's true.
So he might feel some does have emotions.
But yeah, I'm not saying he doesn't feel I don't feel like he's like.
Yeah, he might.
He doesn't get as riled up in the same way as the others.
I think what do you think about Nico Robin?
Do you think Nico Robin could be would be or maybe Nami might be cutthroat enough
that she might not be Nami and Nico Robin could be.
I could see it going either way.
I could see it going either way for both of them.
I think I think because Lilith smiled and she got that Nami would also.
I think Nico Robin.
She finds things cute that are pathetic.
You're right.
She really likes the dark things and she likes dark things.
And like, she finds pathetic things adorable.
What do you? Is there an example?
I don't remember.
Oh, what was it?
It was what's his name?
Kanji Rose, shittily drawn dragon beast.
They used to climb the elephant.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
To climb, so and she was like, oh, my God, you can do it.
Like, it's like such a terrible drawing and everyone was like,
oh, this guy sucks.
But she was almost in tears about how much she loved.
Well, I mean, when she she was so sad when he died, I forgot about that.
That's so funny.
It was such a nice little moment.
I've totally forgot about that.
OK, on the one hand, I mean, Bella, not Bella, why do we keep Boa?
Boa being like, oh, this is agonizing.
Oh, it hurts so bad.
Like that is kind of pathetic.
But yeah, I think that.
Well, not not pathetic.
And I think she would see through the manipulation.
I think is what I mean.
Like she would need. I agree.
She would need it to be like genuinely unsettling for her to actually like it.
So right.
And if it's if it's if it's a normal if it's a normie kind of cute,
she's like, yeah, OK, OK, sis.
Agreed 100 percent.
And I think that rules and I hope and I hope that we get to see.
I hope that we get to see this just it completely not work on her
because I think that's what that's what would happen.
No, yeah, if it worked on Lilith, it would probably work on Nami.
I think.
Although Lilith might be like.
Lilith seems kind of like hyper emotional or she seems very
she seems very emotional and prone to like yelling and stuff.
Nami is a little more calculating, but she's might still.
I honestly think Nami is a little prone to yelling and emotional as well.
Yeah, yeah, she she's she's one of the ones along
with Zoro Zoro and Usopp and Chopper will always scream at stuff.
You're you're right, actually. And Brooke as well.
I think Zoro would probably because Zoro
yeah, has this like.
Memory of like a young girl that like died and that he like traumatized him.
I feel like he probably would be vulnerable to little little boa being like,
oh, it hurts.
Yeah, I think I'm thinking I'm thinking Robin would just yeah, see through it.
So that's so cool.
I hope I hope we get to see that.
Anyway, that I just wanted to say one more thing.
The top with Caesar and George.
They hate Vegapunk.
I had I think Cassidy in in your chat was hinting
that it could be Caesar with the gun.
Oh, or Josh Caesar is the one who has used a gun before as a weapon.
I yeah, when did he the thing is, though, how did he how would he have got here?
Well, you know, that's the thing.
He is a scientist, so I know he could probably science his way in
and he can fly himself, I think.
Yeah, can he just fly like from island to island?
I I think so.
I don't really know.
I think it's really fucking good cloud his his his poison cloud fruit
means he can fly a bit, but he needs to land at some point.
I don't think that was ever explained, but that's how I assume.
If he could just travel between islands with no ship,
like that would be like amazing, amazing capability of that fruit.
But then like, why couldn't smoke or do that?
Could smoke or do that?
Or would he get tired and have to lay out?
Yeah, I think it's yeah, it's probably there's limits to how much
you can you can do that and fly and whatever smokers got.
Can a could could ace just turn into a cloud of fire and go from island to island?
No, he had to use that little that little like rocket propelled sailboat.
Yeah, yeah. So I could I could see it being Caesar.
Yeah, I could see it being Caesar.
And, you know, he got here somehow when no one was paying attention.
Because like that flashback or that that cover story is like
as soon as they left whole cake.
Meanwhile, everyone else was in Wano doing Wano stuff.
Yeah. So there's potentially a lot of time
to judge and Caesar to hatch a plan to infiltrate Egghead
and do some some some little sneaky, you know what?
Totally plausible.
Think the Stussy theory makes sense.
But I mean, you know, this.
It would make sense for for us to be the motivation makes sense.
Yeah, plus it would just like, oh,
that's why we've been seeing it in the cover arc story.
It's like, OK, because it's going to be immediately relevant to
what's what's happening on the island.
Yeah, that's pretty good.
I buy it. So and if he and if he's here,
then probably judges here too, right, maybe.
Yeah, I don't know why they would both be like physically together.
Yeah, I feel like Caesar would be sneaking around.
Judge would be nearby with his ships.
And that's probably not necessary.
Probably not.
I really don't know, because it's sort of like they want to get back at Vega Punk.
Therefore, what do they do?
What are they doing right now?
Caesar might be they are doing that assassinating people.
Or he's assassinating the people.
He's got control of the seraphim.
If they're not here doing this, then I don't know what they are doing.
Yeah, why would say why would Caesar have control of the seraphim?
That's why Stussy would have the control,
because she had the little yeah, this CP zero thing.
But wouldn't Vega Punk's orders supersede her orders, though?
That's the thing that's confusing.
I would only I would assume that either Stussy knows how to operate
the computers and change the programming somehow or Caesar does.
The only thing that's weird about Caesar being here is.
If surely he knows that Luffy is here or he will find out
and he's fucking terrified of the straw hats because they beat the shit out of him.
Right.
And they forced him to collaborate with him and their their assassination of big mom.
I think so, eventually.
Yeah.
Maybe, I mean, it could I guess it could still be a fake assassination
and like Stussy and Chaka are like collaborating.
For what purpose, though?
They've been collecting agents.
I mean, well, that would explain how how the seraphim are in their control
because Chaka is Vega Punk.
And so Chaka has basically the highest authorization to order them.
True.
So that would that could explain that.
Because without without.
Yeah, without without a Vega Punk giving orders,
there's no real explanation for why Vega Punk can't just tell the seraphim to stop.
Did they didn't they say and didn't they say there was some line about like.
The set like one seraphim one CP zero can't like contradict another one's orders.
Like like like once one had given an order, another CP can't just call it off.
Like an even higher order has to be given for it to change.
Yeah, I think they did say something like that.
I feel like they said something like that, which would which if true would mean that
like if Chaka says something, then Vega Punk, no other Vega Punk can intercede
because there's no higher authority would have to carry that one out before another order could be given.
That's crazy.
So so I don't know.
That makes me think maybe Chaka actually is faking his death.
You want to you want to go voice mails?
Yeah.
Well, let's do a little voicemail.
Speakpipe.com slash PCP voicemail.
If you want to leave a PCP voicemail.
OK, there's not there's not that many.
He's a normal amount.
OK. First one image, we got an image from Prince Isolation.
I think it's OK.
It's me.
Oh, I think these are stream moments.
Oops, threw up a little and then get it.
Oh, I'm.
I'm asking who about a little green gummy little green gummy bear while Munchy is benching 500 behind me.
That's true.
Oh, God, my potassium.
Yeah, I keep having like weird heart palpitations and complaining about them on stream.
And then game gamers tavern instructed me on stream that I should get more potassium.
And then I can he had a similar issue once and that potassium helped.
So I've been trying to eat more bananas.
And then don't trust anyone.
They will always betray you.
True, true, true.
Give I'm watching you.
Don't worry.
I'll betray you.
Aha.
I knew it.
You can trust me to do that.
Thank you.
Thank you for proving me right.
There we go.
Oh, thank you.
I knew you'd come through for me.
Grievance hashtag and I'm grievance number 2793 on September 5th, 2016.
Trixie.
I assume that's as Trixie did this, this, this and this.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm a very.
Yes, I am a very cantankerous and generally unpleasant person.
It's true.
Anyway, let's move on to the next one.
It's another image and a voicemail from Prince's isolation again.
God, not another one.
Oh, this is.
Oh, this is give.
Oh, little Pikmin.
Martha's going to die.
Oh, this is from my stream.
Did you carve a pumpkin and put it on your head?
Oh, it's because you have the V2.
Hey guys, let's play Fire Emblem.
Always with it.
There's so many reinforcements.
I've only watched you play Fire Emblem one time and boy, it sure does take a while.
It does.
Boy, it sure does take a while to play it, to do a battle.
Yeah.
Just like in real life.
Yeah, that's true.
I don't remember the Pikmin.
What was the Pikmin from?
Yeah.
Why are you holding a Pikmin?
I would say that though.
I would say.
It's a little Pikmin in real life.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
All right, let's listen to the voicemail.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh, I just realized that I haven't contextualized the last image that I sent.
So that is, you know, been streaming.
And so the next one, this one is Gib streaming, you know, as I made some eclectic fan art
of these two content creators streaming.
Aren't I original?
Aren't I just the most fucking original fan in the world?
Okay, enjoy.
We did.
I did have a little moment where I said, oh, I threw up a little bit in my mouth because
it just happened.
I don't know why I'm saying Kieris to this.
I think it's a gummy bear.
Maybe I'm just generally contemplating the gummy that is something I would do.
I did at one point step away and through my fridge and eat some and eat some gummies that
I just had sitting around.
One of these days, one of these days, how much do you think I should sell like a pound
of gummies for like, like 25 bucks?
25 bucks a pound?
I can't visualize a pound of something.
I think it would be like a sort of a big handful size, you know, maybe like the size of like
a roll of toilet paper.
Yeah, probably smaller than that.
A little smaller than a roll of toilet paper, but like a little plastic bag filled with
little gummies in it.
Yeah.
25.
25 bucks?
Seems kind of steep, but I guess candy is just cheap.
So.
I mean, I mean, a pound is a lot.
A pound is a lot.
We've eaten that for a while.
Well, I mean, I wouldn't, but most people would.
You know, I'll try to see like how much it would actually cost me to make.
You know, as always, I'll have to, I'll have to find, figure out the cost and then, and
then figure out price from there.
These are.
Yeah, I mean, you'll be like competing with candy factories that can make billions of
candies with one cent of production.
Yeah.
I can't, I can't really compete on, I can't really compete on economy of scale.
So I'll have to make them cute.
I'll have to make them cute and funny somehow.
And like.
Cute little.
Like people, I don't feel like people would need gummies in bulk.
They could buy little packets and then you could have the price, you could mark the
price up so that they, they're like, Oh, it's only a couple bucks.
But like.
Scaled up.
It would be sound, it would sound like an unreasonable number, but scaled down.
It's a cute little package.
A cute little package.
But I mean, if I were buying some gummies, like on a Kickstarter, I would hope to get
like a pretty large amount.
I would hope.
Yeah.
That's what I was thinking to do a Kickstarter.
We're like, Hey, who, anyone who buys a pound of gummies, like if I can sell like
20 pounds of these, then like, we're good.
You should sell them.
I would, I would say, I would set the, I would set the goal to like, I would set the goal
to like 50 bucks.
And then like anything over and above that is just, is just gravy.
I don't know.
Yeah.
So I was a bit of a different beast making a food product for Kickstarter.
On, you know, I just, it would be inconvenient to make little packets cause like it's kind
of like, why do I even want to bother with making like a $5 sale?
Like I got to go all the way to the fricking post office.
No.
Yeah, I get it.
Yeah.
I'm just thinking of like in a shop, like a little packet of something, not like a tiny
thing, but like to get, to get the size of a Haribo gummy bear packet.
Yeah.
If I was putting them in shops, that would be a whole different story.
That's like a whole process to do that that I don't even, I don't even understand.
And this is all off topic.
Thank you, Prince, for the fan, for the fan art.
Thank you.
For the stream moments.
I like mine a lot.
I really appreciate it.
It's cool.
Okay.
Next one is called literally world ending user experience three, two, one go.
Ben on stcomics.com.
I noticed that the Beescapades when you're reading Beescapades, the tab, the name of
the tab says the vapors instead of Beescapades.
All the other products are correct, but I guess you forgot to change that one when you
made up page.
So I don't know if you want to fix it or something.
I don't know.
Okay.
Bye.
Yeah.
I didn't thank you for, I'm going to put that in my notes.
I actually noticed there's a couple of broken links.
So pages 83 and 90 and 106 have like, like their next button is like broken, which sucks.
So that's not good.
That's not good.
I have to, I have to fix that.
I will get on that.
I'll do that at some point after maybe when I'm, maybe when I'm actually drawing it or
something, I'll, I'll, I'll get around to fixing that.
It's actually not, it's not hard to fix at all.
Actually, actually it would take me literally like five minutes.
Maybe I'll just do it right after this.
If I remember.
Next one is called a but a epic comic smiley face.
Three, two, one, go.
Also two things.
I just read the escapades for the first time and it was so good.
Why didn't I read it sooner?
It's so funny and adventurous and engaging and the mechanics are great and the diction
is so awesome.
Then you feel good about it and yourself for making it.
On three pages, there were technical issues with the website on 83 and 90.
That's what I just said.
Next buttons that were below the page, the comic page, didn't have the right links.
And then on page 106, it shows that there's a second image, but it isn't loading.
That's the.
So yeah, that's, that's still Rob.
That's what I fucking comic anyway.
Okay.
Hey, good catch.
Too bad I caught them all first idiot.
You say with those websites still broken.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's still broken, but like I knew it was broken this whole time.
Don't you look like a fool now.
Um, Lamal.
Okay.
Next one is called Kaga D's nuts.
Three, two, one, go.
Catching up on my PCP and I noticed that give has been playing some fire emblem.
Yeah.
You're not already aware.
There's this neat little PlayStation game called caring saga made by the creator of
the series shows a Kaga, AKA the guy that Nintendo desperately wants to erase from
existence.
Like he wasn't even named at all in the 30th anniversary art book collection for fire
emblem.
So that's a little bit fucked up at least they had the dignity to credit him for
the switch release of the first fire emblem.
So that's something I guess.
But anyway, caring saga literally just PlayStation fire emblem.
It's got these gorgeous right works.
Um, animation is not nearly as cool as a GBA games, but you know, it looks nice in
its own way and it's a fun little rock.
I highly recommend.
Okay.
I'm looking at it.
Tearing.
I thought you said curing.
It's the caring saga.
We care about this.
We care about you, the player.
Oh, little tiny fruit fly.
No.
All of these images I'm finding on Google are very, very small, but I will post one
anyway.
So I can see what I'm looking at.
So like it's like little guys, little RPG.
Oh, look at him.
Wait a minute.
Look at his face.
Oh, this is a better image.
So yeah, it's grid based, but it's individual.
They're zoomed in.
So they're more like people.
I'm sorry.
All I can see is the weird tangent of how like the line of his collar leads directly into
the line that I think is his mouth.
And that's just bad.
That's just bad design.
That's just bad illustration work right there.
That's a right angle.
Can I have right angle?
No, it's like the one line becomes the other line in a very way that is making me think
I'm seeing some sort of an illusion.
Don't like it.
What is this called?
Curing saga?
Tearing saga?
Tear.
Like I'm crying about it.
Okay, so what are we going to do about this?
I'm going to cry about it.
What's the solution?
I'm not going to play it for the Fire Emblem series, but I will probably have a look at
it because this looks nice.
There's a game that a bunch of people have recommended me.
I'm drawing a blank on what it's called, but somebody made a...
Super Mario Brothers 2.
No, it's somebody made an indie battle network.
It's called something like...
Butthole network.
Love is in the heart or something.
That's not what it's called.
Indie battle network, one step from Eden.
A couple people have recommended me a game called One Step From Eden.
I think they might have even had a voicemail about it.
But I have not looked at it, but I will probably check it out at some point.
Next one is an image.
What is...
Let's see.
Is this a reference to something?
I don't quite understand.
Yeah, I'm not...
I mean, I ate my food and I'm big and fat.
And I didn't finish my food and I'm a skeleton.
Why didn't you finish your food?
You could have averted this.
I don't know. I guess I like skeletons too much.
This reminds me...
Isn't there like a meme or something that's like...
Big fat capital...
This is like a big fat capitalist who's like telling one guy with one...
There's like a black guy with no cookies and there's like a white guy with one cookie
and the capitalist is telling the black guy like that guy.
No, no, he tells the white guy that guy wants to take your cookie.
The capitalist has like a huge plate piled up with cookies or something.
I feel like this reminds me of...
I like the skeleton. The skull is a cool...
The skeleton looks really cool actually.
The angle on it looks good.
It's like our logo.
It's like our new logo to soon to debut.
Oh my god.
Spoilers!
Wow!
Broilers?
Is that like black pudding or is that a sausage?
I thought it was like toast.
It looks like a biscotti.
You know biscotti?
Yeah, I thought it was a lighter color.
Yeah.
But it's shaped like one.
If it's a sausage, why is it off your plate?
You sloppy fuck.
Look.
Just throwing your food around.
Yeah, I was just playing with it and I died.
Turned to a skeleton.
You were too busy tossing your biscotti around.
You couldn't bother to be asked to take a bite of it.
I like how you're just pointing at it.
Maybe I'm asking, are you going to eat that?
Yeah, it looks like you're saying that but I'm dead so I can't speak.
You're going to eat that?
Hey buddy, are you going to eat that?
Nope.
Don't mind if I do.
It's just sort of like if it was like, oh Ben eats so much that I starve to death.
But my food is still there.
Ben has not done this.
I have not done this to you.
You did this to yourself and I'm just here to capitalize on it.
Well, true words.
Gabe, if you died, would you let me eat your egg and biscotti?
Yeah.
Yeah, thank you.
This might happen one day.
Oh no.
And I'm going to need to know that I have your consent.
That means if I ever have a breakfast that consists of a single fried egg and a bit of biscotti,
that means somebody's out there with a sniper rifle.
You have to put the meal down and immediately exit the building.
Sick.
All right, the next one is a vocaru.
You ready?
Yep.
All right, three, two, one, go.
Checking Twitter, doing what I do.
A new picture of Gibbente.
Oh my God.
Fast.
Yeah, what's going on?
Wow.
Wow, it doesn't sound healthy.
Did I even put a picture of myself lately?
I don't think I've seen a new one that lately.
The last one was like the, wait, wait, wait, there was the one of you and you could just
just the back of your head, but you could sort of see your face in the mirror.
No.
Was it that one?
Yeah, it was a selfie.
I thought that one was pretty funny.
No, it was cool.
Yeah.
Not funny.
It was funny that like you can only just barely see your face.
Oh yeah, a little bit.
I was fucked up about like the hairs on the back of my neck.
I was like, oh shit, these feel like they go way down, like way too far down.
And I was like, shit, I got to find, I got to take a picture of the back of my neck to
confirm that I don't look like a freak back there.
Turns out look normal and it's fine.
But then it turns out that the image I took just happened to be nicely put together, I
was just sort of like, yeah, that's kind of an interesting image.
It's kind of like an alternative selfie.
An alternative selfie.
But with the regular kind.
I just won't do.
Sorry, I'm an hour behind on sleep because it was daylight savings time last night.
So that's, you have to, you have to excuse me.
The next one?
Yes, another vote.
Next one.
No, no, no, the next one is the mongoose.
Oh, that was that?
Yes.
Okay.
Yeah.
Three, two, one, go.
I don't know, Jesse.
You've been acting connoisseurs lately.
I mean, LeMau, I don't know.
What if the PCP was among us?
Who would be sus?
Who would be the imposter?
And who would win?
Vote now.
Jesse and Trixie, imposters, voting them out, throwing them in the air a lot.
That's my bid.
No, weird be the imposters because there's two of us.
We've been systematically picking off everyone, making them stop showing up to the show and
quit the server.
Yeah, we started with Jeff.
Was it Jeff kicked first?
He wasn't really kicked.
He was sort of like, see you guys, yeah.
It was sort of like, yeah, this isn't really a thing.
And then we killed monkey, we stabbed him, got him with our alien face.
Yes.
Everyone came around like, oh, shit, there's a body.
What's going on?
There's a big old eye.
Right.
We just kept killing.
I mean, I think the only other official kill was Trixie, and that was suicide.
Trixie tripped out of the airlock.
Oh, no, DeVoo.
DeVoo also, I mean, we never found the body, so we don't know what happened to DeVoo.
Presumed suicide as well.
But I mean, that's the mark of a really excellent kill is that you think it was a suicide.
I like Amongus.
Me too.
Oh, Amongus.
I get it.
Lol.
All right.
Next one is Kongalooia final.
Let's go.
Oh, the URL ends in bonk.
Oh, yeah.
That can't be a coincidence.
Yes, it can.
It absolutely can.
I don't think so.
All right.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh, oh, oh.
He made Mootslow.
He kept you high.
But this Kong is a fuck of a guy.
The number guy can make a cramlin' cry out.
Kongalooia.
Behold!
You just keepacking
Oh, let's be those pineapple scones.
Grace, now let's all reach a zen.
Don't you understand?
Oh, yeah.
Wow.
Nice.
It's just undeniable.
Yeah, it is nice.
He gave it his all.
He did.
And he did it.
The mad lad, he pulled it off.
I'd buy that on cassette tape.
I would buy that on eight track.
I would buy that on a disc.
I would buy that on a floppy.
I would buy it with a mouse.
I would buy it in a house.
Just an impressive level of execution on display on this little project.
All right.
I think we've got...
I think the next one might be related.
The next one is called,
A Reveal and an Announcement,
Dry Dump December at DustyDumps.com.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello, it is me, Dusty Dumps.
I hope you enjoyed the Kong Luya track.
The Saga, the Kong Luya Saga.
That waschly dump.
Well, anyway, I'm here to announce that the DZD Moysmel album
that I announced almost a year ago
is finally done and it's out now.
Yo!
It's on Bandcamp.
It's 23 tracks long
with wildly varying lengths from tracks that are like 10 seconds long
to epic seven-minute oddities.
Holy shit.
Our album exclusive, five of them are bonus tracks
that you can only get if you get the full album.
Each track comes with a little blurb describing the lore of the track
and the conception of it,
and each track also comes with lyrics.
You can sing along at home.
The album is at a pay what you want model
so you can pay me five billion dollars for it,
or just zero.
I think I will.
Oh, that rules.
The album includes tracks such as
B for Kringus Bingus,
The Tale of the Golden Witch,
the Natehead theme song,
Lord of Ghosts vs. King Herod,
and many, many more.
Check it out.
My next voicemail will just be a link to the album.
Okay, see ya. Bye. Hope you enjoy.
Thank you, David.
Thank you, Dusty Dumps.
I might have forgotten a couple of those.
I might go and refresh my memory.
All of these were played as voicemails.
Maybe there's some secrets.
He did say there were some exclusives.
Yeah, exclusives.
We should post this.
We'll definitely put it in the description.
Maybe we'll post this on Twitter,
or post this around.
I'm definitely going to pick it up,
and I'll probably drop,
probably pay.
I'll actually probably pay something.
Anyone that picks that up,
throw this guy a little bit.
Tip this guy for his...
for his...
all the work he's put into this.
I appreciate it a lot.
Awesome.
All right.
Mutsandu.bandcamp.com
That's from Mutsandu.
Kongeluya to you, sir.
I tip my hat.
Just great.
Great stuff.
You want to do the next one?
Cool.
Next one is an image.
Oh.
Okay.
Medical man.
It's a bunch of tweets of me asking
why isn't Medeker dead yet?
Oh, it's my...
it's my plebe and the weave,
hair, head image here.
With the soyjack
on it, of course.
Medeker is staying alive to own the libs.
I was just...
freaking...
Keemstar was like...
he's dying any day now.
He's on my show.
He's almost dead. He's going to be dead real soon.
Why would you trust a thing Keemstar says?
Oh, God, you're right.
I'm so stupid.
I'm so fucking stupid.
Damn it. Keemstar would say the most
entertaining thing.
That's not necessarily true.
I guess that would...
I guess it would be
get more people to watch if he was like,
this guy is going to be dead tomorrow.
And he's second now.
Tune in to watch him die alive.
Before the show, he was like,
hey, Medeker, what if I actually tell them
you're going to die?
What if we keep saying you're going to die?
And I say, no, this is it. No, this is it.
He'll be dead immediately after this
show concludes.
And he was like, yeah, tell him that.
The idiots will believe anything.
And they were right. I did.
Well,
consider this lib owned, I guess.
Next one is called Derriere.
Three, two, one, go.
Fucking tussle, bro.
You want to fight? I'll fight you to the last man.
And
I'll send a battalion.
I'll send a rap stallion
to your house to knife you.
And then
I'll invite you to
this coffin I've prepared
out
by your mother's derriere
in the field.
I'm going to kill you, Ben.
Damn, fuck.
By your mother's derriere in the field.
Was that
was that Ethan Ralph?
No, wait, why would it be?
I thought it sounded a little bit
like a Southern accent at the very end
there, but no.
Ethan Ralph was watching the PCP
and says, I guess my mom's dead.
Well, you know, because his baby
was the samurai, you know, it's
no, I thought you meant like the actual
Yeah, the actual Ethan Ralph
has an actual samurai
reincarnated.
Oh, wow. In the ghost of
Roseanne.
Whatever his fucking name is.
The
Well, I guess my mom's dead and she's
buried in the field and
there's going to be a battle. Bring it on.
It's going to send a battalion
and a rap scallion. Which one are you more
scared about?
I don't know, one good
one good rap scallion can really get
some work done.
Probably I could
be harder to defend myself against an
entire battalion, if I'm being honest.
My house is not like
positioned for like military defense.
So I'd probably be pretty weak to a frontal
assault.
Next one is called Bencon 4 3 2
1 go.
Do we actually know if anyone funded
Ratcon 4 because they wanted to see
more Bencene?
No.
Wait, we don't know that.
It could be that everyone did that
for that reason. It could be
and it should be
but I can't prove it.
Nobody knows
at the end of the day. We only have hearsay
and speculation.
Next one is
called Sonic Review 3 2 1
go.
Sonic the Hedgehog is amazing.
I love everything about Sonic the Hedgehog.
He's blue.
He's fast.
He has an attitude
and he eats the same kind of food
that you and me do.
Hot dogs.
Chili dogs.
Really.
I love hedgehogs.
Just in general.
They're alright.
The only thing about it
is
I tried to play Sonic
and
I thought the point was to go fast
but like every time you build up
a little bit of speed you just ran into
something.
What was the point?
Didn't you watch the Davoo video?
That's one of those reviews I hear
all about. You gotta watch that
Davoo video where she talks about
how it's about
controlling your momentum
to get the big loops.
Blue Hedgehog's
Nightmares.
If only it was Green Hedgehog.
If you want to play a game
a man
after your own heart who wants a game
that's just about going fast
that's Oolulilia
that's Platform Masters.
Did you ever see footage of Platform Masters?
No.
He was making a game
for a while
and it was going to be called Platform Masters
and it was like
let me see if I can find a screenshot of it.
Oolulilia
Platform Masters
Yeah, here we go.
Platform Masters Development, New Forested Mountains.
Okay.
So basically
Platform Masters
is a game
where you just
where you just go
where you just hold the forward button
and go really fast.
There are platforms and there are objects to jump on
but
it's just about
accumulating a huge amount of speed
and getting really high
is pretty much the point of it.
Was he in the middle of a dive right there?
They were flying.
I think the idea is that
it literally works kind of like
a Legend of the Ten Elemental Masters
where your character just holds
their arms out and it makes them
and it makes them fly.
Oh, there's something I really like
about the way this looks.
If you watch
his logs where he talks about development
like
he's got the speed counter and the height counter
and pretty much
he designed the game
so that you could achieve tremendous
heights and outrageous speeds.
But
a lot of what he talks about
is about the parallax scrolling of the backgrounds
and he very carefully
calculated the distance
of every object in the background
and he made it parallax scroll
as you move in a
completely scientifically accurate way.
Even like there's one where you're on the moon
and you can see Earth
in the sky and the Earth will
parallax scroll very slowly
at a scientifically accurate rate
to you traveling like thousands of miles an hour
across the surface of the moon.
That's great.
Yeah, that's where
you really want your development resources going.
But yeah,
it's kind of Sonic inspired.
You can see there's little jump platforms.
Can I play it?
I don't think a playable version was ever released.
No, I like this.
I like how it looks. I just want to jump around in it.
I don't know,
but I think that all that ever surfaced of it
was videos of him
showing development progress.
Unfortunately.
I guess I'll watch those then.
Yeah, they're kind of...
It's interesting to hear him
just how focused he is
on the parallax scrolling
is remarkable.
I think that...
The next one is called
Funny Voice Mail.
Wait, hang on.
Yeah, 3, 2, 1, go.
So that last voicemail was kind of bad
and I kind of wish I didn't send it.
I thought it was a good jumping off point.
So, okay.
So if Sonic the Hedgehog
and Shadow the Hedgehog
were in a gay
romantic relationship,
do you think Sonic
would be the top or the bottom?
That was a nice break there.
He tried to keep a straight face.
He just blurred it out.
I'm not sure if that laugh
was part of the kayfabe or not.
I don't fucking know.
I think they'd both be tops
and that's why they can't... fuck.
No, Shadow was the bottom.
You think?
You'd be a bottom and then Maria
would be the top.
Well...
It's just how it is.
Is that like incest?
I don't...
I don't know anything about the story.
I just know that he likes Maria.
He likes Maria, but she died?
Is she a sister?
I don't...
I don't know.
I think maybe he was made in a lab
and she adopted him.
Maybe so they're probably not.
Look at them, they don't look blood related.
Yeah,
it's probably fine.
Shadow's clearly a bottom because he's
an underling.
Sorry, I didn't mean to say that.
Sorry.
I was going to say hedgehog.
He's a hedgehog?
He's an edgy boy,
but he just wants someone to love him.
Kind of shy.
Just by their very nature,
they curl up into a little bulb and someone comes close
and they're like, don't touch me.
Don't come near me.
That's what I say when I'm the top.
I say don't come near me.
Don't come in my sight, slave.
That's not true.
It's the other way around.
They say that to me.
I have nothing else to say about this stupid question.
Next one is called
How Angry Was Ben St.
This Episode Scale of 1 to 10?
I'm down to like a light 3.
I'm down to a strong 3 to a light 4.
I'm down to a 5.
I'm only at like 6 or 7.
It's going up.
How are you going to ask this question?
I'm down to like a normal.
I'm down to a manageable 3 or so.
That's where I put myself.
What do you think?
Am I right?
Yeah, I'd say you've calmed down.
I have calmed down.
I was at 9.
It was not a productive place to be.
I'm back.
Baby.
I'm back and better than ever.
Next one is called
A Little Pome for Y'all
Let's do one go.
This is not my voice.
Okay.
This is nothing more
than brief electrical impulses.
These that you hear right now
is not my voice.
It's true.
I am an invisible man
and whispers in your ear the news
that in my now you are invisible too.
Imagination games.
Don't tell us Mr. Sensible Guy.
I was always there among the crazy.
I see if we ever knew what a game was
or even what is imagination.
This is not my voice.
I am just whispering in your ear.
Fog Jesse Wood.
Okay.
That was a nice poem I guess.
That was a nice poem.
Right.
I don't want it.
I don't want to comment on the end part.
Next one is called
A May Neutral.
Next one is called Benefit of the Gib.
Three, two, one, go.
Yeah.
Yeah. I can take you more seriously
without the silly voice.
Yeah. I can't tell if
if this is a sincerely meant
sentiment or not.
Well they said it was sincere.
Well they said
they did use that word.
Is that a quote from someone else
or I mean
it's fair criticism.
I mean it's fair criticism.
I don't know.
I'm coping. I'm coping.
I'm trying to get better.
Ben because we used to do a podcast.
I know it's unproductive.
I know it can be
unproductive sometimes.
I know I get a little
heated over some things occasionally.
I know I hold grudges
for
whatever.
It's probably something I should be working on.
Try not to let it
try not to let it
hold me back from doing some things
that I'm trying to do.
Trying to get this
new video.
Trying to get another video out soon.
Do the comic party.
Rebrand the show.
We're moving forward.
It's the 90s.
Our music is about something now.
The 90s.
In the 90s.
Our music is about the 90s.
That's Alex Yeek.
If you're familiar.
He tells a
an old metalhead.
He's like ugh metal sucks.
It's all screaming.
It's the 90s. Our music is about something.
Our music is about things now.
Great. Great stuff.
Well shit that was the last voicemail.
Was it?
Being critical of me.
It's fine.
He's mean.
He was mean. He's mean to me.
Give.
Stop him.
Arrest him.
I am not your policeman or woman.
Hmm.
Well.
I guess he'll get away.
With it.
I guess I can't do shit.
Didn't we have voice jail?
You could put him in there.
Put him in voicemail?
No.
You have to repent.
This is what you get.
You get voicemailers.
Maybe if he didn't put a funny filter on his voice
I would put him in voice jail.
But he did.
So it's okay.
All is forgiven.
That's it.
Thanks everyone for your voicemail.
I think.
What do you think?
I'm thinking we can have the website
more or less online
and pretty much done by next week.
Probably even by the time you listen to this.
And
I don't want to make any promises about
when the perfect planning
podcast will be out, but I will be
starting to work on
I'll be starting to draw more stuff.
I'll be starting to draw this week.
I can't put it off any longer.
And
And thanks for that guy who said
that he liked Biscopades. That means a lot to me
that somebody thought it was good.
Yeah, I liked it.
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
I need to write an outline.
What I need to do is take some notes
and outline okay. Here's where we're at in Biscopades.
Here are the elements that I had
previously introduced.
And then block out a little thing like okay.
Here's where I want the story to get
over the course of however many pages
of Biscopades I want to do. How many pages do you think
I should do? How many pages of Clarissa
do you want to put in?
There's
I think like 17 or 18
pages.
Okay.
You can do however many you want.
It doesn't need to be a big thing, but yeah.
Are you going to do it like standard comic page
format?
I will give you the template
for you to slot your images into.
Yeah, that would be.
That would be great.
There'll be
a left or a right page.
Okay, cool.
So you can put things in margins and stuff.
Yeah, give me that.
Yes.
This is the week that I get cracking on that.
I will
I guess make that
PDF.
And then also next week maybe
I'm going to take
book.
I think the website will come before
the Amazon thing.
Oh, you mean the Clarissa
book?
Yeah, for my
end of things.
Because
that would be great.
I don't even know if it works
outside of the U.S.
It might just be a U.S.
specific Amazon
that's fine. At least a bunch of people
can buy it.
I'd be surprised
if Amazon wouldn't ship to the U.K.
Yeah.
I would also be surprised,
but I think it was on Amazon.com
not .co.uk, but I guess
Amazon.com is the main one.
Yeah.
So I don't know. I still got lots of
guides to read
on the thing like how to
upload your thing and what's the
specifications.
That's just a lot of stuff.
I know what you mean.
Yeah.
Um,
all right.
Let's put
our nose to the grindstones.
They're the next week on the Pro Crastinators
podcast.
Patreon.com.
If you want bonus episodes, if you want behind
the scenes,
discussion to listen to
if you want to have your name
in the thank you
page of the upcoming
periodical.
We'll be doing that.
And
anything else
before we end?
Patreon.com.
I don't even know if you said that.
I think I did, but it's okay.
We can say it again.
Follow me on Twitch
and Gib.
Give and take on Twitch.
Thank you
for listening and we'll see you next week.
Goodbye.