One more time. One, two, three, bang!
That seems very wrong.
It would be even funnier if we did take the offer and did we have to shelter both?
Okay, well that will be hilarious, but let's start.
This bang issue is going to be what finally tears this apart. We knew it was going to be something.
Is this the cold open arc of the PCP?
God, I wish it is. I hate interest. I hate them just in concept.
I just want to hit the ground fucking running.
I really like the cold open last time.
They're just great. There were positives and negatives.
There were no negatives.
Do you mind if I animate during this podcast?
You know what? I'm going to take this time to rail against our audience
and call out the literal cowards in the comments who were like,
did you guys not mean to keep the first part in?
I literally can't believe they were saying that.
Fuck off. Die.
Okay? We're bringing you the real shit.
We're bringing you the raw shit.
We're toppling Nate's totalitarian regime where there's format or structure
or anything makes sense or means anything.
This is a new era.
We clearly state in the clip that we were putting it in the beginning.
Do you think that we just forgot?
We just left in the entire intro and we didn't realize?
Here's my theory.
I don't mind saying if it was me editing, I would have cut that out
and been like, nah, this doesn't need to be an end.
This is it. This is why. This is why.
We need an end. We need an end to Nate.
If only. There was some way to avoid Nate's crushing iron will on everyone
involvement in the PCP.
Only. Editors had any autonomy whatsoever in what they do.
If only. We had any power to loosen his iron grip.
I'm gonna start drinking bang so you can reverse that mental retardation.
I need to start chugging it by the barrel full.
Hey everybody. Welcome to the procrastinator's podcast.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Today with me is Hippo Crit.
Hey.
Uh, Mage.
Stop. Don't do it.
It's a very soft coffee. I like it.
Don't give in.
Nate's here.
That's true.
Don't agree.
Munchies around.
I can't.
You've got soft coffee. I got a soft talk.
You've never been aroused, never been aroused.
And you're playing their game.
And last but not least.
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la.
Everybody.
Wonderboy.
You know, why would you just have...
Dancane is here.
Why don't we just have intros? I feel like we don't even need the pockets.
If we just repeat the intros over and over, that'll be our best material.
Well, I still want to one day do the, what's it like, algorithmically generated PCP podcast via bots.
That'll be good. That'll be good.
How would that go?
Yeah, how would you...
Are you talking about like an actual bot to do that?
I mean, oh well, okay, so theoretically you could take, you could like program a bot to have like certain topics that it brings up.
And you know, it would speak in Robo voice.
Maybe we could work on that and tweak it and send more like us.
But if you just have, you know, I'm sure there's a formula you could follow.
Okay, what if we had like a text to speech?
Like we each took our own audio for maybe like a couple of episodes, just our own audio.
Put it in like a text to speech reader and then just like read the script.
No, no, no, no, we took that.
Yeah, put that into like a procedural text generator.
Generated like, you know, a bunch of shit and just read it and like took turns or something.
You know what Ben?
That sounds like it would be a great idea, Ben.
It reminds me of an episode of Star Trek that I saw.
By the way guys, have you played the new Pokemon game?
No.
The new Pokemon game was a lot of fun.
It's already happening.
Do you guys want to join the Yang gang with me?
No, it's terrible.
You know that Burger King Footlettus guy was not a bot?
It's just a guy with a weird voice.
But I think it would be way less go here than that.
I watched Chills all the fucking time.
I'm a Chills aficionado.
Listen, yeah, Burger King Footlettus is funny, but he is so much more than meets Leigh Ai.
He is a fucking true American hero.
Every video, he is so not confident about the videos he's picked.
Every single like top 10 scariest video YouTubers who have avoided calamity.
He was like two children are in the woods.
Unfortunately, I do not think this video is real, but who knows?
Number nine.
Whoa.
Yeah, that's good.
That's a good impression.
Thank you.
It's a fascinating cadence he has to his voice.
I love it.
It's so fun.
It's so fun to say.
He's a real man.
He has genuine fears and wants in life.
There's one top 10.
I believe it's something like videos of people who have nearly avoided disaster.
Every single video is about people who have nearly avoided disaster.
It's this dude.
There's a video of this guy driving through the rain.
His voiceover, something in effect of like, watch as the rain pours on the windshield of this tired Nebraska male.
He is driving frantically.
The road has low friction and it is hard to control.
And then he just builds up this image of this poor, disheveled man trying to race home for whatever reason.
And then like, the quote unquote disaster that he nearly avoids is nothing.
It just is the entirety of the video, which is the disaster.
I'm going to be a little pro audience here because I haven't heard of this.
I know.
So clarify, so this is a YouTuber who people thought was like a voice bot?
Like an algorithmic voice bot?
It's just a YouTuber has a very, very, very interesting voice.
A very strange voice.
And his name is Chills, did you say Chills?
Chills, Chills.
He's a rapper.
No, no, man.
I had to finish this fucking video.
I thought you were finished.
No, no, no, no, no.
So he's building up the picture of this guy frantically driving through the rain in his typical Chills fashion.
And then once he gets to the end and supposedly something dangerous was supposed to be witnessed,
we were supposed to see something that was supposed to lead to his doom, which didn't happen.
He just says that he threw in this video.
He's such an affinity for firefighters and he wants to give a shout out to all the medical drivers of America
who have to drive through the dense rains.
Was this guy a medical driver in the video?
I don't know, maybe.
The point is, is that he just loves, he just loves like EMT members.
That's bad conveyance.
He just loves people in ambulances so much.
He wanted to be one of them as a kid.
You get really sensitive.
I appreciate the sentiment.
You get him.
You really feel more connected to Chills.
When I was a kid, I wanted to work at a lemonade stand.
Did you do it?
That's the perfect time to do that.
I just couldn't hack it.
The state didn't just give Ben his lemonade stand.
What was he supposed to do about that?
What was I supposed to do about that?
A crew capital and invest in a small business?
No, it doesn't sound realistic.
It just doesn't sound like a thing people do.
Speaking of accruing mass sums of capital.
No, no, no.
Mage was going to speak.
Since we're talking about YouTubers with funny voices or shticks or whatever.
This is one YouTuber I really like.
He on purpose talks very, very slowly in a monotone and people give him shit for it.
But as if they don't realize that he's doing it on purpose and it's so funny to me that they...
Who?
What's the kind of concept?
Name names.
The YouTube is Daft Pina, like Daft Punk, but Daft Pina.
He's a good boy. He's a good person.
I talked to him.
I used to talk to him.
It's not like I do it daily.
Is he a possible political connection that can help me in my quest?
Could he be of use to the Yang Gang?
That's all we need to know.
Could he be of use to us?
Oh, he already has over 100k subscribers.
Okay, there you go.
Let's get him on here.
That's a straight up social media influencer, right?
I'm not sure if he would want us as his associates.
No, don't say that.
I don't know. I'm not proud of you guys.
That's the meanest thing anyone's ever said.
Okay, he's leaving.
I don't know if he doesn't want to associate.
I understand. I get it.
You're not proud of us.
That's a step forward.
That's a step way forward.
That's a leap.
I can't believe it.
Man, I'm proud of you.
Why do you need to rectify this?
Well, whenever we're done reeling from this revelation...
Actually, is anybody proud of the PCP?
I have to wonder.
Because Mage isn't proud of it.
Jesse hadn't even told his friends he had a podcast for three years.
And Tom got banned from Mastodon because of his association with us.
I am still...
That was pretty crazy.
I don't understand what that was about.
Did you hear what happened?
Basically, Tom got banned from this social media platform called Mastodon.
Not quite. From a group on the platform, not the whole thing.
Right. Well, because Mastodon exists in instances.
Like Discord?
Yeah, kind of like Discord, except it's not...
It's like random what instance you're in, I guess.
I don't know.
I was confused about it when he...
Like an MMO server?
I thought it was like a Twitter-esque sort of thing.
It is. It functions like Twitter, but it is an instanced site.
So, there's like different mods that moderate like 100 person groups of it.
And the mod of his instance was not happy with the things he was tweeting.
It's like Discord?
If the actual texting and messaging of Discord was like Twitter,
but the Discord servers, you had a new account for each one of them.
So, you didn't have one account with a ton of servers.
It was just for each server you were in.
That was a new account that you had.
And that account that he had in that server was deleted.
Yeah, okay.
I mean, people should...
We should link this in the show notes for the specific tweet.
And it was because of us.
Well, it was a number of things.
First of all, it happened because he had made a tweet talking about how...
You mean a mastodon?
A mastodon, sure.
Well, the thing is that everything he posts on mastodon is just a tweet.
He just has a program that posts the same thing everywhere.
So, it was a tweet.
But he had tweeted out that, like in America,
their handling of Michael Jackson was this new documentary that is of questionable veracity.
Whereas in Japan, they are still celebrating Michael Jackson
by having a huge reference to him in the New Devil May Cry game,
which he had posted a screencap of.
The moderator claimed that he was being insensitive to victims.
Yeah.
That Tom was?
Yes, that Tom was being insensitive to victims.
Yeah, I hated that because, like...
I mean, the whole idea of...
Tom is defending the only victim who's fucking in the case!
Well, yeah, that's the thing.
It's not even like Tom hates the victims,
because Tom doesn't believe that there are victims.
It would be very different if, like, fuck the people that Michael Jackson,
I believe, did rape or whatever.
But he doesn't believe that Michael Jackson did that.
First of all, Tom is not making a political stance with that comment.
He is making an observation on the different, you know,
like, reaction to the character of Michael Jackson by different populaces.
So he is not making a stance.
He's making a joke, I mean, obviously.
But I suppose the most negative interpretation of that, you could say, is,
oh, look at him highlighting.
He's choosing to highlight Japan's, I don't know, less interested,
or perhaps skeptical reaction to accusations made.
Therefore, evil, I don't know, right wing...
Maybe in their eyes, Tom is like the Holocaust denier of the Michael Jackson variety.
Well, you got to understand the way that things are right now,
because this new Michael Jackson documentary came out,
and very much so, it's created, like, a whole new wave of people who are like,
oh, he was a monster.
And I think they probably did this to capitalize on the R. Kelly thing,
because R. Kelly had a big documentary come out that made everybody realize
he was way worse than they first thought.
I have mostly heard people...
Okay, I kind of...
This happens to me a lot.
Do you really hear about something by way of the backlash against it?
That's almost exclusively how I hear about anything.
Yeah, and I didn't know about this documentary until I heard people grumbling
that people are unfair to Michael Jackson, there's no real evidence against him.
Right.
And then I realized, like, oh, I guess the documentary just came out,
talking about what he's a bad man.
Well, because a lot of people believe that documentary,
that is probably the more, like, majority cultural-tied view of the situation.
I'm sure that this mod just straight-up believes it.
It doesn't even remotely think about the idea that somebody would think that it was just untrue.
To him, it's like Holocaust denial.
So, yeah, so they went to...
They already gave him a warning for that tweet.
Then they found out about a tweet that he had done just promoting the latest episode of PCP,
the podcast.
And I guess this mod actually went and listened to PCP.
Seemed like it, yeah.
And he said that there were a lot of...
What was it, homophobic and ableist slurs?
I believe so, yeah.
Funny.
It had to be said.
You know, I mean, we fucking had the N-word dropped a bunch on recent episodes.
You'd think it would be for that.
Well, I mean, we all just, like, out of pocket say retarded constantly.
I guess that's true.
Maybe we should examine that.
I don't even think it was that Tom said it.
He just said that those things were said on the podcast that Tom associates with.
I believe that's correct, yeah.
Implying Tom talks on the PCP.
You know, and Tom was complicit by being on the episode, I suppose.
No, that's not fair.
That's not fair.
Just because you're in the same platform doesn't mean that you stand by the same...
Like, I mean, like, you and Ben.
You know, like, three episodes.
You've been disagreeing.
Well, Mange, I'm purely playing devil's advocate.
I'm not.
Like, for example, I think if you get like a...
Like, sorry, on MSNBC, which is like, they say it's liberal or whatever,
if you bring on like a conservative to like argue with him and you're a host,
then like, even though you're literally arguing against his point,
one could still make the argument that you're choosing to highlight him
and so you're like...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you're arguing.
I don't think so.
Very stupid.
If we were...
It's not stupid.
I don't think it's stupid.
Imagine we were a, like, fucking, I don't know, white supremacist podcast
and you posted...
A just caller?
Of course not, Ben.
Of course not.
And you posted a link to us.
I mean, that would be spreading our propaganda
and if someone was against that and doesn't think it should be spread,
like, fuck you, get off my platform, that makes sense.
Well, I mean, I think that's essentially what these mod thought was going on.
Ben, can you agree, though, that that is extremely cowardly
for this person to say that like, oh, he doesn't want us to spread our ideas,
but like, whether or not ideas are good or bad should be able to stand on their own.
Like, it's up to everybody to determine if what they're listening to is good or bad.
You know, I struggle with this.
I struggle with this a lot, because like, on the one hand,
I do believe people should be able to say whatever they believe and think what they think.
And, but what if an idea gets people hurt just by its very spread?
And what if it's dangerous?
Then we need to learn lessons from it.
Well, I mean, so like, I've heard discussions about this.
One example is like, let's just say, like, the knowledge of how to create a virus
that would wipe out humanity.
I mean, I think most people would agree.
It's reasonable to suppress that particular piece of information,
because it's purely, you know, would be purely destructive
and no good would come from its existence or people's awareness.
So, okay, so if you accept that, so now there is literally some information
that just should be basically banned and not accessible.
So where, then we have to discuss where the line needs to be drawn.
Maybe, you know, only things that are directly like that should be straight up removed.
But like, in the wake of all the New Zealand shit, they've blocked 4chan and 8chan access in the whole country.
I think specifically, I don't think it was the country, I think it was the ISPs,
the private corporate interests who chose to, and the thing is we can't stop them.
Let me make a cut and dry sort of theoretical kind of a thought experiment, I guess.
If we all agreed that an idea spread harm and hurt people by its very spread
and like by people's very belief in it, like just by talking about it,
it would result in bad things and people being hurt unfairly.
Would we agree that we should stop the spread of it and not let people advocate it and say it?
You know, there's something to be said for the idea of like,
what do they say, sunlight's the best disinfectant.
So I wouldn't even necessarily say every time that it's best to like, surprise that kind of information.
I want personally all the information that exists.
I want to be on the same playing field as everybody else.
I don't want anybody to have information that I have no access to.
My dude, New Zealand is straight up criminalized having the manifesto from the New Zealand shooter.
It's a crime to have manifesto.
It's fucking ridiculous.
That is fucking insanity.
We can learn a lot from this manifesto that's retarded.
Yeah, like for example, all the ways that he's, you know, wrong and I disagree with his conclusions.
Exactly.
But not everyone's gonna read, just mathematically, not everyone's gonna read that manifesto and think wrong.
You know what I mean?
Well, okay, that's a good question.
And it comes down to...
No, no, I don't like this because like what you guys are teetering on is like policing of opinions.
Well, that's exactly what it's teetering on.
Yeah, but like who decides what's good and what's bad, you know?
Like imagine now like a lot of people are saying like, you know, like these opinions are bad,
therefore we have to silence these people.
But like they might be wrong, you know?
I mean, these are the sort of argument that comes up.
Like just for one example, if you've got like, you know, super right wing, like, excuse me,
sorry, something about that.
Like religious people, like for example, some of those people might not accept the fact that like,
for example, transgenderism is real.
And so, okay, that's their opinion.
And now, but you could certainly see why some people would say that this opinion is harmful and toxic.
Yeah.
So you just end up in a situation where those people...
I personally think the best course of action is to have these people and debate them
and then like point out all the ways they're wrong.
No, no, no, listen, you're not going to change their minds because their minds are already made.
You're debating them to change the minds of the people who are listening.
You allow people to decide themselves what's right and wrong.
You don't police them.
You don't force them to think the right way.
I don't agree with forcing people to think of one way or another.
I think that that is a very optimistic way to look at things.
No, I think that is the pessimistic way to look at it.
Wait, let me finish, let me finish.
I think that's optimistic because I think that's assuming people are creatures of rationality
and that when two ideas clash in the public free exchange that like the better one will win out
and I don't think that's true necessarily.
I don't think this is the best course of action, but I prefer this to policing thoughts
because I don't want people telling me what to think or what to make of this.
I don't want people to tell me that.
To be fair, mage, isn't that you simply prioritizing freedom
at potentially the expense of harm or safety, which I don't even disagree with.
I'm just saying that you're using your preferences there to dictate.
You just said you don't necessarily think it's the best course of action.
The reason that this freedom is so necessary is that nobody can determine what is the best for humanity.
For all we know, it could be possible that leaving anyone outside of my particular religion,
whatever that may be, alive, will damn me to hell.
That's possible.
Who's to say that murdering everyone outside of my religion is not in fact the best way forward
for a humanity of whoever's left afterwards?
We have no way of knowing that.
There's no objective standard of which ideas are right necessarily.
We do have to decide that.
Harmony is decided by society as time goes.
It's shifting. There's not a constant agreement.
That's why I want all the info, because it's always going to be changing.
If we said that this piece of information absolutely needs to be unlocked down,
For how long? From whom?
Is this information going to be handed down?
Are we going to form a fucking Templar society to protect this knowledge for the next 2,000 years?
The info is going to get out there.
I want to apologize. I'm going to do it, guys.
I'm going to say the N-word.
I'm going to Godwin's Law this conversation.
The N-word is Nazi.
And I'm going to say that is that attitude not the sort of thing that leads to the rise?
You fucking nigger.
Shut up.
God, we got to stop. I don't like it.
I don't fucking like.
Oh yeah, we're that podcast that says the N-word.
I don't want to be that podcast.
What about being the podcast that doesn't accept that some words,
regardless of context, are always inappropriate?
I do want to be that podcast, because every podcast should be that podcast.
I'm not saying that this is a particularly tactful use just now, but you know.
Everybody laughed.
That's what matters.
I did. You defied my expectations, and you got me to laugh.
You got me the sensible juggles.
But anyway, the point is, is that kind of thinking not the thing,
not the sort of thinking that leads to the rise of fascism, etc.
Because it's like, oh, who knows? Who's to say what's wrong?
No, isn't your kind of thinking leading to that sort of thing?
Because you're policing people like, my way is the right way,
and everyone who's wrong is wrong, therefore they should be eliminated.
The, the, I, well, hold on.
Don't put this on me. I'm just asking questions.
I'm just asking questions.
I'm also asking questions.
Alright, well my questions are better than your questions.
There will be no answer found here today.
I really didn't want politics to come in yet again.
But like, but like, in my heart of hearts,
I know that it's not necessarily a bad thing to talk about politics.
I just never have anything to say of worth.
Same.
Because I...
What do you mean? You're saying shit.
We're having a debate.
We're having an actual debate.
This isn't so much about politics as opinions and the freedom of opinions.
It's not as political as hashtag yangang, exactly.
Indeed, indeed.
But it's ideological.
What was I trying to say?
I'm making politics. I don't care.
I'm not American. I don't care for politics.
Okay, but we're not there.
I want to believe that purple is the best color
and no one can tell me otherwise.
You can't control the flow of conversation.
I mean, you're trying to.
That's why I didn't butt in either.
You just got to let people talk about politics
if they want to talk about politics.
Okay, we're going back to...
Skip the video, maybe.
Let's not go back.
Let's fucking dig into this.
I want to go back to opinions.
I don't think it'll just be...
We won't...
We already know what the issue is.
I want to expand.
Yes, Mage, expand.
The reason I hold this opinion is not necessarily
because I think it's the best way forward.
I don't think it's possible to make people...
All the people just follow rules all the time
and not expect rebellion.
Well, I think within the freedom of being able to choose your own opinions,
maybe Darwin's Law will come into play
and all the stupid people will die out.
I don't know.
Well, here's the question.
Say you're a mod.
I just want truth to be out there, not suppressed
because a lot of the time, truth is suppressed
in favor of...
What's best for the people isn't necessarily the truth,
is a popular opinion.
And I don't like that.
I want to know the truth
and I want to base my opinions on the available truth.
And I can't tell what the truth is
without knowing all sides of the story.
And therefore, I want to know all sides of the story
so I can find the truth myself
and then decide on my own what I want to believe.
Well, question.
What if someone's lying?
What if someone's going on the internet
or wherever going on podcasts?
Of course, of course.
What if they're going and they're spreading lies
and misinformation?
Yeah, and it's up to each individual person
to see if, you know, it leads to truth.
Right there, Ben.
You're assigning malice to that,
but I mean, I'm sure you would agree that...
I'm not assigning that.
They could be doing it by accident.
Oh, okay.
But to lie by accident is not actually a lie.
It's just a mistake.
I didn't say lie.
Well, I did say lying,
but I also said spreading and misinformation.
It happens.
It happens a lot.
As I said, it happens a lot,
but there's a chaotic element in this.
It's not ideal.
It's not perfect.
It doesn't always give the best results.
I know that, but I prefer this
to being told what to think.
I don't like the whole militant idea of, like,
someone decides what's best for you.
Therefore, it's best for you.
Don't question it.
Just follow orders.
Be a robot.
Live your life the way everyone tells you to.
I don't like it.
Well...
I think we've literally covered everything we can cover.
I want to say one more thing.
I don't think we've risen to the level of talking about,
like, should we put a legal ban on saying certain things,
although I guess we could ask that question.
I mean, we're talking about a mod on Mastodon.
We're talking about an individual
that is charged with moderating a community.
In 1984, the story wasn't so much.
It wasn't really a story about how the state imposed control
of everyone.
It was about how the people rose up and demanded
that they be policed and that their speech be controlled,
and it was the people themselves who did it to each other,
as opposed to, like, the government doing it.
So, you know, this is a danger from just within society.
We've got corporations that do it now,
and they're going beyond the government's control,
which doesn't reach this far, at least in America.
Yes.
I mean, in 1984, it was...
I mean, the people did it to each other,
but the government enforced...
I don't know.
I guess it's sort of chicken and egg thing about,
like, did the government impose this on the people
in order to do the people want this,
and the government took advantage of that public desire
or whatever.
I mean...
I don't know how to...
Stop talking now.
Let's move on.
Let's move on to something else.
Fair.
Hey.
No, you've done enough.
You've done enough to yabber in.
Okay. Fair.
I got a thing to talk about.
I've been a bit by the animation bug,
you know, that I did animation at uni,
and then I just stopped.
I made my three films, and then I just sort of didn't do that,
and I went to YouTube and I made video game reviews,
like a fucking idiot.
What a disaster.
Yeah, but recently, you know,
while animating the finale of my webcomic,
I was like, you know, animating's good,
and I like the planning,
I like the animatics and the storyboarding
and all that stuff.
And so, in rapid succession,
there's like two MAPs, multi-animator projects,
unfortunate acronym, but, you know, there we are.
Oh, Miss Anthropony, please come back.
Yes, exactly.
So, like, I'm...
I fucking love that guy.
Miss Anthropony, if you're in the comments,
let us know you're there.
Oh, and if we can see you at BronyCon.
And see you at BronyCon, yes.
Oh, for sure.
Yeah.
I'm serious, I want to fucking...
Ben's gonna get bullied by Miss Anthropony at BronyCon.
He's gonna kick the dick.
I don't think so.
I think we've gone past that.
I think we can have a meeting of the minds.
I'm not even kidding.
I'm not even joking.
I think it would be really fun to, like,
fucking shake hands with Miss Anthropony.
You should take a ceremonial picture of
both of you kicking each other in the dick simultaneously.
Exactly.
That would be iconic.
That would be great.
But, yeah, like, I've been...
I signed up for a Homestuck MAP,
and I'm animating, like, two scenes,
and it's just going really well,
and I'm liking it.
And then I'm still, like,
subbed to Crown Prince, the wolf lady.
Yep.
The wolf lady from the thing.
She had an MAP.
Is she a horse lady?
No, she's always been a wolf.
Wait, no, she's a horse.
She had a horse, but, yeah, you're right.
She's more of a wolf.
Oh, she did.
Deep Lore.
But, yeah.
And she had one which is, like, a really short one,
with a much more sensible deadline.
The Homestuck one is, like, for 413.
It's, like, a big, epic 10-year anniversary
of the beginning Homestuck.
Yeah, catch me one week from then.
420, my dude, if you know what I'm saying.
Hey.
Speaking of which, let me check the calendar.
So, yeah, animation's cool, and I really like
that I'm getting back into a craft
that I've sort of given, like, forgotten about.
It's really cool.
Yeah, that's good.
I feel strong and powerful.
That's really cool.
I mean, it was probably a year ago you made,
what was it, Descend, Estesend, or whatever it is?
Yeah, that was barely an animation.
That was just sort of, like, moving drawings around
in Adobe Premiere.
Like, squiggly lines going on and what not.
It was awesome, though.
It was, yeah.
For anyone, Estesend is a RFCK thing
that is on, it's on the Hippocrite channel, right?
It's on Given Fortress 2.
Right, it's on Given Fortress 2.
It's also clipped on the RFCK Twitch.
Indeed.
Yeah, Twitch.tv slash Rowdy Frickers cop killers.
What was it like to get back into it, Hippo?
Did you, was there any period of, like,
oh, what the fuck is a Toon Studio or whatever I would do?
The beginning was like, I wanted to make an animation
for the end of Balejap.
And so I was going, like, okay, I did this in uni
and pre-production is the key.
If you pre-produce, you know, properly,
then everything falls into place very easily
and then animation is simply, you know, busy work
rather than brain work and you can just get through it.
Yeah.
And by, you know, looking at, like, calendar dates
and thinking about how fast I could make certain scenes
and going through the animatic and the storyboard
and it was just sort of, I just sort of fell right back into it.
I really enjoyed myself making this come together
and all the little gifts that I was making
to, like, show various discourse that are animation-based
and just like, hey, guys, look at this.
It's cool.
I'm good at art
and it's great.
And, you know, my favorite thing about animation
is that you don't need to be good at drawing to do it.
The whole point is that any one drawing stays on screen.
Any one drawing stays on screen for such a small time
that it's okay to be kind of bad at drawing,
which is why I got into it in the first place.
Time, let me gripe about people that post, like,
smear frames from animation
and are like, haha, look how bad this looks.
Well, dumb.
And it's like posting a frame is stupid.
I like that really wide one of Superman
that doesn't prove anything
that one frame in an animation is, like, weird-looking.
Are you familiar with that one?
It's Superman, like, moving sideways into the frame,
but, like, in this one moment,
he's stretched across, like, the entire canvas of the screen.
I have not seen that,
but have you seen the one of the cheerleaders and Kim Possible?
No, no, I haven't.
There's one of, like, all of them sort of in the group,
like, move down.
Like, they squat down really fast before I jump or something.
And so, like, all of their faces are, like, stretched
and, like, stretched.
Their entire face is, like, stretched down,
like, the entire length of their bodies.
Do people actually laugh at that?
Or do, like...
I think at some point, some people did.
I mean, okay, look at this.
This isn't the one I was thinking of.
Check this out.
But look at just...
This is one of the many Superman smear frames.
And I think you'll appreciate it.
Okay, it's fucking loading.
All of the references I've seen to this
just seem to be, like, haha, well, that's crazy.
It looks like that in-between animation.
Not that it's necessarily, like, bad.
I don't think anyone thinks it's bad.
I've seen people post it about, like, anime.
Like, Naruto.
Well, it's funny you say that.
I see a lot of people deliberately celebrating smear frames
in the Sakuga community.
Like, it used to be...
There was a huge backlash against the fact
that people would always, like, shout bad animation
at, like, uh, Shonen stuff.
And, like, when there'd just be, like, a character
who looks off, like, in the background
and people would highlight it and be, like,
this looks terrible.
Though, personally, it's kind of funny because
while I appreciate why, like, it's annoying to people
that that kind of stuff gets brought up
and called bad animation, you know?
Nonetheless, it's not like it's impossible
to not have that happen.
But, like...
It's not a... No, but it's...
But with smear frames, those are obviously there
on purpose, like, they're a part of the animation.
They're meant to be seen in motion.
They look fucking hilarious and great, though.
I mean, this is a technique.
This is an animation technique.
I mean, yeah, it's literally to make up for the fact
that you can only animate so many frames per second.
So fucking wide.
Oh, wait, okay, I found the one.
If animation was, like, 120 frames per second,
you would draw each one of those.
Because you literally can't.
That's the best one, yeah.
That's so...
What amuses me is the face he makes.
It's like, it reminds me of that one anime face.
That one actually looks like he's just really wide
and rectangular, making a face.
He looks like Balrog from Cave Story.
Yeah, yes.
Well, I was thinking the TV man from Dead Leaves,
but that is pretty similar to Balrog.
Did you... I watched that anime at your recommendation
just the other day, and it is very, very much...
He's like a very, very munchie-core.
...get an ai-kai face. Hold on, I'm gonna post this.
It's very, very munchie-core. I love this face.
It seemed like it. It seemed like it.
I don't know, are you down with, like, the dick jokes
and the dick humor too much, though, Munchie?
You seem like you would be into that.
Why would Munchie not be into dicks?
Yeah.
Because he hates sex.
He doesn't want to think about the existence of the penile.
Munchie draws dicks all the time.
That is a gross misinterpretation of my hatred for sex.
But doesn't it, like, fuck, and, like, there is a baby,
and that's gross, that's sex?
It's really cool when people fucking movies.
What, am I stupid? Am I brain dead?
That thing is not?
I don't know.
It's really fucking cool. It's cathartic.
It's like seeing a dude get...
Okay, I think of sex in movies the same way as getting,
like, someone's head blown off in a movie,
and they're fucking gore splatters across the window.
That's exactly what I'm like, oh!
He screams when he sees it.
Yeah.
But in a cool way.
Yeah, same. I agree.
I kind of lost the plot here.
But I really think it's really cool that you're trying to get back
into something that you've sort of thrown to the wayside
in the pursuit of more...
Gold.
You know.
Terrible.
Interesting aspirations.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, like, I never really meant to throw it to the wayside,
but my overwhelming feeling coming out of animation college
was this is really depressing and difficult,
and so many people try so hard,
and all they end up doing is, like, advertisements,
and they never...
When they're 45, they finally get enough money to make a short film,
and I'm like, Jesus Christ, no, end.
I don't want to do that.
So, like, as a career prospect,
they didn't seem like the best thing to go for
because of the way I approached animation.
I felt more fun, you know, doing silly little small things
that weren't, like, you couldn't really sell the stuff I do that well.
I mean, maybe you could, but, like...
Yeah.
And then I became a writer, and now that's my job,
and now animation can become a hobby again, which is great.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's kind of...
There's probably some kind of bell curve or a bounce to be found there,
and it kind of makes me wonder if, like, for your average,
like, non-career established with, like, a large income or following
or anything, for a person like that,
I wonder if it makes sense to, like, have a day job of whatever kind
and then to make their passion project be something they can spend years on
if they want to, and then to, you know, make it as good as they can.
I mean, that's not a particularly weird, you know, set of circumstances.
I mean, that's literally what I've been doing for years, so, you know.
I think there's a lot of value to that, actually.
I think there's a lot of value to having that sort of normal life,
you know, out in the world doing maybe a nine-to-five
or even just whatever other...
That's why...
...mini-label job you have.
And then, you know, come home and unwind.
I mean, I've been changed in my approach lately,
but, like, that's why the six-month-long for a video sort of things
were, you know, taken so long.
What's interesting about, like, working, you know,
just not having a job that you go to wake up, honey, toast, please,
thank you, kiss, goodbye, instead of having something like that
where you can just come home at the end of the day and be like,
well, I'm off from work, and then maybe you can turn on the telly
or maybe you can turn on, you know, your canvas
and give out your praying bushes or something,
you know, you have free time that is clearly yours
as opposed to that when you're doing what we do
and just every waking moment from the moment you wake up
to the moment you go to bed, you could theoretically be doing work.
That's the life of an entrepreneur in one way or another.
There's a lot of benefits to it.
There's a lot of mental negatives to it, I feel.
That's fair.
It's not for everybody.
I think that's for sure.
I greatly...
I almost value it.
I think I might have pushed it away too much, like, out of sight, out of mind
in my youth, and I've been really considered the idea
of having a...
Especially what Hippo is describing
of sort of like animation being like a busy work sort of thing,
just having a job that is sort of menial tasks,
I kind of made it, in my mind, decided,
oh, I'm not going to do that.
That's stupid.
I wouldn't do that.
I didn't even consider it for a while.
But more and more, as I grow maybe a month or two older, I think,
maybe that's actually a good idea.
Maybe I actually want to do that.
Maybe I actually want to have dedicated work time,
where I can spend doing something that isn't necessarily creative pursuits.
And then when I get home, I'll just have that time to myself
when I can do what I please.
I resent.
Listen, I understand the idea that having a regular 9-5
provides structure in your life and is maybe good in a pragmatic sense.
But I hate...
I can't stand the idea that I am laboring with the goal
of making my boss money,
which is the purpose of labor under capitalism.
Well, I mean, you're making Patreon money with your Patreon.
Are you also upset about that?
I don't think you understood what I just said.
I didn't say not...
They're your boss, basically.
You fool.
Yeah, but I'm not working to make money for them.
I don't understand. Aren't you, though?
You are making money.
No, of course not.
How?
Are you having a stroke?
I mean, you need money to live.
Make money for them.
And when you have a job, you labor so that the person employing you
generates wealth for themselves.
I mean, it's called a job,
and you agree to do the job to get paid,
and the reason you have the job
is because you can provide value to your employer.
That's right.
And I don't want to provide value to an employer.
You...
Nate, you got lost.
You were talking about the fact that Patreon takes a cut of your earnings.
Yeah.
That's correct.
But that doesn't necessarily contradict what Ben was saying.
I don't think that's what Nate was talking about,
but that does annoy me.
That does annoy me.
I mean, there's the patrons as well, I suppose.
What the fuck are you talking about?
I'm not making money for my patrons by working for their money.
That's not what's happening.
Isn't that exactly what you're doing?
Are you insane?
What are you talking about?
Wait, wait, wait.
Sorry, you said making money for them.
Yes.
Okay, not money, but you are providing value,
so it's not money.
Okay, but Ben's point is,
is simply that if he works for a boss in a regular job...
Ben just got some issue with money, I guess.
Shut up.
What did you say it?
No, you fucking idiot.
If Ben is working at a regular job,
then that means that his boss is making money off of him,
and he does not want that.
That's what he's trying to say.
That's correct.
He does not want his effort to make money for other people.
And you resent the idea of other people having a boss.
No.
Why are you putting fucking words in my mouth?
Listen, I said this in the comments in the last video.
Someone was like,
Ben, something, something, something.
This must be why you resent people with corporate jobs.
And I said,
I don't resent people with corporate jobs.
I get it.
You gotta do what you gotta do.
Nothing wrong with making a living.
But I resent the jobs themselves.
Jobs are, I mean, not always, but, you know, a lot of,
I mean, jobs exist to generate value for the employer and,
you know,
They also exist to, like, make the world happen.
I don't know.
I don't think they do under capitalism.
I don't want to get into this, dude.
I will just get mad.
You are so retarded, Ben.
You're the dumbest person on the planet.
This pisses me off.
I would say,
well, explain, Nate, why you gotta back that up.
I don't want to get in.
Look, just your whole conception about the exploitation of the worker
who agrees to do the job.
Oh, no.
It's so sad they're being abused by agreeing to take the job
that their employer beneficially gives to them to do
what a sad Satan fares.
I'm going to take the high road and not get mad,
even though you are completely misquoting me
and putting words in my mouth that I didn't say.
I love you.
There you go.
Aw.
You fucker.
That reminds me a very different topic quickly.
The video that you guys recently released,
I just realized at the very end,
you guys lay in one bed, marriage confirmed.
Yeah.
Indeed.
True.
This was never in doubt.
And as with every marriage,
there is one intellectual superior and one intellectual inferior.
I would agree.
And I think we've made our cases well here.
I think we know who's who, wink, wink.
Indeed.
Audience will understand my point.
They will understand the truth.
So is the ending of the T-Bap not an angry beavers reference?
I have no idea what you meant when you said that.
It wasn't intended.
There's this episode of angry beavers where the two of them
wake up after experiencing some kind of dream within a dream
kind of thing and I think one of them slaps the other
and then they keep waking up.
Or no, it was a time travel thing.
I don't fucking know.
No, he kept slapping him into last Tuesday.
That's what it was.
He kept slapping him so hard that he would go back in time
or something like that.
I mean, it sounds hilarious, but it was not intended to be.
I watched angry beavers and I don't remember that.
This is all I remember from angry beavers.
I saw like 15 minutes of an episode at a friend's house once
and it was like the one kept slapping the other back in time
and then like it kept happening again.
And it just had a very similar vibe to that scene in T-Bap,
especially because Phantom kept slapping Keg for some reason.
Because it was the joke.
Because it uses funny.
It was just very...
It felt like a reference.
The question is, Nate and Ben, was the ending of this video
a reference to this bit of a show that no one remembers
and I remember even less.
This very specific moment from the show.
Was it a reference to that?
I don't think so, did you?
I don't think so.
Well, I didn't know if you guys knew it.
I don't know if you guys fucking were huge angry beavers fans.
I actually did.
I actually did really like Angry Beavers.
But I don't remember that specific episode.
I'm gonna find this fucking scene.
It's the one with the beavers.
It's the one with the blonde guy and the one with the red nose.
Yes.
I think I've seen the little beavers.
Norman something?
Angry Beavers Cow and Chicken.
What else?
Cow and Chicken sucked Angry Beavers rule.
That's my official opinion on the subject.
I remember the one where...
Oh, God.
I remember the one I remember best is...
Okay, it was the one with...
They have this candy or something called Lickety Splits
and it's just like a lot with like sap in the middle.
They did gambling or something?
I think so.
Oh, then it was like who...
If they lost some challenge,
the other one had to be their servant for one day or something.
I remember one where they can't sleep.
Like they dare each other.
Like who can go the long way without sleeping
and eventually they get too tired to sleep
and they just stay awake for like eternity.
It was like dystopic.
Okay.
Hey, this is all cool and all,
but on the subject of...
Of race and politics, God damn it.
No, no, no.
Of T-Bap Resurrection.
Let's talk more about that.
So people, in case you didn't see it,
it's not on this channel, but on T-Bap.
It's official T-Bap release.
Episode 26 of T-Bap officially.
Excluding the podcast.
It's only 26.
I checked the stats and...
Oh my God.
Yeah, that was...
Well, I mean, so the whole podcast happened,
but it was the 26th mainline,
like normally edited T-Bap episode.
And it's out.
We max-revived.
It took 9,000 dollars for you to edit one of those videos.
Yes, it was the top award tier,
or it was the top stretch goal for Radcon.
We hit it to max-revive T-Bap,
and we fucking did it.
It has been max-revived, although...
Which was the last promised thing from Radcon 3.
We have delivered on everything we said
we would do at Radcon 3 officially.
And just for the record,
it was on the exact one-year anniversary.
Yes.
It was released yesterday of the day
Radcon 3 ended proper as we were doing it live
in the arena, so...
It's time to start looking forward, guys.
It is.
I still want that GRPJ, goddammit, though.
That was not a promise.
That was not a Radcon promise.
Oh, okay.
Munchy, can I put you on the spot?
No, you can't.
You can't do that.
Okay, I won, then.
That wasn't an article in the Rad contract.
Indeed.
Indeed it was not.
Well, I'm curious about it.
We can talk about it later.
No, we can't.
I know.
What?
No, stop.
Stop.
Hippo, you fucking bitch.
Fucking kill yourself.
Fucking kill yourself!
Okay, all right, all right.
Okay, fine.
Let's move on to Radcon 4,
because we gotta do it.
Wait, let me just finish my comment here,
and we can do that.
But I just want to thank everybody
who was involved in helping.
That was Gib and Jesse, obviously,
providing voice acting.
I really liked how that intro played out.
It was good.
I think it was great.
It was lore rich.
Despite the fact that neither of us
listened to each other's audio,
we had a good back and forth going.
Indeed.
We wrote out lines, so it was great.
Okay, I cannot find this fucking episode of Angry Beavers,
but I figured out exactly what's going on in it.
What happens is that the one beaver
is continually annoying his brother all week,
finding new ways to annoy him,
and then the brother bops him into last week.
That's the idea.
He pits him so hard he goes back in time,
but it keeps happening.
Every time he reaches the end of the week,
he has annoyed his brother so much
that he bops him into last week,
and it just keeps happening until he finally stops annoying him.
Fascinating.
So do more and more time clones start appearing
because he keeps getting sent back in a time loop?
I don't know if it's one of those time travel versions.
I don't think it's like that.
It's grandpa day, but beaver day.
Yeah.
Maybe the episode's called beaver day.
That's pretty funny.
He's got to learn his lesson or whatever.
He's like,
I keep getting punched in the nose or whatever.
I keep getting punched.
Why does he keep repeating?
No matter what I do, I keep repeating the week.
It's got to be it's got to be Norm punching.
Norm's the one who annoys Dag generally.
No, no, no. Dag's the brown one.
Yeah.
Is Norm kind of the smarmy, know-it-all asshole?
Yeah, but Dag is the stupid funny one.
So I would imagine it was Dag annoying Norm.
Okay, maybe.
Yeah, that is the case.
Oh, okay.
All right, for now.
Cha-ching.
Hey, wait.
Wait, let me finish my goddamn thank yous, goddammit.
I just want to thank-
Why are you giving a fucking Oscar acceptance speech
over releasing the T-Bap episode?
Why is this happening?
I just want to say thank you to fit MC for recording
and Victor for filming.
That's it.
That's all I wanted to fucking say.
It was a big deal, but you made it a big deal.
You unzipped me, you piece of fucking shit.
Why did you make me do this?
You ruined my Oscar acceptance speech.
It was going to be such a positive moment.
And now it's ruined.
Did fit MC voice the dad?
Is that what that was?
That's not the dad.
That's not their dad.
That's their manager.
That's whatever.
Or producer.
The reason I said the dad is because I thought
that your dad had voiced him.
No.
That would have been very interesting.
Yeah.
Fit MC voiced Risky Business in T-Bap Resurrection.
Their dad, Gold Standard, appears in...
Gold Standard appears in...
Phantom Reviews?
Phantom Reviews.
Yes, in Phantom Reviews.
And he was voiced by Jesse.
And their mom, Angel Food, was also voiced.
And was that voiced by Jesse?
He was voiced by Jenny Whatserface.
Jenny Nicholson.
That's right.
Really?
You got her?
Yes.
We also got Jenny Nicholson.
I know.
She also played Kimmy Sparkle in the cutie marker fuffle part 3.
Yes.
Which was her character.
But she also voiced Angel Food.
Which is cool.
We did it, lads.
Incidentally, for those who don't know, Ben and I...
So there was some weird thing.
We were both kind of on track to play a character in Friendship as Witchcraft.
And there is one or two lines.
I think it's actually both me and Ben doing two different bits of this character.
This was weird.
They were working on the next episode of Friendship as Witchcraft.
And they asked both of us to voice this character, Craig.
The character was going to be just a regular human who didn't know what was going on.
And was a completely normal person, human person in the world of Friendship as Witchcraft.
But he traveled through the Portland and became a pony.
That was the thing happening to him.
Was he?
Yeah, he walks through the portal in his first appearance.
Oh, I thought he was literally a human.
Like a human human.
He was a human, but he walks through the portal and goes to the Pony World.
I know, but I thought he wasn't a pony.
But whatever.
Okay, maybe I'm wrong.
But yeah.
There was like one line or two lines.
And I think they were going to just alternate between our voices or something.
There was some confusion.
Look, we were fighting over this role a little bit.
So there was some...
Yeah, we both really wanted to do it.
There was a little bit of shenanigans going on there.
They were like, I could be the singing voice and Ben could be the speaking voice or some shit like that.
Really?
I mean that.
Yeah, that was disgust.
The way you're describing it, it makes it feel like they approached maybe both of you to cast a wide net.
And when you both found out, they were like, oh, Jesus Christ.
I really wish they had just come and asked one of us.
I really hope the corporate red tape from that was like the reason the episode never got done.
They couldn't resolve the conflict.
I'm sure that was it.
From what you described, I assumed that they were just telling you both that this guy was perfectly normal.
So you would play him that way when the reality is that he's some kind of like weird split personality.
And that they wanted to have a cycle between both of your voices the whole time.
No, I'm afraid not.
Well, anyway, we both...
Who knows what would have happened?
Yeah, I mean, I don't know.
I would argue that Friendship is a T-Bap was the highest produced, the highest production regular show of the Pony Review Crew.
So we certainly had the cred to take this role.
I mean, if you consider a horseshoe to not be a regular show, then...
Well, I do not.
Yeah, I do not.
Because ours was weekly and his was not.
Well, it was pretty close at first to weekly.
Not for very long.
But whatever, it's not a point.
Anyway, fond memories, fond memories.
But we're canon, two Friendship is Witchcraft lore, so suck it.
Are we?
We're in there.
Yeah, we're in the first episode of Horsewomen. Craig shows up.
Wait, but there is no Horsewomen.
Horse... Episode one was made.
Oh my god.
Was it?
Yes, Ben, yes.
Hmm, sorry, I was drunk. Sorry.
I'm intoxicated.
I was a little bit of an important to say, but angry beavers.
And that's that actually I don't never mind.
Ratcon for everybody. Here we go.
Ratcon for baby.
Maybe, eventually.
I mean, yeah, at some point.
More lectures.
We'll see.
We had ideas for lectures, but none of us have thought...
I have a concrete, hardcore, ready-to-go, anytime idea for a lecture.
So I'm ready.
Like no preparation required?
Yeah, I mean, I would need to draw the board other than that. Nope.
Are you keeping it under wraps?
Yes.
I haven't actually like written out or scripted anything for a lecture until we have like a plan for what we're going to do.
I mean, I know one or two that I would do.
Well, I'll drop this hint.
I don't know.
It's just that I don't need to do any prep work.
I just know everything I need to know already.
So that's sick.
Sick.
Is it about Gurren Lagann?
There's not enough material for a lecture there.
Is it about Homestuck?
Oh, God, I hope so.
I don't know why Nate would be doing the Homestuck lecture.
Because obviously, my famous podcast, Nate Talks About Homestuck, really shook up the metagame of YouTube and changed the world.
I have two planned lectures, but I'm not going to start researching them until we know when Radcon 4 is, because...
That could be forever.
We got it.
Guys, let's do the Radcon 4.
We need Radcon 4 to metastasize already.
Metastasize.
Yeah, I mean, if it's going to happen, we need to actively start thinking about it and planning it.
Yeah, because a lot of people just won't do any prep work until it's decided.
And people are like, well, I'm not going to work on it until I know what I'm going to do.
So, I mean, at some point, you just got to call it.
But that's not going to be for a while, so...
It's looking at this summer.
It's going to be another summer of pain where I'm racing across the map.
Just don't do that, though.
Just have a summer of good.
Yeah, okay.
All right.
That's a good idea.
Hey, Mr. President.
Yes.
Bang!
Sorry, guys.
I shut the present.
I knew I...
All right, this is over.
Oh, no.
What even was that?
Listen, guys.
It was an assassination.
I went to Improv Asylum and I'm suing my fucking director.
He didn't teach me shit.
I'm trying to get some money back.
Hey, speaking of assassinating the president, you were pretty close to doing that the other day, Munchy,
at that Bernie rally.
That's pretty cool, yeah?
Are we really going to recycle content from the bonus episode?
I just want to say we should definitely link in the show notes for non-bonus episode people
that one gift.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No upset.
I can't believe that gift is real.
I can't fucking believe it.
I'm still watching it.
If you want to know the full story, then go to the bonus episode of Sunshine and Rainbows.
If you just want to have confirmation that I'm there, click the link in the description
and you might melt.
Indeed.
Bernie's back in California to complete the political revolution.
And there he is!
And there Bernie is!
Just one of the boys that Bernie.
Bernie has moved his soul to a young vessel and is preparing for his new residency.
I have something that I want to bring up.
I don't have a lot to say about it, but I have a bit.
Do you guys know Petscop?
Yeah, of course.
I know.
I'm thinking of the quote-unquote game.
I thought Munchy, I figured you would know about it.
A pet shop?
No, not Petscop.
Petscop.
It's the game, right?
It is a YouTube channel slash video series that is a let's play.
It's a let's play of a fake game and it's sort of a creepy pot.
The videos and the game itself are both like...
Oh, I saw a game theory on this.
There is a game theory on it.
Recently I found another YouTube channel that talks about it called Nightmare Masterclass.
I have mixed feelings about Nightmare Masterclass, but I've been watching a bunch of it lately.
He has a big examination series on Petscop.
I just think that things like Petscop are really inspiring.
I love things that are...
It has such a novel format and that plays with the medium and stuff.
I think that kind of thing is so cool.
It's so fucking cool to me.
Completely agree and I want to talk about Petscop a lot.
However, I must just say that...
What is the name?
Nightmare Mastermind?
Masterclass.
Nightmare Masterclass.
There are so many Nightmind phony like fucking knockoffs on YouTube now.
For some reason it's just loaded as a medium.
I have never watched Nightmind and I don't think I want to.
Nightmare Masterclass.
Why exactly?
Not that I'm really...
Okay.
So I know.
I clicked like one Nightmind video thinking that I was going to be in for some sort of
like information dump or video essay or something and I remember there was like a...
I don't even remember what it was about.
I just remember I listened to it for 45 minutes the whole time thinking when is he going to
actually start talking about the topic and then the video ended.
Well, okay.
That's a very strange experience Ben because that's his entire thing is information dump
like down the rabbit hole ask explanation of ARGs.
Like that's what he does exclusively.
So I don't know what video you watched.
I don't know.
I don't know either.
It didn't impress me.
Okay.
Well.
But Nightmare...
Sounds like something I would like.
I want to see it.
Nightmare Masterclass.
He's very...
He will...
You know, sometimes I appreciate the spirit of like being willing to make like big logical
leaps and ask what if this means something even when it's something really innocuous and
maybe it doesn't mean anything at all.
It's probably like Preston Jacobs.
That guy isn't afraid to ask the tough questions.
He's not afraid to spend a wild layout of control.
He's not afraid to surmise that Quaith is bouncing telekinesis signals off the moon.
Indeed.
Oh man.
That reminds me because I just...
I watched the fucking Alex Jones on Joe Rogan podcast.
It's a good one.
It was so good.
I haven't seen that one.
Oh my God.
Alex goes off the rail.
I don't know if he's like this every day.
Alex, he is.
All right, but it's so funny.
It's so funny.
I honestly...
That does sound funny.
The only Joe Rogan podcast I've watched is the Andrew Yang one as a matter of fact.
Fair enough.
The fucking...
But it was good and I liked it.
What's his name?
The Alex Jones episode is five hours long.
Yeah.
I enjoyed every minute of it and I am now a fan of Alex Jones.
Dude, Alex is so...
Oh boy.
Entertaining.
He's so...
Like you just have to be like this is obviously bullshit.
And it's so funny.
Even...
I don't even find that much of what he says to be that crazy.
Oh God.
He talks about interdimensional elves, specifically literally interdimensional.
Like when he talks about...
The clockwork elves.
You gotta kill the clockwork elves.
It's just that some of the things he says, when Joe says like, okay, whoa, whoa, whoa,
you need to explain what that is, then he like elaborates and it actually is not as insane.
Right.
But it's...
What he uses up front is just it blasts you with this information that obviously seems
ridiculous.
He's the one who says they're putting chemicals in the water and turning the frogs gay, right?
Okay, that's a great example because the thing is, he's literally not even totally incorrect
because what he's specifically referring to is that there is a documented chemical that
was released into specific water bodies in America, I forget why, but what it did was
it increased, I think it was actually like hermaphroditic mutations in frogs.
So while it's not fair to say that it's turning them gay...
That is in fact wrong, man.
Well, the point is that the way Alex Jones talks...
It's basically completely wrong.
No, listen, the way he talks, the way he explains things is he gets a piece of information that
is crazy and is true and he has lots of these things that he talks about are verifiable
and when they are, he'll say like, go Google it, you know, you Google it, you find out
this fucking insane thing he said is true, but he will phrase it in a weird, somewhat
hyperbolic way and also he will extrapolate on it into trying to understand, but at the
same time, in this Joe Rogan podcast, there's a very clear self-awareness about the fact.
First of all, he constantly says things like, I might be retarded or like, I'm very autistic,
I'm kind of socially retarded, like he'll say things like that, right?
And in the meantime, he also says things like, you know, I don't mean literally, like he
keeps referring to aliens, but then he explains that he's like, aliens just means anything
that is like, not inherently from this world.
So he talks about, for instance, human chimeras, right, which are real, there are real experiments
on human chimeras that were done on like the, they were only done on like a stem cell level,
but like there are, there's not like real like human animal hybrids walking around.
Your brain thinks of like a giant wolf with a human head or something, I just think of
Nina.
That is the totality of his, I mean, in this moment where he breaks down that he doesn't,
like when he, when he says like, yeah, there's human chimeras, and then they look it up.
And yes, there is a thing that happened.
It's just not as extreme as it sounds, but it is not necessarily inaccurate to say that
they are human chimeras, what he's describing.
But then he goes on to say that like, those are aliens, because they are not something
that naturally occurred on earth.
So he considers it an alien species.
So when he talks about aliens, he's talking about anything that falls under this huge
category of what he considers aliens, you know?
So basically Alex Jones says the wrong words, and that's why people get confused.
It's kind of, it's that he, he's trying to explain something that there's not necessarily
words for.
And so he's making up whatever comes to his mind and trying to explain it.
And then if you talk to him long enough, you can kind of extrapolate back and figure out
what he's really talking about, and you go, oh, okay, you're just talking about this.
Oh, all right.
But yeah, that is a, there is a, because I mean, there is a lot of crazy things going
on in the world, a lot of weird, you know, things that are being kept under wraps, things
that are, uh, that are, you know, conspiratorial and like, there is some element of he's sincerely
exploring these things, he's sincerely questioning and like trying to get to the heart of the
matter, but he is an insane person.
I mean, so the way he, the results he comes away with just sound like insane ravings, but
you also have to look at it and go, okay, well, I at least can get that nugget of intrigue
out of it, that nugget of what is real and is identifiable in what he's saying, and then
try to come up with like my own take on it, you know, as opposed to trying to like, at
some point I can switch off the Alex Jones, the vacation of the information and like consider
it for myself.
Um, but the stuff he talks about is fairly interesting.
Like the stuff that is real is all crazy fucking shit that you're like, oh my God, that's real.
I would make the argument that Alex Jones ladens the whatever truth he has in such levels
of extrapolation hyperbole that it, I would make the argument that it is not worth my
time to try to discern true fiction.
That's very fair.
The only thing that makes it that makes it worth my time is that he's so fucking entertaining.
Well, that's like, he's just going, he doesn't stop.
He just gets more intense.
He gets more raw and like he also, he keeps saying throughout the podcast, like I've
got Alzheimer's already, but like, and he doesn't mean it, but there's definitely something
wrong with the man's brain.
Like he will lose track.
There's moments where he just seems to completely not know where he is anymore.
Like he like, is it, he's ranting so fervently that he just kind of is like out of breath
and he's like, what was I talking about again?
Like I, I don't even, I don't even know what the fuck's going on anymore.
And for a good long while, he demanded that every Eddie Bravo choke him out and make him
pass out on the episode.
He just, and like, dude, and after a little while, he was like, can we stop being pussies?
Can you just jump in the back when he was in school?
Like everybody used to choke each other at his school to get high or something.
Yeah, they would all just choke each other all the time, which I've heard.
I've heard a weird shit to get high, man.
I used to know kids used to like, that sounds like the kind of thing that will give you
brain damage.
I used to hear about kids taking a deep breath and crouching down, jumping up, exhaling
and smacking themselves in the forehead all at once.
And it just kills some of your brain cells and makes you feel kind of high for a second.
Great.
See, we should definitely get Alex Jones on this podcast.
Yeah, we should get him on.
He's looking for a platform.
I would love it.
Oh, I can't wait for the Munchie Alex Jones crossover.
Oh, that's what we were all saying too.
We were like, oh, imagine Munchie and Alex Jones in the same room.
Just it would be so great.
Just guess it vibe.
That'd be a great episode of the Pleeve and the Weave.
That's true.
It would just be nonstop.
Have you seen there's there's one clip on YouTube that some it's Alex Jones.
So this wasn't intentional.
It's just a clip from him on his first appearance and Joe Rogan, I think.
And it's just Alex Jones explains the plot of Evangelion and then purely
basically by accident, he details how he interprets like the modern political and
like technological landscape about breakaway societies and whatnot.
And that's it's literally silly.
OK, literally like the what's called the in the Joe Rogan episode.
It's like everything he describes is the plot of something like it's all
it all sci-fi.
It's all relatable to something.
It's all like speculative fiction.
Like it's it's clear from that podcast that he is very well read.
Like he's read a lot of futurism texts and shit and like seen tons of sci-fi.
And like the way he just throws out terminology like very, you know,
casually sounds like somebody talking about sci-fi, like talking about an anime or something.
And like I remember several times that he was just like describing plots of shows
that I was like, oh, my God, that's isn't that just
yeah, like Eva or Lane, especially.
Yeah, yeah, that too.
There is a channel called Art House Politics, which is somewhat
I don't know, it may be divisive to the fans of the show.
However, I think it's really funny and crazy.
And I love it.
And they have a video that is I'm going to link it.
It's going to be in the show notes, hopefully.
I'll just explain the world as a whole.
It's just a clip of Alex Jones, which he has laid in visuals over
in a in a in a very humorous way.
And this is the video that I think about whenever I think about Alex Jones.
Who loves to watch this.
Like he talks in such circles that like having an infographic
trying to like illustrate what he's communicating is harder than you would imagine.
Like like one of the claims that he'll make a lot is he'll just say he'll just throw out there.
There's at least 12 dimensions.
And I'm like, but the thing is he's talking about like string theory.
He'll say he'll say at least 12 dimensions, 10 proven.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
Wait, is he talking about that like 10?
You know that YouTube video that he's definitely talking about that?
Yeah, that's that's not just one video, by the way.
That's a guy's entire channel that has hundreds of videos.
Yeah, but there's like the one that started it.
Yeah, well, the one that that's the funny thing about the 10 dimensions thing
is that if you just watch the one original video, you're like, OK,
cool, sounds reasonable.
Then you see that the guy has like hundreds of hours of explaining
that same point and it no longer seems reasonable anymore.
That's interesting.
Weird. OK.
Um, why does he so why does Alex Jones say 12 dimensions, 10 proven?
And what what's he getting at?
Who the fuck knows?
I don't know.
Well, where's the nugget of truth, Digi?
Where's the nugget of truth?
Oh, well, I mean, I guess the nugget of truth is that there's
possibly multiple dimensions.
I mean, like the main thing that that resonated with me about Joe Rogan's
whole spiel is this idea that he seems to think similarly to how I do
that like humans are all we're basically trying to, you know, escape
entropy, make it to the next sort of exit the dimension that we are in
or achieve achieve awareness of a higher dimension so that we are not limited
to the one that's, you know, this universe that's coming to an end, so to speak.
And this he knows that's not what these dimensions are, right?
These aren't like planes of existence that one can move between.
No, the fourth dimension time or something.
Yes, the fourth dimension.
I don't remember the time.
I don't remember the details of the ten dimensional thing, but it's something like that.
There was a lot of talk of DMT and how it like allows you to access
the fourth dimension potentially.
This is crazy shit.
See, I don't get down with that too much.
But then again, I've never tried.
So I got to try DMT.
I got to do it.
Everyone says I have to do it.
Well, your oh, it's your brain.
Yeah.
Before you die, here's cancer.
I learned that the other day.
Well, that's good.
But did you know that bank here is retardation?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I'm talking it right now.
It's not working, though.
It's not working.
I need to chug faster.
It's not taking effect.
Let's talk.
Let's talk about.
All right.
So you discovered this energy drink called bang that I want to find.
I'm going to try and find it in seven.
Better be quick because I don't know if it'll be around forever.
Oh, did you just you just happened to have been contacted
in like the attempt to get you to like help take down big bang.
Like big, big pharma.
Yeah.
Yeah, and apparently there's claims.
There's like it's being sued by a bunch of people
because it makes a bunch of claims, including but not limited to
that it cures retardation.
Yeah.
OK, OK.
All right.
Well, here's the history of bang
because this is an extremely long drawn out issue that is so
that there truly is a big bang of information.
This is exploded out in the past couple of days.
This is this is being covered in the news.
This is crazy.
This is what we're going on right now.
So I get back from a trip to Boston and I go to my local 7-Eleven
for the energy drink run, which I always virtually do every single night.
And I go there and I see next to the monster.
I see a new kind of look.
I see bang, super creatine, potent brain and body fuel.
And now if you will indulge me, I just want to read the label,
which is on the back of every single bank bottle,
which is what compelled me to try out a few of the distinct and odd flavors.
So bang, potent brain and body fuel.
Make no mistake.
Bang is not your stereotypical high sugar, life-sucking soda,
masquerade as an energy drink.
High sugar drinks spike blood pressure levels, producing metabolic mayhem,
causing you to crash harder than a test dummy into a brick wall.
Power up with bangs, potent brain and body rocking fuel.
Creatine caffeine, COQ, 10 and BACs, branch chain amino acids.
Life is an extreme sport and bang is the extreme energy source to live life extreme.
All three of those extremes are spelled without an E, so it's extreme.
And then there's a TM at the end.
You had to be 18 years or older.
Wait, do they each have a TM?
Yes.
They couldn't have trademarked extreme, right?
No, no, no, I'm saying the end of that.
Life is an extreme sport is tiered.
OK, OK, gotcha.
That's a little better.
It's not much better.
Zero zero carbs, zero sugars, zero calories, zero artificial colorings.
And I am patient.
What's in the number?
I'm patient number, I believe eight million, eight point five million.
I'm patient eight point five.
Do they actually say a patient number?
Yes. What is that about?
That's hilarious.
Like this is the one that's killing you, the eight millionth bangs produced.
Right. So it's to be almost like a like a doctor,
like like it's making some medicinal claims.
It seems well, it is.
It says that it reverses retardation.
Yeah, it seems like this drink needs a disclaimer on it.
Like this product is not meant to diagnose or cure any disease or really retardation.
Be simply, but it doesn't just it doesn't say cure.
Retardation says reverse mental retardation.
I feel I feel like it's definitely like a funny joke.
You'll actually be smarter than a regular person.
I just didn't think people would take.
No, it seems reverse retardation in the sense of the more retarded you are now,
it will flip the script and you'll be even more intelligent.
Once you drink this thing, it will, you'll have reverse retardation.
Right, right.
Hold on, this, the bottle.
OK, I am intrigued by the bottle and there are some numerous strange flavors.
Just as a cotton candy flavor, which I purchased.
This cotton candy flavored energy drink, I get it, tastes pretty good, actually.
Tastes kind of strange, actually, not really like monsters I've had.
It's it's carbonated, but very mildly carbonated.
It kind of tastes like a water, but just has an extremely, extremely
potent, unbelievably potent, like they put too much serum in it.
Con candy flavor, so I'm intrigued by this odd delicacy,
which I am partaking in, and then begins my stumble down the bang rabbit hole.
And I just became a fanatic for this energy drink after navigating
to their official website.
If you care to join me, bang dash energy dot com.
And you'll be confronted with sites unknown.
Dude, you're going to be studying more colors than you borrowed for.
I want a pair of bang kicks.
So fuck yeah.
Yeah, OK, OK, OK, so they don't have just bang, nor do they have just other,
you know, you know, this bag is marketed semi as a workout thing.
So they have, you know, protein powder and, you know, keto coffee.
They don't even have just drinks, delicacies, though.
They have a peril that commercials.
They have healthy keto recipes so you can make your own queue.
Delicacies using the protein powder at various points in the recipe.
They have events.
They have a whole ton of YouTube videos.
They have the bang anti diet, rapid body remodeling blast fat fast
with the CEO, Jack, like literally Jack.
Oh, whoa, spelled like, oh, whoa.
With a C at the end.
A walk, a walk, a walk, a walk, a walk, Jack, a walk.
So I so the the intrigue to me about this, I received an email
and I've seen the bang energy in stores.
I've seen I've also seen some of the other stuff by the company
because it's by a company called VPX Sports who does like all kinds of energy
drinks, they also do red line is another thing you can buy.
Yeah, I'd heard of I just linked to their protein drink, protein rush.
And they also had what was the fucking bar that I've seen at the store?
Oh, the zero impact bars.
Well, apparently, so I got an email from just someone out of nowhere.
The email is called campaign opportunity about false advertising.
It says, I'm writing to see if you're interested in working with us
on a campaign to help prioritize the case with the FDA.
Bang Energy has eight active lawsuits due to false advertising and marketing.
Check out the truth about bang.com to learn more.
I'm sure you can think of some real interesting things to talk about
once you visit the website.
If you would like to participate in this campaign to help spread the truth
and prioritize this case with the FDA, please apply here and let us know what it
would cost to collaborate. So what the fuck?
So these people are offering me money to help spread the word
about the FDA case against bang energy,
which I don't know.
I don't know why I would get contacted about this.
Yeah, I don't know if I'm just if it's just random,
this guy is just emailing everybody with a fucking platform on earth or what?
But if you go to the truth about bang.com,
it's basically just about how they've made all these false claims
about the energy drink, such as that it contains an enhanced form of creatine.
Not true as a patent on super creatine.
Not true can reverse mental retardation, cure Alzheimer's disease,
Parkinson's, Huntington's, other forms of dementia.
Yeah. Yeah.
But at the bottom of the page, it says, don't get bang boozled.
America is noticing.
I've been banged.
Fucking sneakers.
Frequently in what is it?
Defeat bang. Is it the truth about the truth about bang?
The truth about bang.com.
Yeah. There are videos from the CEO
Jack, which I don't know why all CEOs are named Jack now,
but that's just how it is.
Yeah, that's what they do.
So if you also want to mose on over to VPX sports on YouTube,
I will also link that here.
They have a lot of videos dedicated to bang, many of which featuring Jack.
And let me just say Jack is my personal hero
and someone who I look up quite a bit.
He is quite the intense frantic man.
Almost Alex Jones, which depends on the video.
Sometimes I think he hasn't
drank in a bang before recording, but in many he has.
And he has a he has a this is going to sound strange.
I would describe him as like a mixture
between Alex Jones and Butch Hartman, a fairly odd parents name.
That's kind of does he display all the outward symptoms of reverse retardation?
I think he has an IQ well into the triple digits.
Well, OK, great.
So I I got really down this.
This is like a weird coincidence, right?
Digi, that we're both like now entangled in the bang.
Yeah, totally.
Independent of one another.
Yeah, yeah, that's crazy.
So if you want, I will select some some videos for your enjoyment.
But needless to say, this YouTube channel is
a shuck full of great parody level videos
and commercials advertising bang as if it were like a joke.
Yeah, I'm looking at it.
Digi, please don't take down Big Bang
until I've tried that cotton candy.
I'm inclined to think that this might have even been inspired by Alex Jones,
who is by a supplement shill.
Like that's what he does. Yeah, that's true.
Because looking at these, it's like it's the same set up of like guy
at a desk with a big expensive mic with a green screen background
that is probably just in his house.
And like, yeah, these videos are pretty hilarious.
Also, the the banner of the YouTube is just a bunch of chicks in bikinis,
but with just their tits and bellies.
No faces.
No, this is so blatantly, it has to be thick, right?
But then you can go to several of it and get your cotton candy flavored bang.
It's not a joke.
Yeah, to be fair, this might be pointing to their sculpted abdomens.
You know, I'm looking at the website.
I'm looking at the Rainbow Unicorn Fitness Collection.
It's nice. It's like, well, these are these are keto, by the way.
They have the meltdown keto caffeine free.
How to make a keto pumpkin cheesecake?
Yeah, there's a ton of keto recipes on the YouTube channel.
Yeah, this is good.
Older, you know, Ben, it sounds like.
And I mean, their clothes look like they would be in Endless War.
So clearly, they do.
Clearly, bang needs to be the official energy drink of Endless War.
Wait, I. OK, but I'm going to post a picture.
Look at this.
They're they're advertising. They're advertising slime.
Here we go. Bam.
This is what they want.
This is what they want us all to be consuming.
Smoothie bowl. That's literally slime.
They're just repurposing slime.
The colors like slime.
That's fucking funny.
You know, you know, Nate, can you can you let us know the inside?
Is Jack Owowick also the CEO of Slime Corp?
I, you know, number one, the N1 doesn't like us to talk about his personal affairs.
So I can't I can't, you know, that's not relevant to our discussion right here.
There's a there's a there's a lot of our
layoffs of security you got to go through before you get a.
What's the connection about the big man?
What's the connection between Andrew Bang and Jack Owow?
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God, there's Andrew Gang.
There's Andrew Bang.
They're going to go head to head real soon.
Andrew, Andrew Gang is just Andrew Yang's body on top of Jack Owowick, by the way.
It's Andrew Yang's body with with a Jack Owow's brain put into it.
It's OK. A thousand miles per hour.
Oh, it's like 120 FPS.
I don't know what's specifically keto about any of this stuff,
other than the fact that it's low carb, but whatever.
Well, they had some some specifically keto drink on the side, I guess.
Yeah. But I don't know what is I don't know what is keto about it.
Like, pretty much the only thing about keto is that it is having low carbs.
Yeah, you can probably make that claim about lots of stuff.
I'm sure I'm sure water is keto.
You know, like just probably make the same claim about Monster Ultra, for example.
Yeah, there you go.
Or like literally any diet drink.
Yeah, or water. Yeah.
Water, for example.
Highly keto.
God, this bang rainbow unicorn just looks so cool.
Bangster berry killers.
Fuck purple and white and black.
Got to get me some.
I've been marketed to you so effectively.
I'm going to staff my suitcase with bangs
and I'm going to bring it next time I come to Boston.
And you're going to be able to try some.
I'm going to smuggle you some. Don't worry.
We're going to sell this one for all.
I should just walk to Davis Square and just just I just got to be like,
hey, Mr. Mr. 711, Mr.
Mr. Dr. 711 CEO of 711 Corporation.
You got any bang for me? Thanks.
I bet they do. I hope so.
Please, God. Maybe you get your own.
Maybe, maybe.
Anyway, so bang is is an endless joy.
Just just navigate their website.
Look at all of the crazy shit they have on display here.
All the stuff that you can buy.
There's so many.
There's so much. It's a lifestyle brand is what it is.
It is.
Do they utilize the phrase bang for your buck anyway?
No, I don't think so.
No, these are extremely expensive.
You don't want to be thinking about that.
They are extreme. Why are they so much money?
OK, at 711, they're like a normal drink, right?
They're a normal drink.
But these are like $50 for a 12 pack.
Some of them are insane.
Some of them are insanely expensive,
and some of them are just a little expensive.
They they there's like no real like pattern to how they're priced.
Just like the weird the weirder ones cost more.
Maybe I don't know.
Maybe they're hard to manufacture something like that.
Maybe like the keto coffee ones are more expensive
than just the 12 pack of the cotton candy.
Like the newer the newer flavors just cost like double.
I think some of these are like $96 for a 12 pack
for some of like to highly specialized ones.
What the fuck? That's insane.
It's a racket, right?
Bang variety, 12 pack, $31.99.
And that's not crazy.
That's I guess that's fine.
All right, I've had enough fucking bang.
Yeah, yeah, move on to.
Hey, hey, clip clip that clip at everyone.
Clip clip saying did you doesn't want any more.
I just want to say I just got a hilarious
OK, so I got to say whatever.
You know how with with the T-Bap stuff,
I never once on T-Bap ever linked best guy ever stuff
up to this very day.
The first time I ever did was yesterday
with T-Bap resurrection at the very end said like,
hey, look what Kagan fans were up to.
And I linked our channels.
I just I just saw of a first comment.
It's on my Gernlog and part two review.
It's a proto gen solace with a pony avatar
just saying this is such a good fucking video.
Holy shit.
We've got the crossover that's been achieved at long last.
Hell, yeah.
There was at least one subscriber to mine there.
I already I already I already I already I already I already
T-Bap comments like, yeah,
surprise that they knew best guy ever and kickstand it,
but they didn't make the connection until just the people do that.
I don't understand how it.
I had already cashed that check
because when I started this Pokemon Sunnuz lock,
I announced it on on TV.
All right.
I never had I already got a whole girlfriend out of that video.
Oh, God, I mean, frankly, Michelle was a fan of T-Bap as well.
And so I mean, we met much later, like during Mia Maffova.
But it was originally with T-Bap.
Michelle Watch was a fan of I mean, I guess she must figure out
that you existed. I suppose I believe her.
But, you know, suspect it is very we got to open an investigation.
I think she might be a spy from Big Bang.
She does love her energy drinks.
All right. Not every episode has to be two and a half hours, guys.
Yeah, I mean, I'm going to go to to voicemails.
We might want to go to voicemails.
Yeah. OK. Yeah, I'm for that.
All right. I say, let's do it.
I mean, we go to voicemails proper.
We've got to check in with our with our current people
investigating the elusive pizza party podcast.
I don't have the I don't have the sound to queued up the intro music, whatever.
Come on. I tweeted I tweeted at Rebel Taxi.
Oh, I saw that. Yeah.
And I included an ill he's he's mysteriously silent on suspicious.
I'd say very, very suspicious.
I was not here for this whole saga.
Can someone explain to me what's happening?
You don't you know, you don't know.
Really? You miss the whole thing?
That's what we're investigating the whereabouts of the podcast.
Yeah, the so called podcast.
It is it is ongoing yet to be found.
The answers are just not forthcoming.
But you know, the whole hashtag.
Where's the podcast?
No one can find it. There's no clues.
Where's the podcast? No one knows.
Understood. OK, so let's go to it.
We've got someone reporting on the scene.
This is electronic warbear.
He's got some comments to say.
So let's hear from him. Go.
I've started my safari of the urban jungle of Atlanta.
And what is this?
A con for animation and gaming, Momo con.
And who is this special guesting at this con?
Why the pizza party podcast?
Oh, my God, I've begun my mission to find the podcast.
Yeah. Hashtag.
Fulls errands. Boots on the ground.
I appreciate it. Yeah, we've got it.
We've got my fucking vision when black after you said Momo.
And I just had I just started thinking about the Momo challenge
and how and how much of my failure I am for not finishing the Momo challenge.
Well, we've got a so we've got a soldier on the scene.
We've got a special agent.
Frankly, I fear for his well being. Me too.
I mean, when he discovers that it's all a sham.
Oh, I'm sure they'll show up.
I'm sure some some agents, some blank faced, you know, glassy eyed agents
will show up to this quote unquote pizza party podcast panel.
But we all know that it's all a facade below the service.
There is no podcast going on underneath there.
Why do they even have a fucking Momo con appearance?
They don't talk about anime.
Well, because they're they said it's like a cartoon or animation.
Con, I guess. I don't know.
There's no. Why is rebel?
Why is rebel taxis avatar so hideous and a bad?
It's just very abstract.
I don't know what it means or is it's awful.
I guys, I showed you the Toy Story.
Let's play it.
Red Con 3.5.
Yeah, indeed.
Indeed, which is pretty funny.
Yeah.
Have we that to the people or the people aware of that?
Because that is incredible.
I I mean, all that needs to be said is just watch the first episode of
toy pan pizzas Toy Story.
Let's play and just watch it to the end and trust me.
That's the first episode.
Yeah, this is your intro to this.
I can only imagine where it goes from the intro of the video.
It's clickety-clack down the track.
That's what he says to start out the episode.
And it goes so, so far downhill.
OK, you'll know.
You'll know when you hear that clicking and clacking.
OK, let's go to the actual voicemails here.
Oh, this is this is appropriate.
This first mail is from fuck the PPP.
Long live the PCP.
Hey, there we go.
Sounds good.
Yeah.
Yeah, we exist, bitches.
Commands.
So I just wanted to say that the last episode of the PCP was some.
Yeah, and I do not mean gay shit.
I mean, yeah.
OK, yeah.
First of all, Pokemon.
What the fuck is a Pikachu?
Second of all, you didn't play maintro.
Although the version by Ben and Nick was very nice.
Oh, sorry about that.
Capitalism.
Nate, why don't you come hang out in this slum?
Why don't you come to South America?
Literally home to Brazil.
And to call the money from.
Why don't you get some perspective?
Lots of all, what the fuck is going on with the editor contest?
You know, I want to make some money.
Oh, yeah.
Get out of this fucking awful place.
There is Argentina.
But I can't if I use fuckers don't say that I won't.
I want the contest.
I won't.
How do you fix a party podcast?
Well, thank you.
Appreciate that.
I'm glad I said that.
I put that in.
I just wanted to say, hey, everybody who's
waiting to hear back about the editor contest,
we're still voting and deliberating.
You will hear back.
So we haven't forgot.
Obviously, it's high priority.
I've already cussed my judgment.
Indeed, most of us have.
Listen, I edited the last episode,
and it ruined my whole week.
It was a nightmare.
I hated it.
I'm never doing it again.
I'm so fucking eager to pick a winner
and never edit another podcast.
Well, that's great, Ben, because I
think you're one of the people we're
waiting to hear from in terms of your votes.
OK, yeah, I should.
OK, I'll send you the list.
I've got the list.
My B. OK, all right.
I have to do it, too, so I'm dragging ass.
OK, next one, let me see.
This voicemail here is from Arith Dyes.
I notice he says, Arith, not Arith.
I appreciate that.
Go.
OK, I've been playing Final Fantasy VII,
and I just realized that, like, Arith fucking dies.
And I'm at that point, and that happened.
And like, do you get her back?
Or is she dead forever?
What the fuck?
Oh, I love that music.
I grinded her levels of shit.
She's gone now.
What the fuck?
I want her back.
Ah!
Is this one of those things where it's like he's known
forever that Arith dies, but when it actually happens,
he's like, oh, she actually died.
Yeah, like, I actually spent like 20 hours grinding her levels.
I just thought this was a meme.
Yeah.
You knew she was going to die.
Why didn't you?
Why didn't you just not grind her?
Why didn't you prepare yourself?
I mean, to be fair, that's it's.
He didn't think they would actually do it, the Madman.
It's kind of like that argument that's like, you know,
like, if you think that ex-mechanic is in a game,
is overpowered, then just don't use the mechanic, bro.
Like, impose your own difficulty challenges.
Like, I would argue it is a, look, I mean,
I love that Arith's died.
That's dope.
But it is technically kind of like a flaw
that you can invest time and resources grinding a character
only to have them removed.
What do you mean it's tech?
I don't know.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, it's not a flaw.
It can be annoying.
It's a good thing.
It's literally a good thing because you have more
than a story reason to care about Arith.
You know, that's true.
Yeah.
For story sense, that's true.
You have a gameplay reason.
I'm just saying, like, if you just say on a gameplay side
alone, and you spend a much time grinding a character,
especially if you played the first time, you don't know.
Oh, that adds to it.
Well, imagine if in the remake they made it so that all
of her XP goes to your other characters when she dies.
I don't even want that.
I mean, you could complain about it.
Someone might not like it.
That doesn't make it a flaw.
OK, fair enough.
I guess it kind of depends on your perspective,
but OK, I get the point.
OK, now actually, I'll fucking fight.
I'll fucking fight someone criticizing that,
because that's great.
It's just great.
Totally hippo.
Yeah, hippo.
You're right.
You're invested.
You're invested because you work.
Yeah, that's true.
It feels like a real loss, especially if you fucking got
her fourth level limit, which you can get by that point,
even though it's hard, but whatever.
By the way, next voicemail is from, I think
it's senior, sad, and depressed.
It's like SR period, so I assume it's senior.
Maybe it's senior?
I don't know.
But this is another one about loss.
SR period definitely means senior.
Does it?
OK, senior, sad, it's senior.
It would go at the end of a word, because like the opposite
of junior.
It's at the beginning.
I choose to pick senior.
I think it's senior.
Maybe it's senator.
Oh, it might be.
OK, let's hear what you have to say, sir.
Hang on, it's loading.
There it goes.
Mr. Sander, please.
Mr. Best Man, in all times you mention girl and log in,
please explain why in all the videos
that I've watched before now, where you've done so,
you never once said that Simone's brother is Kamina.
So I was thinking like, oh, you know, Simone's brother dies,
but you know, they're not actually real blood
siblings, and he can't die, right?
And so I just never thought about it.
Then when you get to episode nine, you're just there,
and he kisses Yoko, and they're going into a fight,
and you're just thinking like, does he actually die?
I know, I was thinking that too.
I pause it at that point.
I was like, thinking, like, recalling all the times
you had mentioned him, and I was just like, no, he doesn't die.
You know, he's been, he said brother.
How did we get two of these in a row?
You asked for this?
You never said Kamina, Mr. Best Man.
What the fuck is the point of this?
So I paused it, and I scrolled through the thumbnails,
and I saw him.
Episode 16, I saw the thumbnail, had Kamina in it.
That's a flashback episode, you dumbass.
Whoa.
All right.
I had shipped him with Yoko.
I was just thinking they're going to have such cute kids,
but it wasn't true.
He did die.
You know, it is a bit of a sin.
I should do that, Mr. Best Man.
I think you should make a rule.
OK, OK, that's enough.
I heard that before he stopped.
This is me off.
Naheads are fucking banned.
If you're in Nahead, I'm going to fucking ban you from the PCG.
That's just someone who's really invested in current law.
Yes, that's all I got from that.
It fucking drives me insane when you go on my anime list,
because they fucking have a list of,
if the show is on Crunchyroll, they'll
have thumbnails of the episodes.
And the first one that appears will always
be whatever is the last or latest episode.
So if you see a thumbnail with the characters,
fucking Crunchyroll just auto-selects a face
from early in the episode.
So if you see a face on episode 12 when you go to Mal,
you immediately know that character is not dead.
I mean, obviously, it could fuck with you,
like this case and this voicemail.
But I'm always, I'm just like, what the fuck?
You literally have spoilers right on the page
where you tell me about the show at all.
I mean, it's kind of weird.
It's like you want to balance not spoiling people,
but I guess they just want to get a little snapshot
of the content of the episode as a preview.
But yeah, it's just like, this character is definitely
not dying by this episode.
So rest assured.
What's that one show that you talked about
where there's a character who you think isn't,
the twist is going to be they're not dead, but you see them.
But it was like a hallucination or something.
It was like a hologram.
I don't know, you did your, I want to fucking video on it.
You know what, who cares?
Doesn't matter.
Are we talking about Steins Gate Zero?
No, it was like, what's the one with the kids
and like the post-apocalypse, and they're all
sci-fi or something.
I don't fucking remember.
Okay, whatever.
Sci-fi.
I mean, don't they have like psychic powers or something?
You know what, who literally cares?
Shinsekai Yuri?
I think that's what I'm trying to think of.
Wasn't there like a guy who died?
Oh, yeah.
No, it's that he dies.
And then like through the whole show,
this girl like thinks that he is still out there.
And then in like one of the last episodes at the very end,
like she emerges from this dark cave and the guy is there
and he's all grown up like he would be
cause he had died when he was younger.
And then it just straight up at the start of the next episode
turns out she was just seeing shit.
Oh my God.
It was just a different character
and she was just seeing shit.
And it was totally meaningless.
That's fucked up.
So fucking annoying.
And people defend that show.
People call that show a 10 out of 10.
Maybe other parts are good.
I don't fucking know.
Not being impressed.
Fucking terrible.
Okay. All right.
Next call.
This one is hashtag bring back to Voo.
Let's see what he has to say.
This is what I was saying.
This is what I was saying before we started.
Gotta bring back to Voo.
People crazy.
The official scarcity of the Voo.
I remember every episode will have like one mention of them,
but only for like a second.
And then no one talks about him ever again.
I just listened to some of the older episodes
of the podcast with the Voo on it.
And I listened to it with my mom and they were fantastic.
I have not enjoyed a podcast for 10 years.
It was a period of sex one with your mom.
I finally did because of the power of the Voo.
And we barely get any Voo content.
He's kind of like a limited edition thing.
Why is this?
Why do all podcast members have to be
Wait, hang on.
Flaky, floppy, gloopy, basically hardened air
like all PCP members are.
And we enjoy the Voo.
Why is the only Voo content we get a video game?
I can't do anything with it.
What's wrong with that?
I can do it.
It's just late.
You can't do what are you supposed to do with a video game?
I'm usually in favor of capitalism.
But if it takes a couple of government interventions,
national policies, higher tax rates,
utilitarianism, whatever it takes for Voo to come back
on the show, let's do it.
Big problem.
The problem here is that you're barking up the wrong tree.
Like you're asking us why isn't Voo on the show?
None of us knows.
He can come back anytime, any day.
Yeah, literally Voo just doesn't.
I mean, he seems to be very adamant about not wanting
to have a public persona.
So there's that.
He just fucked off somewhere.
Because he wanted to.
I suppose, because I didn't think about this point till now,
but I suppose this whole not wanting to have a public persona
might just mean he does not want to be on podcasts.
I mean, especially ours anymore.
I don't know.
I mean, it would seem so.
Yeah, I don't know.
I do know that he's, go on, get it, go on.
I do know that he has explained a little bit
about what's going on on his Patreon, if you patronize.
Oh, really?
Oh, okay.
Well, mostly just that he's working on stuff
and that the Patreon is active again.
That's pretty much it.
It's not that we like pick every episode
of who's going to be on.
It's whoever wants to be on.
It's just whoever shows up.
Like, listen, we want Voo here as much as you do.
We all want more to Voo.
It's not up to us.
We can't do it.
We, he's gonna come to us.
If you got, like, I would encourage if you want
to know what's going on with Voo, talk to Voo.
Do not, like, Voo really does not like
when other people speak for him.
So, like, I would, I don't want to even speculate
about what's, because I don't really know.
I don't know what the hell is going on with him,
because he barely talks about anything
other than editing my videos.
He's not even in the chat.
He left the PCP chat.
He's not even on.
He did that ages ago.
Let's not be hyperbolic.
He's done that before.
He could come back anytime.
No, yeah, he can come back anytime.
Just saying, if you guys want to know
what's going on with Voo, ask to Voo.
Don't ask us.
I was just gonna say, I see Voo in the chat,
but I realize that's just Victor.
Yeah, yeah, I changed Victor's name and role to be Voo.
It was, we were talking about this right before this.
Wait, so never mind.
I guess we've got a new Voo.
It's okay, guys.
We've replaced Voo.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's all good.
We built a better Voo.
If only Victor ever came online on Discord,
even one single fucking time.
I don't think Victor even has Discord, like, on his computer.
Probably, yeah, probably not.
So he's just like this?
Can't read.
To us, and essentially.
Yeah.
He's just as much of a limited-edition
artificial scarcity boy.
Even more so, even more so.
But yeah, fair enough.
Anytime, people, and don't bug him,
don't harass him or anything,
but I don't know, if you want him to come back,
you could inform him in a polite and respectful way.
I mean, he's on Twitter.
You know, there are ways to contact him.
I don't know if he's still doing that thing
that he had before, though,
where his Twitter, because he had adblocked everything
that wasn't the text entry form,
so that he doesn't see any Twitter except for,
I don't know if he's still doing that, though,
but for a while, he had it so that if he opened Twitter,
it was just a type your tweet
and then a submit button and nothing else.
So he can't even see the response to it or anything?
No, nothing.
Oh, that's interesting.
I don't know if he's still doing that, though.
I copied him for a while.
Dude, I, oh God, what was it?
I talked to Oolulilia,
and he told me that he has software,
he's done something to his computer
at the operating system level
that doesn't let him see certain website,
doesn't let him see anything that Google owns,
including YouTube.
So it was like a robot.
He had much of the internet just blocked from his view.
He's still on Facebook, though.
He's doing that.
Even this is his data.
Such lengths to avoid a certain company
for various reasons, I don't know,
but then Facebook's totally okay.
Well, I mean, it's monopolized, dude.
It's either one or the other,
or you're a fucking in no man's land, basically.
Yeah, I guess.
Space exists.
Yeah, fair.
Did you hear that MySpace just lost eight years of posts
or whatever?
Everybody's, what?
It's lost, like somebody spilled some fucking bang
on the hard drive, and it all exploded.
They really banged up that hard drive, and, yeah.
That big bang is just control.
It's control.
No, do we have any more voicemails?
All right, we've got a couple more.
Let's go through.
Okay, next one is, oh, this is a good one.
It's Ben St. Killed My Grandma.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, but before we play,
I just wanna say for the past three months,
for the entire voicemail section,
I have been on the YouTube homepage,
just like watching shitty fucking terrible
new Western animation like teaser trailers
without the sound on, and trying to match
your guys' voice to shit, ah, Western animation characters.
So right now, right now I am the bunny
from the Secret Life of Pets 2,
being really angry on screen right now.
I highly recommend this experience.
Please give us a screen cap or something.
Secret Life of Pets sounds like the most
human core fucking show I've ever heard of.
But isn't it Animal Core though, because it's pets?
Liking animals is human.
Okay, I guess that's fair.
Okay, let's move on.
Ben St. Killed My Grandma, and I wanna hear about it.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Oop.
Commencing audio playback.
Classified information moving in three, two, one.
Guys, listen to me, I don't have much time.
I'm from the future, the year 2021.
In the year 2020, the PCP falls apart.
When them snakes, the guy who dropped that awesome track,
he buys Ben's kidney stone, reverse-engineers it,
and creates an army of Ben snakes, it's Armageddon.
Ben rises in power, he's playing so much Garfield Go,
that now he declares every day Monday for the populace,
only he gets to experience Fridays.
Every other day's Monday falls.
He controls everything.
The stores only sell keto food.
It's, I can't do this, or you don't think it affects
the PCP, you think I'm being overdramatic?
Listen to this.
As the inheritor, as the new inheritor of title
of PCP dictator, what?
Just like to say, best guy, we wish you well
in your future.
What is this?
And our attorneys will be contacting you soon
and we'll see you in court, you motherfucker.
Ben.
I remember, yeah, that sounds like something
I would say in the future.
In the future, yeah.
You have to drag me out of my gold-plated office
by my dead fucking claws.
When them snakes clones my kidney stone
and turns it into an army of Ben Saints, guess what?
We're all voting for Yang.
We're all gonna be Yang gang.
I guess, fair enough.
So you have complete domination over the world,
but you're still voting.
Yeah, that's right.
Well, Yang gang wants Yang gang for life.
That's really all there is to it, so.
Yeah, I mean, it's, you know, it's incremental steps.
2020, Ben St, the Ben St collective,
elects Yang.
2021, we are Yang.
We replaced him.
All right, let's move along here.
That's a terrifying thought,
but next up is hipster Cthulhu calling in again.
The future's looking bright, boys.
All right, Cthulhu, lay it on us.
Hey, PCP, you know, it's a bit windy outside.
Let me just open the window.
Oh, okay.
That's it.
That's the entire podcast call.
Yeah, this is pretty good.
I feel refreshed.
I feel, yeah, it was nice.
It was cooling.
Oh, okay, you know what?
So last time I said, we got a call from a podcast
in the middle of someone else's podcast.
That one was shit, but this one's a little bit better.
So let's hear what he has to say.
Hello, and welcome back to the podcast
that takes place in the middle of someone else's podcast.
Today's theme of this podcast is the crushing
existential dread you feel
when the members of the podcast,
you are trying to have your respectable podcast
in the middle of don't deem you worthy,
but still have the gall to mention the fact that you exist.
So it's not just like they just missed over you,
but it's like they noticed you were there,
but you were just not good enough.
And you know, in a way that is crushing and soul destroying,
but another way it pushes you to make better content.
So that's the end of this podcast.
Thanks for listening.
I'll give you an example of that, I'm guessing.
Who sent that one?
His name is simply podcast
in the middle of someone else's podcast.
That's all I know.
He sounded a little bit like no thank you.
Maybe it's him.
It's a mystery to everybody.
Well, maybe we'll see improved content for him coming up.
Okay, moving on.
Something about black people with British accents.
Yeah.
What a, it's so, it's so.
Oh, do you think that was a black guy?
Did it, I thought so.
That'd be my guess if I had to guess.
I didn't.
Who knows?
Ben confirmed racist.
Okay, moving on.
That's right.
We've got LPCP roll call, Scorcho.
That's his full name.
Okay, go.
Ooh.
I think it's time for a bit of a roll call.
It's a weasel.
Starting with the DeFu.
Yeah.
And Tom Oliver nades the best guy in the world.
She wears tiny hats.
Yes.
And let's jazz and hypocrite.
We thought we'd be defencings.
Hopefully they didn't miss anyone.
Yeah, I think that was everybody.
I feel very denigrated.
I just mentioned my name.
I didn't even get a blurb.
Yeah, that's true.
I mean, Digi didn't even get mentioned, right?
Oh, did I?
No.
I'm pretty sure you just skip it.
Wasn't he at the very beginning
right before he started saying, or did I miss it?
Oh, okay.
No, it was DeVu and Tom.
Yeah, DeVu and Tom, lol.
Oh, wait, did he miss anybody else?
I think it was just Digi, right?
Well, I think that is lay joke, but okay, moving on.
Okay.
Hey, whoever's editing this episode,
are we gonna use, remember last episode,
someone had a song that we all said,
like, oh, this should be the intro song this episode?
Don't remember, but I believe.
One of the voicemails last was just a funny song
about the podcast, and we were all like,
that should be next episode's intro.
Okay, someone should, we should check this out.
They're all up on the SoundCloud, so we can use them.
Okay, next call.
This is from Mozilla Fennecann, writing it again.
Oh, yeah.
Go.
Hey, you argued about interrupting effects
of podcast or whatever, and as a long-time fan
and podcaster myself, I wanna give my thoughts.
I think that interrupting-
Okay, hold on a second.
I wanna say something.
I think that interrupting is always bad.
I wouldn't ever do it.
I'm really enjoying, it's really hard to listen to.
It's so weird.
I'm just like a bunch of baby chicks.
It's so wrapped in tape
Indeed case point proven interrupting is the best
Wait that wasn't megalovania that was um that was like
I thought it was like a heavy metal remix of the Star Wars cantina
It's not a meme
It is a meme they're both way bigger meme than megalovania is actually about that dude. I don't know mash up mash up
Yeah, but somebody please mix that okay sound off in the comments. What fucking song was it?
Okay, but next call is from I will fuck you up harder than I fuck sheep. Okay, that's he's writing in go
Is it a Welshman, maybe
St. Patrick chased all the snakes from Ireland
Oh, is that why mum she's ancestors fled to America? Oh, I know you fucking faggot
The next time you set foot this side of flamfire put gwingill go get a quenthroble and the silly oh go go go
your ass is mine
I think that was a Welshman, right? That's a real place you made some enemies. Well, so that was Welsh, right give
Like if you look at like a Welsh
Like road signs there are some like extremely long and impossible to pronounce roads play like names
There's a video of a weatherman like a Welsh weatherman like pronounce
He's he says like the weather in and then he proceeds to pronounce a like 50 letter long
Name that makes you know fucking sit but he says the whole thing and it's like an entire sentence of a word
And he just says it perfectly and he seems a little bit just a little bit satisfied with himself that he got through
Without without fucking it up. I'm proud of him. He did a good job
Well, you made an enemy for life of the Welsh people munchie. That's your bad line. I couldn't be happier
Okay, moving on. Oh, we've got okay returning hero riddle my ass Batman is calling it again
The song continues. Let's let's go. I'm so fucking excited
Let's continue
Batman who bangs big booty bitches has gains muscle like no other and he's nothing but beans
So Batman, have you just siphoned my riddle?
It's a crooked code bearer the first line of each letter spells something. Yes bangs be gains
G E
eats B G E also stands for best guy
Yes
Very well Batman. You know, you're done away with this again release it minions. Thanks, Batman
Hey, thanks for you. I have three beautiful women here
Wonder woman cat woman and tell you how cool choose one. I choose and
And Ben's answer here
What?
Another soul saved and a soul laid
Doing it next time if I know God same PCP time same PCP channel
God he got he got Halle Berry
Yeah, it's great. It's fantastic. He got Ben Affleck Halle Berry. He got whoever plays wonder. What's the lady who plays Wonder Woman?
Gal Gadot Gal Gadot Gal Gadot. Yeah, Gal Gadot. Yeah. Yeah, the but it's not the only one who every time I think I hear Gal Gadot
Thinks it's like a like a former Chinese warlord or something or like some kind of sound like that
Makes me think of waiting for
Love you love your stuff. That wasn't our brittle though. That would that just was like
So it's Nate Nate is green and it has sunglasses
Okay, just because the riddle was pretty much the same as mine
Yeah, just because the answer was relatively easy to decipher. It doesn't mean it was not a riddle
It was just you know riddle for babies. My mind was just like who does
Credit where credit is due in rhyming. This is a hilarious fucking premise
It's not that he was able to decipher what each line meant. He figured out that BGE started the sentences
This is comedy. Monty. Do you understand comedy and jokes?
Riddle my ass Batman
Another soul laid
The way he the way he says it he like slurs it to go
It's got like a mouthful of quarters or something, okay
Change nothing up the stakes up the ante. I want more. Okay next one. This is from okay
We've got one more actual voicemail from concerned citizen of America. Okay go
Same you know a lot of the times you guys would say stuff like this isn't an anime podcast
And this isn't a podcast where we talk about anime you losers stop asking about it, but considering I also didn't assume it was a
podcast about politics and you seem to talk a shit ton about that I
Think it's only fair that we finally get the answer to the age-old question
Favorite anime
Let's say our favorite anime is wait, but I don't I don't want you better think real fast you
three
Popey the performer. I think it's good enough. Yeah, I think he speaks for all of us when he says poppy the performer
Leafy ahead into the wild
Nate are you also talking about Shinsekai yori again
Let's just put it down put me down for Shinsekai yori everybody that sounds good
All right film yeah, but oh but only the sub not the
Leafy that leafy ahead into the wild is a Korean animated not even anime
It's about a hen who adopts a duck
It's about a hen who adopts a duck kind of and raises it as her son
It's a heartwarming film and it's really good
It's so good. It's all right. I'm sold. I don't know about you moving on mate maids mate maids
Did you might have because I was saying how good it is like forever ago because I loved it so much I
Think it I think I might have heard about it from you actually. I'm glad you guys. Yeah, I don't care. Well, you should let's end
Yeah, that was that was the last one we're all done people so thanks for listening everybody
This has been another episode of the procrastinators podcast patreon.com slash
Procrastinators, right? Yes. Okay. Thank you. I always I don't know why
Five dollars bonus episodes. We just recorded a new one people
Should we say should we say
It'll come out one two. No, it'll come out three days after this episode comes out
So we'll let you speculate. We'll tell you after it comes out
So give us you know what will do you know what will be out by the time you're listening to it will not be up by the
Time they listen. No, no, I'm asking. Do you know what will be? Oh by the time you know supposedly no, I don't the real the real
PCP dating Sam
Yeah, that's right, of course
But not the not the original one, which will be out two days on from now from when you're listening to this on April 1st
But the other one supposedly will be out
Gonna be a demo I
Think that's it is a demo. Yeah, that's that's right. You know a voicemail by the way go on much. Go ahead
Well, I just want to say that I don't believe you
That's the thing. We'll have to see
I've doubted this project from the beginning April 1st, right April 1st
Hmm that day has no larger significance than I'm aware of so that should be fine
They seem they seem I mean despite the day
They have been on record at saying that the best kind of surprises on April fools are actual things that you think are bullshit
But turn out to actually be real and cool and dope
So maybe you know, I will reserve judgment. I will reserve judgment. How exciting first how exciting anyway
Follow those guys. Well, go go check out if it's out by the time you're hearing this, I guess
Interesting that's that's at PCP dating sim and at PCP dating are the two competing, you know
We got a voicemail from somebody it was something essentially like he made like a in one minute
He made a PCP dating sim that was like a Google text thing you could type into it wasn't I think was a joke though
So I didn't you know what it sounds while we're doing our promos
I just felt the need to say if you're listening to this podcast
And you need more content in your life
Subscribe to everybody on the podcast and watch all their videos. I
Don't know it's it's it's weird because I know there's people who listen to PCP who only like actually follow a couple of us
Or maybe just one or somebody. Yeah, yeah
The conceit of this podcast is a bunch of people who make good videos
So go watch them all make good stuff. Yeah, I well, you know
We'll say good content
Everybody in the group makes good content, so go follow the rest of their content
Because I just I just hear every once in a while people who are like
Oh, I don't know anything about X member of the PCP and I'm like why why do you not know anything about any
Member if you're a fan of one of us, why would you you would like all of our content?
It's all the same kind of shit
There are always there are all every episode there are links to our YouTube channels in the description
Everyone who's on that episode and from our YouTube channels, you know, there are links up in the top
We've got we've got our other social media and other platforms and stuff linked
Mine always links to my web that's right. You're right. Yeah, stuff. Um, yeah, like
Did few like weeks ago now I that video I just made about me talking about what I do
Ended up with a lot of people
Learning about me and like I got contacted about something special and secret and it's cool
Do you mean the hippo talks for minutes video? Yeah, hippo crit talks for minutes. Yeah, sometimes
Focus on basically marketing yourself can go a long way a very long way
My reputation for patreon.com
Slash been saying I had never say it anymore and it's been to my detriment indeed indeed
It was this essential me a foundational meme really. So I'm no so any any
Ben say also read my any marketing campaign eventually starts to ring hollow to people when they hear it too much
It was got to be re-entering. Yeah platform. I couldn't strike the right balance
I couldn't I couldn't I couldn't just keep ramming that down people's throats forever. I had to find a new tactic
So instead I just stopped
Why is this always? Okay, that's it everybody. Thanks for listening
Oh, we can follow us of course at TP craftnators
You should go if you have not go do yourself a favor and go watch t-bap a resurrection link down below people in the show notes
Why is it not called max revive TV? Um, I don't know max reviving is
Relevant
We will see you soon people and by the way, I'm playing a set with a natural
I'm supposed to be working right now
I'm
Working out at the gym pc p-fit boy
I'm supposed to be eating all my greens
Don't forget to subscribe
You don't gotta do some shit on the page young but give us money
Please invite a shirt, don't RFC K, do the endless war
I hope you enjoyed the podcast
Took the next week to hear another blast from the past and the future too
Cause we're utilitarianism is the way to go