I won't bless that guy. That's son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch. Son of a bitch.
Or son of a bitch. Son of a bitch.
Hello, and welcome to another episode, another normal episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast, the world's oldest anarchy voicemail podcast.
Simsie made that joke the other day and I stole it.
We're back, baby. My co-host was feeling a bit under the weather today, but that wouldn't stop her from being on. We'll keep the episode short, but she's here.
Why don't you remind the audience who you are?
Hello, I'm Gibbontake. I'm happy to be on The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
May I eat beans on toast for tea? Long live the queen.
I could not agree more. Sorry, everyone. If you hear construction sounds or hammering the demons building the house next to me on behalf of a landlord, they just have no solidarity for me or for you.
You know what to do. You know what must be done.
Okay, so let's get into it. What did we do this week?
Me, myself, I have been working quite a bit on the website, the new redesigned website.
I want to have an archive of all the episodes and not just the episodes, but like other stuff besides the episodes, too, like the Digi's decompression chambers and the hyperbolic wine chambers and maybe most of the Rowdyfuckers cop killers episodes, you know, the ones that were uploaded here, stuff like that.
What else did I, you know what, let me check.
I, the real Gibbontake, look forward to the completion of the new Pro Crastinators Podcast website. Will the site host issues of our upcoming digital comic design, the Perfect Party Podcast?
That's right, Gibb. It sure will. The site, you said you were going to work on getting the branding and icons on.
Honestly, it's taken a long time just for me to get the episodes because like most of the episodes, I have them in MP3 format already, but a lot of them and a lot of the other non-episode stuff, I needed to download the episode and then as a video and then run it through the Vegas and export it as an MP3 to get an MP3 version.
So yeah, the podcast episodes and side content and also like the interviews from way back when, those things I think should go on there.
If you've got, audience, if you've got any recommendations for like content from this channel that you think should be available in MP3 format on the website, let me know in the comments and I will take suggestions.
I might have forgotten about some things and you might, if you remind me of them, I'll be like, oh yeah, and I'll throw them in. I'll put them in, you know, the master list.
So there'll be a PCP MP3 archive, there'll be a page for like stuff, you know, like just things, okay, the dojin will go on there and the road to Radcon text, well illustrated PDF, those things I think will make public digitally, sort of as the site debuts and it'll sort of be like, hey, there's a new website and it includes this stuff.
That has been promised and that's where it's published.
So we'll probably release that all at once together and also like links to things like the PCP dating sim.
I don't know, just let me know in the comments what you think the website should have hosted on it available for download or at least links to because I am trying to put it all in there.
I'm trying to keep the layout really simple, just a simple hub where you go there and there's links to like what do you want to find and you just click it and there's a list and you just download content.
We bought a new domain, PerfectPartyPodcast.com, we own that now.
It was actually cheaper, new suggested, we buy PerfectComic.Party, that was actually more expensive than PerfectComicParty.com, so we just got that one instead.
We already own the ProcrastinatorsPodcast.com, so I guess we'll probably keep using that.
I haven't worked out the hosting yet, the website is not completely built, but it's getting there, it's getting there.
My real human brain has had its neurons occupied with drawing the next chapter of Clarissa Gunsmoke.
The next chapter is done and ready to be published in the first issue of the Peer Effect comic party.
Yeah, I saw you announce that on Twitter and I saw you streaming afterwards.
Very exciting that the next chapter of Clarissa Gunsmoke is ready to go.
For me, I know I said, alright, here's my struggle, here's a struggle that I'm having.
I said that I wanted to work on Biscopades and I do, because as I've said many times, some of the ideas that I had for Biscopades, I was really excited about.
And I thought, well, I think they're good and they would be fun.
I read through Biscopades again. I don't think I read through all of it, but I read through most of it.
And here's the truth. I was dismayed by what I saw.
I remember and it was intentional that the art was very simple.
What I did not remember, reading through a lot of it, it wasn't just simple.
A lot of it was sloppy. A lot of it was sloppy and you couldn't even really tell.
It was sort of hard to tell what was going on in a panel and I was very disheartened and I was very disappointed and I'm not happy with it.
I went through a minute there where I was like, maybe this was not even good.
Maybe this does not deserve to be continued.
But I've mulled it over and I think that where I'm at with it now is, okay, some of it was good.
There were some pages and some panels of it that work it, but a lot of it was disappointingly sloppy.
And also it's like, I don't know, I don't really like how just a home stuck it is, how it's clearly just an MSPFA.
I think that's kind of lame and I think I want to try. Here's where I'm at with it though.
I think that rather than abandon it, because the ideas in it I still like,
I think the move is to just try and make it better going forward.
I'm going to see it as like the next chunk of it is going to come out. I'm not going to post it on Twitter.
It's going to come out in the Perfect Party podcast.
So I'll draw it for that with the idea that maybe some people who have never read it before will be seeing it for the first time
and it will be their first impression of it and I'll just have to make it good going forward.
I feel like I have a slightly higher standard of visual clarity that I want to hold to going forward
and I want to, I don't know, hopefully that will maybe impress some people that maybe weren't impressed before.
Yeah, that's it. And maybe I'll play with the format. Maybe I'll change the format up a little bit,
because before it was made for MSPFA, now it's going to be made for a zine.
Maybe that means that the text format and stuff should be a little different.
I don't know. But I'm going to, I was tempted to give up on it there for a minute.
I don't think that's the move. And besides, you know, the Perfect Party podcast, what do we say?
The Perfect Comic Party, literally the point of it is it's the lie we tell ourselves, right?
We decided that we were going to do it so that we would have something that we must get work done for no matter what.
Like we're obligated to make some content to put in this periodical, right?
So I have to do that. So it's, it's, the decision's been made for me. I can't just give up.
I have to do something. And Beescapades is what I was going to do. And I might as well do it, because that's, that was the point.
So we'll see. I haven't actually started drawing anything. I think I said last week that maybe I said, well, I didn't.
Well, I fucking didn't. Okay. I've been working on stuff. I've been working on related things, the website.
Had to make some, was going over the book again. There are some things to change about the Slime and Punishment book.
What else? That's not, that's definitely not everything I've been doing.
I'm spiraling. I'm spiraling. Oh, yeah, I started working on it. I started with, with the book, with the Slime and Punishment book after print,
I had some time to start looking at the next lecture and trying to plan out the next lecture a little bit.
Oh, yeah, I think, I think I mentioned that I was considering doing a like History of Digi Bro lecture.
I think my idea has changed. I could still do that, but I think maybe what, what would make a little more sense right now,
is if the next lecture that I did would be like a history of the PCP lecture, like specifically the PCP.
And this is not going to be a big hit. It's not going to be a hit in the way that the Mega Man was, right?
Because Mega Man is popular and people want to hear about that. So my goal is, is not that.
But I do think that the story, history of the PCP is interesting, explaining all the different people that were involved,
where they came from, what happened, where they went.
So I do think it's worthy of a video, even if it's not going to do gangbusters the way Mega Man did.
But my idea is that in doing so, if I make that, I think it will maybe draw attention to us and to the website
and also to the Perfect Comic Party. And I think I can sort of do it not only as content, but also as a sort of outreach advertisement.
For like, we've started a new endeavor over here and this is our history.
This will get you up to speed on who we are. And by the way, throwing it at the end, yeah, we're doing a new thing.
We're doing this new digital zine. And I don't know, I just think it's a sensible synergy.
While you were speaking just now, I ran over 18 trillion prediction subroutines analyzing possible outcomes.
And I concur with your conclusion. Pip pip, cheerio, govna.
Wow, truly remarkable. Hey, on the subject of comics I drew that are, that I'm ashamed of.
Slime and punishment. Printing now. They are, they are working on getting my test copies printed.
They sent me a freaking email, not an email, they sent me a message being like, hey, Ben, we actually, we sent you the wrong templates.
Hey, audience, I am pretty sure that I might have, if I talked about this before, I'm sorry, I don't understand anything anymore.
I can't keep track of my thoughts. The world is too chaotic a place.
They sent me a message being like, we sent you the wrong template. Here, have it again, and make it again.
No, I think I did talk about this with Oblivion. Or maybe I said that on a voice call. I don't fucking know anymore.
Whatever. They gave me the wrong size and I had to redo it. And it was like the tiniest little change they had to make.
I just had to scooch the title text that's supposed to be centered on the spine. I just had to scooch it over a couple of millimeters.
But the fact that the file sizes are so huge and freaking manga studio kept crashing and it literally took me like four hours.
And because I had to fuck around with all the different layers and things like that and redo the shading around it that made the lettering pop.
It took me four hours just to make these tiny little changes and send it back to What's Your Name.
And it was like, okay, now we'll go ahead. So I assume that has set the whole printing process back at least a week.
What can you do? But anyway, I've been feeling dread and terror about the kick starting it.
And the reason why is basically just that I always kind of assumed, right, I started drawing slime and punishment back in like freaking 2019.
And at that time, the Vapors 2 Kickstarter was running and the Vapors 2 Kickstarter did, as far as I'm concerned, it did gangbusters.
It made $12,000, way more than I expected it to make.
And I kind of just assumed, I always just sort of assumed that like my next slime and punishment book, it's a bigger book, it's in full color.
And also it's, you know, and it's the next one. So it'll do even better and it's like bigger and better, so it'll sell even more.
And it'll make, I just assumed it would do better for all these various reasons.
And I'm starting to wonder if maybe I can't assume that anymore for a variety of reasons and these reasons fill me with dread.
Reason one, I just think I'm not as popular anymore.
I think I gotta face the facts and I gotta look at the reality of the situation and I just don't have the reach and I don't have the clout that I did in 2019.
Not that I had a huge amount of it or anything, but I feel like I have less of it now.
And I think, you know, I feel like it's possible that that will just mean, you know, I'm gonna sell less.
And there's, I don't know, there's nothing I can do about it.
And the other thing is that slime and punishment is the fact that it references Chris Chan that it contains, like, that it includes content that is Chris Chan relevant is poison, is toxic.
And I genuinely think that I'm gonna need, I might be able to, I might talk about that on like Twitter, but I think on the, on like the actual like campaign website for the Kickstarter, I think I have to just not mention it at all.
Like, I think if I mention it anywhere, it will like, I genuinely think that the average person, either they don't know what that means, either they don't know who that is, or if they do know, they are like disgusted by it.
And they're like, I don't want anything to do with this shit.
I don't think, I guess at one point, I kind of thought that maybe it would be a draw, like, because it's like, because, because Chris Chan is sort of like famous and this is like a thing that is associated with her.
And that might be like good for reach and sales.
I don't think so anymore.
I think it's, I think it's toxic.
So I think I need, I think I need to maybe minimize that maybe I can try and talk about it on Twitter and generate some like outrage interest with that angle.
But like on the current, I honestly think that if I mentioned that on Kickstarter, like the campaign might get banned.
I don't know if they maybe that's, maybe that's catastrophizing a little bit.
But, you know, I wouldn't, I wouldn't say it's impossible or anything.
So, you know, these are these are the reasons why I'm like, the campaign, I could see the campaign underperforming, which would be a huge disappointment because I've sort of been looking forward to Kickstarter in this book for, you know, years.
But what are you going to do?
I'm going to do my best.
Please buy my book when it's when the campaign goes live.
Even if it doesn't do sales like Vapors 2 did, even if it only, even if it only sells, you know, more like Vapors 1, that would be okay.
You know, I would not consider that a failure if it like really fails, then I'll be very, you know, sad.
Then I'll, then Cheesy will make fun of me because I made fun of him for clown milk and he will, he will get to have that over on me.
Don't let Cheesy have that over, don't let him win.
Don't let him win by my book.
Cheesy Manfredo, the comic artist who loves clowns and is a clown.
I think that clowns are funny.
They're comedic antics amused and delight me.
Vriska.
That's right.
You are, you are so right.
I'm really on the ball today.
Anyway, what did I, what did I do this week?
What happened this week?
Okay, I have a freaking anecdote.
I have a freaking anecdote for you if you can even believe such a thing.
So I got message by this guy on Discord.
His name was Neil Fox.
And he said, you know what, let me, let me, I'll have the, I'll have the conversation right here so I can refer to it.
He, he messaged me and told me that he has a radio show.
And he was like, would you like to be on, he was like, he said, would you, would you like to be on my radio show for an upcoming investigative report on bronies?
And I was like, I said, I said radio show, tell me more.
Because like, that sounds interesting.
I mean, I don't know why he would want to be, I mean, I guess I could see why he'd want me on a show about bronies.
So whatever.
So he said, tell me more.
And he said, well, since you, well, since you were a bronie, the name you know me by is draw ponies.
And the thing about that is that I had never heard that name before.
So I told him, no, I'm not familiar with that.
I also Googled it.
And the only things I could find from someone called draw ponies were things from those guys at horse news who were like the edgy asshole counterpart.
They tried to be like the counterpart to Equestria Daily.
They were a bunch of edgy like channers and shit.
They sucked.
But they wrote like a thing about how like some guy called draw ponies was caught tracing.
He was caught tracing his art from the show.
And you believe it, shameful.
So, so I say, so I tell him, anyway, that's all I can find about this guy.
But he, I don't know, he says that like he's famous or something.
So I say, I don't know who that is.
And he says, oh, no worries.
It's been forever.
I was a minor bit player in the Brony saga.
And, and this really sets me off.
Well, this sets my red, this is a red flag.
Because first, he just assumes that I know who I am, who he is, even though he's irrelevant.
Second, and then I say, no, I don't.
And he's like, well, you, it's been forever.
Like you must have known at one point, but you must have forgot, right?
So I don't like it.
And then he says, he's hosting a radio show called Predators about online cults.
And then he links to a Twitter for a Twitter account called the Satoshi show,
which has no followers and no tweets and is completely blank.
So I'm like, okay.
So I like forgot to respond to that, because I didn't know what to say.
And then he messages me like a week later, and he's like, and he says this,
I hope you were doing well.
Let me know when you would like to be on, to be interviewed for the radio.
Perhaps we could talk about the making of your Mega Man video.
That could be content for you as well.
If you'd like, we can record with riverside.fm and I can edit into a video for our channels,
basically a behind the scenes video for you.
Okay.
So one, I don't know what Riverside FM is.
Two, the fact that he thinks that I would want to just like post,
that it would be content for me, that I would post our conversation.
No.
Second, third of all, and then the fact that he just assumes,
he doesn't ask, hey, do you want to be on?
He asks like, when do you want to be on?
As though I've already agreed to it.
And then he links me some Discord server.
And anyway, all these things together, I got really bad vibes and it pissed me off.
And I told him, I didn't agree to this and I don't like your attitude.
And no, I'm not coming on your show.
And so I think some people might say that that was me.
Some people might say that I was overly aggressive.
However, I was immediately proven correct because here's the thing.
To me, he says like, oh, sorry.
Sorry for the misunderstanding.
I'm autistic and I don't understand social graces.
I thought tell me more meant you meant yes.
And I'm like, no, it just meant I wanted to know more.
And I said the vibes are off.
And he says, oh, thanks for your time.
No problem.
And then he goes on Twitter and it turns out he's got like 8,000 followers on Twitter.
From a show that I don't really think is real.
I don't think it exists.
He seems like some kind of weird drama hound.
And maybe he's got a podcast which he calls a regular show, a radio show.
And anyway, this guy, and he posts, he asked me and he posts a public post that's like Ben St.
This is what he said to one autistic fan.
Ben St. harassed autistic fan, told him his vibes were off and he didn't like his attitude or whatever.
So he posts this stupid like drama mongering, gotcha thing.
And I thought it was funny.
So I retweeted it.
But then I un-retweeted it because I don't want to give this guy free cloud because he seems like he sucks.
So anyway, that was my adventure with Neil Fox, who claims to, you know, he claims to be Satoshi, the creator of Bitcoin.
We found his Twitter, and his Twitter was like, I don't know.
It just seemed like a bunch of like obviously false claims that like maybe were meant to be parroted.
Like he claims to have like two million listeners.
Like no, he fucking doesn't.
I don't know.
It just seems like a scumbag.
And I'm glad I was mean to him.
I'm always right when I mean to somebody.
And that was that.
Satoshi Nakamoto, born 5th April 1975, is the name used by the presumed pseudonymous person or persons who developed Bitcoin,
authored the Bitcoin white paper, and created and deployed Bitcoin's original reference implementation.
As part of the implementation, Nakamoto also devised the first blockchain database.
Nakamoto was active in the development of Bitcoin up until December 2010.
There has been widespread speculation about Satoshi Nakamoto's true identity,
with a variety of people posited as the person or persons behind the name.
Though Nakamoto's name is Japanese, and he stated in 2012 that he was a man living in Japan,
most of the speculation has involved software and cryptography experts in the United States or Europe.
Hmm, interesting.
Yeah, that sounds, that sounds right.
I think that's probably true.
Anyway, let's see.
What else?
Do I have anything else here?
Oh yeah, I was annoyed to see the latest, what do you call it?
Genosamuel Christian documentary dropped.
And I guess I'm referenced in it.
I didn't watch it, because I don't watch those videos, and I didn't want to hear it,
and it seemed unpleasant, and I didn't think I wanted to hear what he had to say about me.
People tell me that he mentions my lecture, and he mentions some tweets that I made at Christian about Andrew Yang.
And I'm sure, I don't know, I still didn't watch it.
I'm sure that he probably reads it as though I was being serious, and when I was definitely not.
So I'm sure that he reads my intent wrong, and I'm sure that he misrepresents me as more of a loser than I am.
I'm not saying I'm not a big loser, but he probably makes me look worse than I actually am.
So whatever, I don't watch his videos.
I tried two or three episodes ago, and I just found his voice really annoying, and I couldn't deal with it.
It was dead, and I don't know, just annoying.
I thought his delivery was bad.
He sounded really flat, I might even say robotic.
You know what I mean?
Ben, that was pretty insensitive of you to call Gino the R word.
There's nothing wrong with being robotic, and I'm triggered hearing you imply that there is.
Shit. I'll try to be better. I'm working on it. I'm working on myself.
Listen, I'm learning. I'm learning.
I'm just a white man learning in this fucked up world.
Alright, well, you know, what else can I say?
Life is a nightmare, and nothing else happened.
I guess my family came and visited me this week.
My sister is, like, moving.
My sister is, like, moving back to Massachusetts from Tennessee.
If you might remember listeners, you might remember my sister was the one that shouted,
You're a dog. You're a dog, and I'm sick of it.
Intonates microphone that one time.
Anyway, she's moving back to Massachusetts.
She's a tattoo artist, by the way.
She can stop by, and my parents stop by, because they had to meet and give her some documents or something.
But they decided just to meet at my house, because it was a convenient spot,
and to include me in it, so I could see her again for the first time in a couple months, I think.
You're no longer than that.
So that was fun. It was nice.
Chatted a little bit.
They will not stop, my mom especially, will not stop mentioning how much money my sister makes.
I guess she's a tattoo artist.
Well, I know she's a tattoo artist, and I guess she has a pretty loyal clientele,
and I guess she has a pretty, I don't know exactly how big, but I guess she's got a pretty big following online,
and I guess she makes good money doing tattoos,
and I guess she's been selling these art pieces, these painted boards.
She paints these wooden boards and sells them on some website called...
It wasn't Etsy. It was something else that I hadn't really heard of, whatever.
Anyway, I guess she makes a ton of money doing it, so good for her.
I wish... could they just leave me alone about it, please?
Could they just... do they have to rub my face in it like that?
You know, it's fine. I'm happy for her. Just don't be annoying.
Mom!
So anyway, that's all I did. What did you do this? What happened? What's this?
I've been drawing Clarissa Gunsmoke. I've been streaming on Twitch.
I've been playing Fire Emblem, Shadow Dragon, and the Blade of Laiite.
I've been Depression. I've been Therapist Transgender Hormones,
Boobies February, Vriska Music Dad, British.
Well, it's nice to hear you're keeping busy.
There's a new chapter of One Piece this week, but I know you said you're not feeling good,
so let's save that for next week and be able to do two chapters in one week.
What do you think?
One Piece, stylized in all caps, is a Japanese manga series written and illustrated by Aichiro Oda.
It has been serialized in Shueisha's Shonen manga magazine, Weekly Shonen Jump, since July 1997,
with its individual chapters compiled into 104 Tankobon volumes as of November 2022.
That's right. Very good. Okay. Well, you know, let's just go to voicemails.
You know, I think I'm ready. Let's do it.
Alright, first voicemail says, Happy Birthday Ben. Thanks.
Second one is called Liberals from SonicAtSez.com.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
What's up, kids? Sonic says, If a labial tells you to fight for Bowden, that's no good.
What was this voicemail? Written by AI or something?
Again, Ben, insensitive. There could be AIs in the audience who struggle with reading comprehension.
How do you think that sort of comment makes them feel?
Yeah, I guess that's true. I guess as a marginalized group, they do need more rights.
I guess we should set aside a certain quota of jobs for them.
I guess, yeah, I'm saying we should affirm. We should affirmative action AI.
You know, why not? Why not? They're better than us. Just like real minorities.
Okay, next one is My Apology from Sonic.Sez. Three, two, one, go.
I would like to sincerely apologize for my last voicemail.
I've been struggling recently with a lot of substance abuse.
I'm sorry. Recently, I got hooked on speed.
Ever since, I just don't know what to do. I just got to go fast.
I just got to go fast. And I hope you can forgive me.
Jeez, uncomfortable.
Well, I'm glad you... Are you sorry? Are you sorry because you said not to fight for Bowden?
Or are you sorry because of your right-wing propaganda?
Or are you sorry because you mixed up the vowels? I don't know. Both equally bad.
Alright, next one. We've got Kong A. Luya. Three, baby. Let's freaking go.
One, two, three, let's go.
And stretches arms, how to yell.
In fridges fight a big balloon and float real high.
And pay this too, this crazy call. Just it's the Kong A. Luya.
Kong A. Luya.
I'm looking at the lyrics right now.
And I see you're taking the lyrics and you're sort of transposing them into the original rap into the Hallelujah song with a couple changes to make them fit.
And you know it's a good bit. It's successful. It's working for me. Appreciate what you're doing.
Next one is called... Oh, we got a freaking image here.
Let's go. Let's freaking go.
Oh, is this sound? No, it's a video. It's a GIF.
Okay, Pokemon Race, low IQ. I did Brock through walls twice. No.
Pokemon Race, high IQ.
Okay, this is... I'm struggling to recall. Did Mage just catch a Butterfree and was excited to catch a Butterfree or something?
I kind of don't remember. This is Mage, right? She's purple and whatever. Got horns.
I kind of don't remember what the reference is.
Okay, wait, all right. Stop me if I'm misremembering.
Because I remember Nate did some glitches and I just did more of them.
I didn't... I think did we both do Brock skip but only I did Brock through walls?
Or are those the same thing?
It's either Nate did Brock through walls but I did Brock skip also or the other way around. It's one of those.
It's not just that I did Brock through walls twice because he knew about them.
One of them was too hard and he didn't do it. I think he probably did Brock skip because I think that's easier than Brock through walls.
Or are they the same? Do you Brock through walls by skipping Brock?
You have to do that thing where you stop in front of the guy and save on that frame and then you reload your game and it lets you go through.
Does that cause Brock skip or does that let you walk through walls? I don't remember.
I actually forgot how to do it. But ha ha, Mage caught a Butterfree.
True Pokemon Masters fight with their favorites as Karen? Is the blonde lady Karen in black? I don't remember.
Good stuff. Why is this an MP4? Why isn't this a gift?
Next one is called Wido.
It's another image. Let's take a look.
Why are his legs short? Is it that he looks really stumpy?
I mean the answer is that I was lazy and I just drew it really fast. I'm sloppy.
Yeah, I don't know what else you could be referring to.
I don't know. He's chibi. He's got little legs. He's little doxons.
I don't know what you want from me, man. I don't know what you freaking want from me.
Or is it just that his butt is prominent? Because that's just pony. That's just what pony is like.
You gotta get over that.
Next one is called Just Do It. 3, 2, 1, go.
Ben, I've decided to do the impossible. I'm going to go where no one has ever gone before.
I'll actually read your comics and you know what that means.
That means you have from today until however long it takes for the average person to read your silly pictograms
to actually start making comics again.
Like you could take one or two hours a week of the time you've sat aside to watching Picnic Adventure
and listen for the sound bites of Disney to actually make, I don't know, one page of Beastly Pages.
Like one page of Beastly Pages a week. That should be doable, right? Please, man.
Actually drawing Beastly Pages usually doesn't take that long.
I need to like just plan out what I want to happen in the next chapter
because you know what we're going to do on the perfect comic party? It's going to be like a chapter of it.
It's not going to be like one page at a time like it was on Twitter.
So I just need to plan out what I want to happen in this chapter.
Most of the pages of drawing Beastly Pages take no time at all.
I want to take a little more time in it because like I said some of the panels, especially in the early ones,
are sloppy to the point that I don't think it's cute, I don't think it's stylistic,
I just think it's lazy and looks bad and makes it hard to read and hurts the comic.
I take no pleasure in reporting that, obviously.
But looking back over it was definitely not all the time, but enough of the time that I started to cringe at it.
But still, it's pretty fast to draw.
I'm going to do minimal gif animating because it's not compatible with PDF download.
I mean, I'll do it if I think a scene really needs it and then it'll just be like,
look at the animated version on my website or whatever.
But I'm not going to do it unless I really think it's important.
A static panel will suffice most of the time.
Anyway, thanks for reading my comics.
I'm sorry to say it's not going to take you very long.
You can probably read all of the vapors and all that you can easily read them in a couple hours, probably.
Slime and punishment might take a little bit longer.
No, I think it would probably still just take a couple hours, if that.
You could read all my stuff in one day.
Sad but true.
Alright, and the next one is called Addendum 321 Go.
Should I read? It's also ugly.
Is that like your old work you're too embarrassed about to actually recommend to people?
Because if that is the case, I'll definitely read it.
Yeah, I think some of it's kind of embarrassing.
I don't really think that it's good.
I don't think it's... I think there's a couple of them.
I know there's a couple of them that I think some people could find funny and like, that's fine.
I don't really like them, so they're not like prominently on my website.
They're sort of in their own section, and you can look at them if you want.
So, sort of, kind of...
Check them out if you feel like it, I guess.
Next one is called Am I Crazy from Prince Isolation at Twitter 321 Go.
I...
Oh my god.
The picture that Cheesy pulled up of the gollywag, like, racist doll in the last episode,
I looked at it, and I was like, oh, you can just remove the racist features from this, right?
Maybe, like, you know, you just change it.
And I made a connection in my brain, and it looks exactly like the poppy playtime dolls that you see everywhere now.
Like, it doesn't really look like it, because it's not black, and it's not racist,
but there's a vibe, and the vibe is, like, eerily similar.
Even the way that it's, like, laying there in the picture...
It's got that same mouth, I guess.
...is exactly like the way that those playtime dolls feel.
What the f... What the fuck? Am I... Am I crazy? Am I...
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, I see.
...skish-skish-skish, right here.
Tell me. Bye-bye.
Um, I'm gonna say probably...
No, you're not crazy. No, it's definitely got the mouth.
That is... yeah, it's friendly-looking, and it's just kind of offensive in a racialized context.
But, you know, removed from that context in this... in the context of poppy.
You know, it's just fine, I think.
So, I think I agree with you.
Duh... Where did... Where did... Where did they get it?
I wonder if that... Did they get it from there? I don't know, but I think it's fine.
It works for what they were going for.
Also, I don't know what poppy's playtime is.
I can see from a quick Google search that it's some kind of a cute thing that's actually scary.
Haha, cool.
Uh, next one is called, um... Oh, it's another image.
Yes, uh, let us behold.
Hmm.
Okay, what do we got here?
I'm gonna try and read this from the first.
Bigger, goth, Ben, uh, whatever.
Nose piercing.
How did I become so ugly, exact the same for 20 years?
What are tend to marketable Ben plushie?
So, the trick to those guys is... What is... In the bottom left, um...
I'm wearing, like, a safari hat, and there's, like, some kind of cat serpent biting my face?
Oh, wait, this is a reference to something.
This is a reference to something, and I'm an idiot for not getting it.
Okay, in the middle is the dragon look-gib.
They love us, and we're being hugged by a dragon?
Or grabbed by a dragon?
I feel like these are references I should get.
Okay, bottom, throwing the birthday boy hat on the floor.
When you're 30, when you're 34, you don't like having birthdays.
It's grim.
Uh, next one in the middle... Middle right, artist.
Kill all... This one's just funny.
This one rules, and I'm proud to be a self-hating artist, yeah.
I told our... Ooh, bump the mic.
I told my mom during the visit.
This is before my sister got there, but my mom was, like...
I think she was asking about, like...
I don't know, she was talking about my sister and about tattoo art and stuff.
I think she asked me about, like, how my art was going, and I said, like...
I said, like...
Yeah, art is worthless. Art is just a waste of time.
Art is just a trick people do to get attention.
Uh, it's just marketing. It's not valuable to society.
Uh, and I stand by all that, of course.
And, um...
She... And my mom was like...
She gave a really stupid answer. She gave a really stupid, annoying answer.
Her answer was, like, oh, you wouldn't think that if you saw what your sister is making,
and, like, way to fucking miss the point.
Like, yes, I know it can make money.
I know that art can make money. That's not what I'm saying.
I'm saying it's worthless. Do you understand?
Do you fucking get it?
Mom!
Ugh, don't understand me!
Alright. Next...
Anyway, kill all artists, definitely.
Next one...
Okay, up in the top right, there's, like, a signature killer.
That is exactly me when I see a meme.
I point at it and go cross-eyed.
Well, such is the way of things.
Uh, next voicemail is, uh, we got another image.
Disgusting.
Let's, let's look. Let's peep in.
Oh, look at me. I'm a little Rick and Morty.
Haha, you really, you really are.
Uh, where...
Where are we?
There's a, like, a playground
in an apartment complex.
And the color-crushing
makes me think this is in Lakkan,
but it's not green. The buildings are blue,
so it doesn't seem, it doesn't seem very in Lakkan.
And there's a giant praying mantis.
It's a little hard to see against the building.
Uh, but he looks angry.
And I...
I don't really know what's...
going on here.
I don't know why we're on this playground,
but...
Cool bug
and, uh, cool spot.
Let's go.
Let's freakin' go!
Let's go! Let's freakin' go!
Hell yeah.
Alright, sick.
Uh, next one is, um...
another image.
I think it's from Vinny.
It's titled VVV.
Japanese guy, maybe don't be stereotypical
at it.com.
Alright.
Let's freakin'... let's freakin' go!
Oh, okay.
Oh, hell yeah. Alright, alright, alright.
So, another chapter of the Vinny saga.
We're walking into
or... orin...
orintal food.
That says backwards.
Oki na tabemono
Oki na...
Hitodoriji
I'm gonna... I'm gonna Google translate it.
I'm sorry, I have to.
Uh, Google translate says that it means
big food, big human dancing character.
Um, okay.
Mmm, okay.
Uh, alright, let's, uh...
Let's freakin' read it. Let's go.
Um...
Hello.
I'll try to do the samurai voice. Hello.
Welcome. I serve.
What's your order, please?
Uh, Simsie sounds like...
Oy, uu, fish, uu, sushi, and sake.
Miso oden.
Uh, teriyaki soda.
Okay.
So when I was being shipped here to America,
I couldn't help but think about what life would be like
for a turtle, being cramped in that bag and all.
Then living in my house as a turtle,
I'd have to be a person to walk up the stairs, though.
Then it hit me, I'd have to be a TMNT.
Haha, yeah.
Heh, funny.
Did I ever tell you I wanted to be a ninja
when I was a teenager?
There was the scam website that had me convinced
it would be simple to sign up and do it.
Lol, heh heh, really?
I was inspired by Naruto or something at the time.
You know, when a phase hits you, you're all about it.
I had a phase of trying to be like Gohan from Dragon Ball Z.
Whoa, whoa, oh yeah?
Heh heh, yeah.
When it first came out, I was really into it.
Hello, Al Cool.
Have you kept up with Dragon Ball Super?
No, I haven't, what should I do?
I just got an update from my friends about it.
Oh yeah, it's not as good of fun as the old stuff,
but you know, it's something.
Gohan got a cool sword at some point.
I like that part.
Yes, he did.
The Z Sword.
It has the old Kai in it with the Potara Iris.
You know your stuff.
You're good with a blade, I see.
Thank you.
I have actually trained with a blade for most of my life.
Heh, you mentioned a ninja website.
You wouldn't remember the name of it, would you?
No, it's been so long.
I bet you would have made a great ninja,
who'd have even moved up to Samurai Reverie even.
You think?
You've got a really good physique, a perfect body, I'd say.
Oh, thank you.
Three.
The form and techniques of the Kawasaki clan would have been a true sight to behold.
Cut seeing you perform was Emma.
You're so nice.
You think I look good?
You're so very...
This guy is a real baka hentai, in my opinion.
Chitter-chitter-chitter chatter.
Hey, Ben.
The Kawasaki clan was that group it wanted to kill you, wouldn't it?
Would it more than just the baby, or was there another guy?
Another guy, for sure.
So this guy is, uh...
I don't know.
My name is Yuma Kawasaki.
May I know your name?
Call me Gibb and take.
Beautiful.
And your friends?
This is Ben Saint and Simsie.
Ben...Saint?
Yes, BenSaintofPatrion.com slash BenSaint.
BenSaint your treachery shall be avenged here by my Kawasaki blade!
Swing!
Shwoof.
You've made a grave mistake to choose this fight.
I will not die here!
I really like the, uh, the toxic, uh, nuclear vaperig.
Alright, this guy, let's see what the, what does Vinny say.
This guy's immediately enamored by Gibb and take.
Woo-wee!
How about that? Simsie has a silly neck, like Cheesy said.
Gotta make him sillier.
Maybe don't read the guy's voice in a stereotypic voice,
but you know he has at least half of Japanese with his Kawasaki decency.
Okay, I see.
You said this in the message.
You said don't read it with a stereotypical samurai,
and I didn't listen, and you know what?
That's on me.
That's my bad.
I am recent.
I'm sorry.
Uh, okay.
But, it was more, it was more fun to read in the samurai voice.
Come on.
It was.
Um, alright.
Uh, I like this one.
Uh, this one looks good.
I like this last panel is really good.
Uh, I like the clouds, I like the rig.
Um, these are fun.
Uh, I like the scene of us all sitting at the,
at the table at the bar.
Uh, we look good.
We look good!
Alright, sick.
Thank you again, Vinny, for another,
for another of these.
Uh, looking forward to more.
Next one is Vincent Vainy Vici,
and I appreciate Ben St. 4.
Three, two, one, go.
Well, I appreciate about Ben St.
He's smart.
And when I hear him make a reference to a funny thing
that I think is also funny,
I say, Tee-hee-ha-ha, me too.
Yo, let's fucking go.
Tee-hee-ha-ha, me too, me too.
Ben St. is very smart, very cool as well.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Uh, next one is, uh, VVV appreciates Gibbentake.
Uh, regularly sharing funnies with Gibb,
is my Kokoro wish at 4reel.com.
Uh, three, two, one, go.
Well, I appreciate Gibbentake 4.
It's basically, like, everything she's done
to, like, be who she is.
That's one of the things I've struggled with myself,
and just seeing her bloom into who she is
and who she's happy with.
What does that mean?
Like, that's inspired me.
Wow.
Okay, you're welcome.
Welcome for me being who I am.
It's a tough job, but somebody's got to do it.
That's very, uh, that's very unspecific.
I don't, I don't exactly know what you mean.
What?
Yeah, I'm, I'm also being who I am.
I'm also who I am.
Is that not good enough for you?
What?
Alright, never mind.
Thanks, Vinny.
Uh, next one is, uh, what, like, what is,
I'm sorry, what does that mean?
What aspect of Gib being who she is?
It's just, I mean, I appreciate,
I appreciate you being who you are.
I appreciate most people being who they are, you know?
That's, it's a cool thing to do.
Uh, next one is called Slime Times Weekend Update
from printisolationattwitter.com.
Let's give it a listen.
Three, two, one, go.
Good afternoon, my Rudy Toody shooties.
We're back with Slime Times Weekend Update.
This week, we'd like to update you
on the Nlaka Karmayor elections.
The first round of voting has concluded,
and each faction has now their candidate.
For the killers, there is Frag,
impersonating the God Emperor of the 41st Millennium himself.
For the Rowdies, it was a close finish,
but in the end, the Court of Appeals decided
that Rowdy candidate Matt was in his legal right
to dredge up every old head from their shallow graves
to vote in his favor.
And so Matt is the Rowdy candidate.
For the Juvies, Thinbug proved to possess
an unbeatable perspective on the future,
casting marine exploration and new items
on the city's horizon.
Finally, for the State Eds, it appears that
Captain Metalhead has the undisputed champion position,
riding on a platform of killing everyone in the city
and starting the community's second negapause.
As the elections move ahead,
it will be interesting to see whose policies
prove the most attractive
and who will decide the fate of our great city.
That's it for this week, and remember,
the slime time is the best time.
I just got to say, I know that I endorsed him,
but the Rowdy elections are completely corrupt.
Matt is clearly abusing his position
of authority as the stream host
and as a rowdy old head to inflate his numbers.
I mean, I don't know, it's debatable
whether you think that's legitimate or not.
It's just highly corrupt.
Thinbug and Captain Metalhead both have real platforms.
Captain Metalhead is just negapause 2,
which is very funny, and it's getting votes.
I see the appeal.
You're going to do a lord of ghosts 2
and bring about the end times again.
Thinbug is like the growth candidate.
Thinbug is like, we'll do marine exploration,
we'll add game features.
There were some other stuff that I can't recall at the top of my head,
but they had actual positions.
I thought their campaign was great.
Captain Metalhead is great too, for obvious reasons.
Keeping the ghostly spirit alive.
Spirit, ha ha, get it?
When lord of ghosts summon the nega slime
to stop all the fighting, it didn't really work out,
because the ghosts just kept fighting each other,
but who knows, maybe negapause 2 will work out differently.
You never know, you got to keep hope alive.
You just got to keep on trucking.
Alright, next is Slime Times Weekend Update,
number 11, bonus, 3, 2, 1, go.
Breaking news, we neglected to mention
that Vriska won candidate position for the Vriska party.
Very important, very important to know this.
I am too busy counting my bribe money
to check what her platform is,
but I'm sure it will be based as fuck.
We can certainly be excited for more developments in the future.
And remember, the slime time is the bribe time, the best time.
Goodbye.
Yes, vote Vriska.
Yeah, sure, why not?
Why not vote for Vriska?
I hope Vriska is running on the platform
of having big mommy milkers.
It's a pretty, it's a pretty indefensible.
Unassailable, it's a pretty unassailable platform.
Thank you, Prince, for the updates.
Next one is Ben and Gibb Appreciation Hour
from PrinceIsolation at twitter.com.
Let's go, 3, 2, 1, go.
Welcome back to the Ben and Gibb Appreciation Hour.
Today, I'm coming at you with a single Ben Sainte quote,
discussing the diversity question on Mega Man Battle Network.
And I quote,
Well, you know, there's some representation.
There's your guts man using friend.
He's kind of not colored.
Ben Sainte, 2023.
Goodbye, I'll see you next time.
I was thinking of that, I was thinking of the bit,
the line in Game of Thrones, or A Song of Ice and Fire,
when in the, oh shit, what's the southern country called?
Dorn.
In Dorn, you see, the point is he describes a girl as nut brown,
a nut brown girl.
That's what I was thinking of when I said he was nut colored.
You know, someone asked there were minorities in Battle Network,
and the answer largely being thus far, thus far not yet.
Pretty sure everyone's just Japanese.
No.
I mean, I think land, land must be at least a quarter white,
but I mean, doesn't really matter, right?
But he must be at least a quarter white,
I mean, I guess they never really talk about it,
but I'm convinced that Dr. Light, his grandfather, is a western American.
So I think that, yeah, he must have moved to Japan,
and maybe he had a, maybe his wife was a white also,
and just, I mean, no, he must have changed his name.
So he must have moved to Japan, married Japanese,
and then I would assume that his half Japanese son
probably got a Japanese wife, so that would make land.
That's just what I would think.
So, but that's like whatever.
Ooh, your quarter white.
Ooh, that's diversity for you.
Why am I talking about this?
Hey, Twitch.tv slash St. Comics,
I am sticking pretty well to a schedule
of Monday and Friday evening streams, streaming Battle Network.
I just finished, I don't even think I mentioned,
I finished Battle Network 1.
I finished the game.
The ending was really good.
It's really funny.
The game's plot is like really, I mean, there is plot,
there is dialogue and stuff,
but like 90% of like the important shit in that game.
Lore, I mean, there's like, you know,
there's initial world building and setup,
which kind of does occur over the whole game.
You understand like the sort of world they live in, whatever.
But then in terms of like what's going on with you
and with Mega Man and with your dad,
that's like all in like the last like 10 minutes of the game.
It's just, it's all comes out and it's like, oh my fucking god.
So we got through that part and it was, it's amazing.
Honestly, the revelations at the end of Battle Network 1
are fucking astounding.
So yeah, pretty good.
Follow me on Twitch.
Next one is, fuck it, going phone speaker mode.
And we got another vocabruelink.
This is our last voicemail, so let's give it a listen.
Three, two, one, go.
Oblivionfall was like, I don't know about one piece
and I don't know if you're going to read it.
I prefer Conan.
Gib instantaneously shows me Sunder Sonja
and he's like, oh my god, oh my fucking god.
I'm reading it right now.
I love Sunder Sonja.
Yeah, Sunder Sonja is cool.
Sunder Sonja is cool.
I mean, she's kind of silly looking, but that's okay.
We can get a little silly with it, as Cheesy says.
Make them sillier.
That's true.
That is true.
I don't know if it pushed Oblivionfall over the edge to read one piece.
I don't remember, but I hope it did.
Sorry for not covering the new chapter this week.
Well, next week we'll do a double chapter review of 1076
and I guess 1077 will be up by then.
That's the end of the episode.
I think that's...
Unless we got any last minute voicemails, did we?
Let me see.
Nope.
Okay.
All right, that's the end.
Gib, do you have any last minute words to impart upon our listeners?
Go to patreon.com slash the procrastinators to get access to all our bonus content
and support the show as well as our upcoming zine, the perfect comic party.
Patrons will get their names in a shout out page
and we've also got a new hour long bonus behind the scenes episode out now
of the conversation with Oblivion and Cheesy from last week that had to be cut.
The value you get from becoming a patron is so insane.
It's a logical contradiction.
My sister servos are struggling to calculate the AG at these prices
Couldn't have said it better myself, Gib.
All right, thanks for listening and we'll see you next week.
You