I'd like to direct this question to Messrs. Lennon and McCartney in a recent article, Time Magazine put down pop music, and they referred to Day Tripper as being about a prostitute, and Norwegian Wood about as being about a lesbian.
No, I just wanted to know what your intent was when you wrote it, and what your feeling is about the Time Magazine criticism of the music that is being written today.
We were just trying to write songs about prostitutes and lesbians, that's it.
And I want you, my friend listening to this podcast, to go to stcomics.com and read my stupid new chapter.
It's out now.
Oh is it up already? You put it there?
It is there right now.
Awesome.
Stcomics.com, it'll bring you right to the beginning of chapter two.
Read it, read it, read it, read it, read it, give me money on Patreon.
Did you put a chapter select?
Patreon, Patreon.
Alright, enough me memes.
Yes, I put a chapter select.
Cool.
We also have with us the best guy ever, Nate Bestman.
Hello, I'm the best guy ever, go to YouTube, watch best guy ever.
I've got a new video, it's finally almost done.
It'll be here before you know it.
Okay, let's move on.
No it won't.
Next up we have the DeVoo.
Hi, I have produced the visuals for the Astroscore Sucks series.
That is completely random.
I have no idea what context you have, listener.
You can give them context.
Go watch the DeVoo's channel, he makes good videos.
And he's making a new video soon.
Right now, yeah.
Probably by the time this podcast comes out.
And last but not least, we have the Hippocrite.
The Hippopotamus, the Crippolophonophagus, the Subrubium.
There we go, I did it.
I did it again, but it was worse.
Fuck you, Ben.
Yeah, that one was great.
Alright, today we only lost six minutes of recording.
We didn't even get a point yet.
Let's just get to it.
We are here today to talk about a topic I came up with and nobody else understands.
So I have to explain it.
It's authorial intent.
And basically, what it means, what it does, how we should interpret it.
Now to explain it, authorial intent is...
Arthorial intent?
What's that mean, Digi?
Authorial intent.
Basically means artist intent.
And it's sort of like how I would explain it is, if I was writing a book and I thought
that I was writing it to have a very specific meaning, then that meaning is my authorial intent.
You know, whatever I intended for you to get out of the book, that's authorial intent.
Now, if you read it and you get something else out of it, then that is, you know, the not-authorial intent.
Now in recent years, well not in recent years, this is a very old idea, probably 60, 70 years old.
But recently in the internet, in internet criticism and, you know, I guess I'd say not unprofessional,
but like, you know, normal people writing reviews and shit.
Amateurs.
Amateur, that's the word I was looking for.
Though it's not all technically amateur.
But anyway, on the internet, the idea of death of the author has really picked up over the last few years.
It's become a very popular method of critique, right?
The idea of the death of the author, which I believe was proposed by Descartes, someone like that?
Jacques Derrida.
I don't know if that's how you pronounce his name.
Derrida, the guy who's impossible to read because none of his shit makes any sense.
But he proposed the idea of the death of the author and the idea was that authorial intent doesn't necessarily matter.
Like, whatever you interpret out of the work is its own work in your head, in a way.
Like, if I read a book and I construct a meaning of it in my mind,
then that meaning is not necessarily less valid to talk about and criticize than the actual author's intent.
Now, I like death of the author conceptually because I think it can lead to great stuff,
you know, writing about your own experience with the work can be cool.
But I also think we have a danger of people not giving a fuck about authorial intent anymore
and thinking that authors are fucking idiots.
I think that's the world we live in now.
It is.
I guess.
I don't know.
It always seems like that's part of the picture.
You know, if you're looking to get into something, you should at least, you know, find out what they were going for
and then you can make your conclusions from there.
And if you don't know, then I guess you don't know.
I kind of like the idea of being able to just make your own conclusions regardless.
Like, if you just don't care what the author thinks, I think there's space for that to exist.
Like, if you get something out of a work, it doesn't really matter if the author meant for it to be there.
You know, for you, it was there.
Yeah, I totally agree.
But here's where this podcast is coming from, alright?
Specifically, this is to address a comment that I get a lot on my videos and I'm sure you guys have all gotten to,
which is that you are thinking more deeply about the show than the guy who made it.
Yeah.
Yeah, I've heard people say things like that.
I get this all the time.
I'll get, like, like on my Ava videos or something, you know, I'll point out, like, the way that a shot is constructed
and they'll be like, there's no way they put that much thought into it, you know.
Well, I, um, I agree that that kind of flippancy about it is wrong-headed.
But I don't think that, like, I think in a way, in a sort of roundabout way, I agree.
Because when you take a work and you analyze, like, oh, this shot was composed this way to emphasize such and such,
and you know, the color composition here represents this.
It isn't like, it isn't like that all these detailed notes and conclusions you draw,
like they were all mapped out ahead of time and deliberately put there by the author.
But, but that doesn't mean, that also doesn't mean that those things weren't the authors.
That is debatable.
In the case of Ava.
Okay, you know, some authors do, like, do do that.
But, but sometimes a way a shot is framed, an artist can just kind of subconsciously arrange things in a way that feels right to them,
but that accomplishes a number of goals.
I think that a lot, you know, just kind of come out of it.
In a lot of cases, including Digi Bro's analysis of the Ava shot composition,
the collective thought that was put into that shot by all the people involved in production and writing obviously outstrips any individual analyst.
However, obviously an analyst or reviewer or critic or whatever has the advantage of being able to look at the completed work after it's already been all put together.
That's, if people who aren't creative probably can't understand that when you start creating something,
you have no idea what it's going to be by the time you're done with it.
So you can't necessarily think about things retroactively.
And so as a result, there is a huge advantage to a reviewer who can already look at everything and how it all plays together already.
You know.
Yeah, I guess.
I still think, I think there's a lot of people.
I think there's a lot of like authors or creatives who like really do just think about everything, you know.
There are.
And I mean, like...
They may not necessarily be able to like tell you because the way they communicate is through their art anyway.
So they wouldn't be able to tell you why they did what they did,
but they'd be able to put it in because they knew it was the right thing to do.
Yeah, like if a shot emphasizes a character's, I don't know, despair or something,
they weren't necessarily thinking like,
now to emphasize the character's despair, you know, I will crop his eyes here and I will color it like this.
They just like drew the shot that looked right to them and it emphasized the despair.
And you can retroactively point out the ways in which it emphasizes that despair.
Right.
Yeah.
I think like, I mean, I could definitely see, especially on the level of like a comic artist where it's more sort of intuitive like that.
Like one guy, you know, making a thing, but like when it comes to like a show or a production or a film,
and there's like multiple people approaching the angle of every shot, you know,
every single scene is like sort of not necessarily designed by committee,
but there's people have to talk about it to each other, you know,
like my brother, Victor, who's a, you know, an aspiring film director.
I guess I should just say he is a film director.
He just hasn't made any like, you know, professional films.
He's like, you know, a Hollywood.
Yeah, he's still trying to get into grad school, but um, that shit.
He's a, you know, he's told me before, like when he was working with this guy,
who's like an assistant director or like a, like his lead camera guy for a couple of shorts they were doing,
like this guy had so little ability to understand the nuance and Victor's writing,
like he had written the script and showed it to this guy and the guy just didn't get any of it.
Like all of it was over his head.
Victor had to explain to him like exactly why every shot would be filmed the way it was,
why every line was written the way it was, what it all meant,
what each thing was trying to express,
just so this guy would be on the same page as him when filming his movie, you know, or acting in it.
In this particular case, he was acting in the, in the script, uh, Ye Olde Kitten's Paw.
If any of you have seen that one, it was on, it's on the Modal Soul Productions channel,
and the guy who was the lead actor in that, like...
That's the guy with the, at the bar, and then he goes to the beach.
Yeah, I have seen that, and I thought it was a cool script that was completely hamstrung by the acting.
It was, and that guy, the guy who was the lead actor, is the one I'm talking about.
He had no comprehension of what the script meant.
Like Victor had to carefully explain to him why the character would say these things,
what they were thinking, what the message is, like why this scene, why is it presented this way, you know.
So in other words, Victor had thought about all that, and I don't know that he necessarily had, like,
like you said, it became more analytical and retrospect, where, like, he wrote it emotionally,
like, what made sense to him, but then when he had to, like, teach the actor what it meant,
he had to then analyze it and explain it to him, you know.
But I don't think that, that means he didn't put thought into it.
He, you know, he just understood those things intrinsically and was able to write already knowing what would be,
what would communicate that, you know.
You know what, that reminds me of something I was doing, in fact, just, in fact, right now, actually,
and yesterday, where I've written something into a script and now I'm editing it in,
and I find that upon reviewing the script that I have read,
there's actually a few more questions that I have to answer in order to make the shot convey,
you know, the sort of baseline idea that I was trying to get to.
And I have to do this research and kind of figure out my own point and then put it in there.
And my whole point is here, like, there's a lot of thought that's going into all of this shit, you know.
Yeah, you know, one of your old videos, did you, bro, you talk about, I don't know why I keep saying all those syllables each time.
Yeah, I know.
I don't know, it's kind of warm today.
I'm getting kind of...
It's hot in the mother.
When your oldest videos, you talk about authorial intent and you say, you know,
a lot of people, if they watch something and it sucks, they usually will accuse it of having been made thoughtlessly.
Like, the people who did it just weren't putting that much thought into it,
but what's more likely to be accurate is that a whole bunch of stupid thoughts were put into it.
For an easy example of this, you can watch Bird Demek or Cool Cat Saves the Kids,
people who clearly thought about everything that went into those films.
Man, I'm sick of the room not getting mentioned in these things. The room's the best.
Everyone needs to give it respect.
I'm sick of the room being mentioned. That one's kind of an older, infamously bad movie.
We're talking about the modern age.
Bird Demek's pretty old.
Well, yeah, in all the cases, like, yeah, those are just filmmakers who are incompetent
and they don't know how to...
It's not that they didn't think about what they were doing.
Yeah, like you said, stupid thoughts.
They don't know the technique, they don't know the craft,
they don't know anything about what will resonate with other people.
So, the movie probably made sense to them, but they just failed at communicating it to others.
But that doesn't mean that they didn't try, that it didn't add up in their own heads.
Yeah, for example, the guy who made Cool Cat actually changed the movie some
because of the critical response I think most of the time.
Right, that pretty much proves it.
That it actually resonated with him on a couple of points.
He was like, oh, that's a good point, yeah.
I just think it's like ridiculous to me to think that anyone other than the author
would be thinking harder about something than the fucking author.
Well, if something is like...
I mean, if something was like a completely corporate, cynical, you know...
That means even more thought's been put into it.
Not creative thought.
Yeah, I don't think people are judging it on the same basis as like,
okay, we got like in Jack and Jill, a lot of thought was put into that product placement.
That shit was like almost on another level.
No, that's what I mean.
Like Jack and Jill, everything that's in the movie, they knew what they were doing.
They just didn't do good work.
They deliberately did not do good work.
They decided to make something lazy, you know.
But that doesn't mean that they understand it less than you do by watching it.
Like, if you watch that movie and you analyze all the product placement
and you say this movie was clearly made with this intention,
it probably was made with that intention, you know.
Okay, well here's a question, because we are...
I believe we're tending to count the collective thought of the creative and production teams behind something.
So should we also square that against the collective thought of the fan base?
Because I was scrambling to come up with an example of something that the fans have thought about more than the creators.
Sonic Adventure 2.
Maybe?
Sure.
Sonic in general, I guess?
Yeah, that one especially.
That particular one especially.
I feel like maybe the amount of additional narrative that people have added themselves into.
Right.
But it's one thing to interpret things from the story.
It's another to write fan fiction about it.
And I just don't know what you're referring to.
I think there's a level where it becomes just death of the author thinking, right?
Like, maybe, I don't know how much the fans understand that they're doing it.
But when you get to that point where it's obviously not what the author intended,
then that's where you're invoking death of the author and making your own story, you know?
Yeah.
And of course, part of this debate, I guess what I'm trying to do here is not so much to say that there's a definite line between the two,
and some people are right and some people are wrong.
I just want to sort of push it back.
I feel like people have reached a point of assuming,
because of death of the author and because of analysis and stuff,
that people are starting to think that authors don't think as much as they do about shit.
Where I think that the majority of stuff that people get out of work is almost always intentional,
and then there's that smaller amount of stuff we put into it,
the headcanons and the reading too deep shit.
Right.
And then there's the thing that the Beginner's Guide game it commentates on is,
don't try to comment on the author because you're going to be wrong.
Right.
And then Aaron's Signal made that video about it,
made that video explaining it,
and it was a game about not explaining things,
and he has this faux existential crisis at the end that I thought was amusing.
I don't think that was a faux existential crisis.
I think that was a real existential crisis.
It was scripted, but he tried to make it seem like it wasn't.
And to me, it was amusing and made me feel very smugly superior,
because personally, I've never felt like this was a...
That's never something that I've had to reconcile.
It's never something that I felt was a problem.
For me, I always...
For me, whenever I...
If I think something about the intention of an author,
it's only because I'm very, very confident in it based on everything I know,
and I don't think that I'm going to be wrong,
and I don't say things that are like stretches.
So for me, it's not an issue.
Pretty much everybody, if you talk about Ava and Galeon,
everyone always brings up how Hideo Kiana was depressed,
and he was interested in psychology and all that,
but no one got that because they just watched Ava and assumed that about him.
It's like, that's what he said.
He said, I was depressed.
I made this show about being depressed, you know?
And so it's like, okay, we got that.
And it's cool, because that kind of authorial intent can inform your enjoyment of a show,
where there's a lot of people who like Ava even more because they know that.
They're like, now that I understand what he was trying to communicate,
I can resonate with it that much more.
So when it comes to reviewers and analysts and the fans of said reviewers and analysts,
I guess they have the question of,
well, how much are you supposed to talk about the author,
and how much are you supposed to talk about your own interpretation?
Well, I'll tell you what.
My standard is I talk about whichever one is the most interesting.
There are some videos I've done where...
Sometimes I'll play a game or watch a thing,
and my opinion of it is really boring.
Even if I liked it or I hated it, I just think my opinion is boring.
And if I made a video out of it, I would barely talk about my opinion.
And then sometimes I think that where it came from was not that interesting to me,
or vice versa, or both.
And so, like for example, there was an indie game that came out in late 2015
that was very popular that I'm not going to name because we bring it up in every episode of the show.
Thank you. Thank you, Dubu. I really appreciate that.
And that game comes from such a similar...
I feel like it comes from a pretty similar place as me,
because there's a lot of things in it that remind me of a couple of games that I made
that aren't very good at all, but there are certain elements of that particular game
that are so similar in such a specific way to games that I made,
and I only made a few that made me think,
wow, this is a work where my opinion and the opinion of the author are like equally interesting.
You know, I have made a couple of videos where I deliberately went like way out of the realm
of what the show seemed to be intended to talk about,
but I always sort of... I don't know. I don't know how well I signposted it.
I think I did because I made them kind of funny,
but I have the video No Kome and Nihilism,
which is where I way over read into a harem show
in a way that is obviously not intentional, but it was funny.
Oh, right. I remember that one. That came through.
I couldn't really tell that at first because I didn't know anything about the show.
I could tell based on the title and the appearance of the show that that was the case.
And then with the Food, Sex, and Life in Kofuku Graffiti episode,
that one as well, where the show is just about cute girls eating food,
and I tried to take it to this philosophical place of like,
eating food is sexy because it reminds us of life and childbirth or something.
It was clearly meant to be like an almost irreverent analysis.
For me, if there's some trashy or fun-loving, just regular run-of-the-mill comedy action thing,
that isn't deep, but it inspires deep thoughts in me,
the feeling of watching that is exactly, I mean, like, not that different from
if it really was some big high-brow artsy thing.
If it makes me think really advanced things, then it feels the same way to me,
whether or not it tries to be.
It's just a matter of like...
I just forget. If something makes me think philosophically,
I just consider it to be a philosophical deep show.
Yeah, like, I mean, and I'm not saying it's not because of that,
but like, it's definitely a difference where like, with those shows,
I in no way think the author intended the things that I was saying about the shows,
but like, you know, there's so many other shows that I talk about where I totally do,
and like, and those two videos were so out there and far-fetched that I don't think anyone would,
like, assume that I thought that the author meant that.
I mean, someone told me you're reading too deep into this.
I'd be like, yeah, that's the joke.
Your authorial intent was that the other person's authorial intent was not being addressed correctly.
Your authorial intent was their authorial intent.
I like stuff.
It's my favorite.
I stepped on a frog. I hope it wasn't an ancestor.
Okay, some people don't seem to understand.
Donatello should be the PCP mascot. No, go on, sorry.
Some people don't seem to understand that you can talk about a work and analyze a work
and bring up the themes of a work without necessarily attributing those things to authorial intent.
Sometimes anything you say about a show or a thing, people will hear as you're saying that, you know,
this is what the author intended. It isn't.
What is even the point of making that distinction?
I don't get, like, if you point out what the author...
Well, if you say something's a theme of a show, someone might counter with, oh, that's dumb.
Obviously the author didn't mean for that to be there, which is not fair.
Well, the authors don't always, you know, mean for things to happen, so who cares about the author?
But at the same time, like, if you're talking about just the show or just the author...
If I got X out of a show and someone says, but the author didn't intend that,
I mean, that's an invalid point.
You know, I think a lot of viewers or listeners of this podcast may be wondering,
like, where are we coming from on this? Why is this a topic of concern for us?
Because did you want it to.
I want to say what I think the concern is, is that we put a lot of effort into stating our opinions
or our thoughts or our interpretations into an entertaining product,
and we are, I think we're pretty well trained, we've pretty well conditioned ourselves
to not say our opinion of something unless it's going to be interesting or funny,
whereas most commenters just want to say their opinions and don't want to put in the effort,
and so they'll just either hide behind authorial intent or hide behind the death of the author
as a cheap, quick tool to just categorically back up whatever they want to say
and make something funny or interesting about it.
Yeah, and to use either one of those as a categorical defense is wrong,
because both of those are just, like, you know, accepting authorial intent as valid
and totally throwing it out as a valid interpretation of the work
are just two different ways of looking at a thing.
You can't say, oh, this wasn't intended by the author, therefore it's worthless.
You also can't say, oh, you know, it doesn't matter what the author intended
because it's not interested in it.
There's just two fucking opinions.
On a similar note, DeVoo, did you see that legendary thread that I got into on the Reddit
arguing about the game that shall not be named on your video about it?
Oh yeah, well, yeah, talk about that.
That guy had such specific ideas about what the game should have been
and he had very specific ideas about how you should have presented your ideas.
And it finally got to the point.
He finally made a response that I just, I read it and I understood what he was saying,
but every single thing that he said was just so wrong that I had no retort for any of it.
I finally was just like, I think everything you just said is wrong,
and that's all I have to say.
And he was like, okay, good day, sir.
You hit argument bedrock, that's a good shit.
Yeah, we hit argument bedrock at that point.
That's kind of pulling us back to our reviewer rules episode where we talk about people
who have their rules about what you need to talk about.
In regards to that discussion.
This guy was very specifically, you should have said this,
you needed to say that and because you didn't, your video was bad.
On a small level, I always hate when I get a comment like, I don't know,
when you talk about a game, if you were to make a video about, like, a...
And then you're like, wait, you didn't say get dope?
What, don't dude?
No.
Why are you not supposed to talk about that?
We've all been trying to say the game that is not named.
I had no idea.
Wow.
Just censor that, just censor that.
Whoever's adding the censor that.
Yeah, put a censor break.
Davoo might actually censor that.
I think he might, because I think he's...
I'd like to talk about, like, the idea that if an author, like, say,
Hitataki Miyazaki, or whatever his name is, the Dark Souls guy,
the Dark Souls Demon Souls guy.
Hero Hito Nagasaki.
He did good games, all of them.
And, like, he's got, like, a track record of, like, him being a director
and good games coming from it.
And it's...
If you could...
I mean, it feels like it's easier to say, yeah, that's what he intended
when you're, like, analyzing his next game.
Because...
Well, that's the thing.
Like, when I start doing, like, my stuff where I really lean hard on, like,
this is what they intended for this shot to be,
it's usually because I'm, like, pretty confident that that creator knows their shit.
You know?
Like, someone like Miyazaki, you don't just make three games that are all perfect on accident.
Like, he clearly knows what the fuck he's doing.
He clearly, every element of the game, it's a...
As Mr. Beetson called it, the Gesamtkunswerk,
where everything about it is perfect and it all plays into each other perfectly.
The rest of you remembered that word.
I think it's a case...
I think it's a case of he just had very specific ideas about what the game should be.
Yeah.
And they ended up being good ideas that people really resonated with people.
And then he, you know, doggedly stuck to them
and that philosophy through all of his games, which is what made them good.
I just...
I certainly think that, like, like, yeah, maybe he didn't, like, know
that this was gonna be something everyone would think was the best idea ever.
But he definitely knew what he was doing.
You know, it's fair to say that if something goes well,
it's probably because he decided that that was, like, that was his intent for it to happen.
I mean, there's definitely plenty of stuff where the author completely did everything intentionally
and thought they were making something great and no one liked it.
Like, that's definitely a thing that happens.
But it's still, the author understood, like, they did what they wanted to do, you know?
It's just harder to say definitively when they've only done, like, one or two things.
Right.
Like, sometimes you can look at a work and you can say that this was not what they intended
and it got fucked up somewhere, right?
Like, for instance, when Max Landis was the screenwriter, Max Landis,
was interviewed by Red Letter Media and he was talking about how, you know,
once he sells off a script and once they go and make it,
it can be changed so fundamentally that it basically doesn't, like...
Like, it's not even his work anymore, you know?
Like, he was saying that all the nuance of the script can become so different in the film version
that it's basically a different product.
And so, like, to him, the film is no longer, like, written by Max Landis by the time it's made.
The script was written by Max Landis.
The film is just its own thing that, you know, that exists with or without him.
So, I definitely think that if you tried to watch Max Landis' films and then be like,
this is what his authorial intent is, then it would be lost somewhere, you know?
Because it's not necessarily coming out to be what he wanted it to be.
Whereas, you know, other cases where it's, like, if someone drew a comic
and they seem to be very confident in their comic that everything in it is exactly what they intended,
and then you read it and you're like, this is shit,
it just means that their authorial intent was stupid, you know?
Yeah. When it comes to independence.
That's me. My authorial intent.
Are you saying my authorial intent was stupid, Digi?
No, I like those.
It's because you didn't like my shit.
I'll kill you.
Yeah, I know.
It was good comic. Don't worry about it.
Okay, okay. I'm sorry.
Like, I'm sure it's, like, I read the first page of the Vapors Chapter 2
and Vincent takes the book Infinite Jest,
and he's so sure that having this particular book is going to make him, like, a king,
you know, that people are going to worship him.
Yeah, people admire his wisdom.
Obviously, you chose Infinite Jest because it's the perfect book for that, you know?
What the hell is that?
Is that guy trying to talk and failing?
No, it was just, sorry, I made a noise. Ignore it.
So yes, Digi, I guess my, I guess my authorial intent did shine through in that one.
Right.
Because that's exactly what I meant it to be.
I looked at it and I thought, oh my god, it's Infinite Jest, a giant book that I have,
for years, thought the title sounded so cool that I've wanted to read it.
And I'm pretty sure I got the audiobook because I accidentally had an audible subscription
for, like, a year and didn't know I was paying for it.
So I used all the points I'd built up to buy, like, a fuckload of books,
and I still haven't listened to it.
So, like, that particular book, I was like, I completely understood why that one,
why Infinite Jest, you know?
It's got, like, an air of mystery around it, right?
Yeah.
It's kind of got, like, a little aura, sort of.
Well, it's got the title alone, like, makes it sound like it's about the whole fucking universe,
you know?
Yeah.
Infinite Jest.
It's, like, ironic and meta at the same time as everything else, you know?
Like, it's got that...it's infinite, but it's a joke.
Like, all of infinity is a joke, you know?
I know, man.
And you're totally right that I chose it very deliberately based on, you know...
And that's the next part of this I wanted to get into.
Like, part of the incentive to do this podcast was that I wanted us to talk about how the reason we understand
that creators put a lot of thought into their shit is because we're all creators
and we put a lot of thought into our shit.
Yeah, me, but yeah.
Well, except Gib, obviously.
Like, I can't imagine...
I mean, it depends on the...
Look, alright.
Like, I can't imagine putting something in something that I make without...
I mean, you gotta at least think about it a little bit.
Here's the...
It bothers me that you've got to draw it all.
Yeah, the comic especially.
There's this meme that was going around.
I wouldn't even...I don't know if it's a meme, per se,
but it's something that, like, people were posting all over the Internet
where it's a...what your English teacher told you is the drapes are blue
because they represent the character's depression
and what the author meant was the drapes are fucking blue.
This is an image that got posted everywhere.
People took it as like a, yeah, fuck my English teacher.
Fuck intellectualism.
Reading is just dumb, you know?
And I'm sitting here like...
And of course...
If I was an author and I was writing a scene where I was gonna mention the drapes
and I wanted to mention what color they were,
then the first thought going through my head is,
what color will convey the tone of this scene?
If it's a sad scene, I would say the fucking drapes were blue.
Or if they were yellow, I would say that the yellow of the drapes contrasts with...
Like, he was driven mad by how the yellow drapes didn't reflect his fucking sad mood.
More commonly, you could be like...
You could mention that, like, it's raining and someone's died.
Like, that's a more common thing.
Yeah.
And that's also a thing that English teachers tell you to think about.
Let me explain this from a practical perspective.
Let's say I'm making that scene and let me say I'm doing it in a comic.
And so I drew the drapes and I click on the fill bucket tool
and I'm gonna select a color.
In the time that it will take for me to drag my mouse over to the color selector,
I will probably be able to come to the very obvious conclusion that blue will be the saddest color.
It's not even, like, hard from a, like, a schematic standpoint.
And that's why it's possible.
Because you have to realize, like...
When I was scrambling to come up with an example of where fans thought about it harder than the authors,
I thought, hmm, the Beatles? Like, no.
They, you know, they spent, like, a year making each of their albums for an entire decade.
There's no way anyone could top that.
Because they have so much time.
It's their job.
If you have a job and you make hamburgers and you think about how many hamburgers you make,
every one of those hamburgers represents a thought or a consideration
or an intent in a creative work that a full-time artist has.
So just understand, it's not an impractical thing to do,
it's to think about everything you put in.
Yeah, and it's not, like, if you're an artist or creative, this stuff, like, it instantly makes sense to you.
Like, the example that I wanted to bring up the most when I was planning this podcast,
because it's such a weird, specific thing that didn't need to be done, but I did it,
was when I made that drunken rant about the life of Pablo, the new Kanye West album.
And it's just, like, for all intents and purposes, I got up in front of a camera, drunk as shit,
and just rambled into it about my opinions on this album.
But what I did before I started filming was I have a backdrop where I have, like,
a bunch of vinyl albums and a bunch of art books.
And I took down one of my anime art books and I put up a vinyl album of Rat King's So It Goes.
And the reason for that is that I wanted to have one really great rap album in the background
so that if anyone questioned my credentials of reviewing rap, I would have proof that I like rap music.
You should have also put a black friend in the frame so they could know that you're also, you know,
it's appropriate for you to be judging them.
Well, fuck those people. I actually did get a couple of, like, don't review black music comments,
and I banned them.
Ah, jeez. Well, that's just Kanye's meme now, so...
But, you know, and I had people who pointed out the Rat King album.
They're like, oh man, sick Rat King album back there, you know, because, like...
So it worked, yeah.
Yeah, like, I don't know that that made them, like, take my opinion more seriously per se,
but it was just like, I wanted it to be somewhere back there.
Because I looked at my collection and I said, well, what I see from where I'm sitting is, like,
a pop album, a rock album, and an R&B album. None of this is going to make people think,
like, people might just say, oh, you don't like rap music.
So I'm like, alright, I'll put in the black fucking rap album of last year.
Well, here's a thought.
You definitely put the Rat King album there deliberately.
Yes.
But to the viewer, it's open to interpretation what you meant by that, you know, like,
something might say, oh, he's here to show that he does have good taste in rap,
but someone else maybe might think that you're trying to draw, like, a comparison
between Pablo and Rat King and try to say, oh, this is also an overrated album.
You know, like...
Why would I own it if it was an overrated album?
I don't know.
Why would I own it on vinyl if it was an overrated album?
I'm just saying...
I get what you mean.
Yeah, there are multiple...
You can interpret a thing different ways, like the blue drapes thing,
like maybe it's meant to convey depression,
or maybe it ties into some other aspect of the character, the blueness,
or maybe it's just a throwaway detail that isn't meant to convey anything.
The solution, yeah.
It is included deliberately, but, like, it isn't always clear cut.
Right.
The deliberation of this problem is interviews.
Get interviewers.
Yeah.
This is a side note.
Here's a rule for interviewers.
Before you interview someone, watch all the other interviews that that person has done,
and write a list of all the questions that have already been asked to them,
especially the ones that have been asked 50,000 times,
and don't ask any of those.
And if you can't come up with any new questions, don't do the interview.
Just a completely unrelated thing.
But good interviews are how you can dig into creative intent,
which is why I think that if...
Well, an interviewer serves a more insidious purpose of just giving exposure
and not giving you shit about finding out anything more than we already know.
Yeah, I know, but we're talking about the morals here.
In fairness, like, most...
I mean, I won't say most, but, like, a large percentage of creatives
want their stuff to be interpreted by the viewer,
and they don't like explaining it.
Right.
And so if they don't want to...
I am 100% like that.
Yeah.
I feel that way 100%.
I wish I could be like that, but I can't.
Like, I will absolutely explain why I did that.
I do not try.
If someone wanted to do a seven-hour interview with me
to explain everything I've ever made, I absolutely would.
I have.
I feel.
Yeah.
See, I don't want to.
I don't want to, because...
I took a 44-hour interview.
If you do that, and you sit down and you explain every single thing that you thought,
there is absolutely no room for anyone to interpret otherwise.
But that's not untrue.
Because that means that people have...
Everyone has to make the decision of whether or not they want to...
They agree with you.
Yeah, they want to take the author seriously.
That's true.
I do think...
Because, like, authors...
What authors are afraid of when they don't, like, say that stuff
is that they're afraid that people will latch onto everything they say
and not want to interpret it differently.
Because so many...
A lot of people do value authorial intent.
That's, like, the most valuable thing.
Which is, paradoxically, why they get mad at you
for supposedly over-analyzing something.
Because they want to believe in authorial intent as, like...
As what matters.
But if what you say was the author's intent, like,
is more advanced than what they had already thought,
then it's a disconnect.
It's like, oh, God, I'm thinking about it wrong.
I didn't understand it as well as I should have.
Well, I think both are fun.
I think people understanding exactly why I did something
and getting the same thing out of it is cool.
And people getting something out of it that I couldn't have thought of is cool.
I like both.
Right.
There's definitely been plenty of times where people have, like,
interpreted something really weird out of my work,
and I've been like, that's cool, man.
You know?
I mean, even just all the people who take my videos as, like,
motivational speaking or something.
Like, so many people who are like, my...
I got through depression because of your videos,
and I'm like, I didn't intend that, but okay, you know?
You know, tons of shit like that, you know?
And...
But my point is just simply that with the whole life of Pablo thing,
that, like, that was something that I threw together in five minutes,
but I did think about it and put it in there,
and that's how easy it is, you know?
And, like, even mistakes in my work, I know what they all are.
You know, every time someone corrects me on something in a video,
it's like, I know.
I edited it.
I looked at it.
I stared at it.
All right?
I heard it, you know?
Well, you've had things that you, you know, should...
I mean, you don't always know every single thing, right?
You've been corrected in the past.
Does that mean nobody should ever correct you, you know?
Uh, yes, because I don't want...
Like, I don't get what they think they're...
Like, I can't change it.
It's out already, you know?
Well, so what?
So, like, I mean, the comments are a part of the...
a part of the universe of this video.
It's a criticism, you know?
It exists to, you know, correct mistakes and shit.
Only if I don't block those comments.
There's a lot, by the way, listeners who haven't heard any...
haven't heard of us before.
There's a lot more nuance to Digi's opinions on blocking comments here
that he's not explaining.
So don't call him a hypocrite.
There's more to it than that.
I think currently...
I think currently it's, uh, it's overly optimistic to assume anyone watching
hasn't seen most of our content, but maybe one day.
Maybe one day.
Oh, I don't know.
I think that's...
Well, maybe they're just new and they're not familiar yet.
Yeah, sure.
Sure.
Just watch my video on closing comments over on Digi Bro after Dark.
Yeah, very...
I went in deep about it.
But, uh, yeah, no.
Like, it's...
There are some times where people will correct, like, my pronunciation of something
and I did not know that I had pronounced it wrong.
Dude, you mispronounce words all the time.
Yeah, and a lot of the time I do it on purpose and knowingly.
Like, like...
Why?
Because I don't like the other pronunciation.
Like, I like...
You should be correct.
It's just how I say it.
I'm not interested in your head canon of how words should be pronounced, you know?
But my...
My point is like...
We have a shared language here.
We're trying to run a society and you're...
You're...
You're violating the whole operation with your...
With your go-in row.
You're going off-road.
Dude, there's so many words that I've just made up and invented for my videos
or found whole new uses for.
It's like...
You know what it's like?
It's like I have...
When I was a kid, I listened to the Fuli Kuli soundtrack all the time.
It was like my favorite thing to listen to.
And as a result, I...
Since I didn't speak Japanese at all,
I made up all these lyrics.
Now, if I...
Go.
If I make a lyric video to Fuli...
To like...
To like Little Busters or whatever,
and I write down all my head canon lyrics,
is it wrong for people to correct me?
Because I...
That's what I...
That's my version of the song.
Saying a word differently is not different.
It's not the same as changing the word.
Like, I don't think anybody would be confused if...
Did you...
Did you say niche or niche?
Yeah.
There's nothing else that sounds like niche.
There's nothing that hits you in the head and you're like,
Oh, something's wrong here.
What's going on here?
And you should lock that feeling deep down inside,
because no one fucking cares.
Look, if I left a comment every time I was bothered
by the way someone pronounced something,
I would never stop leaving comments.
Every video I've ever seen has a pronunciation
that bothers me in it.
You know?
Like, no one knows how to pronounce Japanese shit.
No one knows how to pronounce other shit.
I'll comment on your weird pronunciation,
so I guess we're at an impasse here.
I don't know.
There are lots of bad pronunciations in the vapors.
That was a joke, because that's impossible,
because it's not audio.
Everything I say is, I'm actually American,
but I just pronounce everything wrong.
You just think that's how it's pronounced.
That's what gets to me the most,
is that everyone has different dialects.
So like, to say that I can't pronounce a word a certain way
is like, I don't get where the disconnect comes from.
Like, just because no one else pronounces it that way
doesn't mean that it's not a dialect
that is specific to me.
I can actually agree with that.
There's no really wrong way to say anything.
And I think the fact that people get upset about pronunciations...
Then you just get into the fundamental point of language itself.
Well, I think what this is, why people get bothered
about pronunciations plays into the very first episode
of Hello Internet, which was called
Being Wrong on the Internet.
How many times do people correct your pronunciation
and how angry are they about correcting your pronunciation
if you pronounce it on a podcast or a Let's Play?
Is it less intense?
I would say it's less intense,
but it is still very much there.
But it is less intense, and I think that's because
in a proper video, people expect you to have this level
of professionalism and objectivity,
not just objectivity of opinions.
Even people who understand subjective opinions
still think there's like objective standards
you have to play into, which is, I think,
another category of this whole author intent thing.
Davoo, what was the name of that video?
Being Wrong on the Internet.
It was the first episode of the Hello Internet podcast.
I just came to say Hello Internet.
Alright, kill yourself.
That's the funniest thing I've ever thought of in my entire life.
Right. Good one.
Yeah, I nailed it, okay.
I was getting nailed for, in my latest video,
I said Nodame Cantabile,
I guess it's pronounced canta bide,
which is like a fucking Italian word.
All these people are shitting on me for it,
and I'm like, why would you expect me to be able
to pronounce a fucking Italian word?
When have I ever suggested that I know any Italian at all?
You know, like, I just...
To me, when I hear...
There are some things that humans are expected to do,
you know, outside of what anime reviewers...
This has always stuck out with me in my mind, right?
There was this one time that I watched,
like, one of the first anime video reviews I saw
was this British guy talking about Hajime no Ippo, right?
And the way he kept pronouncing it was Hajime no Ippo.
And, like, the first time...
Did he watch the show? They say the name over and over.
Yeah, but he's like, as soon as I heard it,
I was like, well, he's British.
Words sound different when they come out of his mouth.
And the funny thing is, even though at first I was like,
oh, God, but then over time,
that's now how I pronounce it more often than not.
I now love saying Hajime no Ippo.
Like, it's hilarious to me.
Dude, we need the Hippo to do a review of the Ippo.
Yeah.
Get on that. Get on that.
And, like, I knew what he was talking about.
I knew what the show was.
Like, he probably, on some level, is aware
that he probably doesn't know how to pronounce it
because it's a fucking Japanese name, you know, like...
The reason I say Kantabile in my video
is that I learned that show in 2007
when I was 16.
So I didn't think at all about the pronunciation.
And I've just been saying it that way for nine years.
And there was a moment when I started editing the video,
like, once I had the audio figured out
and I started laying in clips, I went,
oh, my God, I probably pronounced this wrong.
Like, Kantabile can't be a word, you know?
But then I went, eh, everyone knows what I'm talking about.
It doesn't fucking matter.
And I finished editing the video, you know?
And then I've got people who were like commenting,
I'm almost vomited when I heard Kantabile.
That makes sense. That's appropriate, thematically.
I don't think that's what they bile.
I think we've gone pretty far afield.
I think we've gone pretty far afield
with the topic of authorials.
Yeah, well, guess what? Conunciation is too funny.
So we're going to keep talking about it.
People may have realized there's a trend in Digi's videos
whenever he talks about a particular character
from Hunter Hunter, he always goes,
Kidua! I can't even do it correctly.
Kidua.
Because in the first video I did, I said,
Kidua, and people fucking...
There was hundreds of comments
pissed off at me for the way I pronounced Kidua.
That's obviously the right way to do it
because everything else sounds gay and stupid.
Yes, it's Kidua.
Kidua.
So there's a couple of videos where you just talk
and that's one of the few concessions I've made
just because there were so many comments about it
that I couldn't...
I was like, I don't want to live through this again.
Like, I'm going to change...
It's not how I would ever pronounce it in my everyday life.
If I was talking about the show to anyone,
I'd say Kidua because that sounds right
or Kidua.
Like, it might have been how I said it, but like...
Kidua.
It's got to be that way in the video.
And no one complains when I say it that way.
So Kidua.
Completely changes the entire tone of my voice.
Like, you're listening to me speak in a normal American accent
and then suddenly, oh yeah, and in Hunter Hunter,
Kidua has this great character arc.
It sounds fucking stupid.
And the most intense example was the pronunciation
of Shinseiki Evangelion.
Yes.
Which was very intentional.
Because you go Evangelion
and I go Evangelion because I hear you talk about it
more than anyone else.
Yes.
When Demo says Evangelion, I'm like, okay, fine.
And people can go Evangelion or Uvangelion
or Oyvangelion, whatever.
But people got mad that your first syllable was different.
And so you wanted to highlight the fact that
the Japanese title is not even the same words.
No, it's Shinseiki Evangelion.
So this goes into people having these false ideas
that there's like these objective standards of pronunciation
that you're supposed to hold up to,
which brings us to this...
I just wanted to say one pronunciation thing
that I kind of might be amusing.
I never watched Dragon Ball Z as a kid,
but I did read the manga of Dragon Ball.
Did you call it Dragon Balls?
No.
Is that what you're saying?
No, but the...
I pronounce kamehameha, like kamehameha,
because that's how it's written.
Sure, sure.
Instead of the kamehame, and I always think
kamehameha is stupid.
But it's correct.
I read Sasuke as Sasuke for the longest time.
Really? Sasuke is a really cool soccer of the beautiful.
Naruto!
I thought it was Sasuke.
Oh man, that's even worse.
Sasuke.
Oh, so you're saying that you read it before you saw the show?
I just saw it.
I'm surprised.
I read it in 2003.
I read it before the show existed.
But yeah, anyway, Davoo,
what were you going to use that to branch back into...
Stupid Reddit moderator guy
who disrespected Jesse...
Oh shit.
Endless Jesse's professionalism.
His AMV, yeah.
He's not...
It's a shame he's not on this podcast right now,
because the reason he's not...
The intention he has for not being on this podcast
is he's asleep, so...
Yeah.
You know.
So let me explain this conflict very quickly.
There's this Reddit...
Jesse made an AMV of Ava and Gelyon
and posted it on the Ava subreddit.
And the moderator there, like,
jumped down Jesse's throat for the fact that
he had changed the aspect ratio of the video.
And this guy was like,
I was only able to last 10 seconds,
and I just wanted to throw up because your aspect...
A lot of people talking about throwing up lately
in response to shitty videos.
He was like,
I just wanted to throw up because you changed the aspect ratio,
and any prof...
He literally said any professional AMV competition
would have thrown this out immediately.
He just said any reputable AMV contest.
Yeah.
Which is the weirdest thing to say,
because it's not an AMV contest submission.
It's some video some guy made on YouTube for fun.
Yeah, and later on...
He's using this other standard.
Later on, this guy was like,
you know, in the professional world,
you have to do professional correct things.
You have to do X, you have to do Y.
And if you do it wrong, you'll get fired.
And I pointed out, look, if...
Fired from YouTube.
Yeah, yeah.
If this guy were working for a company,
and they told you to not stretch the aspect ratio,
he wouldn't, right?
Right.
And I told him.
Yeah.
This guy...
No, you don't understand.
This guy wouldn't...
This guy would be laughed out of any professional AMV contest
that he tried to submit to.
Meanwhile...
Man, I want to make a shit-com now called Fired from YouTube,
starring Jesse Wood over the giant Eva AMV debacle.
Guy, I really like how you accidentally said that as shit-com.
What?
Did I?
Ho-ho!
That was on my authorial intent all along.
Yeah, there we go.
I choose to ascribe that to the work that you just made,
that meaning.
Yeah.
So, like, I told this guy, look, Jesse,
this guy is a professional YouTuber, you realize?
He puts thought into what he's doing.
He's not like an amateur.
You know, I think the only kind of shit-com Jesse would like to be in
is a shit-com, but sorry.
Yeah.
And I can understand why these people on our Eva
didn't understand that Jesse is like an actual YouTuber.
The kind of person who must hang out on our Eva
has got to be the most insufferable...
Moderate our Eva.
Right, the moderator holds the shit.
And according to his tag on the site,
he's also a moderator of avageeks.org.
Yeah, I looked into this guy a little bit.
So this guy's like a lifer.
This guy spends a lot of time.
And he will not accept the skewing of the aspect ratio
of his precious work.
Right, because what I really wanted to rip into this guy for,
not that it's his work,
not that I didn't get around to it,
but this guy spends so much time being moderators of websites.
How much time does he have being in this so-called
professional world here, you know?
Probably not.
I mean, has he done any?
What's his standard?
I don't know.
Yeah, I feel like any one of us have accomplished
way more artistically than this guy.
And so I was trying to phrase that to him
in a really soft way by being like,
you know, you're more of a technical person.
You're not much of an aesthetics person.
You have to understand that aesthetics are also important.
He's like, no, these are objective facts.
Like he said the word objective over and over again.
And Jesse clarified so many times,
like dude, this is not an objective thing.
Like you can have your standard,
but like obviously there are times
when change of the aspect ratio
might be a better way to go.
All of us think of the stretching as better.
And I said, you realize this guy is a professional YouTuber
to which this moderator said, and I quote,
no, no, he's not.
Not by a long shot.
All of those pauses were different sentences.
See, he's making the word perfect.
He's using some other definition or something.
Well, he literally did not understand
that Jesse is literally a fucking professional YouTuber.
Yeah, because then he went into his Patreon
and was like, well, you're not making that much money.
And I pointed out, yes he is.
This guy doesn't even do his stats right.
He looked at Jesse's Patreon and saw the amount that he makes.
And then he looked at my Japanese Animes
and assumed that was the only channel.
So he was like 11 videos over the course of the year.
That means you only made like $3,000.
And Jesse's like, huh.
He has no idea what he's dealing with here.
How about you quit it with the financial analysis?
Anyway, the point is, authorial intent,
Jesse wanted the stretch aspect ratio.
It was on purpose.
It wasn't because he didn't understand
what was aesthetically appropriate.
He fucking wanted that look.
And I think, personally, it looks better that way.
Yeah.
I had no idea it was stretched.
I thought it was possible.
I hadn't even noticed either yet.
And this guy is like the worst example
of when this philosophy goes awry.
Because this guy just insistently said,
these are objective true standards
based on my experience.
You don't have experience.
Making YouTube videos doesn't count.
Running AMV contests counts.
Not that he had won any, of course.
I mean, if he did, he should have brought it up.
He specifically said that if he won some,
that would be pretentious.
But just saying he was part of them isn't pretentious.
Yeah, this guy's logic.
Look, this guy has a profession.
No, that would give you fucking a reasonable reason
to be saying the things you're saying.
Whatever, whatever.
All right, let's get this up to another topic here.
I have to have a little bit of payoff to this story.
Just one sentence.
Okay.
I eventually basically indirectly called this guy a smug asshole
because on the internet, you're allowed to be a smug asshole,
but you're not allowed to call people a smug asshole.
So he banned me from R.A.V.A. for 30 days.
And then later on, I emailed him, I PMed him saying,
you represent the worst ideas that I absolutely oppose.
Like your ideas are terrible.
Yeah.
And so he permabanned me from R.A.V.A.
And so then I, in a genius move,
permabanned him from R.The Procrastinators.
And he's on just a blast.
Got mutually assured destruction.
Yes, just the way when we become super famous
and he'll want to get in on the huge TPC sensation,
he won't be allowed and he'll wish that that day
he had taken a different course of action.
It's like being banished from Athens, you know?
There's no worse fate.
There's nothing worse.
All right.
Let me move into another thing.
So I've been saying all this shit about how authors
totally intend to put all this stuff there.
And now I'm going to backpedal a little
and say that authorship, like the genius of it
is not just having amazing ideas,
but also being able to recognize when great shit
just falls into your lap.
Sure.
Because like an amazing amount of my editing
is serendipitous.
Like I just throw a clip into the editor
and I'll happen to notice that there's like one scene
that just happens to match up with what I'm saying
and then I base everything around that.
Like for instance, I did all these AMV compilations recently
and each one I would just like set up all the clips
from the person and then I'd try to find a song
that vaguely had the same tone as those clips
and then I'd put it in and then like there'd be little moments
where the animation just so happens
to coincide exactly with the music
and then I just time everything around that.
So like all the clips are just laid in in chronological order.
There's no like advanced editing.
It just so happens that I was able to find songs
that perfectly timed with certain moments.
So like it looks way more thoughtful than it really was
just because I was able to recognize small,
you know, match cuts and stuff like that.
So like, yeah, I think a big part of creativity
is not just being a genius,
but recognizing accidental genius
and being able to tailor it to fit what you're doing.
It's a hard-knock life being a genius.
Didn't what you just said
conflict with what you were saying before,
you said before that it's basically impossible
that a viewer can think more about a work
than the creator did,
but from what you just said, it seems like sometimes
a creator can just kind of do something haphazardly
and just sort of have it work out, you know?
Well, he did say it was contradictory.
Yeah, I think it's not necessarily that it's
contradictory per se.
It's just not a rule.
I think that as an author,
your ability to recognize those things
and then make them work
is also part of what is the skill set, you know?
Like the lines between intentional genius
and just realizing something that's okay.
The lines between coming up with a good idea
and realizing a good idea just fell into your lap,
those lines are very blurred.
And by the way, you can't ignore that during
the whole editing process,
like there's tons of tiny adjustments being made,
like you have the opportunity to remove
or add something at any time.
So by the mere virtue that something is there,
especially when you're doing something like editing,
you decided not to remove it.
Yeah, that is intent right there.
Well, I mean, you could have missed something.
No, it's possible.
You could make mistakes or miss something in the editing process.
Or include something, you know,
that other people see that you didn't so share.
Like, you know, I'm sure we've all heard the Bob Ross quote,
like there are no mistakes, just happy accidents,
where, you know, he'd fuck up a painting.
Which I absolutely do not agree with when it comes to editing,
but okay.
Well, he would fuck up a painting
and then he'd just turn it into a different painting.
Right, right.
I mean, obviously if you have,
if you've already written a script
and you're trying to make a video
that is an exact interpretation of that script
and you somehow fuck it up,
then you're gonna probably just have to redo it,
you know, but like, you can, a lot of the times,
transform something into something else
by way of, you know, the serendipitous nature of it,
where you just kind of, you spilled,
like Jesse Wood with his fucking man-child marsh.
It was just like his floor exploded,
so he made a video out of it, you know.
Like, it's not that he creatively intended,
hey, I'm gonna fill my room with water
and then fucking take all my toys and throw them in it.
It was like, the ground is capsized
and shit water has come out.
I happen to have a bunch of pirate themed toys.
Let's film a pirate adventure, you know.
And of course there's also plenty of skill involved
in his comedic timing and being able to come up.
He was able to know exactly,
probably able to know how funny things
are gonna look on the camera,
how things are gonna look, you know,
when it's all edited, he's able to prepare for that.
The best endless Jess example is his fuck updates video,
which was just him turning on the camera,
pointing at his computer,
and then letting out an emotional reaction
he was having at that exact moment.
And anyone could have done something like that
if they had a camera on hand.
But what people don't realize is any regular person,
it wouldn't have been nearly as funny
because he's trained himself to be able to do
that kind of thing really well.
And as a result of people not realizing
the level of skill involved in that,
the bajillions of people have posted it on Facebook
and removed his channel name at the end
because they just don't think it's art.
Because they just think it was an accident.
One of the biggest reasons I watch all of Jesse's content,
even when it's like Beer Quest,
where he's just reviewing beer,
is that he's so amazing at some random shit happening
and he turns it into part of the joke.
In the latest Beer Quest episodes,
there's parts where he'll just start spinning a beer
and then he just drops it and it breaks.
And then he doesn't ever just like,
oh, I fucked up, I need to redo the video.
It's always like immediately, oh my god!
Now I've ruined Christmas!
He turns it into a hilarious joke immediately
and the video just becomes a different work of art
than what it was originally going to be,
but he recognized it and transforms it into the new thing.
So yeah, he's fucking great at that.
And for me, that doesn't happen as much on camera and stuff
because I'm not nearly as good at that kind of shit,
but I do that a lot in the editing bay.
Almost all my editing is like,
I threw a clip-in, found a moment that kind of matched,
and then based it around that and it just happens to work out.
So I guess, like, authorial intent,
it could be like, you notice when stuff is good,
when it just seems to happen, or you plan it,
but nothing really matters until you make it public,
until you present it.
Everything is just the process.
So I'm going back to Evangelion, which is, once again,
a show that used its...
like, it totally did art from adversity in a brilliant way
because the first half of the show is very clearly
everything they planned it to be.
The first half is gorgeously animated,
every shot is very well-considered,
all the facial expressions, all the shot compositions,
all of it's very clearly trying to communicate certain emotions.
And then the second half of the show is like,
they completely ran out of money, the budget went off schedule,
they had to change the script because of, like,
sarin gas attacks and shit, all this bad stuff happened.
And so they went, alright, we can no longer do
what we were doing before, what can we do now?
And so they created something that, while, like,
you may or may not find it to be on the same level of quality
as what they were doing before,
but they very clearly created an artistic work
with what they had, like, they made something
that was so different and out there,
that it's actually one of the most memorable things about the show.
Yeah, and you know what, it does a bunch of different things
in its production that probably would be not approved of
by the professional industry.
It's a good thing Neon Genesis' Ava Ngellion
was not posted on our Ava, or else that moderator would have said,
why is he holding, why is Shinji with the robot
holding that guy, and why is it a still frame for eight whole seconds?
There's no animation. That would be rejected.
That doesn't make any sense.
Davoo has no chill! Davoo has no chill!
Why is Shinji just a pencil sketch flying across the screen?
They didn't finish animating it.
That wouldn't be accepted at any animation contest.
Holy shit.
Man, I was giving you shit, Davoo, for, like,
obsessing over the sky and paying off.
Holy shit, it was so worth it.
So worth it.
All right, I don't think I can add to that,
and we are about an hour in, so...
That's a great place to add cap.
Any closing thoughts?
I think we've got a lot done today,
like we do every day.
But what are we going to do tonight, Ben?
I am going to give a shout out,
because I said this in the intro before that we lost
because of my fuck up,
but I want to say thanks for Reverse Spectrum.
You said you really like how I plug my Patreon
and you gave me Bastion.
I really appreciate both of those things.
I really love that your plugging yourself has become a staple.
Yeah, I got rewarded not for the thing I'm plugging,
but for plugging.
That's what he's a fan of.
The plug was not the one that they wanted,
but it was the one that they needed.
Yeah.
All right, everybody.
See you next week.
Bye.
Everyone say goodbye.
Say goodbye.
And go and read my fucking thing at
stcomics.com, or I'll kill you.
Yeah, intentionally.
Yeah.