Hello everybody and welcome to another amazing high-octane-action episode of the
Pro Crastinators Podcast.
How's it going, it's me, he's on the podcast, Ray, it's me, Garfield, here to bring the
mood down for everybody.
Fantastic, I would expect nothing less.
We have the Paladin of Purple, Lethal Aurora Mage.
How am I a paladin if I'm a mage?
I don't know, you're multi-classing, like in Final Fantasy XI, the best game in the
series.
But I specialize in purple magic.
Yeah, purple magic is magic done for your deity, purple, so you're also a holy mage,
so you're a paladin.
It's fine.
Okay, acceptable, acceptable.
We have Nate, the Starfleet boy who's been through to some strange issues with the holodeck,
is now in this desolate wasteland with no resources and no idea what to do.
You can't tell, but I am dabbing.
I don't think that, I think it's against Starfleet regulation.
That's absolute.
We have the Energetic Scrapper, Ben St.
What?
Oh god, he's lucid.
You'll pull something together eventually, I'm sure.
What?
And we have the Desert Overlord himself, Munchy with Tiny Hats.
Listen, the channel isn't growing, PC pinny socks are on the low, they're down 6% since
we started this episode, everyone's going fucking crazy, they're all in a panic.
And I know what we have to do, we have to do a major rebranding project and we're going
to change ourselves from the ProCrastiners podcast to the Pimplecrushing podcast.
Listen, my mom signs into my YouTube account on fucking daily and watches Dr. PimplePopperMD,
some fucking Zitcrushing videos.
And I think if we can tap into that niche mom market who just love to see pus fly every
which way, then we can jack our subscriber number up and rake in that fucking superchats
as we do live Shekels for Heckles, except we've rebranded it, so now we pop each other's
pimples.
And I've got like 6 episodes worth right fucking here for you, so let's just get on with that.
Imagine our new idea, the PCP, the only YouTube channel by moms for moms, I think that's the
direction we need to head.
Munchy, would Shekels for Heckles be rebranded Pimpin' for Pimples?
Oh fuck, this shit rites itself, dude.
This pimple popping phenomenon, it's kind of like a, I wouldn't even call it, it's like
ASMR adjacent, it's like parallel in the sense that it's not like ASMR that like relaxes
you through like voices or whatever, but it similarly relaxes like Michelle, like Michelle
is into it and loves pimple popping videos, it makes me want to throw up.
Mom, can you have your own account?
Stop using my account, it's in my recommended videos, mom.
Do you guys not, do you guys not at least on some level understand the pathos, like
I get it, I do get it, not the pathos, what's the word for it, not the shot in Florida?
It's like getting the long piece in a Tetris thing, it's like you know, it's like setting
up a Tetris thing and then having like an L block or something at the perfect right moment
to get the Tetris.
Yeah, yeah, the catharsis of the pop, like I get it.
I understand it, but like, okay.
Forget about the pops.
They take it to like the extreme, well there's like, okay, there's videos that are like more
like more like deep level surgery, like where they slice up on the back of like a dude's
head.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, no, not into those, not into those one bit.
The pimple popping videos, that's baby shit, I could do that, well I could do that if I
ever had a pimple in my life, but unfortunately I was cursed with perfect complexion.
But you know, anyone, anyone who's greasy and disgusting enough, I'm actually in diamond
form, it's an Emma Frost thing, it's actually, yeah, it's my second mutation, but you know
most people can pop pimples, but what I just want to see someone go into the doctor with
some fat abscess like hanging off their neck and someone's got a poke at it with a scalpel
and like they got to like take a syringe and like draw the shit out at first and they
just like, they like make an incision and it just like explodes like a volcano, that's
not a volcano that's erupting, a volcano that is like boiling over with like the hot chunky
fucking lava spilling out over the side, so, it feels like victory for me, I'm feeling
it like vicariously, that victory through that person, getting rid of that monstrous
abscess.
Guys, since we started talking about the rebranding, our picture is up $500, we have to keep going.
Oh no, we gotta keep going, we gotta keep going.
The thing about the cyst is that they don't even give good catharsis because like, they
cut open the skin, they go in with like you know a spade or a shovel or a trowel or something
and they like scoop the abscess out, but that's not the end because what then must happen
is they have to go in with tiny little scrapers and scissors and cut out like sort of the
sort of sac or skin or membrane that contained the cyst and that part is one, a bit gruesome
and two, it's just boring, so it's like the emotional arc of a cyst video is just, it
sort of slowly peaks early and then trails off to nothing and then stays down really
low until the very end, the cutting out of the sac is extremely unsatisfying.
I haven't had the pleasure of watching this on a live human, but I have had the pleasure
of watching it on a digital acclamation, like a 3D animation on YouTube of a transformation
from a penile to a vagin, and the process of going trans, it's like going ghost but
going trans, is the most like brutal thing that I can ever do.
I watched Ranma one half, sure, it's so terrible, it really just freaks me out.
Remember when Ranma would say, I'm going trans whenever water, time or that.
I like to think of the human body as like, I know this is wrong, but it's like good,
it's like good.
Oh, it's so wrong, it's fine, it's fine, but then with this pimple popping shit and general
all surgery and stuff, it's like, oh my god, just the human epidermis is so fucked up and
so disgusting and filled with pores and like, what even is a zit, what even is a zit and
how does it get so fucking big?
That was always my answer, when I was a kid, that was always my question to the adults
who tried to tell me that God exists and that we were created in God's image and even as
a child I was like, have you seen people, like we get like fucking like zits and like I've
had like ingrown toenails before, like what the fuck is that, you have to go to the doctor
and they have to like slice open your toe to fix it.
Because you just grew wrong by accident, sometimes like one day you wake up and like you're like
25 which is supposed to be like your prime, that's the sequel to grow up and grow home
is grow wrong, yeah, grow wrong, like you just wake up one day and like all of your bones
are just dust now and they don't feel good ever again once you're like 20, yeah, or I
mean they're just cancer in general, just like just grow right, stop growing wrong cells,
what the fuck, what even tell triggers them to grow wrong, I don't know, I have no idea,
I will, I will, I will, I will put too much of that dank weed man, I'll, I'll posit a
new theory though, I know what causes cancer, it's all that aspartame I'm drinking, Conrad
Collins aka Digi Bro, I can't wait for you to never hear this but if you did you'd freak
out because every time I say that it pisses you off and I find it hilarious, well you
know that's, you know that's the leading cause of aspartism, yeah, yeah, that's, why do you
think Digi drinks Diasoda all the time now, I mean I applaud him, I applaud him, it's better
than sugar in my totally uneducated opinion, I mean pick a poison, do you want to become
retarded or do you want to die of cancer, these are your two choices, it's, it's, it's
do you want to die of cancer or do you want to become fat, you either die of cancer or
live long enough to see yourself become the retard, hey, hang on, doesn't being fat cause
cancer, doesn't obesity lead to cancer as well, I think everything leads to cancer, it can,
it can, it even worse, it leads to death, right, true, sometimes by that mechanism,
that's a weird thing, I want to, I'm going to draw a Garfield comic where, where John
just leans in like Garfield's like in his little box bed and John leans in and says,
you know obesity can cause cancer Garfield and Garfield just looks like at the viewer
and is like Mondays, there's John, John leans in and whispers in Garfield's ear, you know,
even with seat belts on, people die in car crashes all the time, I just thought that
was interesting, there's a John, you know Garfield, you can have an aneurysm at any
time in your life, no matter how healthy you are, it can just happen and you'll die, there's
a giant, giant sign at my Starbucks and this is, this is not like a, like my local Starbucks,
this is just like every Starbucks in the area in California, there is like a, a piece of
legislator in, in the California law code, they have a piece of the local legislator
hanging, they have a local legislator's ear that they sliced off, they're holding it
ransom if they don't enforce coffee policies, it's, it's just this like copy and pasted
on like every restaurant they could think to go to, like every piece of fast food or
just normal sit down restaurant, it's all this little plaque near the door that just
says, this like, like food distributed here has been known to cause cancer by the state
of California, like have a nice day, so you can't eat anywhere, like seriously it's ranging
from Starbucks to like fucking Whole Foods to anywhere, you go and then it's just like,
oh this causes cancer by the way, I'm like, well I want a fucking green tea for appuccino,
so you know what, I'm getting cancer and I'm gonna love it, yeah.
I mean the odds are everyone in our generation is gonna die of cancer, we're just exposed
to so much carcinogens at this point.
Maybe the solution to cancer is mandatory death sentences at 35, so that you just don't
get old enough to.
That would definitely motivate me to start working even harder.
Yeah, right, there was a start to the episode about that, you get executed by the people
when you're like 65, cause they don't want to deal with old people, cause they're a
drag on society and I'm just saying it makes a lot of sense.
It's true.
My theory is that cancer was actually created in God's image and it was meant to be our
natural predator and we're not supposed to be here and cancer is the flood that's gonna
take us out.
Yeah, God I hope so.
I have a, speaking of obesity, speaking of obesity, speaking of obesity, I have a boring
announcement to make, are you excited, are you excited, gents?
I hope you have obesity, I hope you have obesity, I got the test results back, I'm positive
for obesity.
Woo!
Yeah.
No, I hit my record low weight the other day, I was 167.5, I couldn't believe it.
And all you had to do was chop off his head, the least useful part and then I lost.
Anyway, pretty stoked about that, I went, you're gonna say 175?
No, 167.5.
Oh, that's pretty damn low.
Pretty low, pretty low, still it's weird, everyone tells me, everyone tells me like
Ben, you don't look overweight at all, like you can stop that, and I'm like, well according
to BMI, I'm still like two or three pounds over the line to overweight, so I'm just gonna
keep going, thanks.
Right, I agree completely.
Well, muscle mass affects that as well.
Yeah, yeah, which I'm probably lacking in.
Anyone who tells you you're not fat wants you to be fatter than them, that's the truth.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, I agree.
A hundred percent agreed.
Definitely, definitely do not trust anyone who says anything nice about me, they definitely
have an angle, there's no question.
I have a very similar thing to say, this is my main thing I wanted to bring up, I've
instituted a policy, so I'm going to Hawaii for Christmas for Michelle's family and just
to be in the best place in the world again, I highly recommend it, and so I'm instituting
a policy because I hate how my fucking love handles are disgusting and fat and I want
them dead, so I've instituted a policy that I'll be doing in perpetuity at least until
I go there in like a month and a half, and I'm beginning another one of my famous wacky
acronyms, it's Redouet, Redouet, R-E-D-U-I-H, run every day until I'm hot, that's my plan,
I'm starting it today, and I'm not going to stop until I'm hot as hell, and that's it.
Literally, try keto, that's my recommendation, also, just incidentally, I went four days
without eating this week, almost by accident.
Like, ever since that fast, you don't need it anymore.
I, okay, it was on the day of the stream, you've been de-shackled from the ties of human
consumption.
On the day that we streamed, on Wednesday, on, you know, on Roddy Fricker's cop killers
on Twitch, I woke up kind of early, didn't eat, you know, I don't usually get hungry
in the mornings.
Well, like, I just, don't you love that fuck is censored, but cop killer is just fine.
Yeah, cop killing cops is fine, but the F word is not cool, it is not cool, guys.
Well, we gotta bash the fash, but let's go on.
Fash the fash.
Fucking left, left wingers on Twitch, ah, fucking millennials.
They, they, so yeah, so that day, you know, we woke up, stayed up for a while, you know,
stream happened, did that, it was night time, I just never got hungry, went to, didn't get
hungry at night time, went to sleep late, I'm not hungry, so I won't eat, woke up the
next day, the trend continued, by day four, I was just like, I might as well keep going.
But then, I, then I told someone, some people were like, just die, people were like, why
are you, why are you fat?
Like, there's no health, there's no real health benefits of going that long, like the benefits
of fasting don't continue for days and days, and I was like, yeah, fuck it, four days is
fine, I don't need to make a thing out of this, so I just ate some shit, I just ate some nuts
and cheese and whatever.
I mean, imagine, just, just for a second, Ben, and everybody, imagine if your hunger
mechanism stopped working correctly, and you just didn't get hungry, maybe through, that's
what was happening, I did not get hungry at all until day four.
But there you go, but that doesn't necessarily mean you're actually getting the right or
best nutrition, just because one doesn't experience it.
No, no, not necessarily.
Okay.
Like two, I was thinking I would just go another week at that point, because I was like more
than halfway there, but then I was like, well, it's, it would, like there's no actual point,
it would just be a numbers thing, it would just be an arbitrary, like, hit that number
goalpost, so whatever.
And you know, you know, to Ewan and Munchie's point as well, I am aware that like, running
every day is not enough to just be, to get skinny.
You die at that point.
My point, what did I say?
It's an important thing.
Oh, you know, maybe you might have just been, Ben, I'd just say, just go keto, which is
the perfect point.
All I said was try keto.
Okay, okay.
Well, fair enough, I should do that, and I intend to, but this is, it's so much easier
for me to institute, I've noticed this about myself in a huge way, I need binary switches,
on off choices, that if I do that, I can get things done.
And if I don't, I fuck it up every time.
You mean like, you mean like you have to go all or nothing?
Yes.
To have flipped the switch of I will now run every day is almost easy to do.
It's easy to do that.
It's easier than being like, I'll run three days of the week, any three days that I want
to.
Way easier, way easier than that.
I get that.
You have less wiggle than to fuck up.
Decide.
The wiggle room is how I find excuses to fuck up.
Exactly.
If I gave myself, if I gave myself, look, you know, one day a week, I can eat, you know,
one carb thing or something, then like that one thing would hang over me all the time.
And I would constantly be debating like, should this be the thing?
Should this be the thing?
Maybe I'll eat this and then I, you know, but if it's like, no, none, then it's not,
it's not hard because like, I'm just like, oh, I see, oh, that's, that pizza, I just
can't eat it.
Well, like it's out of, it's out of the question for me to eat that.
The idea of fixing my diet has long plagued me, because it's a far more complicated overall
thing than to be one easy switch.
I know I need to fix that.
I'll work on it.
Diets are so hard, there's so much conflicting information.
I get, I get, yeah, it's like, you can, you can read two different books on the subject
and come away with completely different answers to what is a healthy diet.
It's interesting we're talking about diet, because that was what I was going to bring
the table and say that I'm sorry, Ben, but I'm abandoning, I think I'm going to abandon
keto.
I think I'm pivoting into paleo.
I think I'm, I'm continuing my bio-happiness family.
I love paleo.
I don't even do anything.
Paleo is just about feeling better than other people.
Is that so?
But, but, but before we move on completely.
All diets about that though, really?
The best diet.
I mean, I like paleo in the sense that it discourages bulk grains, which I don't believe
in.
Absolutely.
I don't know if this will sound cruel or not, Nate, but I don't mean in such a way.
But I kind of forgot that you were like, yeah, you're like the fitness guy, I guess.
I forgot about that for a while.
That's fine.
For a while, that was like your characteristic is that you were the fit person who, you know,
did anime reviews, I guess, but I kind of forgot about the fitness part until just now.
Well, that's perfectly acceptable.
And I mean, I think what that really speaks to is not really that I've gotten much worse,
because I'm actually on an upswing currently.
But it's a, it's that everyone else is up to their game.
So I stand out less by comparison.
And while that's unfortunate for me, it is good overall.
Yeah.
But I'm switching.
I like Keto a lot.
I lost a ton of weight.
I'm down, I think 15 or 16 pounds in like five weeks, which is pretty good.
So why would you stop then?
Okay.
Because I feel sick constantly.
That makes sense.
Ever since I've started Keto, my stomach has felt an agony.
I've had like heart palpitations all the time.
Don't really want that anymore.
Well, that's just life, man.
Listen, Tom, listen, Tom, you're 30 now and that's, and happy birthday, by the way.
That's just, that's just the rest of your life.
I tried Keto for a while and it hasn't really worked for me, but I think it might be due
to the fact that I don't have a gallbladder.
So I can't really process the fat too well.
I read that, like, you know, you can't do Keto.
I don't know what gallbladder does.
I don't think so.
Well, and it produces the thing, it produces the thing that helps you digest fat, I think,
or something like that.
I don't know.
I'm not, I'm not, I'm not a, I'm not a biologist, but I read that you can do Keto without a
gallbladder, but it's kind of different.
I don't, I don't see why you wouldn't, although I guess you'd probably have to ask a doctor.
My understanding was that the gallbladder was, was a thing that helps to digest, like,
fibrous stuff and plant matter better, that is harder to digest in the body.
I, I could be wrong.
Wait, are you thinking of the appendix?
Oh, I'm thinking of the appendix, yep.
My bad, my bad.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, okay.
The appendix is like, someone, I read that, like, the, what the appendix was for is back
in caveman times, when you would have a pile of berry, like loose berries on the ground
and you would scoop them up along with like dirt and rocks, and you would eat it all at
once.
Your appendix would secrete some kind of substance that would coat the rocks that you ate along
with these precious berries with some kind of goo that would prevent them from tearing
open your anus on the way out.
Or something.
It's funny, it's funny.
Yeah, but we don't need it anymore because we don't eat rocks anymore or something.
The last, like, 30 seconds, the call just cut out and started like nothing but gibberish
and then immediately cuts in and it's, and then you say anus on the way out, just anus.
I don't know what I missed.
Out of context, out of context.
Yeah, yeah.
This is like, silence, silence, signus, tear your anus open on the way out.
Yeah.
I was like, okay.
Yeah, this is a horrible nightmare.
If it sounds like we're interrupting each other, it's because everyone's speeding up
and slowing down and cutting out randomly at an unheard of time.
I am also getting that, yeah, it sucks.
Clean.
Hey.
If anyone's got a...
Wait, wait.
Nobody heard my Garfield-ism that I threw out there in the middle of that cacophony.
I said, the best diet is depression.
And then fucking Garfield stands up from his bed box and he's emaciated as fuck.
And then he looks forward at the viewer and says, Mondays.
That's how they all end.
They all end the same way.
So, Jesse, are you just going to make better Garfield comics now?
Is that like your new role?
Because you've already had like three good strip ideas just in the last 20 minutes.
Yeah.
Well, I'm imagining like they end on sort of a Ren and Stimpy-esque hyper-detailed
close-up of his face saying Mondays.
This is good.
I don't know.
Well, I just realized that I am Garfield and that's literally who I...
I mean, aren't we all Garfield on some level?
That's his appeal.
He speaks to all of us in a way.
Yeah.
All of our worst instincts.
We're all just trapped on the window of a moving car down the fucking highway to hell.
And it's Monday.
Fuck.
We're all trapped in these bodies that will eventually decay and die and get fat first.
What is that noise?
Whose fucking dog is janglin'?
Yeah, what's a jingle jangle?
Sorry, it's Odie again.
I'll just get him off the fucking table.
It could be my cat's bell.
I'm sorry.
He's hungry and I cannot go and feed him at the moment, so he's going to be a nuisance.
Oh, when he's hungry, he's just going to bring a bell.
Cats hunt for themselves.
No, he has a bell on his neck.
Oh, okay.
On the collar.
Is it like a choker?
Like an emo choker?
No.
He's got a thought collar.
Yeah.
You know, this has bothered me for years.
And I've never said it out loud, but I'm finally going to own up to it.
This might make me unpopular to posit this controversial thought.
It bothers me that Odie's retarded.
Well, here, I mean, the thing about that is all your people are being poorly represented.
No.
Oh, got him.
And this is me talking, not Garfield, even though I'm sure Garfield feels similarly.
Because there's other dogs in the Garfield universe and they're not stupid.
So why is Odie stupid?
I was going to say, is he retarded or does he just have different priorities than Garfield?
He's almost always depicted as extremely retarded, though not always.
He's a mute.
Like all the other animals at least can communicate with each other.
But Odie's just like-
My favorite piece of Garfield lore is that Odie is not John's dog.
He is Lyman's dog.
Oh, yeah.
Who's Lyman?
Lyman?
Okay.
It's like in like pretty early on in the comic, John's friend Lyman moves in with them for
a while and he is this mustached dude and he brings Odie with him and he just is there
for a while and then he eventually like goes off to join the Coast Guard of the Navy or
something and no one ever hears from him again, but he just leaves Odie and now Odie
lives with him.
But no.
Odie is Lyman's dog.
Look up Lyman.
You know, John coveted that dog so much.
He's so coveted, a companion for Garfield that one night he snuck into Lyman's room
while he was sleeping.
Yeah, yeah.
And like stabbed him to death and buried him under the floorboards and said, oh yeah,
he just, he went off to join the Navy.
Yeah.
Someone comes to ask about it and he's like, oh no, this is my dog.
I've had this dog forever.
This is my dog.
Yeah.
He's all-
Oh, yeah.
Odie's like, where's Lyman's John?
You know, you can see it in his eyes.
And like, you know, where am I going back home?
And John just looks at the camera and says, you've always been here, Odie, you've always
been here.
And then da-da-da-da.
Zoom in on a fly.
And then slow zoom in on John's face.
Slow zoom in on John's face.
You've always been here, Garfield, music sting.
Slow zoom in on Garfield, Mondays.
And so-
Cut to black.
Roll credits.
Better to make sure that Odie doesn't rat about what John did to Lyman.
John gives Odie a lobotomy, and that's why Odie became-
Oh my God, it's so stupid.
Yeah.
So the dog doesn't rat him out.
Yeah, you know, really, John was the one who was truly Odeous.
Oh.
Welcome, full circle.
Oh, and also he baked Lyman into a lasagna and he fed it to Garfield.
That's also a thing.
Oh, sure.
Hey, hey, you would get so many lasagnas out of the meat of an entire person.
That's all I'm saying.
That's true.
There's very little meat in the lasagna to begin with.
You would have to be- you'd have to be some meaty lasagnas, they're just going to take
you along.
You're going to have Lyman in the freezer for quite some time.
I think Garfield found like a finger bone or a toe, like halfway through the lasagna
and realized, but he just loves lasagnas so much and he just-
Yeah.
He already had that taste.
He's shoveling it in.
No, he loves lasagna.
He's like this, right?
John knew that Garfield loves lasagnas so much that he would find the finger, eat it
anyway, and then be so consumed by guilt that he would now feel complicit in the murder.
So he would never say anything.
Oh my God, John.
Makes sense.
He's smart.
If there's one thing I miss from being a brony, it's all of the shit, terrible, gore, creepy
posse to fan fiction that you could read, and there was just a whole library full.
There was just a whole fucking boatload.
There was a library of Alexander worth of pure knowledge that you could just unearth at any
moment.
Take you back to the rainbow factory, duckball.
Exactly.
Take me back to fucking Party of One, take me back to that shit.
Yeah, Party of One.
No, Party of None.
Sorry, Party of None.
Right, right.
So there's even less than one now.
At the end of the day, that was pretty much the thing about My Little Pony was just how
active and just how prolific the fan base was.
In fact, I would say, tell me if you agree with this, Munchie, that pound for pound,
per capita, the only fandom that is as prolific as My Little Pony might just be Endless War.
Well, okay, okay, we have to adjust for inflation and for how long they've been alive.
I would say you've got, okay, I'm talking per capita, like, like in terms of, in terms
of like, works, work, like fan work per person per second.
You know what?
Okay, I would agree with you.
The only rival there, and I think the true successor is Furries, though I feel legitimately
that Furries is Jean, because it's so decentralized.
It's not really a fandom of anything.
It's not like a, you're not a fan of anything, if you're afraid.
You're just a fan of being a freak, I guess.
That's your one calling, that's what you want to do.
The Furries thing is too much.
I'm calling for it to be over immediately, cease and desist.
I'm done with Furries.
I don't know, man.
That's got momentum.
That's got some like cultural momentum behind it.
The fact that it's like become a community and a subset of people, like a category of
human, upsets me.
Jew, Gentile, Furries.
Because now you can't joke anymore about like a cartoon animal character being attractive,
or else you're a furry.
Like it used to be, everybody made those jokes.
Everybody was fucking, oh yeah, fucking Lola in Space Jam is hot as fuck.
Everybody used to be into that.
Everyone believed it, but now everyone's afraid to admit it, because as soon as you say that
maybe Lola is fucking a hottie, well then, it opens the floodgates with the Furries come
out and they go, you're one of us now.
You're one of us.
And they fucking, they slap that big giant head on your head, and they push you down
a corridor, and they keep like adding parts of the furry costume as you're walking down
this corridor with no other way out, and they're whipping you with chains, and they're hurling
insults and throwing rocks at you.
Oh dude.
It's a gauntlet.
And it makes you one of them.
Remember the one where that like Marine is getting strapped into like his power armor
suit in preparation for Starcraft?
It's like that with a fur suit, and then it comes out, hell, it's about damn time.
Yeah, it's like a prune.
I want to go to Furry Convention just to see what it's like.
I want to know what it's like on average races, and you know what will happen?
I'll go there, I'll get all suited, I'll get all tatted up.
Oh, brief segment, I'm actually writing a 400 page fan fiction.
It's been an AU slash sequel to the How to Train Your Dragon series, and it's just exactly
the same.
It's like dragons are actually metaphor for tattoos, and it stars Hiccup who's been
renamed to Tatlis at the beginning of the movie, and he has to overcome the sphere by
Baguina tattoo.
Anyway.
That was the most zoomer sentence anyone's ever spoken.
You know what?
Anyway, enough of that.
That was all in parentheses just then.
I just figured out some men would hang out.
It's going to be the same as any other convention, it's just going to be like people just hanging
out, kind of being bored, being like, oh, what panel do you want to go to?
Nothing, I just kind of want to hang out, and then the other person's like, yeah, okay.
Furries, I don't think you're going to be that weird in person.
I want to go anyway, I want to see what it's like.
Only after, only behind closed doors.
Just now, while you were talking, I figured out the metric, the test of whether or not
someone is a furry.
So they made a Looney Tunes show a couple years ago.
It was like a sitcom update of the Looney Tunes.
Oh, god, yeah.
This is exciting.
Clines and Daffy are like-
No, what was it called?
I don't remember the name, but I know the one.
But Lola Bunny was in that show, but they had updated her to be more contemporary and
more fitting with today's feelings on what a cartoon sexy bunny should be.
So they made her less overtly sexualized and less busty and buxom.
Lola Bunny in Space Jam is a dystopian nightmare.
She's the pinnacle.
You can say she's a nightmare, but she's definitely sexualized.
Well, not herself.
I don't understand.
But the way that she is just this sexualized token female who is defined by being better
at everything than all men, and all men are immediately get heart eyes and swoon and fall
over at their boners because she is present.
It's regressive, but it does have merit because she is hot.
Sure.
So here's-
So granted.
So in this new contemporary Looney Tunes show, they toned down her sexuality.
They toned down how hot she is, but they made her more of a character with a zany personality
to match bugs and daffy and stuff.
So I think the test of whether you're a furry is if you're attracted to Space Jam Lola,
you're not a furry.
But if you're attracted to the new Lola for her personality, you're definitely a furry.
Wasn't New Lola, in that version, wasn't she like a sort of neurotic, obsessive stalker
girlfriend or something?
Yeah, I think so, yeah.
Okay, gross.
She was like the attached girlfriend meme.
So I guess I'm definitely not a furry.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, I don't know if this is allowed to be shown, if we can link this safely in the
show notes, but I really want this T-shirt.
It caps me walking down the street with this fucking T-shirt on.
This is awesome.
She's crying.
It's so huge, and it's the entire body is taken up with that image.
Why is it on a T-shirt?
It's just so inappropriate.
Munchy, you need to buy this shirt and wear it to the furry convention you go to.
Oh my god, yeah!
I want to wear it.
I mean, there's nothing technically showing.
I think her cheeks are covering up.
Is that not her little bunny pussy showing?
No, she's wearing it.
I don't want to zoom it in to find out.
Well panties are clinging to it in a way that tech...
You know, it's a little hard to say honestly.
The geometry is questionable.
I'm going to post a link to anyone who wants to buy this below.
I'm going to buy it.
I'm going to use our Amazon affiliate link to buy this T-shirt of Bugs Bunny Spanking
Lola.
Woo!
That's utterly expressed.
I guess to those who haven't clicked it, it's Bugs Spanking Lola sexually over his
knee.
I just said that on a T-shirt.
On a T-shirt.
That's a T-shirt that I would wear in a music video while having post Malone tattoos on
my face.
That's right.
Oh dude, there's another variant.
You'll see if you click that link where her ass is more red.
Like she's gotten more wax.
Oh, it's the sequel.
Yeah, it's the sequel.
It's like five different ones for each weekday.
It kills the question, we do a proper progression through the week.
You start with the first one of her just standing next to him, then the second one of her bent
over.
You pull down the panties, then getting redder and redder.
Progressively redder.
At some point, tears form under her eyes and it starts to be less hot, but it keeps going.
And then in the last one, she looks at the viewer and says, Mondays.
I'm like, where's the tat shop and get tatted up and they're going to be like, what kind
of tattoo do you want?
I'm just going to put on my sunglasses and not respond to them.
And just wait for me to wake up from my cocaine and do stupor and just wake up and then find
out how many tats I've got with this sick ass shirt because I guarantee they're going
to give me like five for free because they're so aroused.
I'm sure that's true.
Speaking of fandom in general, I just wanted to say that I played DeVoo's game, Autominus.
Oh, I want to stream that.
I want to stream that game myself playing it.
You should.
It would be good.
Yeah.
It'd be pretty good for that.
I just want to say, I honestly loved it and it was great.
So great job, DeVoo.
So here's my endorsement.
Everyone really should play it now that I have played it.
Took me like an hour and a half, maybe, or two hours or something.
I'm pretty intrigued.
I'm pretty intrigued by it.
I feel like I should.
I saw it and I meant to be like, jump on it.
I don't know.
But you know.
Life goes on.
The download link wasn't there when I first went.
But now it is.
So I played it.
I'm about halfway through it right now.
It's great.
I wanted to play it.
It was like, it looked cool and it's like, it's a DeVoo game.
So I'm like, I want to play a game about DeVoo.
He's my friend.
And so I got my stuff set up.
I was going to record it.
I was going to do like a let's play of it.
It's fucking, you know, ruin it for myself.
Like I do everything because you're fucking recording and you don't enjoy it as much.
But I was going to do that and I was fucking, I tried to download it and it wouldn't download
it.
Like set off my antivirus shit and I couldn't figure out how to do it.
Oh, wait.
I got the same thing.
Yeah.
Do you use AVG by any chance?
No, mine was a vast.
A vast antivirus.
Yeah.
I had to.
I remember I got that.
I had to like go into settings and create like a specific exception for like this file
path or something.
I gave up.
Totally.
I went back to bed.
Like my, like it's fucking Mondays, dude.
Yeah.
Like I can do, I can do anything no matter how complex it is as long as you warned me
beforehand.
But like if there's one unexpected step, I'm done.
I'm fucking out.
Like don't make me do one thing more than I thought I would do.
Get it.
I don't want to do it.
I'm going back to bed.
I'm getting back into my fucking anxiety blanket because that one extra step just fucking gave
me a mental breakdown.
Oh, wait.
No, you know what I did?
I just, I just disabled my antivirus.
That's what you got to do.
That's what I tried to do.
You just got to turn that shit off for a minute.
Which Davoo should probably, I don't know if there's a way around that, but like if
we both have that problem, I couldn't even find like where to disable it.
I found a thing that says like put it on passive and like that sounds kind of disabled, but
that didn't work.
It still wouldn't let me play it.
I might be able to, hmm, if I, if I, so it's an EXA, right?
If I put it in a zip file and put it online, you might be able just to download that, which
I wouldn't be for everybody, but like I could easily probably share that with you guys.
That might get you past that first thing and then just unzip it and then it might work.
I do that at work a lot.
Yeah, maybe.
I don't see how that, aren't you just downloading the EXA directly from itch?
Well, I mean, I mean, whatever, they're having a problem getting the EXA, but if they're
just given like a Google Drive link to a zip file that contains an EXA, your antivirus
will miss that and not, uh, generally.
I mean, that's, I do that sometimes.
All right.
You know, okay, but in the furries, back on the subject of furries, I have more to say
on this.
The point of this was, Davoo, I loved the game.
It was great.
I had one huge complaint with the game.
A gigantic problem.
Is it a spoiler?
Should I cover my ears?
This is not a spoiler.
No.
Okay.
In very slight indirect terms, it kind of is, but not really.
It's that, okay.
So the game is great.
Love it.
Get all the way to the end and the thing is, at no point in the game is there any kind
of fail state.
There is a save game mechanism that you can use to save and turn it off.
And this game is, you know, it's like an hour to two hour game.
It's easily done in one sitting.
Okay, so when I'm playing the game, I saved it at the beginning just to like try out saving,
just to like see how it works, already going above and beyond.
But then I didn't, there was no need to save at any point past that end of the game.
At the very end, when you've done everything, there is something like sort of kind of a
final boss type event.
And the thing is, it's the only time in the game where there is a fail state, which brings
you, there's no do-overs.
You just get like kicked back to the main menu after restart from your save file.
But here's the thing, I didn't save the fucking game since my test at the very beginning and
I was not conditioned by the game to be taught that saving was necessary because there was
no failure states.
It should give you like, it should give you like a, it should save.
So I literally lost 100% of my progress playing the game.
It should give you like a, there's no turning back from this point.
Do you want to save?
Something like that would have been good.
Or even if there was just some sort of continue state, like a do-over of that final thing,
that would have been fine as well.
But no, I just got fucked.
And I, like, I want to do it again, but I'm like, Jesus Christ, I really liked it.
But do I immediately want to use another hour to get through the game again?
I don't know.
Yeah.
Probably not.
So I went online and okay, one spar, one spar is the only man in the world who's made
a let's play so far, so I could just watch the final cutscene because I'm already too
good.
I spent more time doing this.
One spar hasn't uploaded the final part of the let's play.
Just do it one spar, release the fucking video.
Who was once known as Wolfspar.
That's right.
Okay.
So Jesse, actually I would have really appreciated a let's play.
So I need this let's play to exist so I can see the end and figure it out.
You know, I also, I think, you know what, I think, I think I'm actually going to stream
that tonight because I am streaming tonight as I do on Sundays for the ending on Twitch,
twitch.tv slash stcomics.
Go follow me.
And I will, so by the time you're listening to this, dear viewer, I will have already
streamed it.
It will be on my videos page.
Thank God.
Yeah.
I don't know if this is better or worse than the spanking shirt, but this one is like a
bad fusion of Bugs and Lola.
A fusion, you say.
This is the same one.
No, it's not.
Okay.
It's not showing the one I linked or the one that I clicked on.
Oh, there's like other versions.
Yeah.
There's a bunch of different shirts in there.
One of them is just, wait, well, oh my God, wait, I will figure this.
This is important.
Yeah.
There's a whole, oh my God, this one, that's just her face on like an R&D shirt and her
face blends into it.
It is really weird.
There's a lot of weird ones here.
Oh my God, this like dark purple one with like sort of a pink gradient on it has like
a really badly drawn version of like Bugs giving her a piggyback ride.
Yeah.
Here we go.
I fucking, this is the one I was talking about.
Oh my God.
What the fuck is that?
What the fuck?
That's like more of what that's hot dude to me than the spanking shirt.
Like that is.
I put it on a t-shirt.
Unironically, that is somebody's fetish.
Like I would, no, and not, not a joke.
I would wear the spanking shirt because it's hilarious, but I can't, I can't conceive of
a reason I would wear this weird fusion shirt.
Not even fusion.
Like they're conjoined in this.
They're fucking.
Lola Bunny.
Lola Bunny is a weird anomaly of a character that just like popped up one day in Space Jam.
You know what it was?
It was like the Hollywood bigwigs who were making Space Jam were like, oh, we got to,
we got to get something for the, for the boys to watch.
We got to get a character that would be like what, but we got to make it a cartoon.
Okay.
Just, just make a fucking female Bugs Bunny.
But they didn't know the power they were dealing with.
They didn't know the, the power of the Chaos Emeralds they were toying with, they would
create this incredible sexual nexus of energy that was Lola Bunny that has been twisted
and perfected.
No, they knew.
I, I kind of, it seems like the next is Robin Hood, Robin Hood came first.
Okay.
I thought, I thought it was Nala from Lion King, but I guess that is the perfect way
to describe Lola Bunny, a nexus of sexual energy.
It's true.
She's like a blood-borne creature where like when you look at her with zero insight, you're
like, oh yeah.
I mean, okay, cute bunny.
And then like, as you start to look at more furry shit, like you, you start to get more
concerned about what you're actually looking at.
All that raw sexual power coalescing at the center of the universe, like a black hole.
It's like an ultra dense apocalyptic event.
These t-shirts is illegal or something because like, they're just taking fan art and putting
it on.
But what method of curation are they making these?
Are these like, they feel randomly generated.
They don't feel like they're even like, these feel like they were made by anything.
Who's really going to go to court to protect their drawing of bugs?
The same, the same supercomputer that churned out Spider-Man carrying pregnant Elsa to the
hospital in a wheelbarrow is churning these out.
That's true.
I feel like at the, when you, at the end of spore, we were all disappointed, you know,
you build up your universe, you acquired new civilizations, you obtain enlightenment through
whatever means, and then boom, you finally make your way to the center of the universe.
And originally it was just going to be Lola Bunny, the center of all power and commerce
and culture.
But they were like, the people aren't ready for this, the people just aren't ready.
So then you just start over and you continue the quest eternally.
I have a game rant, I have an angry rant about a video game, since you were talking about
another one.
Fucking, so I downloaded the re-release of Castlevania Symphony of the Night on PS4.
Yeah.
And we all know that game.
Oh no, I know where you're going.
Okay, all right, all right.
So everybody knows the dialogue at the beginning of Symphony of the Night.
Die monster, you don't belong in this world.
It was not by my hand, it was who was that fucking did the thing, and you bitch.
Yeah.
Enough talk, have at you.
They fucking changed the dialogue in the re-release, they re-recorded it, they rewrote all of it.
What the fuck?
This idea that the old dialogue is hokey now, or is it good?
Oh, hey, I'll bet the game would be way better if we changed this classic dialogue that everyone
remembers, everyone would appreciate that.
The new dialogue isn't even better, it's just as hokey in its own way, so there was no point
in changing it, it didn't make it better.
What was the new dialogue?
It's totally, I mean it's not memorable at all.
Is the original Miserable Pile of Secrets?
They changed that.
They changed it to be less hokey and trying to make it sound more natural in English,
but it doesn't, it just sounds weird in a different way.
But Symphony of the Night is where what is a man, a Miserable Pile of Secrets comes
from, right?
Yeah, they just made it totally bland, they removed all the soul and all the fucking fun
from it, they sucked all the fun out of it to make it more fucking good, I guess.
This is a total example.
Feels like they would just re-record lines solely to get some voice actors a paycheck,
you know what I mean?
I was just thinking, literally what is the motivation to redo this literally iconic
scene in video games?
I think it might be a friend of the developer or whatever, like a voice actor guy wants
a paycheck, let's re-record the lines and get him one.
I think it's worse than that, they probably think, and worse than that, they probably
think rightly so, that if they didn't change it, some snarky reviewer on some website
somewhere would be like, well the dialogue clearly doesn't hold up and it's fucking
bad now and it's all hokey and queer and gay, but they wouldn't say queer because you can't
say queer now.
But they'd, you know, in so many words, they'd call it queer and gay.
Yeah, of course.
Well it is queer and gay and I like it that way.
Yeah, and I love it.
And it's fucking...
It's fucking...
I don't know.
It would be one thing if like, when they remade Resident Evil they changed the dialogue and
that to be less silly, but that's because, you know, that was a remake, it was a full
from the ground up.
The whole game was...
I have to go feed my cat because he's gonna make noise the whole podcast when you're back.
Like the point of a re-release is supposed to be to preserve these works of art for future
generations or for the current generation that wants the convenience of being able to
play it again.
I could go into the other room if I wanted, take out the disc, plug in my PlayStation
again and set it up, but I'm already in bed, man.
I want something on my PS4.
I want the convenience.
I want something that I remember preserved forever and then I put it in, I paid twenty
dollars for it and it's not like how I remember it and I don't like things that have changed.
That's it.
That's my being mad for today.
But Jesse, just don't worry about it though.
Like it's for new people, right?
You just need to shut the fuck up.
It's the new generation.
Yeah, you idiot boomer.
The new generation needs to experience these classics.
It's not for new people.
Fuck the new generation.
It's for me.
It's all for me.
You know, okay, it's true.
That does extremely disturb me and make me want to kill myself.
But the good news is that I believe this repackage also comes with Rondo of Blood, which I want
to play so that I might do that.
Yeah, I played a little bit of Rondo of Blood and I'm like, it's too fucking hard.
I just want to play the game that I've played before a thousand times.
I mean, I love the, I mean, I'm a huge fan of all the MetroVanias.
I played literally all of them and love them.
Old Castlevania is fucking hard.
I mean, when I was making my Castlevania video, I was like, I feel guilty having never played
a single Simon Castlevania game making this video.
So I'm going to go do that.
And I did.
And it was really fucking hard.
And I could beat it.
Tom, Tom, when me and Munchy were over for for I Am Games and you guys were playing that
like, what was it?
It was like, the Castlevania kickstarter, but it was like the side project like like eight
like 16 bit.
Yeah, it looked.
Yeah, yeah, that game looked pretty fucking cool.
I mean, right.
Art looked really amazing.
I actually did almost beat that game for that game.
I actually did get to the final boss.
I've got it on switch.
I look, I meant to go back and beat it.
So in that way, I kind of have almost beaten like a classic Castlevania, even though it's
not a Castlevania.
It's a new fucking thing.
But that game is not a Castlevania.
No, it's it's by Iga or Igarashi, the guy who made Simply In The Night.
Oh, right, right, right.
He's a new boy.
He's a separate boy.
This talk of like re-releasing games, making them different and updating them has got me
thinking about Let's Go Pikachu and Eevee, which released just like a couple of days
ago.
I've been seeing a friend play that lately.
What do you think, Lads?
Well, it's bad.
The fact that they think, I've said this a thousand times in its old hand, but they
think that for some reason, the new generation is just stupider.
The only thing they can think is that the new generation is stupider than what came before.
So this is a remake of Yellow, and everyone played Yellow as a kid, or all the millennials
did.
I thought it was just fun, and they got, and this is children who are doing this, children
who grew up with, you know, the anime.
They play Yellow, and it's a fucking fine time.
No one rides in streets.
No one's like, um, but how do I get past the search?
How do I find the batteries in the trash can?
I don't understand.
Because Pokemon is fucking too easy.
It's way too hard.
Even if you continually lose against a gym leader, you'll still gain experience if you
kill any of their Pokemon, and you'll just eventually overpower them and win.
But for some reason, they think, no, guys, Pokemon has to be for the kids now.
You millennials, you 20-year-olds, you've had your chance with Pokemon.
Now it's time for the children to play Pokemon.
We need to make this game baby game, because it's for the children, okay?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
are you as cool in my head Jesus Christ?
No, you're trying to be yerde
No
your your bif behold
OK, go on
I want to hear it
what's fun about Pokemon Let's Go, is that it's the game that you know and
you can play it again and like they've re-done everything and like oh like wow I can see like this
modern 3ds graphics and this old like fucking location and it's just it's the
Pokemon catching is like Pokemon Go
but it's still fine, like you get experience
for catching them.
That doesn't sound like fine.
I'm being swayed back to the other guy's side now.
Well, I mean, it's, because like,
you get experience for how well you catch the Pokemon,
so like you get party experience and stuff.
It's a bad experience for catching Pokemon.
Everything, they changed.
Everything, they shit's different.
Okay, I know.
Everything that's different about Pokemon, let's go.
From mainline Pokemon, it makes it worse
and like takes away from what I like about the game.
The fact that you can like access your box at any time
is a great change.
It's a great improvement.
I, Tom, listen, no offense, but I hate you.
That's fine.
Your opinion sounds pretty shit to me right now too.
So like we're just on different wavelengths.
That's fine.
Okay, well, hang on, hang on.
I think there might be at least some disconnect here
because honestly, a lot of what I've seen in Pokemon,
let's go, seem like really good things
that we would want in a Pokemon game.
Like just the idea of being able to see the Pokemon
like on the map and then touch them.
Like that's cool.
It's okay, I guess.
I like that.
Yeah, first of all, I disagree with the idea
that the younger generation deserves Pokemon.
I don't think they do.
I don't think that kids deserve it.
They already have it.
They already have it anyway.
I'm upset.
I've been waiting my entire life
for a home console Pokemon game with like modern graphics
and you can sit on your couch,
you lay in your bed and play it on the TV screen.
Been waiting my whole life for that.
They finally make one and I look at it
and it's got like Pokemon ghost shit in it
and they did it wrong.
They finally did it and they did it wrong.
Just to spite me and just to give it to the...
Next year, what everybody wants is coming next year.
Ultra Sun and Moon are on the switch.
They announced Pokemon, let's go.
They said the mainline series is coming next
and that's gonna have all the regular mechanics.
This is not a replacement.
It's just a comfy co-op game where you can relive
your first Pokemon adventure.
This game is for some reason-
It's fucking kill me,
fucking kill me instead of that.
No, you're a fucking idiot
because you're playing this game for the wrong reason.
If you're saying like,
I wanna like fucking do a hardcore Nuzlocke run
in Pokemon, let's go.
Hey, I know.
Not why you play this.
Let's play a Pokemon game.
Let's play a Pokemon game where you go on an adventure
and catch monsters and become the very best
like no one ever was, only, only.
Let's make it so you don't have to fucking
think about it at all.
That sounds great.
It's not even that you don't have to think about it.
It's, I mean, we're not-
Yes, it fucking is.
I've seen it.
You can literally, you can literally double team.
You can two on one enemy trainers.
You can fight their one Pokemon with two of yours.
And you don't have to do it.
It's just like, if you would,
like me and Digi just sitting there playing I Am Games,
just shooting the shit and we're just like,
oh, Digi wants to jump in and just like play the battle
with me because we're just,
we're just enjoying and having a good time.
It's not, like it's not a hardcore game,
but it's not a bad game because it's not a hardcore game.
It's just a casual, fun, like nostalgic experience.
Like the newest ad for Pokemon Let's Go
is literally a shot-for-shot remake
of the original like Pokemon TV theme
just done with in-game graphics.
So like this isn't like for new people.
It's for people who have good memories of this game.
Just want to play it again and have a good time
and just chill out.
And it's fine.
If that doesn't sound fun to you,
then this isn't your kind of game,
but that doesn't mean it's a bad game.
It's not.
No, Tom, let me stop you right there.
The fact that it is not my kind of game
does mean it's a bad game.
To you.
Because being bad means nothing
other than that I don't like it.
And because I don't like it, it is bad by definition.
I made a video about this on my YouTube channel.
Well, I don't like it for tearing people apart,
making us fight.
I don't like it.
Yeah, it's making us all yell.
Yeah.
So much for comfy.
I like how the stupid of the topic.
Yeah, I have nostalgia for old Pokemon.
No, I don't want to play some baby version of it
to relive those memories.
The stupid of the topic, the more political
and fervent the discourse becomes.
It seems like.
Yeah, it is.
It's true.
Like, before it was all like the fucking Garfield,
Monday's shit, and that was pretty stupid.
Then it was like, oh yeah, well, furry is.
And that was a little bit more stupid,
getting a little bit more heated.
But then you start talking about whether the new Pokemon
game is too much for kids or not.
And then all of a sudden it's like, well, let
me stop you're right there.
So no, no, no, let me finish.
Let me finish.
Let me say what I want.
You were invested.
Yeah, I am invested.
I just can't think of someone.
Because the more frivolous the topic,
the less afraid I am to have a strong opinion about it.
Here's the thing.
Pokemon Go players who haven't played the main series games.
I would say the majority of people who play Pokemon Go
have played the main series games.
Let's examine the people who haven't.
I know someone.
It's Kazzy's dad.
Is Kazzy's dad this fucking portly Bostonite going to be
like, oh, you know what?
I really want to get into main series Pokemon.
It's almost like the reason I play Pokemon Go is because
it's a mobile game.
And I can play it on my phone.
It's not like you can trust me.
You know what?
I really, really care about Pokemon now.
So I'm going to go out.
I'm going to buy like a $200, $300 video game machine,
which I'm going to play exclusively Pokemon on.
And that's what I'm going to do with my time and money.
I have time for this.
I agree that those people are not going to buy it.
But by the same token, you just said the majority of people
who play Pokemon Go play the main series.
So if you're already playing Pokemon Go,
and this game works with it, and you can trade guys
between it and stuff, like it's another game.
They would already be doing it all the time.
If you already play the main line series
and you have a functioning brain,
no offense, Tom.
Love you, love you, buddy.
But then you shouldn't like this new fucking remake.
Look, it's just a different kind of game.
And it's still fun.
It's just not the same kind of game as a main line series.
It's why it's not replacing it.
I mean, it's fun.
It is good.
I don't hate remakes as long as they're good.
OK.
But OK, this is a remake of a different style.
It's a different interpretation.
There's a value clash here for sure.
I am definitely not the kind of game.
Just wait for I am Games video, which is coming out probably
today or tomorrow.
And yeah, it'll explain that more.
Based on what you said, Nate, were you saying, Nate?
Well, I was just saying, I can already
guess the content of that video, which is I'm not saying,
oh, I don't give a shit.
I'm just saying, I already know there's clearly
a distinction between, I mean, I'm really not
a comfy gamer guy.
I'm really not.
I'm a like to be challenged guy.
I'm not saying I'm better.
It literally, objectively, doesn't matter.
I'm saying it, Nate.
I'm saying we're a higher breed.
We have a better pedigree.
We come from a better fucking casual mood.
I mean, no, no, no, no.
It's not even about being casual or any of that shit.
My opinion with video games has always been they're a great
friend.
You're a fucking doom fag.
From doing things I actually care about.
So I'm not going to sit here and spend all my time
100% think some incredibly hard game,
because I have more important things to do than 100%
a game that when it's done just goes back into the fucking shelf.
I play it because I'm playing on the street.
There's another factor here.
And it is basically, it is what direction is the Pokemon
company going?
Because I want them to go in a different direction.
They're making a, OK, here's the thing
that I'm also happy with about Pokemon Let's Go.
And I'll tell you why.
If they have, because they said during E3 when this game was
announcing everything, that they're
going to do this two-prong approach going forward
and see how it works.
So if they dump all the casual stuff into the Let's Go series,
then that frees up the main series
to be more hardcore and not have all the baby shit in it.
I would like that very much, but I have no faith at all.
I have no faith at all that that will happen.
I think they are lying or mistaken,
because I don't think they will do that.
There's no way.
Look at Sun and Moon.
There's no way they're going to stop the baby if it can't
design a Pokemon Let's Go series.
I don't know.
Then it sounds like fourth one is just
a shitty series that you guys shouldn't play anymore.
That's correct.
That is correct.
I go back and forth on this.
I feel like maybe, like we had the switch to 3D
in Gen 6, and then there was Gen 7.
And I didn't play Gen 6, but Gen 7 was pretty good,
but I don't think it was quite there.
I feel like in Gen 8, I don't know.
I feel like they might really nail it.
They might nail the formula in Gen 8.
I am extremely anticipating to see what development choices
they make in the next game, because I
think that'll tell us a ton of information about where
they're actually going.
I mean, if I'm looking at the series history
and I'm having to guess, here's my prediction.
They add a bunch of frivolous bullshit
that nobody cares about.
Remove a lot of features for no real reason.
Yeah.
Like maybe they add a new version of contests.
Wouldn't that be cool?
It is not a cynical position at all
to think that a series has declined,
because it's not like never.
None of us are happy right now.
None of us are like, oh man, it's so good to hate Pokemon.
We get such catharsis out of making bad reviews of Pokemon
or something.
I am not happy that Pokemon, to me,
has gone downhill in a way.
It's not even a new thing.
It's not even like I thought this for years or something.
This is an extremely new development for me.
I'm still in like a shock, like denial stage,
where I just think, wow, why is this happening?
Stop it, please.
High points of the series for me
were Black, White, Two, and Sparkle Souls.
And that wasn't that long ago.
That was like what?
Like a couple years ago.
That wasn't very long.
Yeah, four, five, six years ago?
Man, I don't know.
I don't know if it's gone downhill
or if I've gone downhill.
I mean, I didn't play Ultra Sun and Moon,
but I heard that they weren't much better than Sun and Moon
were not as good as White, Two.
I can't really keep track of them.
I mean, to me, it's like all the gents are the same,
like all the Pokemon gents.
I mean, they're all police officers.
They all look the same.
You know?
All the Pokemon gents.
You know, the gents and Pokemon.
Oh.
You fucking pheasant.
No.
Oh, damn it.
I was rubed.
I mean, is rubed a word?
Can you be rubed?
Sure.
Why not?
There's a game.
I think I'm at Ruzed.
There's a game that I have in my Steam library
that I come back to fairly regularly to play with friends.
It is called Yet Another Zombie Defense,
and it is $0.99.
It's a shit shovelware, like Steam, green light,
push through the doors as possible to turn a quick buck.
When you open up the game, the file on your computer,
like on Task Manager, it says My Game, all caps,
and it has an Xbox controller logo.
And it just is you are spawn in this like Unity graphics,
like only default settings.
Like, they didn't actually make any of their own models.
It's just like default shit, and you just shoot zombies forever.
And that's literally all the game is.
And that game, I could recognize, is shit, but I love it.
First of all, for, because it's funny, because it's hilarious.
It's called Yet Another Zombie Defense.
Like, even the title is exasperated at what it is.
But not only that, just because it's such like an easy game
that I can just call up Ethan whenever I want,
and I can be like, oh, dude, you up for it.
You up for the Yet Another Zombie Defense session.
He'd be like, oh, hell, yeah, we get past our high score.
We gotta get past night 20.
And then we can do that, and it'll be a great time.
And I feel like that might be the sort of thing
that you do, Tom, with this video game, where I don't,
I mean, I think it's a difference between you
thanking the game is bad or not.
But it's more about the social aspect of it
rather than the game itself being good or bad.
I'm just sick of playing games being easy.
Like, I was already way sick of it.
And now, a way more easy Pokemon game comes out.
And I know that's just me.
I know that's just me.
All the Pokemon games have been easy since the first one.
Yeah.
Well, look, there's a huge fucking difference
between the ease of like, sun and moon versus like, diamond.
But like, the writing's been on the wall forever.
That doesn't mean it's good.
And that just means my points are correct.
But it just means that after like two decades,
you're going to have to be like, I guess
this is just a simple game.
I hate this argument.
I hate this argument that we should just give up on Pokemon.
I'm not saying you should give up.
I'm just saying like, go and expecting
that it's probably going to be a simplistic game.
Like, I don't think, I agree with you.
I would like the challenge of red and blue back.
Because like, Pokemon red and blue
wasn't so challenging that I would just like, stop playing it
because I have better things to do.
It's like, enough like, oh, like, I actually
have to like, think and try.
And like, when they released Fire Red and Leaf Green,
I was like, ah, they made this way simpler.
Like, that game was still fun.
I still enjoyed it.
Because I'm like, whoa, it's like, better graphics and stuff.
And like, this is like, a deeper realization of the world.
It's interesting to see.
Like, is it better than the original?
No, but it's still an interesting experience
to see this again with different hardware.
Like, that's a cool experience to me.
And Let's Go's doing the same thing.
It's like, it's a new experience.
Like, we were talking on the stream
how like, there's so much more detail that like,
I know where I'm going, but it almost doesn't even
feel that familiar.
Like, if it wasn't, because did you
was saying how like, the level design of Let's Go
is still kind of like, geometric and right
angley, like the original Game Boy gamers.
But there's so much detail in it,
that it almost like, the visuals,
like the actual technical details of the visuals
are way better than like, Sun and Moon, for example.
But Sun and Moon were designed from the ground up
as a 3D game.
So the geometry and stuff is more organic
and less right angley.
So the actual like, level layouts
are more in depth in Sun and Moon.
So these like, level designs feel more basic
because they're based on 1996 Game Boy games.
But visually they look great.
3D, 3D was a mistake.
The series never looked better than it did in Gen 5.
And it never will.
I want, we've talked about Pokemon a lot
and I feel it always does come down to one thing,
at least for me.
It's true.
I mean, even if I want Pokemon to be good,
the proof is in the pudding.
Maybe the next games will really be something
that shakes things up.
Now that there's been a divide between hardcore
and soft core players, to whatever extent we'll find out.
But the real answer is, go play Crystal Clear,
go play the ROM hacks, that's the shit.
We should just all go play Crystal Clear.
And apparently that's the good one,
that everyone says to play.
I don't want to seem like a doom bringer here.
I don't want to seem like someone who's saying
the apocalypse isn't anything.
I don't think Pokemon has degraded to such a point
where I don't like it anymore or something.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I'm allowed to be mad, aren't I?
I'm allowed to be like, oh man,
things were better like a couple years ago.
Do I not earn that?
Do I not have that?
Sun and Moon weren't terrible.
They were just like, you know,
they were no black, white too.
They were just exasperating.
They were no hard-goal, soul, silver.
And that's a shame, it's a shame that the sequels
are not improving.
Yes.
For a while they were, every generation,
every generation from one to five
was a straight improvement at fact, hashtag fact.
I don't know about four.
Well, why not four?
Why not four?
I'm so fucking mad at you stupid millennials.
You don't fucking get it.
Shut up.
Physical special split.
Shut the fuck up.
A hard-goal, soul, silver were,
but the main like diamond pearl were not.
Yeah.
I didn't like diamond pearl that much.
All of your problems with it.
Three was a huge step down from gen two.
Three?
I don't know about that because just gen,
I mean, I skipped gen three,
but it added the physical special split, right?
Gen three took out the day-night cycle,
which was so cool about gen two.
They reduced the amount, like you only had eight badges
again instead of 16.
So the game was half the size.
And then in order to get like the evolutions
they debuted last gen,
you had to buy GameCube games
just so you could port them in.
Okay.
I understand.
And those trumpet sounds were fucking disgusting.
And to this day,
it sounds like nails on the chalkboard.
Halfing the game isn't good.
And they'd never been able to top that either.
But the immeasurable benefit of having like abilities
and natures and shit like that in battle,
completely revolutionized the battle.
Okay, here's the distinction.
In all of the best Pokemon games,
they kept adding more and more stuff
to the battling system,
because that's how you interact with the game.
Stop pretending that Pokemon isn't about battling.
Because that's literally all that you do in the game
is battle.
That's all you do.
Mechanically, the game has only improved
and I don't think it's ever slid back.
Oh, I wouldn't say, I think it has.
Man.
It's been bogged down.
I hate the natures and all the hidden stats.
It's just ruins the whole fucking experience.
No, those are, they add to the game
but you can ignore them if you want to.
No, they're like totally like, eh.
Nah, I don't like them.
Nah.
That's 10 out of 10.
I was gonna hate that more passionately,
but I fucking ran out.
I hate when people are like,
this comes a lot,
this comes a lot in smash community discussions
where it's like, why do you want the game to be competitive?
What, just fucking, it just turned your brain off.
It's just a party game.
I don't even, I don't want anyone else
to experience the game in any other way than my do.
A.K.A. I only ever want to play like four players
with Atom's on.
I fucked up the starting of this conversation so badly.
I'm not saying that you can't have parties
or anything like that.
I'm not saying anything remotely.
I'm just trying to say that it's fun
to play games competitively.
It's fun to try hard.
Devils advocate here, when you're at a party
and you're all playing Smash
and someone is really good, the party's ruined.
Well, just don't get that.
Okay, okay, first of all, nothing to do with the game.
Because I was Princess Peach and I killed Steve,
I killed all of Munchie's friends
and once with fucking in a display of power
yet unrivaled by man.
And we all had a great time
as I was destroying everyone
with my incredible Peach powers.
Having the game be balanced and be able to be competitive
does not detract from the party aspect in any way.
There's absolutely no reason to not have it
being competitively viable.
As a loyal Peach player, are you excited to play as Daisy?
Because I feel that strongly.
Didn't you see my video?
My E3 video, I was so excited, I sang from the heart.
Did I, maybe I missed it, but shit,
I don't know, I have to go watch it again if so.
Oh shit, yeah, I did a whole video about Daisy
and how cool it is and how excited I am and shit.
She's got like a weird side B.
I mean, what's the deal?
What is it?
Or it might be down, I forget which,
the one with its toad, it might be her neutral B.
She like swishes back and forth,
it's a really bizarre motion.
I am, honestly, Daisy is my number one character
I'm excited to play as.
I mean, I'm very excited to play as Daisy,
but I also feel a little bit of guilt
because Peach is like my best friend.
She's like the best girl.
She's like been there for me this whole time
and sometimes I'm gonna have to be a Daisy.
Sometimes, look, look, I can't be a one,
I can't be a one princess guy, okay?
I'm too cool for that.
I wonder, do you think, just quick aside,
do you think that the game or the fucking, the pro circuit,
now that like, smash ball charging stuff
is like a meter that gets charged,
is that gonna be like switched off for tournament play?
Or like, yeah, okay, well, all right.
I was gonna say, Daisy and Peach,
I think literally have the best one
because it both gets an instant kill
and they also can be fully healed,
which is just like the best combination of shit.
Yeah, there's no way they would ever allow
smash ball to turn into whatever.
In Eastergames, they switch to whatever.
Nothing more asinine and infuriating
and obnoxious in the world than being at a party
and everyone's playing Smash Brothers
and everyone's having a good time,
but there's that one guy who's like,
yeah, we gotta do a final destination, we know items.
Turn off the fucking items.
We gotta turn off the items.
It's not a real fight, it's not real competition,
it's not competitive.
First of all, I hate the items.
I hate them.
No, the items are, okay.
I vehemently disagree with the notion
that having items on is somehow less competitive
or less of a game of skill.
Yeah, I'm with you.
I'm with you, Jesse.
No, it's so much more random.
It's live, it's live.
Yeah, yeah, it's live.
It's random, but it's not.
It's random, it's fair.
Like, you still have to know how to capitalize on using it.
Yeah, I don't get it.
I don't get it.
I don't get the idea.
It's totally insane.
Mate, no, knowing how to use the items,
knowing it's a whole different skill set
that the final destination crew
just totally pretends doesn't exist.
I can't even take this armor seriously.
Yeah, like, yeah, you can get a lucky,
you can get a lucky drop, you, shut up.
You can get a lucky drop
and get a hammer and win because of it,
but I still think that the better player will win more.
Oh, wow, look, it's a Pokeball.
It spawned right in front of me.
I'll approve it, though it's Kyogre.
It helps the entire screen.
Oh, cool.
Like, you just get one Masterball spawn next to you.
You get it, and it's like, I don't know,
fucking instant win, Mewtwo, or whatever the fuck it is.
I don't know.
It's, that's silly.
Look, look.
Like, it's fine.
Here's the thing.
In a real combat. They're not bad.
In a real combat situation, you don't get to go,
okay, here are the rules and here's how I want them.
And if someone attacks you in a bar,
you're grabbing a bottle, you're grabbing a chair,
you're grabbing anything you fucking can
because that's competitive.
Bitch.
Yeah, okay.
Well, I mean, I actually practice what I preach,
AKA Bushido, and I believe in honorable duels.
So maybe look it up one of these fucking days.
I think the competition,
it's not like about a bar fight, it's a sport, you know?
He's right.
Yeah, it's a closed, sanitized environment.
The only sport that I believe in is professional wrestling,
where there are no rules
and anyone can do any stupid shit they want.
And that's the one true sport.
So somehow I've finagled my way into being right once again.
I'm a different breed, you see.
I'm a Zoomer.
I grew up with Smash completely different
than I see everyone describe it.
Here's how Smash Plane goes with me.
My friends come over.
We talk about the latest Smash tournament.
Then we go into 1v1s.
And it's a great time when we all laugh
and we all play like Friendly's 1v1.
Non-fountaination, we do a plethora of stages.
And it just is great because we're actually trying
and it's somewhat a competition.
And when we lose or win,
it feels good because we're with our friends.
There's no hard feelings or anything,
but we're still playing the game
like we're actually trying to.
And it's not just fucking easy, nothing matters.
That's how it was for me in college with my buddies.
There was always kind of in the back of our minds,
there was the idea that we're trying to get better
because we did participate in tournaments
every once in a while at college.
So there was that idea that we were grinding our skills
a little bit to try to up our game for that.
So yeah, I guess I was involved with the scene
at least a little bit.
So I was trying to play to that.
We turned off all the stages on the random selection
except for the ones that were tournament viable.
You know, shit like that.
Fuck yeah, dude.
Oh my God, it's gonna be so, okay, okay.
No more fucking, oh, Pokemon isn't good.
Listen, Smash Bros,
it's gonna be a little bit fucked up.
Listen, that's a short, but, but.
Oh my, I never in a thousand years
thought they would listen to this argument
because it wasn't like the most, you know,
and it's not like, oh, bring back wave dashes.
It's not the loudest things in the community.
But the fact that they have not fucking, you know,
final destination mode, not that they have bathroom mode,
but they have hazards off.
That you can turn off hazards and play on any map you want to
and have it not just like spawn weird boss battles at the time
or just change, like transform
into fucking bizarre awful versions of itself
over and over again.
Like you can just turn off hazards
on fucking WarioWare Incorporate.
You can go there and have the weird like pseudo battlefield,
you know, like it's like a block stage
with two extra platforms on the other side.
Oh, glorious.
I love that so much.
It's so good.
Me too.
I'm so bored.
I'm so fucking bored, you guys.
What?
Hey, Mage, how are you doing?
How was your week?
You haven't said anything in like an hour.
I wanted to say that you guys were so passionate about things
I didn't want to butt in.
No, who cares?
I like Pokemon.
You doing anything interesting this week, Mage?
No, no, I've been dead.
And then I had a whole bunch of mobile apps
that consumed my life for like forever.
Yeah, Mage is becoming a digital crazy cat lady
to reestablish before the podcast.
I have like four apps that are all different cats.
You're playing that Neco at Sumay?
One of the things, yeah, I have like four different apps
with cats of them.
And one was Dragons.
Well, I played Neco at Sumay a couple of years ago.
I think I deleted it at some point.
It's so cute.
But I replaced it with Matt.
For a while, I was really into Magikarp Jump.
You guys ever play Magikarp Jump?
Oh, yeah, I played it for a little bit.
Magikarp Jump was actually pretty fun for a while.
I like to turn off items when I play Magikarp Jump
competitively.
I just think they really have to disperse.
They introduced too much randomness into the fun.
Exactly.
My worst nightmare.
It's no longer a game of skill.
Guys, guys, guys, guys, my worst nightmare.
The thing I dreaded the most with Magikarp Jump
was like having my Magikarp get taken away by like a Pidgeot.
Is that a thing that can happen?
Yeah, there's a random chance.
You clearly did not play enough Magikarp Jump.
Yeah, you can fuck up and lose the game.
It can be stolen by a Pidgeotto.
It can be, there's one other thing.
It can evolve into a Gyarados.
And you can evolve it into a Gyarados, which
is the worst thing that can happen.
No, no, no, no.
Nate, you don't understand.
Gyarados are worthless because they can't jump.
They just fly.
Who the fuck cares?
This is a jumping competition.
Is this a thing where you have to avoid the rare candies
so you don't accidentally overlevel and become
a Magikarp Jump?
No, it's pretty hard to evolve them by accident.
But you sort of have to go out of your way to do it.
But if you do, you lose the game.
Or well, you don't lose the game.
You just have to start over with a new Magikarp.
That's a feature, though.
Yeah, there's some secret thing you got to do together.
Damn, I'm going to download Magikarp Jump right now.
I really like it.
I like how rooted and lore it is because there's one of the.
I have a deep lore of Magikarp Jump.
Well, it is, though, because one of the Pokedex entries
says that certain Magikarp that get old enough
can jump over mountains.
Does that happen?
Well, I mean, not in the game.
But the Pokedex does say that, yeah.
Well, I mean, but what's the lore relevance
if you don't actually jump over a mountain, then?
Well, I mean, the point is, what the fuck?
The point is that your Magikarp are jumping really high.
But you said the lore is that they jump over mountains,
but they don't do that.
So, man.
Are you fucking stupid?
The point is that they jump really high.
Jumping over a mountain is just an example
of how high and far they can fucking jump.
So the game is about jumping really high and far.
That's sad, though.
Why?
I mean, being an old Magikarp that never became a Gyarados,
it's like being an old virgin.
Yeah, I mean, that's true.
But the ones that become a Gyarados are like,
they're the exception.
I'm pretty sure that the way that the economy,
the ecology of Pokemon works,
like only like a very rare Magikarp,
actually becomes a Gyarados.
Maybe it's worse to be a Gyarados.
Maybe there's something that we're not privy to
in the life of a Gyarados,
because they've always got that twisted snarls.
They've got the mouth of it.
They've got dry mouth for days.
They've got a sore throat, dude.
They look so miserable.
They live under water, Munchie.
They can't jump.
They can't compete in the Magikarp Jump League.
They can fly, though, right?
Like as a kid, I'm like, oh, Gyarados is cool,
because he looks scary and angry.
But now I'm like, oh, man, Gyarados is living
with a lot of anger,
and I don't know if that's healthy for poor Gyarados.
Maybe Gyarados just has a resting bitch face.
I think it's a mental health issue.
We have to.
You know, that's true.
Yeah, I could believe that, too.
So I got a text the other day.
I know what to find out.
That enraged me.
It was from someone I don't know.
Already on there.
I'll just, I'll read the exchange.
I'll read the exchange that we had.
I get a text that's like,
where is it, where is it, where is it?
It's like two down.
Here we go.
It's a link.
It's a link to a GoFundMe,
and then it would help a tremendous amount,
if you donated, to my GoFundMe page.
And yeah, yeah.
So I clicked the link just out of curiosity,
and it's the name of some girl that I don't know.
I don't recognize the name.
It's a picture of what I presume is her and her boyfriend,
and it's like, help me escape
from my abusive home or something.
Okay.
And then, I didn't read the whole article.
There was something about, you know,
my mother says that it would be better
if I killed myself or something like that.
Have you considered she's right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I kind of wish I'd read the whole thing now
so I could go into more detail, but I didn't, whatever.
So I text her back, who is this?
She says, who are you?
To which I respond, you're the one
that sent me a request to donate to your GoFundMe.
No thanks, BTDubs.
And I was very upset, and I'm still seething.
I'm still seething with rage
that anyone would intrude upon my personal space like this.
It's disgusting, and I hate them.
Yeah.
Did they respond to that at all?
No, they did not.
But that was just yesterday,
so they guessed there's still time.
That is very rude.
So I guess you just like mass send out
to like all our contacts or something?
Just like, please donate to me stuff, something?
Maybe there's like some lists you're a part of,
and every time someone wants to mass send a text,
your number's on there.
It's called the government no fly list.
Oh, shit, you're right.
Those people got a lot of extra money kicking around
from all the flights they're not taking,
so they're a perfect candidate.
They can't escape and get an international number.
I just felt like an addiction to GoFundMe lately.
What? How so?
What?
Well, because like, you know, you see them,
every once in a while, someone on your Facebook
has like, oh, here's my uncle.
He was in a car crash, or here's my friend.
He needs a wheelchair or something like that, you know?
Yeah.
You're always seeing them, and just like,
I see the GoFundMe as a people who are in bad situations,
and like, I get this feeling inside me.
That's like, I'm not trying to virtue signal,
because it's not altruistic at all.
It's a feeling of, I have to be better than everyone.
I have to be better than people, so I have to donate.
I have to donate $100 to all of these people,
and I do.
Oh my God.
I donate $100 to each worthy cause that I find.
Dude, I'm sorry, but fucking gag.
If someone was fucking burned in an accident, $100.
If somebody was fucking broke their ankle
by slipping on ice, $100.
You all get $100, because I have to be better.
I'm better than people.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, Jesse, I'm not a GoFundMe.
I guess if they're burned, I don't know.
GoFundMe's for you, they're all to me, for no reason.
Here's, I mean, okay, I guess, like this article
did not convince me that this person's situation
was actually dire.
I guess I could kind of get it if I was really convinced
that someone's situation was really dire.
But at the same time, no matter how dire
someone's circumstances are, it's not my responsibility.
It like, it's not my responsibility to help people
that have been burned, or crippled, or are dying, right?
Like, there's a million of them in the world,
and I can't help them all, so why should I help any of them?
Now is a perfect time to reflect on the teachings
of one iron rand, because what you're describing
is exactly the mentality of the,
I forget what they're called, of the parasites,
or of the people who are manipulated by the parasites.
One should keep in mind that it is a virtue
to build oneself up, because it is only when you build
yourself up, and see that you are the optimal human being
that you can be, that you can then provide
the most value to those other people,
not that they deserve it, or anything,
self-interest is the most important factor in the world.
But, you know, it'll be objectively more useful.
Well, Ayn Rand was a crazy monster.
The reason to help one of them is that there's one person
who's more happier than you left them,
like, you know, when you started out.
Thank you, thank you.
But you'll just end up spending all your money on this shit.
All of your money, you donate a little bit,
you know, like, you might as well just go fund me.
You're not gonna, I'm not saying to spend your 401k
on this fucking person out of nowhere.
No, listen, you see one person who has these
bad circumstances, you feel bad, you donate the money.
But guess what?
There's a thousand more in the exact same
or worse circumstances that you didn't give money to.
And I'll get to them all.
Why did you give money to this one human being?
I'll get to them all eventually.
One day when I'm ready, I'm gonna fix the world.
I'm gonna fix them all.
The thing is,
is for some reason you resonated with that person
to go fund me just a little bit more.
I think the idea is,
there's no shame in that.
It's not what you're gonna want.
Then the reason you're donating, you're not donating
because of anything that you're donating
because their marketing was better.
Hey guys, guys, guys, guys, guys.
Yeah, what's, I don't understand what's wrong with that.
Stop rewarding failure.
Yeah.
Guys, I'm sort of on Jess's side.
I would like to help people, but the thing is,
a lot of people take the goodwill of other people
and use them like, you know, scams.
And they could say like,
oh, hey, I need a new wheelchair or whatever,
but they actually don't.
And they just use the goodwill of people.
And I don't want to be one of those people they get used.
And I feel sad that people do that.
I've never done that before.
Like, sure, I've donated to things before
and it's been bullshit,
but like that's just the risk you take.
Like if I had the choice,
if there's a cause that I believe in,
and I would rather like give the couple bucks
and like find out I got fucked,
then not do it and feel shitty about it forever.
Look, I would never say that everybody who's in need
is a bad person or won't use it responsibly.
But like, I get approached by homeless people a lot
in Cincinnati.
There's a lot of them asking for money.
And this is a real, I was hyperbolic before.
I was exaggerating, but this is a real point.
I never give any of the money specifically
because I really just have no idea who this person is
or like, if my giving the money will actually help,
will like, I'm actually facilitating a bad lifestyle
if I continue to do this.
Yeah, but it's true.
I don't know if it's actually going to help them.
But I think what Jesse's talking about,
if he's seeing these GoFundMe's on Facebook,
I'm assuming there's like some,
like you know them or you know the people who know them.
I get it, like I've been approached by bums
and there are like grifters and people who are dishonest.
You know, it happened to me
when I was with you guys in Boston,
that lady, I gave her $10 and she's like,
give me more, so I had to give her $20
and she was still like, well,
can you give me a little bit more
because I do have like five kids.
I'm like, lady, enough, get away from me.
You've made me mad now and now I regret helping you.
And like, when you get sort of like grifted like that,
it does like make you not want to help anyone else.
It's like, people who are shitty
and like take advantage of your kindness,
they're just sucking the kindness out of the world
because they're preventing you
from wanting to help anybody else.
But with the GoFundMe thing,
the examples I gave were real examples.
It's like, there was a guy who was burned
and a guy who needed a wheel.
And these are like, these are friends
that I know on Facebook.
So I know they're not scamming me or grifting me.
I know they're real people.
Okay, that is different.
I don't understand your argument, Ben,
about if you can't help them all, then why help one?
Because you're helping one person.
What is not self-evident about that?
I think the idea is that it's not a double standard
or anything.
This person that you're helping
does not deserve help anymore
than hundreds or thousands
or millions of other people.
Right, but you're in contact with them.
You know, I think the idea is that if everybody...
So what?
That's an accident.
That's an accident of fate.
And you don't owe them anything.
Well, no, you don't owe them anything.
This is about owing.
This is about you wanting to help someone.
Right.
Why would you want to help someone?
End of sentence.
Even if it's a stranger,
if it's a stranger who is like tangentially related
to a friend of yours,
I know that that's making my friend feel better
or more, you know,
so that's one less degree of separation where I can go.
If it's, listen, okay, okay.
If it's someone you know,
if it's someone who is like in your life somehow,
who is in your sphere,
that makes sense.
If I was rich, right,
if I had more money than I knew what to do with,
which is not even that much,
maybe if I had twice as much as I do now,
I would have more than I knew what to do with,
then maybe, right?
If I had disposable income
that would not go to any other thing.
But I don't.
I mean, I'm a big believer that money does not actually,
like people who win the lottery,
how it's so common for them to lose it really quickly
because they haven't built up the, you know,
much management.
I catch myself saying stuff like that.
It's funny how we're bringing up the idea of like,
being against charity when like the vast majority of us,
like a good portion of our income is basically charity.
It's not charity.
It is not charity.
I'm disgusted that you would say that.
Yeah, I mean, I pretty strongly disagree with that one.
I was gonna say that, but.
That's totally not true.
A lot of it.
No, no, no, no, no.
Tom, Tom, Tom, I was sort of thinking that,
but at the same time,
we are providing something in return in a sense.
We are producing content.
You're producing something, but it's free.
Like nobody has to pay for it.
They pay because they want to.
Tom, it's a different goddamn payment model
than traditional exchange.
That doesn't make it charity.
It's just that it's divided amongst.
It's a not a direct exchange for goods and services.
It's like, I like what you're doing.
Therefore, charity should be a dirty word.
Okay, look, look.
If I give a homeless lady $5 and then she sucks my dick,
it's no longer charity.
It's a transaction.
I mean, that's true.
Or it's I'm being raped and mugged, in which cases.
But that's not what we're doing.
It's like we're going around
and sucking everyone's dick for free.
And if they like it,
they'll give us a dollar every now and then.
We're going up to people's cars
and watching their windows without asking them.
And then maybe they'll give us a dollar afterwards.
Not exactly the same thing.
That model is a little closer.
But it is closer.
Well, honestly, that's such a dumb point.
I feel silly even arguing this.
Okay, can we at least agree
that like our income is based
on the goodwill of people, basically?
It is.
That's my point.
It's based on goodwill.
And so it's charity.
I mean, I think most of you are probably in the same position.
As someone who does don't, I mean, not a lot,
but I do donate to a few Patreons.
And I do not feel like I am giving charity.
I feel like I am exchanging currency for a service.
I mean, but you're not.
That's my whole point.
As someone who gives Patreons to you,
I don't feel that way.
You don't feel like what, Munchie?
I don't feel like I'm getting like a service.
Like I'm getting your service in between.
I'm giving it to you because I just like your stuff.
Right, that's my point.
I don't know if I'm supporting it really in a way.
You, okay.
Hang on, hang on.
I feel like I'm supporting the people that do the things.
Right, but that's not the same
as buying something from them.
Well, that's my point.
I am sure there are people who consider their donations
on Patreon or whatever, like effectively charity.
I'm sure there's some people like that.
But that doesn't mean that like some people,
you must admit at the very least,
some people must have the mindset that,
oh, I want to fund this person's work.
Therefore, I will contribute to doing that
by giving them money.
And to me, that seems like that's the main reason to do it.
I agree that that's the main reason,
but my point is that that logic is based on goodwill.
It's not based on, because people who give to the PCP,
other than people who do bonus episodes,
but like in general on Patreon.
Which is the vast majority, by the way.
Sure, but people in general on Patreon,
like your personal Patreon,
I don't know what your rewards are or anything,
but like they watch your videos, which are for free.
They do not have to pay for them.
And if they like you as a person
or they like the content you make,
they decide to give you money as a gesture of goodwill.
They do not have to, because if nobody paid you,
like the videos would still be there to watch,
and assumedly you'd still be making more
if you made half the amount of money you have
because you're trying to build that career.
So the videos themselves have no financial like worth,
because they're not, the market value for them right now
is free.
That's why I think we hit an impasse,
because I do not agree with that.
Why? Who paid for your videos?
Literally nobody.
The patrons.
The patrons paid for them.
No, they didn't.
Look, my situation is a little bit different
because I-
Look, forget me, because I'm a little different
because I actually have a full-time job.
Let's take somebody like just for example, Digi.
Digi's lifestyle, his ability to make videos, et cetera,
is literally paid for by his patrons,
because that's how he lives and makes his money.
Like yes, he makes YouTube money as well,
but it is 100%, the vast majority of his income
is from his patrons.
So you can't just say that there's no relationship,
like that clearly-
No, Digi's lifestyle is funded
by the goodwill of his patrons,
but his videos on the market are worth $0
because they are not for sale.
We might get cut up in semantics here a little bit,
because I think we generally would agree on this stuff,
but I think there's a slight difference
in the terminology that we use.
All I'm saying is that Patreon is goodwill,
not a market transaction.
See, I agree that it is goodwill,
which is why I have never given money
to anyone on Patreon ever,
because I don't think that way.
And it's true,
because I have a distinct lack of goodwill in my heart.
So that's true, that's true.
I just think that it is certainly a factor,
and maybe you would argue
that it's less of a factor than I would,
but it is a factor that people feel
they are getting something.
And I mean, I hear this from my patrons,
but again, okay, let's consider that anecdotal, so whatever.
I would argue that I think a large percentage of people
are saying that they're getting something for it,
even if it's just the satisfaction,
which yes, is goodwill-centric,
but it is supporting an artist
so they can keep doing what they want.
It's supporting an artist.
You're supporting the creator.
You're not buying their products.
The products are free for the most part.
I think that is, yeah, I'm sure.
And that's the only tiny distinction I was trying to make.
I don't know.
I feel like they're-
And that is similar to charity
in the fact that you're just giving people stuff.
My patrons are purchasing the pieces of my soul
that I continually chip off of myself for their benefit
and the constant sacrifice and toil and blood, sweat,
pain, tears, and tragedy that I go through
to make these things.
That's what I'm selling.
I don't know.
In Jesse's case,
because a lot of Jesse's stuff is just for patrons,
so that is definitely-
That is true.
I release a lot of stuff exclusive to patrons
that no one else sees on patreon.com slash endless jest.
It's exclusive and no one else can see it.
You have to be a patron and it's hilarious and cool content.
So there you go, people.
So a lot of it depends on the model, right?
I mean, we-
I guess like charity to me implies that like
the person receiving the money
isn't giving anything of their own.
And I think in any of our case, in anyone's case,
most people who have a patron are giving something
unless it's like a total scam artist or something.
Yeah, yeah.
Even people, like for example,
like a lot of us do live streams.
When you're live streaming and you get a donation,
even that, I don't think it's charity
because you are getting something in return.
Right.
I mean, even if it's something that like-
Donation.
That takes no talent or no work,
like just a random live streamer,
even if it's something that doesn't necessarily
take a lot of skill or thought,
it's still you're giving people your time
that you could be spending with,
you love ones or spending on yourself.
But like, true.
I think the difference is that patron and donations,
you get them because the person wants to,
not because they need to.
Nobody has to pay money to get into your Twitch stream.
No one has to pay money to watch Best Guy Ever videos.
They do it because they want to do it.
But if I want to go to the theater
and watch a movie legally,
I have to give them money first.
I can't just walk into theater,
watch the New Avengers movie,
and be like, yeah, that was pretty cool.
I'll give Marvel five bucks.
It doesn't work like that.
Different models.
I concede that Goodwill is definitely an element here.
But like just for example, on my page,
I have at the very least,
like my patron discord that only patrons are in.
So just even adding something like that,
I think does change the equation.
They're getting a reward.
Right, at that point,
if to get into your discord is a product,
your discord does have a financial,
whatever that tier is,
because you have to pay that amount of money to get in there.
And it's a subscription service,
because as soon as you stop paying,
you're no longer in there.
I think charity is a product.
So that is cool, and I'm all for it.
Everyone should be charitable.
Yeah.
Well, okay, I think we agree.
I agree, patron.
Definitely Goodwill is a major element,
but I still think there's a large people are.
I wanna go back to something that Ben said earlier about,
like if I had all the money in the world,
then of course I would give more to charity and stuff like that.
Like I catch myself thinking that all the time.
I always think like, oh man,
if I ever have like a million dollars
or a billion trillion dollars,
I'm gonna give it to everybody.
Everyone's gonna have fun times.
I'm gonna make people's lives less shitty with my money.
If only I had that million dollars.
But then I catch myself saying that,
and I think to myself, well, wait a minute,
how much money is enough?
Like where's the bar for when I have enough money
that it's suddenly okay to be charitable?
And that kind of makes me go, well, fuck that.
I technically, I can be charitable now,
so why the hell aren't I being charitable now?
And that's what makes you wanna fucking do it.
You know, there was a Sam Harris podcast about this stuff,
and basically he was trying to find out like the most,
I think I've talked about this before,
but it was like, what can you get for your bang for the buck,
the most good done for like the least amount of money,
such that like everybody could do it?
And it was something like-
Is it like wells, like drinking freshwater wells in Africa?
I mean, similar.
It was actually insect nets for like South America
to prevent like mosquito-borne disease,
like what is it, malaria, I think.
Malaria?
And so like, that's something for like $30 a month
that most people can afford.
Like if you do that, you can really make
a serious positive difference in the world.
So like there are answers to these questions
for something like that.
Yeah, instead of giving it to,
well, I probably shouldn't say your whole name,
but you want me to read some of this GoFundMe?
Sure, yeah.
And I will read it free of judgment.
Okay.
And I will just let you-
The judgment already happened earlier, let's go.
Well, I mean, I made the judgment not to donate,
but I mean-
I guess the thing itself could be independent.
But as, I mean, as you've heard
from the things I've said on this subject,
like that there's not a high bar of badness
to make me not donate.
Yeah.
Here we go, here we go.
Here's the pitch.
What would your parents say to you
if you called them following a dangerous car accident?
My mom told me she was glad I got into one.
To me, this sort of thing is normal.
Though I've lived with this for too long,
Tristan and I are trying to move out of my mom's house.
Should I not say real names?
Does it matter?
I guess just from here on, yeah.
Okay, T and I are trying to move out of my mom's house
to get an apartment with two friends of ours to start-
Oh, this is good.
Oh yeah, to start our YouTube channel
and engage in our creative endeavors.
Yeah, that takes a lot of fun to just start a YouTube channel.
Okay, all right.
Oh yeah, we originally scheduled to move
in January due to saving,
but after yesterday, we want to get out as soon as possible.
For most three bedroom apartments, blah, blah, blah, blah.
I want to raise money, blah, me and my friends.
So we don't have to be around this abuse anymore.
If we raise $2,000, we can leave immediately.
M, our close friend, is moving in a week.
Originally, he was gonna blah, blah, blah.
The more time we wait,
the longer I'm around my toxic mother.
T, M, and I all want to be in a supportive environment
where we all support each other all the time.
Wait, he said T, M, and I.
Who's the third person involved here?
Not, no, I as in the pronoun.
Oh, well, I thought the way you said it was-
There's a T, there's an M, and there's her.
Who she refers to as I, as one does.
But who's the, wait, who's the third person there?
Who's the M?
There's someone called M.
Well, okay, are this person in some sort of
three-way relationship?
Is that what's being implied here?
No, no, no, she said close friend.
Oh, okay, okay, all right.
So she's just like trying to do it.
Anyway, blah, blah, blah.
Here's the rub, here's the rub.
Picture of her and T.
T has a nirvana shirt and cherry red dyed hair,
and he's making a terrible fucking
Japanese V sign with his hand.
She, this girl J, I'll call her,
has a big ole nose ring and has like,
you know what, God, you'd have to see,
you would have to see this picture of her to understand.
But we won't share it with people.
Let me, in a minute I will post a picture,
but she has like, she has like, you know, like long,
it's gotta be like a silver wig,
and she's got like, like drawn on eyelashes
that like are, like go under her eye
to make it look like a big sparkly anime eye,
and she's got like, weird like blush face.
She's got a nose ring and she's like,
she's all pink and like spotty
and like looks like a fucking freak,
and like, and here's the rub, here's the rub.
There was another GoFundMe.
She's raised $439 on this campaign out of a goal of 2,000.
It took her two days to do.
It's not bad.
She, a year ago, she had another GoFundMe.
It was on a different account,
but I know because the picture of her
has her in the same kind of makeup.
And the GoFundMe was, help me cremate my cat.
And the goal was $200, and she raised 100 of it.
Damn it.
You don't like cremate half of it.
We didn't quite get it.
Had to bury Fluffy out in the backyard,
like a common, like a common beast.
Had to just eat her to make up that extra hundred dollars.
Here's why, here's why people of the world-
How to reinvest that cat meat
back into my personal economy.
This is why you don't want me donating these people.
Here's why, because in order for me to donate,
I'm gonna have to grill this person
and talk to the other side of the story,
AKA the mom, to find if this is really all stacking up.
Is there some bias here?
Like, I wanna know if this is actually
an injustice being done, or if it's just some like,
I mean, not to be judgy.
Maybe she's just a little emotional kind of a person.
Things have been taken a little bit out of control,
and the mom's not a legal monster.
You can never trust anything that a young person says ever.
Anyone under 25 is just a liar, period.
The word that stands out to me
in this description is yesterday.
She says that this exchange,
when she got into a car accident, called her mom,
and her mom said she was glad she got into a car accident,
happened yesterday.
That is such an outrageous claim, I just don't believe it.
I feel like maybe she was mad.
You know, I can see how you would say something
close enough to that that you could interpret.
If you were angrily, maybe she was angrily she crashed the car.
Maybe she said, well, you were being reckless or something,
or you're irresponsible, so you deserve to get in this car accident.
You brought this on yourself or something.
And she structured the way she makes this claim now
to make the worst possible interpretation possible.
She's phrasing it as like, my mom literally wants me to die,
which I don't believe.
I mean, maybe it's true, but I just don't,
I'm not going to take it away from you, but you know how I really...
I would find that much more shocking than if this person is just emotional
and got in a bad fight with her mom and then said,
oh, I'm going to go on, I'm going to make a go fund me,
and I'm going to move out with my boyfriend, T,
and we're going to move in with Mason, and I'm going to show you,
I'm going to show you that I can beg for money on the internet.
What just gets me is that there's so many people in the world
who love an excuse to like prop up people like this
without any kind of questions asked.
They see any kind of claims of victimhood,
and they're like, I am on board.
I'm on it. Here I go.
Wait, someone says that someone says they're in a bad situation,
someone says that a bad thing happened to them, I'm there.
I'm fucking there.
Comments, hope you guys are able...
Kiyoko says, hope you guys are able to get to a more healing environment soon.
Someone with a Japanese username says,
nice to help a local need or a smaller one.
I can relate with the one to get out of a situation like this.
Dawn says, no one should have to live through abuse.
Good luck, and I hope you heal quickly.
Harley says, I want you to feel safe and happy.
When I stream, I'll draw a picture of you
and tell my streamers to go donate to you.
Man, every since fucking Kavanaugh got into the Supreme Court.
It's been constant abuse, constant rapes of mother
against their children verbally and otherwise.
It's just a madhouse out here, guys.
Michi says, I am so glad that you're alive.
You're one of the best, sweetest people on Facebook and Deserve...
Okay, this person probably knows her in real life.
It sounds like it, yeah.
You know, so anyway, it's a bunch of bullshit.
What do you say, Jesse?
And the more I read of it, the less...
I went in there with an open mind and an open heart,
and the more of it I read, the closer it got.
So, you know, that's me.
That's me in a nutshell.
I think the...
Maybe this says more about me than it does about her.
The real way that I determine the limits of my charity
deep in the true dark pit of my hateful, vengeful soul
is just like, I won't give to anyone
whose story is less sad than my own.
That's a good move.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Absolutely.
If it's like I was paralyzed and I can't support my family,
well, okay, okay, I'll help this guy out,
because that sucks a lot.
But if it's just like someone like,
oh, my environment sucks and I'm trying to move away,
well, join the fucking club, you little brat, you know?
I've been trying to move away from my environment
for fucking 50 years.
You know what's interesting?
Not to make it overly political based on that,
but I think that that exact reasoning
is why a lot of people who are accused
of having white privilege have little sympathy for that
because they're like poor people and life sucks.
And they're just like, well,
while it is literally true that I have white privilege,
frankly, like I'd like to stop being, you know,
crushed under the boot heel of just life in general.
So yeah, well, you know what they say,
you can still lose on easy mode.
Indeed, indeed.
Yeah, that's always been my thoughts on it
or my feelings on it is because like,
you hear, you've got white privilege
because you're not black or you're not a woman
or you're not a minority.
But then when I sit down and think about it,
I think I've never met a black woman or minority in my life
whose life was worse than mine ever.
Sure.
I mean, my life has been harder
than any like black persons I've ever known.
So, fuck you.
Maybe I'm talking out my ass here.
What I will say about this is like, okay, like yeah,
if white privilege is a thing, I think,
but I would rather have, I think it seems to me
that like rich privilege is much better than white privilege.
And I would much rather, if I had to do that,
I would much rather.
It's a class thing.
I would much rather be rich than,
God damn it, let me finish my sentence.
I would much rather be rich than white.
I think that's a much bigger advantage.
As Mage said, it is, people point this out a lot,
but yeah, it's like the real division is class
as opposed to anything else.
It's like, I think it's big.
Don't you love it when you make a point so salient
that you are interrupted by fervent approval?
It's the time.
Fervent what?
Fervent approval.
Like everyone is just like jumping down your throat,
ah, shut up, you're absolutely right,
and I agree with you.
God damn, that's such a good point, yeah.
Why does this podcast always get so political?
Why do we always like to send into this?
I don't know.
Am I being political?
I just think it's-
I mean, slightly, I don't know.
I just think being rich is the greatest privilege of all.
I do believe white privilege is a thing.
I just, I don't think it's-
There's other privileges, some of which might trump it.
Some of which might trump it.
Except for rich and poor, like that's all it is.
That's the only real divide.
Oh shit, I said Trump.
I said Trump, it's political.
Don't ever say Trump.
No, I mean, it's all just a distraction
from the real privilege, which is wealth.
Wealth is the ultimate and only-
I, yeah, I would say that wealth
is probably the ultimate privilege, yeah.
Makes sense to me.
Wealth, it is-
Maybe a few centuries ago, it was nobility,
but we don't have that anymore.
The real privileges-
Nobody cares about that anymore.
That people take for granted are not like racial
or gender privileges or sex privileges.
The real privileges are like being born wealthy,
being beautiful, not having like abusive parents
or like having good parents is a privilege
that people take for granted.
Like those are the real privileges
that like people don't think of,
cause all they could think of,
everyone spends sort of like brainwashed into this,
oh, it's race and gender.
Everything is race and gender and sexuality.
Like no, it's there's other social factors
that determine privilege.
Yeah, I mean, race is a factor.
Like that does affect things.
Like you can't, you can be, you know,
excluded or marginalized on that basis.
It's just when you ignore everything else
just for something like that.
But it's, yeah.
It's like everybody's got blinders on
for race and gender and shit.
And they're ignoring that, you know,
if I can, you can have all the so-called
white straight male privilege in the world,
but if you grow up and your fucking,
your dad is an alcoholic
and he like throws you in the tool shed
and like whips you with a telephone cord,
then you're probably gonna grow up
with some disadvantages.
You're gonna be messed up in the head a little bit.
Yeah, yeah.
It's just cause those external things
are so easy to recognize and easy to group up in.
That's true.
They are, yeah, yeah.
They're very, they're very apparent.
You can't just make it sound right and be like,
you're clearly have like shitty parents.
You came from an abusive household, you.
But you can definitely say that there are
more abusive households for lower income people.
And you can also definitely say
that there are more minorities in lower income households.
Like you can say that it's all,
as long as you have self-awareness about what you're saying
and you're not just going around going,
ah, white people and fucking straight, you know.
I don't know.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I feel like I'm saying the correct thing.
I know that I would never say something that wasn't smart.
I know that, so.
Yeah, yeah.
Same, same.
I'm gonna jump on that bandwagon real quick.
I wanna say it quickly.
I think it's also important to have like a stable family home.
Like.
Yeah, that's what we're saying.
Yeah, yeah, it's a very important factor.
People very easily overlook, I think.
Yeah, I've said this a lot about,
or I've thought this a lot in my private dark moments
of bitter rage and resentment.
When I think about my good friend Digi, bro.
I just thought like Digi talks a lot about being privileged
and like the ultimate privilege that Digi has in his life
is having the family that he does,
the supportive mother and father
and the talented siblings.
Like I look at- For sure.
Say it with me and Ben, I think.
Yeah, like I look at the way like a person,
like Digi grew up, just having that family unit
that I never really had and I'm just like,
that's the ultimate privilege in life.
Like if I had had that,
I would be like a way contented person, probably.
Makes sense. I don't know.
It's just everyone thinks that the thing they didn't have
is the ultimate privilege.
Like no matter what you have.
You know, everyone kind of wants to-
It's always gonna be the crassest greener
on the other side of the fucking-
And everybody wants to be like, I did it myself.
They don't want, like there's an incentive to downplay
your own privileges, whatever they might be and so on.
But nobody does it all by themselves.
Absolutely.
You know, as the other village people said.
You know what is-
You know what is the-
He does it all by himself.
I said, young man, put your pride on the shelf.
You got privilege because you were born white
and some would make you rhyme.
And that is not all right.
We did it, Reddit.
Hang on, Munchy was jumping in.
I wanted to hear his perspective, I mean,
if you wanted to share.
All I was gonna say is that I don't disagree
with any I owe to what's happened here,
but as an SJW myself, I feel like everyone knows this
and everyone also does still talk about wealth.
In fact, I would say that I probably hear that more
as a thing than the caricature of everyone's
just fucking crazy about jumping on white people
for white privilege.
I almost exclusively hear social political class thing.
I might just be the bubble that I'm in,
but I feel like we might not be giving people enough credit.
I hear a lot, I hear Reyes talked about it a lot more.
I hear race and gender talked about a lot more than class,
but maybe I'm just not watching the right YouTube videos.
Yeah, that is true, Nate.
I think the people who are talking about race and stuff
are just more vocal, but there is definitely,
I mean, you look at like a lot of like.
Look at Tom's like Communist Tumblr,
and then you'll see.
Exactly, my lord and savior.
None of this is to say, none of this is to say that like,
I don't want this to be interpreted as like,
I think the world's going crazy
and everyone's a crazy SJW who's obsessed with race.
I think by and large, most people are sane
and have the ability to make logical distinctions
in their minds.
I mean, we're definitely not the only ones
that have these ideas.
I think we're the only ones thinking
about this galaxy brain level stuff here.
I think everyone knows we're just fucking
stuck in the fucking dirt.
That is the one good thing about living in a world
where everyone has gone fucking crazy
and is mentally retarded is that I can say
just the most basic obvious shit
and people will think it's smart
when really it's just in the whole world.
It's really easy to look intellectual online
when you do that shit.
Yeah, like all you have to say is that like,
oh, you know, it's probably bad to hate
other human beings for no fucking reason at all.
And people go, oh my God, that's like the most,
that's the most salient fucking thing I've heard all week.
I, that's, I feel that way too,
but I never knew how to put it into words before.
The bar is set so low now for being smart.
That's true.
You know, that's an interesting effect.
You know, does anyone else notice this
and just think about like their own videos
or the videos that are popular
and just think like, Jesus Christ,
this is such a basic fucking point.
Oh yeah.
The point of me making this or watching this.
Sometimes I feel like maybe I'm just an asshole
in my own head, right?
Because I feel and almost,
I feel almost always, like almost anything that I see,
I feel like is at least on some level,
some basic shit that I could have said
and I could have done and I'm not impressed by that.
Oh my God, you know what this reminds me of?
This extends to almost everything
that I see and experience in life.
Very much, especially on the YouTube landscape.
But I watched a movie yesterday, The Big Short,
which is this movie.
Oh, I love that movie.
I love that movie so much.
I like that movie.
It basically, it's explaining.
Is it about my day?
It's a dramatic reenactment
of like the housing crisis bubble collapse
in 2007 or whatever.
And okay, what was interesting about it,
this was honestly kind of insulting,
but I get why they did it.
They talk about how like, blah, blah, blah,
like it's a movie about banking, right?
So they're like, oh, CDOs, IRAs, blah, blah, blah.
You obviously don't know what that is,
which is true, no one does.
And that's kind of the point of the movie
that no one gets it.
So to explain these technical things
and use these like silly metaphors to get it across,
they'll be like, we're now cutting to,
what's Margot Robbie?
So it's Selena Gomez to explain to us at a poker table,
so that your fucking retarded ape-ass brain
will understand what's going on.
And yes, like it's true.
I needed a baby metaphor example
so that I could get it, all right?
But I didn't need you to pretend
that I'm only gonna listen to Margot fucking Robbie
sitting in a bathtub.
Like, frankly, that's more of a distraction
because I just wanna have sex with this creature.
I'm not interested in listening to her talk about this shit.
So I wish it was like a fucking,
I don't know, fun teacher or something.
It was annoying.
I thought it was, I don't know,
kind of funny in a way, the way they did that movie.
They were definitely trying to be glib with it.
I felt, I don't know, I felt a little pander too,
unintended, like more than they thought they were doing.
But it was a good movie.
But like the point is, it's just like,
I feel like that's kind of like what YouTube videos do.
And like, I made my video about Huey's Law or whatever.
It's just about taking whatever fucking idea you have.
How about something like, I don't know, it's okay to be gay.
And you put in like a big, elaborate music video
where like, oh my God, can you believe it's like
actually not a problem to be gay?
You make a big production.
You add like some sad music things
as you talk into a camera about.
You talk about, you're making a video
talking about how like the new Ghostbusters
isn't as bad as everyone says it is.
And then at the end, and then you suddenly,
and then you suddenly cut away to like a new angle
and you bring in some sad music and you go on a tangent
about how you understand depression
because last year you too attempted suicide
and it was a really rough time in your life
and you were in a bad place, but you're better now.
And thank you to all my viewers.
And thank you to all my viewers
for watching my content and supporting me.
And then your Patreon quadruples overnight.
Yes, I don't even disagree that these points are valuable
and can be said and it makes all the,
there's probably lots of people who still need to hear it.
I just hate it.
I just hate it when I feel talked down to
and it's like it's so little substance at the end of the day.
You take a thought or a feeling that you have
and you just dumb it down and chip all the nuance off of it
and then you wrap it up in pandering
and you fucking, you throw it out there
and the dumber it is, the more simplistic and moronic it is,
the more people will fucking flock to it
and hail you as the same.
The more basic it is, the more relatable and comprehensible,
the more people will latch on to what you're saying.
Yeah, and if you-
It's literally lowest common denominator.
And if you use the word mental health at any point,
then you automatically, a million views
and everyone thinks you're the best person who ever lived
because- Yeah, yeah, yeah, everyone's like, I too,
feel bad sometimes. I too feel bad sometimes.
I understand mental health issues.
I too have social anxiety and depression.
Like, who doesn't have social anxiety and depression?
Am I right gamers?
I just like, I hear the words mental health anymore
and just like, my eyes just instinctively roll
so fucking far into the back of my head.
I'm so sick of it.
You know what it is?
It's not like mental health isn't a real thing.
No, I could agree with all of it,
but I would still be so fucking sick of it.
You know what was interesting?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There was something interesting-
Wait, wait, wait, let me say what I'm saying.
Like, what it is, is it's the same thing as charity.
It's the bad eggs that are asking for charity
that don't really need it.
They're abusing people's goodwill.
It's lay people fucking armchair diagnosing
and self-diagnosing a bunch of bullshit
has just made discussion about mental health issues.
It has poisoned the well and turned it into a thing
that I don't feel that I should take seriously,
don't want to listen to on the internet.
All of the scummiest, most like narcissistic,
terrible people that I've ever met in my life
have also just so happened to be
those mental health fucking people
who are always constantly talking about their depression
and their bipolar and their manic fucking what's it.
And it's like, the more people talk about mental health issues,
the more they think they can get away
with being a slimy fucking piece of shit.
Yeah, it's like drama, you know,
the people that say that they don't want drama,
the people that say that the most are the most drama-prone.
Listen to this.
Because they're thinking about drama the most.
I suppose that's true.
So the other day, I was watching a PewDiePie video
and it was like his news show or whatever
and he just brings up that it was in the news
that, you know, Superwoman on YouTube,
she's like one of the biggest people,
okay, Lindsey Singer, whatever her name is, Superwoman.
She made a video and I brought it up here.
Look at this video, it's called I'll See You Soon.
Okay, it's an announcement that she's like leaving,
that she's gonna-
Is she taking a mental health break?
That's effectively what it boils down to, yes.
And like, okay, that's fine, that makes sense.
Let me, can I make a prediction?
PewDiePie's point on this was like,
he was basically like, why was this necessary?
Why do you need to like make a big production,
just leave?
And I mean, this is coming from a guy
who's been through the fucking ringer
and has been squeezed and, you know,
manhandled by the fucking legacy media,
trying to fuck him up and call him, you know,
an all right Nazi and all this shit.
And so he's been through the scandals
and he is fine, whatever.
And he's just like, what's the big, why are you doing this?
Like just leave, make a humble announcement
and then come back.
Why you got a virtue signal about all this meant?
You know why?
The answer's obvious.
So that your Patreon will quadruple overnight.
That's it, it's easy.
It's so easy to just throw out some words like this
and get, you know, even if you don't have a Patreon,
love, support, attention, any of that shit.
I don't look, look, okay, okay.
I don't want to vilify this person because-
I have to watch the video, so I have no idea what she says.
I was being, I was being salty one time
about this kind of thing that I'm being salty about right now.
People like, I mean, it wasn't about mental health
specifically, but it was about people using buzzwords
and saying the right thing to get sympathy,
to get, you know, to get, you know, goodwill to,
and you say the right thing and your Patreon
can quadruple overnight because what, for various reasons.
I was being salty about this and a guy on my discord,
AJ Shoup, AJ Shoups, who I think you know,
he's an RFCK guy, he said, and this stuck with me,
he said that, well, you know, like success is,
what is it, like opportunity?
It's opportunity plus action.
And so like, the way you succeed is when an opportunity
comes up, you take it, and if you don't,
you're just like denying yourself success.
And so for the, to not, to not do, like if a time,
if the time becomes ripe that you have the opportunity
to say something that will quadruple your Patreon,
why wouldn't you say it?
Exactly.
So like, I can't even be mad or vilify these people
and I don't think that they're bad for doing this.
Look, just look at this real quick.
I put just posted another image,
this YouTube spill channel, whatever,
literally makes a video called Superwoman Leaves YouTube
teaches everyone a lesson.
And you can see a snippet from her description of the video
that says, mental health is important, y'all.
And I'm just,
And just the fact that it's become,
The fact that like sincerity and like,
like exposing like your real feelings and sadness
has become like a formula for money and success
is like so scary and converted.
Cause like,
Yeah.
I think about doing, like you see these videos
of YouTubers where they come out and say,
this is what I've been dealing with.
And this is, you know, how much my life sucks.
And this is what I've been thinking.
And like I sit around and I think about making videos
like that all the time.
Like I think about, you know,
I wish I had the courage to be a little more open and honest
and say, so this is what's going on with me.
And this is what I'm dealing with.
And, and just, you know, but like,
it's scary for me.
And I feel like it's supposed to be scary.
And if it's not scary for you,
if you do it so much that you,
that it's like normal and it's what you do for money,
then you've perverted it and made it that much harder
for other people who might actually, I don't know.
It's just shitty people cheap and everything good.
It's what it comes down to, like we were saying.
Like stoicism, stoicism itself is not rewarded
in today's like culture.
It like advertising one's, one's, you know,
victory status.
That's what's rewarding.
Yeah.
And I feel, I think I'm a kind of stoic guy
who like hides his pain.
Yeah.
And I feel like I have,
and I feel like I'm punished for that.
I feel like I have failed to capitalize on.
I mean, it's not capitalizing on the market opportunity
that the millennial culture has presented to us, I guess.
I think.
I can feel that, yeah.
You guys are giving too much credit
to practicing bad, literally bad mental health practices.
It's not cool to never speak to your friends
about your problems or to pretend
that you don't have any.
Talking to your friends is different from like.
I agree with you a bunch.
Making.
But it's also not cool to turn it
into like a thing for profit.
And just use your fucking-
Yeah, no, I'm not saying it is.
It's a middle ground, yeah.
I'm just saying, I guess I felt like the winds
of the conversation.
We wouldn't want to-
Everyone just, you know, everyone deals with stuff
so just no one should talk about it.
I think it's a good place.
Look, when I said that thing about being stoic
and hiding my pain, I didn't mean it as like,
I'm better than these people that are open about it.
But I agree with you.
We're like, encourage a type of overcompensation of it.
Look, you guys know-
I don't even, like I was saying before,
I can't even be mad.
Yeah.
I want my instinct is to be mad
because I feel like people that get this kind of support
and sympathy, they're capitalizing on something
that I just can't, either I don't know how to do it
or I can't bring myself to do it
or I just haven't done it
or it's just not applicable to me or something, whatever.
It's something that I don't have.
It feels like-
My instinct is to be salty and mad,
but I can't actually pinpoint what is being done wrong here.
Unless like, if this is being done cynically
and like calculatedly, then I would say, ew, gross.
But I don't know that.
I don't know anything.
I think because it feels disingenuous
when you capitalize on something like,
something that's so personal and sincere
and like that's giving you a hard time
and you're sharing it with people
and it's such a very sort of like a vulnerable moment
and people then capitalize on this moment
that it doesn't feel sincere, it doesn't feel good.
I'm not saying everybody does this,
but some people literally whore out their depression.
Yeah, yeah, the fact.
Yeah, the fact.
I am in all support of people sharing.
Like different people deal with different things
differently, a lot of differences.
But like, you know, so like I have a few friends
that do come to me and talk to me about stuff
and I'm more than happy to help.
I do that too sometimes with friends,
but for the most part, when the big things happen,
I usually don't share it with people,
but basically to vent sometimes it's good
and therapeutic and I am all supported with sharing and stuff.
But when people, like you said, whore out their depression,
that's when I draw the line, I guess.
What makes it weird is not, no individual case
is like horrible and like, you know,
I can't point to an individual case and be like,
oh, this person's bad, this person's being a whore or whatever.
But the fact that it is like a recognizable pattern,
like a widespread recognizable pattern and for success
is dystopian and horrifying.
I think these people who, you know,
do these sort of things makes it harder for people
to genuinely share their problems with other people.
Yeah, that's what I was saying exactly.
Yeah, because, you know, like you just wanna be honest
with people and share your experiences and whatnot,
but then like you're afraid that you'll get good compared
or like, oh, you're just whoring for attention
or you're just trying to be a victim.
You don't wanna be lumped in with YouTubers.
It's like there's such a stigma
because of what YouTubers have been.
It's like these narcissistic like,
yeah, this is me and look at me.
Like I don't wanna be that.
No one wants to be that
and you'd hate to get compared to those people.
So yeah. I do think some of this just kind of makes sense
with the widespreadedness of like us kind of all whoring
ourselves out to varying degrees on social media.
You know, I've always described or I've recently described
like being a YouTuber as like selling your personality
as a service or like whatever, you know, that kind of shit.
So like you really are exposing yourself
more probably mentally and like,
cause people like I really try to keep a wall here,
but if I was like a daily vlogger
and was just putting like everything I had
on the internet and stuff
and like people could see everything I do
and they can be like, oh, that's shit.
Then like that'll mean a lot more
than if I like edit a video, it's not funny.
And people are like, well, that sucked
cause it's not like me, they're attacking.
It's like a product.
So maybe that breakdown of that wall
is what's leaving people more mentally vulnerable
or something to this stuff.
I don't know.
I've felt like less and less comfortable
with that kind of stuff.
And like, I mean, I don't do social media anymore at all.
And like, I haven't been on this podcast for over a year.
Like, I'm at the point where just like,
like chipping off parts of my personality
and parts of my experience to like give to the world.
It's not fun, it's exposing and it's scary.
And I don't know if I really like it.
It kind of makes a day job seem like a nice thing.
Yeah, it absolutely does.
You don't have to sell your soul.
Put me in a comic book store
and let me like work behind a register.
I feel like I'd almost be happier.
I don't know.
And now I'm doing it.
Now I'm doing the thing that I was just
fucking talking about.
Cause now I'm fucking, so you just can't,
it's like a trap, you know, you fucking shit.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
Well, I'll tell you what team.
How about we go to those questions?
Wait, no?
I have, you know,
I want to say, I don't usually do this,
but I actually came into this episode with notes
and like top, I have a list sitting in front of me
on topics that I wanted to talk about.
I never have this, but I have this this time.
And we only got to two of them.
And I'm like, damn it.
I had actual stuff that I wanted.
But what are we going for?
Like two hours now?
Yeah, a little over two hours.
Yep.
Man.
So, okay.
Well, I'll leave some of these for later.
However, there's one.
Before we go on the questions, I have one thing.
I feel like I have, I have sensed a sort of confusion
or a sort of widespread false belief
that I live with at Digi's house with like Tom does.
And I just want to say no.
Is that true?
I just want to put that.
Where did that come from?
Who said that?
I feel like I've, I don't know where I saw it.
It might have been on like the PCP fan discord or something.
Or some, I don't know, I feel like that one time.
Maybe it was, yeah, maybe people got the impression
because I've been on IM Games.
But I feel like some people believe
that I live with you guys at Digi's house.
And no, I have my own place.
And it's a real cool guy, so cease the bullying.
I'm way cool guys.
Yeah, I'm a cool guy.
And I don't know.
Okay, I guess there's really nothing else to say about that.
We're at Digi House.
Did I mention that this is,
people stopped calling it Monkey House?
Oh, you did mention it.
They call it, they call it Wheel House now
and their name sucks.
I refuse, I refuse.
Yeah, fuck it.
It's Monkey House.
Bring it back, Monkey House.
Okay, well, never, sorry,
that was a bit of a dead-end tangent,
but at least it's out there now.
You got our announcement, you're okay.
All right, let's go to these questions here.
Wait, wait, oh man, I feel like we can squeeze
one more Monday joke in here somewhere.
I just gotta fucking think of it.
Hey Garfield, what's tomorrow?
Oh, John, you know what the worst mental health thing
of all is?
Mondays, okay, there we fucking go.
Okay, I got that, here's my YouTube video confession
for all my fans.
Sorry I haven't posted in a while,
but guys, it's Monday and I just can't do it anymore.
What do they say about like,
what's that thing like in winter you get depressed
is like seasonal affective disorder, SAD?
I think it's SAD, well Garfield's got MAD,
Monday affective disorder.
People, people.
His mental health just plummets.
We need to take mental health seriously, people.
If Garfield was in a coma.
Oh my God, he said what I feel,
but I could never put into words.
I have to fucking give him the cash.
If we don't start taking it seriously,
Garfield is gonna shoot up a school,
and you know what they're gonna say in school?
And it'll be your fault for not supporting
Endless Desk for saying this right now.
All school shootings happen on Monday.
I was gonna say, school shootings are just
a Monday thing, I mean, I assume.
Well then obviously the way to end school shootings,
every single one, all Mondays.
Yeah, the way to end school shootings
is to abolish Mondays.
Garfield's united with those.
Hey, quick question, if Garfield was in a coma,
let's say for three months, and then he wakes up,
and he wakes up on a Monday,
but nobody tells him it's a Monday.
Would he know it's a Monday, even if nobody tells him?
Would he somehow know?
I'm gonna say he would because he always gets the splort
on Monday.
What's the splort?
The splort is a pie that seemingly comes from nowhere,
a hand with a pie in it that hits Garfield in the face,
and the sound effect is always splort.
So somehow, he would get squirted, he would know.
He could deduce it.
I think he's got a sense for it now,
and he would very quickly realize that it was Monday
because like pianos would fall on him from the sky and stuff.
What a tragic belief system where he's doomed one seventh
of his entire life to be sheer agony and misery.
It's not, it's not belief.
This is not like the secret kind of like,
like his believing makes it so.
This is like, like the universe conspires
against the Monday.
Yeah, and this is like a scientific law of the universe
in the Garfield canon.
Mondays will get you.
I guess that makes sense.
All right.
It's like, it's on every Monday, it's like he gets hit
with Chris Chan Sonichu's Cursier Hamehawai.
Yeah.
Okay, let's get to a question here.
Oh, so we're going to the questions.
This isn't an actual question,
but here's a little sound bite from one spar.
Listen up.
Here we go.
Hello.
It's time for voicemails.
Yeah.
Oh, I like that.
Voicemail intro.
Sick.
That is nice.
Oh, that's good.
It's a good idea.
Yeah, okay.
It was good actually.
I like having like a stick.
It makes sense to have a little jingle for a segment.
Yeah, way to go once, Bar.
And by the way, please finish that fucking
a DeVoo game shit.
Okay.
Finish that fucking DeVoo game shit.
I can't remember the name of it.
It's long.
I always forget.
Autonomous.
Yeah.
Finish that let's play so I can watch it.
Or Ben, whatever.
I don't care.
One of you.
All right.
Next one.
This is from, ah, here we go.
This is from Radcon Israeli Defense Four.
So like four, you know, like the numbers.
Okay.
So let's see who we've got waiting for us in this country.
Radcon Four.
Radcon Israeli Defense Fours.
All I need to do is pretend that you're Jewish
and the Israeli government will send you a ticket
to Israel for free.
So all you need to do is find a way to pretend you're Jewish.
Digi, Victor, they already look Jewish.
So you guys can just get away with that.
Ben, Nate, you're Polish.
That's basically Jewish already.
Rest of you fags have to get circumcised.
That's it.
Bye.
I'm just saying, if we could somehow
trick the Israeli government to fund our trip
for Radcon Israeli Defense Fours,
that would be pretty good.
I doubt they're including return tickets, are they?
Radcon Four Israel.
Oh, God.
Do they not include return tickets
when you take this trip?
Yeah, you can only go, but you can't leave.
I mean, it kind of makes sense.
The goal is still a friend.
We'll go for free and kickstart the return flight.
It's like, hey, hey, everyone, I'm doing a go fund me.
Help me escape from this abusive environment in Israel
where they won't let me leave.
Okay.
You guys know how you can't ever choose what you remember.
So there's going to be some wayward thoughts there
for some reason are stuck in your mind forever.
I used to watch a ton of conspiracy theory YouTubers
and there's this one phrase that stuck with me.
Whenever I want to ratchet up things to 11,
I think to myself to the phrase,
what happens when the no fly list becomes the no leave list?
And that's like past 11, past 10.
That's like the top of the food chain.
Like, you know, like, let's get this party started.
Let's kick this from the no fly list,
the no leave list real quick here.
The no fly list to the no leave list.
It's like, it's like you've got your stereo.
You go one to eight, like pretty good.
Click it up to nine.
It's like, oh, let's go a little higher.
Next one, no fly list.
You're like, that's pretty good.
But we could go one further.
No leave list.
Yeah, yeah, exact right.
You like, you get on the plane to leave
and right before it gets off the runway,
Master Hand plucks it out of the fucking air
and puts it in a bag somewhere.
That's the hand of Trump.
A marble bag.
It is the hand of Trump.
A big orange Master Hand.
Oh no, but his hands are tiny.
That's the joke, so they have to.
Oh, that's true.
So it can't be a Master Hand.
It'd be Crazy Hand.
No, oh no, oh no.
My Master Hand joke turned into a Trump joke.
No, I hate when that happens.
Please donate to my GoFundMe.
No way, you're gonna get a show on Comedy Central
in a couple minutes.
So that I can get away from my jokes becoming Trump jokes.
The good news is you're about to be, yeah,
much like I said, given a Comedy Central special
based on that one Trump joke.
So, you know.
Yeah, all I have to do is remove all the humor
and punch lines from it.
All right, we got a voicemail from Mr. Bones,
who I think we've gotten in the past.
Let's go.
I recently rewatched the Digi's lecture on The Dick Show.
And I know that some of you have been familiar enough
with the story and what was going on with it.
And considering that it seems that Jess
is now back on some of these podcasts,
I thought it'd be worth asking,
are any of you still keeping up with The Dick Show?
And if so, what do you make of the continuing narrative?
It feels like in the year since that lecture was released,
there's been so much hot goss to come out down the pipes
that it kind of feels like a whole new lecture is necessary.
And I know that PCP lectures are, you know,
there's a lot of competition for what would be put in them.
But my question is, would Digi or any of the rest of you
ever consider doing the hot goss too?
Well, it would have to be Digi to do it.
To be honest, I watched a bunch of,
I watched like maybe half of the,
I was gonna say best guy ever,
biggest problem in the universe.
And I didn't finish it.
By the time I was there, like, you know, the whole,
the thing happened, they split up, Dick Show started.
I watched a little bit of The Dick Show,
mostly just like incidentally,
when Digi happened to be watching it,
and I happened to be in the room.
I didn't, so I haven't actually seen that much.
I haven't kept up, most of what I know about it
comes from Digi and that lecture.
That's me, that's where I'm at with that.
So no, I haven't been keeping up with it.
Has anybody else been keeping up with it at all?
No, I think when he did the lecture,
I was, I was, you know, all caught up.
And right around the end of the time,
I fell off the train of pretty much watching anything.
To me, like the lecture kind of like put the capstone
on my interest and like, I can let this go now.
I wish you'd given us some examples.
I have no idea.
I guess I wish Digi was here.
I have no idea what it was about anymore.
The goss itself just got so fucking tiresome to me
and boring after like, yeah.
It's like, like now, like,
I think I see tweets from mysterious every now and then
it just kind of seems like a lot of sort of past,
I don't know, like a stereo is funny,
so I don't want to shit on him.
But like a lot of what I see is just kind of like
passive aggressive, like look at this,
look at this new really stupid thing Maddox is doing.
What an idiot.
He's just embarrassing myself.
The stereo is just fucking hilarious.
It is like the epitome of being a dead horse though.
Like, I mean, you won the Wall Street.
Yeah, yeah.
What more can you do to this man?
I mean, maybe something good actually happened.
I mean, it does start to feel,
it does start to come off cruel after a while
and it does start to rub me in the wrong way a little bit.
It starts to come off cruel,
but on the other hand, Maddox did bring this lawsuit
and like caused this whole trouble that like, you know,
a stereo and everyone else is having to deal with.
I mean, I can't put myself in a stereo suit in the first place.
So I get why a stereo feels victimized.
I think that that makes sense.
And like, it's not like any of these things
that Maddox does in the suit, like any of the like,
it's like, ha, ha, you know,
we have to legally prove these a cuck.
Like that is funny, but it does start to be like,
it's sort of been the same story for what,
like a year and a half now.
I just feel like it's gotten to the point where Maddox,
like I feel like I might see a news story
that he killed himself and then it won't be funny anymore.
That's kind of where I started leaving interest in it.
It's just like, it's like, it's like,
it's like a flawless victory fatality.
Where do you have left to go
and like making Maddox look worse than he actually is?
It seems like that to us,
but I think to them, it's ongoing.
No, I totally get why, you know,
a stereo suit if I was in his shoes,
I'd be mad and fucking want to fight too constantly.
But I don't like, his fucking, his,
a stereo suit's videos where he was like,
Tom Phillips, the game reporter,
are like the funniest videos ever.
Like that's what I love.
And like his dumb characters,
like the fucking, that Bayou voice that he does,
is like a Cajun guy, that was incredible.
And like, I like Dick when he's just being the guy
who like rants about stepping in dog shit
and like has those everyday problems
and like goes crazy about him.
That's good stuff.
But no, I just, even if it weren't for like me
getting bored of the goss,
I just kind of really fell out of watching
or listening to fucking anything for a long time now.
I just fucking don't care about the internet.
I'm just real curious, based on what this guy was saying,
like it sounded like there was new goss.
I wonder if that's good.
It seems like none of us actually knows that we also
maybe there was some recent development of,
but I don't know.
Yeah, I don't know either.
All right, well, whatever.
Next, next call.
This is from easily influenced idiot.
Okay.
So people have told me that I'm smart.
Wrong.
Which is wrong.
Yeah, but how can I abuse that people think
that I am smart?
That's it.
You're a cartoon character, buddy.
But the question was, how can I abuse the fact
that people think that I'm smart?
He is not smart, but people think he's smart.
How can he use this to win?
How can he use it?
It sounded like a fucking mad hatter.
I did believe it.
Yeah, I know, I know.
I sound like a cartoon character.
How can I, how would I?
Keep in mind, he's not smart.
He's not.
Yeah, that's difficult.
I was gonna, well, in that case,
you can make people do what you want
by just telling them this is a good idea and I'm smart.
But since you are dumb, if you do that,
bad things will result because your ideas are bad.
That's probably true.
Okay, he's gotta do some sort of like,
he's gotta get in some sort of situation like King
from One Punch Man, if you're familiar.
Whereas everyone thinks that King
is the strongest man in the world,
but it's all due to misunderstandings and shenanigans.
He is actually just a gamer boy, basically.
He has no abilities whatsoever.
But everyone thinks that he's super strong.
But it's honestly, the role of King in One Punch Man
gives me such anxiety every time he's on screen
because I'm constantly terrified.
He's going to be found out this time,
that this is gonna be the time.
So I don't know.
I don't know if I can in all conscience
advocate anything that is in any way
not just upfront about how dumb you are.
It sounds to me that like the best thing to do
is you just keep doing what you're doing
because you've obviously already fooled everyone
to think you're smart.
You just ride on that social credit and just keep going.
Okay, because you're not smart,
you will not be able to make any grand plans happen.
But the good news is,
you can just make people think you're smart
and use that in small ways
to just get general social benefit.
Here's what I think.
You should team up with someone who is smart,
but maybe has low charisma.
And then you should be the mouthpiece,
and he should be the ideas guy.
That's a great idea.
Go hit up the chess club.
And the two of you can rise to the top together.
Hit the nerd club,
hit the computer programmer desk,
be elite hacker or something.
Yeah, do that.
That's what you need to do.
Yeah, you gotta find a partner
that fills in the gaps in your stats.
Team up with a smart guy,
work really hard and eventually you can get that farm
and tend the rabbits.
Based on that voice mail,
this man's charisma is obviously off the charts.
So, you know.
Yeah, because he sounds like the mad hatter all the time.
That's his real voice.
And everyone just finds it so charming.
He is literally lording the club that is that tea party.
Oh yeah.
Oh, he's lording that club too.
All right, next question is from our next voicemail.
Do it, I dare you.
Well, I think called in last week, but let's say.
All right, motherfuckers.
I take my precious time out of delivering pizzas.
Oh yeah.
Close your car door.
I still do.
I literally never stop.
Never stop delivering pizzas for a whole straight week.
And I asked, I needed to know whether or not you,
you were sledding.
And I spoke, I guess, with two intellectual,
two grand of a way of speaking.
And so, none of you understood that I was asking.
I was pleading for advice on how to,
whether or not I should go fucking sledding.
Sounds like munchie after he's gotten a job.
It's a living cold place where it sometimes snows.
But if I go up to the mountains,
there'll definitely be snow.
If I just go on, if I go on a mountain,
there's like 99% of the time it snows.
Okay, all right.
Wait, what is this issue?
If you guys ever slitted, I can't make decisions.
And there's people on the internet who I listen to
tell me about what it needs to be.
So fucking talk about sledding.
Yeah, okay, if you request,
oh, and it, and you still don't, yes, agreed.
If you, yeah, go sledding if you feel like going sledding.
Sledding is awesome.
That's it.
You know what, there's a hierarchy, all right?
It's like snowboarding is at the fucking bottom.
Snowboarding sucks.
Skiing is a little bit more fun than snowboarding.
Barely, sledding is at the fucking top.
Sledding, anyone can do it.
You never mess up.
Even if you wipe out on a sled,
it's somehow it's still fucking part of the,
it's great in the hilarious.
That's part, that's part of the fun.
If you wipe out skiing, you failed at skiing.
But if you wipe out sledding, you're still just sledding.
And also you fucking died.
You just become, yeah, it's part of it.
You're supposed to wipe out.
You're supposed to go like 90 miles an hour
on that little, on a thin piece of plastic,
like for babies, and you hit the end of the fucking hill,
and at the end of the hill,
it kind of goes up a little ways.
So you have fucking fly 50 feet in the air,
and you break your fucking leg.
That's sledding, and it's fun, and it feels good, dammit.
It feels good.
If it's good enough for Calvin,
it's good enough for you, dammit.
Yeah, yeah.
Those great, those great fucking,
you know, like 10 series long comic panels of Calvin,
like discussing the philosophical concepts,
eventually just smashing into a fucking tree.
That's how the last Calvin Hubstrip ended, right?
That's true.
Let's go on an adventure,
and they were sledding down the hill.
It was a big hell.
Did you really die?
Is that what's implied?
Oh my God.
Yeah, and actually, no.
He woke up right before he hit the ground,
and he was in a coma, all of a sudden.
Oh.
Is that in any way true?
That is completely not.
He just sled down, and then Hobbs turned to him,
and he said, listen, honey,
the doctors say that you think I'm a YouTuber.
Listen, I know you think,
I tell you to like, comment, and subscribe,
but actually, I'm your husband.
Please wake up.
Yeah, please wake up.
I'm trying experimental technology.
Can you hear me right now?
Wake up, wake up, Calvin.
Hey, remember that guy,
that voicemail that we got that was a message
from a higher reality telling us
that we were all in a coma and need to wake up?
Did anyone do that?
Did anyone take his advice?
I didn't.
I did.
I went on and got some snacks, and then came back.
Yeah, okay, good.
That looks good.
Yeah, Calvin wakes up from his coma,
and the doctor explains that you see, Calvin,
it was all a dream composed of metaphors.
Oh.
For example, the character of your mother
represented your repressed homosexuality,
and the character of your father
also represented your repressed homosexuality.
The character of Kock,
represented your repressed desire to suck cock, you see.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's just all that.
Your sexually ambiguous friend, Susie,
clearly represented your deep, gay butt fuckery.
Oh, shit, my groceries are here.
I'll be back in a minute.
All right, let's go on to the next one.
Wait.
Let's go on to what?
Oh, I was confused if Ben actually went to get groceries,
or if that was part of the Calvin and Hobbs bit,
but I'm like, wait, why is Calvin getting groceries now?
I lost something.
I'm gonna assume.
Okay, next call is from, I think this is real talk.
This is from real talk.
Let's get real.
The PCP are just human, fallible beings, mortals.
Do not look up to them,
except if you're looking for financial advice from Nate,
that is just about it,
or perhaps art advice from a hippo or pen,
but it's not people who are just trying to figure out
their careers in life, just like you are.
However, maybe they're just a little bit older,
and you'll figure it out too.
So don't idolize people with a lot of pen install
because it's just gonna hurt you in a lot, right?
So, don't forget to take your call drops.
Yeah, I appreciate Marvin the fucking Martian calling you.
It sounded more like a Dalek, but just like a calm one.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah, you know, you start out kind of in tense,
but you're just like, you know what?
Yeah, you know what?
Do whatever you want, make your own decisions.
I like when people call in with a point
and then refute their own point as they go along.
Has this become like a meme of people saying,
don't put us on a pedestal or anything?
No.
It seems like I've heard, did you say that a lot,
or something, I figured people say that.
Like, I don't know, I feel like if your options
are to either put me on a pedestal
or like put me on a place where you don't like me,
then by all means, put me on a fucking pedestal, please.
Please.
I would rather be liked too much than not enough.
Climb the pedestal at patreon.com slash best guy ever,
everybody, head over there and show your love of height.
Well, all right, I mean, yeah.
I mean, I think we have talked about this a little bit
about like how you shouldn't listen to us
for fucking gospel or whatever.
Like, yeah, I mean, I don't know,
I just feel that point's pretty clear, I guess.
But it's always nice to hear from the voice
of a literal alien, so that's-
Look, if you ever catch me saying that you should
go outside and risk the elements
and brave the world on a Monday,
then you know that I need to be off that pedestal.
I have lost my right to the pedestal.
Don't listen to me if I say that.
But anything else I say, you can listen to me
because it's pretty fucking, it's probably correct, you know.
Here's a voicemail I assume is either from or for Mage,
it's from UwuUWU, you know, with the little face,
so let's see what he has for us.
So, I've been watching the drawcast a lot lately
and it's really inspired me to try and learn how to draw
and hopefully become an animator someday,
so like beer games and shit.
So I was wondering if you guys have any tips
for getting good art relatively quickly,
relatively being like a year or two?
Andrew!
I think your art is fucking amazing
and I hope to be on your level.
Yeah, okay, okay, okay, yeah, okay, yeah.
Okay, is it done, is it done?
Yeah, okay.
Andrew Loomis is funneled with a pencil, that's it.
That's all you need.
Google search Andrew Loomis is funneled with a pencil.
You'll find a PDF like the second Google search.
That's it, don't come back.
Fun with a pencil.
What kind of information is contained in that tome?
Just for the later.
It takes you from literally not knowing
what the fuck is happening, how do I hold a pencil,
to being proficient in like 60 pages.
It explains drawing in the only way
that actually makes sense.
You can like be like, all right,
here's how you draw the head from this side,
here's how you draw the pencil.
Does not matter until you realize,
oh wait, here's how you draw.
You take shapes that appear in the world,
but then you basically reverse engineer them.
So instead of thinking about a skull as being a skull,
you're sitting about the skull, okay, what is a skull?
It's like a sort of elongated sphere,
then there's the nose is sort of like a triangle,
like trapezoid sort of thing, okay, okay.
You don't think about it in terms of like symbols,
what you think a head looks like
or what you think a nose looks like.
You think you bring it out into the geometric shapes
and that's what that guy does
and he explains it to you in greater detail in that book.
No one says that, no one's like,
no one starts out drawing and he's like,
okay, time to learn the geometric shapes and shit.
No, that's what you have to do.
That's how you actually learn how to draw for realsies.
So do that.
How about you, Mage, got any suggestions?
Hey, I think Munchie has better suggestions.
I just draw like a lot, but yeah, I guess, you know,
using other people's examples of how to do its best.
But like, I mean, like the more hours you put in,
the better you'll get at it eventually, so.
How about you, Tom?
I would ask Ben as well, but he's not here.
Gesture drawing, draw from life a lot.
Understanding that drawing from life doesn't mean,
like the reason I never drew from life when I was a kid
because I hated drawing realistically
because I didn't wanna draw photorealistic stuff,
but none of my art teachers ever said,
just because you're drawing from life
doesn't mean you have to draw every last detail.
Like gesture drawing is about getting the idea of a figure,
not like doing every last little like skin pour.
So once I realized that, I started doing it
and my figure drawings got better in literally two weeks,
like orders of magnitude better.
Figure drawing, gesture drawing.
Yep, I'm doing that right now.
I've been doing that for the,
I think I said this before, but yeah,
I've been going gesture drawing classes every Monday
and I've been doing that and it's been absolutely fantastic.
Oh, that sounds fun.
I've improved nocibly in the short amount of time.
It's just fantastic.
How about you, Jesse?
How do we get the MS Paint masterpiece from within?
Put it on the canvas.
Well, you gotta go to a figure drawing class
where they take their clothes off.
That's the first rule, and that's really the only rule
because once you,
Hey, Kale.
Once you see a naked lady contort her body
into all manner of shapes and figures,
well, then you get that boner
and then you get that spirit,
that real fighting spirit in your soul
and you become a man.
And once you're a man,
you can draw whatever the fuck you want.
And if people say that it looks bad
or if it's a poopy drawing, you say,
no, that's my artistic style.
That's my flair.
That's just how I draw.
I hate that excuse.
I don't, well, I saw the naked lady,
so I'm a man now.
So he knows,
I think he knows a little bit more about drawing
than you made.
She's seen the naked lady.
I just wanna reinforce this point with,
okay, Uwu, so you called in, right?
You did a good thing.
You asked a question, it was a fine question.
We heard it and we responded.
You have the expertise.
Okay, I just wanna tell you,
you now have one year, okay?
I'm not, fuck that two year thing.
You have one year in order to,
Munchie just gave you the answer.
He gave it to you.
Just do that.
Did I miss anything?
You did.
This guy asked a question about recommendations
for how to get good at drawing in one year or two,
but whatever, a short amount of time.
Munchie said, what was the name of the book again, Munchie?
Andrew Loomis's Fun With The Pencil.
Fun With The Pencil, that's the one.
I mean, there's no figure drawing for fun, right?
There's one called like,
there's one called Figure Drawing For Something.
Figure Drawing For All It's Worth.
Yeah, yeah, Figure Drawing For All It's Worth
is my pick for Loomis, but you know.
I've been reading all of Loomis, he's all great.
The reason I suggest Fun With The Pencil
is because he takes you from such a low level.
Yes, that's good.
He takes you from the absolute beginner.
Yeah, Ben, didn't you literally decide
to get good at drawing in a year and did it?
Yeah. So there you go,
just do whatever the fuck Ben does, there you go.
And yeah, yeah, what I did.
I mean, don't do everything that Ben does,
but you know, basically do whatever the fuck Ben did.
I just do most of it though.
I feel passionate about this call.
You, this guy was literally just given the answer.
Just do that.
Read, start with Munchie's book.
That sounds like the easiest one.
Literally do that one thing.
And if you don't do it,
I don't wanna fucking hear you complaining
about how hard it is to drawing.
You should be drawing every single day for 365 days
in a row without stopping.
And if you do that, you'll be good.
If you don't, you'll be a fucking pissy baby piece of shit
and you'll have no one to blame but yourself.
So go fucking do it.
I refuse for this to be some masturbatory advice bullshit.
I will fucking gun you down in the street
if you have not actualized in your fucking dream.
You fat motherfucker.
So go do it.
I will expound a little bit.
Like what got me like before, before I did,
I kinda like got, I mean, you know,
obviously you never stop improving,
but I went from like, I went from like a three to like a,
well, I don't wanna rank myself on how good at drawing,
but you know, I made my big leap in maybe a year or two.
And yeah, like I had read Bakuman
and I had watched Strip Search.
And those two things got me really hyped
and motivated me to learn.
And then yeah, I read a bunch of Loomis.
I read some other stuff, but Loomis was the best.
And then I watched a lot of,
I watched a lot of like YouTube, like drawing tutorials.
Some were bad, some were okay.
I used to watch a lot of psychra streams and psychra,
like videos that was pretty inspiring and educational.
Yeah.
Do you know the YouTuber Proko?
No.
Well, someone in the audience will.
The Proko is like an old drinking buddy
of my gesture drawing class teacher.
Like they are friends.
And Proko is like a big huge drawing YouTuber.
I was like, like, I don't know, like probably like a bunch
of fucking, like a million subs or something.
So, and that crazy.
Really?
Yeah.
That's cool.
Weird.
You got to get in touch.
Yeah.
You got to use that connection.
Hey, hey, I just podcast.
I was wondering if Proko could listen to it.
It's called, it's called the Procraster.
It's called, it's called the Zit Crushing podcast.
I think I like it.
What was it?
The Pimple Crush podcast.
Yeah, Pimple Crush in.
By the way, you know what?
I meant to say this earlier, but just,
I watched a Joe Rogan podcast episode
that I would highly recommend everyone in the world
listen to, featuring David Goggins.
I think his name was first, his last name was David.
His last name was definitely Goggins.
Everyone should go listen to it.
It's about, it's like two and a half hours long
of this guy, Goggins.
He's a black Navy SEAL, which is relevant
because like he says very few black guys become Navy SEALs.
And a lot of, he says, a lot of has to do with it
because it's so water based.
Is it because they can't really?
That's really what he says himself.
Yes, that's what he says.
But the whole, the whole can't swim meme?
He says it's real.
I'm, I'm, I'm agnostic.
I'm just reporting the facts.
Okay.
Here's, here's the point.
This guy tells his life story, which was like,
he was the most like decrepit piece of shit broken down,
sad, fucking, fat sack of shit in the world.
And now he is.
I was down and out with the blues.
That was him.
That he got himself to the YMCA.
He one day, okay, this is why I love this guy so much.
One day he was a huge avid fan of Rocky.
He would watch it like every day.
He was a huge fan.
Yeah.
He's already a wise man.
And it was, oh, and he loved platoon.
He loved platoon, specifically for the scene where Elias
keeps getting shot in the back by the natives.
This is trying to run to the helicopter,
but he keeps getting up and keeps attempting to escape.
He doesn't escape, but he's fighting to,
even though it failed.
His struggle was valiant.
So this guy Goggins was a fat motherfucker, piece of shit.
And one day something snapped.
And he listened to the thing for the details,
the Joe Rogan podcast, David Goggins.
And he just decided that's it.
He's going to now do everything he believed in.
And he started small.
He didn't do it all on day one,
but he just fucking stuck with it.
And he is now one of the most hardworking,
dedicated, driven pieces of people in the planet
was a supremely decorated Navy SEAL from nothing.
Listen to the podcast.
It's insane.
That's Nate.
What?
That story's a little light on the details.
Okay, it is.
Because I don't want to waste everybody's time.
They really should go listen to it.
Yeah, okay.
The point was he had been abused by his dad.
He had incredibly low self-esteem.
He literally faked having confidence
and being like a capable human being.
He was poor.
Well, don't we all.
Indeed, he was poor.
He had no money.
He lived with his mom.
He would go home and cry
about how sad he was about his life.
He had extreme social anxiety.
But then one day, I forget,
I don't remember what it was,
but just something changed in his mind.
And he began to think about, wouldn't it be crazy
if I, me, this huge loser, he was an exterminator.
He just quit his job when he realized this.
How old was he?
What?
He was 24, I think at the time.
I think he was 24.
So not so, he might have been 22.
I could be wrong about that.
He was around that age, though.
And he just decided,
he had always wanted to be a Navy Seal
and then he just decided to do it.
And he is now like an insane ultra marathon runner.
He is the world record holder for pull-ups,
having done 4,060 or something in 24-hour period.
Oh my God.
He is an ultra marathon runner.
He ran over 100 miles in 17 hours
when he was starting out.
He's just an insane guy.
And when I just think about all the people
out there in the world.
Wait, is he not, is he not a Kenyan?
No, he's an American, he's American.
That's so weird.
There's like, cause there's like that one,
there's like that one tribe of people in Kenya
who are like disproportionately like the best marathon runners.
And I was like, I was sure that the world record holder
for marathon running would be one of those guys.
Nope.
Based on what he said,
seems like ultra marathon running is honestly more question
of pain tolerance than anything else.
And patience, and patience.
And a lot of people just don't have that.
So the point is just like when I hear this question
about like, how can I get better or something?
And there's an answer given immediately.
I've just, this is why I'm literally starting,
what is it, Reduwe, run every day until I'm hot
because I listen to this podcast and I'm not going to stop.
When people have the solution and they don't do it,
they're worthless and they deserve death.
But when they capitalize on it,
that is when I respect them and they are good.
So do that and listen to that fucking podcast.
We'll put a link in the show notes.
Everyone should listen to it.
It's great.
It's good.
I like it.
And also draw every day.
Back to, I forgot to mention as I was saying how I got good.
Also, I drew every day for a long time.
Great.
That was also part of it.
Okay, moving on to the next one.
Oh, and finish thing.
This is from-
Don't just do sketches.
Like yeah, do a gesture drawing,
but then like finish it on top of it.
Because every stage of the drawing process
is its own skill set and you need to practice them all.
Makes sense.
And also finishing things in general.
Finishing things is a skill in and of itself
that should be trained like a muscle.
Man, that's so true.
That's an important one.
Yeah.
Next call, relevant, is from I hate myself a lot.
Let's see what he's got for us.
Okay, choose one.
Either everyone you try to communicate with
doesn't understand you or people just inexplicably hate you.
What you choose and why.
Both of those are already my life.
Both of those-
Wait, that got cut off.
My life is already both of those things.
Hmm.
So it's a choice between no one understands you
or everyone hates you.
Is there the ability to recover from everyone hating me?
Or is that set in stone?
I think this is permanent.
Well then why?
Okay.
I think these are just your conditions.
That first option.
Okay, I guess if you can communicate with people,
they still might be willing to do things for you
for example, sell you food even if they hate you
so you might not starve.
But if everyone hates you,
then they might just let you die in the streets.
So, you know, maybe I'd probably go with the first one,
I guess, I don't know.
I mean, you could probably figure out a way
to have people like you,
even though they don't understand you.
Like, oh, who's that guy?
He was like emperor so-and-so in San Francisco.
I know what you're talking about.
He was an insane person who was like,
I think he was trying to be president for a while
and then moved on to emperor.
I know you're talking about it.
Okay, no, he was like a emperor,
his name was Emperor Norton.
Yeah, Joshua Norton in San Francisco.
He was like a kind of rich guy,
like a stock trader or something or like a rice trader.
And he lost all his money, basically lost it,
dressed up in a military uniform
and stalked around the streets of San Francisco
for the rest of his life,
claiming to be the emperor of America.
And everyone loved him and he was great.
So like-
Emperor denied his throne.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, people would pay him quote unquote taxes
if they saw him in the street, you know?
Like they made dolls of him.
He printed his own money,
which some people actually accepted
in the San Francisco area just because-
Damn.
He was like a local hero.
Everyone was like, man, this emperor Norton guy,
he's the best, we love him.
Yeah, so that guy was insane and nobody understood him,
but everyone loved him.
So I feel like maybe you could finagle something like that
with the first one.
That sounds like a clear choice in my opinion.
So I'm gonna go with that one.
I agree.
Yeah.
Okay, we've got one more call
and this one's a special treat for everybody.
All right, we're once again visited by the wonder,
the creature known only as racist forest gump.
Oh, here we go, here we go.
Janae, I'm gonna join the KKK, Janae.
The forest you already noticed for the last week.
Stop.
It's not gonna be as funny the second time.
Why are you doing this?
But Janae, it's funny because it's racist.
No, for us.
Why do you need this joke?
Why?
Janae, it makes me feel good inside
when I make people laugh, who do I look up to?
Aw.
Why don't you just go outside
and get some real fucking friends, son?
Why don't you just do that?
What?
But Janae, I'm with Tony and I got AIDS.
I can't make friends, I got AIDS, Janae, I got AIDS.
I wasn't here last week, so that was new to me.
Yeah.
This is forest gump, a new beloved character
on the progressives podcast.
You know, I still have hope for him.
I think he could make some recovery here.
I think lots of people, lots of racist people with AIDS
go on to live very successful, happy lives, fulfilling also.
There's still hope.
In Trump's America, there's hope for everyone.
Even racist forest gump can rise to the top
in Trump's America.
There's nothing to say.
Let's just wrap it up there, everybody.
Are we done?
That was the last one.
This is a racist forest gump,
the last note we're going out on.
He's the headline for this podcast.
Yeah.
All right, cool.
Well, thanks for being here, everybody.
Patreon.com slash The Procrastinator's podcast.
Bonus episodes, there's 19, 20th coming pretty soon,
and the next one's gonna be pretty good, what I suspect.
I thought it was just Patreon.
Oh, the bonus one?
I thought it was just Patreon.com slash The Procrastinator's.
Did we add podcasts at the end?
Okay, you're right, there is no podcast.
It's just The Procrastinator's, I fucked it up.
Oh, you fool, you just cost us millions.
I just cost us everything.
Everyone thought that there'd been an update,
so they unpleased, and then repledge to that one.
We just lost the big account because of you.
No, we...
We gotta get back the big account,
or the boss is gonna,
this is a million dollar deal is going down.
Well, go to, pay a Twitch.
No, wait, I meant Twitter, Twitter.
At TPCrastinator's, you can send us your Bitcoin wallet key,
so we can get in there, please do that,
so we can remake these costs of living that we just lost.
And I guess that's it.
Patreon.com slash The Procrastinator's,
that's the real deal.
Give us your money, enjoy listening to the show every week.
The next bonus episode was my idea.
Actually, the next two bonus episodes were my idea,
and they're both genius.
They actually are both great.
We're trying to up our game,
and I think we got some good stuff coming.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, that said, we'll see you next week, people.
Thanks for being here.
Have a wonderful time,
and hopefully this came out at 2 p.m. when it's supposed to.
Bye.
Good bye.
Last week, they were like, I crave more PCP.
Anyway, goodbye.
Yes, also bye.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
But I'm not working, I'm doing nothing.
My dick, I'm jerking, myself, I'm sucking.
I am an asshole, I am a stupid.
I've got a deadline, don't wanna do it.