It's The Pro Crastinators Podcast starting. It's starting. It's me and Tom. It's Ben Saint
and Tom Oliver.
Yo!
The boys!
We're here. We're back.
The boys are back in town.
Never forget.
Never forget who didn't leave you hanging in these trying times.
These trying times. I feel so sad in these trying times, Tom.
Dude, I feel like-
I feel like he's trying Tom's because you're trying my patience right now.
You know, that's fair. That's fair. I have that effect on people.
Shape up.
Yeah.
I'll do my best.
So we're back. We're back for another week of whatever this is. What do we want to touch
on?
We want to talk about-
We have a full docket of exciting high energy topics to talk about this week. I'm sure.
Just bursting at the seams with adrenaline-powered discussion.
Do we want to comment on the ongoing frustration in the comment section?
Maybe we should. Maybe we should say something definitive, if not descriptive, if that makes
any sense.
Right. I kind of don't want to. I feel like we already did this, but-
The comments were particularly-
There was a lot of jokes. There were a lot of joke comments last week that I appreciated.
Indeed, indeed.
But people continue. It's like people continue to want to know why isn't Nate and Digi and
whoever else on the podcast.
It's strange because there really is no further answer. There's no mystery about it. The answer
is- Ask yourself, why is X not on the podcast? Why is it on the PCP? And no matter who it
is, the answer is because they don't feel like it.
It really is.
That's it.
There's a lot of conspiracy theories starting to pop up in the comments.
Oh, what could have happened?
This huge thawing out.
Ben and Nate are brothers, right? So they can just text each other if there's something
wrong, but they're clearly-
Why don't-
They must have had a falling out. They must hate each other. They must be ready to shoot
each other in the face.
Why don't they know? Why won't they talk about it? Why won't they just answer the question?
What's the mystery? What are they hiding? I don't know.
It's not that exciting, unfortunately.
It's really not.
We don't have any high-energy gossip that we're hiding behind our lethargic facade of this
podcast. It's just not true.
I don't know how to explain any more simply than that.
It's a beyond whenever you want show, and if someone's not showing up, it's just because
they don't feel like it, and that's it.
I mean, Nate just said he doesn't feel like being on the show right now, and that's all
we know.
He did.
That's all that really needs to be said. There's no feud.
He's still, because Nate does all the finance stuff.
He runs the pay calculations and everything.
Yeah, he's still doing the spreadsheet stuff to calculate pay and whatever.
He just messaged us yesterday talking about how we need to get some stuff in for the
diss track. He's still working on the diss track and the music video and everything.
That's right.
There's not a schism.
Nate is still around. He's still talking to us.
We are still working on all the Radcon content that is still in the other.
I had actually wondered about, there's some Radcon stuff that I know the status of, and
there's other stuff that I didn't know the status of.
I was wondering about what Nate mentioned yesterday to Hippo asked about it a while
back.
Should we say the diss track?
Is that a spoiler to say, or do people know about that?
I don't know.
Do I care at this point?
I feel like it's been so long since Radcon that the joke is kind of old now and that
when all this comes out, it's going to be like, okay, that's cool.
This has been dealt with.
You know, it'll just be for the real OG fans.
That's true.
If you're an OG, PCP head, I feel like it's going to be evergreen.
If you're not, then our Radcon in-jokes probably wouldn't have landed with you no matter when
they came out.
It's going to take so long.
We're going to get to the point where we finally drop it and we're going to get a bunch of
comments complaining.
What's all this high energy content coming out?
I thought the Procrastor's podcast was a relaxing chill vibes, no fucking drama shit.
We're going to shed our whole audience and then, yeah, if more people start being on,
people will be like, why is every episode such a clusterfuck?
This is not the PCP that I remember.
I started listening to the PCP around the same time I got my first gaming console, the
PS5, and I don't understand what this means.
Dude, that's something we could talk about, the fucking PS5 and the new Xbox and all that
shit and how all that's being announced and the new graphics cards.
Gaming's getting so much more complicated, guys.
It's expensive.
They're upselling us.
Games are $70 a pop now, confirmed.
I have only, I don't keep up with it because I don't ever intend to purchase a console
again, but I have been seeing a lot of shit about the $70 price tag.
It is a nightmare.
And some shit about the PS5 will come with a version that does not accept physical discs
or something like that.
It's $400 for the digital version.
And if you want to pay $100 extra, you too can get an optical drive that was advanced
technology 15 years ago.
Oh boy.
It's almost like they're trying to kill the used games market so they can have everyone
buy only digital and reap all the sick 30% cut they get for every digital purchase through
their storefront.
What?
Weaponize and capitalism against the pro terriot?
Wait a minute, Tom.
Are you telling me that the AAA gaming industry is engaging in anti-consumer practices?
Do I have a name for you?
Check out.
You should watch some guy named Jim Sterling.
He'll set you straight.
Yeah.
And pop into him every once in a while and watch his latest few videos and go, yep, gaming
still looks like shit.
I haven't watched any of his videos in like half a year because YouTube just stopped recommending
them to me and I unsubscribed from like every channel that wasn't like a blender tutorial.
So now like all my old subscriptions and like recommendations are just gone now.
It's very strange.
Well, I had watched him before and I watched him again recently and it's-
It's still the same thing.
Nothing's changed.
The more things change, well, the more things change, the more they stay the same.
Now there's a new kick about how like Ubisoft is not only, you know, terribly anti-consumer
and a bad company and evil.
It's also like stacked with like, you know, sexual abusers and people that covered for
them.
And I guess to Jim, this is a problem or whatever.
He's made this a big deal or something.
God.
That's the new, that's the new, the new goss from over there.
Yeah.
In case you didn't want to go and catch up yourself.
Are you telling me video games are not made for the love of making interactive entertainment?
Are you telling me the single biggest entertainment industry on the planet does not come from a
place of passion?
Say it ain't so.
You know, it does.
The groundlings, the groundlings doing the labor probably do love games.
Oh, absolutely.
But Bobby Kotick doesn't like video- Bobby Kotick's not a gamer.
What?
No.
How?
This is why these fucking commies don't understand, as they tweet from their iPhones that capitalism
made, by the way.
You know, the capitalism's bad.
Don't they understand that if we didn't have monopolies or conglomerates like Ubisoft,
then the only people making games would be like just human beings that like them and not
like a multinational conglomerate that, you know, does all this bullshit.
That packages their games.
Can you imagine if every...
What would we do if we didn't have Ubisoft to siphon off the surplus labor value of the
people who love making games for us?
If all the video games that came out were just shitty fucking indie titles like Undertale,
imagine a games market where everything was like Undertale instead of like a bloated microtransaction
infused nightmare.
I don't remember, I don't remember ducking behind cover to regenerate health in between
rounds of firing my gun.
Ben, Ben, you don't fire a single gun in Undertale.
What a failure of a video game.
You can't even play with your friends.
You can't even put...
What is the point if I'm not playing a virtualized sport, playing the same three maps over and
over again in 20 minute chunks while I'm throwing money at skins?
What's the point?
It's like you just read.
Like half of what you do in Undertale is just read words.
Cringe, bro.
Cringe.
What does that mean?
I didn't buy a $600 PlayStation to read books, you fucking idiot.
Toby Fox, what a hack.
Okay, okay.
No, no.
Video games, bad.
Is Among Us an indie?
Among Us looks indie.
It's gotta be indie.
It looks so indie.
AAA developers, they don't make 2D games anymore.
That doesn't sell to fucking normies.
I think I'm gonna pick up Among Us and give it a try.
It looks titillating.
It looks like a lot of fun.
I like the idea of a game where you lie and betray your comrades.
Among Us is $5.
There is no way this is not an indie game.
Really?
Oh, wow.
Okay.
That's pretty good.
It's cool.
All right.
That's probably gonna be $5 well spent.
I could play that for like an hour and it would be $5 well spent.
So that's pretty good.
Speaking of, oh man, speaking of a deal, of a deal and a half, do you want to know about,
do you want to know about my gummy shit?
Please tell me more.
I saw your tweet and I demand clarification.
Yeah.
Okay, so let's...
Right.
So, to briefly recap, the ingredient that I use, isomaltoligosaccharides, a fiber derived
ingredient from tapioca is...
They don't seem...
I can't find it on Amazon anymore.
So, I went to Alibaba, the place that I was looking...
That I'm getting the pins made and stuff for the RFCK Kickstarter.
And I looked there and lo and behold, yeah, they have it there.
There's actually a whole bunch of distributors that sell isomaltoligosaccharides.
It turns out that it's actually like mostly made in like China and Japan and around...
In the East or whatever.
So, yeah, and it's a one kilogram bag that I bought from Amazon cost me like $12.
A kilogram over there from a lot of these places costs like $150 to $2.
So, amazing, right?
What a deal.
The only catch though, is that these are like industrial suppliers and I mean, I'm still
looking but it seems like a lot of them have a minimum order on the order of maybe like
100 kilograms, which is like 220 pounds.
But I bought like 20 pounds of the stuff, about 10 kilograms on Amazon before and that
cost me like $200 because it costs so much more per pound.
So, if I buy 200 pounds of it from Alibaba, it'll still cost me only maybe like two or
300.
You're up by a factor of 10.
It won't even cost that much more.
You're getting 10 times more for your money.
Yeah, and I'll have it forever.
I'll have it forever.
So, I don't know.
I'm thinking I might do it even if I have...
I mean, I might find someone who will sell me less.
I would ideally only like to buy maybe like 10 or 20, like maybe 10 kilograms, 20 kilograms
tops, but if I have to buy 100, I mean, I'll probably do it and I'm really hoping that
it shows up in like a big like barrel or oil drum or something and I just like keep it
outside because it doesn't fit my house.
Oh, yeah.
I can imagine the joy the mailman will feel rolling a giant oil drum covered in Chinese
text in the middle of a pandemic over to Ben's house.
I made a batch with an alternate form and a fructo-ligosaccharide and it's bad.
It not only has a weird taste to it, but it gives me gas and I hate it.
I don't know.
It's like bad for you or something.
It's like not...
It's edible, but it's like, no, don't do it.
And I was thinking...
I was thinking about RFCK gummies again and I was thinking about how I would make them
and I was looking at Amazon because I'm like, oh, I ordered a big block.
I ordered like a full kilogram of sheet gelatin and like a kilogram of sheet gelatin is like
a lot because a little bit of sheet gelatin goes a long way because it's highly concentrated.
So I spent $60 on a full kilogram of sheet gelatin because sheet gelatin is superior
in every way to the powdered.
So I'm going to get that.
I got that and now I'm going to have all this.
I'm going to have all this IMO, isomaltoligosaccharide and I'm like, well, I'm going to have to
do something with all this.
So I was thinking about RFCK gummies and I was thinking about how I would make them and
I thought it would be actually kind of easy because RFCK has fruits.
Do you know about crops?
Do you know about RFCK crops?
I don't know anything about RFCK.
RFCK exists.
Well, juvies can farm all these crops and there are a whole bunch of them.
There are blood cabbages, a purple killer flower is a popular one, pink rowdishes,
suganma nuts, razor nuts, joy beans, bright shade.
I'm going to forget.
Pulp gourds, paw paws, an American classic.
So there's all these fruits that they have over there.
What are the functional differences between them gameplay wise?
You can mill them and milling them gets you different things.
You get different colored dies from milling them and I think other things too.
I'm not exactly sure what each one gives.
But yeah, you mill them at the mill to get stuff.
And I'm thinking, hey, oh, and dire apples.
You can't forget about dire apples.
And I'm thinking, okay, all I would need to do is buy fruit shapes and then just color them differently, flavor them differently.
So I could just have a blue apple and make a dire apple.
Easy.
All I could do, oh, black limes.
I could just have a lime-flavored gummy, a lime-shaped gummy, diet black.
Make it lime flavor.
Sell it.
Bam.
I could sell them in bags of a pound to the incredibly small market that I'm sure would be in.
But there would be a small but incredibly dedicated market that would probably be all over it.
You got the whole following thing on lock.
You really should be quintuple dipping into that.
That's what I'd be doing.
So I was looking on Amazon for fruit-shaped gummy molds and they're all crap.
They're all terrible.
They all have pineapples and I don't want pineapples.
I want a pear shape.
I want an apple shape.
A generic berry would be fine.
A citrus.
It was simple.
Simple, but they're very limited.
There's very limited things on Amazon.
Maybe I should check eBay.
I could expand my search on eBay.
You got to go back to Alibaba.
Or even Alibaba.
Or yeah, or even Alibaba, which has proven to be a better source of literally everything that I have checked it for.
People are sleeping on Alibaba.
Seriously.
I use AliExpress and Banggood all the time.
I use Banggood just because it has a hilarious name.
And I love shopping on there.
Is AliExpress related to Alibaba?
I was going to ask you if you know, because I'm not sure.
I've never dug deep, but I would assume they have to be some sort of related thing, right?
One could just be a knockoff of the other.
I mean, it's China, so it's very possible.
They have no protection for those things.
All I know is they're both pretty good.
Wait, sorry.
Some idiot said something wrong on Twitter and I have to kill them.
Oh, no.
Live.
We're watching it happen live, everyone.
Okay.
Or I am.
You guys are listening to this a week after it happened.
Okay.
Some fucking moron just deliberately misinterpreting something incredibly clear that I said.
So Twitter is usual.
What else is there?
It's just Twitter and Twitter.
You're not used to it by now?
It doesn't just bounce off you?
It doesn't.
No.
I am used to it, but it doesn't bounce off me.
I still get mad.
I see your problem.
So, yeah.
So that's the gummy update.
I want to know immediately when the 200 pound oil drum shows up at your house.
Honestly, honestly, I hope.
I kind of hope that I do end up just buying 100 pounds because like fuck it, you know,
that'll keep me in gummies for years.
The memes alone will make it worth it.
I'm going to make them for years.
I'm not going to give up and stop making them.
I've put in all this work.
I'm not just going to stop.
That's true.
It's not even a waste.
I will literally use all 100 kilograms of it.
Lamal.
Some of them have a minimum order of a metric ton.
What the fuck?
I mean, presumably you would sell it to a factory or something.
I mean, I guess.
An industrial manufacturer.
It's not for plebs like me, but I want to get in on the market.
You say that now, but once it becomes a burgeoning business.
Yeah, a year.
All of a sudden a metric ton.
It's just like, that's my minimum order to you.
You know, business is booming.
That's, you know, speaking of buying in bulk, I've been fulfilling the vapor's orders.
I have sent out basically all of the ones that don't involve like a, a sketch or a signature.
I'm putting in like pretty, like I'm putting a lot of detail into the reward drawings.
Like I'm coloring them and everything.
So it's taken me a while, but hopefully it's worth it.
But I'm actually getting pretty close to being out of copies of chapter one.
Because I had lots of leftovers from book one from the first Kickstarter.
So the idea was that I would just sell them again during this Kickstarter, which I did.
And I don't think I'm quite going to run out.
But I think if like everyone who ordered, but has not like signed up, put their information into their reward survey.
I think if everyone did that, I would in fact run out and have to order like another shipment of it.
And then it's like, ooh, well, would I order another 500 because there's a price break or would that be wasteful?
Maybe I should just get like 100 or something.
I guess it depends on how many you need.
If you need like four, I would just say just go down to Kinko's and get four made.
Yeah.
You know what?
If it's like, if I was going to do another like mass Kickstarter or something, then maybe I would order another few hundred.
But like, no, in this case, it would probably be like 20 or 30 that I would need extra tops.
So yeah, okay.
That's actually, that's what I should do.
Problem solved.
Glad I could help.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Yeah.
Gummies, gummies and vapors, and vapors too.
That's what I've been up to.
So like, hold like last two months of your life.
Do you pretty hardcore?
Yeah.
Okay.
I got to mention one more thing.
It's got me very excited.
It's another RFCK thing, but we had the War on Quickville contest, you know.
Yeah.
In Retribution for the Bicarbonate Rain, you know, we had to go after, after, you know,
the Slime version of Lock-a-Com moved from the Beta Prime Timeline to the Alpha Timeline,
and Slime was restored to Dimension C197.
You know, obviously there was nothing left to do but go to war.
So we did.
And me and Gib judged it.
And boy, oh, fucking boy.
It was like, like right until before the judging, there were like no, there were like less than
10 entries.
There were like so few entries and they were mostly small.
There was like an image or like, you know, like one, like written a text story or whatever.
And I was like, oh God, nobody's entering this one.
This is like, this is a complete bust.
But then like an hour before the contest judging, like 30 people just like bombarded it with
entries.
And we had possible, I would say possibly some of the most, some of the most legendary entries
that I've heard.
Some of the most, some of the funniest ones.
We had like this, this song, Oreo Sama made this, he wrote this song.
It was called Blood.
Was it Pissed Blood and Shit?
Fuck, I might be mixing around the order.
But we were fucking, we were fucking, or we are split, where our sides were split.
RoboDobo wrote this, this like really long story about Paradox Crocs and Sonic the Hedgehog.
Sonic the Hedgehog and Crocs both want to be the one to defeat Christine.
So they have to fight one another in order to, you know, the winner gets to go on and do that.
And I don't know.
I'm not going to explain it because it wouldn't be funny if I just told you like what happened.
But oh my goodness.
Oh my goodness gracious.
I could not, could not breathe.
Was that the winner of the contest?
It was a winner.
There were multiple winners.
Both of those were.
We named six different winners.
Because we were very, very generous.
And I just want to, I don't know.
RFCK, thanks for, this goes out to all you kids out there.
Thanks for, thanks for making that a real fucking banger of an event, I guess.
It was, it was truly epic.
Fantastic.
Very, very good.
Very good.
Okay.
So that's been my week.
How's your week been?
It's been interesting.
I mean, I went to a hotel for like four days from like Sunday to Thursday.
Because I was just like.
Why?
Because I've been trapped in this house doing nothing because, you know, back pain slash COVID.
And I was like, I can't stand it.
I need to change a scenery.
This is driving me nuts.
I'm just going to go to a hotel.
Really?
Just, just to get out.
You just, you just booked a hotel just because.
Just because.
Just because I felt like it.
I was like, I just need to break.
I need, I need to change a scenery.
I'm whatever.
I'll not do any work.
I'll stop working.
I'll just like chill and do nothing, whatever.
And so I did that.
And I just went to a hotel for a little bit and it was kind of gay.
I was, I was hoping it would be like a change of scenery and like stop working.
Would allow me to like recharge my batteries and kind of like recenter myself and like,
all right, this is like what I'm going to do.
Just kind of like lame.
Just kind of sucked.
Just kind of dumb.
I guess it's cause like the only time I go to hotels is like go to conventions and hang
out with people.
And so I had like meant to leave and like hotels are like, cool.
But when you there by yourself, it's just the worst.
It's just crap and dour.
And it's cause of COVID, like they didn't even have free breakfast, which is like half
the reason to go to a hotel is to get free breakfast.
They didn't even have that stinks.
The best thing is they had a fucking vending machine that had like ice cream bars, like
go get ice cream whenever I wanted with no effort.
And that was pretty cool.
But other than that, it was like a dollar.
The dollar's fine.
I can handle a dollar.
No, I mean, I mean the hotel.
No, the prices are pretty low.
It was like to stay there for like five days.
I think it was like $330 or something.
It's not a huge deal.
That's, I mean, that's more, that's more than I would spend.
It's more than anyone should spend.
You must have, you must have been, you must have really wanted to get out of it.
It was, it was very bad.
The desire to leave was very strong.
It was a very, not a premeditated decision.
I was just like, fuck it, gone, done, by, and I left.
So that was cool.
But, um, yeah, not, not great, not super fun, but I just kind of like,
dick around and just like, okay, I'm here.
Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait, did you just dick around like on the hotel grounds
for like three days or how many days?
This is like four nights or something like that.
I just kind of was just like watching TV or just going around,
like going around the town because like I went like one town over
and just kind of like doing stuff around there.
Do you, do you want to say what the town was or is that?
It doesn't matter.
It's the, it's the middle of nowhere in Massachusetts.
They're all kind of blend together once you get outside of Boston.
It's all the same thing.
Um, yeah, sure, sure, sure.
But yeah, so it's just doing that.
And then on the last day, I like hurt my back again.
Uh, so I came home and then I was in bed for two days and I just
watched more cartoons and it was great.
I watched like all of the Owl House, which I've been meaning to watch.
That was really cool.
I watched all of season one of Amphibia.
I watched all of Infinity Train, which is amazing.
I saw you tweeting about Infinity Train.
It's so good.
It's, it's, it doesn't, it doesn't look good.
I don't want to watch it.
The art style is not good.
And that's the reason I didn't watch it, uh, back before.
Cause it's like, oh, this looks ugly as sin.
And then my sister, what I object to about it is just that it looks
like every other fucking cartoon these days.
It's like, it just, yeah.
It looks like a worse version of every cartoon out these days.
It's just like a very generic art style.
And so I was not invested in it at all, but the story is really cool.
And the way it's told is, it's like, did you watch over the garden
wall from like five years ago?
I watched it, um, like a couple of years after it came out,
but I did eventually watch it.
Yeah.
Infinity Train reminds me of overgarden the wall in terms of tone.
The story and everything is nothing like it, but like in terms of
just like being kind of like vague and like not really understood,
not knowing exactly what's going on and not being sure what's
going to happen next.
Infinity Train does that as well.
The story.
Is it, is it an ongoing series?
It is ongoing.
Um, but the cool thing about Infinity Train is that each season
is its own story.
So, and then the next season, there's a new protagonist.
Uh, that's one of the, one of the.
One of the minor characters from the previous season.
So every season you're like, hmm, I wonder which random person
that only showed up for like a small segment is going to have
an entire, their own story next season.
It's a really interesting concept.
How many seasons are there three so far?
And the reason why I want to bring up Infinity Train specifically
is it's going to get canceled because everything is bad.
Uh, the guy who makes the show is like, yeah, I had eight seasons
planned because like eight is like an infinity symbol.
Haha.
I'm clever.
But he had like, he had like eight seasons he wants to do.
And like there's like, he's building to something bigger.
I guess there's like an underpinning thing that they've been working
towards.
And, uh, HBO is just like, this show is like too complicated
for children, even though we're fucking HBO.
Uh, no, we don't want to make this anymore.
And so like they haven't been renewed for season four,
which really sucks.
Why did they make it in the first place?
I don't know because like that's the dumb thing is because the
first two seasons were on Karch Network, then HBO bought it to
put on HBO Max and they're like, actually, we were wrong.
This is dumb.
And now they're trying to get rid of it.
I'm like, you fools, you Neanderthals.
Cause like the third season was the first one on HBO.
And so they're like, oh, we don't have to make it just for
children.
And it got like way darker and cooler and like could do more
things.
Uh, and then they're just like, what if we didn't do these
anymore?
I'm like, oh, you fucking, you rubes, you morons.
Uh, it makes me really mad because it's so fucking cool.
It's so good.
Uh, like the concept is that like huge, like random people just
end up on this train that goes on for infinity.
There's like a million different cars that like go forever.
And you get like a number on your hand and that number represents
like, uh, how bad whatever fucking problem in your life you
need to deal with this.
And you're just trapped on this train until you can figure out
how to deal with your shit.
And once that number goes down to zero, you get off the train.
Uh, and each character has their own things they're dealing
with.
And like these cars are just like randomly generated by a
machine algorithm to like, uh, help them like deal with their
shit.
And it's really fucking cool.
And it's, it's just like really mysterious on how everything
works.
And, uh, it's great.
And it's a 10 out of 10.
And I recommend it super highly.
Watch infinity train.
The episodes are short.
The season is short.
There are 11 minute episodes.
And that was going to be my next question is how long is the
season?
How long is an episode?
It's like, it's like 10 episodes a season, 11 minutes a pop.
It's like watching a short little movie.
You're in and out and done.
Not even.
It's good.
It's not even that bad.
Okay.
It's super good.
I think it might maybe give it a little, a little look.
The first season's first season's like at eight.
The second season is like a 10 and the third season's like
another 10 or a nine.
They're, they're really good.
Um, okay.
Yeah.
I see.
Definitely, definitely recommend that.
And then our house and amphibia are both really good too, but
they're much more, I don't want to say generic, but like they're
basically just following the gravity follows formula.
Like if you've seen gravity follows, you've seen amphibia and
owl house.
They're the exact same thing.
It's, it's like hygiene.
So the comedy's written like exactly the same way.
It's like, wait, wait.
You're comparing.
Wait, what is the same thing as what amphibia?
What is amphibia?
Amphibia.
I don't know what that is.
Amphibia is like a show where this like girl gets isochided to
a world of like amphibians, like a fantasy kind of world with
like, like frogs and toads and newts and stuff.
And, uh, that came out last year.
And then owl house is where, uh, a girl see owl house is about
that like, no, I'm thinking of loud house.
Sorry.
No, I don't know anything about owl house.
Yeah.
Owl house is about a girl who gets isochided to a world of
like sorcery and shit.
And they're basically the exact same kind of premise.
They have the exact same kind of comedy as gravity falls and
they follow the same sort of structure.
I, I just hate how fucking cartoons look these days.
I don't know.
I hate, I just looked up amphibia.
Oh, look, it looks the same.
I'm going to, I'm going to look up owl house.
I think owl house.
Is it going to look the same?
It looks a bit better.
I think owl house is probably the best looking one out of all
the ones I've been talking about so far.
Oh, it's, it's close enough.
I don't like it.
I like, I like owl house.
I mean, aesthetically, they all look very similar, but like the,
I guess the good thing about be having like a simplistic art
style is they're all animated pretty well.
Like the animation is really smooth and stuff.
It's not that I don't understand why they look like this.
I understand the advantages.
I just, I mean, I'm with you.
I made a whole video complaining about how like modern cartoons,
they're like very stylized, but they all use the same kind of
stylization where like when you become that like, uh, uh,
yeah, vague and like not representational, you have so much
more room to play with shape and stuff.
And most of these cartoons don't.
And it's sad.
Yeah.
Cause like the, the what, like the American cartoon industry is
very like, uh, nepotism.
I don't know if that's the right word, but like it's basically
like, like Alex Hirsch is the voice of like one of the main
characters on the owl house because like, I think he,
like someone who worked on gravity falls is now the lead of
that show.
And then he was working on another show before we got gravity
falls.
It's like, they're all just kind of giving their friends shows
and like that's how all these things get made.
So they're all pulling from the same continual pool of talent,
uh, which is like, that's why they're all, they all feel the
same.
Like all these shows are written exactly the same way.
Like gravity falls has like, you know, these like.
Just.
It starts with like a lot of like one off kind of character
things, but then you have this older mentor character who has
like a dark secret and like more complicated past.
And as a story goes, it gets more complicated and the owl
house and amphibia both do exactly the same thing.
And it's just like, these are good characters and they're good
stories.
And I recommend the both.
I mean, to an extent there's the like, you know, there are only
like seven different stories you can tell.
But when like Disney puts out three of the shows.
It's the same people.
Within five years and they all follow the exact same beats to
a T.
It's just like hot pop from amphibia.
He like knows what's really going on with Anne and like where
she came from and she, he's like keeping it a secret and
they're slowly.
Hinting at it.
It's like, oh, so just like fucking grunkle stand.
And then it's like an owl house.
It's like, Eda, the old witch, she has like this dark past and
knows more about the shit than she's letting on.
And the story is getting more complex as it goes on.
I'm like, oh, so just like grunkle stand.
It's like the exact same thing.
I'm like, like this is fine.
Like it's good.
And like I'm, I'm, I'm able to turn off my brain and enjoy these
shows and have a good time and they are fun.
But at the same time, I am just watching two more versions of
Gravity Falls again.
And like, I get it.
I'm fine with that.
But at the same time, come on, mix it up a little bit.
Mm hmm.
Um, but Infinity Train is its own thing and it's fucking based.
That's why they're going to cancel it.
And these other shows are going to keep going until they're done
because that's.
Is it confirmed?
Are they definitely canceling it?
It's not confirmed, but they haven't been renewed yet.
And a bunch of the staff has been moved to other projects.
So like it's all but confirmed.
Oh God, they'll have to fucking Indiegogo it or whatever.
Or they'll just get like someone to keep, keep it going as a comic
something as a lot of these shows do.
Oh yeah.
Sure.
Yeah.
There's always that.
There's always the, uh, the incredibly lucrative comics market
you could break into.
Hey, you know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
They can, they can join me.
They can join me in the clouds.
Indeed.
Get that, get those kick starters going.
That's, that's where the real money is.
Um, oh fuck.
That reminded me of something.
Fuck.
Oh no, it's gone.
Oh no.
That was like.
I was, uh, oh.
Gotta take note spend.
You gotta be ready to go.
I should have written it down.
Oh no.
Wait, what, what, what were they doing?
What was I doing this, this week?
There was some show.
Oh.
Oh, I remember.
I watched another.
Cause you know, I watched them, um, the, uh, who's afraid of Virginia Wolf.
Yes.
Two weeks ago, I think.
I asked on Twitter for recommendations for, um, another other movies like that
that are just about people talking.
And, uh, there, I got a lot.
I got a lot of recommendations actually.
And, uh, I picked one.
I picked one at random and I watched it.
And I feel this, someone, someone said like, I love this.
I love the genre of movies about people talking.
It's a good, uh, and then they listed some of their favorites and I picked one and I
watched it and I feel bad because I didn't like it.
Oh fuck.
I hate to call this person out and say, Hey, your favorite.
It sucks.
But, uh, I'm.
You gotta do it anyway.
I'm going to do it anyway.
This was a, this retro PK recommended cat on a hot tin roof and guess who's coming to
dinner.
And I had not seen either of them and I watched guess who's coming to dinner, which is about
a, um, uh, it is, uh, about a, a, uh, a girl, uh, uh, visit her parents, uh, and is like,
I'm getting married, but uh-oh, she's getting married to a black guy.
What the fuck are we going to do about this?
Parents cope with this shit or will they have a fucking problem?
Uh, uh, and it wasn't, I mean, I wouldn't say the whole thing was, I didn't hate all of
it.
There was a lot of like pretty good dialogue throughout a lot of the movie.
Um, there's a lot of like, you know, there's, there's pretty good, there's some intrigue,
like, you know, the, the, the guy, he's like, he talks to the dad and he's like, they, they,
they, they make all these ultimatums.
He's like, listen, I want the daughter's like, I'm getting married to this guy.
No matter what you say, I just wanted to, you know, introduce you before and we're going
off to get married, like, you know, in a week from now and then later and then privately,
the guy is like, hey, listen, you're her dad.
Well, I'm going to tell you, even though she wants to get married, no matter what you say,
I will not marry her unless you say it's okay because I don't want, you know, problems in
my life.
It'll be too complicated.
And then like later on, they're like, and the dad's like, oh, well, I just need some
time to get figured out by this.
Okay.
Well, maybe in a, before the week is up, I can, I can come to terms with it, but then
they're like, oh no, the timetables moved up.
Now we're going tonight.
Dad, you better, you better give your blessing tonight or the wedding's off.
It's like, ah, fuck, you know, and that's, it's fine.
That's all fine and all.
It's good.
And, and also racism's bad.
So I, I agree with the general thrust of the movie, but I was deeply, deeply annoyed at
the way that basically the main character of the movie is the racist dad.
And like the movie is very sympathetic to this old racist white guy who's having like
a real big problem with the fact that he's always marrying a black man.
It's very sympathetic.
It's very, which is, it's not the worst thing in the world.
Like I get it.
It's okay.
And you know, he does in the end, he just decides, you know what, I also think racism's bad,
but it's really annoying because all the black characters in the movie, except for the guy,
except for the fiance, all the other, and his mom, I guess, but all the other black characters,
like the, the maid and the dad are all portrayed as like, sure, this white guy is kind of racist,
but these black people, like they're really racist.
Like they're the real racists.
They're like way against it and they won't even be dissuaded.
And the final scene of the movie, the white guy, he stands up and he just, he delivers
like what I think is meant to be like a big like moving speech, but the moving speech
is he basically just recounts the entire plot of the movie as though I hadn't just watched
it and then like pronounces to all these characters how like he's decided that actually racism
is bad.
And it's okay for my daughter, Mariah Blackman, and the, and the black dad who thinks his
son should marry a black girl just like doesn't even say anything about it, just meekly accepts
it.
That's the end.
The white guy has said it, he's, now that he's accepted that racism is bad, the movie's
thesis is proved, and we can all sit down and have the titular dinner.
Alright.
I thought that was so irritating.
Would you say this movie was a victim of its time?
Is it?
I'm sure it was, I'm sure it was seen as extremely progressive in its day and I guess to a degree
it's good, the movie's about how racism is bad, but the way it's framed is like real,
real annoying.
There's still some vestigial racism in the characterization.
Yeah, just in some of the choices, just in some of the choices that they make and how
they choose to present it and how the conflict is resolved, it's like, I don't want to sympathize
with this guy, fuck this guy.
Well, yeah, I mean I guess I can understand that.
I guess I'm assuming the point is that it's trying to show this, it's a flawed character
growing, but when you-
Yeah, no, yeah, I'm being a little hard on it, I'm being a little hard on it, I get why.
I get that it's like, I mean the movie is made, I'm sure the movie was made with a mostly
white audience in mind, right?
I'm sure.
It's like an old Hollywood movie and it's, you know, there's a whole, I mean there's a
whole subgenre of movies that are about how racism is bad, but they're all, they're framed
through the context of some kind of, this white guy, you know, this white protagonist,
yeah, he's kind of racist, but you know, he's got a good heart, he's a fundamentally good guy,
and then he, you know, meets a black guy who's like, oh, you're not like those other black guys,
you're different, oh, that's the other thing.
The way the parents are like, they come around to the guy marrying their daughter, but it's
this guy is like an insanely quality, he's like hyper over competent qualified, he's like a,
he's like this famous like, like biomedical professor or something, he's like,
he's not like a normal, they really don't decide like, oh, racism is wrong.
They decide like, okay, this like one like super qualified famous black guy, like he's
alright, they're not all bad, you know?
Like that's what it takes to get them to be like, maybe it's okay for her to marry him,
sorry retro PK for sitting on your on a movie you really like, I'm sorry, sorry.
I don't know if I don't know if they're even listening, but maybe someday.
But I'm going to keep, I'm going to keep going.
I'm going to keep watching movies about nothing happening.
Man, if you want to watch a movie about nothing happening and every people just talk,
can I recommend a little movie called Colerx?
I don't know if you ever heard of it.
It's a small indie film.
I have, I have never actually seen clerks.
What?
Wait, wait, wait.
No, yes, I have.
It's in black and white.
Yeah.
Yeah, no, I've seen clerks.
You're my age.
You've definitely seen clerks.
Everyone, everyone 31 has seen clerks.
You say that, but I feel like clerks was a little bit before our time.
Like clerks was was cool.
Like clerks was new when like, Gen X was like teenagers, right?
Maybe.
I don't know.
Everybody, everybody I grew up with was like, clerks was so fucking cool.
You got to watch clerks.
So maybe it was just my social circle, but it made me feel like clerks was like a cultural
important thing of our time, our age.
I think Kevin Smith was a little bit.
I think Kevin Smith's heyday was like a little bit before you and me.
But, but, but like it's a little enough.
Yeah, by a little enough that it bled over.
I did.
My, my circle was not like, we didn't talk.
Clerks was not like a thing we were super excited about, but somebody mentioned it.
And I watched it at some point.
That's the one where the lady is like the professional like jerks off the animals for
semen or something.
Like as a vet thing.
That's the part I remember is like the lady jerks off dogs for artificial insemination
or something.
And there's the thing about snowballing.
Yeah.
Am I?
That's that's incorrect.
Yeah.
Good stuff.
My girlfriend's 37 dicks in a row.
That's the part I remember.
Doesn't the guy, doesn't the guy like die in the bathroom?
A guy does die in the bathroom.
Yes.
And the lady fucks him because she doesn't know he's dead because it's dark and like
rigor mortis.
She thinks.
She thinks it's.
Boilers for clerks.
Yeah.
You've never seen clerks.
They're the fucks wrong with you.
You idiots.
Yeah.
She thinks she thinks it's Dante.
The main character goes into the bathroom and fucks a dead guy because she thinks it's
her boyfriend.
Right.
Cause cause the dick.
Cause the hard rigor mortis dick.
Yeah.
What a classic.
What a what a what a time to be alive.
Yeah.
Spoilers.
I never saw clerks too.
That's what I'm thinking of.
Clerks too.
Is okay.
There's some funny.
There's some funny moments.
It's not as good as the first one.
As one would expect.
It's weird.
It's weird that I'm like have like watched two movies.
I like never watch movies.
The last movie I watched was a before like this month was um fucking um what was the new
um Mad Max.
Fury Road.
Just Fury Road.
Which I watched in fucking like last November.
I thought you meant like when it came out and like that's like five years ago.
You haven't watched a movie in five years.
God damn.
No.
It's not that bad.
It's okay.
Yeah.
Um I've been watching a lot of Godzilla movies because me and Jack Saber doing a podcast
going through every single Godzilla movie called Squadzilla.
It's pretty good.
Oh, it's pretty.
That's pretty good.
That's pretty cool.
That's a pretty good theme for a podcast.
That'll be that's a much that's a much better theme than the.
It's really weird being on a podcast with like topics to discuss.
It's it's strange.
Never never done it before now, but you know it's an interesting change of pace.
You know, you know, when I when before we started the PCP, I was like the PC.
I was like if we're if we're all going to start a podcast, there should be a theme.
We should have a theme like like for instance, you know, watching every every whatever about
Godzilla, whatever, Tokusatsu.
Wait, is Tokusatsu a different thing?
That's just like the live action special effects genre.
So yeah, Godzilla movies would fall into the Tokusatsu genre.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Like watching every like I pushed for something like that, but I didn't have any specific
nobody had any specific ideas, so we didn't do it.
So we decided to just do different topics.
I mean, to be fair, in most of the conversations since that initial one about topics, I have
championed that idea along with you that like if we're going to like do something with topics,
we would need to niche down.
That's like how you make a podcast successful is like you attract an audience around something
people are already interested in.
And yeah, which is like like that, like that was what I thought a podcast should be.
I had just I think around the around the time we were starting the PCP, I had just finished,
I had been binging the Oh, fuck, what's it called the worst idea podcast, the one where
every every week they watch grownups to and then they record a podcast talking about grownups
to they did like they do like a hundred episodes.
I only I only watch the first I only listen to the first one.
Well, fortunately, I didn't make it all the way through season two.
The fact the fact that they can even get 50 episodes out of that is amazing.
Well, after after a while, I mean, they do they do keep noticing like weird little things.
But after a while, they start like they start talking about like the personal lives of like
all the different like the most minor actors.
And like they start, I guess, one of like the jocks in like a party scene or whatever is
played by Patrick Schwarzenegger, Arnold's son.
And, you know, they come and I guess and I guess Patrick Schwarzenegger was dating like
Taylor Swift or something for a while.
And so they have this they create like a little segment, the Patty Schwartz party time where
they like have like a week of a weekly update on like the goings on in the life of Patrick
Schwarzenegger, talk about his relationship with Taylor Swift and how that's progressing
and all that, which, you know, was great.
But, you know, but if you want, if you don't want to have your podcast be about something
as specific as that, that's fine.
But and and yeah, my and my thing about topics is just as I've always said is like, if the
podcast can just be about whatever topic, then like all you got to do is just show up and
mention whatever topic you want to talk about it and we'll talk about it.
We don't have like not you.
I don't I don't see the utility of like deciding ahead of the episode was like, OK, this episode
of this podcast is going to be about some, you know, Godzilla movies and then next week
it'll be about whatever the fuck, you know, you talk about Godzilla if you want to talk
about I think the idea is just to corral the conversation and keep the entire episode on
point for marketing purposes.
But I would just say go the extra mile.
If you're going to do that for the whole podcast.
Yeah, if you're going to do that for marketing.
Yeah, I don't think I don't know if it works that well unless you go all out with it and
make the whole thing.
It's like because nobody's going to say like, oh, have you heard about this podcast?
Yeah, they did an episode about such and such thing.
I mean, maybe.
But they're more you're more likely to just get word of mouth.
It's like, oh, have you heard about this one podcast?
It's all about like it's a whole podcast about us to topic that I'm interested in.
Yeah, grow about grownups to or about, you know, welcome to night.
I mean, at this point, the procrastinators podcast is a personality driven show.
And that's like the other side of the spectrum we've always been talking about in our inside
baseball meetings is like it either needs to be about us personality wise or about a
specific topic being in the middle is just like the worst of both worlds.
And yeah, the discussion never really grew past that point, unfortunately.
But, you know, but, you know, I mean, I wouldn't mind being on like another like some podcast.
If someone is saying, Tom is if someone invited me on to a podcast that was strongly themed
around something, I'd love to be on.
But no, I'm not talking about the Godzilla one because I've literally never watched the
Godzilla podcast in my life.
But if but that sounds like something that I would be interested in if I were a fan of
the genre.
So I wish that great success.
We just we just need to.
You said you inject you inject me Jackson.
I mean, Jackson Sabrespar because me and Jackson are big Godzilla guys and we've watched all
the movies multiple times and Sabres only seen the new American ones.
So we're basically bringing him through the whole series and forcing him to watch all of
them.
Yeah.
The only the only one I think same the only Godzilla movie I've ever seen was like Godzilla
2000, which I saw in theaters.
I did too.
It left no impression on me.
It gave me a giant erection because I loved it.
It was incredible.
Yeah, I really it's super cheesy and super bad and they butchered the dub horribly that
I found out years later.
But at the time I was like, oh my God, they have really bad looking CGI missiles.
Yeah.
Godzilla 2000 in theaters was dubbed to my dude.
Wait, no, it wasn't.
It had like fucking it's not it's not even called Godzilla 2000 in Japan.
It's called Godzilla Millennium.
No, didn't it have like an it had like American action stars in it, didn't it?
Or not action.
So you're talking about Godzilla 98, the fucking one that had Godzilla look like a fucking
lizard man.
And they killed him on a bridge with six missiles and he hatched a bunch of eggs.
I need you to blow up Madison Square Garden.
And it was really set in New York and was raining all the time.
It's the it was it was the worst movie of all time that left.
I'm talking about I'm talking about the one that had like the little guy running
around like Godzilla 98.
We don't talk about that movie.
It's a living nightmare.
Oh, OK.
Two thousand was a quick dub of a the first Godzilla movie that came out like after
the the high side or hayside or hayside series ended.
And they just for some reason brought it over to America and dubbed it and ruined it horribly.
But it was still the best thing I ever saw because it was two years after that horrible
98 American movie and it was back to form and it was cool.
And I liked it.
What is what is the that's like the movies that came out in the 90s.
So like it started with like Godzilla Returns in 1984.
And then it went through like a bunch of like the classic old monsters redone like Godzilla
versus Mecca Godzilla and Godzilla versus Space Godzilla and King Ghidorah and stuff.
Like they're they're like groups.
They group the movies until like whoever is like Emperor at the time or something.
Like there's like a name for each of the show a series.
Yeah, just back in like the 60s and 70s.
So then there was the Millennium series which is started with Godzilla 2000.
And then there's like a new era now that's called like the Rewa era or something.
I don't know.
I'm not.
Is is the Emperor of Japan.
I don't know the shit.
I bet did you know it's animated Jason enough that she might she may know.
Maybe maybe maybe.
I guess I guess we'll have to ask who knows if only she connected corrected my
pronunciation to Hey say I believe because I didn't know how to even pronounce it.
So she must know someone this knowledge.
Fascinating.
Wait, what's that?
What's that?
What's that podcast called?
That we do.
It's just called Squadzilla.
There's some channel on YouTube.
Oh, you already said it.
There's a channel called Squadzilla already on YouTube and they have nothing to do with
Godzilla at all.
And it's really stupid.
And like for the longest time the related video on the first episode of our podcast was
MLB versus like some fucking like like video game or something like major like baseball
crossover, like a chart thing.
Like this looks like the cringiest channel of all time.
What about what about what about BLM versus Godzilla?
Like who would win, right?
Like Antifa or or or.
I mean, when you think about it, who does more property damage than Godzilla?
He's a card carrying Antifa member.
I mean, Antifa set the whole West Coast on fire, Tom.
Godzilla.
Can Godzilla even breathe fire?
Does he have like radiation breath or something?
He can destroy everything.
That's why that's what made Godzilla.
That's his power.
He can destroy it.
That's what made the end of Godzilla 2000 so cool.
They had this really cheesy dub line at the end where it's like, why does Godzilla keep
saving us from evil monsters all the time?
And then like the main character in the movie is like me because there's a little bit of
Godzilla in all of us.
And you're like, oh God, what a crappy ending to this movie.
But but then it cuts to Godzilla.
I don't know.
But then it cuts to Godzilla like doing this like 360 nuclear flame attack and destroying
all of Tokyo while the theme starts right after he says that as if to say fuck you.
And it was the best ending to a movie ever.
Super cool.
10 out of 10.
Godzilla Millennium's based.
Watch it.
Hi.
Oh my god.
I'm I'm I'm checking out squadzilla.
You've got the you got the it's got like a nice little animated intro here.
Oh my god.
This looks great.
Well, we have Saber Spark has a million subscribers.
He has money.
He has he could pay people to do things and make stuff.
Oh, sure.
Yeah, yeah.
I guess that's got that big YouTuber money.
Was it was this a saber saber spark venture?
It was I think it was either my or Jack's idea because we were just talking about Godzilla
in like, you know, discord calls and stuff like we should do a podcast about this.
And here it is.
So the new episode should probably be out by the time this podcast is out.
Only episode three.
Yeah.
King Kong versus Godzilla the original 1962 or 64.
Something like that.
I think it came out.
Wow.
Yeah.
Nifty.
Hey, just in time for Kong versus Godzilla remake coming out the end of this year.
Someone someone in the audience with a million subscribers.
Invite me onto a highly specifically themed podcast with a cool animated intro.
Why?
Why don't you?
Right.
At me at me on Twitter.
I mean on Twitter.
Yeah.
Hook me up.
Please.
DMs are open.
Yes.
Actually, they are now.
They were not.
I had my DMs close.
Yeah.
I don't know why I didn't like deliberately do this.
I had my DMs closed.
But someone wanted.
I guess the Pym fell out of their Vapors like envelope and I was like, okay, DM me your
address or whatever.
So I can like, like, what's your what's your name on Kickstarter?
And so I had to open a DMs on Twitter so I could get their info.
And I was like, why did I have these?
Why did I have the DMs closed?
I had had it open only to, you know, people that I was following or mutuals or whatever.
I don't know.
I don't know why that was.
There's no reason.
No reason for that.
Twitter has a lot of really dumb settings that are set on initially.
Like, have you ever gone to the settings and realized that like for a lot of the times
only show high quality responses is on?
What?
It'll like filter out certain people that it thinks are low quality or something.
Oh, shit.
Just not show you notifications.
What?
Yeah.
Go to settings, notifications, and then quality filter is usually on.
Oh, my God.
No, it's on.
Oh, no, it's on.
Isn't it dumb?
Why would you have that on by default?
I'm just like, I want to see all the responses.
I don't care if you think they're low quality.
Fuck you.
Don't judge people that way.
I don't know.
Like now I have to wonder, like whose tweets has it been filtered?
Well, that's the whole thing.
Whose tweets has it been filtering?
What have I been missing?
Like how much of an asshole have you been to people who have been like trying to talk
to you and you just never saw it because Twitter decided they were low quality.
Fuck you, buddy.
I mean, you still get like notified from like ads and stuff, right?
You must.
I don't know.
It doesn't say what that means.
There's a learn.
This won't filter out notifications.
Okay.
It won't filter out notifications from people you follow or accounts you've entered.
So it might filter notifications from people that if I'm not following them or if I have
an interview, that sucks.
No, I want to know when I get added.
Yes.
Oh God.
Ah, cripes.
Twitter continuing to be a great platform.
What a fucking nightmare.
I hate it.
Man, Twitter fucking.
Oh, hey, okay.
Hey, how do we feel?
How do we feel about Ruth Badger Ginsburg?
I don't know.
Oh God, yeah.
I don't know if there's much to say about it, but...
Not yet, at least.
It'll be interesting to see what happens if we get some hardcore hypocrisy going on.
We're gonna.
We're absolutely going to.
I mean, yeah.
Yeah.
There's no...
This is the kind of thing.
This is what Republicans...
This is what Republicans base their...
Scrabble and lie and do all their power-grubbing shit for.
Like, waiting for an opportunity like this.
This is the time to cash in all their chips, you know?
Do you...
I mean, okay.
I agree with you, but do you honestly not think that if the tables were turned, the
Libs wouldn't be doing the exact same thing?
Okay.
This is just politics.
This is just how the game is played.
To a degree.
Oh God, well...
I do think that the Dems would rush to fill the seat.
Yes, obviously.
But the hypocrisy is that the Republicans went to such lengths and were so shitty about
they blocked and blocked and blocked Obama's nominee.
Right.
So, yeah, I guess.
I guess they probably would do the same thing, but the difference is that the Democrats are
not going to, in like the name of like bipartisanship or whatever, they're not going to pull out all
the stops in order to like block the Republicans' nominee.
They're too, I don't know, they're too complacent or they're complicit or like they don't give
that much of a shit or whatever.
Or whatever their fucking problem is.
They just aren't going to like resist it in the way that the Republicans would.
That's the asymmetry.
Maybe.
We'll see.
Yeah.
They're just...
There's just nothing to talk about this like, yeah, because nothing's really happened.
It's just like...
Yeah.
We'll have to wait and see what they decide to do.
It's all just talk at this point, yeah.
Yeah.
Which is, I guess, kind of good.
Because the longer they don't do anything, the better chance it is that like, you know,
the precedent that they set will continue to be a thing.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Because there's only a couple of weeks.
There's only a couple of weeks left, really.
Well, there's only a couple of weeks until the election, but then there's the...
Trump is still the president for the rest of the year, even after the election.
Yeah, until January.
So it could happen then, too.
I mean, that would be...
I feel like any chance you would have to even wiggle your way through without issue,
like if Biden is elected, and then December 14th, Trump's like,
and the sky's in.
That's when you're really fucked at that point.
The blowback would be astronomical.
I don't know.
I don't know if they're worried about blowback.
What would be the consequence to them if there was blowback?
I don't really know.
Like, the Republicans would be angry that they pushed it through,
but they already hate the Republicans.
The Republicans would be happy that they pushed him through, you know,
just because they're already on their side.
I don't see this as a thing where the Republicans stand to lose very much.
The only thing they stand to lose is if they were to fail to push a nominee through.
Well, I guess that's what I mean.
They would be attempt to push, and there'd be a lot of pushback to prevent it from happening,
and they get a lot of, like, bloody their nose for no real gain.
Because I feel like as soon as the process would start,
because I would assume there's still some checks and balances.
I'm assuming Trump can't just be like, that guy, and then it's done, right?
Like, there has to be more to it than that.
Democrats just care more.
Democrats care more about decorum than Republicans do.
Democrats will fail to act if it's like, oh, no, that's beneath me,
even if it's something really important, like blocking Trump's judiciary nominee.
The Republicans wouldn't give a shit.
They don't care if someone calls them a hypocrite.
It's like, yeah, sure, fine, but I'm gonna do it because I want it,
and my constituency demands it, and I'm afraid of my constituency.
When the kind of precedent was set with Obama,
is that just like a unwritten rule, or did that become part of law?
Which precedent do you mean?
The precedent that you can't appoint a judge during an election year.
Is that on the books now, or is that just kind of like a gentleman's agreement?
No, that's not a real precedent.
Okay, now I'm no expert or anything, but my understanding is that
that was basically just the Senate, which was controlled by the Republicans then as it is now.
Like, just simply refused to convene to vote on a nominee.
That's right, but like...
It wasn't like a legal precedent.
Right, but my understanding as well is that like, in order to justify doing so,
they try to make it, they try to set an official precedent with that maneuver going forward.
I mean, they would say anything.
Well, that's my point.
Was it just bullshit, or was their actual legislation put down in response to this,
and is it on the books now?
You know, I don't know for sure.
My gut is that it was just complete bullshit.
That's my feeling as well.
But it was complete bullshit that worked, and...
It's very strange that it worked.
It completely worked because Democrats are not willing to get their hands dirty
in the way that Republicans are.
They're not willing to like get down in the weeds and like...
I don't know.
I know...
There's a video about this specific thing by Innuendo Studios.
It's called, They Go Low, We Go High, and it's about how Democrats like won't fucking...
won't get their hands dirty with shit like this, even when it's important.
So I don't remember exactly what the circumstances was,
but I know that there were things that Obama could have done in order to force the issue
because the Senate was going...
It was...
It's extra constitutional...
To put it nicely, it's extra constitutional for the Senate to simply refuse to convene on the...
It's not that they even held a vote and voted against the nominee.
They simply refused to even hold the vote, which is like...
I guess there's no rule that they can't do that,
but it's definitely not the spirit of the law that they should be able to do that.
It's like finding a loophole.
And Obama probably could have found some kind of similarly extra constitutional means to force the issue,
which would have been just turnabout.
But Obama sort of...
He would tweet.
Every so often, he would tweet like,
hmm, 150 days with no vote.
Hmm, 300 days with no vote.
He's like passive-aggressive.
Obama handled this like we handled YouTube cancelling our channel.
Yeah, he's exactly right.
Exactly.
That's the Democrats.
They just crossed their arms and they'll go,
hmm, those Republicans sure are bullying me right now.
But it's okay because this is a bad look for them.
And there's going to be huge blowback for this.
This is really going to cost them down ballot.
And meanwhile, the Republicans are like, I don't care.
This is the time for me to exercise power.
There's no point holding power unless I exercise it.
This is the time, even if it costs me my office, it's worth it.
Like, fuck everything.
Republicans are sounding kind of based right now.
They're making them sound kind of cool, Ben.
They have the will to power in a way that the Democrats simply lack.
It's just a shame that they are monsters and do bad things with it.
Lamal.
But yeah, so my expectations are that this RBG situation will shake out
probably in the worst way that it possibly could.
It's probably a nightmare for civil rights.
Dab.
Yeah, it'll be interesting.
I can't wait for what's his name, fucking Lindsey Graham or whatever.
There's like a clip floating around on Twitter of him being like,
use my own words against me if this ever happens the other way around.
And now it is happening and it's pretty funny.
You say Lindsey Graham and I think of Graham Linnum.
I don't even know who that is.
That's the guy who, he was one of the co-founders or makers of the IT crowd
and he was like the big Twitter transphobe.
No, I got nothing.
He was a TV writer who got fired from all his TV jobs
and these days he's known as the top dog of Twitter transphobes
before JK Rowling de-throned him.
Lamal.
Yeah, I guess that's not the circle I tend to associate.
What a time to be alive.
What a sentence.
Oh, boy.
Oh, man.
Actually, speaking of JK Rowling, one of the big things they revealed,
no, no, no, this is funny.
This is good.
Okay.
One of the big things they revealed at like the PlayStation digital event
a couple of weeks back was the new Harry Potter game,
like this Hogwarts game, the big RPG that looks pretty good.
Oh, I think I know where you're going with this, but yeah.
And they made sure to go out and make very clear JK Rowling
has nothing to do with this game.
And everyone got like their shits from that.
That was pretty funny.
And I just thought, wouldn't it be great if they just didn't have a gender option
when you make your character in this Hogwarts game?
I just think that would be the funniest fucking thing in the world
and they should totally do it.
Sure.
I don't know anything about the game, but yeah, be funny.
It's set in like the 1800s or something.
So it's like a way, way, way prequel to like Harry Potter,
but it's just like you're a dude at Hogwarts doing your thing
and like you fight monsters and stuff.
And it's like an excuse to make an action RPG in a popular IP to make money.
Like that's the whole point of it.
But I mean, the thing about that is that, you know,
for marketing purpose, because there's all this blowback against JK now,
they'll say that, but the reality is that maybe she might not be involved in making it,
but like she still owns the company and is profiting.
She's still getting paid massively.
So, you know, if you were going to boycott the game,
you know, still do it, definitely, I guess.
But yeah, I mean, I'm not going to buy a fucking Harry Potter video game.
No, I mean, under any circumstances, even, even the best of circumstances.
The Harry Potter comparisons to RBG have been pretty cringy.
Wait, what?
Have you seen like the article from Vice saying that she was like the Dumbledore of real life?
What the fuck?
Yeah, like that's like their big, like Vice's big article celebrating her,
her legacy was saying that she was like our version of Dumbledore.
I'm like, can we please stop being this pathetic?
Yeah, that is, um, that is like peak, that is like peak millennial horseshit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh God.
It was really bad.
And then like that other, there was another tweet where someone is it Ruth Kanda?
I don't know.
Oh, OK.
What do you, what do you think?
I saw one that's like some, some quote unquote journalist or whatever,
some fucking blue check mark is like, I told my daughter about Ruth Bader Ginsburg
and she, and she cried.
And then she did the Wakanda pose and said Ruth Kanda forever.
Yeah, I said that too.
Like you're such a liar.
No, she fucking did it.
Right.
It's so dumb.
Like, who do you think you're fooling with these like blatantly transparent
attention bait tweets?
I mean, on the one hand, it's a lie, which is bad.
And on the other hand, like, why would you make a story like that?
Why would you say that thinking that like, if that happened, it would be cool.
It's not, it's not cool.
It's like a fail on multiple levels.
I don't, I don't understand.
I don't understand these fucking Twitter check marks.
What are they thinking?
There was someone else who was like, who's like, like, um, RBG going to heaven
and seeing Chadwick Boseman and she was like.
Oh, queen, queen.
Yeah, queen.
Yeah.
Just like, come on, man.
I did see that one.
I didn't see.
What are you doing?
It's so, I don't know.
It's just very strange how like there's like a whole group of people like, oh, I
almost like the bulk of like an entire generation.
I guess you could argue that like have just conflated fiction with reality to the point
where like making statements like that or saying that like, she's the Dumbledore of
real life, have some sort of like deep meaning when it just makes you seem like a child.
Yeah.
When you say a card carrying man child, say you're acting like a child, you've really
sunk fucking low.
I mean, I feel, you know, I feel a little bit, I feel a little called out sometimes when
like people say like, oh, fucking millennials, like saying some cringy shit about Harry Potter,
because I mean, I grew up really liking Harry Potter, you know, it was, I really like the
books.
I didn't, I didn't care for the movies that much, but I was really into the books.
So, like, I kind of get it.
But, you know, it's in situations like this when like something of like, something of
like real like geopolitical importance is occurring, like something that's really gonna like affect
people is happening and some fucking, and some fucking idiot who called, whose Twitter
bio says cat mom, like make some fucking comparison to like, oh, Ruth Bader Ginsburg was like, you
know, I don't know.
Who's that?
Candace Owens is like the Dolores Umbridge of something where it's like, fuck off.
Like, shut the fuck up.
It just, it just comes off of like your, your frame of reference in life.
Yeah.
So small and so limited that you have to retreat back to like your small pocket of pop culture
references in order to make comparisons to reality.
It's one thing to have reverence for a piece of fiction because we all do.
We all have pieces of fiction that an entertainment that have really affected us.
But like, the real world is the real world.
It doesn't need to constantly be referenced back.
It's like, I can.
To Harry fucking Potter.
I actually don't need to contextualize the, you know, I don't know, the war in Iraq or
whatever in the like, but like, oh, was McCain was, McCain was like, he was like, you know,
a Snape basically.
Like, you think he's a bad guy, but he was actually kind of good.
And then, you know, I don't know.
Fucking the other guy was some other shit.
I can't even, I can't even think of enough Harry Potter characters off the top of my
head to complete this analogy.
It's just very bad.
What's the point?
It's just embarrassing.
It really is.
It's embarrassing for me as a, as a, I don't, I don't know if I, I don't know if I'd go
so far as to call myself a Potter head.
I'm, I'm certainly not an active Potter head.
I just like the books as a kid.
You don't, you don't have your house and your Twitter bio.
Like what's wrong with that?
Ravenclaw though.
In case, in case anyone's curious, just put that out there.
Man, oh fucking man.
Yeah.
Well, that was, that's what a week.
That's what a fucking week.
Do you want to go to voicemails?
Let's go to voicemails.
We got a bunch of them.
Okay.
Right.
Our first, our first voicemail of the day is from probably just depression.
Sounds accurate.
Three, two, one, go.
And what else do you like this?
I have no backbone to defend shit.
I like, I like, I've always loved Scotch people.
This was a teenager.
But now if everyone comes to attack, I just, you know, yeah, I guess it is a,
I guess it is a white boy fantasy.
I guess it is a bunch of fucking video game references and some outdated hipster shit.
I guess.
Yeah.
I guess pretty gay.
I will kill myself.
Yeah.
Wait, wait, what was that about?
I missed the beginning part.
I'm going to listen to the beginning again.
And what else do you like this?
Um, I have no backbone to defend shit.
I like Scotch people.
I've always loved Scotch people.
There's like a little audio clip that's like, cuts out the key word to that first sentence.
Honestly.
Yeah.
I can't quite make out what he's saying there, but I guess he's talking about killing
himself.
And, uh, I don't know.
I don't, whatever.
Don't do it.
Yeah.
I guess, I guess I'm obligated to say don't do it.
The world sucks right now, but it sucks for everybody.
Not, it's not you.
It's the world.
Yeah.
That's, that's really the lesson to take away from 2020.
I think maybe, maybe there's some, maybe there is some, some, some comfort to be gleaned
and that like, if you feel, if you feel bad right now, it's probably this, it's pretty
close for me.
If you feel bad right now, like, like, of course you do, right?
Like you can tell that like it's not your problem.
Uh, uh, everybody, everybody feels like that.
Clearly at this point in history, we can all acknowledge that like the problems are
external to ourselves.
Right.
Unless you're.
Yeah.
Unless not to say you don't have personal problems, but like there's a baseline where all fucking
right.
It's rounding in right now.
And, uh, I don't know.
You have that camaraderie with everybody around you is that everyone's dealing with
shit.
Yes.
Take.
I don't know, dude.
We can all feel bad together.
Yeah.
Misery loves company.
You know, we can all, we can all just, uh.
Read Harry Potter again, because that's all that really matters in the world.
You, you who sent this voicemail, you know, us on the podcast, all our shitty commenters,
you know, all, all of us are united in, in how, in how bad 2020 has been for us.
So, you know, take, take heart.
Um, the next, the next one is a, is a YouTube link, but let's listen to the voicemail.
Maybe it'll explain what this deal is.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, lads.
I made a little funny video about a certain best guy.
It's a little too long for a voicemail.
So I'm leaving you a link.
Enjoy.
Oh boy.
The video is called Mr. Best Guy.
And, um.
Oh God.
It's five minutes long.
It is a five minute long video.
And.
All right.
You know.
It is.
It is, it is five minutes long.
I mean, I, I see some, I see some Nate criticism in here, uh, you know, early on.
And then there, there's more and I don't, I'm, there's, I don't get it.
But I'm sure that I'm sure there's more to it.
Uh, link in the description, I guess.
I don't know.
I guess I'm obligated to put the link in the description.
Uh, if you're interested.
We brought it up for this long.
Yes.
Leave them there.
Leave the, leave this man your opinions about that if you would like.
Next one.
Prol Jester in love.
Oh God.
It's a minute 22.
Jesus Christ.
Three, two, one, go.
This is a hell of your own creation.
Violence from no beginning is tyranny.
Impress me.
But with the backdrop of revenge, no one would even blink.
Have you even considered the violence that we have suffered by so-called elites?
Their vile shadow has covered all of their sins, shrouded in deceit.
But the truth is clear.
Their actions do wreak.
Many hadn't got one.
I was the, yes, me, that they refer to this hidden violence as federal policy.
Their crimes are masked under a flimsy guise.
Rip it off from their faces.
Come on now, you guys.
Now, I have to give my thanks towards your expression of myth and consideration to my message.
Truly, I was humbled by your participation in my craft.
Also, I was arrested for acts of violence and I was wondering if you could pay my bail.
My gesture, rather, and have set up a GoFundMe at gofundme.com slash Ben St.
I had to perform a mean palatio to get this message out.
So thank you truly for your time.
I hope gofundme.com slash Ben St. forwards to patreon.com slash Ben St.
Abolish prisons.
Free this man.
Thanks for the funny poem.
No problem.
Okay, next one is called Bad Voice Mail.
I appreciate the honesty.
I can't wait.
Three, two, one, go.
So, it's Thursday.
Yeah, that's right.
I haven't even seen the episode yet.
It's not even out.
I have a few predictions to make about this week's episode.
I mean, last week's episode.
Number one, Nate will not be there.
Number two, Ben St. will be there.
Number three, I have a vision.
You've already talked about some degenerate leftist topic.
Yes, I can see it.
Yes, you've done it.
It's in my brain.
And if you haven't talked about it yet,
just take this voice mail as a jumping off point
to talk about some degeneracy.
Don't.
Well, you titled the voice mail accurately,
so I'll give him that.
Is that your phone ringing in the background,
or was that his phone?
That was his phone.
Well, yeah.
Yeah, we talked about the most degenerate thing of all,
the Supreme Court and Harry Potter, Der.
Well, I was a little better than bad, I guess.
Just slightly.
I mean, it was very obvious.
Like, if you're going to make some predictions,
that's like the most flaccid predictions of all time.
You've got to be specific.
You've got to be like, you've got to predict, you know,
which American city is going to have a mass shooting this week,
and then be like, oh, yeah, they're going to talk about that
on the PCP.
That would be impressive.
Next one.
You would have been wrong, because we didn't.
Right.
Yeah, yeah.
But if you, you know, what if he called the mass shooting,
but was wrong that we didn't talk about it,
and then we're just like, ah, this guy, idiot.
I would just assume he was the shooter.
He's like, I predict that I'm going to go out to fucking, you know, cowards.
He just really wanted to be talked about on the PCP, you know.
He's like, oh man, I bet the PCP guys will get a real kick out of this mass shooting.
He's going to go out and all yell, I'm the reason people are dying.
He's like, this, this will get me noticed by the PCP for sure.
And you know what?
I think I'm contractually obligated to say that if someone, if that happens,
we will not discuss it on the show.
Definitely not.
It's, it's not, it's not, it's not up for discussion.
We do not endorse violence in any way except against the state.
Except against property, violence against property for sure.
Private property, not personal property, the kind owned by capital.
You understand, you know, you've, you've all read the bread book.
Okay, three, next one is called registered call number 0870443.
Three, two, one, go.
This is a call from the state voice and attendee.
This call will be monitored.
Please hold.
Hello, Samurai-san.
In the voice jail.
Hippo-chan.
This guy.
Fuck off.
Last week.
Vote for jail.
Not gorilla.
But Samurai forgiveness.
Steal rubber hippo-gibbo-chan.
Samurai-kran.
Choosey tuboremu.
Beno-san.
Fuck you.
Samurai.
In the jail.
Because.
Oh.
No.
No, no.
Voice of Selmeto.
From a voice of Aryan Gangu.
He have erect penis.
No.
No, no, no.
Damn, that's what she, that's what happens.
That's what happens.
You should, you should have just let, let well enough alone.
You should have left those sacred scrolls.
I, I, I, um, the Samurai, Samurai's been showing up like in streams and stuff.
Samurai's been, Samurai's been harassing me.
He's been bullying me online.
We give the people in voice jail internet access.
He showed up in my discord.
He's a, I mean, he's everywhere.
He's like, he's got, he's got, he's got spies in the walls.
God damn.
I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't escape his, his various Jutsus.
That sounds vaguely ninja-esque.
This is a Samurai.
I, some, I think I, ever since I left the clan, I conflate the two sometimes.
It's so hard, so hard to remember which is which.
Um, but, uh, sucka.
Uh, next one is from an urgent bulletin from the news at thegovernment.com.
So this will be important.
Not.gov.
I think this might be fake.
Three, two, one, go.
Wow.
If it's fake, how does it have a music stinger?
Konnichiwa.
You're right.
Welcome to Samurai News Network.
I am a host, hentai Hiroshi.
Top story today.
Kawasaki, Samurai Karano Rida.
In no voice jail, and no possibly repovictim.
Rido Suspect, Samurai Tretaru.
Ben no Sentosa.
We will stay with this story.
I was watching, guess who's coming to dinner at the time, it couldn't have been me.
But until next time, sayonara.
I don't, I don't know.
The bit that just won't die.
I think this, it was, it was fake news though.
That was, that was the definition of fake news.
Indeed, it did.
Next, next, I have an alibi.
Next one is from, uh, Xander.
Three, two, one, go.
How do they're PC penis people?
Um, Ben, you might recognize me from endless war because I designed those pins of you and Munchie.
Um, I wanted to ask you guys what do you think about.
Enjoying content, enjoying content mindlessly or like just enjoying something because,
because recently I watched Devilman Crybaby and you know, it was a pretty good show.
I enjoyed it, but, um, storytelling wise, kind of mad, kind of flat.
I didn't care about any of the characters and I watched it and I was like, um, okay, cool.
But then after that, I just started liking the, just Devilman in general.
Like I started, I read the original manga, which I don't know if it's better than Crybaby.
I'm not sure yet.
I haven't thought about it.
But like, I've just sort of been enjoying Devilman and like Devilman Crybaby, it's the same show.
It didn't get better, but now I like it way more now for some reason.
Is this, is this what, is this what normal people do?
They just enjoy things because it good and then, and they don't have to analyze everything like story structure wise.
Um, yeah.
End of voicemail.
Send.
Um, I'm not, uh, I mean, he started out saying enjoying mindlessly,
but I feel like what he was describing was not mindless enjoyment.
Oh, actually, the first thing he said was enjoying Kant,
which has been a completely different voicemail than enjoying content mindlessly.
Yeah, that's, um, you know, the,
It's like a hard left right there.
I don't, yeah, I don't, I don't know if I agree with the categorical imperative,
which is, is that Kant?
I'm like 80% sure that's Kant.
Okay, fuck, never mind.
Um, uh,
Eleazar, cut that out.
Eleazar, if that's not correct, cut that out.
Insert whatever guy it was.
It wasn't, it definitely wasn't Hegel.
I don't think it was Hegel.
He was the dialectics guy.
Um, but, uh, I mean, I enjoy mindless things all the time.
Like I fucking, I'll put on those fucking, uh, identifying luck in Mario Party videos
and just let them auto play for like six hours.
And I have a great time.
Um, and that's, and that's nothing.
That's just noise.
Um, about, it seems like he was saying like, uh, uh, enjoying something just
because you're familiar with it.
All right.
I guess so.
Which, in which case, um, I,
Enough the power of franchises.
That's why like Hollywood and stuff abuse franchises so much.
That is the power of franchises.
And it's, it's a real thing.
And like it's just, it's not,
I totally understand why it happens because like, I mean,
I was just talking about Harry Potter before and like, you know,
Well, I don't know if that's a great, it was like, I don't,
I don't watch any of the like extended Harry Potter shit.
I'm not, I didn't go out and see fucking fantastic beasts or whatever.
Uh, so maybe that's not a great example, but like,
I get the appeal of a franchise and like, oh, this is a thing I'm familiar with.
That's why, that's why I don't,
It adends all of you, it adends all of your previous experience with the
entries in the franchise or whatever new thing they're trying to do.
And that's why they work so much better.
I, that's why I avoid media in general because I don't,
I don't want to get, uh, to, to an extent I'm being a little facetious,
but I'm, I'm being serious too.
Like I kind of don't want to see anything new because if a new franchise were to
begin and I'd seen it, that would give it like fucking power over me.
That would, they would be able to entice me to go and like see their new movie
or whatever.
And I don't want, I don't want them to have that.
I don't want to be, like God, imagine if like I gave a shit about Star Wars
and like think of all the fucking movies I'd have had to go see,
like in the past couple of years, like Jesus Christ.
New movies made everyone hate Star Wars.
Nobody liked Star Wars anymore.
That's deranged mental people.
That's true.
I mean, yeah, maybe.
I mean, imagine, okay, well imagine, like if I, if I gave a shit about Marvel,
I would have had to go and see, like over the last decade,
I would have had to go and see like 30 fucking movies.
I had that.
I had a good time.
No, no, you didn't.
You're wrong.
Um, so I guess, I guess my point is that I, I try, I just like kind of go out of my
way not to do that, not to enjoy things in that way or any other.
I think I'm just embarrassing myself.
Sounds about right.
Yeah.
It's pretty, it's pretty base.
You should try it.
Try it sometime.
I just, I just think like you have to, you have to keep a critical mind.
Right.
It's so easy to like get pre-programmed and be like, oh, I'm going to enjoy this
because it's like my thing.
Like, like PlayStation and Xbox fucking drones, you know, and just like,
I'm going to get the new PlayStation.
Cause the last one was good and like, fuck you for liking Xbox fucking console
warship.
So cringy.
$70.
I mean, gaming is an expensive hobby.
What do you expect?
I'll pay anything.
You just have to like, you got to differentiate like all of your experiences
and understand like another good thing is like, uh, studios, you know, like people
are just like, oh, like Bioware.
I love Bioware.
It's like, that's just a name.
That's just a logo that people involved in working at these studios are
different than who they were 20 years ago.
And like that, that logo is there to confuse you and to trick you into thinking
the things that you liked back then still exist when you have to be able to
examine each piece of content individually on its own merits and divorce
your feelings of nostalgia for the brand in question and be like, what is this
thing?
And that's hard and difficult because like our brains are like pre-programmed to
do as much intellectual shorthand as possible.
And that's what capitalism preys on.
It's like, it's like, like Homestuck.
Like, um, the new, like Homestuck 2, it's, I mean, it's called Homestuck.
And I guess Hussey is technically somewhat involved in it, but like it's not,
it's not being made by the same guy.
So I'm not going to like, or like, or like any, I don't know, any fucking like
company, right?
Any fucking, yeah, I like the point about like, you know, the name of the brand is
just like, like it's the people that made it that is the important thing.
And like, I guess if like, they sell it under like a Bioware name, it's like
the implication is like the same people made it, but it could have been like,
they could have just sold that name to some other people and like they released it.
I mean, they do that all the time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, sure.
And it's like, hmm, weird.
That's weird.
I mean, they did that with Star Wars.
Like they sold Star Wars to Disney and people just went because it had Star Wars on
it, even though none of the original people involved with Star Wars, even George
Lucas was involved.
It's just like, this is just part and parcel of like, intellectual property in general.
Yeah.
If you want to be fans of anybody, you should be fans of individual creators.
Because there's a very clear one to one through line between person and product.
Yeah.
You know, that's um, if Vapors three is garbage, you know, it's Ben's fault because
no one else is involved.
Good luck, Ben.
Fuck yeah.
Um, base.
Uh, okay.
Yeah.
Good.
Uh, I don't have anything else to say about that.
Yeah.
Next one.
I don't, I want to skip this next one.
That's fair.
I don't like, I don't like it.
Okay.
No.
You talk me into it.
It's called, it's called based Tom.
Sounds like, sounds like, sounds pointless, but we'll give it sounds like propaganda.
All right.
Three, two, one, go.
You know, the Dick sucker last week was saying that the commentators are too cowardly to call
in and give their opinion.
You know, I'll give my opinion.
I really don't think it's you three that, that the people are frustrated with.
The podcast is fine.
You know, it's good background noise.
It is what it is.
It's just, we have this Nate cloud all over everything and it's just, it's another game
grumps thing.
It's the John and Aaron all over again.
People don't know what's going on.
People have been, you know, uh, part of this community and all of a sudden a major member
just disappears and we have no reason or no explanation why.
And I think that's actually what people are frustrated about.
You guys would just bring it out in the open.
Maybe this can begin to heal.
Otherwise it's just going to be the no Nate, no watchers crying, the Nate heads crying.
It's just going to continue like this.
So I think as soon as it's brought to light all this, we can move on, you know.
This is, this is exactly what we were talking about at the beginning of the episode.
There's this, there's this sort of.
I mean, maybe, maybe, I mean, I, I thought we did talk about it, but maybe we didn't
talk about it enough.
Maybe it's our fault for inviting this kind of speculation by not spelling it out.
But yeah, this, this expectation that like there must be some sort of some, some kind
of some sort of like reason and like, no, just doesn't feel like it.
That's, that's the reason.
When there's no official comment and very specific detail, people will fill in their
own fan fiction as, as the internet works.
I don't know what that had to do with me being based by appreciating.
That wasn't even about Tom, but okay, that's fine.
All right.
Fair enough.
You know, hopefully we've, we've dispelled this at this point.
And, and, uh, oh, oh, the next one, I hope this guy bought the shirt.
Oh, wait, I, I feel like maybe we, I don't know.
I feel like maybe there's something to say about the shirts from last, last episode.
I released the shirts before the episode came out.
I did.
And, and everyone thought they sucked because am I flattering myself to, am I flattering
us rather to say that like, oh, that's just because they hadn't heard the episode and
they didn't know the context.
I feel like they probably still suck, but not as much if you have context.
Uh, maybe.
I mean, I thought they were like, when we were, when we came up with them, when, when
we, when we were talking about it on the episode, I thought it was pretty funny.
So I thought, I mean, it was funny in the moment for sure.
I felt some good, some, some good feels in my heart when crack was like base states,
a good pun even before the episode was out.
And it's like, yes.
Crack got it.
And then someone else said like, ask, like, oh, is the COVID joke that like, if you wear
this, you won't get COVID cause no one will come near you.
And I was like, yeah, more or less.
So like a couple of people like were able to infer.
Um, few galaxy brains out there.
Thank God.
But, uh, okay.
And so I'm looking, I'm looking at the analytics and no, nobody, nobody bought either shirt.
So, you know, you could be, that just means that you could be the first you listening at
home right now.
You could be the one and only owner of an I have COVID shirt.
Uh, you know, if you're, if you have the courage.
Um, but anyway, voicemail from I have COVID three, two, one go.
So the PCP lately has been a little sparse for lack of a better word.
And, um, so I was thinking, maybe you guys should get a guest or something.
And, um, there's just really cool YouTuber guy you should have on the podcast.
His name is, um, Cotherix the dragon.
He's really cool.
And I think, uh, he would make a really good, um, member of the podcast.
Sure.
Do you know who that is, Tom?
I have no idea who that is.
He is, he is a blue dragon.
Um, I don't, I guess I don't really know his deal.
I guess he seems okay.
There's like a, um, he's got like a couple of videos that went pretty viral.
There's one that's like, oh fuck, what is it?
It's like, I think he might have like a, hold on.
I want to remember what, what the big one is, like the one that I found him through.
Um, uh, Cotherix, what's, what's his biggest video?
There was one that like went pretty viral.
Uh, and I had to click it because like, what the fuck is this?
Um, I don't see, I don't see.
Oh, it was why we should bring back child labor.
I think that was, that's not actually his biggest one, but he had this one about how like child labor was good.
And he, he basically gives this like, this like shitty, like a NCAP explanation of why the free market and whatever.
But he goes like, he goes pretty, by the end of it, it's clear that it's like a parody or whatever.
He talks about like, you know, kids could like lose their limbs and machinery.
But like, if we had like a better workforce, like we could invent like auto mail, like in full metal alchemist.
And then all these kids could have all these cool robot arms.
They would be sick.
I don't know.
I'm picking up what he's putting down.
Yeah.
So I think Kothric seems fine.
So what I'm saying is, yeah, he, he should probably be the next member of the, of the, of the PCP, I think.
Well, we were talking before the episode started about trying to get some guest scones.
We were talking about trying to get some guest scones.
I'm not opposed to guests.
I just, I don't, we don't know anybody or I don't know anybody.
You know people, but that's, I know some people.
Maybe instead of trying to get someone with a million subscribers on you onto their podcast,
we seem to get Saber with a million subscribers onto this podcast.
I mean, I mean, that's one, that's one way to do it.
Then, then he can do an episode called what ruined the PCP and finally answer the question for everybody.
I got it.
I figured it out.
We're good.
All right.
I'm going to start, I'm going to start sending some DMs right now.
We're going to get this.
We're going to get this going.
It's going to be great.
That's, that's, that's pretty good.
That's, that's pretty okay.
We can do that, I think.
I don't, yeah, I just, I don't really like know any other like YouTube or internet people outside of the PCP.
So I get, I, hmm, do I?
No, I only, I only have like the most cursory of like business relationships with like,
I've been on a podcast with like one or two people and that's like it.
I slid it ourselves too early in our career and now we're a pariah.
I mean, Tom, how do I, how do I become a well connected internet, internet, the face of the internet like you?
You just have to get in on the ground floor of a fandom and then everybody who's in that fandom goes on to become incredibly successful due to market trends that you yourself don't understand and can't capitalize on.
That sounds pretty gay though.
I mean, my life is pretty gay, so you're on point.
Is there a better way?
Hmm.
Be personable, I guess.
No, that's out of the question.
Look at me.
Look who you're talking to.
It's fair.
All right.
No, I'll figure something out.
You got to, you just got to do the tried and true artist tactic, Ben.
You got to find somebody who's relatively popular, make them lots of free fan art until they become your friend.
Because they feel indebted to you for giving, for you giving them all this free stuff.
I can't do that.
You're your own worst enemy then, Ben.
I'm hearing a lot of I can't.
I can't do that.
It's too, it's too degrading.
It's too demeaning.
That's why I don't do it either.
And that's why we're both on this podcast and nothing else to our names.
I can't, no, I will, I don't want to fucking curry favor with someone who's higher on the totem pole than me.
I want to just fuck the totem pole.
I want to knock it down.
I don't grovel and be like, ooh.
Now you're talking about a totally different goal than what you just initially asked.
Ooh, Mr. Someone with six digits, someone with six digits subscribers.
Ooh, I made you a, I made you a, the, the, the closest I ever came was I did like one piece of fan art for a couple of the artists on a, on a strip search.
I did one and then never again.
And I never looked at their Twitter feeds or anything.
I don't interact with them because I, some of them are like smaller than me, but like I'm, they, they even, even those ones won't acknowledge me.
Because I'm just, I'm just too much of an insignificant ants for even other insignificant ants.
Don't care about me. Hmm. Hmm. Cringe.
Um, so anyway, that's, that's that problem, problem solved.
I don't know.
Uh, whatever.
Imagine if we could have internet famous, uh, YouTuber, uh, six digit subscribers, Nate Bestman.
If you could get him on the podcast and we could start going places.
If only, if only we could get, if only we could get Digi, Digi-nay, formerly Digi Bro on the podcast.
That would just be, that could be our big break.
I even think, you know, that, that's like a whole audience.
I'd really turn the show around.
Yeah.
Very true.
It's impossible though.
It's impossible.
God damn it.
No, I, I am important.
I was on the pizza party podcast.
I found the podcast and then I went on it.
When are we going to have pan pizza on the show?
I, I don't think pan pizza is a human being.
Um, I don't,
I have a connection through Paleo Steno who knows Jim, uh, Jim Gisrael who's on the podcast with pan.
Is he the tall guy?
I have it in.
He's, yeah, he's the big tall guy.
He was, he was not on the episode that I was on, but okay.
Damn it.
Yeah.
Jim is unironically.
Jim is base.
Jim is cool.
No.
I love talking to Jim.
He was just me, cheesy, uh, pizza man, uh, uh, Nolan and Izzy.
And, uh, yeah.
The only one I know from that show is Jim and he's actually really cool.
I see.
Lol.
Um, Paleo knows Jim.
Okay.
Yeah.
Get fucking, get fucking, I mean, did I, I probably talked about it that like pizza is,
is like a weird automaton pizza was like, I like said a bunch of like, I made a bunch
of like weird jokes and just set a bunch of weird shit and like cheesy, just like talk
shit to him like right to his face and did, and pizza just had like no reaction whatsoever.
It was just like, okay, anyway, let's talk about this cartoon news.
Let's talk about this new pilot of whatever released on the Disney channel or whatever
the fuck.
He's like completely undeterred from his goal.
He's perfect for the internet.
Just like the criticism just bounces right off and just keeps, keeps attacking that target
demo.
Yeah.
Completely.
It's admirable in its way.
But um, no, we, we, we really do need to cross pollinate the PPP with the PCC, PCP.
I mean, I mean, I tried, but it didn't, it didn't happen.
So we're going to have to have another go.
Somebody else is going to have to find the podcast.
I'll extend my social tendrils as best I can and see if I can trap anyone in my web and
pull it back.
Oh, who is it?
People were saying, oh, since we're on the subject of guests.
I kind of want to ask, um, this is someone who I didn't know, but I saw a bunch of people
talking about him, um, because he mentioned my lectures in a recent video, his name.
Oh my God.
I can't believe I'm blanking on his name because I fucking watched like all of his videos this
past week.
Uh, it was, um, Cybershell, this guy, do you know, do you know Cybershell?
Yes.
I had never heard of them, but I watched.
I haven't watched any of their stuff, but we were talking about this before the show
started.
Oh God.
That's right.
I can't even fucking remember what I, and you're like, Hey dude, uh, we should have
a Cybershell in here.
I'm like, that's cool.
And then you're like, do you know anything about Sonic?
I'm like, I'm a pretty hardcore fan of some adventure and could geek out about it.
And you're like, go, right, right.
Cybershell talks about Sonic and I personally don't know anything about Sonic, but cyber
has seen my son at you lecture and my tales of its trolled lecture and mentioned them
in a recent video about tales gets trolled, which was pretty cool of him.
I would love to have Cybershell on.
We could open our hearts together about Sonic and maybe we could live and learn a bit from
each other.
Uh, Cybershell, his, I, I watched through his catalog and his, his best video to me,
he has like an hour long video explaining like, what's the deal with Chow?
Like how do they work?
And I, that's like,
That's some deep lore.
That's some deep.
Like, yeah, like, yes, please give me an hour long video.
Okay.
Yes.
Please give me an hour long video of some guy just explaining some like weird shit in
an old video game for, for a while.
Like, yep, that's, that's what I want.
Uh, so that was pretty based.
Uh, okay.
Okay.
We've, that's, that's enough about that.
We've got another voicemail from I'm Just Being Cool, three, two, one, go.
So the other day I was at, uh, Walgreens getting some extra large condoms and the employee
came up to me and was like, Hey man, you got to wear a mask in here.
And I was like, Hey man, I'm just being cool and he was like dumbstruck by this statement.
I turned 360 degrees and walked out without paying.
That's what it does.
It was pretty good.
Fuck yeah.
I'm glad we have our first testimonial that this is an effective strategy to getting through
life.
And if that hadn't worked and they'd like called the cops on you for shoplifting, you
could have just told the police, Hey, I'm just being cool.
And they would have instantly left.
Why don't you know, I think really think we could help like people of color avoid like,
you know, uh, a quote unquote police involved shootings.
You know, I think they just need to tell the police that they're just being cool.
And you know, then I kind of think it there, it's their own fault really that always please
violence happens because they don't just tell them they're being cool.
Like that's what they should have done.
And like, it's their own fault if they don't, frankly, at this point, at this point, when
everyone should know better, okay, well, you know, that sounds, that sounds like a fact
to me.
And as they, as they say, facts don't care about your feelings, speaking of which, yes,
our next voicemail from facts don't care about your feelings.
Here it is.
Three, two, one, go.
Look, I'm not sexist or anything, but the weakest need to destroy the strongest killer
in a fight in real life.
Wait, wait, it's just biology.
They're just stronger.
Um, Ben, please defend yourself.
Did he say that a rowdy would defend, would kill the strongest?
Who did he say?
Yeah, he said, he said that rowdies were physically biologically stronger than killers.
And that's just a biological fact.
I mean, this is just the, it's, it's simply the, it's the Batman versus Superman debate.
Like, yeah, like Superman is stronger, but like with prep time Batman wins because he
can like, you know, he knows the weakness that he can attain.
The killers, killers work out at the library.
Killers will use their superior tactics.
Killers can bring killers would, you know, they would, they would, they would create
like a, a, some kind of anime scheme wherein they would, they would mine up a bunch of
like red chateau a night or something and like play, you know, from, from the dimensional
rift to Trestle Mystan or something.
And they would like place that all around the battlefield and detonate it before the
fight even began, you know, like, like they, like killers, the thing, like the thing about
fighting a killer is that a killer doesn't even enter the battlefield unless the stage
has been set for a completely unfair fight, uh, that they, that they cannot help but win.
So it's, it's like, it's, it's factually, it's like, um, it's, it's, it's unthinkable.
It's unthinkable.
A fight, a fight that a killer would lose simply wouldn't occur.
They wouldn't allow it.
So that's my answer to that.
Uh, uh, uh, it's simple, it's simple logic.
Next one.
I don't like the, I don't like the name of it, um, but I guess I'll play it.
It's called, it's called trunes.
So that's, that's bad, uh, three, three, two, one, go.
You guys ever noticed that like half like the trannies you see online are like not even
real trannies.
They're just like fetishists.
I think it's really gross.
What do you guys think?
I don't, uh, I don't, I don't know if we should, I don't want to paint in such broad strokes.
I don't know if we want to be generalized enough to answer that question one way or the
other.
So I'm just going to let it be.
I don't know.
I don't feel about that.
Okay.
Next one.
Uh, uh, it's called not racist, just don't like them.
Oh God.
I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't,
yeah, here we go, here we go, three, two, one, go.
Like yeah.
I'm an anti-Semite.
No, I don't support a group of people who ritualistically mutilate their children.
You got a problem with that, buddy?
Something, something, Adrena Chrome blood libel.
Uh, uh, next one's called Yup, three, two, three, two, one, go.
Okay, so that last voicemail was pretty good, huh? Can I get a voice grail? Yeah. Yeah.
I'm getting a voice grail for sure. Ha ha, beast.
Maybe if you dabbed, but he didn't do it. He didn't pull the trigger.
Well.
Alright.
So close.
You know what? I gotta say, I gotta say, I don't agree with what you say, but I will defend to the death.
You're right to say it. And, you know, the more I think about it, the more I think that maybe you've made some,
hmm, maybe made some good points here today. Maybe I should go look up a YouTube video touching on some of these topics you've raised
and just kind of let the algorithm autoplay me some more about them afterwards and just kind of see where that takes me.
Hmm. Hmm. Sounds like an adventure.
Don't try this at home, kids.
Next one is 29. Three, two, one, go.
Alright, I called in last week and Ben St. said, and I quote,
Oh God, this guy must be so powerful. And I am here to say, no, my friend, you are powerful.
Also, sorry for possibly contributing to the samurai's loss of voice grail.
Until next time, sayonara.
Okay, can you summarize that for me because, and I don't know, I'm embarrassed to admit this, but my utorrent software started playing an ad for Wendy's
while that was playing, and I don't know how to stop it.
So instead of that, I just heard an ad for Wendy's.
Well, he just said that you called him, he was too powerful last week about something, and he's like, he's not too powerful.
And he's sorry that he might have fucked up the samurai getting voice grail.
Why would you be sorry for fucking up the samurai? That guy's a fucking asshole.
I have no idea. Also, Ben, uninstall utorrent immediately, get qubit torrent, it's ad free, you fool, you absolute rude.
Utorrent fucking sucks, it used to be good.
Yeah, but now, qbit torrent, get it, open source, free, no ads.
How do you spell that?
Just qbit torrent.
I will look into that.
Yeah, utorrent used to be good now, every now and then it plays an ad, and it makes all these like clicking noises.
Like, sometimes it just makes noises like a mouse is clicking in the background of my computer, and it's like very weird and gross.
Yeah, I hate it.
No, no, no, qbit torrent is silent and doesn't do any of that shit. It's just good. It's just good.
Thank you for the tip. Much better.
Alright, next one is from Encouraging Words.
Alright.
3, 2, 1, go.
No, Nate.
Yes, watch. See you next week.
You left that comment in the comments, and he was so-
I'm glad to hear the audio version.
And you're so proud of it that he had to put it in a voicemail.
Well, it's an obvious pun, it could have been somebody else who knows.
No, it was the same.
I know who left this, and I know his comment.
This is that guy. This is voicemail god.
I've revealed that I do not know the community as well as I should. Shame.
Are you aware that that really racist guy, that transphobe guy before, was the same as a keto kitchen or whatever?
Take a bite, change your life.
Now that you mention it, they are like the same voice.
What was the name of that? Was it Keto Kitchen? Keto Cooking?
Was there more to it? Fuck.
Do you remember?
I don't remember the exact phrase.
I just remember take a bite, change your life.
I do remember that as well.
There's just so many bits. It's hard to keep track of all these bits.
There's been a lot of bits.
I guess we've been doing voicemails still feel like a new thing,
but I guess we've actually been doing them for a pretty long time now, haven't we?
What we're going to have to do is, one, we inevitably completely run out of gas.
We're just going to have to do the recap episode of the PCP.
We'll just have one of the best voicemails.
We just send in audio clips of our own show to ourselves to listen to and then comment on.
We should do...
That's a good bonus episode.
What if we did for a bonus episode?
What if we did a commentary track for old PCP episodes?
I like this idea.
I said that like a joke, but as I was saying it, I was like, I kind of think it's a good idea.
Go back to episode two and just...
Yeah.
Yeah, I think that would be funny.
Okay.
All right, we'll put that on the burner.
Put that on the maybe pile.
Yeah, we should do that at some point.
Anyway, thanks for watching Nate or No Nate.
We're Rain, Wind or Shine.
Next one, just your friendly neighborhood snowman.
Three, two, one, go.
So as a Northern Norwegian that uses words like she for clocks and he for cars all the time,
I am perplexed by you saying that English has gender imbued in its language.
But then I realized right at my doorstep, there is this little language called Finnish,
which doesn't even have gendered pronouns to refer to people.
So you just say it to girls and it to boys.
Which is, you know, that's something to add to your ideas about gender and language, I think.
And how their gendered system worked in society before they got too influenced by the Swedes and the Russians.
So get on that, people.
I'm not really into that, but hey.
Unironically, I think that's like a huge barrier to like the gender kind of conversation in general,
is that they're creating more complexity instead of simplifying.
And I think people just have a general aversion to more complexity.
Instead of creating like dozens and dozens of pronouns that you have to ask for,
make one, just like get rid of gendered pronouns all together and just have a singular pronoun
that refers to everybody that covers all the bases.
And that would have made it so much easier and caused so many jokes to no longer be effective.
I mean, we literally, we have that, we just have they, we have singular they.
Right.
Yeah, like, I don't know.
People, you know, people that are people that that are like all these neo pronouns.
Like if we had just gone in that direction for the beginning, there'd be no attack helicopter meme.
None of that would would work because it's just like, oh, it's a real word that already exists and we're simplifying language
instead of making it more complex.
Gender critical people or whatever, you know, they say that like, oh, I don't know.
I think they see it as like, oh, all this, all this trans shit, all this gender shit.
Like, why is it so complicated?
Like, gender is like these people whole identity or whatever.
But yeah, like, no, I think it makes more sense to think of it as a reaction to, you know, an overly complicated like social system we have.
You know, why do we need to have, why, why must our language be constructed in a way that one must specify gender when referring to someone by a pronoun?
There's no need for it.
It didn't have to be that way.
Yeah, pretty, pretty, pretty good.
Finish on what's up.
It's pretty cool.
I didn't, I didn't know that.
I wonder if there's probably other, there must be other languages to do it.
There can't just be some.
Yeah, for sure.
Okay, next one.
Elmo's got a gun.
Oh, oh dear.
All right.
Three, two, one, go.
And the power they took from the people will return to the people.
And so long as men die, liberty will never perish.
Too bad the technological singularity is coming when we're going to defeat death.
Yeah, I hate, I hate that.
Definitely not looking forward to that.
What did that have to do with Elmo?
I don't know.
Was that a quote from someone?
I like, I feel like I'm,
what's that, what's that movie fucking?
Oh my God, it's from a movie.
I'm trying to remember which one it is.
Give me a hint.
I'm blanking on everything.
I can see, I can see the clip of it in my brain.
Were the worlds?
No.
Citizen Kane?
No, yes.
No, not citizen Kane.
I don't, I don't remember.
Is it Charlie Chaplin's the dictator?
It might be.
I think that is what it's from.
Huh.
I think so.
That is the movie I was thinking of, but I could be wrong about my reference.
You know, I said that as a joke.
It's like the speech in that movie is,
wait, I haven't actually ever seen it.
I feel like the speech is from Charlie Chaplin,
like in character as Hitler, or as like a Hitler analog.
And I don't feel like that's something that you would say if you were trying to be Hitler.
I haven't seen the movie, but my understanding,
my understanding is that the, isn't at the end of the movie,
there's like a speech where like breaks character,
and like it's like a kind of an offlifting thing.
I'm not sure.
Maybe I'm wrong.
That might be right.
I don't know.
I haven't seen it.
Well, give it a week.
We'll find out in the comments if we're completely botching this.
I hope so.
I would appreciate it.
I appreciate knowing.
Let us know in the comments.
Not in a respectful, corrective way,
but in a you fucking idiots kind of way.
I mean, honestly, honestly, just like insulting us for,
with that, like I would be, that would be.
It's fair.
It would be fair.
It would be refreshing to be insulted for something that like,
we genuinely fucked up, you know, you know, you're right.
I'll take that.
That's an improvement as uncomfortable as it would be.
Okay.
Next one is we no longer hear technology.
Three, two, one, go.
Booms and busts are built under the pillars of capitalism.
There will always be people who starve and there will always be people
who kill themselves because of economic depressions.
Money is debt.
The internet shows us how hopeless human beings can be when they are unlucky
and find themselves with beliefs.
Like the hyper object called the economy is worth more than human lives.
They weren't so stupid.
We could instead build an economy at its core that cared about human lives.
But that's capitalist realism.
And now Mark Fisher and David Graber are dead.
I'm going to go back to playing anti-platformers,
hugging my pillow and listening to Jungle Now.
Some real shit.
That was some real shit.
Resource-based economy now.
I didn't know Mark Fisher.
Mark Frisco was based.
Rest in power, my dude.
Mark Fisher must be the guy who wrote capitalist realism.
I didn't know he was dead.
David Graber debt the first 5,000 years and many other good books.
Also dead recently.
Nobody knows of what actually.
Nobody knows.
They haven't released what was his cause of death.
They said it was like lung related.
So I thought it might have been COVID.
But I think they're saying that it's not.
They say David Graber died of natural causes.
They say don't worry, it was natural.
But I don't know what that means.
That sounds like someone who killed them.
Not naturally would say.
Oh jeez.
Let me say it like that.
When you say it like that, it sounds a little sinister.
Oh god.
You're saying that by not releasing the official story of what happened,
we're going to start creating fucking fanfics.
I mean, I just...
We've been played.
We've been played by the world.
Someone who opposed the...
I don't see how someone who spent his life opposing the interests of capital
would have had any enemies that would have wanted him dead.
That just seems like a ridiculous thing to say.
And you should apologize.
I'm sorry.
I'm definitely speaking irresponsibly.
Thank you. That's big of you.
I'm going to go check on my stocks right now.
Next up, Cross.
Arlo was right.
3, 2, 1, go.
I just got Super Mario 3D All Stars and as a zoomer,
that means I was playing Super Mario 64 for the first time ever.
And Jesus Christ, Arlo was right.
The sideways somersault jump is amazing.
I come every time I use it.
What do you guys think of Super Mario 3D All Stars?
If you have it and also fuck the commenters,
no Nate, yes watch.
Fuck yeah.
No Nate, yes watch.
Let's get a chant going in the comments.
That's our new mantra.
Should I make a fucking t-shirt of it?
Maybe, maybe I just fucking will.
I'm feeling a little mischievous.
Feeling a little mischievous today.
Can't wait to sell zero copies of that shirt too.
Yeah, but you know what?
It'll make our catalog look nice.
That's true.
Super Mario 3D All Stars, was that the one?
Yeah, they released it for Switch last week.
It's Mario Galaxy, Mario Sunshine and Mario 64,
all ported for the Switch.
Oh, sure, sure, sure.
I have a bone to pick with Mario 64 on that.
They took out Solange Bowser.
Oh, I saw that.
I saw that.
Unacceptable.
Why does he say Solange Bowser?
It's supposed to be Solange King Bowser,
is what it's actually saying.
Solange King Bowser?
Charles Martinet.
Yeah, he confirmed it in a response to Twitter a couple years back.
Solange Bowser?
But I guess it just, the heat was too much for Nintendo to take,
and then Switch just says bye-bye now or some gay shit like that.
You know, I was never super great at Mario 64.
I did not master like things like the sideways long jump or whatever.
I'm pretty basic at it.
I think I got 120 stars on the DS port or remake or whatever.
I did too.
Yeah, but I don't think I ever really mastered Mario.
He's got these weird, all these crazy fucking jumps he can do in that game.
His moveset is so fucking robust in 64.
It's pretty impressive.
It's like the first proper 3D game.
Yeah, they were just like,
it's almost, they just had like an endless war mentality.
Just add more features, more fucking features.
If there's any combination of things that we can fit a new jump into,
let's just give them more jumps.
Just put parallel universes in there, it's fine, just do it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So that's what I think about it.
No, I haven't played the remake.
I have, I bought it, but I don't plan on playing it because for some reason
Nintendo's only selling it for seven months and then they're stopping printing.
So I'm just going to hold on to that for a couple of years.
Because a Nintendo game never is worth less than like retail price.
So I have nothing to lose in everything to potentially gain.
Oh, you bought a physical copy.
Yeah, I bought a physical copy and I'm just going to hold on to it for a while
to see if it accumulates any value.
Really? You saw it as like an investment opportunity?
Yeah, you know, why not?
I mean, I already own all the games on their original platforms.
I'm not like I'm missing out on anything.
And it sounds like the ports aren't even that great because like the,
for Sunshine specific, like for Sunshine, like the whole like flood mechanic
works with the pressure sensitive triggers, which the switch doesn't have.
So you lose some control there.
And then Galaxy was all about pointing with the Wiimote and there's no Wiimote on the switch.
So both those sound like nightmares to play and then 64 plays fine on everything.
Why the fuck do you even buy it?
Hmm.
Unless you're a Zoomer.
Did you ever play the one on DS?
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
They added all these characters.
That was pretty neat.
That was pretty cool.
You started Yoshi.
It was cool.
It was a cool little subversion.
But you started Yoshi?
Yeah, you started Yoshi in the beginning of that game.
I don't even remember.
You have to find Mario.
Yeah, dude.
I remember finding Luigi and Mario and Wario and I guess Yoshi's the fourth one.
I remember there were four.
Yeah.
I had a little mini-game said like we're gimmicks with the touch screen.
Like you could play like Blackjack with Luigi and shit.
It was weird.
It's a weird fucking game.
Yeah.
Next one is from Antonio P. 321 ago.
Hello.
My question is, is the universe real?
Yeah.
Okay, next up we got Oblivion Fool.
The universe has to be real.
What would it even mean?
What would it even mean for the universe not to be real?
Well, I mean, isn't the kind of idea that once a species advances enough, they'll create
a digital reality.
And since that can happen multiple times, the odds are that you exist in a fake reality
as opposed to a real one because there's only one real reality.
Oh, yeah.
I guess.
I guess we could be living in a simulated reality inside of.
That's an Elon Musk talking point though.
So I don't know how much you want to get into that.
Like then the simulated reality is still real, right?
It's not like.
I mean, it depends on, I guess, semantically how you want to get into it because even if
we exist in a simulated reality, that simulated reality exists in reality somewhere.
I mean, a video game really exists, even if it's just code or whatever.
Did you know lights in video games use real electricity, bro?
It's true.
Can you imagine?
If you're asking, is the universe a simulation?
Questions like that.
I hope so.
Please questions like that.
I don't even like put too much stock into not because I don't think they're interesting
thought experiments, but because it doesn't affect your life in any real way.
You know, it's the same.
It's the same way as like arguing like a deterministic universe.
It's like, even if it is a deterministic universe, we all operate as if we have free will.
So we still have to operate under that assumption because even if there is a deterministic universe,
it's beyond our capacity as human beings to interact with or even understand.
So like it's cool to think about, but it doesn't affect our lives in any way, shape, or form.
It doesn't affect our lives, but like counterpoint, our lives are meaningless.
So why even why care whether or not something affects them or not?
Like why is why isn't any less valuable just because it doesn't affect our lives?
I guess my point there is not that like there are people who like I feel care too much about
trying to figure out if there's a deterministic universe or not.
And I just think it's cool to kind of like talk about when you're like half drunk with
somebody, but like at the end of the day, it's not going to affect anything.
Like there are more important tangible things you can focus your time and energy on.
But what I'm saying is what I'm saying is what if the tangible things actually don't matter
at all, which they don't, nothing matters.
Our lives don't matter.
So I mean, if you're like super fucking invested and like I need to figure this out,
like it's no more or less relevant than anything else.
But I just think there are more closer to the ground concepts that can better your own life
than chasing the existential question like that.
What I'm saying is your life better worse.
It's all an illusion.
Your life is nothing.
You're just dust in the wind anyway.
You know what I'm saying?
So like you still exist as a human being like with with your own likes and dislikes and
things you want to do.
And so like just from that very selfish perspective, you know, pursue things that affect you on
that level, I suppose, and like the community around you.
Sure.
I mean, of course, but I don't know.
I really, I really, really want this universe to be a simulation.
But so I don't know.
That that's it.
I guess that's it.
I just really want to.
And when I think about it, I think, boy, I sure hope the answer is yes.
What a damn fucking shame that I will never know if it is or not.
I think that's like the brain we're in part of it, right?
Because it's just like, but I want to know.
Yeah.
I mean, more so than knowing I want it to be true, even if I don't know.
That's that's that's where I'm at with it.
There'd be a little bit of relief, wouldn't it?
It's like, oh, this wasn't even real anyway.
Oh, sure.
Sure.
It would be a relief.
It would be a relief if it were true and I were to find out.
I'd be like, oh, fuck.
Yeah.
But like, I don't know.
Still.
It's it's it's comforting to think that it is that it could be true.
And if it were true, if it were true, it would be a comfort.
And so to imagine, I guess even just to imagine that it is true is like sort of a relief, I guess.
I guess that's how people view religion.
But that's just kind of, but then that kind of stresses me out because I'm aware.
Like, well, I mean, I don't, I don't actually know.
And like, when I think about it, it's like, well, okay, imagining it being true,
it actually just raises the very real possibility that it isn't true.
This is the real world and all that exists.
And it is just, you know, a big fucking problem.
And I'm terrified now to have contemplated that quite possibly true fact.
Oh, dear.
So I guess in that way, I would say, yeah, probably best not to think about it,
not because it's not a useful thing to think about, because nothing is useful,
but because it upsets me.
Tram.
Okay, enough.
Next one is from Oblivion Fool.
Haha.
Three, two, one, go.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine.
I like the number nine. Hello, guys.
It's me, Oblivion Fool.
I've been counting the numbers on Speakpipe because I'm losing my fucking mind.
The last week has been an absolute fucking clusterfuck of bullshit.
Mostly good.
Some a little bit bad.
The good stuff is a million views on the new ComeZone.
Sick.
20,000 new subscribers in a single week.
What the fuck?
That's cool.
A little bit daunting is the fact that I'm working on merch for Welcome to the ComeZone
only to discover that another YouTuber, Dakooters, who has way more subscribers than me,
is already selling Welcome to the ComeZone merch.
Like, what the fuck?
Like, I'm the one who's supposed to do that, but I guess I'll just compete.
I don't know.
I'm going to make shirts.
Should I bother with mugs?
I feel like the mugs are fucking waste of time, but I don't know.
On a side note, a few fans of the PCP and PCP adjacent discords have let me know that
they don't appreciate the big-titty mommy-milker semen demon that I put in my ComeZone video.
They say, the booby too big.
If only the boobies were smaller.
It's like, fuck off, dude.
You're an absolute fucking coward.
What are you afraid of?
Big booby can't hurt you.
Why are you siding with the police?
Fuck the police.
Fuck the big-titty police especially.
And fuck you!
Um, yeah.
Yeah, I don't disagree with any of that.
I, well, now I'm curious to see the big booby.
Okay.
So, alright.
Hey, I feel like I'm missing some context here.
Are you familiar with Welcome to the ComeZone?
It's that song, right?
What song?
Oh god, now I gotta find it.
Uh, it was just that like weird like visualizer thing with PCP guy in the center
with like that digitized voice just talks about like, come and shit.
I mean, I've, I've never seen this before.
We definitely all listen to it.
I've never seen this before.
It's like the first result right here on.
Yeah, you know, I see it now. I see it now.
You've never seen this?
No, I've, what is this?
We all, this is like years ago.
It's like from two years ago and we, we've,
I'm pretty sure we listened to it in a voicemail or something like that.
Maybe it's just long enough.
Okay.
Well, so.
I'm like legitimately surprised this has almost 6 million views.
I had no idea.
That's incredible.
How does it, how does this have 6 million views?
I think it's like, isn't it like a mix of like,
actual like real songs that just happens to use visualization?
Tangentially related to our show.
Cause there's links to like infected mushroom songs and stuff.
It's, it's.
What is the world coming to that like, yeah,
there's a link in the description to subscribe to the procrastinators.
On this video.
Yeah.
Six, six million people watch this video and didn't read the description
and subscribe to the procrastinators.
They didn't do it.
I mean, oblivion falls got 61 K subs.
Just do that.
I mean, that's oblivion fall after dark.
I don't, I don't know how much on this other channel.
Okay.
Okay, whatever.
You know, this is great and all, but like I'm,
what was that about the big booby?
I don't, I don't see any big booby in this video.
I'm not sure, actually.
I was too distracted by thinking about big boobies and I wasn't listening to anything else.
Oh, wait, I.
Okay.
There's another video on his channel that's called your come won't last,
which sounds like a similar song and it's kind of got a similar visualizer.
I mean, there's like some I go faces in this video,
but like, no, I don't see any titties.
No, no.
Are you watching that your come won't last?
No, no, no, I'm talking about the.
Okay.
I think he must be talking about because on your come won't last,
there's a lady with the big booby mommy milkers.
So.
It's a good shit.
That's not it.
I mean, no, those are definitely not too big.
Those are definitely not too big.
Not even close.
They are.
I would actually say those are, those are, those are perfect.
Those are, that's, those are my ideal right there.
Just like that.
Too, too big for me is like a, a, a, a, a, like comical, like,
like, like, like parody level.
And these are not quite there.
So.
Perfecto.
That's, that's what I think.
On that question.
Okay.
I just want to give props to oblivion fall.
Your come won't last for least September 11th, 2020.
Based.
Very based, very based.
Okay.
Good.
Good to hear from oblivion fall.
Make merch, slay all your enemies.
Don't ask us for advice with scrubs.
We don't know what the.
Yeah.
Zero, zero shirts sold.
Next up.
Ben, you are cool.
I have disagreement.
Smiley face.
Glitchy.
Send at start.
Frowny face.
Okay.
Maybe it's supposed to be sound.
Oh yeah.
Probably.
All right.
Three, two, one go.
So I was catching up on the past two episodes of the podcast today.
And there are a few situations where I feel like Ben in particular was
looking at moral questions and too much of a vacuum.
The first one being he went on like this fervent outburst on his
discord about some woman that people on Twitter were calling sexy
was actually very unattractive in his opinion.
Obviously, if that woman does not see you saying these things in
the discord, then she won't be hurt by it.
But you have to look at it in the context of you posting it in a
discord server where people are going to say, wow, Ben really
just made a very hostile atmosphere about someone not appealing
to his like subjective preferences.
Obviously, that's going to make people feel like threatened and
uncomfortable.
You don't want to do that.
You're just that is you are the asshole for that reason.
Okay.
So the other thing is the pornography of real people.
You're saying you can't think of a reason why it would be bad if
like the person does not see it.
Obviously, it's the same type of thing where if they don't see it,
then yeah, I wouldn't be a problem for them.
But if someone makes pornography of a real person disregarding
like whether they would want that or not, then what that
communicates is, hey, I'm willing to go behind people's backs and
break like personal boundaries for the sake of commodifying
them for my own personal gain.
Obviously, that is just going to again make people feel uncomfortable
and like threatened by doing that.
So you should not do it.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm not going to lie.
I turned out of that whole thing.
Okay.
All right.
I have some, I have some.
About the discord thing, I understand why it was a little,
maybe a little too hostile and why people wouldn't like it.
And I'm not even going to say like, oh, these people are just
being too sensitive.
It's fine.
However, I just, you know, you know, actually no, I don't have anything
else to say about that.
It's fine.
I'll leave it at that.
But on the, okay, about the, these are like, about the porn
thing, like, I don't know, are you assuming, are you assuming
that they're making the porn to sell it?
You're like, is that the assumption here?
Because you said they're commodifying it.
I mean, I think that probably it is illegal to make, to sell.
Like a person owns their own likeness, right?
You can't like sell, you can't like sell a person's likeness
unless it's like for the purpose of like criticism or critique
or parody, right?
So like if you were going to make, yeah, it would be wrong to like
make and sell porn of someone to commodify them that way,
unless it were some kind of like statement about a public figure
for the purpose of commentary.
But if you just, if it's, if you're just talking about like just
the act of like drawing someone naked, like, I don't know,
because you just, because you want to see it or even just because
other people want to see it, like, I don't know.
I don't, I think, I don't, I can't think of, I mean, are you
saying, is this an argument that like one, one mustn't do it?
Or is it an argument that like it's like wrong or like, like,
it's mean or like it's bad or it's rude?
Because like, I would agree that it's maybe rude or unkind even,
but like, I, like, I'm drawing the line at saying like,
oh, but you shouldn't do it because I'm, I don't know.
I don't, I just, just because I think something is like wrong
or unkind, I am not willing to make the leap to, you know,
therefore it is, it is, it is something that no one should do
ever.
Ben confirmed okay with racism.
That's right.
Yes, true.
Got him.
Click that.
Um, but like, I'm just kind of, I just kind of think,
I just kind of think people, I'm, I just don't, I'm not,
I don't like cops.
I don't like cops and people like, oh, people shouldn't,
oh, people shouldn't do that thing.
Oh, well you did that thing and that thing was wrong because it,
because of this, that and that reasons and it was,
and it was uncomfortable for these people and like,
and they, they know they should, they should be a law like,
no, that's cop behavior.
Um, I don't know.
Okay.
Whatever.
Fair, fair enough.
Fair criticism.
All right.
Thanks for speaking your piece, idiot.
Next one.
Utilitarianism and holy shit, bro.
Titties and boobies.
Three, two, one, go.
Like, okay, morality.
Like, why not just say like, if something increases overall well-being
in the system, then it is good.
And if it decreases overall well-being, then it is bad.
Like, dude, like, what the fuck dude?
Like, holy shit, bro.
Fucking titties, fucking boobies.
Okay.
Well, the really obvious rebuttal is to then,
then you have to quantify well-being and how do you do that?
That's the, that's the answer.
So when you've, when you've, when you've worked that out,
make another voicemail and lay out your.
Not to mention well-being for some people can be bad for other people.
And so you have the moral question becomes, okay,
is it okay to fuck up some people's lives for the benefit of others?
Which is the whole critique of utilitarianism in the first place.
Yeah.
Yeah, true.
Like, is it okay to like go and deliberately reduce one person's well-being
because it will like, yeah, raise like more people?
I guess that's kind of like, you know,
the trolley problem question, right?
Yeah, it's like, is it okay to deliberately kill this person
because it will save these other people?
Yeah.
And like, yes.
In the trolley problem, yes.
Of course you pull the fucking lever.
Well, I think, I think utilitarianism,
utilitarianism works in like a binary situation like that,
but the real world is often more complicated
and utilitarianism breaks down with multiple variables.
I mean, yeah.
I mean, you're, you're just,
I do think that probably at the end of the day,
if you could, if you could like, prove mathematically that like,
yes, a thing increases like overall well-being in the world,
then maybe you could have an argument for,
yeah, so it's okay to like fuck someone over because it...
It's just tyranny of the majority at that point.
Yeah, but like, but you can't prove it.
You can't like, there's no formula that you could,
you know, mathematically we can see that like,
yes, murdering this person will,
you know, create enough happiness to compensate
in like the people at large or whatever, right?
You just, there's just no foundation for it.
That's the trouble.
It's hard to define.
Next up, phallic person, gear third.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, I heard you had a big cock.
Nice.
I've heard this track before actually.
Okay, well-being.
Amazing.
It's, it never gets old.
No, never gets old.
Three, and I hope that next time it's just every voicemail is just
nice cock, bro, nice cock, bro, nice cock.
Yeah.
It's all, it's all I want to hear.
Next up, zinthus schminthus schumilashimia.
Cool.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey there, appreciate you.
So basically,
I've been trying to change my name for the past decade.
On the internet, I mean, I'm trying to have like a cool name.
That's not shit.
Right.
Because that, because of the age of internet, I had to like.
This guy's such a fucking croon chair.
Yeah.
Basically decide my name at 12 years old.
What?
And, um.
Oh, right.
Fuck you.
I ended up with schumia, which has always been, always been
mispronounced, either by shimuya, shimila, shit like that.
I said it right.
I said schumia.
I guess I put the answers wrong.
I've been trying like xinthus with the cool Y and T-H's and X's and shit.
Yeah.
Azorath, Metreon, zinthus.
That's right.
That's good.
Go for it.
Just do that.
Problem solved.
Do that.
Yeah.
It's a nightmare.
How the fuck do you come up with an internet name?
And how do you change it after 10 years of use where all your emails are named after
it?
You just do it.
You don't need your emails to fucking match your internet handles because that's just
for you.
No, that's not public.
Nobody sees that.
My email is IAS.
You can change your comic.
You can change your Twitter handle at any time.
You don't have to make a new account.
You can just go to settings and change your Twitter handle.
If you want to change your Twitter handle, just fucking do it.
Also, here's a hot tip for if you want to change your Twitter handle, if you're at
handle and it's already taken, just put an underscore after it because when people search
for you, they'll just start typing and they'll never get to the underscore because they'll
find your profile before it finishes.
Yeah.
But it's ugly.
It's ugly having that underscore in there.
It's fine.
Yeah.
I mean, yeah, it doesn't matter.
You just have the actual word in your name and nobody will notice because they'll type
for it and they'll never get to have to type the underscore.
It'll pop up and they're recommended before then and you're fine.
You're cool.
I mean, unless the person who's got the name has more followers than you, they'll never
find you.
They'll find that guy instead.
I don't think so.
Take care.
No, it's like a fish game, like an eater game.
It's like get more followers than a person.
Change your at handle to their name so that you come in on searches above them, so people
looking for them find you and then you gain their followers and then once you grow, you
pick someone else who you've now become bigger than and you just repeat, oh my god.
That's it.
That's how you do it.
That's how you beat Twitter.
It's how you become the top dog.
Well, try it out and let me know how it works.
I think it's foolproof.
All right.
So anyways, that's how you that's how you fucking do it.
Yeah, you just thought being afraid of it and just do it.
Easy.
Don't worry about the emails.
I have like so many email accounts and they're all a clusterfuck, but it's just it's just
the nature.
Oh, it's it's really funny because because my the Alibaba account that I'm using is
tied to the the ratty Frickers cop killers email.
My name in there is like it's but the name listed on the site is rowdy fucker and like
the lady that I'm talking to about like making pins and stuff calls me rowdy because I mean
I'm sure she knows that that's not my real name, but like that's my listed name.
So that's what she calls me.
God, the killer himself being called a rowdy and you can't even correct it.
I'm under cover.
Nice.
I'm on I'm undercover.
You know, I'll place the blame on them if anything if things go south.
Next up, funny jokes.
Let's let's hope so three, two, one, go.
One I hear a funny joke, a man walks into a bar, ouch.
What did one Frenchman say to the other?
I have no idea.
I don't speak French.
Two muffins are sitting in the oven.
One says, wow, it's hot in here.
The other one says, sure is probably about 350 degrees Fahrenheit.
Well, who's there to to who know to whom a horse walks into a bar.
Well of the patrons quickly get up and leave realizing the potential danger of the situation.
Love animals.
You won't stop laughing at these animal memes.
Click here to view them.
Don't worry.
I will eat my own ass.
Do you have an explanation for this Tom?
No, I do not.
I.
Well, I'm sorry.
Viewers, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
We put you through that.
We suck.
We all suffer together.
I mean, I mean, I know 2020 has been pretty bad.
But, you know, like this, this too, we can all we can all suffer through together and bond over our mutual distress.
We hear you.
We see you.
Last voicemail.
Tom, are you excited?
I am.
It's a reference.
I understand.
Is it?
It's metal gear rising.
Oh, well, it's called this isn't my sword.
No, I didn't.
I didn't play it.
What do it?
Yeah.
It looks pretty cool.
Three, two, one, go.
Eleazar.
Where are we still here?
Just suffer.
Every night.
I can feel my energy.
And my jokes.
Even my racist jokes.
The podcast I've lost.
The light novels I've lost.
It won't stop hurting.
Lights like they're still there.
You can feel it too, don't you?
I'm the one who got caught up with Canton.
A group above YouTube monetization.
Even above Patreon.
And I was the parasite below.
Feeding off Nate Bestman's funny power.
They came after you in voice jail.
Then in PC prison industrial complex.
Canton just keeps growing.
Swallowing everything in his path.
Getting bigger and bigger.
It's almost as big as my dick now.
Eleazar.
I'm gonna make him give back our past.
Take back everything that we've lost.
And I won't rest until we do.
Well, I'm disappointed.
The title was Metal Gear Rising.
And that was Metal Gear Sub 5 reference.
You fucked up your game references, you fool!
What the fuck is a Metal Gear?
It's a bipedal tank capable of not launching a nuclear strike.
Oh, wow. That sounds pretty cool.
They should make a video game about that.
You know, it's budgetary constraints.
You know, it's a lot of shit.
It's a lot of polygons.
Who can afford them these days?
They're too busy modeling every single pore on Keanu Reeves' face
for Cyberpunk 2077.
They don't have the budgetary resources to make a Metal Gear game.
Maybe someday, though.
Wait, is that the... is Kojima?
Is that Kojima?
He's not in that now.
Oh, okay, well.
Um, well, fuck, that was it.
Oh, god, I'm gonna...
Pray to god that we didn't get any more.
Okay, no.
You're...
No, no, no. As soon as the podcast starts, that's the cutoff point.
I would...
No, you know what?
Don't give these people ideas!
Eleazar, cut that out!
They'll never end!
Yeah, you're right.
It'll be like...
Like, I mentioned the War on Quickfill contest.
Like, people were submitting...
Like, I said, like, the entry started flooding in, like, right before...
Right before the judging.
But, like, they were still flooding in, like, as we were finishing...
Like, as we were judging the last entry, like, more were still coming in.
We had to be like, okay, that's it, no.
No more allowed.
Oh, god.
Um, yes.
Yes.
Um, but I guess that's the, uh...
I guess that's the episode.
Um, Tom...
I don't know.
Yeah?
No.
I'm just gonna say, maybe you'll disagree with me.
I thought this one was kinda almost middling energy.
Like, there was...
There was some good banter going on this week.
Oh...
I know, we fucked up.
We fucked up pretty bad.
I don't know.
The new...
The new PCP, and you with an Umlat PCP, is about being low energy.
It's something you just put on in the background.
You just put it on on your tablet, and you hand it to your toddler.
And you just let it auto-play.
Right, right.
To make us add revenue.
That's the new model.
YouTube rewards this kind of content.
You know, frequent, regular, long-form content.
We're sorry.
We'll both make sure to pop an ambient before we start recording next week's episode.
We apologize for any energy that may have accidentally slipped in to this podcast.
And I assure you, it will never, ever happen again.
Do we mention that Gibb's on vacation?
We didn't.
We didn't mention that at all.
I meant to say that at the beginning.
Yeah, Gibb is not here because she is on vacation.
She's on a dog vacation.
It's literally a vacation for her dog, but she's going also.
Incredible.
They're just like, yeah, let's go on like a two-week vacation to let the dog get some fresh air.
Going to a cabin or whatever.
So she will not be here next week either.
She might be back the week after that.
I'm not actually sure.
I guess we'll find out.
Okay.
I think that's really funny, and I wanted to mention it because it's very, very good.
Very good facts.
So send us a voicemail for next week at speakbike.com slash PCP voicemail and patron us at patreon at patreon.com slash, is it the procrastinators?
Yep.
Patreon.com slash the pro.
Wait, let me double check that.
I don't trust procrastinators.
It is the procrastinators.
Okay.
Um, patron us at patreon.com, if you like what we do here and you have it, if you like the episode, if you like the episode.
Get in early for the early episode commentary tracks that may or may not actually end up happening.
Oh, we should do those.
Oh, we should really do those.
You think those would make good bonus episodes?
I think they'd be pretty funny.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's probably true.
We can just record one, and if it comes out like shit, we'll just pretend this never happened.
We could, we could do, we could do like one and make it public and then be like, okay, we're going to make more of these, but they're going to be bonus or something.
Yeah, yeah.
Something like that.
Okay.
HD remasters of our own podcast.
Works for every other industry.
Which is put lots of bloom on it.
Anyway, anyway, yes, get, get in on that.
Patreon costs us that procrastinators.
Um, and, uh, hey, if you really want, if you really want to be cool in a PCP sort of way, maybe buy a shirt by a I have COVID shirt by a based state shirt at.
I don't even know what's what's the URL for that.
It would be our store, our store friend.
It's teespring.com slash stores slash the pro procrastinators, but there's dashes where the space to be.
So the dash pro dash procrastinators.
Links are all in the description links and links in the description, baby.
Um, all right.
And that's going to do it.
That's going to do it for this week.
Are we out?
Yes.
We're out.
Then let's, then let's go.
Oh, goodbye.
Goodbye.
See you soon.
Bye.
You know, that was kind of good energy.
It was pretty.
Yeah.
It was pretty solid.
It was pretty solid banter.
Yeah.