Jump down, jump down, and then say some fucking gay shit.
I'm gay!
Hello everyone and welcome to this week's episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast!
That's right everyone, you should be excited because this is a very special week, but first let's introduce everybody who's here today.
It's me, of course, the best guy ever, King of the Castle, Lord of the Manor. We also have Ben.
It's me, Ben Saint, of Patreon!
Wow, wow, what a meme.
Digibro!
Hey, what's up, buddy?
We've got Hippocrit.
I wasn't prepared for saying anything.
And we've got Jess Endlet G, also called Larry the Comic.
And finally, Tom Oliver, the best one of the three.
That's right, okay, so today is a very exciting day because what we're doing today is we're touching each other's dicks.
We're putting them in our mouths. We're making a
spherical circle and we're just going all kinds of crazy because this is the great circle, Jerk!
Yeah!
You see, you see viewers, as it happens, we're all the best and today we're gonna tell each other that over and over again.
It's come to my attention that there has been far, far too little shilling of ourselves on this channel.
It's become a big problem. The people need it, the people crave it, and so this is our response.
I wouldn't say shilling. I would describe it as fluffing.
Well, you can shill yourself.
I mean, you know, it's, you know, pick your turn, it's all good.
Let me fluff my ball here.
I would describe it as campaigning.
Yeah, everyone's all about campaigning nowadays.
All the campaign trail.
Suddenly, all of us, like, just spontaneously grew ties out of our shirts.
Yeah!
And I don't know if this is relevant at all,
but it does so happen that we are recording this on Guy Fawkes Day, the man who tried to blow up Parliament and upset that
establishment, and that's why you need to vote for Bernie Sanders.
Write him in on the fucking ballot.
I'm for that. I'm for writing in Bernie Sanders.
And, you know, yeah, write in whoever.
Write in, write in this guy.
Write in, and let G, write in me, write in anybody.
Okay, so let's, let's, what are we gonna do here?
We're gonna pick somebody and then talk about how they're the best.
Is that what we want to do?
The concept here is each of us is gonna take our hand and we're gonna just, you know, 45 degrees to the right.
Grab the next guy's dick.
Jack, jack at it, jack at it, jack at it, jack.
Okay, so why don't we start?
I mean, I'm looking in, in the chat.
We got Ben is the first.
So let's just all start with Jack.
No, no, no, not me.
Jack and a dick.
Oh, I'm sorry, Ben. You're the top of the bill here.
Um, here's, for friends, is what I like about Ben's work.
No!
It's, it's something Ben first.
I can't take what's helpful.
Let's do Nate so he can shut up and he'll have to listen to us talk about him.
Uh, okay, I guess.
If you want.
Uh, who wants to talk about how cool Nate is?
Oh god, this is gay.
Right, that's the point.
It feels weird, right?
I didn't know it'd be gay.
I think without a doubt.
This is the most homoerotic one.
Yeah.
This is the part where everyone's realizing.
No one actually wants everyone to say where it's cool.
Okay, if you guys want to do me, I can take it.
I've steeled myself.
All right.
If we actually were at Radcon, if we were to do the gay thing, I think what would happen is we would get our dicks out.
Sex?
But we would be like, oh, I don't want to be the first guy to touch someone else's.
Well, yeah.
Even if you're not gay, that makes you the most gay of the group.
Standing in a circle without dicks out, looking at each other like, oh.
All right, all right.
I'm going to be the man to grab the dick first.
I volunteer as tribute.
Everyone, please praise me.
Just heap my well-deserved praise upon me.
Ben, I know you.
I've known you for the longest.
And I remember back when your art was not what it is now.
In fact, when we started TBAP some four years ago, perhaps now.
Three or four years.
I think it was four years ago.
I thought I think it was less than three.
Or maybe just about three years ago.
It was the end of 2013.
Right, okay.
So that's three years.
Three fucking years.
And your work was much less polished.
Comparing the stuff that you were producing then to what you're doing now with the Vapors and the Champion.
It is incredible to me that someone could advance that much in the span of time.
Yes.
And I've always liked how you are not like me where I need the security of making a plan.
I have my job because I don't trust myself to just go jump out and do something.
But you have never been like that.
You always just go jump headfirst into things.
And I've always admired that.
So there you go.
And you did it with your art.
And you know, TBAP was a similar sort of venture.
It was your suggestion, even though we both contributed mostly equally.
Yes.
I'm sure I'm glad.
Yes, wow.
That was very heartfelt, Nate.
And I appreciate that.
I don't know what to say.
I was really gay though.
Real gay though.
I'm just impressed with the way you can make like...
I'm just impressed with Magda.
I like her. She's great.
Magda's the best character design of all time.
Her hair is so awesome.
I love everything about it.
It's the coolest thing.
And she's got a very distinct silhouette.
I am jealous in terms of art skill.
Because I've always wanted to make like a comic.
Even a small one.
And then you just like, I'm going to make one and you did it.
And you made a website.
Over like six months I did it.
I mean, yes.
You had an idea and you just...
It was good.
It's got a good style.
Let's talk about the fact that Ben's area of expertise
is inherently more valid as art
than what most of us do,
which is YouTube and which is worthless
and should not exist.
I am the only real artist among us.
Yeah.
I lend us an air of much needed credibility.
You know, even aside from credibility,
it's good to just have diversity of any kind.
Aside from just a bunch of video guys
who just make videos,
it's good to have it.
Yeah, I like that because Ben's...
I mean, Ben is kind of a video guy.
And I like that some of us
can do more than one thing, you know?
Like, I basically don't do anything
other than videos and podcasts.
So it's cool that we have people around
who can simultaneously
can be in a video if need be
and can be good in a video if need be,
but also have like a whole different thing,
which Ben and Tom both...
You did just produce an album.
I don't want to get to the circle jerk of
Digit too hard right now, but I'm just...
We'll bring that up.
We'll touch on that.
I just several times stroke on it.
I respect the fact that Ben
is of a different breed
from most indie comic
people.
Because when you read
the Vapors, for example,
they're not falling in love
and nobody is a woman with a dick
and there's not any
trance, icky trance stuff
happening.
Yeah, thank God.
I'm confused. I'm confused what you're praising right now.
Well, I mean, compared to the landscape
of DeviantArt and Tumblr comics
that are bursting out of the internet at the scene...
You have the sort of like
Seinfeldian
aversion to anything trying too hard
to be deep.
So everything that you write comes off as
pretty sincere and real because it's not trying too hard.
Oh.
I feel that way too.
I feel like...
I hate to write a story
that's just easier, that's been written before.
Or that could be
described as conventional in any way.
I agree with Jesse in that I feel like
when I see most
art on the internet, I think
I immediately like
find a trend I'd compare it to.
Even great art. Like someone
like a GGDG
with cucumber quests. Like beautiful, beautiful art.
But when I see it, I think
this kind of reminds me of the New Wave Cartoon Network stuff
and what's going on on Tumblr a little bit, you know?
And I see all this art that's very
homestuck or very Tumblr, very this or that.
And I look at your stuff
and it's obvious that your manga inspired
but it doesn't look like manga
but it also doesn't look like
OEL, you know?
It's just its own thing.
It doesn't quite look like any other...
It doesn't make me think, well, this is
obviously where he comes from, you know?
Well, yeah. It could stand out
if it was on a shelf from other people
trying to do comics.
For sure.
Ben, I think there are two distinct things
about you that I really respect and appreciate.
The first is just like your raw ability
and like being able to draw the way
you draw the way I wish I could draw.
Like if I imagined in my mind
how my art style would naturally develop
over the course of five years, it would end up
something like yours.
Just like, because I've always been
a really big fan of like
bold line art, like really distinct
character styles and like your art
especially with the champion really brings that
but you still have a lot of like sense of detail.
Like things are simplified
and streamlined and cartoonish but there's also just
enough detail there to give it like some dimension
to the grit that a lot of super simplified styles
don't have anymore.
And that's something I've always struggled to try
and do in my work that I've like streamlined stuff
but it's kind of gotten too streamlined
and I think it looks too basic.
But you definitely like ride that line really well.
And then the other thing that I really appreciate
about you is the fact that you like are able
to just like focus in on one thing
because like I wanted to do my comic
or I wanted to write my book and stuff
but I still want to do the YouTube
because I can't really let go of that
to the YouTube part. I want to do videos
and I want to do writing, I want to do blogging
and all these things but like you did T-Bap
they're like T-Bap's done, now I'm doing comics
and like just focusing on that one thing.
And I can't do that.
I am really good at focusing
but it's to my benefit and detriment
because I get obsessed
with one thing and I can't think about
anything else.
I've observed this cataclysmic
effect this could have in person.
I feel like the benefits would be
worth it especially for someone with my
mentality which can't do that at all.
It's always going to be a bit of the grass
is greener like if you're not like that
you'll see the benefits but yeah it's still
I mean there's certainly plenty of benefits
and I too would praise Ben for that
although I also have watched how
like none of the champion
was drawn in the last month
because of the Pokemon
I did get
obsessed with making the Nuzlocke vids
to the champion's detriment
I think the videos came out really good
but yeah.
There's a term for that kind of
hyper-focusing on one thing to the exclusion
of other things. Does it start with an A?
It may.
I'll leave it open to interpretation.
Another real cool thing in fact
just your very last... Artist.
Artist is the word.
Of course.
The last Nuzlocke
you did
that amazing
horrifically
tragic ending with the whole musical bit
that was great
and you know since you don't
do a lot of video editing on the whole
I very much am glad to see you
kind of adapt and do something like that
I mean nothing about it was hugely complex
but to take the extra effort
to put it in. I spent
a lot of time on that ending
because like I finished
that episode and I was like this is really
sad and I felt really sad
and I was like you know what
I should really edit this
I should really just go all out
and just push the sad angle of this scene
and just do everything I could
just do the flashbacks and the music
and cut out
the words I'm saying so that
I cut out a couple of like jokier lines
that sort of detracted from the pathos
of it.
Change the end card
just have it fade out on a whole different thing
and it was well done
yeah but I did
because I'm not really a video guy
it did take me an extraordinary amount of time
but I had a fucking vision
that I wanted to realize with that
ah well it was
yeah it knocked it out of the park
and if everything goes according to plan
the fucking finale will be
even more like that
I hope. Awesome.
I gotta say my time observing Ben
as an artist has been a constant
one upping of impressing me
more where like my first
exposure to Ben is
the first t-baps
which were not good it was
shut up you were great man get the fuck out of here
you don't know they had keg
and phantom that's the first couple of them
well they were sent to me because I was
the EQD poster guy
and I get sent this video that's like
you know these I
I didn't really take in the designs of the OCs
which are great but like the actual drawing
was not that amazing
it was a ritual we were performing
and the audio was really bad
but then suddenly I get sent this one
where all of a sudden the designs are great
and I assumed that you guys like
you know paid some artists
to like revamp your OCs or something
when I first saw it like oh wow
now suddenly the art is good and the audio is decent
and then alright I'll definitely post this on EQD
and then all of a sudden each episode
there's all these new
artistic styles coming in
there's all these different ideas
there's this one where phantom horn is like in live action
and he's spilling ink all over the page
trying to draw stuff
that was fucking genius
that was the moment when I was like
whoa these guys are fucking great
and then phantom reviews
and keg reviews these huge art
like animatic projects
spent like six months
drawing fucking phantom reviews
spent me so much
I could do it so much faster now
that's the only thing I can say
and then when I met you guys
and you were like talking about your OCs
and all the shit you'd made up and I was just like
this wellspring of creativity
being wasted on ponies
and then finally
we made the, we had the
collection of the greatest pony OCs
every single one of our OCs was the
greatest pony OCs ever made
that is no hyperbola right there
sticky situation needs his own comics
there was sticky situation
there was ultimate pumpkin
there was a horsefister
horsefister oh there was a silver lining
silver lining a good one
he was awesome are we forgetting any
I think we might be forgetting some
but eventually that great talent
stopped being wasted on ponies
and then for like months
Ben's like I'm working on this comic
and now I remember when I like
when we did the comic trades
at a brony con and I know Ben remembers
me saying this but I was just so impressed
with how dynamic Ben could make
the poses of the ponies like so
fast because the comics jam is you have
five minutes to draw
one panel of a comic and then we all trade
you know and everyone else would just try
to draw like an okay
picture it would be like
I'll try to draw the
face and make it look okay you know
I'm talking about other like people who consider
themselves artists other deviant art artists
and stuff you know people were friends with
they're drawing like a
a decent looking
photo of a pony
Ben would draw these super dynamic
poses of like a character
doing something you know like
doing some really interesting
thing that totally brings it to life and I
would split I would split it into
I would split my panel into multiple panels
and draw like scenes
playing out
and like just I remember that
you know over time
I mean I eventually saw the Vapors
this is fucking great you know I love the characters
I love the art style and everything
and then
everything you've done since then has impressed me more
like I liked Brunswick
even more than chapter one of the Vapors
you know I like
champions art is even more impressed the character designs
are fucking just gorgeous
in champion those are my favorites incidentally
is both the girls from champion
yeah
Agatha is the cutest Agatha is
number one waifu from the Beniverse
and then I was shocked all over again
when inktober started
because you started doing these like really sketchy
ink drawings
with like different colored pens
in totally different styles
because I only know you for like the minimal look
and then suddenly you're drawing these like really
detailed robots and like
these muscle men and shit
and fucking and I was like where did this come
from because this is almost
even cooler like even cooler
than what I know you for like I like the
minimal Scott Pilgrimmy stuff but the
the hyper detail stuff I was like man
I want to see Ben draw a fucking post apocalypse
war story now with mechs and
shit um you know totally
Erygia anyone who doesn't know
what I'm talking about go to Ben's twitter look at his inktober drawings
all of those were like
like literally concept completion
in like 30 minutes like even the big robot
like that's a completely chilling what's Ben's
twitter handle it's at Ben something
it's also ugly it's all so ugly
with two L's on the all
but like that robot is
a completely original robot design
it's not based on anything Ben just
came up with a robot and drew it and it
looks like what would be
in you know like an 80s
cyberpunk manga or something
but it's it's not actually
it's not someone else's design
here's a here's a flattering comparison
since we're talking about robots do you know that Aichi
Ryota has said that if he finished
one piece one day he'd like his next series to be
a mecha series or some sort of robot
that would be crazy I mean this is
it was probably like 10 years ago at this point
but he did say it and to
to cap off my praising
Ben's artwork you know
just like two nights ago me
and Ben and DeVue did like a little
drawings jam where we just like for
10 minutes I gave us a topic and we'd
all draw a picture and like I would
spend like 10 minutes just
trying to make a comprehensible
face like just that I want
you to understand that this is a human
is all I was worried about and
you know DeVue was drawing these like weird
esoteric things and then Ben
would show us like a page with like four
different illustrations on it you know all
these different characters doing all this different stuff
that's also on his twitter did you I
I want to mention that I've never
been I've never been sadder
that you're not a better artist because the
picture the vapors fan art you tried to
draw was like yeah the bet it was
beautiful I loved it so much but then
you looking at it it's like I couldn't
even tell what it was
no yeah it was it was great
concept no execution at all
it was amazing though it was Vincent lying
in bed vaping and he was vaping up a cloud
that was taking the form of like a
beautiful girl yeah yeah he was like
vaping he was he was like vaping
his ideal girl yeah
it was supposed to be a qt 3.14
as it says in the clouds
I might totally say I like that so much
I might go and make it myself because it's
really I hope so you can actually
why was God awful
like the image you have in your mind is
so much better than what you would look
at if I showed it to you
especially because I drew Vincent like
totally wrong um
but yeah and other than that I'll also praise
the fact that Ben Cannon will eat
anything
Ben has this might not be
considered a lot of people might think
you know they might think Ben
he doesn't shower very often
so bad
because I never leave the house okay
has no scruples about anything
some people might see that as a bad thing
but personally I really
I legitimately admire the fact
that Ben will eat
absolutely anything
I don't like it because it's there
I just want to put on the record
we've been saying this shit to Ben for years
and he never believed us we've got outside
proof now we've got testimony
it's not just us
I know
I have terrible hygiene it's because I never leave
my room that's the reason
by the way Ben
speaking of your art
here's a little inside scoop folks
for people who like the vapors
I remember when you were finishing it
you would finish basically the whole thing
if I recall correctly the very last thing
you were working on was just one panel
in the middle that was like a shot
of the apartment building after Vincent
I think came back home
with a shot of the building from outside
of the dorm room yeah
that is by far
well it's the most
attractive looking picture
frankly
it's kind of my favorite thing you've ever drawn
just that picture of the building
just that picture of that building
like the way the clouds
the spooky way the clouds are coming out of some windows
and the lights
I do really like that
it was a great picture
it's a bit like my banner on Topastic
or something because I really liked it
appropriate
Ben put your dick away
who are we sucking next
Patreon.com
there's never been a better time
I'm just imagining
Ben
literally holding his dick
about to put it away and then he goes wait
and then he shakes it and says like
Patreon.com
gross
alright well next on the list here
thank you everyone for all those kind words
and even for the less kind ones
our next I guess is Digi
since he's number two on our list here
just skip me
why do you get to fucking
opted to skip
Digi
I'm very impressed all the time
that what you do
with your life is exactly and only
what you want to do and no more and no less
and you are
you have
I don't know you've just got like a drive
you've got a drive to exhaustively
catalog your thoughts on this one
thing and you've
formed your whole life around
doing that
and it's pretty amazing actually
thank you
I'm very jealous of the fact that
you have been writing
for so long that you're so good at it
that you can do all the stuff
you do really quick
just crank it out
such a good talent to have
or skill to have
to be able to do what you do for a living
I was at that speed
I was trying to write a script for my Lisa
thing and I was like this is not coming
out good and I thought you know if
Digi could bang out like ten pages on this
like if he were the one who loved Lisa
and wanted to make a video on it the video would be done
in a day honestly at this point
I wouldn't even have to script it
exactly
this is the problem with praising me
is that I'm just going to double down on all of it
I'm sure you will
let's not beat around the bush here
because Digi is obviously leading the charge
for all of us
into being successful at all of this kind of
shit
which one of you is sucking off a vacuum cleaner
stop it
I'm vaping hard
dude you're vaping I'm vaping dude
guys
good work Kieran that cancer
we're the vapors
thank you
Digi
the professionalism that you bring
to doing all this shit
is
it'd be an understatement to think that I use it
as
the path that I am hoping to follow
it's pretty much
try to copy what you're doing
and frankly there's no higher praise
that I can give than I am willing to follow
all the same path as what you're doing
and it's not like we make the exact same content
or anything but
you always talk about how
you're trying to blend your boogie and your pop
your wish
to make your content that you like
but then possibly even equally important
is to make it digestible to people
make it popular and get it out there
so people can appreciate it
that is a very valuable lesson
that someone like me
I think would really resist
because I'm kind of a foolish
naive idealist about these things
that I'm trying to shake off
but seeing that you've just done it and it's worked out
so great, relatively speaking
I think it's been
extremely helpful to me
and I'm just, I'm really glad to know you
and to
sort of be able to be involved in this kind of stuff
super gay
full gay on this
I don't know, I'm being honest
you're not holding anything back
somebody has to
get the gay going
yeah, somebody has to get the gays out
what have I been reduced to that I'm leading the gay charge
oh god
I apologize
I respect that Digi does not
let himself get bogged down in perfectionism
at all
like for example
yeah, his stuff totally sucks and it's great
he's basically garbage
like when I was over there
and we were putting the finishing touches
on the bedroom bedrock album
and I gave him the verses that I had recorded
before I came over
I was listening to Get Action, I was listening to my verse
and I was like, I feel like I could do this part
a little bit better here
but Digi's like, what I just posted it and I'm like, okay
I remember that
if it had been up to me, I would have just recorded
my verse a thousand million times
and the album would have never ever come out
well it's funny, Jesse
because you're the one who's always saying
if you really love someone
you'd love them warts and all
like you'd love all the imperfections
about it
but I hate myself
so I must have no warts
I release stuff that's like
I release stuff that I have big
problems with but then over time
I gradually just kind of take that as
like, oh well that's just part of it
it's just a flawed thing
and that's just
a part of the product
an excuse to not have to keep working on it
mostly but
it's kind of an art form in itself
to recognize that your standards
that you're bringing as the creator of the artwork
whatever it may be are not what people
are going to be viewing it as
and I think guys like me and Jesse
I would say it's a huge weakness
I definitely have a problem with that
Nate, you introduced me
to a quote
it was like, in this moment
I'm euphoric
no no, it wasn't that one
it was
art is never finished only abandoned
I don't know who said that
but you told me one time and I was like
wow that's so true and you know it's
part of art, part of being an artist
is learning the ideal moment to abandon it
when continuing to work
is going to no longer yield
worthwhile results
that is a very difficult balance
to find
I'm still working on it
that's one of the advantages that Digi has
it was given to him
it's just that he's produced more stuff
than any of us and as a result
he's gotten just more experience
at what is appropriate, when to stop
when to keep going and I think it's served him
quite well
there's another thing
I want to talk about
that you're not embarrassed at all
to wear your influences on your sleeve
and just copy things that you think would be cool
because I've always had a problem
with like
every time Jesse does something interesting
Digi says oh I want to do that and then you do it
and it's like
if I were to
feel like I wanted
to copy somebody
I would feel apprehensive
I would feel like it's wrong
or cheap
in some way but
I never feel like there's anything to be ashamed of
when you do it
recently you did
the podcast
by yourself where you talked about the thumbnails
and I'm like
I kind of agree but I don't want to copy him
I got over that
and I just changed them all and it is better
that video created a storm
where like everyone's out there changing their fucking thumbnails
yeah
this isn't about Digi exactly
but I remember in one of
in one of Mumki's nuzzlocks
he says like hey guys if you like my videos
and you want to do nuzzlocks like this
don't feel like
go ahead and copy me
because I've copied this from everyone else
so it's like
just do it
Mumki is even more than me
very willing to wear influences on his sleeve
and Jesse as well
Jesse I mean directly
quotes wrestlers constantly and stuff
and the way I see it
and the reason I do it that way is that
for one thing I don't think there's such thing as original ideas
like you are the product
of
what you've experienced before
no one learns how to write
who's never read a book before
the fact that you even have the idea
of a book is because you've read a book
and
your ability to write is going to be the summation
of all those other people's books
combined with yourself
and then also whatever you take from someone else
you're going to inherently make it different
by not being them
even if I just outright steal a Jesse line
and deliver it the way he can
so it's going to be different
it's going to have a different meaning when it comes out of my mouth
so that's sort of my philosophy about that
you know going off of Gibbs Point
a little bit ago
where he said it's made him more open and stuff
about influences
and that led into what you're talking about now
it's funny to me to think back
because you know how keg standard
one of the things about the character
was that he
loved anime but was embarrassed about it
it was like ashamed of that
for anyone who isn't aware that's
our old pony OC
right, right
that was very much a real thing for me
when I was in high school I wore a lot of anime shirts
and I just didn't care
because I was a silly little boy
but in college I sort of developed
thanks to the friends I hung out with a little bit
who didn't appreciate the stuff that I did
I definitely kind of repressed that stuff a little bit
you were rubbing them talking about it
that's right
wow that didn't admit to like an anime
well I think it was
I think it's a bad thing
to not be honest about the things that you like
and I've just noticed over the last couple of years
since meeting guys like you Digi
and Jesse too
and just kind of getting immersed in this stuff
that side of me is like the best guy ever
Persona who just like has all these wifey's
around him like I feel like that's
more true to the guy that I've always wanted to be
and I think it's through the influence of guys like you
that I kind of was able to
you know realize that about myself
let me say I may have said this to you
before Digi but
back in the day when I discovered you
when it was pony time you know
which it always is
not that that ever stopped
it's pony time
you know what they say even a broken clock
is pony time twice a day
so I remember like I watched a couple of your videos
and I was like this guy and I remember that
my impression was like this guy is wicked
uncool and he's wicked lame
but he's so like
he's so enthusiastic
about the things
that aren't cool about him
that it kind of circles around to being cool again
that's kind of exactly how Jesse
said he got into me
that it was obvious that you were
doing this lame stuff
you were doing this lame stuff but delivering
with so much confidence that it didn't feel that lame
yeah the confidence
is great
the fact that you're just
you never second guess yourself
or at least never in a video
you would never say
well maybe or maybe not
unless I legitimately am not sure
if the information I'm saying is true
if it's like an opinion thing
you've made your decision and then you say it
and it's like that's me
until you change your mind
the thing about there being no
guilty pleasures
I've taken into myself
and I've made it part of my life philosophy as well
it's an excellent point I think
um
well thanks for all the
and that's why on every digi video
go smash that motherfucking like button
thanks
thanks for all the gay praise everybody
but I want to say for our audience
because I was kind of
was going to have you all skip me
because I feel like the point of this is to
to pump people up who aren't as watched
and obviously everybody
but uh like what I want to say
about this is that every single one of the things
you guys have praised me for
is something that was
something I had to learn
and was all something that I you know
have taken on over the years
you know I started writing
my anime blog in 2007
and none of the praise you guys are
lavishing on me would have been true
back then except for the fact that I write
fast and that was always true
and I was a lot less consistent
but I did write fast
and try to get ideas out there as fast as possible
and I think that
that had a huge
did a lot to make all the rest of it follow
and um I've quoted this before
from shirobako there's this part
where this old guy says like you know
you have to get fast when you're young
because as you get older you lose endurance
but you you will keep gaining
skill you just won't have the endurance
to just do a whole lot of things really
fast and I really think that because
I was just young and so full of energy
I just made so much bullshit
just an endless sea of
bullshit and if you go read my blog
it's all there it's all shit
go read anything I wrote before 2011
you'll be like holy fuck
I can't believe that I listen to this guy
ever you know but
uh but that's what it took
you know it took just getting out all
that stuff and I I'm
glad that everyone because
I have all that experience and I'm so good at analyzing it
and explaining it that I can tell
that to other people and they can skip a lot
of the steps that I had to go through you know
like that speed is
kind of like the core strength there's the seed
that allowed you know it's other shit to
come for seed
which we'll be
coming out of your dick once we can finish
up this inter concession yeah I've blown my load
I'm putting it back so who's
so who's next who's next on the
hypocrite hypocrite is next on the list
oh oh what what
can one say about a man who
was both hippo and
gibbon and gibbon monkey
and crit uh we all kind
of just fell in love with you gib
back in the pony days
when you were on give and take making your
shit there and you were
there was something you know actually what was great
about uh the way me and Ben first
noticed you was that you
made these big old fucking
um compilations of like what other
guys were doing like there was all the people
doing just reacting to the current
pony episode but you went
way further than other people and did this
whole big animated thing of like
all the analysis dudes and me and
Ben lost our fucking mind this was the
first time we thought anyone gave a shit about us
when among the other people you animated the two of
us just made these little dolls of us
put us in there we were losing
our shit we were over the fucking
moon we were somebody cared about us it was
the best the the thing about
um hippo
the thing or well since we're talking about back in the day
yeah the thing about your your
pony videos is just you just you just
went way further than anyone else and you actually
had jokes and you actually did
like made original art and you had like
original jokes and comedy
and bits and stuff and you just were way more
creative about it um than
anyone else was and
um to this day
I mean you've got you've got a sense
of humor and a sense of comedic timing that
is not like anyone else and is
probably the best you're definitely I think I think
you're the best at that stuff out of any
of us I think that um
I've I've always thought that
uh like because hippo always
is is down on himself and his writing and
stuff but I genuinely think that he has among
the the funniest
and best writing slash editing
of anyone here or anyone and like
like it's hard to
put my finger on like specific
things but I just really like his videos
a lot and he's like
totally a unique voice
like yeah I've
never heard or seen
editing or delivery like
his by anyone else ever he's a totally
his own thing
you know like I I'll never forget
I think this is when I really really
started to like you stop it was I forget
which which uh pony episode it was
but you were just like uh talking about
something like and we'll be back after the break
and your arm just breaks and it's like
I like it
like it was oh yeah yeah I'll
tell you what I think after the break
I like it yeah it was
uh it was 10 out of 10 it was just
stuff like that in this pony
shit I mean you know
you've got it's great all right all right so
I love the character
of hippo as in the hippo
yeah um he is awesome
and every time he's in a video
I'm just overjoyed
to see him
he's a wonderful man
he is a wonderful man
and top 10 hippos is one of my favorite videos
of all time
yeah give your stuff
is just so unique you know you could
never mistake your content
for anyone else's and I'm sure you have your
your share of influencers
like people you've kind of pulled things from
but it's all combined in such a way
that just never
ceases to just like really like
intrigue and entertain me like every time I watch
one of your videos whether it's a give and take pony
or a hippo crit it's always
just so distinctly you
and in almost like I've been
sitting here like I don't know how do I even describe
my admiration for what you do
it's so it's like
beyond words the only thing is like
you're really great with puns
like your twitter everyone needs to follow your twitter
your twitter is a singular
a singular experience
twitter was made for you
the site can't be like sold or destroyed
because then I don't know where I'd get your puns
and you could find him at the hippo crit
right yeah the underscore
hippo crit right or is it all one word
I think it's just the hippo crit
yeah I think so remember just
it's such a it's it's cool to
see the things that you choose to make
like the first thing that you did that got
big was those like
what was it like just the
compilations like the pony compilations where you just take one
fucking who would think to do this
to take one word from like every
episode of the show and every time it's
and just link them back to back to back
and like people love them it's
I would just that's so
not something I would ever think to do
and it just I think it really shows
that's kind of like my favorite thing about hippo
is exactly that
I feel like you are almost
innately just like so
creative that it
like you always give yourself shit about like not
not writing enough
or not being a good enough writer but it's just
the ideas that make it so
unique that like you know I feel like
with with Jesse or Nate
everything's Jesse does have
some videos that are that are more just like
I turned on the camera and some weird shit came out
but like with Jesse and Nate everything
has to be this very formulated perfected
production and with you it's just like the first
thing that came to your mind was already a good
idea you know and
there's so many like give and take videos
that I enjoy just as much as the hypocrite
videos where it's just like
you went outside with a camera
with your brother and like
filmed you like running around in the grass
and then like did three layers
of green screen of like weird shit happening
and in every single one of them
I'm just like this is this is great
this is all they want this is this is all
it needs to be this is all the youtube
video needs to be for you remind me of
Gib as a crater you remind me of here
Amaru from from Bakuman
who's like this this totally
bizarre guy who just decided
to start doing manga and then it was just
like the best at it and like
he makes orders 11 hates himself
and he's like he hates himself and he hates
it but he's doing it to get that sweet Ico
puss so you know keep on your stuff
is so deliciously
weird like yeah when
when did you post a video I know what
it's gonna be he's gonna talk about some anime
he might go pretty in-depth it might
approach y'all at some point
when fuckin when when Nate post a video
it's like okay he's gonna make some jokes
he's gonna have some yucks and some fucks and some
yeah yeah so but but then
when I see like a new hypocrite video
I'm like I don't know what the fuck
kind of weird ass shit's gonna be
like like your your your recent
Mario RPG
video your fucking head was just sticking
out of the ether
for no fucking reason
it's like most people would like stand
in front of a green screen or like have
it off the side and your fucking head is
just like coming out of like a green screen
fucking vagina in the middle of the screen
like how you going and then you didn't even
mention it you didn't even like draw
it wasn't addressed the whole video was
like that I love that too
because hippos the best at like creative
solutions because
I mean that is a great solution to the
problem of the green creating solutions where
no problem exists yeah the
grpj
well the grpj in the beginning
I already thought it was a genius idea because
all he did was just like lay a green
screen over a couch just on a fucking
pile yeah it's like a pile and just play
video footage of it so it's like you would
think when people think green screen
they think you know it's it's a
green it's in the background you're standing
in front of it like a teleprompter you know
you're pointing stuff out but no hippos just
in his house on a couch
and there just happens to be a green screen
that's just playing the game it's
not even like lit correctly
or anything you know has like invented
and mastered a new form of
green screen martial arts
and and but the the reason the new
one happens is because like because
my brother Victor was watching it he was complaining
that hippos was sitting right
in the middle of the green screen so you couldn't
really make out a lot of the footage in the
Kingdom Hearts video and I brought this up
and it was like I'll find a way to do it differently
and so now he suddenly is
like just a face in a morph suit
he's the fucking Zordon
yeah he's just Zordon
yes that's it that's it
he's like it's a genius solution
it's not the same as talking about your animation work
which is just as fantastic oh shit
the spiders the fucking spiders
and there's a fish oh my
god a fish at my door
they're both really
great and it's a shame that
I know they must be really time intensive to make
because I wish
I could see more of those
you know
go ahead game
what?
I thought you were gonna say something I was gonna say
I've noticed in both of the
two big animation things you've done
oh okay there was actually
tallest man, fish at my door
and spiders
I always really love your use of
like I don't there's not much background
noise but then the sound effects are really
distinct I've loved your use of sound effects
in your animations
are they all fully
effects like did you just record them yourself
there's there's a quite
a few that I recorded myself
cool I got most of them from
freesound.org
yeah but um
yeah I mean the sound
I'm gonna give you a freesound.org
as them in the circle Jerk and I'm saying
oh
I am really appreciated
appreciated this is highly
appreciated this is highly specific
but there's one shot that really impressed
me in it's called spiders are people
too is that what it's called yeah yeah
in spiders are people too there's a shot
from the ground looking up a power
line and the power the power pole
line just like like
bends and sways
before like the power lines get pulled
taught and then snap and the
perspective and the motion on that
pole looked fantastic
there's a lot of great
the overhead shot of the spider
going into the house and the one where
it like when it strings itself up and it
just kind of starts turning and turning
back because it can't really control its momentum
there's a lot of adorable shit in
that and
just in everything hippo does
it's all about timing it's all about
perfect comedic timing and just hitting
you with the most left field
thing and and the fact
that I think more
so than anybody else hippo is
willing to completely sacrifice
everything for a joke where
where hippo will have a video where he's like
explaining a point and then just
gets bored of explaining a point
and would rather make a joke instead
and just that point is just gone it's just
if you think about it that kind of explains
his life in general he sacrificed
everything to be a fucking
joke
it's just I mean it's
so it's such a like subversive way
of doing it where if you watch like
a John Tron video you know like
obviously hippo comes from that camp
of like video makers where you talk about a game
and there's jokes but those people there's
always this very clear sense of like
there's the intro joke you talk about the game
little you make a joke you show a little scene
that's funny haha whoa that scene's funny
you make a joke you say a little analytical
point you make a joke hippo will like
just wind his way through all of
those he doesn't feel the need to talk about
every aspect of the game sometimes
he makes a real
analytical point you know which is something
John Tron never did you know he just
goofy funny man about video games but
even or like a you know AVGN
it's very much like joke analysis
joke analysis hippo will just
say something really interesting
some point he obviously wanted to make
that's the most interesting thing about the game
it's not encompassing the whole game because
proving whether the game is good or not is
not really what the video is about
it's about just here's an excuse to talk about this
game you know he it doesn't
feel like I'm getting this comprehensive
Mathematosis review
but it's also not just a joke it's like
here's this game I love here's
the thing I love about it and
it's got graphics
what's the line in a
what's the line in the the coyote versus
cheap dog one where you said like
it's got visuals or something like
that yeah something like that
I forgot exactly but
I just I just couldn't think of like
like usually you say
it's got this and that and this yeah I
can think of it I laughed so hard at that because it's like
anyone else would be like you know it's got
this really unique visual style blah
blah blah and I hate that because it's like
there they think that because they're doing
a review they have to at least touch
on every point even though they have nothing actually
to say about the visuals they just like
and also it's got great visuals
I'm like yeah I can see I don't care but you
you're just like yeah I don't it's got
a graphic you know
whatever yeah
yeah
I for one am deeply invested
in the character arc of hippo
and want to see I want to see if he ever gets
his goddamn YouTube channel up and running
because I always assume that that's what he's working
towards but they keep getting shut down by
the hippo crit he's like no that's not good enough
we gotta you know
he's been like a you know the
the lists he's been doing
that's sort of his I'm allowing him to put
them on my channel for now
for like exposure
he does want to have his own
you're paying him an exposure
oh no
the hippo crit organization has been exposed
he doesn't know what the fuck's going on
he doesn't have a union
that poor creature
I do let him live with me though
let's put a roof over his head
I paid cult corona exposure in a backfire
because everyone likes him more than me now
yeah that's true that's for sure
which I mean anyone got any closing things
to say about hippo crit or shall we
I think it's amazing that so many of us
have like this other alter ego
character that we let live with us
you know there's hippos got the hippo
Jesse's got cult corona, Nate's got action
draft, I've got Ben and DeVue
with him
oh my god
yeah it's true
DeVue is kind of a fiction character
he's not here right now
I rest my case
holy shit
I was just digi in a green screen
suit the whole time
exactly
alright give we love you buddy
let's move on to Jess
Jess I don't like anything about
let's talk about cult corona
he's my favorite character on the internet
he's the cutest and the strongest
and I just hope
that he counted that demon in the furnace room
perfect
I don't disagree with that at all either
yeah right
here's something serious about Jesse
your work ethic
is like a truck
that I fuck
it's real
it's great
just looking at the work that went into
putting aside even all the videos before
horseshoe finale
that is the seminal work of Jesse's
career thus far
a year of fucking work
not to mention the fucking years that went into sculpting
the narrative for the payoff
it's incredible
you can't even describe it to people who haven't seen it
it was all for nothing
because it can't be described to people
yeah that's the worst thing about it
you'll see that
that's the thing in Jesse this is something that I
think that you and I share
is that we are both completely retarded
and we make the things that we like
and we don't think
nearly enough about things that will
be popular
or whatever I mean maybe I'm selling you short
but I certainly feel that way
I do think about what will be popular but it just makes me angry
it makes me want to progress back into what I want
well Jesse
it might be true that the horseshoe finale
is a niche work that will never
find a mainstream audience
but to the people that it
was relevant to
it was deeply meaningful and impactful
and I admire
that a lot
these people that are along
for the ride with me
I'm going to show them something
yeah right well Jesse I think that
that whole plight of the artist's art
about you Jesse is the fact that you've taken
like this
you're just like yourself
like the way you interact with your fans
and stuff like if anybody else tried
to do it it would just blow up in their faces
but you've like sculpted your personality
and the way you present yourself
that your fans love getting shit on by you
essentially so you can do whatever the fuck you want
they've been well trained
yeah
I admire that a lot because I always
have to like try and think of how I'm
going to appease the people who follow my stuff
to a degree like I got to balance
the entire comment section is reek
and I'm fucking
I'm Ramsay Bolton
they know their place
it really is great
and that you know
you can make the content you do and actually
make pretty decent money
yeah that's what I was going to say I was time
even though you're a niche creator
you make so much more money
than me for example and that's why
is because you deeply impact
the people that are along for the ride with you
you have something to say
and create your own cult following
and they're looking at it for all it's work
and it's fantastic
and I understand
I completely understand why
your audience is so deeply invested
in you
yeah
I was going to say
I'm very impressed that
despite living in like a really dirty
poopy spider
spider infested basement
you still managed to attract
many winches from all over the place
it's very sexy with you
it's very cool
at present Jesse is the most
well laid of the whole PCP
yeah that makes me mad
I'm mad about that
it's a bit of a burden I'll be honest
I got plans baby
I'm cooking up some shit
I don't know what that means at all
I've got a witch's brew brewing in the other room
right now
we pour it like a little potion
and a woman's going to come out
like what the fuck are you working on over there
it's definitely true that
it's going to vape
is that what you guys are doing
are you practicing your vape food until you can produce
the white food out of the vape
it's definitely true that
like any time more than two days goes by
without a video from me it's probably because
I'm on some romantic sojourn
yeah
that's not an exaggeration
but literally I'll be like
how come I haven't heard from Jesse in like two days
and it's always because there's some girl at his house
you know
I said this about
Digi but it's also very true of
Jesse in different ways
and it's that I am
I've always liked
really
forceful guys
because I was a pretty timid guy growing up
and I'm not really that way anymore
but I really respect
your approach to life
even if we disagree on a lot of stuff
how you'll just you know scream
and cry and you know
pee yourself
about things that set you off even to the slightest degree
it's just a lack of
you know it's a double edged sort of like
a lack of compromise comes with shit
you know being tough a lot of the time
but it's just so cool
Jesse's uncompromising nature
is definitely remarkable
and my
uncompromising emotional instability
is an inspiration to all
like just
really like the story about
you just punching the shit out of that kid in the movie theater
like that's like the coolest thing
I've told everyone I know that story
like it's
and everyone comes away like with
like yeah awesome what a cool guy
I still haven't told
the Halloween story from this here at
Cody's butt chugger ball
oh shit
let's just say
I turned it into a butt chugger brawl
I know this one
I won't reveal it just yet
it was a ballroom blitz for sure
I've been influenced a lot
by your videos that you've made
at first I didn't like the idea
that you knew that you were influencing
people
it was an aversion to it
like I don't want this guy to tell me the truth
but
it was true like you were really cool
and I liked it and I tried doing stuff
and
I think my ultimate downfall
no one wants to hear the truth
yeah I feel like that's literally
there's people like clicking on Jesse's videos
and saying I don't want this guy to tell me the truth
it's really how I think
a lot of people feel but
I got over it because I'm cool
it's tough for some people to swallow that red pill
because
even though you're very abrasive
a lot of the time you're really correct
on a lot of things
even if you're not
I just love your
it's a combination
of your confidence
and
your emotional connection
to things like you embrace your emotional
ness
but you're also
I don't know
you're genuine enthusiasm
about things
is an inspiration to me
who struggles to feel anything at all
I actually
I feel exactly what Ben's saying
I've been so
inspired by that first time
we all met at BronyCon
I've told the story before that Jesse was
saying how he cried on the plane
thinking about Kermit the Frog
because for me it was such a like
man when was the last time I just
cried about a thing
being so good
you know and so
I've kind of taught myself more after hearing
about that to
when I see something that legitimately
makes me feel something to try and embrace
that feeling as much as possible
and try to really feel it and
convey that feeling
I would consider myself
a pretty lazy person
my whole life
up until a few years ago
when I found something that I actually
it's kind of a cheat
because I just enjoy making videos
so I didn't even really earn like the
hard work that I'm willing to put into it
but I mean the whole reason
that I continued doing stuff was because
of seeing I mean we saw that like
Digi, me and Ben saw that Digi was successful
doing this stuff
but even more so like the content I wanted
to make was stuff like Jesse's content
and it's been a big
inspiration to the kind of stuff
that I've been trying to make specifically
the way that you are able to flip
and like the best comedies
can do this between hilarious
and extremely heartfelt like the other guys
were saying like the fucking
like the Hulk Hogan nigger video
just like ah fucking
I said nigger you know what
and then it just turns into this whole world
fucking brother nigger
it's just this whole thing
but like the way that it all
it's like a swirling mass of chaos
and then it all spirals into one point
and then you get this like focused thing
that it was all leading up to
like that's the sort of thing that I have always tried to emulate
the delicate balance
the delicate balance of comedy
and pathos
and is something that I value
a lot in art
I think that's important
it's kind of my favorite thing
and the musical stuff
that you've put into your videos
that's like my favorite thing to do
let's talk about Jesse's raps
Jesse
I think your raps might be
some of your my favorite content that you make
and you know I like a lot of your stuff
so that's really saying something
your fucking lyrics
are sometimes
genius I'll just there
I said it
sometimes your lyrics are
the dandy rap to this day
is something that
I find inspiring
that a friend of mine could make
and makes me think that maybe I could do something like that too
I mean when I was making my keg standard
rap thing or it was a big mac rap
which turned out it wasn't great or anything
but I was inspired by that
because I thought it was so fucking good
I want to make things like that
he packs so many
he packs so many bright ideas into his thought balloons
that his metaphorical spark lights the room
when he expresses himself
he impresses you well then he don't need help
so why the fuck should you
is that a Jesse lyric
that's get action
um
I don't even know where to start
and I'm not gonna go into as much detail as I could
because we'd be here all day
Jesse
is my I'm gonna say
outright my favorite
artist of all time
and also
probably my best friend
so
I'm coming from a place of extreme bias
that there's
nothing that I've ever connected
with more than Jesse's stuff
and I mean it's kind of the basis
of all of this we formed as the horseshoe crew
you know we formed around
because he was the horseshoe king
we were all like we kind of bonded over
mutual respect for Jesse's
work it's I mean me and Jesse were already friends
and then we saw these other people and like to me
it was like the mark of someone being cool
was that they appreciated Jesse's stuff
the mark of the horseshoe appeared on their body
and they knew it was time
it's like the brand of sacrifice in berserk
you knew that you were fucked once that shit
I was thinking more like the Tanak
the Tanak and the ESD
you know the we have like
each of us has part of the horseshoe crew on our ass
so isn't this just actually what cutie marks were
isn't this the cutie mark chronicle
oh yeah oh my god
um oh my
yeah wait never mind I was going to say
oh my god tenacious D was cutie marks
and I remembered that that's been pointed out a thousand times
back in the Brody days anyway
um yeah like
for me it was my sonic rain boom
that gave everyone here their cutie marks
oh my god
like Jesse represents
everything that I
especially that I was trying to do
before you know I'm like a more
cleaned up presentable version
you know like my stuff is very
it's it's it's very
like accessible and
and digestible
and Jesse's isn't but
the stuff he expresses is all stuff
that I'm like man if only
I could do if I could do if I
had his particular set of talents this is
exactly what I'd want to say you know
everything Jesse says is something that I'm like
why didn't I say that why couldn't I be the one
to do that video you know and
there's so much I've taken
from him in terms of like
god everything everything to do with my
vlogging is you know is
because of Jesse essentially
you know with few exceptions of like little
things I've taken from other people
my rapping
heavily inspired by Jesse a lot of it is
just seeing him as
one of the only people I see is better than me
you know in like a general sense
like Nate's a better editor than me
Hippo's a better you know comedian
and you know Ben's obviously a vastly better
artist but like when I
think of myself in terms of like
my net
quality like
the only like Jesse's one of the only people
who I'm like I can definitively
say he has a better body of work
than me you know like I get
more value out of watching all of
his content that I would out of watching all of my own
content and so I
see it as like I have to get
that good I have to one day
be able to say I've made as many
good videos as Jesse or I've made as many good
raps as Jesse and that day will never
come because he's still making shit
you know he'd have to die for me to be able to
pass him you know
because I keep getting better but he also
keeps getting better where you know
and we have
now we also we influence one
another you know where a lot
of the way that we will put raps
together it kind of sequences into
each other you know we make reference to each other
we're
I can't like you can't separate
our artistic careers at this point
I mean you could but like
for the future but like if you looked at the
individual work we're doing so much of it is
connected I mean now we're doing like the plebe and
the weave which is like you know this
amalgam of things me and Jesse
are interested in and how our chemistry
works you know it's going to be interesting
when all the people who who just know about
you did you realize later on
how much of an influence Jesse was and then
go back and look at all his shit and are like oh
my god this is madness
yeah I mean in a good way obviously
like all the positive influence
you know I had it was a very
gratifying experience at
radcon because of the fact that you know
we've all hung out twice before
at brony con in the past you know we all
met at the brony con in
14 and 15 we all met
and you know we got we all got the hang
out and it was it was it was a very gratifying
experience to realize yeah everyone's exactly
as cool as I thought they were you know if not
cool yeah and it was like wow
these guys really are cool guys I really do want
to hang out with them I really do want to be
friends with this group of people and to make
this whole you know everyone you know
move into one place kind of thing happen
but like it was at radcon where it was
especially that we just
got to actually hang out and me and Jesse
had never really gotten to just hang out
before after all these years of doing podcasts
together and talking all the time and stuff
and then like when me and Jesse
hung out I was like yeah I'm
exactly as good a friend with Jesse
in person as I am online you know it there
was no awkwardness about
hanging out with Jesse you know
when we when we were like
going to cook out or something together
and it's like this this feels like if we
if we did live in the same place we'd
hang out all the time and I was like
I got to get Jesse down here god damn
all my other friends all my offline friends
are gone I don't they've all abandoned
me so I need Jesse
to be my best friend
I'm just a left bro
I've got Ben and he's pretty
pretty good but I
feel like I can step up one
I know I'm an adequate digi
it's fun
uh yeah
Ben is the rebound for digi
no no
I'm a lifting buddy
we're lifting buddies
yeah I mean we hang out
a lot more than just to lift but
I got a
one quantifiable thing
that I like about you Jesse
is I really like your voice
and I love how many
cool voices you can do
some of them sound kind of similar they're always
they're always great
what do you mean they all sound similar
yeah we're totally different
is that Raphael
and oh no fuck is that Donny
and Colt are going back and forth
I can't even
the more you bring up
it's not that they sound too different
similar it's just that
you can go
from one to the other really smoothly
well I happen to like very much
how Jesse's characters all kind
of sound like the exact same guy
I enjoy that
well it's sort of like
the voices like Colt Corona
and Donatello exist on the same octave
but there's like a little bit more
of like an oscillation between them
I don't know what the word oscillation means
but I think
you just throwing some rapey vibes
for Donny and basically you got it
I can't even like I'm scared
to open the Pandora's box of saying
like specific things because like
there's so many little like just the fact
that Jesse invents memes that I will
then use forever until
chicken and tea
dude we all like walk around screaming
that now like like me and DeVu
like every time I go in the kitchen because DeVu only eats
chicken like he just fries himself
chicken every day and I come in he drinks tea as well
yeah yeah he eats chicken and tea
every day and I always come in and I go chicken
and tea
and I'm probably the guy who complains about
memes the most in the world but I'm also
a meme machine
when you make your own memes
it's a totally different thing
it's not the same as regurgitating other memes
which we all do from you
we have inside jokes and we have Twitter accounts
doesn't mean we're making memes
Endless Jess is an inside joke
the one group that matters
a big one for me is the Baba Duke stuff
where it's just like Jesse
made this bleach review like
two years ago where he just
decided to call all of the
all of the bad guys
Baba Dukes like anything that's like a
there's Baba Dukes and Skelly Man and Spooky Dukes
and then he just kept saying it
and eventually now in my mind
scary things are just called
Baba Dukes like that's just how it is
that's the world I lived in
that was a fascinating thing for me
I gotta come clean I had no fucking idea
what a Baba Duke was for like a year and a half
and I pretended that I did
I pretended that I understood what the fuck
everyone was talking about
it took me until like Jesse talked
he watched like the um
fuck what was it?
I thought it was Crampus
Crampus
I think Jesse like described what a Baba Duke was
like he talked about it at some point
and then I was like oh okay I can now pretend
that I always knew what this was
I don't understand the confusion
there's a movie called Baba Duke
and it's about a scary ghost
I didn't know that
and I chose not to investigate
I'm just saying like Jesse
will do that thing where he brings up something
obscure and you know
a lot of the time it'll just
seem like something he made up
a lot and then to learn that it's
you know it was based on something else
ironically though in the movie Baba Duke
the
Baba Duke is really more of a dookie spook
than a Baba Duke
what do you know?
Baba Duke's spook is one of my favorite Jesse characters
incidentally
yeah my brother really likes that
Baba Duke's
Baba Duke's spook is
he's like the lowest possible octave
of the cold corona
he's my favorite guy
and in my head
he also lives
Jesse's always saying how all the characters
exist and have their own lives inside his head
I feel like I somehow
I adopted Baba Duke's spook from Jesse
and he is a part of me now
he lives
Baba Duke lives today
I'm sure if Davoo were here
he'd talk about how the
environment of your basement is such a rich character
in of itself
it's filled with all these kooky characters
and all these things that have taken place there
and that is one pretty
awesome consequence of doing all your
filming in a space like that
I will just also say that Jesse
is prolific as shit
and if you follow all his channels
new Jesse content is coming out all the
fucking time
it is insane
and you know what
here's one last thing I have to say about it
I remember when Ben got me into
in like 2013 I didn't believe him that it was good
I watched it and found that I
did enjoy it very much and then
he also was the one who showed me all of you guys
which consequently is kind of what got me into
YouTube in the first place Ben just like
talking about like these pony review guys
that's when I really got into it
and I remember so
clearly Ben saying like dude
you've got to check out this fucking like crystal empire
review by this guy
like the footwear man it's fucking
insane you won't know what the fuck is happening
go watch it and I did
and I remember I remember
it was fucking yesterday
crawling out of that fucking rarity fun house
like the fucking nightmare from my darkest dreams
and like
I think
that was the moment I realized like holy shit
these videos don't have to be a bunch of
bullshit like this guy didgy bros doing
fuck that guy
this guy knows what's up
it was a paradigm shift
I really liked that video I did discover it
before I really got into the whole footwear
and horseshoes
I think that was my entry point to the footwear universe
yeah I want to throw in
I found it isolated I want to throw in one more
specific thing just because this is something that Jesse
also says it's his favorite thing about himself
and I also really appreciate it it's the
physicality of the videos
because in that
in that cold corona video and this is another one
that like I took as an influence and I've like trained
myself because I was afraid to do this before
that
Jesse comes out of that tent
downs a whole bottle of corona
in one go
he drinks an entire bottle of corona and then
just smashes it on the floor
he in real life did that
it's not a sound effect he threw the bottle on the ground
and it smashes the fucking pieces
I've sampled it in a song before
and like
that level of just willingness
to break shit and like make a mess
and you know and make videos
that you have to clean up after yourself afterwards
you know Jesse throws himself
through a table in one video
he you know just breaks a table
by jumping on it
you know several times actually
I think in the
cool cat one there's a part where you like
fall through something
he would knock bottles of beer all over the place
you know constantly dropping and breaking stuff
and like I was always
afraid to do something like that to like damage
something and then
like the plebe in the weeb finale
of episode 3 would not have happened
if not for that influence you know
the willingness to like say
let's fucking destroy the set
and that's all my stuff
that's getting thrown around there
and I wanted to go so much farther with that
but I was stopped
it felt a little strange
I wanted to put a sword through the fucking wall
I wanted to knock those walls down
I wanted to put like
I wanted to jump through them
have like an outline like a loony tube
going through the wall
the plan was that the most over the top thing
would be lighting a poster on fire
and that would have felt pretty extreme
but the fucking thing wouldn't light
but I like
even then like I mean fucking wine
got on everything and I was like
this is like my actual collection
that we've just soaked in all the shit
and I was like but it was all worth it
because having those things
is not nearly worth as much
as having made that video
that was the last ending
so yeah
I really admire that willingness to go all out
and just break something
including yourself
for the sake of a joke
my upraising was very much
to like never fuck up shit
never break anything, never do anything bad
and see guys like Jesse
or like Red Letter Media
who just like trash shit
absolutely love it
and that's why I would really love
Jesse's life, I want to study
what led him to be this man
who would you know do this
there's any element
of Jesse's videos you don't understand
watch like three wrestling promos
and it all makes sense
every single thing is
kfabe until Jesse's videos
and then I read the wiki article and started digging into him
like I get so much more of Jesse's
it's all just a combination
of like professional wrestling
deep-seated childhood
trauma
and a predilection towards
violence
those are the ingredients for the perfect little me
yeah
another thing to give you credit for
HIPPO's been trying to say something
I was going to say that there's a difference between
the Red Letter Media people
and what Jesse does
because Red Letter Media they make
props that they can destroy
and Jesse fucks up his actual living space
and he doesn't always clean it up
like if he smashes a bottle
it's just there for like weeks
and it's cool
there's fucking glass and you walk around without my shoes
and socks and a year later it goes way deep
in your foot
a huge part of the horse shoe finale
behind the scenes was that Jesse
he had ruined his whole room
for the sake of it and he couldn't clean it up
until it was done so for six months
he lived in like just absolute
squalor
remember that shot from rarities in main hatton
where he puts on the fedora, lies back in his trash
and just basks in it
and just loves the life he's living
I love that shot
I could never do stuff like that
just the amount of stuff Jesse's gotten me into
the panel cast
I'm now reading comics
wrestling podcasts
I mean fucking broken mat
you've all developed kind of an interest in wrestling now
yeah broken mat
I've never watched any wrestling my whole life
until Jesse's stuff
I opened when he started the wrestling podcast
that like every little thing I hadn't understood
about Jesse's videos all made sense
as soon as I learned what wrestling was
and how it works and how the people act
and I was like oh
that's why he does it that way
you know and uh yeah
and now wrestling is cool to me
and broken mat saga
it's like my favorite thing that's happened all year
yeah
I wonder if like
if you do like another top 10
videos of the year
the whole broken mat saga would go on
maybe
the last one was particularly analysis videos
but uh maybe
uh yeah
that's enough for Jesse
well guys
goofy
get out of here
that's all I got to say
yeah that's tough
alright well now it's your turn
yeah next is me
wait wait what are we doing
I just came back what are we doing
I'll say something about Nate
Nate
of all of us
you are the most not fat
that's very true
and that
and it pains me to say because it's such
an embittered
jealousy an envy deep inside me
you are a handsome boy
but I do take a lot of
inspiration in the fact that Nate actually
truly takes care of himself
and looks like a human
I think it's actually
a huge influence on the whole rest of the group
because I don't think
if we were a group of all
fat, slubby guys none of us would try to
change like we'd all see it as
well everyone else in the crew is but because
Nate is there said it like the first time
I met him I was like fuck why am I not
like you know
think about it like I mean we all do the same job
we're all YouTubers right
so if Nate who by the way
currently in school
and holding a full time job
and making videos
is still able to find time
to work out his body
what'd you say
it's elected president he's got it all figured out
I'll write him the best guy ever
for president fuck yeah
he's like the Paul McCartney
of the group oh yes that's my favorite guy
yes the proactive one the one
that tries to get all the others to be more
and I'm the John Lennon who beats his wife
yeah
Nate I
like I know we haven't even started
talking about your actual creative output but like
as a person I mean
okay PCP is entirely Nate's idea
and his child and he built it
and Nate has the most like
Nate is the most adult
person out of us he is the one
who when all of us are fucking crying
about I don't want to I don't know how to
set up a hotel
oh yeah
like you know like Brody Cod's coming in
Nate's like alright guys we gotta get a hotel
we're like I don't know how to do that
you fucking call them
you pick up a phone and you dial seven buttons
and you're done he sent the whole thing up didn't he
he's done it every time
every time anything happens we all just
defer to Nate because he's allowed us
to become even more infantilized
because I like how we all
have such a specialized role that
if one of us were gone it would all fall
apart immediately it's like
it's like the community roles like one leaves
and everything goes to shit you know
it's a delicate balance yeah
Nate organizes things keeps things in check
he's the only one who actually gets people
like on the fucking show every
week you know sets the
times gives a shit
gets the video I mean I'm the one who edits
all the fucking things and uploads them but
Nate made the channel in the first place and cared
enough when all of us were like yeah it's
no one's gonna watch our podcast and Nate's
like well I want to do a thing
you know we've had the idea let's follow
through yeah good follow through
I mean who else would actually
spend six months editing a video
and not give up on it other than
Jesse I guess yeah
because for me
if I work on one project for more than a month it's
fucking dead it's not gonna be finished
I don't know how you do it
like there are a lot of things you do in your videos
I don't even know how he does that in Vegas
yeah there's this word that starts with an
A coming to my mind I just don't know
I can't read it I can't see it
one thing that I
that I like
I'm particularly impressed
with you by
is that you've learned basically
all of your stuff since you started
the pony stuff like all of
all of your skill has nothing to do with any
training you just never touched
never edited a video before
T-Bab
let's be perfectly clear
everyone in our audience probably agrees
that Nate has the flashiest editing
out of all of us and
Nate has been making
and editing videos for the
least time of everyone in this group
and he taught himself all of that
all of us are self-taught but Nate's doing
the best editing and he's been doing it
the least time keep that in mind everybody
that's true that's true
and he has like the most outside
responsibility
yeah while doing everything else in the world
I watched
the potty cast live
when it starts off and you're like
you read the chapter name and then the screen
bulges out and explodes
and it says live
and I got so fucking hyped
because I went how did you do that
I don't know I don't know how to make the screen
bulge and explode you know I could
probably think of a thousand uses for that
but I have no idea how you did it
um
researching effects
just yelled so hard that it actually
exploded
I do yell a lot
speaking of yelling
I do like the fact that
you have a very like
powerful voice
in that you can do all that sort of stuff
you've got a great singing voice as well
and your voice acting is very good
I remember watching the Gurren Lagann video
and just the way like some of the lines
were delivered like which is
perfectly done
like um
responsibility
you don't love it enough
like the reverb you put on it just like
it's like perfectly punctuates that statement
it makes it so much more powerful
in all your videos
in all your content
you commit fully
to every joke
every line you deliver
you just completely follow through
with it as far as possible
um
I'm also alright
so my greatest
praise of you Nate is also going to be my greatest
criticism
the best thing
the best things you've ever done
are they have like what I was saying with Jesse
that blend
of comedy and pathos
the character
of best guy ever
is so steeped in that
deliciously
but there hasn't been enough
of it
and I want
to experience
the full fucking best guy ever
story because I know I have insider information
about stuff
and I want it realized so much
just so you know folks
Ben helped me film
not one but two
scenes that are for upcoming videos
like over a year ago now
like two years not just scenes
like whole fucking
things like we spent whole we spent
like entire days filming
yep
and I want those videos
it's coming
I'm sorry I'm sorry
Daveau would say that you are
Daveau has repeatedly described you as the best
hype man on YouTube
that you are more capable of
instantly and intensely
generating hype for a thing
I mean very true
and then your face freezes and the whole universe
shows up on screen
I was like I'm in for a fucking trip
that looked amazing
because honestly when you started
best guy ever
I know Nate can talk really well
I've watched all of the
t-bap stuff but
it's been Ben who's been doing a lot of the
visuals so I had no idea
how your videos were going to look
I knew you were going to say a bunch of great shit
but I had no idea how they were going to look
and I was like oh my god
what where has this been
let's just say I had a monkey
off my back at long last
what fuck
and once again that's a technique I
don't know how to do I can kind of imagine
how it would happen
the level of effort that would go into
what I'm thinking you had to do makes
my stomach churn and makes me want to die
I could probably like
find like tutorials on how to do
the sort of things you do I would just never
I would always try to
look for a shortcut first
because I don't want to have to do all that work
all the moving parts and transitions all happening
together and at the same time
in like an intricate web
of stuff
shit going on in the screen
when his face I don't know how many different things are happening
when you say it's going to log in time
and your face goes ah and the
title comes out and the galaxy is happening
I freeze the frame
so I pause the video I had to
then mask out the eyes because
two independently animated swirls appear
behind each eye the universe has
to fade in the words have to appear
in time with the music in the background
all these things are happening just for that one
and it has to come out of your mouth
and I had to animate it and mask it
properly so it's coming out
and then you have 20 more minutes
to go after that
let's make that line
that word clear animated
that is an animation that's
happening there you know
yeah in very impressive visual stuff
I wish it came out twice as frequently
or three times or four
times as frequently
and it's not even just that the editing is good
is that you spent so long
writing and researching and
with your new with your ghost in the show video
you've been researching so much to get it
absolutely perfect it's true
it's like you really go
like
you make it worth the time I think
there's nothing's worth
the amount of time it takes
I mean it's a really good
video like nobody could
make a video that good
I would challenge anyone
in the world to make
as about the topic
that the Gurren Lagann one was about to do any
better and nobody
else had their life
like defined by Gurren Lagann
the way I mean actually there's a lot of guys
out there and girls you know everybody
who loved Gurren Lagann but
you know it's a particular
it's close to your heart
plus like my particular love of like sci-fi stuff
like that's like
kind of the main thing it's like even more important
like even the video I say like yeah like
comment is like my favorite character ever
and yet he's not even my favorite
thing about Gurren Lagann you know it's like
I mean I'm just gonna say I think
Gurren Lagann part one
is one of the greatest
YouTube videos ever made
both the concept
and the execution of the concept
are perfect
it's the best possible idea
because it's I mean
I assume that on some level it's
based on the meme
of the four guys watching
Gurren Lagann right like
that's not a Gurren Lagann
specific meme
it was popularized partly with Gurren Lagann
you know that probably
was part of the thought process
right it's something it's something that's
kind of like you took something that's kind
of tied to the series already but then
totally made it your own and then
executed it so fucking
like because when I watched that I was like
okay this had to be a bunch of individual
shots on a green screen
and there's so many photos
and they're all taken perfectly
like they're all good photos but your
poses and your emotions
like it's it's you know it's acting
you have to show those feelings I can't
do that I would probably was taken
more than once to get it
yeah well here's a little insider info
the way I did that was I actually
I just filmed myself and then just did
a bunch of poses and freeze frame
on the appropriate probably
I was easy to get a whole bunch yeah
but like I mean I say easy but it
took me like two fucking days yeah
and I literally
could not do
that like because I can't emote that well
I can't I can't act on screen
and you it was hard I thought
that my faces were like ridiculous
looking but actually they were like more subdued
than I expected them to look that's how acting
is you have to like really over exert
it because the human face doesn't actually
go that crazy you know but
like when I was
watching it and the other thing is that
it had to be you because
you start this video off
making yourself you did all this stuff
like costuming to make yourself look shitty
and then reveal yourself
to be this like this
awesome cool Adonis in this skin
tight fucking
girl in the gun shirt you know screaming and holding
drills and wearing sunglasses and it's like this
weird trick that you pull on the audience
to make us think that you're some gross nerd
you know I showed
when that video first came out I showed it to my
my friend ghost lightning and he was like
you know I started this off I thought it was going to be
a little shit and by the end it was the greatest
thing ever you know and I was like that's exactly
what he was going for like
yeah it's perfectly
done you really
is the best guy
yeah
you did it you say that shit to me you're getting banned
we're just letting you know
that was to the commenters
I think you were being completely serious
no it was to you guys you're getting fucking banned
from the mpcp
anybody else want to suck Nate's dick more
he really is the
procrastinators podcast
you know
I feel that the procrastinators podcast
is a fitting name for something that
I mean that mage came up with actually
did she?
she was the one who changed the name of the other track
when we were on Skype she changed it to the
procrastinators like years ago
what was that like two years ago
we were I forgot that the reason we named it
that is just that the chat was already called
that
I totally forgot about that
we would change the name all the time
I remember
and then one time we changed it to the
procrastinators and then later when we were
deciding on like a nonpony
group name we just decided on that
because it was there but it feels particularly
apt to me because I was very guilty
of that it's funny
it's entirely true that like all my video stuff
started with the pony stuff
just you know fucking doing whatever
but um
like up to that point I felt pretty
down on myself as a person
because I mean at this point in my life I'm like living at home
had failed to get my degree
while all my friends had
and in fact I should be getting it
next month is when I'll be finally
finishing my fucking school it's done guys
it's fucking gonna be done
I can't believe it
I'm so I'm proud of you Nate
I'm very happy
I'm glad but it's funny that this whole
praising thing
I hate all
I hate myself and I see all my
I see all the huge problems I did
I'm just gonna pretend that you guys represented me
accurately and fully
oh fuck off we did
eat a dick you bastard
okay let's move on
we could follow this up with the airing of grievance
no let's record that
and then never release it
because we will all
not be speaking to each other anymore
the procrastinators will end
it'll be the last episode
the big last episode years from now
when we all hate each other we're all sick
we're like let's do it I'm done with PCP
we're gonna end it with a big finale
of everything we hate about each other
the last thing ever released
in life
when I wasn't speaking to anyone
for two months over the
summer I came up with
Jesse's like
five way revenge
and I haven't enacted it yet
yet?
but it is a real plan
and I have sections
for each of you within it
and I just
I had a change of heart and you were all spared
from it at the last minute
but it still exists in a vault somewhere
and I don't want it to
like Batman has his contingency plan for the Justice League
exactly
we ever step out of line
I have no doubt that it actually is real
I had the perfect
contingency vengeance for each
and every one of you
I want to see it so bad
I only pray Jesse that you had the foresight
to prepare one for yourself
that was the final part
of the revenge
I was like the guy in 7
like the last part of it is
okay let's move on
to the count of Monte Cristo
like you come back after 7 years
after we let you take the fall for something we all did
and then you have to get revenge on all of us
and like fuck all our girlfriends
and daughters and shit
we can only hope
for a future that bright
okay let's move on to our final guy here
Tom Oliver
yeah
Brony Curious my friend
I haven't heard that name in years
I haven't either
so you started YouTube
like at the same time as Digi
is that correct or did you come later
I'm just curious about that
was he first? okay it was like paleo
started and then you right
it was around the same time
it was around the beginning because I started
because paleo basically told me to do it
because I was talking his ear off about all this
like gay horseshit
and he was like you should just make video
people would care about this more than me
and I was like yeah but I don't make videos
and then it kind of became a thing
and I was like okay I guess I'm doing this now
and that's just sorry
I was gonna just ask
so what were you doing right before that
and this is just to where I want to start
talking about you
like if paleo started you to do that
what was your role before that because I just don't know
I was mostly focusing on drawing
like that's kind of like what I went to school for
and what I kind of envisioned myself doing
I never really envisioned myself being a YouTuber
it all kind of happened by accident
and now that I've started I can't really let it go
even though there are other things I want to do too
so
right now it's just like let's try and do
all of the things
and that's still a work in progress
this is not the Tommy Oliver interview
what I was just leading into
was I was curious about that
because I was thinking before
about all the stuff that you've done
and about
how awesome it is even though
it's just like I don't think about it that often
like when I think back to it
you made like a fucking Trixie comic
like a children's book that you just made
wait no that was
it was Scootaloo
I did a Trixie comic as well
it was an issue one and I never did the rest of them
they were supposed to be six and I did one of them
yeah right right but like right now
you run your fucking your tech channel
and it also happened
that you were a major collaborator
on like possibly my favorite youtube video
of all time which is Anthony C's
a cancel out wedding review thing
and it's just
looking at your body of work it's fucking
it's amazing that you did all this shit
that like all these different things
you know you pulled from the various
things you've done over your life and
I've always been wanting to know more about
I wanted to read your children's book
I never got around to it after this give me that shit
I've read it yeah it's good
it's extensive
I wanna ask you a big fucking thing
but let's do it later
anyway I wanna say
the Tommy Oliver interview will come
the interview series will be concluded
one day I've got something to say
it needs to be stated
that the branding and the thumbnails
on Rebel Pixels are the greatest
I've ever seen in any youtube channel
in history they're beautiful and
astounding and every time I look at them
I get a big penis boner
yeah they are pro level shit
yeah the professional presentation
is good is great
and it's consistent on your
especially on Rebel Pixels and also on Tommy Oliver TV
yeah how about those fucking
like slow movement
camera shots in the Rebel Pixels video
looking over the things yes like I know
that's like a twenty dollar investment but like
a lot of guys wouldn't think to do that
and it just adds so much professionalism
to a video like that
the commitment is off the charts it's awesome
I'm I wanna
I was gonna say that I kind of
I've always like admired your
your like
your ability to speak on podcasts
and in front of cameras you never seem
to have too much of an issue getting
your point across like you've always been
like a good talker even though
you may not think it because you put
yourself down a lot and I think you shouldn't
because you're actually pretty great
you and hippo you and hippo
are the same in that way I suppose
yeah both of you
like dramatically
undervalue yourself in comparison
to what your talents are
I mean what Jesse was just saying about the thumbnails
like I think
Tom you're like the most underpaid graphic designer
in the world because
you're doing what would be
professional graphic design work
and you could sell that to anybody
and they'd buy it at a real price
because it's real graphic design work
on all your channels and your website
you built a website from scratch with a type
of technology I'd never quite seen before
that it's like
webm's or something what is the
mechanic that your source was lost
uses well so those are just
they're just regular
mp4 videos but I went into
the auto player and they have them so they
automatically play instead of and when they
start playing as soon as they start playing they hide the controls
so you can't get to them so
they work like gifs but they're not
huge because a gif that big
would be like 15 meg would take forever
to download but the video is only like 2 meg
so they work just like gifs but
they're actual videos and you just go in and code
to hide all the UI and stuff
I've literally never seen a website built
that way before
and I really like it
like the motion comic
because you've been working on it forever
and like in each different iteration of it
I'd seen it and never clicked for me until
that website and like when
because they're all the same size
and they kind of play in this
natural way where you click on each new page
and it makes perfect sense to read it that way
and I was like he finally did it
he cracked the code he figured out how to make
this make sense to me
the way to make it work was to say fuck all of your sites
I'm doing it myself
perfect
speaking of the motion comic
it looked really good
I never really thought of you as an animator
but some of the animations
in the comic
were really swell like just
off the top of my head there's a close up of the monster's foot
like hitting the ground and then pushing off
as it like chases them
and you know it's
multiple frames and it moves really smooth
it looks good man
it was a talent I didn't know you had
until I saw it in action
yeah a lot of the skills
in that were just like because
like I hadn't done them before
it's like fuck I need to do this thing
I guess I have to sit here and like
make it work
the website thing I didn't want to do the website
but it's like well I have to because there's no other way to do this
and then the webm thing was like I was originally going to do gifts
I'm like they're too big so I guess I got to figure out
how to get around that so it's a lot of like
progress because of like necessity
over it. Necessity is the mother of invention
and that is very true on that entire website
I mean I
yeah go ahead
I was going to say that you seem to like
work really hard for like
to make like ideas
or like to
find solutions to problems like
you didn't want to draw backgrounds for your comics
so you just learned how to do 3D
oh yeah
you were just making 3D things and it was like
shit like that's a lot of work
I've done 3D and it's fucking
atrocious
but you got quite good at it
I learned quite a bit about how
like comics are drawn and like how
digital art works from watching you do it
on streams like I never
thought about what a 3D environment
could be used for as the background
of a scene until I saw you do
it and I was like oh yeah
that's yeah of course
like of course you can do that but who would
have thought to it who would have learned how to you know
um and
I definitely think you're the most multimedia out of
all of us I mean you can you can code
you can code a website
you can uh you can do 3D
you can do animations you can do
hand-drawn artwork you can do digital
uh I mean what's the word I just said
about the fucking thumbnails a minute ago
graphic design graphic design
typography you understand
um
like all those every single one of those
is like a different aesthetic skill and I think
it's under undervalued people think
of artists as like I can draw
good you know but like when you're making
the aesthetic of a whole channel
more going on there yeah you seem to
understand every single one of the component pieces
that Sorceress Lost has a
font it has a logo
and they all make sense and they all flow
into each other you know I mean I kind of
know looking at your stuff that
there's like a lot of multi-layered
shit going on I mean I coded my website too
it's not as fancy
it's not as uh it's not as advanced
as what you did with yours though but I
appreciate it yeah
actually like I used your website to help make
mine though oh yeah
cool I thought I told you but I was having
a hell of a time with the resizing of the buttons
as the screen got bigger and yours just did
that and I was like Ben how did you do that I don't
even I think the first time we talk about you like I don't
even know how it happened so I had to like I'd
go into your code and look at it like
or I'm gonna figure out how the fuck this worked
and it was like you set some value to a percentage
instead of an actual like number
and that's how they were they were shrinking
and stuff I scaled my divs man
you gotta scale those divs
fun fact I made a best guy ever
website right when I started best guy ever
and paid for a couple months to host the domain
but it has gone away because I always
thought I'd make it pro because the thing
I had was a piece a shit it was garbage
and I always plan to improve it but
I could never get anything like Ben's
probably because I just didn't commit enough time
I could like it's a fucking time commitment
yeah it is it's like
it's probably like somewhere between three and four
months to like make that whole thing
half of it was just like bugs because I remember
I spent like a week straight
of just like
the the footer
would fuck up and like certain times
it would like push past the bottom of the
the screen at certain resolutions and I had no
idea why for so for a week I was just like
googling things and typing in random code
trying to make that work and I was like a week of time
just like getting the footer that no one will
read to work right yeah
I mean I think I actually started doing
end cards in my videos after you did
like I saw the way you
laid out your end cards and I was like
I'm gonna copy that and started
doing it more that way because you had
I think you were one of the first people I saw who had
created an overlay graphic to
to frame it all in and like had
you know like the titles of videos under them
and stuff and like you know put in all these fancy little
things just and even beyond
because I could talk about you as a you know visual
designer but you also
write actual fiction
well which is something
I think only you and Jesse
can like do that out of
this group like write fiction
novel stuff
you did this fanfic this
like extensive novel length
fanfic and I remember reading it
and being like Tom you can actually
write why don't you do this
and you were like I want to but I'm
tethered to these five
YouTube channels and all this other shit
I'm actually writing I think I might do
sorceress lost as the novel
it's switch format so many times
so what I'm thinking right now
you're only five days late for nano-remo dog
I know
I wanted to start that but like I have
some friends coming over for a week for my birthday
so I'm like I can't nano-remo while they're here
because that was the plan I was going to go from
Inktober straight into that because I was like
I have like ten old story ideas
from high school and college that I've abandoned
like that'd be cool if I just nano-remo'd
like each one of those and just shit them out as like
garbage like I finished this idea from
like a decade and a half ago even though
it's like total trash so that
could be interesting but I'm thinking the
motion comic just takes so much work and I
really enjoy doing it but I hate
the fact like I really enjoyed working
on it up until I posted it
and then it's like you have to update this like on a
weekly basis or like now you're on a time limit
and like time limit is stressing me out
so I'm just like I want to like do those
like kind of like in short bursts and just like
have like a couple things like oh this is just like
a little advertisement or a little like
it's Overwatch totally influence me
the way they're marketing Overwatch is brilliant
because like their entire advertising campaign is
not canon because it has nothing to do with the game
at all I hate that
it's more like the game isn't canon to the series
like the game is just nothing related to the actual characters
the game is like
it's completely I
enjoyed the videos they make for the game
more than playing the game but like
they made a super smash brothers and then just
none of the characters are from anything else
they're just like now they're fighting
it's really weird because like none of it even makes any
sense in the lore that they're like putting all this
kind of effort into because like they have like
these two groups of like you know the Overwatch guys
and the Talon guys and then you can be them on the same team
and be buddy buddy or just like
inspired by the genius writers
over at Riot Games to make League of Legends
you know there used to be a reason why all the characters fight
got retconned out now there's just
no reason why they fight it's just they just
are doing it what is that right what are you
fucking doing I'm sorry
they got a few schools
that's all they care about but like
there was a reason as they
advertised something
completely different from what you're buying but you got attached to the characters
I was like what if I do a bunch of
just focusing on these characters doing like short
little endearing things
and then if I was just writing a novel about like
them like the actual story
like now you like the characters so you'll
read it you fucking hate reading because
everybody under the age of 25 hates
reading
if you make it a light novel you could go to Japan
well my whole thing is right now I'm starting like
really small I'm like if I can write a better story
than Reki Kawahara like I'm good like that'll be
my that's my first stepping stone
if I can do better than that
whatever he gets a good artist and
he's she gets popular for whatever reason
Tom I was going to say that
you know they were saying that I do
you know adult sorts of things
professional type of stuff but you
continue to me impress me with your
like the way that you reach out to the
tablet companies and we talked about this before
how you get them to send fucking
free shit yeah that's the
that's the best I don't know awesome I don't know how
I would even go about doing that and it's great
it's incredible I would just assume that
they wouldn't it wouldn't try and hope they
reply but you know the
the the chutzpah it takes to
reach out to do that I just I wouldn't have even thought
that's the thing but I mean maybe you just
had done research and know they would do it but nonetheless
that is pro shit and I
I seek to emulate it because it's good stuff
it's pretty cool there's actually
I found recently a website
where you can go on
there you sign up for an account and you have to like make
your Amazon because it's all through Amazon make your Amazon
account get nice and pretty and then you can
get discounted things that vendors want
you to review on Amazon through there and they'll
just kind of like 50% or give you them for free
50% that's not bad so I'm
like looking through there now it's like not like super
expensive I'm gonna be like here's a 4K TV
for like 90% off but there's like smaller
things so like I don't know and then I want to
I'm trying to like make Rebel Pixels
like more professional like I just got this like
handheld gimbal for the DSLR so you can be
like walking shots I don't have to be stuck in my
basement like I'm gonna get
my friend I'm like you I want to do a review on the
Surface Pro 3 so I want to get like super
pro and be like I'm gonna walk around town
like go to places and use this you just have the
gimbal and follow oh that's that's classy as fuck
super sexy is gonna be great
dude the thing you did with somebody I don't
maybe it was like your sister something but
someone was filming you when you went to the
store to test out the tablet
in like the Apple store like the new
thing that was announced or Microsoft store
I brought I brought that was awesome
I brought the tripod and the
slider and just set them up like in front of it
and just like I just record over there for like
and they're like yeah fine I was wondering
what they said about that they were they were
surprisingly chill I was like expecting to be
like the fuck's wrong with you they were just like
oh it's the hundredth youtuber is in to
film our fucking shit yeah
but yeah that was that was fun
cool
where's did you die looks
he died he's dead
he's dead well I think is
Tom I'm just curious about so
professionally where do you see your career
going right now are you are you looking to pursue
you know go hardcore with the tech
stuff with rebel pixels or are you going to
like split your time between that and doing
sorceress loft stuff what's your what's your
focus right now I
my problem is I can't really focus on it
that's why I'm saying like I really admire
what Ben can do he's like I'm going to do
the champion and then like that's all he did
and like didn't I'm like one of those people
that like I thrive off of feedback so I
constantly have to be putting stuff out to like
feel better about my like own existence
so if I just sat there in a room
for like five months and did nothing and I
had no like I mean contact with
humanity I just like my own like
self doubt would be to wait me because I've been
writing this first chapter
and I've gotten way farther with it I
ever did with the comic it's like
everything that would have taken forever
but like the whole time I've been writing it for like
six months have been like this is garbage this is
crap this is like not good I know
the feeling but I really want you to
work through it because I know I've heard you
stream talk about like you know
the characters in the story and the setting
in the world and stuff and I know that there's a
lot going on there
and I just want you to get it out
I want you to write it or
you know put it out there by any means necessary
well I'm hoping that
as soon as this podcast is done
I'm sitting down and I'm finishing the first
draft because it's like 95%
done it's like 12,000 words
that's awesome so
that will be done and I'm going to send
it out to a couple people get some edits and then hopefully
I'm hoping it'll be out
by the beginning of next year I'd love to
like start 2017 off with the banks like here we go
yeah man pay attention
it's cool you know it's funny
to me that you brought up the like wanting
to do things that are faster that was my exact
reason for starting to do
YouTube like seriously because
in school I had done I was a programmer and done
game design and realized that
I hated it because it took like years
to release anything to anyone that wasn't
total garbage and was like polished to a reasonable
level so I abandoned that shit
and now I'm like the guy who takes 6
months to finish a fucking video
I hate it it's not
what I signed up for but
nonetheless nonetheless
that's how you just do bestie boy vlogs
yeah I gotta probably work with the next master piece
I gotta talk
I wanna talk about what uh
I wanna talk about what is like
the biggest influence that Tom
had on me and in turn
that I had on all of you
that you might not even realize
because
Tom, Tom's the first
person I met like as a
video maker like the first friend I made
as someone who made videos
you know I hadn't like
I was new to you talking about your history
yeah well I was I was new to YouTube
I started making videos he was doing the same kind
of thing at the same time
and we both became aware of each other like
fairly early on
and started collaborating and stuff
and we became friends we started talking on Skype and shit
and the
the most important
thing to happen to me and Tom
in this early period was that we both
were trying to become
like professionals in this we wanted it to be
a career but this is when Hasbro
started like taking all you know started
uh marking everyone's videos and shit
so I had gotten
um you know I had just
I had left my job to do YouTube
making like $600 a month through ad revenue
the first couple of months which is crazy that I
did that well those two months but like
I don't even yeah lucky to make
that much now well that's not true anymore but
for a long time I'd be lucky to make that much
but like I got monetization disabled
completely and so me and Tom were like
how are we going to make money
from this you know like we started
basically me and Tom were going to make
something kind of like
the horseshoe crew or the PCP where we were
like gonna you know market ourselves
as this team
we were gonna build a website and try to make
some kind of system where people could pay like
on a monthly basis to access
try to make a kick stuff we did we had a whole
document right out there yeah kind of like exactly
what happened we believed in the weed we were gonna do yeah
it was almost exactly like that 2012
2013 or something yeah and like the high
like we had like this like crazy
like our goals had like this huge
escalation where a few if we got to the
certain amount like $45,000
and we would just move in together and make
blogs every day and stuff like that
so yeah
but we had all these
different plans to try to make money and
then around this time
when all this stuff was going on Tom
found Patreon
and if it
weren't for Tom finding Patreon
I wouldn't have a Patreon and none
of you would have known about Patreon
so that's true yeah like the whole
idea of like let's try to
find a way to get people to be able
to pay for this was very much like Tom's idea
it was like I remember this
I was watching this is like when I first
got into you guys when this this whole
shit was going down I remember it very well
I think the I think the t-bat Patreon
was largely modeled on
Tom's Patreon it was modeled on Tom's
now you mentioned it was like totally
I forgot about that but it's the truth
because Tom Tom knew a lot more
about like marketing and
business kind of stuff than I did at the
time not that either of us knew a lot
but you know he was
he also like Tom knew more about
like trying to merchandise and stuff we tried
to launch TV t-shirt stuff
it didn't go very well but like
what is it
Alicorn Princess
well Tom also had a whole t-shirt website
that he was running at the time that like
that's kind of amazing because Patreon is
like the cosmic radiation
that gave us all our fantastic four
powers yeah
yeah
like it was it was all just like
me going Tom like what do I do
I can't make money and he him going
me either bro let's figure it out
you know and like we were we were gonna
become this like this duo of
of finding a way to make
money but then Patreon showed up and Tom was like
well this works and we were like oh okay
I guess we'll use that
and we've been using it ever since and all
of our careers are based around it
not to mention the meme of you guys
being gay for each other
that is a meme that has persisted
and only grown
that meme is expanded to contain all of us
yeah it's so great that the
PCP gives gays more representation
in the media
it's kind of shocking how little of that
there is now because me and Tom had
lots of gay stuff
like made about us
it was just a brownie thing
totally a brownie thing
and uh
should we try to
like us the artists in the audience
to start doing more gay
I don't necessarily want it
I don't think we need to ask I think this podcast
is already gonna jump start
this is the circle saturation
it is
I'm sure we're gonna get a circle jerk illustration
this is a strong image
and by the way guys
some strong bold images
make sure to draw my dong the biggest
I should have done this at the beginning
the tradition I went to urban dictionary
and looked up circle jerks so it will indulge me
have a listen
now this is a two part thing so be patient
so number one when a group of males
sit in a circle jerking each other off
okay standard but part two
clarifies not
it stresses this is not what it is
when a group of males stand in a circle to jerk off
onto a cookie or anything of the sort
that retarded frat game
is in fact called limp biscuit
which kind of imply which is why
the namesake of the band is so horrible
you know
there you go
we got something to do for retcon too
we're gonna limp biscuit it up
the limp biscuit podcast
get down with the sickness you mother get up
come on get down with the sickness
the limp biscuit podcast
not about the band
look forward to it
alright well are we wrapped up
cut my life
into pieces
this is my last resort
I'd like to say
in closing that you guys are
probably the most
important
people who have affected me
in my life up to this point
and I'm really glad to know all of you
and makes me happy
that I can be involved in your lives
in whatever way and we can do things like this together
same for me I'm really happy
and I feel lucky all the time
to be a part of this
gay little circle
that even jerks
like someone pointed out before
I tend to choose my friends
I seek out people who I feel
are better than me at something
none of you
are as good as me at most things
but at something
most of you have one talent
that is useful to me
I choose my friends
like I choose my women
that I can beat them into submission
everyone here is definitely better than me
at least one thing I agree
we're a robust little group
it's true
you're all my best friends
for me
a huge part of what makes the PCP
what it is and I've said this before
is that we're all united
we're all trying to do
kind of the same thing
we all want to be successful through creativity
and the glue
that holds it all together
is that we actually like one another's shit
that's the most important quality
of the
particularly of this core
PCP
is that we all really like one another's work
I love Ben's comics
I love Nate's videos, I love Hippo's videos
I love Jesse's videos and I love Tom's
things he actually puts out when they happen
and I love you guys's
Android Don
is that a vision thing
it's from the panel cast
no one but me has actually listened
to the panel cast
I was gonna, one of these days
alright
well thanks for listening everybody
I hope you enjoyed this and I hope you jerked off as well
that's the name of the game
and if you're not paying to play
then you can go pay fucking get the fuck out of here
goodbye, alright everyone say goodbye
bye
thanks for watching
I'm surprised at how many nice things
we found to say about you
now I'm supposed to
be working
right now
but I'm not working
I'm doing nothing
my dick
I'm jerking
myself I'm sucking
I am an asshole
I am
a stupid
I've got a deadline
don't want to do it
what the hell is wrong with me
I'm
supposed to
be making
money
I'm supposed to
be creating
funny
things that the people
gladly will pay
for
artistic genius
that's what they came
for
instead I'm
tweeting
hashtag repeating
that's why there's no
heat and holes in the
ceiling
yeah
it's quite the burden
it's a hard
knock life
being a genius