Most companies that sell products make money by selling them to consumers.
Pyramid schemes typically make money selling overpriced, difficult to sell products to their own distributors,
who are typically aspiring entrepreneurs, hoping to build a business.
Hello everyone, and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I am the best guy ever, Pharaoh best guy ever, because we're talking about Egypt today, of course,
and we've got Mr. Mummy Hippocrit.
What was that entire intro?
I don't know, you're a mummy now for this episode.
Okay, hello, it's me.
Yes, Ben Anubis, dead?
Yes.
Welcome to the Luxor Hotel, where you gotta die and go to hell.
That rhymed because I'm a genius.
Did you know that in Egypt, pharaohs were all buried with their pets?
That's what Tom Oliver is, he's one of these things.
Pyramids weren't made by the Egyptians, they were made by aliens who were worshipped as gods in the past.
Google the Anunnaki, it's all fucking real!
You know, before we get into the actual topic, I just want to relate an anecdote that my Spanish teacher in high school...
Mr. What's-his-face?
Mr. Oh God, what was his name?
They called him Mr. Subella.
He legitimately believed that the Incan ziggurats were made with some kind of advanced lost technology that used sonic waves to levitate stone blocks into place.
Look, I've watched Ancient Aliens, I know exactly how all that shit was made.
Is it possible?
Maybe!
Alright, I have a question about that.
I have a couple of questions.
Why is it that they have the skills of a tier one minecrafter, these aliens?
Why are they making it more advanced than that?
It's gotta be some sonic nonsense.
Yeah, of course.
We make up for our lack of technical ability with our creativity.
That's why, you know, given the correct tools, we can make crazy shit.
The aliens, they got the technical shit down.
They're just not very creative, right?
They make a big giant 3D triangle and they call it a day.
That's true.
There was a lot of sonic powers back then.
There was real sonic mania.
Yeah, there was a real sonic boom back in the day.
Yeah, relevant to our friend Hippocrates here.
Alright, let's begin, everybody.
So, our Egypt theme episode is about pyramid schemes.
I understand it was the process of worshipping alien skygods.
Yeah, that's right.
So, okay, let's check over our buddies over at Urban Dictionary
to see what they've got to say on the situation.
Okay, here we go.
Pyramid scheme.
This is definition number two.
The best scheme to ever set up once you learn to never underestimate,
I hate this already, the stupidity of the human majority.
Just make sure you don't get caught though.
Oh, I regret reading that.
That was terrible.
I know, I know, right?
Okay, let's try another one.
Here's the top definition.
I should have just gone to this one.
A fraudulent business model illegal in most places
in which participants are paid to recruit more participants
rather than commissions on sales.
Frequently passed off as multi-level marketing
by incorporating sales of an unmarketable product or service
into the scheme.
In such cases, participants are usually required
to maintain a monthly purchase quota to qualify for payments.
Alright, well, that's really it.
That's the one.
Now, it's like the business version of a zombie plague.
Multi-level marketing is the softer, gentler form
that is supposedly legal.
The politically correct term, if you will.
That's what pyramid schemes call themselves
to get away with being pyramid schemes.
Right, and Gib, you described it as similar to the zombie outbreak,
but it'd be like the zombie outbreak
if in order to make more zombies,
you didn't have to just touch them.
You had to convince them,
like, no, you've got to understand,
being a zombie is great.
You're really going to adapt to our lifestyle
and become part of the family.
If you buy this $49.99 protein powder,
you too can have this amazing zombie complexion.
Yeah.
Well, I was thinking of it more in the sense
that eventually there's going to be so many of these people
in the thing that there's no one left to recruit,
and they're like, well, we're going to just starve.
There's no brain sweet.
We're all zombies now.
Eventually, that's true.
And they all fall over.
That's a fair point.
It's interesting that you brought up protein powder
because just the other day,
I was coming back from the gym,
and I happened to stop in, I think, CVS or whatever,
and I was getting my gigantic five-pound box
of protein powder in the things.
And as I was buying it, this dude's like,
hey, hold up there, friendo.
And this was just like two days ago.
Have I got something for you?
And he runs out to his car.
He's like, don't leave.
Wait, wait, wait, was this the guy who worked there
or just an intern?
No, he was loitering in the lobby.
I think he was buying something legitimately,
but he happened to see an opportunity,
and he dove on it when he saw me buying protein powder.
He's like, oh, this is actually kind of sad.
So he comes back with a pamphlet
and a little packet of some stuff.
And he's like, here, this is the best protein powder ever.
We grow it in Greenland.
It's new.
It's fancy.
He was actually stumbling over it.
He grew this protein in Greenland.
What the fuck?
It might have been Iceland, but what are those?
And he was like, no, it was Ireland.
It was Ireland.
It must be some soy protein, then,
around somewhere.
It definitely was.
But then he was stumbling over the pitch.
He had clearly just learned this,
and hadn't internalized it yet.
So I don't think this was really a pyramid scheme
as much as just a sales pitch in general,
but it was interesting.
It was a similar sort of situation
that I just happened to find myself in.
And it needs to say I threw it all in the trash
as soon as he was out of my eyesight.
Why did you even wait?
Why did you wait?
You should have done it right in front of him
to send a message.
But that's the thing.
In order to deal with these kind of situations,
I make it seem like I'm on board,
and then immediately throw everything away
once they're gone,
so that I don't have to deal with the social ramifications
of rejecting someone.
It's much easier for me.
You're just like, hmm, thanks.
This is some good information.
Dumps in the trash.
Well, I'll look all this over and get back to you real soon.
Let me pass this off to my secretary.
Dumps into garbage can.
We'll be back pretty soon.
And then Oscar the Grouch comes out.
He said, I like it.
It's good.
You said I could go home at five.
I don't want it.
Oscar comes out.
He's like, oh, this looks like a real good money-making opportunity.
Incidentally, I did look at the nutrition facts.
Only 21 grams of protein per serving.
My other thing has 25 grams of protein per serving.
So fuck this shit.
It's probably got, like, essential oils.
It's got any more expensive.
Essential oils or something, or, like, electrolytes.
Yeah, I'm sure.
Some amino acids.
It's a superfood.
That is protein.
Yeah.
What is our angle on pyramid schemes?
Because I don't think any of us like it.
I know.
I think some of us have experience with it, right?
Yeah, tell stories.
Yeah.
Well, Jackie suggested this topic to me.
And I thought it was great because I have personal experience with it.
As she does too, she's known people that have been involved in it.
And then I went and I did some research.
And there was this blog called Not Quite Fairy Tales Blog,
which is a girl's personal account of getting, like, deep, deep
into the fucking MLM rabbit hole.
It's a multi-level market.
Oh, multi-level market.
And it's a pretty gripping read, and it's absolutely disgusting
the way it all goes down.
And then there's a documentary called Betting On Zero
that is about this investor called Bill Ackman, who is, um,
he's going after, have you seen it, Tom?
I watched it.
It's funny because, like, I watched this, like, three days
before you brought up this topic.
So it's just, huh, I'm prepared for this.
Yeah.
It's because he basically, he invests tons of money in the idea
that a company called Herbalife will fail
because he's convinced that the company is a pyramid scheme.
So the movie is basically his quest to, like,
out Herbalife as a pyramid scheme so the business will fail
and he'll recoup a huge amount of profit on his investments.
Interesting.
Anyway, for me, my personal experience is that I was almost
recruited by a vector marketing to sell Cutco knives.
That's what happened to me.
This is when I was, this is when I was pretty freshly out of college
living at home and desperate to find a job.
And they preyed on me because I was weak
and I didn't know any better.
Yeah, I think I was on Craigslist or something
and I saw an ad for vector marketing
and I, you know, responded to the ad and they said,
I'm coming for an interview.
So here's what happened.
I went, I drove down, I put on like a suit or some shit
and I drove down.
I was scared shitless because I really need this.
I really fucking need this.
So I go into the waiting room, into the lobby in this office building
and I wait for my turn and I go in and I talk to this smug,
this smug, clean shaven bald guy.
He's like a youngish guy and he's just smirking.
He's like, he's real fucking confident in himself.
He asks me like, he asks me like some bullshit question
and he gives us all, he gives everyone in the room a presentation
where like, oh, this knife is so sharp it can cut a penny.
So you take the knife and you like, oh, you cut a penny into a spiral
and like, this is what you're supposed to do.
And the idea is that you go around door to door
being like, hey, I want to sell you some knives.
You go into their home and you cut a penny in front of them
and you're like, oh, it's so sharp it can cut a penny.
And they're like, okay, but the thing is you got to buy the knives
from them to then go out and sell them.
So there's no, they're not hiring you to do anything.
You're buying product from them
that you will hopefully then go on to resell.
So like they profit no matter what just by bringing you on board.
But I didn't realize this.
I was so desperate for a job that I was like,
this is my fucking ticket out of dad yelling at me all the time
for being an unemployed asshole.
So I was, and I'll never forget,
after the interview went down, I was waiting
and the guy calls me in his office and he's like, Ben.
So after talking to you for a while
and reviewing your credentials,
we have decided that yes, you are qualified to work for Vectormon.
And I was like really relieved.
I was like, oh, thank you.
I was like, I'm really grateful.
It's embarrassing looking back on it
because now I know what was really going on.
And so I went home and I was like, mom, dad,
I'm going to sell knives.
And looking back, I don't know why mom and...
That's philosophy, physics, grief.
We're really paying off now, baby.
I know, right?
And looking back, I don't know why they didn't be like,
Ben, this is a scam.
Like they should have, I don't know why they didn't just do that.
But they were like, are you sure about this?
Are you really sure about this?
And I was like, mom, dad, what do you want to do?
You're always telling me to get a job.
Here's a fucking job.
What more do you want from me?
God.
But at some point, considering I was like,
I got to pay like $160 for this knife set.
Like I can't fucking spare that.
And also it doesn't seem right that I need to buy product
to work for a job.
So I ended up...
So like the fact...
Yeah, my lack of money ended up...
My lack of money got me into that situation,
but then it also stonewalled me from getting any further into it
so I couldn't go through with it.
Years later, I was again jobless
and I responded to another ad for some other company.
They'd said they'd give me an interview.
And I went to this office building.
It was a piece of crap in the middle of nowhere.
It was underneath a karate dojo.
Sick.
Yeah, but I went inside and I waited around.
And it turned out that this interview was not even one-on-one.
It was basically a group presentation.
And this was not quite the same.
I didn't have to buy in to do this,
but basically I would just be selling insurance policies on commission,
which is pretty much the same thing.
It's no risk to the company.
They're not hiring you for anything.
You're just selling their product and they'll give you a cut if you're successful.
So it's basically another multi-level marketing thing.
But this time I knew what was up.
So at the end I was just like, I'm out. I'm out peace.
And that's my fucking story.
How about you guys?
Well, Ben, that's cool,
but I prefer people who succeed at multi-level marketing.
I want to hear a champion who's made the world his bitch.
Someone who really had the hustle.
The hustle they need to make it work.
Exactly.
To be honest, I would kind of like to know
some insider stories from people who have risen up in the ranks
at least a little bit and become that recruiter guy.
I wonder what that's like.
I seriously recommend the Not Quite Fairy Tales blog.
It is horrifying.
She manages to sell a little bit just from her own get-up-and-go,
going around and looking for it.
She becomes like a complete fucking slave drone to this company.
Her whole Facebook and social media presence becomes dedicated to tweeting about it.
To tweeting about it and tweeting about products,
posting selfies of herself talking about how grateful she is to have this job
and how wonderful her life is now that she's got this job,
even though she's like hundreds of pounds in the hole for the entire time.
But they're just like, fake it till you make it, girl.
You've got to tell people how great this is.
That's so evil.
It's really evil.
They're like fake it till you make it.
They say that under the guise, show people how great the product is
so they'll want to buy it.
But no, really what they're doing is fake it till you make it.
Tell people how great this job is so they'll be duped into fucking signing on
and becoming your subordinate.
And you're duping yourself into not letting the reality of the situation phase you.
Yeah, and of course she eventually finds out
that this super with it successful together girl that recruited her,
she was just faking it until she made it too.
She wasn't making any money either.
Nobody in the chain was making any money.
They're all in the hole.
The people that are maintaining their high rankings
are literally buying the products for themselves
and keeping their quote unquote business afloat that way.
It's a nightmare.
Some of the most evil shit out there, man.
That's not how capitalism is supposed to work.
It's purely parasitic.
You succeed in an MLM by duping people into falling for the same trick you fell for.
Once you realize that the products won't sell,
that's the only way to make it work.
So what I want to know is did the girl ever cross that evil bridge
and become like, I mean, I know that she was advertising it for her.
Did she ever willingly acknowledge it like,
I am now duping people and you know what, I've got to do it
if I want to dig myself out of here.
Did she ever get into that place?
No, not quite.
There was this kind of thing where like she got her like step sister
to buy some makeup at a kind of a shitty price
and then she like couldn't refund it even though the girl changed her mind.
But she wasn't like, no, she didn't like act.
She did recruit some people, but she didn't like, I don't know.
She wasn't too, like clearly there are worse people.
Sure, but the funny thing is even in a situation where you're doing this,
like human beings are crazy adaptive.
You can get yourself in the headspace where you don't think you're doing anything wrong with this stuff.
Wait, no, I changed my mind because she did the fake it till you make a thing
and she did recruit people.
So yeah, she absolutely duped people, never mind.
She was just as bad as any other others.
What I'm wondering is if like, we could call these people evil and all that,
but I'm wondering if they're not more helpful to think about it
that like their perspective has been fucked up
and we need to see the light, you know?
Because they've been told by people they think it was successful that this is how they did it.
And so they're just following the blueprint that they've been given.
Same if you go to any job and they're like, this is the way you do it and then you do it.
You have no proof that that works, you just take them at their word.
That's true, until you learn as you go.
Until you're just like, wait, they're fucking me over and then you're screwed.
You think it's a legitimate job and like any talk of like,
oh, well, my products aren't selling, this stuff is not good.
It's like, that's all like, you're being negative.
You need to work on your attitude.
You need to have a positive mindset to succeed in this industry.
But a positive mindset is just like, buy everything we tell you to buy.
It's all that business talk.
I feel like there's a whole sect of human society that is the businessman.
And it's so weird and alien that they get in their heads.
The way to succeed is to be this way.
And I think it's really just dumb people following a blueprint, like you're saying.
They don't know what they're doing, but they know that it makes them money,
so they just keep doing it until they get really rich.
Like smart people generally don't go down that road,
but when they do, they rise right to the top because they know actually how to do it better.
There are rich people in these pyramid schemes,
but they're only at like the very, very top that have like just lucked into a situation
where they have huge networks of people underneath them.
Wouldn't Erbilife have like the president's group wherever the fuck it was?
You got like this like diamond pin and they were like,
they did these huge big presentations where like hundreds of people went.
They're like, they showcase these guys and then it's like, you just have to keep going.
I have like 15 sports cars now.
Erbilife's the best. Yeah.
And everybody was like cheering.
If I can do it, you can do it.
Fucking bullshit.
What's what's evil about this is that so in like normal capitalism,
the whole idea is you like generate a product and you give it to people who,
you know, don't have the skills or whatever to make themselves or the time they've just got other specialties.
And then you do an equitable trade where you both gain.
And that's where that's where society progresses.
I mean, you know, in this kind of system,
that's like through that trade,
that's where all the great stuff that we have in America has basically come from through this process.
But like nothing is being created in this system.
It's kind of like the banking system only that actually lending money does sort of allow growth in some way.
The business model of these, you know, pyramid schemes that pass themselves off as MLMs
by having a quote unquote product that's for sale is that the product itself is not anything special
and it's overpriced for what it is.
It will not sell on its own.
But the structure of the way that you recruit people and then you incentivize these people like you need to sell.
You need to sell the stuff at any cost if you're going to make your quote unquote business work.
So that creates the incentive to buy and to sell.
So like the products are designed to be bought by end users.
They're designed to be bought by the people you recruit so they can sell.
So the only people buying the products are the people suckered into it.
Or the quote unquote employees.
They're the ones with the interest in purchasing the products.
Any system of trade like this that isn't about delivering as high a quality product as possible to the people
at a minimum has its priorities skewed and is evil.
It's disgusting.
Watching in the betting on zero documentary they interview the guy who's in charge of Herbalife
which is another company like this that sells like health products and stuff.
And he is some like he's like an ex Disney executive.
But he talks about like he talks with such confidence about how like this business is great
because we're bringing like we're bringing these great products to people.
Like we're providing we're providing a great service like we're bringing important fucking health benefits to the people
and we're you know giving tons of people like an opportunity to make money
like we're supporting these communities.
Like the the movie is it's part of its centers on this like this Latina community.
This Latino community that's like a bunch of them have been suckered in.
They've been like tricked into buying these like franchises of Herbalife the only for the products not to sell
and they they're ruined and they lose tons of money and it causes tons of problems for them.
And they're like protesting this company because like we were duped you know by promises of success
that we're not representative of your actual company.
And meanwhile fucking what's his name.
The CEO of Herbalife is like yes you know we love the Latina community.
You know they're part of our they're part of us.
We're happy.
We're happy to give them this opportunity.
But it's a fucking sham.
The worst part of that is they have they they bring the guy who's who's who's betting on zero.
The guy they follow they bring him in to have this like meeting with these people bringing the lawsuit against Herbalife.
All the people that got duped and then Herbalife hires a busload of people to counter protest them.
During this meeting there's tons of Latino people out there with signs saying how great Herbalife is.
And they've all been paid to do it to make it look as if these guys are all full of shit.
On that subject is Herbalife hiring because I could really use some money.
I would totally counter protest for money.
I'm not that dedicated to this cause.
You know if you're going to say we're all we're all missing the important question here because we're all morally vacant.
We need to the question we need to ask is how do we make the PCP a pyramid scheme so we can all make tons of money.
Clearly that's the question question here.
I like I like where your head's at.
I like where you're going.
Well I'm actually the head of a pyramid scheme.
It's called it's called my patreon.
It's called patreon.com slash Louis Batten.
The way it works is you patron me and you give me money and then you get other people to join in and the patron.
And then they can replace the money you're giving me.
So you'll you'll be my patron without having to pay.
You just need to recruit people to do it for you.
And then everybody can go into my patron discord chat and they can say hey I got in here without paying.
And then everyone will be like like it'll be like fuck it's sick.
And then the people down the people they recruited are going to be scrambling to find people to pay for their segment for their portion of what they're you know.
The word is minimum guys.
This isn't quite a pyramid scheme.
It's a pretty far cry from it really.
But like I it's funny to me to think about the way patreon sort of works and that it incentivizes creators to like patron each other and then just recirculate money.
Because the whole deal is like does it.
Well yeah like there's there's a big culture of like ooh go out and patron everybody.
Keep forwarding money to your creators.
But the thing is or to the creators that you like as an artist but the thing is every time that you patron anyone.
Patreon takes their 10% or their 5% cut or whatever from the money that's being patron.
So if you if you if somebody patrons you a dollar and then you're like great or let's say $10 and then you decide to patron somebody $5 or something.
Like and you're using the money that you're making to do that.
Like you're just giving patreon the money and no more is actually getting to the creators.
You know you know what I'm saying.
Like if you.
Yeah.
Patreon gets like double and triple dip on that because like it's the same $10 but they've taken their cut twice out of the same $10.
I remember I remember seeing someone's patreon that was like he posted like inspirational quotes and writings and stuff.
But his model was like my model is like you patron me all patron you.
And in this way like like it boosts both of us.
But like yeah.
Only the only person getting paid in that situation is patreon itself.
Everyone else the money is just disappearing.
Dupest thing I've ever heard.
I read this and I was like yeah okay this guy looks like he's fucking got it because he's got a pretty high patreon number going.
But he's giving that all back to the people.
But he's.
Yeah.
It's a fucking sham.
That's why I make a point of not patroning people as a person who gets money from patreon.
I pay for you hippo.
Oh that thanks.
Because I love you.
And you deserve it.
I just don't.
Thanks.
Oh no.
No.
I'm going to back myself into a corner with all this praise.
I don't know what to do.
Okay.
I'm with you though.
I have never patroned anyone and will never because I would much rather just PayPal the money directly if I was inclined to do so.
That's true.
Yeah.
PayPal is a better for that.
Although for me to you it would it would still lose money because of the country difference.
That's true.
PayPal's recurring payment function is it would be a superior alternative to patreon but nobody wants to do it.
Right.
And I kind of.
The masses need their centralized platform in order to make up for the fact that they have no brains.
I don't really blame them.
I mean.
I just doesn't.
I mean it just doesn't have that.
I don't know.
Like I can't put my finger on it but there's something more friendly about doing it through patreon.
There totally is because it's made for that.
There's a cultural zeitgeist.
Yeah.
There's just a there's just a culture now of doing it.
Objectively speaking the PayPal is better but patreon just is so much more like appealing.
I think what it is is that for PayPal you need to be given a link to and then type in stuff.
For patreon you go there and you have an account and you just press a button.
Really.
Yeah.
Like it's it's it's.
Although that is one of the downsides.
It's not that much simpler but it's simpler enough that people would do it over.
People would do it over PayPal and not to mention it's like a far more customizable thing.
I'll tell you what PayPal needs to do.
PayPal needs to get in this game so I can stop giving patreon.
You know like I lose like a 10% cut of everything I made through the combination of like money
being transferred to like the like the like the credit card people who like process the
payments and stuff and then also patreon takes their 5% cut.
So like everybody loses 10% off that shit.
PayPal already has this technology built in for free.
They just need to work on their public image and they will now get all the traffic that patreon gets.
They just need they need a PR campaign to step their shit up.
Elon Musk.
I actually know if you still works at PayPal or whatever but they need to get their shit together
and organize this and just make it so that they have a similar platform to what patreon does
with the like customization and the cute memes you can put and the little descriptions what not
and your your your campaign or whatever.
I think that's the end.
Patreon needs competition desperately.
Absolutely.
I would welcome it from a corporate monolith like PayPal.
I kind of want them to fucking be squished.
It's funny because like they'd be squeezed to improve themselves.
Because like PayPal is like a big company.
They're so like normal.
Patreon has the edge of being like oh we're all into indie art guys.
We're in a spice art.
Totally how they did it.
You come to patreon and everyone's like oh well I guess I will.
It's actually funny because like patreon actually killed the first site to do this because
patreon wasn't the first site to be said.
Really?
Yeah there was a site made by Hank Green called Subbable.
That's the one.
And they were running that for a while but the thing is they never got it out of like beta
or whatever because like only certain people could use it could join Subbable.
Like you had to be chosen for it and they kept that up for like a year or something and patreon
just like fuck that we're gonna do what you did but let it be open for everybody and then
eventually.
Well you know that's capitalist for you.
I was sad.
I was sad about that because I actually liked Subbable's model better.
Yeah Subbable's model was way better.
It was the way that my patreon is set up where I give rewards based on total patronage not
on like monthly.
So like when you donated money to Subbable it like built up like your bank and then you
could spend the money in like lump sums to get rewards instead of like having like monthly
things.
So it was way better.
It was like a hundred dollars and you pledge five dollars a month.
Once you pledge a hundred dollars total then you could unlock that reward and claim it.
That's good.
So but they got killed because they didn't develop a site fast enough.
That's the market baby and I assume you guys know about the little bit of controversy that's
been going on about patreon demonetizing or you know shutting down the accounts.
Now there's a lot of sides to that and we don't need to go into it too much but I was actually
pretty pretty pretty convinced by the arguments that Mr. Patreon man made in the in the video
that he made.
He did like an interview with Dave Rubin.
I did.
I did watch the interview that he did with Dave Rubin and it was it was I felt like I was
concerned by the fact that he just said like a lot of the situations like I don't know what
I would do.
I'm like dude you wrote the rules.
You're the guy.
You're the guy dude.
What who am I supposed to ask these questions to the thing is is though like people were
saying because like it was Lauren Southern who got demonetized and she's like a right
wing political commentator and people were like pissed off like this is a political thing.
But if you look at like the history of patreon like banning they've also banned like you
know anti-fog things and like left-wing stuff too.
So it is like they are sticking to their their their terms of service or whatever it is.
It still is like a bad precedent to say about this.
I have a thought about this.
I've been thinking about for a while and I only recently was able to to articulate it
clearly.
So let me tell you let me ask you guys what do you think about this.
So so common these days when someone is like let's just say like when when Sargon of Akkad
for example got kicked off of Twitter as it was recently you know like people good riddance
fair enough.
It doesn't matter how you feel about it.
But the point is as he's kicked off the people like his side of the argument says like oh
you know that's not fair.
This is shutting down free speech.
I mean not everybody's making that point and like he would acknowledge like Twitter's
a private company.
But that's the thing.
The other side would then say you know the leftists who are happy that he's gone.
No Twitter is a private company.
They can do whatever they want dude.
You just have to deal with it.
This is you know fuck off.
And so okay so that's a fair argument.
But here's what I'm wondering about that situation.
So as time goes on more and more these companies like Twitter are the ways that we actually
communicate in the real world.
Like this this is becoming like just the public marketplace as opposed to gathering in the
town square.
A better example for this is like Twitter is bad enough but like Google Google is super
politically motivated at this point.
And like that's been made clear Google essentially is a public utility at this point like you
can't function without using their services.
So like if not like legally from an ethical ethical standpoint they should be apolitical
and not mingle in that at all despite the fact that they're a private company.
Like there's like you know just recently when I watched the interview with Mr. Patron
man there were like he talked about how Patron exists to cultivate a certain culture and
you know he was big jack in his dick about like no we're creators we're the creators
place and like he was like so for example you cannot sponsor like a porn thing on Patron
like that's against our terms of service and I was like hang on I know people right
now who have Patrons that are about porn and are you know like that's what they do.
So where's the I didn't even think that was the case I think he just means like actual
pornography because you can like draw porn I think they're fine with that I'm pretty
sure I'm pretty sure I am aware of like like models and they're definitely cam girls and
stuff on Patreon for sure photographers and like you know erotic photography that is definitely
being funded through Patreon at least as far as I am aware I have definitely seen such
some people would argue there's a difference but I think that's bullshit I think like at
that point like there's no difference between porn and like like why just like Jessica
Negiri for example has a gigantic Patreon one of the biggest and I only watch her to
jack off that's what I do that's what her content is for so I don't know what other utility
it has so I like that seems like a clear case I don't know at least I just think it's dumb
to ban porn entirely I think I think it's it's as valid as anything else because that
would that's like I am just guessing but that's probably a huge amount of Patreons income is
like various porn things I'm sure I'm sure you know oh yeah like that girl who makes like
that you know this thing so Kimi Chad that's exactly what I'm thinking of yes her every
time I think about her I just want to kill myself she makes like 50 grand a month or
something it's like she makes she makes over six figures a year like easily well there's
a decent amount of paid okay but the point I want to get to about this was like yeah it's
basically this issue of like being it being treated as a public utility like right now
there's this whole thing about net neutrality going on right now and I actually don't know the
status of it right now I don't think anything's changed at the moment but but the point is
that like we're trying to make the internet be treated as like again a public utility like
the phones are so right now AT&T cannot say hey we heard that you were talking about big gay
dicks on the phone so we're shutting down your account because we are a good Christian company
and we don't want that shit on our fucking airwaves well actually you can't you can technically do
that I mean that's happening right now because uh is that so uh because in the aftermath of
Charlottesville and stuff like yeah you know the you ever heard the Daily Stormer it's like a
Nazi website they um they were reporting on that and like everyone got pissed off about Nazis
and so the the company that hosted the Daily Stormer pulled the site because they're like
we don't support this on our platform so they pulled the entire site even though they weren't
technically doing anything illegal they took it down and then they went to google to host it there
and google's like fuck you so now the site's gone and so that's yeah that that's a great example
that's exactly the same sort of issue here like that's that is a private hosting company deciding
we don't want to host it but then like for political reasons nobody wants to host it and so there's
a denial of service going on like it's censorship by by you know by virtue of what it is if nobody
question though is is this is this unfair or is this fair I don't know how we got here from
fucking pyramid schemes but here we are ladies and gentlemen I was I was just going to say we
ventured pretty far afield by now we have but I still want to get back at some point to turning
the pcp into a pyramid scheme it's a very important topic I think we can do it if we put our heads
together okay okay let's let's think about this all right well we just well you know we this
is the product joining the pcp I've got hang on I've got it everybody okay all right the product
that we're selling is podcasts on the pcp channel what we do is we outsource people like templates
of like images or maybe like the theme song or whatever we give them assets to make their own
podcast this sounds like react world I was just gonna say exactly that's that's where I'm going
with this and so we this is sort of a licensing deal for us we give them people that they make
their podcasts and then they make money on them but they have to pay us a royalty for the usage of
that shit and uh and then there you go that actually sounds like a great idea and I no longer hate
react world because I see that they were actually geniuses and we need to get in on it we need to
succeed where they failed agreed agreed they were visionaries we need to we need to corner the
market on actual literature literal pcp and add that we're starting a multi-level marketing
uh corporation um we need people on the streets the pcp is brought to you by pcp guys we've we've
this is embarrassing we've gotten away from our roots we need to get back to gallons of pcp
you know and whatnot think about it like this just just find five people to sell drugs for you
and each of them finds five people to sell drugs for them by the time that you go down
two two steps you're you're fucking walter white only you don't die at the end spoilers for breaking
back yes spoilers everything works out great for you forever there's no problems um all right well
i'm down where no just where where can we find drugs well we just gotta hit up my voice someone
send send send someone send best guy ever's uh p o box some drugs and we'll start
no we can't we can't do that because then we're in their pyramid scheme because we're relying on
them for the drugs we can't that that'll fuck it all obviously we're gonna start with we're gonna
start from ourselves we're gonna start with donations like our initial our initial source of
capital will be will be donations donate drugs to the pcp pyramid scheme a hashtag pc pyramid scheme
um find five people who will tweet it for you um and then they'll find five people to eat it for
them and on and on um yeah and uh by our dude uh here's how it works here here's what you have to
do okay hashtag uh pc pyramid scheme and then tag tag five of your friends and they have to tag
five of their friends and eventually uh hashtag pc pyramid scheme will be will be a global worldwide
phenomenon and everybody will be saying what the fuck is this this is not a joke everybody this is
real this is real everybody go hashtag pc pyramid scheme tag five of your friends and keep it going
forever uh let's yeah i'm gonna do it right now actually good all right let's let's get it rolling
that people won't know for a week uh what the fuck you're talking about but uh well it's the day it
airs no that's right that's right i'm okay i'm gonna wait i'm gonna wait until the day this airs and
then i'll do it good thinking good thinking yes we'll all do it then you should just schedule the
tweet so as soon as it goes up it posts and then you're you're fucking ready can you can you schedule
a tweet you have to be able to there's no way you can't schedule so i've never heard of such a
twitter that i've never needed to do it but now you can schedule a word there's no i've never heard
of anyone scheduling a tweet oh my god you can schedule a post was that good was that good you
can you can schedule a patreon post you can't do that god twitter sucks okay hey here's what you
can do if you have to do a workaround you can uh have a video on youtube you can schedule that video
and then you can associate a tweet with it that that is true that video that at worst case scenario you
could do that what if we made what if we said um make a make a fucking make a fucking youtube video
that's uh just just the text hashtag pc pyramid scheme it'll be like an arg no one will know like
just like a storm of videos hits starts hitting youtube you know tag wait can you tag people on
youtube you can't can you no you can't you can put you can put their twitter name in the title
and when it tweets it out they'll get hat mentioned on twitter okay that's something yes yes um
all right you know you can choose you can choose uh you can choose whether you want to be a silver
member um who's just who's just tweeting or if you want to be a gold member and be a member of the
of the pc uh president's club hashtag pc president's club yeah you you make make a video and tweet at
the pc people who are gonna make video responses and they gotta tag five more yeah we're gonna be rich
guys where does the money come from exactly um i it'll it'll come it'll come it'll come no the money
is gonna come from drugs like once everyone's excited about pc pyramid scheme then we start selling
selling crack cocaine to kids everybody would be on drugs and everybody would be asking what is
hashtag pc pyramid scheme they're gonna look us up they're gonna uh they're gonna say oh i love this
podcast they're gonna go on the patreon they're gonna go pay loads of money and uh that's how
we're gonna grow as a channel oh and should just make a reward tier that is the pc president's club
so when everyone hears this one they'll be oh that's a good idea include include uh include um at
tpcrastinators in your uh in your pc pyramid schemes tweet yes please yes well it'll have a
hashtag pc pyramid scheme so yeah we can search for that okay okay well i just meant so people
i just meant so people would know that it's this is our this is our scam and um and we're the one
we can get immediately arrested when they figure out what we're doing
yes this is good this is good i like this i i like where our heads at gentlemen i think we've
got big things coming to us um is that it oh wait wait no no you gotta link our patreon you gotta
link every we we don't have to go viral oh yeah of course oh and make and make sure to fake it till
you make it tweet tweet hashtag pc pier tweet hashtag pc pyramid scheme and talk about and talk
about how now that you now that you watch the pcp uh now that you're getting all these sweet bonus
episodes through our patreon your um your your your life is so much better uh you're being paid
you're being paid every fucking minute of every day are we rebranding the bonus episode tier as
the pc president's club is that what's happening right now that'll be the sub name that's the sub
name oh yeah i've got it i've got it the you're being paid in attention we're gonna pay attention
to your tweets yeah you gotta find five people who will pay you attention and then they'll find
five people who will pay them attention uh yeah it's brilliant it's it's it's gonna work guys what
we're selling what we're selling what we're selling in this multi-level marketing company is mind
share in the public zeitgeist that's right that's right we're selling that's our current age of
social media what is more valuable than attention not money i'll tell you that much not a damn thing
not a damn thing we'll pay you an exposure it's it's it's it's oh yeah this whole this whole scheme
is just it's just it's an exposure is just traveling up the line just just like more exposure being
paid to your upline and they're paying their upline and on and on until it all reaches us
and we become legendary viral superheroes fantastic that's the end goal but don't tell anyone
we're doing we're this we're we're gonna pretend we're doing a public service but we won't say
what that service is the pc public service pc public service the pc ps we got the pc pc the pc ps
what else uh the the pc pc d the pc b e i don't know these are all the sacred words of our viral
marketing campaign words of power attack kill destroy these words used by an elite group of
online hackers known as the pc okay all right uh so there you go we've rolled out our whole
whole operation we've really we've really made a lot of progress we banged out a whole business model
in what like 40 minutes yes yeah yeah and it's not a joke it's not a joke you have to do it if
you're watching this i'm gonna do this when this fucking video goes live of course this video will
be tweeted with the hashtag pc pyramid scheme oh the hashtag should be edited into the video
covering most of the this is the first video of the gold tier is is making a video with
hashtag pc pyramid scheme yeah yeah the publicly available one to to to get him in to get him on
board yeah yeah give him a taste show show everyone how much better your lives can be with uh with
hashtag pc pyramid scheme in your life all right well with that said uh i feel like we're good let's
how about we go over to questions now i think we're all set any any final points to make about
pyramid schemes in general uh don't do them not right not recommended oh i i did just want to say
that my only exposure to one was uh in um uh welcome to the nhk welcome to the nhk or i though
there was a simpsons one too but when uh that lady uh was doing it and it looked real spooky uh so
don't do it it's not good oh and sato like the main character bought into him yeah they're really
sad the way they pray on like vulnerable weak people is like the most evil thing in the world so
yeah don't so remember all of our audience please hash treat the hashtag pc pyramid scheme that's
what you are you're not vulnerable at all oh yeah i changed my mind do them do them do them all
start starting now start while you're young well that's what makes our special ours is the one
that's not like that ours is really good and remember it's multi-level marketing it's not a
pyramid scheme hashtag pc pyramid scheme that's what they do by the way the the the the the the
biggest repeated phrase in mlm is like it's not a pyramid scheme pyramid schemes are illegal and
what we're doing is legal so clearly it's not a pyramid scheme guys that's our quote that's our
that's our um our catch phrase that's our story and we're sticking to it hashtag not illegal
excellent a gig were you saying something about this uh only that i've never seen a human being do
this in my life i've only ever heard about it i mean no one's ever approached me to say uh please
buy some matches or something i one there was a traumatic event in my life that was directly
related to a pyramid scheme so i was at a football game and there were a bunch of cheerleaders and they
started climbing on each other's shoulders and it was it got more horrible it just they formed
this triangular shape right in front of me oh god i couldn't fucking deal with it yeah i what a
fucking scam there was there was a time scheme it wasn't it wasn't those crappy sluts i hate them
to make that pyramid that's for they were they had designs it wasn't a pyramid scheme per se but
there was another time that i got called by a company that wanted me to come and listen to a
pitch for a fucking time share you guys know about time shares a little bit you sort of you buy property
and then rent it to other people is the gist i think the idea is that you're renting a property but
you're renting it collectively with like other people so you're so you're paying rent on this
you're paying rent on this property but you're only paying for it for like you know like one
month out of the year or something like that so like you you make money from this or is it just for
your enjoyment no i think you're maybe supposed to i just i don't know i i really like to rent
that house i can't live in it but you know that'll be fun the pitch gotta be a money thing it's got
it's not no that for the person owning that property that sounds amazing because you can
definitely charge more than just regular rent yeah adventure you get it from 12 different people
you're like making twice normal rent on the property you own oh my god people with money
are so privileged i hate them all people with money are so dumb what are they doing the pitch for
time shares is like uh like imagine being able to say i've got a little place in the swiss Alps
because like for one month out of the year so you can go on like holiday for one month and
just lie or whatever just i guess it makes you can just lie you can just lie yeah oh yeah you
don't have to buy it to say that nobody said yeah but i got fly to the fucking swiss Alps no
i'm just gonna but i got but i got called by a timeshare company and like they were they gave
me this song and dance about like oh we've got a big opportunity for you and at some point i
realized it was a timeshare it was so i was like i was wise so they were like so will will you be
attending and i was like i'm gonna fuck these guys and i was like yeah reserve that chair for
you guys make make sure nobody make sure not to extend this invitation to anyone else i'm gonna
be there but i think monster but i think they knew master puppeteer you no i think they could
tell from my tone because the lake because my tone changed and the ladies started being like um so
and i was like yep i'm gonna be there i'm good because i went from i went from skeptical to
like full-on enthusiasm and i think she knew something was off right but i did my but i did
my best i i own an entire tectonic plate guys come visit for one for in the middle of the
pacific ocean for one sixteenth of a second out of each year i own the continent of australia
yes excellent you're the king all right let's uh let's go to our questions everybody let's
okay here we go um uh the okay here's here's one that i don't understand why it's here at
meaty learner 509 asks on average how many times does this guy ever say sorry okay on average how
many times per day does best guy ever say haha well all right that's pretty pretty much constantly
i don't do i say that is that like a um you just said it right now that's true it definitely
sounds like the kind of thing you say it's the number of haze is very specific yeah only two you
can't have more than that uh i would give it 20 20 times per day that seems reasonable uh oh is
somebody checking the uh the the patron one for questions oh these are from the twitter obviously
i actually see a good one here from our at our at underscore who asks what the fuck constitutes a
good question hey that is an excellent question that we so there you go just be like just ask
this question and uh you're safe yep there you go that's the answer to that one um a good a good
question uh is not some meme shit like a good question like actually demands some like discussion
to come to an answer uh a good a good question is something that like one or more of us is
actually interested in addressing yeah and also uh nothing ever to do with favorites yeah
basically basically a good question is a question that we couldn't answer on twitter itself it has
to be more than 140 characters requiring the answer so we can actually get into it and actually think
a little bit as opposed to just being like what's your favorite anime that's yeah that's i got to
say that what's your favorite anime is the worst question it is the worst question that you can
possibly ask uh like a lot of people ask questions that are like the meme that currently makes them
giggle let's ask about that's like i mean someone tweeted here like death grips is online like i
know that's a meme going on right now and i know death grips are cool and all uh i guess that was
a little bit better because it is kind of like a but what are but what are we supposed to what are
we supposed to say about that exactly that's what makes it a yeah if the punchline is the question
instead of the answer then you fucked up yeah i would say that's fair but then again there was
exceptions to everything so if you just have like a genius idea then shoot it out but you know
you'd see it better be a genius or i'm gonna skip fucking it you can take that risk if you want but
you you risk public ridicule for everyone to hear so indeed step forward brave so well here here's a
kind of a question by fado on the fado on the patreon lounge uh is there a difference between
favorite and best absolutely uh no some people say there isn't but i've always disagreed with that
i think that if you wait i i feel like deja vu i feel like i argued this a long time ago vehemently
and was furious about it for weeks i think that's true i think but i don't remember when but my
position my position on this is that if you think something if something is your favorite that means
that to you it is the best so like to to to be like oh well this thing is my like i like to me
this is the best but like i really it's not the best like the best is this other thing because
other people see it this way like that's bullshit like that's just being fucking dishonest is that
true across all categories yeah i think so i don't think it's a true across categories well dealing
with like uh like um observable facts and figures and stuff like okay which is yeah if you're talking
about if you're talking about like i don't know some medicine or something and maybe like some medicine
in like 90 of cases has no adverse side effects and is great but to you it has adverse side effects
like sure you can be like yeah like well this doesn't work for me like like to me this other
medicine is better but in but okay but if we're talking if we're talking about statistical stuff
we're talking about art but if we're talking about art and opinions i think it's really
disingenuous to be like this one's my favorite but i think this one is better but not for me
like whatever i agree with ben on this with with regards to art i feel like there's no
like like think of it think of an example where it would not sound weird like who are you to
who are you to speak on behalf of the general population no you can only speak for yourself
on these matters you can okay like uh if there's a show that you like because you were a kid and
you really liked it so you have like a personal attachment to it but as you've got older like
for me the bible black english dub is horrendous but i love it it's like my favorite thing in the
world uh uh it's like it's like the best dub ever to me even though there are dubs like i don't know
bakano or whatever they're like technically wonderful but like i like the bible black dub
because it's so fucked up and retarded like it's clear which of those is better but i like the
bible black one because it's got this you know special thing that i like about it what about
that business well i mean it's one thing to recognize that more people like another thing
than than your favorite thing but like what's the point of being like okay well well this one's
my favorite but this other one that other people like that one's technically better like what's the
fucking point we have to define the word best we have to define the word best personal preference
those are two different things i think i think instead of saying your favorite yeah yeah those
are those are two different things but like why would you use why would you so you you got to
fucking specify okay hang on all right yeah what are you saying i think the way it should be is that
because like a lot of people us included say oh man that's the best thing i've ever seen
we don't actually mean like best we're not thinking of it like that we're just saying i really really
like it right it's um so i feel like if you're talking if you're going to say uh this is what's
considered the best you just say this is the consensus masterpiece this is consensus favorite
and but this one's the best this because you're trying to convince people usually
yeah i feel like i feel like best and favorite are interchangeable
i see i think we all understand what the word favorite means it's just like the thing that
you get the most enjoyment out of you like the most if we're just talking about art you know
as one subcategory but i think we need to define the word best i think that's
entirely where the problem lies in this discussion so what do we actually mean when
we say best here like the one that the most people like yeah me uh but is the one that
the most people like as in it's like it's got the on average highest score or is it the most
technically provisioned i think the scientists would say this is the most perfectly perfect
thing i think the best would be technical proficiency okay you know like this is the best
art like the most like technically proficient whatever yeah this is my favorite style there's
like there's like tears there's like very obvious tears um within which there's like very you know
like there's the stuff that's like really well done but it's uh what's the best it comes a lot
down to personal preference and then this thing whoa you said what's the best comes to personal
preference but isn't best some sort of objective all right i'm saying oh lord okay what i'm saying
is what i'm saying is there are say video games there are games that are just broken and don't
work and nobody likes them and uh then there are games that are you know really really good
but nobody not a single like there's no consensus on what is the best so the word best is kind of
meaningless and it's interchangeable with favorite when you're saying like what's the best of a series
of games that are all brilliant like nobody will ever agree so best and favorite will be interchangeable
in that situation but if you're comparing like okay um something that just doesn't work with
something that is really good then there is a clear usage of well this is better i guess i guess my
my perspective on it has always been that the best is referring to technical measurable
quant like aspects of a work and favorite is just like emotional like how you feel i think
that's something that makes sense i don't i don't think it makes sense to judge
our based on technical proficiency use best as a substitute for favorite but i think that the
way it is is like the the the closer you get to the um the the mythical best thing um the less
useful the word best becomes because people stop agreeing with each other i think i think using
the word best to describe an opinion is worthless because it doesn't mean anything but if you're
talking about best in terms of a quantifiable aspect it totally makes sense and and how do we
deal with the issue of ironic enjoyment of things like my bible black dub that's like my favorite
like i like that basically ironically it was not intended to be good but it is good and like the
room and shit like that's a whole like best versus favorites when you consider that shit like those
are on the opposite side of the spectrum people people still use the word best when they say oh
it's the best worst thing ever i would say the room is like but but if i like the room is like
my favorite movie which it is one of and i then like it totally would not be even close to like
the best movie ever made but it is among my favorites i think like how do you get that i think
that even if you're enjoying something ironically if you're getting the most enjoyment out of it out
of all the things then yeah it's your it should be your favorite thing so even if it like accidentally
became entertaining it good like the room then like it still it still is what it is and you can
judge it by like i really really think that it all just comes down to how much enjoyment do i get
out of this thing and like looking at it from like oh well what's technically the best what's
done what's most popular i think those things are like i don't see the point in evaluating a works
when somebody when somebody has uh like when somebody has a best and they say it's the best
technically i i don't feel anything from their recommendation because it's not their favorite
i i think what what it comes down to is that the the technical best is kind of useless for me
because i don't get the sense that like i don't know what they mean i don't know it's it's it's
hard to explain i had a point i think i see what you're saying yeah like yeah best if you're if
you're talking about art what's the point of knowing which is the best wouldn't you rather
know someone's favorite because like that's the one they actually liked more so you know what
who fucking cares what's the best art i mean i see where that's coming from i just i just don't
think the word makes any sense if it doesn't yeah what tom was saying it means and it's like some
sort of yeah but the thing is people people just use it like that i think i think people
use the word best incorrectly all the time because i don't think the best talks about
subjective opinion i mean eventually best is going to mean favorite because of the way people
are continually using it wrong right because basically the moral of the story is everyone's
fucking retarded except for us the moral of the story to me is that language is way too fucking
imprecise and it's incredibly frustrating because the whole point of our argument here
is that we don't agree on what the words mean and if we did this is why this is why language
has to be replaced with hip thrusts and funny poses that's the only real language whoa funny
poses is that a jojo reference dude what the fuck is that it's a meme i don't know i was thinking
i don't get it it's people people will get it they'll give you force um oh those are good
those are good guys would you want to pick another question i think that's all right i
forgot i think i think we've run this one into the ground ladies and gentlemen that's an example
of a good question yeah it was yeah that was insights debate because it's like who couldn't
who couldn't know the truth hey here's a question from at on twitter at lamp pros from g r yeah okay
asks uh do you like horror films if yes any expectations for the upcoming movie it i do
not really like it sucks so uh yeah no i just wanted to say it sucks oh make a video with
as the title it's not out yet so uh i think it is i will believe it a couple people i follow on
twitter saw it and they said it was amazing oh okay okay well it was amazing did they huh they
said it was like any the general consensus from what i can tell us that's the best even king adaptation
are you i just saw the dark tower dude and that was a 10 out of 10 i didn't actually see it uh
i have no i don't care about horror really it scares me i'm not a horror fan at all it's either
scary or boring oh okay well dude that's the thing okay so i i hated horror for a million years until
i played silent hill two and three and now i have found myself well games are different games are
different because uh like i love resident evil one on playstation uh i haven't played any other
versions uh you know i i'm sure it is but like it's it's just like the fact that i can i haven't
played resident evil nothing will happen unless you said better and i'm just arguing that best
and better only means technical things you fucking pass it you fool uh like like like
the thing with a game a horror game is uh it's all down to you you have to push forward
it's sort of like like like like in a movie when somebody when somebody's about to open a thing
and you and you tense up and you say no don't go in there you are the guy who is not going to go
in there but you have to do it to complete it's like the tension is so much higher because you
have to do it oh right it is yeah all right right that's why silent hill is so fucking
super works way better in games than it does in movies for sure you know because then it's
it's about you it's happening to you i just watched um it follows the other day which i
thought was it was like more artsy than it was like horrific though it was pretty scary um yeah i
think after i play sound hill like i do have more of a taste for them and i i'm enjoying the more
i i said before that i don't like horror movies but not too long ago i watched one called creep
have any of you seen it no no it creep it it's it's it's really great it's really fucking great
it's not there's it's not some like ghost some ghost story bullshit um it's not there's there's
jump scares but like they are there for a reason and they make sense in the fiction why there would
be a jump scare okay and it's it's it's really unlike any other horror movie i've seen before and
it's really fucking good and it's like it's like funny too like like this like the situation is
scary intense but it's also kind of like funny and absurd in a way how old is this film uh not
less than a decade i think like it's not okay it's not recent but it's not old either at least i
don't think so yeah i i highly recommend uh creep so um yeah but that doesn't say anything about it
i don't care about it i'm not gonna see it oh i right i forgot about it um i i had recently
watched actually the the entire old like adaptation of the of the old uh you know it adaptation or
whatever that had uh tim curry and shit and uh i i quite liked that even though it's been
memed on a lot with the the balloons and the clowns and you know all that crazy shit i quite
like that and uh i was definitely not i mean i'm sure it was in the camp of most people thinking
like i mean i i'm well known to hate uh uh remakes and shit and that's what this is so
can't say i was really looking forward to it but i am sort of interested to see because i just like
horror movies now and uh i don't know like this guy looks kind of cool and i'm just curious to see
if it does well and whoever just said that it's been getting good reviews like that's the first
i've heard of its actual quality so i probably will go see it and uh yeah yeah i'm kind of excited to
see it i just i just hate being afraid because i'm constantly afraid of my own inevitable demise
so i don't need to add to that fear so i i agree generally the feeling of being spooked is not a
pleasant one that i don't know not at all it's creep didn't spook me well i guess it kind of i
don't know it i i didn't mind the feeling it gave me i like i like the feeling of being spooked
where my retarded reaction can entertain other people like my blood like i used to play resident
evil uh with my brother in the room and you know he would just look at me going ah because he was
for some reason like like better at dealing with it and it was just it was just like the
dogs burst through the window and every single time i jumped and i screamed and it was hilarious
and i like the fact that that was funny and then it was like a really it was really nice after
we were like oh phew are you are you picking another question name no no no just i have a
question about this topic and it was just where horror films invented to to to force teenagers
to sex each other is that what they you know you know what i'm saying do you mean to force them
to sex each other in the films or to force them to sex each other in the theaters in the theater in
the theaters is this a breeding scheme you know to make them spooked and i don't think they were
invented for that but they've been co-opted by teenagers and we need to we need to take them back
because we need to wage war i agree they have which would you not agree i mean i've only watched a
few horror films is not my thing but would you not agree that the pg-13 rating is the kiss of death
for a horror film um enough to say but it seems that way let me let me look and see what creep was
rated you know i actually i just downloaded um uh what's the one about uh uh god i don't want to
say but the one about the black people that came out recently you know i'm talking about uh get out
the family get out get out i swear guys it's it's just that's the distinguishing characteristic
for the film um but yeah like i downloaded that and i've been wanting to watch it but then i think
back to my experience when i'm watching um uh when i when i was watching uh uh fuck is that
is it it follows yeah it was it follows and like so that movie was good but then i remember the
moment to moment experience of watching it as i'm like wanting to die because like okay so the the
scary thing in that movie is like there is a creature it or whatever that just it follows you
but it walks very slowly but the thing is it can take on the appearance of anyone at any time
so like in a crowd it could be any of the people there uh and you get it by like having sex with
someone who's like it's following currently it doesn't matter but like oh the spooks oh the spooks
really got to me it was uh oh it was painful like that's like the pain of watching but it's the release
that comes when you get like you get through it and you're okay and you can reflect on it that
feels that feels good i like that creep creep is rated r although i think it pretty easily could
have been a pg 13 so i had dude what if because you were saying about ratings i just had this idea
what if just like spicy curries and stuff the the spooky things would have a rating system
instead of scoville units or whatever it is it'll be like spookville units and how it is
will be denominated by little little ghost emojis next to the thing and if it's got five
either change you want to see in the world dude lal i i i would like that it's like it's
oh it's only got two two ghosts on that on the spookville rating that's not scary enough for me
uh that that's good uh well we're basically out of questions on the twitter we got any
others that's not true i'm looking at the twitter right now and i want to answer this one from aj
case 997 uh you're on a deserted island with one other pcp member who do you take munchie
no one to survive well well you what you're stranded on a pc on on an island you get to
have one other pcp member with with you who do you take munchie there's no question there's no
yeah mage i'll fight you too late you have munchie all right fine uh can i take another of myself
that's that's what i would take if i could oh of course
i really am the best boy oh my god i can imagine i can imagine you just jump the
stuff i ever just jumped the shard i forgive me everyone uh okay i i'm out of questions on here
do we have any others to answer in the in the thing oh it's terrible here's a question i want to
know the answer to uh funky asks hippo will you ever talk about jack x um maybe i have played it
but i'm not enough to have an opinion yet wait a minute hold the presses everybody oh actually
sorry finish your finish your point that i'll that i'll respond i'm sorry no my point's done
okay it was just uh i see an important question here by malady on the patreon lounge uh the thing
it's just how can i throw money at the pcp oh my god everybody go on over to patreon.com
slash the procrastinators you've got a great great question great question best one i've heard so
far that's an ideal question that is perfect that is perfect uh uh yeah pledge pledge money guys if
you have pledged a dollar i think is the minimum to get into the patreon lounge where we where we
check for questions here that uh you know we we look there more closely than on the twitter
and you can buy what else oh yeah five dollars to get into the bonus episodes there's four no
there's six out now including the death note one we just did uh we got t-shirts available there's
a link in the description we get money from that shit and i think that's everything hashtag pc
pyramid scheme hashtag pcp president's club yes wait wait wait before we end um i need a pressing
question from uh at santita mulis on twitter uh are you going to throw a turning 30 party for ben
i don't know guys are you well i'll get back to you in what like eight months or whatever when
it's your birthday again we'll see you're gonna you're gonna have to you're gonna have to start
planning before then you guys are gonna have to really really big old bash we're gonna we're
ben's gonna walk into the room we're gonna shout surprise as we all gather around the center
piece of the grand guillotine in the center of the room we know what you really want for your
birthday bed you guys you guys really you guys really know what i'm about his head just gonna
roll is gonna look up at nape like you really are the best guy and they innate nods nape nods
knowing his turn is coming oh that would be great and then one day you know in like 10 years or
whatever when we all turn 30 only munchie will remain as the sole surviving member and then it'll
be his job to decapitate the he'll just he'll just wear a necklace of our skulls yeah i would
expect nothing less he'd wear he'd wear them around around his wrists like a like a little bracelet
on his giant meaty hand on his gigantic figure that's true as as our power levels dissipate
they will be absorbed by munchie as we're all executed internally he will only grow more
massive in size as uh yeah as as he does that shit all right well that's it everybody we're
all done before we go i just want to reiterate again hashtag pc pyramid scheme uh tweet it tweet
about how great your life is tweet about how how how thankful you are for the opportunity to watch the
pcp how you're your own man and how you're making a sustainable living by watching the pcp
hashtag pc presidents club make videos showing how rich you are how many how many material
goods you've accumulated how much wealth you've achieved with the help of the pcp
tweeted at everyone tweeted at five people and they are obligated to do the same or we
you will at least five tweets on your tweet and just remember to fake it till you make it
even if you don't get it the first time don't don't get discouraged you're rich you're rich from
watching the pcp they can be too if they just hit that retweet button make that video how the the
mere payment of five dollars to get into the pc presidents club has been so so quickly recouped
by the paying attention that we've been doing you made you made that money back tenfold yes
exactly at least don't be afraid to no nobody hates an exaggerator you know they're the most
celebrated people you made that money back tenfold in exposure hey exactly put that parentheses
and in small font you may not be rich but we have enriched your lives exactly okay that's it
everybody go go and do that shit and send us more questions down twitter use hashtag ask pcp
we review them here we'll answer them and there you go go to the patreon buy our shirts etc etc
thanks everybody and we'll see you next week bye
yeah uh
Seoul I am a stupid I've got a deadline don't want to do the with