Nobody knows who I really am. I never felt this empty before. And if I ever need someone to come along, who's gonna comfort me and keep me strong.
Hello and welcome to this week's episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. Today is a post-mortem episode of farewell to Swartz and hello to Scalymans.
It's the end of Bleach and we're here to say goodbye.
There's also Scalymans who we won't see anymore. So it's me, the best boy, with Endless Jess, and Gibboshit.
That's me.
It looks like a nightmare. I pray that Bleach is wiser and just lets sleeping dogs lie and let's it be buried in peace.
Knowing the nature of Shonen Jump, they probably won't. But we'll see.
Anyway, so why don't we just first touch on what we thought about the actual ending.
Just like these summary chapters, and we can talk about the last arc, we can talk about the legacy and the continuing opinions we had of Bleach as it went on.
But to start, I was personally pretty okay with the way things ended. I thought there was pretty much nothing else they could do other than just show this person sexed.
This person, they had some kids. This is what, like 10 years later I think. They have some kids rolling around.
Karen has teats.
Karen's got some massive fucking honkers and it's awesome. She was always the sexiest one.
And, you know, we all share-
Why would they ruin a perfectly good lolly by having her age 10 years and giving her 10 years?
That's really disgusting, honestly.
That's a good question.
It makes me sad.
I'm a little tired of the cliche of ending a series with 10 years later, you know, whatever is happening.
I don't know. I don't really have a better solution. I just am annoyed that they all do that.
Harry Potter did it. Fucking Bleach did it. Just everything in the world does it all the time.
Avatar didn't do it.
Let's be creative people.
Avatar did not. Avatar was great. That's exactly how Avatar should have ended.
Well, it's because they spend like 700 chapters. They forget to like develop the characters throughout the story.
So at the very last moment they're like, oh shit, I guess we should do that all at once in the last chapter.
Here's 20 years later they've all got kids.
But you know, nothing amazing happened. Ichigo has married Orihime and they have a son.
We all saw that coming a mile away.
Repulsive. Absolutely repulsive. She was always the worst girl.
What the hell happened to Tatsuki? Where is Tatsuki?
She's here. She's finally back.
No, she's not.
I want to bring to your attention the fact that, first of all, I like the fact that at the beginning,
when Ichigo was getting his powers, it was really cool.
And then all his friends were getting powers and I was like, oh cool, they're going to get powers too.
And Tatsuki was the best girl.
Tatsuki and that long-haired dude got fucking shit.
They were supposed to have powers. I know it. And they just didn't get them.
Because he ran out of time. They got screwed, man.
They got screwed.
But I was like holding out hope that she was just going to be later.
And something was going to happen that she was finally getting to the mix.
Because she had a really cool character design.
There was a whole arc where they just talk about the origins of Chad's and Orihime's powers as full-bringers.
They could have so easily just snuck Tatsuki and that dude in there.
And just said, oh, they got powers too. They're full-bringers.
But he just didn't.
Instead, we got a bunch of characters that nobody likes.
So Tatsuki got the fucking shaft. She's often a fucking dumpster somewhere shooting up crack.
Speaking of Tatsuki getting the shaft, is she sexing that dude?
They're together a lot and they're fighting, which is very Japanese-couple-y.
I think they're doing the dude.
I hope so. I hope she's sexing somebody. I hope she finds some degree of happiness in her now worthless, empty Ichigo-less wife.
Hey, you know who wasn't in this ending chapter?
Where's the red-haired girl who used to grab Orihime's tits? Where is she?
She probably got AIDS.
I liked her.
Lesbian AIDS.
She got it. Yeah, she got lesbian AIDS.
That's true.
But yeah, Tatsuki, she's completely out of the comic and just not even there.
She was going for like 200 chapters or something.
And then right on this last chapter, she's in exactly two panels, but the thing that really annoys...
Really?
Yeah, only two panels and the thing that really annoys me is the second panel.
There's like a text balloon that's covering her face when there's plenty of room in the top left corner of that panel.
She's watching TV.
The last insult, Kubo.
And she can't even fucking see her face.
I'm so angry.
Well, you know, okay, to be a little fair, at least she was in the color spread.
That's a nice color spread.
I'm still angry.
And she's hidden by...
Yeah, she's like, I'm yelling at my boyfriend over there, who I'm obviously in love with.
Hey, that dude is there, that cool dude who used to have sex with all the girls.
That really short guy.
That's cool, I guess.
I like that Uryu is just like hidden.
Look at Orihime and her fucking gross apron, like a fat old busted mom.
She's like 20 years old.
She's like she's 50.
She's doing that like Asian woman aging thing where they go from 20 to 50 instantly.
I hate her.
She looks fine.
What are you talking about?
She looks happy.
She's content.
Ichigo became a doctor, dude.
He's making that bank.
I've always hated Orihime.
She's just tits.
She really is just tits.
Remember the whole arc with Ulkiyora and like, oh, I'm developing this like relationship
with Ulkiyora, my bodyguard.
It's like a weird thing, but I didn't care.
I wandered dead the whole time.
It's not cool.
Tatsuki, I mean, okay, let's just get the elephant out of the room.
Ichigo belongs to the Rukia.
That should have been, that should, like, okay, I understand.
Renji and Rukia are a good couple.
Ichigo, Orihime's, I'm sure she sexes Ichigo plenty.
That's fine.
But really the best, the 10 out of 10 relationship here should have been Ichigo and Rukia.
You know, I don't know.
I'm in support of the Rukia and Renji thing because, I mean, Renji has just eaten shit
throughout the entire series.
Yeah, that's true.
It would have just been like one final insult.
They haven't get cucked by Ichigo at the very end.
I'm glad he got something.
There's something about the way Renji is designed.
Ichigo does not deserve Rukia, so you're right.
Renji and Rukia, they belong together, okay.
Yeah, but there's something about the way Renji was always designed that made him feel like
a surrogate main character, like he was almost the main character guy
in terms of like just design and powers and coolness.
Like he would have been the main character if Ichigo hadn't existed,
but because Ichigo does exist, Renji just jobs out to everyone constantly.
They're very similar.
Only Renji is cooler in every way.
Yeah.
You know, he's got cooler tats.
He's got sweet glasses.
He's got a fucking snake sword.
His fucking sword turns into a whip.
What more do you want?
What happened to that baboon guy?
It was a baboon that he turned his sword into a baboon.
It was Renji's sword, but remember, okay, remember how they started doing this thing?
God, please.
In the anime, they had that whole filler arc where the swords turned on people.
They had to fight their own swords, but then his sword wasn't a baboon snake anymore.
What kind of a world is it where a man has to fight his own sword?
What have we fallen to, Kubo?
What is this hell we're living in?
I thought you were going to say, what is this world?
Existential nightmare after another.
Wait, what were you saying, Gib?
I thought you were going to say, what does this world come to when a man has to fight his own baboon?
Which I thought was a lot funny.
A baboon with a snake tail.
You can't even trust your own baboon anymore.
It's Planet of the Apes.
It all started with Rukia's, I mean, Renji's sword.
Hey, you know what was great about Bleach?
That Rukia got a bonkai, and it was the coolest bonkai ever.
She was icy.
She was white.
She was beautiful.
She was pure.
Just the fact that Kubo lasted long enough to make that happen makes Bleach worthwhile.
Yeah, and she became a captain.
Thank God.
She's accomplished something.
She's captain 13, man.
Her captain died that sad, but he was kind of an asshole anyway.
But she's picking up where he left off.
Oh, it's great.
She's getting that fly white coat.
Oh, God.
And she was blushing.
She was so proud, but she was looking forward to her future.
She's got a bright-ass future ahead of her, and I can't wait to see it.
Oh, wait, I won't.
It's okay, though, because I can imagine it, and that's all I want for the end of the series.
No, no, you can read the sequel series with their little snot-nosed punk kids.
Wait, is the sequel to Bleach detergent?
Ooh.
Is that what it's going to be?
What do you do with Bleach?
You put it in clothes to remove the stains.
Okay, let's sell this right now.
Let's sell this right now for the ages.
Why is it called Bleach?
Is it because of Ichigo's hair color?
No, that was a thing he said.
He named it after Nirvana, something or other.
Oh, that's right.
Can you explain that in a little more detail?
I forget.
I don't know.
I heard it sometime.
Why is it called Bleach?
Well, Nirvana's first album was called Bleach.
Yeah, and he said he named it after Nirvana.
Okay, that's it.
It's named after Nirvana.
Okay, we're done.
Let's never bring it up again.
All right, one thing I want to talk about is how the last boss, Yohwach, or whatever
he's called.
Yohwach.
No one in the world can pronounce that name.
No, for coming up with that name that no one could ever pronounce.
It's like Y-W-A-C-H-K.
I think it's supposed to be.
There was not even an anime at that point to tell us how to pronounce it, so no one
will ever know.
Yes, that's true.
Why did the anime end already?
Wait, wait, wait.
Yeah, the anime ended a long time ago.
I forgot that Japan is a superior culture that writes its words phonetically.
So I'm going to look it up right now and we will know exactly how to pronounce it.
I still don't really even know why and how Ichigo won in the end.
Yeah, I have no idea what happened.
I just showed up and said, I tricked you.
And then he was like, oh shit, that gets to trick me.
And then he died.
That was it.
Okay, I'm reading it right now.
His name is you.
Oh my god, this isn't even fucking legible.
Oh god.
Okay, it's you-ha-ba-ah.
That's what it says.
There's a B in there.
There's a B.
Oh, it must be the W sound.
It's like-
You-fwa.
This is fucking ridiculous.
That's silly.
You-ha-ba-ah.
I think it's like some German name or something.
Oh wait, wait.
You-ha-ba-ah.
Whatever.
It's Retire.
It's the worst name ever.
Also, by the way, so this guy was like the man Zangetsu inside Ichigo all along.
That's so stupid.
That makes me mad too.
Fuck it.
That was retarded.
It's like, yeah, everybody's got their own sword and the swords have people inside them
and everyone's got, like, his is a fucking baboon and Ichigo's is like this cool guy
with sunglasses standing on a sideways building.
That's the coolest shit ever.
And then you get like halfway through the series and it's like, no, actually that's not it.
He's actually like a Quincy guy because Ichigo's also a Quincy and also-
Yeah.
He's also the main bad guy and also, I guess there is no guy inside of his sword.
What?
Like the hollow one was like his real power or something.
What is that?
Why isn't everyone's sword just another them?
Are the Shinigami also hollow people?
To be honest, this is where I lost track of what the fuck was going on.
You know, this is like the Heartless all over again.
The Heartless don't have hearts but the Nobodies don't have hearts but they do have bodies.
Okay, no, that's just a matter of terminology.
It's very simple.
This is actually incredibly complex and makes no sense.
Heartless and Nobodies make sense and I'll explain it to the world one day.
The promise day.
I don't quite know.
Well, I'll do a Kingdom Hearts series and one episode will be explaining what the fuck is going on with Heartless and Nobodies.
I don't know what the confusion is yet but I haven't played the second in the series.
Oh yeah, it's pretty clear in the first one.
I mean the card Heartless-
In the first one it's just like these are black guys.
Kill them.
Kill black guys.
It gets the story of Kingdom Hearts.
Kingdom Hearts 1 could not have been simpler and that was a big strength.
I know now.
Without a doubt, Kingdom Hearts is white.
Yeah, so I was going to say that like, so one of the things about Bleach is that it had massive, like in game terminology you'd say feature creep.
Like they just kept adding like, you could call them, they're all like mini games.
They're just like extra like little gameplay mechanics.
Like we got the visards now.
I think it wasn't so much the different types of people but they're just the sheer amount of all the different types of people but they're just the sheer amount.
Of all the different types of people that just kept being relevant.
I was going to say.
Like they were all the same amount of relevant which is like, ended up with nobody being interesting.
Right, that's a big problem.
Yeah, and it really is kind of like what Kingdom Hearts 2, I mean Kingdom Hearts 2 is the greatest game ever made.
But Bleach does share similarities with it in that it absolutely increased complexity.
Like every time.
Like all these like weird new power sets that don't make any sense.
Yeah.
Like again, like at first it was-
Fullbringers still make almost no sense.
They're so simple at first like they've got a sword and then the sword turns into another sword but then it can turn into a super sword.
There's three stages.
And that's all, that's great.
Bonkai's instantly in the world fell in love with Bonkai's and said, I want to see every character's bonkai.
That's all you needed.
Even by the end of the series still all anyone cared about on the forums and stuff was like, who's we got to see everyone's bonkai before it ends?
That's all anyone cares about.
That's the only thing that kept me going.
It is.
And like you were saying before, the fact, yeah.
Yeah, they're like, but then all of a sudden it's like, oh but now Ichigo has a new power set and he's a new kind of person.
And he's a half breed cross Quincy Fullbringer fucking five time judo champion soul guy.
And it's like what's happening?
He's got like a new sword.
Now he's got like two swords that are different from his original sword.
So now he's got a whole new set to learn, a whole new bonkai to learn that didn't end up doing anything anyways.
It did nothing.
He went back to his original sword in the last fight.
So what was the point of any of it?
Okay, like to be fair, Bleach got canceled pretty recently.
Like he finally, the axe came out.
It's like Kubo, let's wrap this shit up in like the next two chapters.
So like I feel for Kubo in that I think he was building to something a little bit more than just the like, oh I went back to my true sword.
Like I think he had a little bit more in mind.
It's not his fault, but it also kind of is his fault for taking so long.
It is his fault for just making one, making Bleach take the path that it did, which was fucked up.
And like you were saying, it really all to me comes back to like, everyone in the world agrees that the beginning of Bleach is the best part.
And like you were saying, the fact that everyone has their own like Zanpakhto spirit.
The fact that like Zang- fuck Zangetsu was like this weird old man on the sideways building was so interesting and compelling.
And it like, it made everyone think like, what does this say about Ichigo?
Especially when later you see that,
and by the way, this is like the only other one we see in like the whole series.
So like fuck you Kubo for not exploring it more.
We see Renji's weird baboon snake thing and we're like, whoa, like they don't even have to be human.
Like there's so many possibilities you could do.
There's so much shit you could do with that.
And instead of going into the complexity,
Hang on, hang on.
Yeah, instead of going into the complexity that he already built in by doing that,
he's just like, no, we just need, we need more different powers.
We need full bringers.
We need visors.
We need hollows.
We need all this shit.
And it's like, it did the exact opposite of what he wanted to do.
Instead of making us care more about all the people's cause like,
Ichigo's got like 10 different kinds of powers.
It made us care so much less cause we couldn't keep track of it.
And none of it felt important anymore.
You know, it was a big mistake to go in that direction.
He really should have just deep dived into one, one kind of thing.
Just Zanpak toe powers, man.
And like those fights could have been just as interesting forever,
just with that original set of powers.
Like, once they all have their fucking bonkais,
then it's just like who's gonna train and become the best swordsman
or the best at like the keto shit or how do the different abilities
like rock, paper, scissor with other opponents.
Like that's interesting, but instead it's just this fucking power creep.
It's this, ooh, I don't like it.
These skill trees.
You can tell that he felt that he backed himself to a corner
by like giving Ichigo his bonkais so soon.
And he keeps adding these caveats like,
oh Ichigo's bonkai wasn't it 100% cause he had just gotten it.
Or like, you know, shit like that.
And you know, those are, those are fun.
And I even like Vizards.
I straight up like Vizards.
I think crossing over between Shinigami and Hollow,
I think that is cool.
I think that is interesting and makes sense
because Hollow and Shinigami powers are inherently linked.
But it's, you know, after a certain point just gets to be too much.
All the other shit.
Quincy stuff.
I mean, Quincy's were kind of cool.
I think it was only What's His Face, only Uryu.
That was interesting.
And I'm even okay with bringing in a couple more.
But like, I mean, okay, what even was this like end?
There was just a Quincy world the whole time.
I don't even know.
I completely lost track.
I guess there's a Quincy world.
And we just found out about it.
I still don't even know what Quincy's what are.
I thought they were humans that destroyed demons
instead of sending them along.
Like, okay, Shinigami are dead people.
They are the opposite coin of living people.
What are Quincy's?
I don't know.
I thought they were just a tribe of living people
who were spiritually could see fucking, you know, monsters
and they killed them and stuff.
And they shoot them with bows instead of swords.
It was cool.
But then they have swords too.
But then at the end they're fighting the Quincy's
and some of them like turn into monsters.
There's one of them is a giant bird chicken man.
Like what the fuck is going on?
What are these creatures?
I don't know and I don't care to know.
It was too much.
I couldn't keep track of it.
The best final boss was the giant hollow,
the grand hollow, the really tall guy with a long nose.
You know that guy.
Yeah, the Mano Scrande, I believe.
Yeah, those were the...
They were cool.
They should have been fighting those all the time.
I mean, ever since I saw those,
I've been going to Taco Bell and be like,
hey, where's my Mano Scrande?
Super size me dog.
And they're like, get out of here.
And some of the Bonkai reveals near the end.
They just like petered out and were totally dumb.
Like they introduced this character in the beginning,
this guy Kenpachi.
And like, he doesn't even know how to use his sword,
but he's so strong anyways.
Gosh, can you imagine if he ever figured out
how to actually use a sword?
What would happen?
He'd be the strongest guy ever.
Well, at the end of the series,
he figures it out and he fucking loses.
And that's it.
And that's the last you fucking see of him.
Yeah, that's the last you see.
What happened?
All right, dude.
All right, first of all, get this.
Okay, so there was this whole thing
way back that people probably didn't fucking remember.
Beaches wasn't going on for like 13 years or something.
So at the beginning, when you first see Kenpachi,
after he fights each go and loses,
there's this whole thing about like,
Kenpachi's Riyatsu is like, it's the biggest.
Like he's just the strongest dude.
So his Riyatsu, they say at the time,
is so strong that his sword
is in a constantly released state.
So the fact that later on,
like when we get to the end,
he just, oh no, that was wrong.
He hasn't released it yet.
Now we're going to.
And like, so he does his like Shikai release later on.
And so like, what that feels like to me
is that we were cheated and lied to
at the beginning of the series.
All that interesting drama about how like,
Kenpachi's Zanpakuto had been unsealed
because he couldn't seal it,
because he's so strong.
Those were just lies that Kubo had told us
to make us care about his character.
Or really, he just, you know,
maybe he'd go that direction
or maybe he would like go back on it,
which is what he did.
That's false advertising.
I don't even remember him using his bankai.
I don't remember anything.
Well, they did mention at the beginning
that he just doesn't know its name
and can't talk to it at all.
Right, but that was part of the drama, dude,
that even though he didn't know its name,
even then, he was so strong,
he couldn't help but like have it be released
because he was just that strong.
It was a lie.
And they finally reveal this bankai,
and like, I don't even understand what it did.
It just turned his skin red and made him scarier.
He gets red and he's strong.
And then he got beat up.
So what's the, and then, oh,
and then they did that fucking thing
where, what's her name,
fucking Yachiru or whatever.
Who are you?
No, Yano Unoha, Unoha or something.
No, not Hisaka, the little fucking...
Oh, Yachiru, Yachiru, yeah.
That's what I said.
But yeah, they did the thing where like,
she disappeared, so it's like,
well, maybe she was the spirit of the Zanpakuto
all along, but they didn't follow up on it.
But then, nope.
No, they did follow up on it.
And nope, she's just somebody who's weird
and she's got her own Zanpakuto.
She's just not.
Well, then why does she disappear though?
Because Kuba's a fucking hack.
That's why.
Yeah.
How does a fucking Zanpakuto have its own sword?
Is that like...
Such an asshole, like he's so strong
that it turns out even his sword has a sword.
I wish that were true,
but that would have been awesome.
I figured out Yachiru was the spirit of the Zanpakuto,
but she's just not.
And so, fuck you, Kubo.
That was a cool idea,
and you just completely fucked over it.
So what we have to assume, what we're left with,
based on that, all we can assume is that
Yachiru took her clothes off
and ran off into the woods and was never seen again.
For no reason.
She came back, like, for a little bit
to do something, I don't remember.
I'm gonna look it up right now.
Go on, Gable, I look this up.
All right, I was just gonna say that
the idea of a guy being so powerful
that his sword has a sword
is just a hilarious concept.
That could have been the most
comedic character in the whole thing.
I agree, and I wish that's what happened.
You know what, we need to just come together
as animators and make Bleak,
and we'll do it right this time.
We'll do how the series should have been.
We'll have real skeletons.
We just...
That's when it was missing all along.
It was missing the live action.
Those Ray-Harry-Harry stop motions
and bad skeletons.
That's what it needed.
Okay, I don't know.
Maybe I'm wrong.
Like, it says that Yachiru appears
to Kenpachi in the fucking wiki.
I don't know what the fuck is going on with this character.
Who cares? She's dead.
Do you remember seeing that, like, that
image...
info-image thing that was, like,
trying to explain everything that's going on in Bleach,
and it was, like, a huge thing,
and it just kept scrolling and scrolling.
I still don't get it.
And I remember, there were these pretty cool
power charts that people had put together
that showed, like,
you know, like the different abilities
that individual characters have.
It all funnels to eventually talk about,
like, Ichigo at his peak,
like, at the end of...
You know when he turns, like, black,
and he does, like, the I.M. Zangetsu,
or whatever, like, at that moment,
he had, like, ten different powers
from, like, ten different things all at once.
Or maybe it wasn't that, it was later after he gets his full bringer.
Whatever.
The point is, it was...
It's, like, cool to think about
what, like, what abilities
are going on with the characters, but the problem is
Kubo never does anything with any of them,
interesting, other than, like, this guy is
stronger than that guy, and it's obvious.
And that's it.
The only thing that happens with the abilities
is to show them off in a battle, and then the character
is just sitting around forever.
It's...
It's almost as bad as Fairy Tail,
but at least the art looks nice.
By the way,
uh, remember how Grimjaw
just showed up again?
He's been gone for years. Remember that?
I remember that. I'm never gonna forget that.
He's called Blue Hair. He's cool. I like it.
Bring him back.
He was cool, but didn't he fucking die?
I mean, I thought he did.
Also, wasn't he, like, a bad guy or something?
Why did he, like, suddenly show up to help
Urahara?
Every shown in real...
Everyone who gets beat up by the hero who doesn't die
becomes good. That's just what happens.
Yeah.
It doesn't work outside of Dragon Ball Z most of the time.
They just don't know how to do it.
Also, um, why was, uh...
Why was Kurosuchi never executed
for his millions of crimes against humanity?
Like, it kind of rubs me the wrong way that he's, like,
still allowed to be a Soul Reaper at the end of the series,
considering he, like, mass-tortured,
like, thousands upon thousands of innocent people.
He's, like, the biggest monster in the entire series.
You're talking about...
You're talking about 12 captains, Science Man.
Yeah.
He's the worst killer in the whole series.
Um, yeah.
Kinda.
But because, like, I guess, like, the Soul Society
is just so corrupt to the core, no one minds.
Dude, I'll tell you what it is. I'll tell you what it is.
It's just that I just don't remember that he committed...
Like, I just don't remember what he did.
And yet he's still around doing things,
so I guess it wasn't a big deal.
Like, remember, like, early on, when Urri you fought him,
and he's like, I promise you, I will kill you one day.
But then again, I guess not.
See you later, guy.
Yeah. He's kind of flippin' about that shit.
He doesn't really care.
It's just, like, I guess, like, people like him,
because he says cool things while he tortures people
and kills them, so he's, you know...
He was kind of cool in that he fought people
with science knowledge instead of, uh,
you know, Zan Park co-shits.
There was that one fight when he was fighting
the Science Arankah guy in Geocomando.
That was a great fight.
When he, like, trapped him in an infinite torment
of nightmare land, that was pretty dope.
Like, super slow motion.
But he probably, like, practiced that technique
on, like, orphans and shit.
That's so true.
He definitely did. He definitely did.
Man, yeah. Good point.
That's a hell worse than death.
He bribes all the policemen with his fashion money.
He makes them sexy zones.
Nobody cares.
I mean, he made that bitch that,
remember, at one point,
in fact, after that exact fight,
there's, like, his lieutenant,
like, the clearly, like,
she's like a flesh golem or whatever.
Nemu or whatever.
Yeah, whatever her name is.
His flesh golem number two.
She, like, comes over to him and does what is
clearly implied to be, has sex with him
right then and there, and then, like, he's suddenly healed.
And it's, like, awesome.
That's not even a criticism.
I just love it.
That's the coolest thing.
He's the only character in the whole series who has sex.
And he's, uh, worse than Hitler.
That makes me mean every character should be having sex
constantly.
Ranji and Rukia should be having sex all the time.
Yeah, yeah.
Ranji should be sexing Rukia with his fucking snake baboon.
Whoa.
Oh, okay. I thought you were going to say sword, but no.
Okay, yeah. Just the baboon that's fine.
With his Bankai.
He puts on the snake baboon suit
and goes to camp.
He does the mating dance.
Oh, do you think Rukia is kind of a
frigid in bed?
No way. I think she's, I think she's
less loose.
She's got an icy sword, but she's hot.
She melts. She melts.
Yeah, she melts in your mouth, but not in your hands.
Uh, man, this is just shit on
bleach for an hour.
The podcast.
I was going to try to bring in some positive things.
I also didn't make sense.
Yeah, what's that?
Uh, fucking Kiriko's
genius plan to make Kanpachi
learn his shikai or whatever.
It's like, okay, turns out
Unahana is like the strongest, most badass
person ever.
First of all, never bought it for a second.
So Kanpachi, you kill her
in the vain hope that maybe you'll get stronger.
Yeah.
Lock the two of you in a room and you're not allowed to come out until she's dead
because she's the strongest
and I, um,
because that's my plan, because I'm the leader now.
I'm a smart man.
The thing was...
Yeah, give, please try to explain this.
There's one thing that I think...
That's where I started to lose it. That's where it began.
Well, I don't know whether...
I feel like that was planned because I've heard that
in interviews, he says he likes the idea.
Kubo likes the idea of
bad guys
looking like good guys and good guys
looking like bad guys.
So the idea that the sweet captain was actually
a fucking crazy person.
Maybe.
She did that really weird hairstyle, which
did turn out to be sort of relevant.
Well, that part of it was cool, but I just don't understand.
Why couldn't she train him
without dying?
I guess he just wanted to get rid of her
because she never did anything.
He never did anything.
He just personally didn't like her.
She fought him
when he was a kid
and he was the only person ever to wound her
or something.
He had to kill her
to realize...
He had to get as strong as he was
when he was 9
by killing her,
and that would do something somehow.
It was terrible writing.
Kubo's a fucking idiot. He doesn't know how to write a manga.
He's a bad man.
He's a very bad man.
He just...
Man, God, like...
He touched my heart.
He really did.
It's always said, but
I can't even fully describe
how hype I was
at the end of the Soul Reaper
arc,
when, you know,
Eisen reveals, it was me, Austin!
It was me all along!
God, that honestly,
when he sweeps his hair back
and takes off his glasses,
that was like...
It turns from a nerd into a cool.
That was like the coolest thing
that ever happened in any anime I had ever seen.
Just that hair!
And like, he had all these plans
he had done, and like, he's strong...
He did like Kido99
or Hado99 or whatever. He's like stronger than everybody.
It was the cool...
And then, up in the sky,
we see the sky crack open and this giant
guy look out, and it's like,
holy shit, what is this guy planning?
Where is this gonna go from here?
Wait, what was that eye?
It's a shitty monster we see a while later
who just fucking dies.
It should have been like the king of the hollows.
It was just some big hollow.
Sucked. It was gay.
Yeah.
It was never. And Eisen
stayed cool, kind of.
You know, he was never intended
to be the actual main villain.
It was originally going to be
what's his face.
The guy with the little
dingley thing on the end of his head bobber
that killed his mom. Grandfisher.
Grandfisher. Yeah.
Whatever happened to that guy?
He got killed by Ichigo's dad.
But the dad wasn't mad.
He was like, I understand you killed my wife.
NBD dog. NBD.
Yeah.
Never really... I'd be mad.
I'd be mad.
There's something that's like,
so much happens.
Like characters die and things,
but I can't remember any of it.
I barely remembered that
something happened to Ichigo's dad
and that's why he's not around.
Did he die? Who did he die to? I forgot.
That was revealed a while later.
He gave his power to Ichigo's mom
because she was a Quincy
and she got attacked by a hollow.
He was around at the beginning.
Ichigo's dad was around and he died sometime.
He didn't die. What are you talking about?
He died? What?
I think he died to give
Ichigo the power to defeat Aizen
the first time or something.
Like when he went black hair.
Oh, he didn't die. They were just training.
Wait, did he really die?
I gotta look this up.
I don't think we saw him since.
He wasn't in the last chapter.
I'm googling this shit.
I thought it was weird that he wasn't in the last chapter.
If you fucking died, man, I miss that shit.
Yeah, but the fact that we're confused about it
and I can't really remember properly
is indicative of how shitty it feels.
It's just like all this stuff
that's supposed to be hard-hitting
and it's like, I don't know.
All this promise and potential
and it just peters out into this long,
goopy fucking soup
through a straw.
It's just like drinking a bleach.
Bleach up my ass.
A little umbrella.
Yes.
You know what bothered me
and was just one of the big signs.
Honestly, this was really late
but it was just something that always annoyed me
was that it turned out
and this was never really explained
but there were kind of some implications
about what was going on.
So when Ichigo first gets his powers from Rukia
the sword just appears in his hand
kind of out of nowhere
and maybe it was Rukia's sword.
I don't know, he kind of just gets his own sword.
That was really cool.
And then later on it evolves into
his big sword
that's like his release or whatever
and all that was cool.
But then later in the series
we find out that
there's this one hip-hop dude
who makes those swords
and he gives them to people
and then they just kind of like
grow into them and they just kind of imprint themselves.
What the fuck was that shit?
I thought it was much cooler
because he just has a sword.
They built it up like
they manifested from inside the people
which is why they were based so heavily on
their personalities and shit
which is why they were interesting
and then he just pulls this fucking hip-hop guy out of his ass
and says hi made him.
That whole area up in the fucking sky
there's like the heaven of heaven
or whatever.
It's such a weird...
It's weird how they're just mortal
like everyone else
by with a big powerful weapon.
I actually, I do like that
because they're all, in fact, the fact that they were
like, what do they call it?
Got a goatee zero or something
because they were like, they had all been captains
who were just like too fucking good
so they had to go up above
and you know...
They all died or something, something happened.
They lost.
You know who was cool among those though?
The best one was that lady
who was captain of squad 12
or, oh god, I don't even remember
Uki Takei, no.
Urahara.
So there was the captain of 12 who leaves
and she was like science lady.
She was this weird moon
science lady who we finally meet
and she was so cool
and then she just does like nothing
and that, you know, that's really the story of Bleach.
A million characters show up
and then they all do nothing.
And then Ichigo does it.
And then Ichigo just does it.
It feels so wrong.
It just went so wrong at some point.
I hate that they have kids.
That was the dumbest thing
that made me roll my eyes.
It's only been 10 years.
So what did they just like immediately start making?
Who the fuck...
Why does Japan promote fucking teenagers
having kids?
Dude, I'll tell you why.
It's because their population is going down the tubes.
They need to encourage fucking on a massive scale.
They want to...
The last chapters of shounen
mangoes.
That's how they do it.
If they sell you out, a happy ending is
to get married and have kids.
I'm just telling you, that's in sync with Japan's current policy.
I don't care about Ichigo's brat.
I don't care about Rukia's fuck trophy.
Who gives a shit? And why the fuck?
Why is Rukia's kid a soul reaper?
That doesn't make any...
You could just be a soul reaper.
The fucking kid cannot be older than nine years old.
Does anyone understand
the rules?
When you die, Rukia didn't start off
as a soul reaper, right?
When you die, you either
become a hollow if you're an evil person
or if you got regrets or whatever,
or you go to soul society
and when you're there,
because you all start out in the shit place,
but if you're really good, if you have strong
spiritual pressure, you can move up
and become a shinigami, which is what Rukia did.
There's a revolving door
of souls that just go back and forth,
but how do you become a human again?
How does that happen? Do you have to die as a soul reaper?
Yeah, I thought it was explained once
that when a soul reaper dies,
he just becomes a new human.
He gets reincarnated or something.
I miss that day in class.
Why are soul reaper people
even able to have children
if that's also where dead people go?
Where's that soul coming from?
People are being born there and dead people are going there.
Wouldn't it have a massive overpopulation problem?
I don't fucking know.
I find it hard to believe
that after all that stuff that happened,
Rukia just immediately
fucking spread him and said,
put a baby in me.
Now that the guy is dead,
the bad guy is dead, I want to start
popping out kids.
Dude, it's been 10 years.
Even after one year,
I'd probably be fine.
I don't really think that's that big of a deal.
Like I was saying, and I remember
the ending felt very much like Naruto's ending,
where they show all the new kids.
Like we're the new...
No one should ever have kids ever.
I hate children, they shouldn't exist.
I just realized,
why is Ichigo's son
a shinigami already?
And how?
Because you is talking about Rukia's kid.
I hate them both.
But Ichigo caught his powers
but he's dead.
Hang on, hang on, we have to establish
that what actually happened is,
those guys were born,
they went to visit hip hop man,
he gave them little baby swords
for them to imprint themselves onto.
They then carried those swords with them
all the time, until they made an impression on them
and developed their shinigami powers.
Because as we know now,
as wise bleach readers,
that's how you actually get a shinigami now.
You have to visit hip hop man
to get yourself a magic sword.
It just seems like really annoying
to have a kid and just say
you're a soul reaper now.
Even with the soul reapers who look like kids,
like Yachiru or Toshiro,
they look like kids,
but at least you think,
well they just look like kids,
they're actually 100 years old.
But this kid is literally a fucking baby!
What are the standards?
The standards are
Naruto ended,
now there's Ninja babies.
Is this just cronyism?
She can like skirt the rules
and deem her child a soul reaper?
That's irresponsible parenting.
He's gonna get eaten by a fucking grandfisher
because he's a baby, he doesn't know how to wield
that fucking sword.
It's too big for his arms.
Alright, I'm gonna tell you the harsh reality, Jesse.
No!
When Naruto ends, you get Ninja baby kids.
When Bleach ends,
you get little
shinigami kids.
And one piece, when it ends,
you get little rubber pirate kids.
That's just how it works, it's going to happen.
We can't fight against the tide of fate.
They're born as pirates?
They're all wearing...
They've got the fucking hats on and the...
God, I hate Japan!
I hate them!
Two nukes was too few.
We gotta finish the job.
Um...
You know, like at the end of Avangelion,
when they had all those Ava babies...
Yeah!
When Asuka started popping out robots...
Oh my God.
Rey...
I don't know.
Rey was naked.
That counts.
Rey, I don't know.
Nobody knows.
Okay, let's take a break
and let's now
talk about the good things
that came of or that we remember from Bleach.
I've got some.
I loved several of the opening
and ending songs from Bleach.
The first one's great.
That one, Hanabi is great.
I forget, but you sure.
It's like...
Yeah!
At least I think that's the one.
Whatever, there's a bunch of good ones.
And I liked it.
Bleach was one of the first series that I watched
when I got into anime.
Bleach in its heyday was so stylish,
it was like nothing else, man.
It was the coolest.
It was the coolest in the future
as a fashion designer.
It's going to be great.
Maybe he'll join Square Enix
and start working on Final Fantasy.
Oh no!
It's the worst possible fate!
This is the darkest timeline!
Kubo, you need to go back to Bleach!
Make a detergent.
Just keep pumping him out.
Wait, what's Nirvana's next album?
He needs to make Smells Like Teen Spirit.
Nevermind.
Uh...
Oh, god.
Imagine the things that Kubo could produce
with Tetsuya Nomura if they teamed up.
The kind of belts, the kind of zippers...
They could make an anime so bad
it would destroy the world!
It would cleanse the earth in fire!
Cleanse it in Bleach!
We need it. We need that.
I do like Kubo's artwork.
And the fact that he managed to do...
His colors are gorgeous, for sure.
He managed to do a different
little version of the
number of the chapter in each chapter.
Which I thought was neat.
Oh yeah!
I did like that.
It's just a little...
He's a good artist.
I'm just sad about it.
That is definitely true.
Let's talk about that.
How good his art is.
I think just as a consequence of that...
He probably spent so much time on it.
He, you know, infamously
wasn't one to spend too much time
focusing on backgrounds.
But his character designs
really always looked great.
And were some of the best in all of Shonen Jump.
Incidentally...
I'm just thinking about the art.
And I always think of this one when I think about good art.
Especially Rukia.
In their little devil costume here
for this Halloween spread.
Oh god, look at Toshiro spreading his legs
like a fucking slut.
He's like, he's a child Kubo.
He's a child.
He's fucked up.
Who's the person in the little orange thing
at the top?
Or he may.
As a little plumpkin.
I think.
I assume.
What else was good?
You know what was cool?
He had ginger hair.
That's unusual.
Yeah, that was crazy.
That was the beginning when he had to defend himself
from bullies.
Because his hair was a weird color.
Just because his mom had weird hair color.
I remember this one point.
This one part where, yeah, that bit.
But like...
The thing he said, I think he was like
he just got his phone out and he started calling an ambulance.
And he said, before he started fighting them
he said he's counting how many people there were.
Oh yeah!
That was so cool!
That's such a badass thing to do.
He did another cool thing like that again.
He lost the bad boy thing fast.
He just became like a
what's all this Shinigami stuff
and then he was a deer in the headlights
for the rest of the whole series.
Yeah, there's not much to say about Ichigo's personality
unfortunately.
He was very...
I gotta do it!
That's what he said every chapter.
Remember that time guys
when he stood around and watched
because like he
was the only one not under Aizen's
Shikai control.
Remember that time when he stood around
and watched them stab
the Lieutenant of Squad 5
in the back because they thought it was Aizen.
Remember when that happened?
I remember when that happened.
That was awesome to me to go.
Like he's just standing there like
what are these guys doing as like
I forget who teleported behind
Hannah through her stomach.
Man.
That was brutal.
What an asshole.
Say something goddammit and then afterward
he's like guys what do you do
and guys
fuck you Ichigo you piece of shit.
You stupid idiot. You're the worst guy of all.
You ruined it.
You know what was cool though?
Kubo's favorite character was always Rangiku
just because she was a big fat titted bitch
and I respect him immensely for that.
You know what was great about Bleach?
The porn.
There is great porn of Bleach out there.
Of Rukia.
There's some good flash made by Zone.
Rukia's got a lot of porn
or Hime actually doesn't
have a lot of porn out there I think about it.
But really it's Rangiku.
Oh and Yorichiru.
Yorichiru?
The black cat.
She is the sexiest girl in all of Bleach.
Oh my god I forgot this amazing doge
and I read when I was a kid
a ball about her and she was naked and they were taking
a bath in the hot springs. Oh my god it was so sexy
it was amazing. It was the coolest thing
that ever happened to me in my entire life. Thank you Kubo.
I thank you every single day for making Yachiru
or whatever the fuck her name was.
Yorichiru she's the coolest oh my god.
Yorichiruichi.
She was the best.
Whatever.
You know I'm talking about.
I'm gonna google black chick.
This is what Bleach really is.
Bleach a series of like pretty images no one remembers the name of any of the
characters yoruichi there it is yoruichi that's the one yoruichi was the
best character and you know it was cool she would just show up not even she's
a she's a shini guy but she doesn't even eat her sword she just gets like
weapons from from urahara and just punches people and they fucking die all
she needs to be naked beat people that's right she gave what if what if she was
having in a porn and you just turn into a cat for some reason that's what I
explained oh yeah go on what if she did that while somebody had a penis in her
and then they would be fucking her pussy they'll say the line that everyone
says about that a cat is fine too that's a meme that's a that's an a meme
because there's there's a dojin about me there's a dojin about yeah there's a
dojin about a dude like chasing some lolly or something and he's gonna fuck
her and then she just turns into a cat and she's like hi I've got you now he's
just like a cat is fine too dog I'm a raw dog in this shit whoa he's raw dog in
this cat yes so okay so Bleach is done so we're dead for a while and I don't
even count the new thing as Bleach as was Naruto because it sucks Bleach has
kind of been out of the big three for a while has it I've always considered it
still part of the big three I know we do but if you keep if you keep up on like
the Shonen Jump scene like Ichigo does not show up in like the big like whenever
they show like the main characters of Shonen Jump it's always Luffy and then
Toriko a lot of the time and then like there's another spot is kind of just
open for debate but it is it's not Ichigo like he doesn't make it into the top
ranks anymore and it's it's cuz this thing was less popular obviously so like
there's something about like the covers well I'm talking about the popularity of
series you know of Shonen Jump because you know like there was this whole
thing about Naruto Bleach and One Piece because they were by far the most
popularly series at least in America but also in Japan they just sold the best
and they lasted the longest and they were always in the cover of everything
Bleach has faded away Naruto is done Naruto retired pretty much at the top
but One Piece is actually the top and has been for a long time but I'm just I
mean I'm interested to see if something will rise to take its place or if maybe
they're not gonna do as long-running series anymore I mean Toriko is ending
pretty soon so that'll be like only one piece will remain as like a big long
running thing I mean I guess it was that's a different magazine I don't
know what I'm talking about I'm just I'm just saying the legacy of Bleach is
coming to an end and it just fills me with wonder about about what the future
holds especially for Shonen Monk well it's hard to to think about what's gonna
happen because when it first came out when Naruto and Bleach were big yeah
coming out we were like teenagers we didn't know what the scene was like we
didn't understand what had come before we didn't really know anything about all
that shit true and now there's been going for so many years like there's
not really where any way you can predict there's no reason that this should be the
way it continues there's no reason it's always gonna be a big three it could
just be that One Piece is the best forever and everyone loves it I think years
to come well that is when that is when that ends there might not even be
anything to come and take it up to take up the mantle of the best one you know
yeah I've been thinking about this for a while and it's really dawned on me
lately that like I mean One Piece is read mostly by like 40% of the One Piece
readers are between like 18 and 25 or like 18 and 30 or something so that like
most people read it but everything in Shonen Jump isn't made for like a 26
year old man like me like I don't even fit in that category anymore I'm like
older than that now and it just like they're they're appealing to kids with
this shit and like when I think about like over the years I've gained a lot
of knowledge about Shonen and like I'm able to recognize tropes and like I
could read a series like Bleach from the start now and I would I pretty well
Bleach took a lot of twists and turns but for the most part I'd be able to know
like where it's generally going and so there's not a lot of mystery in it the
mystery lies in like the specifics of like oh what's the bonkai gonna be like
what are the in-universe like surprises and twists gonna be but like if you
don't buy into that as much which I'm doing less and less I noticed it myself
like less Shonen have that kind of like instant grab on me these days but but
like I'm not the the people they're trying to get to buy the magazines in
Japan to like you know fun Shonen Jump they're trying to get like 10 year old
boys like 12 year old boys in Japan because Shonen Jump I don't even
sold it I do think that like there's a lot of people in your similar situation
like there yeah they grew up on on Shonen Manga and like we're like the first
generation and then raised on this shit yeah I guess I'm not sure I'm talking
about Shonen Manga well maybe not but like there's clearly gonna be like
people making cool stuff for our demographic like not just for our
demographic but people of our demographic can enjoy I mean Steven
universe is a stretch but it's it's that sort of like that's really cool for the
gay demographic though you know what I mean though it's like it's it's like a
action show but it's also like got a lot of themes I mean or resonate with people
of any age classic example is my little pony which you know is for little
girls but not bad not bad not bad was I was gonna say something else forget well
if it comes you can say it um yeah I don't know I just I'm interested in as
I'm getting older I'm taking more and more notice that like there were things
and it was gonna say okay go ahead go ahead I think that the things that we
like in one piece that still are cool yeah it's like the the willingness to
not take itself so seriously because like when we were younger we enjoy things
that are like serious and like really emo and dark have you guys seen elfin
lead it's the best anime I've ever yeah and when you get older you're like that's
stupid yeah yeah but like if something is like deliberately stupid in that sort
of cool way kind of show came up and it was like it was more literally just a
bunch of skeletons and a guy with a cool sword and a bunch of guys with cool
swords killing skeletons yeah and that was all it was then first of all be the
best thing of all time yes exactly it's like it doesn't it doesn't care about
being a serious thing yeah has all the cool fun action that we liked from stuff
like bleach yeah that's that's that's cool I like stuff like that as long as I
want to make stuff like that I agree I agree though I have I have slightly
loftier ass well not not I don't want to say loftier but I want to use
entertainment to educate people and to control the destiny of humanity to make
it better and smarter and cooler that's those are my goals in life
surprise that we got to a place where I could say that in this bleach podcast
it's utterly shit but yeah I want to lick Rukias but I want to put my tongue
right between her butt cheeks I want to lick her anus then I want to she's
called inside all fist inside of her butt and then I want to raise my fist in
the air and as you remove it and gaze at that permanently wide hole you'll say
don't you forget about me Rukia and she won't she'll never be able to by the way
I'm just I'm looking at this Halloween thing again and I'm just noticing that
Kubo took the time to deliberately draw Rangiku's nipple sticking through her
thing and you know that's really what I respect about Kubo at the end of the
day the fact that he would take the effort to do that to clearly draw the
nipple visible through her outfit ten out of ten ghosts have nipples anyway
sheenie gammy aren't ghosts they're Japanese Samurai's of the dead wait
actually I guess they are like literally death gods oh yeah death god it means
death god but gods are like ghosts so you're right never mind why is the
afterlife so weirdly based on like Japanese culture why you don't get it
Irish the real world the real world is based off of the afterlife the
Japanese are the ones that got it right yeah everyone else fucked it up okay I
actually think that sort of makes sense and it's because sheenie gammy
inherently are a Japanese concept so it makes sense for like their culture to
be Japanese where all the Shinigami are from which are a very specific thing
like these are Japanese death you know what would have been really cool was that
I know it would have been like another new set of things but wouldn't it be cool
if like there was more than just you know the Japanese death god is sheenie
gammy area and then there's plenty guys who are like German but what I mean is
like you go over to another realm and it's like oh it's the European like all
that all that Viking stuff like the what's it called Valhalla you go there
you see these big fat guys with beers and ale and you're like yeah and but they
have source they're they don't have source they have axes with names I'd watch
that and watch that show and then they could they'd be cool but then there'll
be more characters and more things and I'll be like oh no that's too many well
I mean if it was still just like the gimmick of Zanpak toes just you know
you know I mean they could call it that or they could give it a different name
but it's the same thing like that doesn't clutter things at all that's just
the same shit he's just new powers you know that's no that's no worse I think
that's see that's the sort of thing I'd prefer over like full bringers or just
like whatever Quincy's new Quincy's with Magic Quincy like there's there's the
new Quincy's right now I think we've tired of retired of this topic bleach
sucks but it was kind of good once the end I think that pretty much sums it up
I I think I'll miss bleach a little bit mostly because I found bleach at a time
in my life when I was first really getting into anime like I might even
have watched it like before I got into one piece in a big way but it was all
around that time when I watched like every anime I could find in high school
and it really really made a strong impression on me and so on that basis
I'm glad it was around it introduced me it's it's you know it's kind of like a
decent starter anime you just can't have too high expectations for what it's
gonna do I would recommend the people who haven't read bleach go read the first
like to the end of the first arc when you know when Ichigo wins he gets his
Bunkine wins and then just make up your own ending you know like you just skip
to the last two chapters because you're done don't even worry about it but I
think that first part's worth reading if you're into shonen I like it rookie is
cool each goes cool no each goes actually not cool only rookie is cool
Renji was cool Renji and rookie had deserved their own series yeah yeah that's
it what's that put my whole fist right up her bungle okay that's it we're done
talking about bleach thanks for listening everybody goodbye
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
what the hell is wrong with me I'm supposed to be making money I'm supposed to be creating fun things that the people gladly will pay for artistic genius that's what they came for instead I'm tweeting
yeah it's quite the burden it's a hard-knock life being a genius