Do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do it and that's the end of the podcast everybody thank you for watching.
So rude. Don't forget our good friend that's the Clay Saban.
Fuckbitch is podcast here is everybody.
Yay!
So today's topic is a technical one that some of us are more familiar with than others and
Cicely, but you know I should have beat around the bush for like an hour before I got
That's what it is. It sounded like munchie laughing
It did it did I like to booze like in the distant background laughing like he's off doing something else still listening
No, I pulled the fucking mic away for myself. Oh, it was a spike. Okay every time you've done that
I always assume it's it's quieter because you throw your head back and laugh as loud as you can
That's why it sounds like an owl DNA, man
I imagined he's like pacing in the back of his room whenever he's not talking trying to think of what to say
And then he bum rushes at the mic like oh, it's time to go. Exactly. Um, I
Yes
Hi, I'm close at the microphone now. Is that good? Yeah, I'll just keep looking at
Let's stop fucking around here people. Oh, we have to be as unconcise as possible. This isn't even non concise
This is just off topic completely totally irrelevant. Well, that's that is relevant to this point because I think people when they think of concise
They don't exactly know what it means, right? Okay, so when we talk about concise writing
It's about how quickly you can sort of make a point and like just
Clearly communicate your intentions without beating around the bush and stuff and like there's a there's a huge difference between
Going off topic or even being long-winded like you can be long-winded and concise
I think I haven't looked at the definition of concise recently. I don't know if it has to be short
But like for instance, I often get accused of
By that anime snob that that my hero
Yes, yes my hero, but that's an amazing app whose videos are all under 10 minutes long
And he gives me lots of shit for my videos being longer
And he often says that like, you know brevity is the soul of wit and stuff like wow
He's a smart dude. Yeah, his videos are just 20 second segments from other people's videos. Like what does he even do?
Well, that's the thing is that he he keeps his stuff so short that he never makes a point and it's not that he's
Necessarily concise. It's just that he's brief
And you know what? Yeah, that's interesting because I just went to urban dictionary comm our home base
To look up the definition of concise and it is relevant to this
So the other full definition of definition here is concise to be brief
But inclusive able to sum up a topic succinctly
succinctly without elaboration or superfluous detail
And so the point here is you have to be making a real point in order to concise and if that is lacking that you're just being brief
I guess it's it's how much useful interesting worthwhile shit is packed in per minute
Like whereas that anime snob will often try to he'll take a lot of different points and make individual videos about all of them
I'll just put them all in one. You know, it's not that my writing is not being more concise. Yeah, I'm not I'm not being
I'm not not being concise. I'm just making a lot of points in a row, you know
And that's what he doesn't seem to there can be a lot by the way
There could be lots of works out there that are really verbose and really long-winded
But don't come off like you're wasting your time as long as you're interested in all the material out there
You know, you know, maybe some is it? There may be some very popular
harem anime franchise out there that might have a lot of long-winded conversations or maybe some
I've been reading that might have a lot of long-winded conversations
But if all those conversations are really fucking interesting, then shut up is good as long
It's just that it's really hard for people to meaningfully fill large amounts of dialogue with actual interesting things to say and like anime often
I'll see like like any show in series
I was talking about this like a show in series will start off with a lot of interesting things to say because all the thought goes into the
premise of the show or the or the manga or whatever and then like they just get away from that like I don't know
I think that's part of what makes like Hunter Hunter special or even Yu-Haka show is that
Every battle is concise in those shows where like there's just a shit load of battles
Like you watch you Yu-Haka show or Hunter Hunter would always struck me about those shows is no fight ever lasts more than one
episode, well, that's not true of early Yu-Haka show, but
Hunter Hunter and what's another show? I was thinking of the
Dragon Ball Z
There's
Certain shows where yeah, like a fight is always like at most an episode to an episode and a half
And it doesn't give you time to get tired of it
It just gets in shows off these cool powers right and like makes the point and goes you know and like so many people will give
Showing an anime shit just for being so long
But like how is it long is it long like DBZ where it really is just wasting a lot of fucking time, right?
Or is it long like you Yu-Haka show where it keeps making new points?
Well, dude, there's there's shows I'm gonna bring out as great examples of I think is as great concise writing and one is of
Course Gern Lagen because so much happens every episode of Gern Lagen
It really moves the pace forward at a wonderful brisk pace does not waste your fucking time
And the other one is high school the dead and I really think high school the dead
You know, I made that me a mafia episode about it is really great
And I didn't talk about it as much but that show definitely makes a point in every episode every single episode like
There's probably like people would often think that because it's a zombie show
It's gonna like waste your time and be a bunch of faffing around like oh zombie fights all the time
But no like it's real human drama all these characters developing every single episode you can see them changing and evolving over time
And like the directing is great. It's super hype. There's intense moments all the time
It's got you know, the crazy fan service and action happening all the time
It really again, that's a show that does not waste a second of your time
You feel like you're learning something every time you're watching I I want to I want to say something about like Davoo was in playing that
No, I'm playing it saying users webcomic, right? It's it's Homestuck. He's been reading
Could you could could you say despite its length that Homestuck is concise?
I would not you could probably tell the whole the whole all the fucking conversations of Act 5 in a much more linear
Condensed fashion it just wouldn't be nearly as funny and you get to know all the characters
Yeah, I mean like because I'm what are the end of Act 5 now
And it's like it's like what actually happens in Act 5 gets summarized by the self-insert
Vector in like a couple of pages and it's like, okay
This is actually pretty straightforward plot. It's just told really fucking out of order, you know
Well, the thing that yeah, the thing that I'm thinking of is like it's it's not being brief
You know, it's different from just being brief. It's different from cutting things out
You know like you could you could argue that a lot of the things in Homestuck that seems stupid eventually become relevant
So like how much should like how much is I don't I don't get it
I'm very I mean you guys are talking about conciseness like, you know what it means. I don't really understand it
I don't think like I mean, it's essentially as I explained
It's just like not it's a consistent presentation of new ideas as opposed to reiterating the same idea
Give you ever what watch like Inuyasha or Rambo one-half. Nope any of that kind of shit. No, okay
Well, you've seen Dragon Ball Z, right?
I read it. I don't know if he has
Reading it's actually way better than watching it
So, okay
Well, there's like in Dragon Ball Z for example the classic thing is that like a single fight that maybe took out like a couple chapters in the
Manga like gets dragged out for like for the classic things the Frieza battles at the end of like the first arc of DBZ
Like it takes like so many episodes for just and barely anything happens in those episodes
It is such a waste of your time to like actually sit through
Yeah, that's the thing like that's why I'm thinking like Homestuck so much of it is so great and interesting and it's not
It doesn't feel like a waste of time. It's not like that Homestuck is actually making like like it goes on for so long
And it goes through things like, you know, in case we weren't clear
Davoo was arguing that Homestuck was concise. Yeah with good stuff
It's not concise with like a conventional normal like plot that you would understand as a normal thing
It's just concise with you know characters being manic idiots hours
I would argue that Homestuck does have moments where it does kind of just hammer on the same
Some of those conversations like the exact same conversation you read earlier, you know
Like there are moments where it's it does push it a little bit
But I do think the story has so much going on that like it deserves to be as long as it is
You know, it's appropriate to say that conciseness does not necessarily mean better in all cases, of course
Yeah, I would say that Homestuck really adds a lot of flavor by having like it is about a bunch of teenage drama
Stuff happening between kids it makes sense that wouldn't be concise these kids waste a lot of everyone's fucking time mostly their own
But yeah, and like I said, it's it's about what it deserves like yeah with Dragon Ball like
Because the manga exists and everything like we know Dragon Ball Z didn't need to be as long as it is
We know you could have told they may have improved that without exactly like we know you can do it without taking up that much time
So to me, that's what concise is it's like tell the story or or write your thing
Whatever you're doing just do it in the smallest amount of time that you need and that's
People don't understand that you do need some
Humanity in there you need some extra and like I talked about this in my video about how I learned how to write gooder
Where I in like 2010 I became obsessed with simplifying my writing and like I cut it down until it was like just the bare
Essential language needed to communicate the point, but it felt like a fucking robot, you know, yeah, so like I
So I started going back in and adding in phrases and like adding in stuff that just especially for my videos stuff
That just sounds right to somebody like it engages your brain in a different way
Yeah, you need to have some like you know we're nice and concise
You know those those videos Davoo keeps posting about like a robot obviously made this video
Yeah, those are concise and that's uh, they don't fuck around. They really tell you
Across the United States or whatever hold the fuck on they're not that size the robots don't know shit about fuck
They'll just be like number 12 number 12 person who obstinately refused to tear down their house as Chinese
Highways are trying to be built this person really stood up for themselves and didn't stand down to the man number 11
This guy really goes to show how much society can't progress when some people are stubborn like shut up
Robotic you're fucking boy. So, you know like I did you saying I think there's like four like steps that people go through to like
Master and art step one is you just learn how to basically do anything you learn how to basically write put together a little bit of music
Put together a little bit of painting it starts out small and then as you get more ambitious and more skilled you make something big and
encumber some and
Bloated and then you start learning how to refine your skills and and you just get smaller and smaller until it's this perfect condensed ball
That doesn't have much breathing room and then you use your newfound perfection
Skill to just slowly weave stuff back out
It's like watching like an explosion in like an anime where like it goes
Then it sucks back in and then it slowly wooshes out again. That's what I come for is yeah
Yeah, like like the like the the whole earth. Yeah, the whole the trees go like
It's either real or hey, uh, somebody made me always our good friend
Ukrainian the artist boy made a drawing of like someone when you were posting those pictures of oh, I was gonna say by the way
Did she's calling in live from Gaikon?
Because it was called a Gaikon you don't need to change it to Gaikon Gaikon already sounds like
Gaikon 3 or Gaikon 4 that was the thing that somebody post this guy posted Gaikon 5 and then
Ukrainian drew a picture of me on of the fucking skateboard just being like
I only meant to stay a while as I was like wearing the bunny suit and flying through this guy
It's great. Thank you. You're a gift. You're a gift. Anyway, let's get back to so I don't know
Why don't we talk about like the way that we try to be concise writers? I want to say one thing
Like we're saying that conciseness can be bad
What is the the worst concise thing like the two concise the thing that is way too concise
What Ben would tell us a story and cuts out all the interesting parts of it and just tells you the facts
I went here. I fuck this dude. I went home done
Story was definitely too concise
Yeah, I mean it's just that
I was gonna say like going off of what Nate said if we're gonna talk about how we are concise
Or do you want to talk first about art or about analysis because I think if there's a fan at home of the PCP
They're probably high school or college age. They have to write a lot of essays and what's scary about being
Concise is in an essay as you usually have, you know, you have to do eight pages
So how can you be both concise and stretch that shit out to eight pages just worry about you guys have
To teach you to do is just to learn is just to get the basic discipline of typing shit out
It's only when you get into college that they start telling you to actually how to write good school
Well, that's school. Yeah, I would say your system of this world only once you have base level mediocre confidence by the time
You're 18 and maybe if you work really hard and put all of your future life savings and do this degree
Then you can be decent in your life. I'll tell you I'll tell you to do like well
You know, I because I learned how to be concise because of an English teacher
but I was taking a
Like that class was to learn how to be a better writer and most college classes won't teach you that
They want you to learn how to write a college paper, which means pumping in as much frivolous bullshit
It's humanly possible to reach 50,000 words like if you look at like cider
talking about his thesis like
Like you you inherently through working your way up through school. You will learn how to bullshit
You will learn how to stretch things out. I learned how to do that back in high school
And here's my advice if all they give you is a minimum word count
Don't try to be concise ever if they try if they give you a minimum word count
Write as many fucking like as many ways of saying the exact same shit as you can to reach that word Jesse
What the fuck are those clicking noises? I'm hearing in the background. What are you doing? What is that? It's Jesse here
Yeah, that's I see I am also in this episode everyone
Yeah, I wasn't going to say anything, but Nate revealed your mic, so we don't hear you chewing
It sounds like you're eating tic-tacs. It sounds like you're just down in tic-tacs. I'm fucking around with shit
Jesse's always done that. Welcome to the Procrastinator's podcast. He's always like flipping a screw around into other screws on his desk
We're just doing that. I don't know what the shit all the time. It's white noise
I'm fucking building infiltration tools. I'm fucking living Persona 5. That's what I do
I stay at my desk and I create tools to infiltrate people's palaces
Hey, I think you're the only person. I know who's played Persona 5. Is it good? How you how's it going?
It is good. It's pretty okay. That's a topic now. That's a
It could be
It could be except that you're the only
My favorite Persona is when in Apescape 3 you can turn into a knight. That's my favorite one
Yeah, so talking about before we
Saying if they give you a minimum word count, you should be as civil as is possible
Yeah, if they give you a minimum word count and no maximum go apeshit if they give you a maximum word count
That's where you guys start worrying about it because that's why I learned to be concise as I had gotten so used to trying to pump as many words
Into a paper as possible and just like writing, you know
My life have I ever had a maximum word count? I think that could be why I'm such a fucking ridiculously
Yeah, this never cut my words down. This teacher. I had he told us to write a story about a
What was it? It was like write a story about a some a teacher who you learned something from or something some shit
Oh, he's just trying to beat himself off everybody right about me. This was like brand
We just this first paper way to write for the class and it was something like that. I know that's what I wrote about
I don't know if that's what the topic was but he said like
700 to a thousand words and I wrote like 1300 and I turned and I'm thinking like ha I am I surpassed your word count
But he like yeah, I'm even better. I know a thousand words. That's nothing to me
And he's like no I wanted this to be
700 to a thousand like you went over you need to go through this and like simplify it and so I took out a bunch of words
I got it down to like just over a thousand and he reads it
He's like there's still a lot of stuff in here like like he points out some stuff
That's like unnecessary and I was like yeah now that I think about that is unnecessary and I work it down to like
700 words and it was like a tight little piece. It was much better like I'm reading over it
And I'm like wow my original fucking blue because I didn't do I didn't try to control myself ever ever ever go to school
So yeah, like the whole conciseness thing there's not like any like it's not like some sort of magic different way that things can
Be good or bad. It's just a different lens of how to approach
Removing things that are not good and adding only things that are good, you know
I think that that's I feel like that's part of what makes
Cartoons Western cartoons better now than they were like in the previous era
Where a lot of cartoons would just have a lot of episodes that don't matter much, but then you see the universe
But then you see oh no, no, I'm talking about you doing it backwards
All right, listen for a couple of minutes you have to all agree with me for the point to be made so
Like adventure time it feels like they're really trying to make only awesome stuff happen
Whereas I honestly feel like when I look at a lot of older shows they're like well
I guess this episode something just kind of okay will happen. They're just really
Man masters of the universe kind of just yeah, just just make only the cool stuff happen
Just try to cheat, you know, just just make a dessert. That's nothing but chocolate and vanilla
You know, not every guy tune has like a continuous storyline and character progression and shit
Like sometimes you just want to see SpongeBob hang out at the Krabby pad. Yeah, but do the best ones of that hang out at the Krabby pad
Yeah
Yeah, no, I totally agree with DeVue on that point because that's what I've always struggled with but like a lot of longer shows is like
For instance, Ranma one half as you brought up earlier as a show. That's not at all concise
There's just so much fucking wasted time in that show. It's a hundred and sixty episodes
And like the first like 20 tell this really like compelling
Romance story and then the last like like like throughout the show. There's about 60 episodes that are like great
Out of a hundred and sixty, which is pretty good
There's about 96 that like you like should watch and there's about 60 that you just shouldn't you know and like you have a
Actual posts
Yeah, I'm watching guide for Ranma like it's like, you know, here's like the minimum you should watch
Here's like each different tier of episodes essentially and the ones that you shouldn't watch
It's because they just boil it down to like the basically flander eyes the characters a perfect example
Is the second Ramo and half movie which is fucking dog shit and it like all the movie consists of is the most
Basic idea of what each character is like just using the most obnoxious running gags
Like the movie effect because movies are always afraid to like challenge the status quo
So there will be no development in a lot of movies like that and and just not even doing anything with the characters
Cuz like the best episodes of the show are where you see them change a little bit or you see some kind of small
Insight into who they are whereas the worst episodes are when they're just being like again
Flander eyes like just like what what is this character known for oh?
She she always she always trips and falls in the main character and calls him a baka Inu
You know like that's that's something that has to happen every episode so then you get a movie and it's just that yeah
It's just and it did it with like every character in the show, which there's a huge cast kind of a complete waste of time
I mean help fucking SpongeBob does the same thing the first three seasons have like say let's say 20 ideas
And then it's been like 50 seasons now and they're still just cycling through the same ideas for some reason
I just realized okay, but Spongebob's a little intro to this episode should be the the preparing the Krabby Patty dramatic intro thing
Cuz that's very unconcise. It's like just making you sit around but that's the point
That's like anti-humor. I know it's great. That should be the intro just saying guys, okay, okay
Tell that to whoever edits this see whoever at Ben I guess oh
Okay, there you go you and Ben are really fighting over this editing spot. This is good challenge Ben make Ben into a real boy
Please make him work for something in his life
Yeah, okay, cool, but I do like it though
Well, I think there's a place for shows like Spongebob that I mean they don't challenge their status quo at all like but they're completely focused on
Being you know sort of consumable pop entertainment that just brings you I don't know like there's you're not learning anything watching a
11 minutes of the episode rather than like a season-long story arc. Yeah, so it's not really comparable to like
I do think it's comparable and I mean like do you think it is?
I mean Ramo and half is the same story like it doesn't it doesn't really have an ongoing plot
It's that Ramo mixes in like that that character development stuff because there is like a thing
We're we're waiting for like relationship
16 episodes of Ramo is all the development in the show like after episode 16
It just cuts off and like because the development that happens supposedly it's just the same thing over and over again
It's just the characters
Realizing that oh, maybe we do love each other, but then it goes back to status. I mean I'm not as familiar with with Ramo
But here's a better example
Future Rama like there's certain episodes. We all remember a future Rama either because they're the really dramatic ones
Or they're the ones that are so hilarious and like over the top with their concept and really did something unique and interesting
but there's other episodes of future Rama that are just like
Just whatever dick around like do the same thing we've done in a million other episodes and like no one remembers those ones
I think you know those some people are annoyed by those
I love almost everything about future Rama and I think it's because again
It has a more comedic tone and it can get away like you're never gonna be super disappointed when there's just a future Rama episode
That's just if it's just hilarious
I mean even the baseline of the show is pretty good and like a show that I think is
Very close to all killer no filler is Rick and Morty right where like, you know, we've got two two seasons and
There's like maybe three episodes that I would be like, I don't know if I want to watch that one if I was Marathon
I don't even know if I go that high. I don't think there are any I'd love them all
I mean, I will rewatch all of them right right for sure
But like there's a couple that aren't as good as the other like raising gazorp is or not as many people are gonna watch that
Yeah, again, you know
But like so much of it is so strong because they really do approach every episode with like let's come up with another
Crazy-ass idea like let's always have it so it's something you never thought of that's always gonna be like a little bit of a mind
Blow even when it like repeats like, you know, the the whole marriage between
Jerry and
What's the name?
Yes, like Jerry and Beth's marriage has been it's it's kind of beating a dead horse at this point
That's true, but they still find new things to do with it, you know, so like even though it's kind of status Khloe
It's still like by the end of the episode you'll be like, okay, I guess you earned that one
How specifically are you relating this to being concise?
Well, just that I think that
Consciousness is about presenting new ideas like like like each I think it to repeat the same thing
You already said is to not be concise and like you can draw a parallel between this in like an analytical video where it's more
Immediate and in a long-form TV show
Does a long-ass intro to the video is like this show came out in 1994 and it's pretty good
Even that stuff's not so much a problem. It's when they say like
When I first watched this yeah, I didn't think it was good to be good
But then after watching it it turns out it was literally filler
You can literally just like the show the show is good. Yeah, and I did this in um, I
Showed there's a video of how I edited the writing for my Kemono friends video because the original opening sentence was like
Like if you just want to know whether or not I think this show is good
The answer to that is that yes, it is good, right?
And so I cut all that out and wrote Kemono friends is good
That's the edited version and it literally conveys the exact same meaning. Yeah, like it doesn't add or subtract anything
It's just the same sentence, but with way fewer words
I remember digi there was a time when you used to edit out
Literally every single gap between any words you said, you know any any any breasts that you you would cut them out
And you would delete them back in and yeah, because it became so dense with information that people
I mean, I'm not sure people had problems with it, but I did it was a bit. I still do that
Um, I just did it recently because I just uploaded a a big long ranting rambly podcast about Pirates of the Caribbean 5
Yeah, and um, you know when you're recording it
It's all coming off the top of your head and you're going on and on right, but I
Definitely I went through meticulously and shortened the breaths and put the sentences to each other like almost
Imperceptibly like just like you know like half a second closer to each other
But when it's an entire podcast and you're doing that between every sentence
You might shave off a good like half an hour of redundancy of just listening to me like breathing between sentences
And to be clear I mean I still cut out all breaths and all everything
It's just that what hippos referring to is if you watch my old pony videos the words literally run into each other
Like a sentence. There is no space
It will be like like one word finishes and like I would edit it that way
I would edit it so the words literally ran into each other and it's actually headache inducing to listen to like like when the videos
were like 15 minutes long and it was all like that and I'd be going between different points with no transition or anything
And so it was like it was hard to process even for me like I'd listen to it back and be like getting a headache
So I actually had an effect sometimes where I would feel suffocated
Because I don't hear any space to breathe and it's like it tricks my mind and like yeah
Like it fucked with me
I would actually feel like like loss of breath listening to some of this episode's back
I can't get another review show that does that's always done that to spectacular effect named that zero punctuation named after the gimmick
Yeah, and you know he just writes it around that gimmick
It's like almost ever the whole almost every video is like ten seconds of a point ten seconds of a joke
And it it's like peanut butter and jelly is from one to the other constantly
So you're you can generally I think the fact that those are only five minutes long helps
Yeah, you can generally get all the point if you just just just empathize with your audience all the time
That's sort of a higher level skill in any art medium thing is being able to constantly
Simulate what it's gonna feel like to the person who this is for watching
You know who didn't do that in a in a big way
I didn't when I was making my Lucifer video that video was not it was
Concise there you go. Yeah for sure dense with too much information that I when I was editing it in slow motion
I thought okay everyone's gonna be able to get this gonna be able to read it. No problem and
Yeah, that's that's the problem
I've always had with with edit like editors that you know the extra credits guys still do this
Occasionally which really annoys me because I used to do it and I realized it was terrible is to have like a pun image on the screen
Yeah, which relates to like a single word in a sentence and then you know the viewer is then looking at this image thinking wait
What's that got to do with it? Oh, I see and then they've missed like the rest of the sentence in the style the next one
I've done some of that and and not liked it in the long run as well
Extra craze is fucking dog shit. I hate them on every level imaginable
Anyway, when it when it comes to to making my own things concise
I find it very difficult to imagine
Like when when the writing is bad
Until I've recorded it and I'm listening to it and I'm like, okay that sentence is stupid
I can cut that out because it doesn't sound right. It sounds like what I just said, so I can't read it very well
I'm not like a word guy, but when I'm listening to it
That's when I usually cut down all the all the the the extra crap. I'm the same way give I do it the same way
I think perhaps the most important part of the writing process is to have somebody else read your work and tell you
Uh, yeah, you made this point like three paragraphs ago. Do you do you do that? I think you've talked about doing that
Mom definitely all of my videos I do for my main channel
I have one of my friends like Asperger or somebody read through it and that kind of thing
It's really have friends who are actually good who could actually I feel like 90% of people listening are gonna have friends who
Have no talent in this kind of thing at all and will never be good at all and so well
I think anybody can read something. Yeah, it's it's I don't think it's necessarily you have to be
You know a linguist or whatever to know that something is not concise if you just read it
And you're like I don't get this part that's it's weird and stupid
You know that's just what the viewer will think when they're listening to it
And did you bro has told me that in private?
He told me he loves it when fans send him work that they wrote and he loves to edit it for them and send it back
Oh, right
That you know, that's interesting because I I think I have a different mentality about it
And it's I'm probably not any better, but I have this weird
Fetishistic desire to be independent in everything I do or like have control over everything so I never ask anyone for help
Well, you can always tell them
With what they said like oh, yeah, I see your point
It's like an attitude where I don't want to ever have to rely on anyone's feedback ever
I want all the skills to be contained within me, but whatever. I mean, that's just small thing
I got it
I mean you can learn the skills by having some sorry give
Like if you know if you have a friend who can teach you those things and then you eventually learn it from them
Then you will have the skill for yourself
Well, like I mean, okay, that makes sense
But to me the way to do that is to make the video all the way and like if there's problems with it
Okay, I'll fix it the next round. Well, yeah, I would do that, too
I wouldn't I wouldn't give them like one paragraph and be like is this okay
I'd I'd give them the whole thing and be like what am I gonna do like I mean
I what am I gonna do like send you my scripts and be like digi is this concise tell me what do you think I don't want to do
What's wrong with that? Why are you proposing it like it's crazy? Well, that's a great thing to do
I guess cuz that cuz then it's not just mine anymore than someone else has done right like I know I've checked scripts for some of you
Not me nigga before but I don't know who I think I made hippo check one of mine one time
I know I've checked hippo stuff on his blog before incidentally any you guys could send me one
I'd be happy to do it if you ever want
The thing about that
I was gonna talk about is I don't like
Like the idea of giving anyone an entire script because then all my jokes are spoiled and especially any of you guys
I don't want you guys to to see my script and see what I'm going for and then you know not be surprised and laugh at a joke
I mean you don't laugh, but it's just I like keeping cool things to surprise and I don't really usually like asking for help for that reason
But it's spoiling it for one person to make it better for thousands, so he's got to get around that mental block
But then again, I really care much more about what you guys think of my content than any of my audience for sure
Of course. No, you're all
Okay, I don't I don't know that I would
Trust any of you guys or anyone at all sure like proofread
Like a YouTube video that I'm writing like if I'm writing a book or a novel then yeah
I'm gonna look for an editor or someone who knows about books and novels
But if I'm writing an endless Jess YouTube video nobody gets to fucking touch it, but me
I don't think anybody needs to touch yours because yours are perfect. Well, you know to be fair
You know Jesse is not as my only one like him to be and there are I'm sure there are some changes that Jesse could make or any of
Us could make. Oh, no, um, the thing is what Nate was saying is that we want it to be our own thing
So if we make a mistake, we want to we want to personally learn from that
And I guess asking for help if you have like a very specific
Like question like like sometimes I come into the chat saying I can't think of a word that means this because I just need a word
I need a word that describes something. Well, and yeah
Direct advice from people is not the right idea 95% of the time unless you are like just just
Starting out because really the best thing to do is just make it and then sense
Clues and tells and signs and subtleties from the reaction that people get like digi all the time
Well explain how he tools his videos to cater to the way that people are reacting
But scarcely does that come in the form of just doing what people say they want it comes in the form of analyzing their reaction
And coming to new conclusions that they didn't even realize
That that comes down to a lot of the the classic. What was it prego sauce? Oh, yeah
It's a principal in economics about pasta sauce about how
Like basically they were trying to find new ways to make pasta sauce and they like asked people what what should we do?
And people gave suggestions and those didn't sell it all instead
They just made stuff up and gave it to an audience and the audience ended up liking it
And it just goes to show how the audience does not know what they of course, of course
Like they know whether they like it or not, but they don't know what they want it to be
You're slightly confusing. I am jimquisition videos. He has one about pasta sauce about I don't know if I've seen either
Then he has the other one about he has the other one about coffee
Where in focus group testing if you do a forum if you give people you ask people directly what kind of coffee they want
They over well money say they want a rich dark roast because that makes you sound cool
But then if you actually observe buying habits people usually like a shitload of ice and milk and cream
Yeah, they like weak-ass water down shit
So like when I I mean I will all the time ask people like hey
What should I make a video about or something like that?
But I never do anything that suggested to me like I'll ask I'll ask like all the time
Like I'll go on Twitter and do like polls or like ask people and then not do any of it and and instead
What I'm really trying to get is more of like just a sense of what people think I do right, you know like almost like
Yeah
Understanding the nuances of what makes art good is sort of what we all specialize in and monkey parodies us for thinking
We're so good at specializing in because
Yeah, like you know, I've experienced this make a fucking video like hey guys. Here's this game
It's called Undertale and here's five reasons why it's good and then everyone's like that's not why it's good
It's good because good characters and the good music
It's got good music. I mean that's why I know that people don't know shit
What my audience thinks they want from me is like go take
Like just make another video about the next episode of Evangelion, you know like oh there's got it
You talked about the first nine
There's got to be just as much to say about episode 10 or like take FLCL and break it down
We know there's a lot to say about FLCL because of course there is you know, but like well
Is that what is that actually going to be what they want when I make it? You know, is it or am I going to go?
definitely like
judging by
Like a YouTube comments. It's clear that
Nobody knows how to scrutinize my work correctly
They all do it wrong. So I definitely and I think that is not just applying to me
I think that probably applies to most people
I think that you should definitely cultivate the ability to scrutinize your own work
Before you like you shouldn't have you shouldn't depend
That is true
That is true, but you are in the entertainment business
So if people are not appreciating on a high on a large enough scale at some point the responsibility does fall to you
Right, but what he's saying is that you don't listen to what they say is wrong with it
Oh, of course, right. They don't know anything about like I mean like I feel like when I'm going over my own writing and I'm you know
Editing it and taking out redundancies to make it into a video mode
I mean, I might make mistakes and as few redundancies might get by me even
But I would almost rather have my mistakes left in it than have someone else fix it and have their stamp on it
Yeah, you know like whenever I've made like a mistake
I would rather if I if I make like an mistake early on and like I say a word wrong
I'd rather use that as an opportunity to do a silly editing thing to show how fallible I am like something
Anything to make it like more like, you know, I would just work with what I have even if I made it
Yeah, in the event that someone gives you constructive criticism and it actually
Works it actually makes sense on its face then follow it in the event that happens
You know whole time. I was making videos Digi was the only one who ever gave me like constructive criticism that like made sense
And was correct and even then I always told him that he's wrong just for artistic integrity reasons
And then just silently fix the problems later. Oh
You've all done that to me. So it's fine. Don't worry
And I don't worry. This is how it's supposed to be. It's never said like oh, I changed my titles and thumbnails
explicitly because you told me to 500 times
One time
But I well, it's yeah, but I mean it's not like we talked about it behind your back
Give me a second here. It's not like DaVinci tells me Nate. Do something
I am the DaVinci of YouTube
Everybody at home
Hypothetically if you happen to not be a youtuber and maybe you're like a kid writing an essay
Don't be afraid to show it to people and get advice. We're not yeah, not all YouTube writers like we
Yeah, and I want to bring up like it's well. It's funny that no
We're not moving away until I clarify that it's not that Digi tells me something and I do it
It's that I have I saw the signs were all pointing that was me that was all me
I was explicitly saying to everyone guys, but I've done the research. I know the results
I don't do this. It's not like I'm there looking at your full month study. It's just a guy tell me what all right
Well, okay. I anyway made a realization. Okay, it's funny to me because Nate and Jesse and hippo are all very much like
Suggesting like I want it to be my product and like my it's it's all me and I don't want somebody else to like affect it
Yeah, I feel the total opposite. I will
Freely allow anybody's mark to be made on my video
I mean I blatantly copy other people's styles and tell like say so I do videos that other people suggested just recently I did
Why I dropped every anime I dropped because some guy on Twitter said it would be a good idea and I was like, hey
Yeah, let's do that and but the biggest way because I have to do edit my videos and I give him literally full rate like free range
You can do whatever the fuck he wants. I don't yeah, but I think the thing about that is that, you know
I will for me anyway is that a lot of the the comedy has to be like coming from me
Like if I think it's funny
It'll be like a thing like either I edit or I say it that way or like, you know
It's a different type of video too, you know
It's it's a different it's a different process because sure but like I mean I like
A lot of what happens in my videos now is just not my ideas or comedy
It's just devues and I like it more than what I would have come up with like yeah
But there's also the case that if I had if I say if I had an editor
He might do stuff that is worse than what I would have come up with and I would have to teach him at that point
Because like I know I'm very funny when it comes to things
Did you did you put in the time and you know, you know, the diva has been fully vetted at this point
So yeah, I mean if I had if I had a diva maybe but I don't have a diva. There's only one
I could be your diva tonight mom and dad will never know
I mean, I just yeah, like I constantly get offers of people
Why too sorry, did you know I constantly get offers of people
Like hippo said of like offering to edit my videos for me
You're like, you know, just decrease some of my workload and get more of my stuff out there, right, but like
If I have to train someone to edit the way that I would edit then that's like would take up just as much time
And be just as redundant as me editing it myself
It's a business cost, you know, like I when I was working on the galco video with this this new guy snooping turtle who is great
He's wonderful. Like I put out a Twitter like hey, I'm looking for a new editor
He was one of the guys who responded I checked out everybody's work his I like the best
So we ended up working together and you know, like we it took time like we went through and we went through the whole rigamarole
Of like going through like every bit submitting to me for approval. Okay, we'd work on in the next part submit that okay
These sorts of changes need to be worked in I need to do some editing and then stick it in and send it back
And but like I was willing to do all that not because it was super efficient at the time
But because I see a future relationship where we're doing more work together faster more efficiently better
And he's certainly he was interested in that and hopefully he still is hopefully hasn't changed his mind
So yeah, it's it's like an investment a sort of long-term investment
I'm much more interested in personally is
Trying to to make it so that I can get away with the least editing possible if you watch my my demon souls review that I made
It's basically it's there's nothing I put a few gifts on I put some video game footage that I recorded in a live stream
I liked your skeleton boys. They were yeah
And that was it. I just put relevant clips in and it was great and people's really like that because it you know
I didn't need to do
What just that that that one very simple
Editing choice right at the beginning of just having the skeleton gifts with the trombones along with the music
Those are trumpets you buffoon
Trumpets whatever
It's trombones because they're skeletons you assie. Oh
Jess to go back to the last point you made
You don't want somebody else to edit your stuff
I know I know there was some talk in this chat about having one of us help out edit the plebe in the weeb
Like what did you decide on that? Do you still think like you are the only one who can do that? Yeah, that's um
Well now it's well like in my mind the plebe in the weeb at this point has morphed into like another
Aspect of the endless Jess grand narrative. So now no one can fucking touch it. Oh now it's trapped in my brain
It is there is one episode that we had talked about having Nate edit for reasons that will become apparent when the episode
but like releases
the um
Yeah, like everyone I started to hear the rumblings like five months in like where the fuck are these episodes?
Yeah, and um
So the only reason you didn't hear the rumblings earlier is because people keep asking me instead of you
I guess but then they found out I didn't communicate well enough that Jesse was editing it
So everyone would just ask me where is the plebe in the weeb all the time
And I really love the clear I don't say as Jesse the artistic vision conveyed in the editing
It's so like it's all from Jesse's perspective and he just doesn't give a fuck. That's what's great. It's really great
It's really yeah, like that's the that's the reason because it's like how can I explain that idea to like an editor and have it
Make any sense like it can only be like how do I like how do I sit down the guy and be like, okay?
This this is not or this is not an anime talk show
This is a show about me ruining an anime talk show because I don't want to be there and it's all from my perspective and
When they talk about time slowing down
You're gonna slow time down and go into my brain and look at the French Revolution
Set to the music from cross and which was an anime that came out two years ago that nobody in the world watched
And also every time that Jeff coughs, I want you to zoom in on him coughing for no reason at all
To be an extended ten minute section at the end where everything that did you saying about directing an anime is
Reflected in like weird like filters on the screen and his head gets fucking stupid and weird when he says the word off-model and shit
Like I can't possibly it's someone down and explain it would be it would take longer than editing it myself
But that's a very visionary video, and I'm sure you could have likes like smaller shit that you could pass along
You know like it's funny for me because of my most like my big videos like the main channel
Highly edited stuff is the one I want out of my hands and in devues
Whereas the stuff that like I couldn't possibly give to him that like I have to put my creative stamp on would be like
Insomnia analysis because it's so fucking weird like my even I don't fully understand my intentions with it
But it has to be me because how could anyone possibly know like I mean I'd just be giving you like a bunch of
Completely meaningless footage and being like do something with this
It's like how do you know which rap song matches best with the emotion that's on my face in this granted this clip
Yeah, I mean that's entirely true
There's definitely projects that are for you and you alone to do but like I mean the reality still exists
Of course that there are plenty of projects that you can have other people do right like galco and one punch man
Like you didn't edit those those I just wrote the scripts
And I thought you know what these are cool and all but I don't really give that much of a shit about the things that I brought
Even though I you know those are all at the time. I thought hey
These are really cool thoughts. I want to tell a story about or whatever and but yeah
I was happy to pass them off to give somebody else to edit and came out good
Wow, this should have a lot to do with the topic conciseness. Yeah, well, I mean a conciseness
But the workflow that the thing about writing concisely is that it's not a topic you could talk about for an hour
I want to ask everybody like do you guys have any specific things that videos do that waste time that isn't hey guys?
Sorry, I haven't made a video in a while and also when I thought the show was gonna come out
I thought it was gonna be this but it turned out to be that any other specific things that you feel waste your time
I mean, it's just constant what I see in like especially analysis videos is constant redundancy and just
Saying the same thing three different ways and not seeming to realize that you're doing yeah, you know like hey guys
It's RC anime and like it's RC anime. Hi guys and guys. Hey, it's RC anime. Just stop it
We got the first you know like I remember going into making videos because I've always felt that making a point
Concisely is a thing like even back when I made videos in like 2008
I'm like I hated when people were like hi everybody. Hey guys. I never I've never started a video with hey guys
Sometimes I started a video with hello as dramatically as possible when I feel it's necessary
So I've always had a I've always been a stickler for not wasting time
I feel the same way about that specific thing. I always was like if you have to say hello get out, you know
But you know over time people have said well, I mean, you know, it's fine. It's good and it's good and it's fine
I'm like, I guess I guess it is good and it's fine and and sometimes I do it
I just you know when I'm recording
You know that guitar whole video or vlog right?
Sometimes I don't start with the point because I don't know what I'm doing. I'm just saying the fucking
Correctly, there's one video of yours where you're like this game is just
good
Capulary what's that?
My favorite of all time is hippo's line
It's got level design and like that was
Yeah, almost like any kind of setup at all is sort of
counterintuitive to
Like the the YouTube format as a medium like
Like in like in skits, for example, like you have a like a wacky character
showing up and
Something happens. You're having a conversation with like a cult corona and like
I like
Looking at it like as though it were like a movie or a TV show like
Screenwriting tells you that like there should like this this conversation needs to make sense
Yeah, yeah, and like the sentences need to flow together
But in a YouTube video that just makes it like long and take away from the point of the video and just boring and redundant
and what and what I eventually came to learn is to
Harness the inherent like popcorn II stupid stupidity of YouTube. So like
Cold corona doesn't need to come in and say this is why I'm here and this is what we're going to talk about
I can just like throw him in as a complete non sequitur for no reason but and just get to the goddamn joke
Tar like as in a centaur sequitur, what? Oh
Boy, oh boy
So as I was saying, you know, you can go into videos of going I'm gonna be concise
Well, I don't know if what I said made it's not necessarily easy
So when I started making videos like trying to do it professionally and all right what I'd come into is wow
I have this like interesting point to make how the fuck do I make it concisely?
So a lot of times I just didn't it took me like three paragraphs
But I could have written it in one paragraph
But I didn't know how to make that paragraph and what I there was one video in particular where I was talking about gravity falls
And shit and I was just like at the point. I was trying to make I felt like I needed
I needed three paragraphs to make the point because like
Basically, the first paragraph has the first 30% of the point then the second paragraph has the second 30% of the point and so on
But in order for those paragraphs to even make sense in the English language
I had to keep repeating the first percentages over and over again and just weaving more in each time
It's just it's just hard. It just takes a lot of legwork
You just have to listen to mr. B tongue videos on repeat every day. Yeah, I want to get into why I think it happens shit
And I'll also say of what Jesse was saying about cold corona like if you want to everyone should emulate
The existence of Cal Chuchesta as a side character in videos because you can watch any needle drop video and he never
Explains what the fuck Cal Chuchesta is he just shows up and says some weird shit in in like 30% of his videos
And you just kind of have to either know the lore of the channel or like you're just gonna go
Okay, well, I don't know what that was about, but it was funny, you know like
Because who cares what it actually is absent what who the fuck cares
But um the reason I think it happens where people repeat themselves so much is that
They feel like this point needs more weight than the amount of words
They can use for it and this happens to me a lot
Um and the biggest place I see this happening in anime analysis in particular is when trying to describe visuals
People will always say like the visuals of this show are really incredible
But they don't know how to explain that in more depth
So they say like the animation is really great the color design is really great
Yeah, the the way that things flow together is really great and they're basically just emphasizing again and again the point
They made already the visuals are really great
And it's cuz like
Unless you can pick apart like one moment to really dig into that then it's hard to
To describe that in broad terms, but there it's like you've got something in your brain
That's like no I have to make sure they understand they have to know how great the visuals are
This can't just be a flippant one-off point in the video
But you end up just repeating yourself ad nauseam and an example and like not to throw shade at this guy
Cuz I love him, but super eyepatch will just had a video about the newest season of samurai Jack
And he kind of does that with the visuals where he talks about it for like three minutes
Basically just emphasizing again and again how good the show looks and like the on-screen footage is doing all the leg work as it is
He didn't need to say anything. That's really the point that he's just trying to fill time so we can show you slides
It could very well be but like it obviously it doesn't that could be effective
But just make an AMV put an AMV in the middle of your video that'll do enough
Emphasizing one point over another doesn't can't just be made through the amount of words used it can be done through the tone of the words used like
Yeah, you know the character designers are fine
You know the locations are fine, but that mother fucking knows on the main character. So goddamn shoot moving on right
Forget that swears exist for emphasis. So that's why I like to use them to make things look
Yeah, I was actually just thinking about that from Homestuck after pages and pages probably novels worth of chat logs
There's one moment where the way that you read the chat log is slightly different to really emphasize an important sentence
And like obviously super eyepatch wolf does this because for him the most important thing is to say the title of the video
He's like why as dramatically as you should watch
Show
That shit cracks me up every time but like um, I think the best way to do it in is is to
Like what I do with my composer videos were like, I know I can't say seven minutes worth of shit about an anime composer
So instead I'm just gonna play the fucking music and pop in every once in a while and say that was good
Like canapa has almost done something similar with animators except he talks almost too much because he will just keep repeating like and the
Animation here is drop dead gorgeous
And then he'll like play a clip and then he'll say and then over here the animation is so incredible
I like play I like I get it dude. Just make it just make a sake of a mad
Just have like an intro to it or something which I did that too with my
Videos that I always forget exist because they weren't on YouTube
Where I just like showed off like the early work of a bunch of like or it was directors who had previously been animators
And I had this video where it was basically an AMV where every once in a while
I'd cut in and say here's this guy and here's the stuff he did and then it's just another short AMV
You know cuz like yeah, sometimes you don't have enough words to really describe it
So like don't try to force the format on it
Be an analysis this particular brand of decisiveness you're talking about does not actually save you any time
It's just saving you a number of words wasted on the page
Yeah, well because it just sounds like shit when someone just keeps
Over and over again, you're like I fucking get it
You know just I feel like it's more effective if you just show it and and the audience will feel it emotionally, you know like
The Lucifer in the biscuit hammer video where you at no point or better example the girl in the gun part one
Like the bulk of that video is just an AMV with images showing your emotional reactions
Imagine how fucking garbage that video would be if instead of all those reactions
It was you describing your reactions to each moment and then that moment was so sad
Like in this moment was so uplifting none of the words it would it would be terrible
It would be awful to just oh my god
And then they got like twice as cool and then I was like four times as cool
Yeah, and I mean that's all those visuals are really saying yes, but it makes you feel it the same way like you
You're just you're going from a face that looks shocked to a face that looks utterly shocked
Then a physical transformation of my body exactly a real man
And it's like we we feel what you felt we don't even have to see the show to understand what you were feeling and like it means
It just hits you way harder to see it that it would be to hear it and like that's
Perfect conciseness you basically summarized and reacted to an entire fucking show in four minutes
Presenting the full range of emotions you felt a video is a fucking masterpiece
Absolutely a fucking masterpiece
You know what I'm kind of tired of is
Blowing smoke up Nate's ass about his girl
Yeah, well
What I'm kind of annoyed with is people being you know, they got all their concise talking but now with
With more, you know super eye patch wolf nerd writer sort of breathy talkie sort of oh
Fucking so cool guys. They they give it
Just those two seconds of imitation were hilarious to me
Make a parody video give
Yes, but that there's never really enough breathing room for me to feel like any of it means anything
Oh, yeah, I agree because I'm editing a blood-borne video and I've I've got this whole big
Filmed live-action bit at the beginning and I didn't expect it to be like really long
But at the moment it's like literally the size of my actual analysis that comes afterwards
And it's so good just listen just watching it and seeing how slow it is
It sets the tone of the game and then also the review because I you know, I'm silly and it's like it's
It has I really like it. I was just watching it. I'm like, why don't why don't and that analytical videos
Have more than just a small pause and then a swell of music before going into a big old boring thing
Those guys are a little bit to one note like they really they stick in one emotional range when they don't understand
I mean if they're trying to make a grand point. I really think like my girl log in part two does that correctly
It's it's about building to a point and you could be silly and you want to catch people off guard and make them laugh
And surprise them and then at the end when you're making your grand point
It's at that point that you've earned the climax. That's when you hit them with like the big music
I literally can't watch Nerdwriter anymore because I feel like every video he makes is trying to make the exact same point
This thing is impressive. Yeah, or Captain Christian as well. Like it's always it's always just building up to like wow
They sure did think about that. They sure didn't work. They sure did their jobs and made something good, you know, like but um
someone who I think does that kind of dramatic presentation well is a
Um body video where like it actually sucks you into the world. He's describing, you know, like he because it is like like
Hippo said with a nerdwriter. He's not slow enough. He's being slow to sound dramatic
Right, but then it just creates this kind of white noise feeling because not everything he's saying is dramatic body
I just feel just describing what's good about this movie and it's like this doesn't need this dramatic emotional
Wait, I don't think I was like a story teller
Is it all the stuff he's talking about is just the souls games which never get tired some of hearing about how great they are
Yeah, well and they have a consistent tone
So he can apply the same thing to every one and it it makes sense because you're always listening to
Because he's always making all the edits slick and I'm sure it's just because I make videos
But it always distracts me
Everything everything about nerdwriter distracts me now like because all I see is the artifice
Like I can't I can't even understand what he's talking about anymore
Cuz all I see is the artifice of the shit that he's been doing for two fucking years and has changed none of you know
Yeah, but like he always tries to like adjust the settings ever so slightly you never see quite the same thing, right?
You can just look at his thumbnail. It's the same feel and he has like 20 different fonts, right?
He really puts a lot of effort into typography and it's really distracting the typography is really distracting
It is it is great as I it's great on its own
But it's great in a way that takes away from it, you know
Just like I remember the day that I found the font that I use all the time now
That was a good day never had to think about what font to use is that the TBAP one
No, showcard gothic that was the TBAP one, but now I use Microsoft Tiley Microsoft Tiley. I'm all blue highway, baby
I know you are and I don't even think it looks good. I just it looks nice. It's fine. I'm gonna hate fonts
I'm getting pretty sick of blue highway at this point, but that's how I should feel. I don't want to change the font. It's like
Yeah, sorry hippo
Just to just to finish the blue highway point. Yeah, I I also like I mean I again
I don't even think it necessarily looks good. It's just that no one else uses it
So like it's so definitively mine that like and I don't know a better one, you know, so it's like fuck it
Let's just stick with this might as well. Okay. What were you saying though?
I was well, I was just saying I hate fonts and every time I have to choose a font is the fucking worst thing because I can
Never remember what fonts I've used before I never keep a record of it because I can't be able to type it down and then save a file somewhere
And then you know go on and use it forever. I
Can't remember them. I can never remember what I have been used
I I would recommend doing what Munchie did which is genius which he has a font called my script where it's just you turn your
handwriting into a font and
We use that for the s4 diaries like all of the like title cards and everything because Munchie had designed
The backgrounds for that and so if you watch like the ending of those videos
It's a great-looking font that he had of just his handwriting and like it was
Making fonts at age like 14
Yeah, I remember as other children are just finger banging in the backseat of mom's minivan
Just get serious kids get on Munchie's level remember CGP gray talking about how he like has
Specific fonts for specific purposes like there's one font that always is used if the words represent his own statement
From his own mind then he has another font that represents the collective opinion and another
Font that represents like straw man or something. I don't remember it's an early episode of hello internet
Where he breaks down like the different fonts that have different voices and I thought yeah
Fonds the thing the thing about that is that when I'm when I'm trying to type it like I need some text and I just go
Okay, let's get a font. I've never really prepared to think for any sort of a length of time about what font will be appropriate
So I feel like if I don't sit down and think about all these different fonts and which ones work for different things
I'm just gonna pick a random one every time because I can't be bothered to think about it because I just need the words on the screen
Yeah, yeah, what you should do is you should decide when you like you should use it in a video
And then what you should do is next time you're making a video open up that old Vegas project be like
Ah, yes, this is the file or this is the font I use and then use that and eventually you will just remember forever
There are font finder software. I did that like a website for my
Different give finishes point. Yeah, what we're saying
Well, I did that for my my pony reviews, but I got bored of it and now I can't I don't want to use it anymore
So now I just have a font that I will never use as opposed to a bunch of fonts that I will just randomly use at any time
Hey, Nate, let me finish this point. I intend to I am suffering with three-second lag here, brother
Boy person, okay, but yeah, there was talking over each other going on
So somebody had to go first. Okay, but in any case, I feel like we're done. I feel like we've hit the wall here
We're just kind of rambling. Why don't we go to questions? What do you think? We I'm okay with that
Monkey, did you want to talk about concise writing in fiction at all since you're here and haven't said shit? Yeah
In fiction or non-fiction Jesse wants to say something to her, and yeah, what Jesse, what were you gonna say?
Jesse Jesse
Don't remember. God damn it. I felt like I had a lot to say about this topic, but then I got scared and became confused
Okay, well the monkey you can go on and then maybe you'll remember
Yeah, I mean just I've already kind of said it in terms of concise writing
You can never trust yourself because you know what point you want to make but that point not might not be clear to somebody else
Who is experiencing the writing for the first time so I would say
Always find a trusted friend or parent or teacher to just look over that shit and tell you if you sound like a retard or not
I don't have any friends and also maybe more than one because I've started to have some concern that
Because I pass all my scripts to DeVue and I just kind of count on like well if DeVue gets it
It's fine, but DeVue also will listen to my video over and over again
And is definitely gonna understand it by the time it goes out and then sometimes I think maybe both of us
Understand it better than the audience is going to yeah
Fair enough to be fair. I don't do that as much
I mostly listen to it like once and then I just sit on it for days
And then maybe I listen to it one more time and then I go into editing it the last couple of videos
I've done like that. So hopefully not I don't know
I just I do I worry sometimes that me and you are so steeped in my
Analytical voice that we will autumn like of course we get the point that I'm making
And then but I have some videos that I'll return to like six months later
Once I've forgotten what the point was that video and I watch it and there's certain parts or I'm like
I don't know if I was clear enough here
You know like oh, I don't know if I really like if the audience will really appreciate what I'm saying unless they watch the video twice
You know because sometimes I'm too concise and I guess we need a PCP editorial department
Yeah, well the funny thing is that I I think I am amazing at editing anyone else's stuff
Like if it would be you then yeah, it would just be me
But then somebody would have to do mine probably you know
And it would just have to be tell me if it makes sense or not and if not I'll go fix
I remember one time there is this website really ancient web
1.5 website that was like dude pay us to give you the service of us editing your
Writing your pros and it goes on and on about how you really can't notice the flaws in your own works
And it was just talking about how much you really needs to hire editors and we're here to serve you and the html
Was so fucked up that you couldn't even see half the text
It was like uncensored and all the buttons were too big and you couldn't it was like an absolute mess for website
They specced into editing too hard and didn't put it into web design. They thought that was just like huh irony
well, yeah, and it's funny too because
Because I used to always show my videos to Victor and I'd ask him like did you get all that like did you understand it and like
Half the time he's like yeah, of course because like Victor does think analytically too like a lot of the time stuff that I say
He thinks is obvious and he's like you mean to tell me that people wouldn't know this already and I'm like no most people are
Retard and don't think about anything
But then there's also stuff where I will present it to somebody and I'll say like did you get that and they'll say yeah
And it'll be like well, what what was the point I was making they're like, I don't know like I know I understood it
I just don't know what the hell it was about. I'm like, yeah
Understanding works. Well, it's kind of just consume stuff though. They don't really yeah
Well, I think there's a lot of people who like just like kind of watch the video and like they can tell that what I'm saying makes sense
Yeah, they just don't fully process it and like they just go. Yeah, that was smart like I can tell that was smart
Yeah, I don't know what you said though, you know, like well, that's the thing some people aren't
Analytically minded in that way and even if they did understand it like properly
They may not be able to communicate it because they're not good at that
Yeah, they wouldn't be able to tell you back at you. I think that's true Victor like I think Victor understands all my videos
And just can't explain it back to me
But I have had people who I know
Don't get it and and like cuz I could see it in their eyes. They have that deer in the headlights retard look, you know
It's kind of like me and me and Jesse were discussing
rap lyricists recently and how
We both think MF doom is overrated
Because everyone always talks about how amazing doom is for his like crazy rhyme schemes and stuff
But most of his lyrics are literal fucking nonsense
And I think it's just that people are so impressed by like
The fact that he's making all these rhymes and like in stuff that they don't like it just goes over their head
And they think well, I just don't understand it cuz it's too smart. That's a real a lot of a lot of rappers
I notice really
Tend to bog themselves down in the show-offy like internal rhyming
Right to a ridiculous point and it is you know, it is impressive
But a lot of them are also not saying anything. Yeah, like it's like rap like there's been a lot like yeah
Like some of the best rappers ever, you know weren't rhyming every single word
They were just saying statements that rhymed
Yeah, like shake your fucking rapper
Yeah, if you don't see the vision if you don't see the vision in over your head. I'm floating
I got your girl deep throat
You're just not you're not up to stop which one is that that's a drop God somewhere. I think I
Could be rap God is like I mean in fairness rap God is like about the idea that he doesn't have to make a point
He's just flexing nuts, but that's why it's an obnoxious fucking piece of shit song
Hey
Wisdom in what is a juggalo? I don't know but you ask what it is. Well fuck if I know
Like showing shit to our family, you know like I have some pretty decent resources for that because I could I have my dad, right?
And my dad is someone who is?
Intellectual and is analytical and open-minded
But is like a baby boomer who has literally no interest or point of reference for anything
I care about and always forgets everything that I tell him after I'm done explaining it
so basically I'm able to use him as like a
Mechanism to like if I can explain something in a way that he gets and is mildly interested by then I know I'm doing it correctly
Like one time I explained Sonic OCs to him, right?
So first I had to explain Sonic and then the adventure era and then the concept of fandom and then OCs and he was like oh
Okay, and I can tell in his face when he's getting something or not
So yeah, yeah, you can use your family
You can't bother them and waste their time and waste their life
To help my kids good for that as well
Except that he has such a short attention span that somewhere in the middle
He'll like notice something out of the corner of his eye and it'll completely make him wipe all memory of the conversation
He's having he's a squirrel like a human squirrel
My brother as well. My brother is I guess I'm going down the list here
Just so that you guys can compare it to your own families and think about what resources you have in them because like my brother is someone who
Can appreciate all the things that I appreciate in art, but has an
Unbelievably short fuse for giving for no longer giving a shit
So it's like if anything isn't perfect then he's gonna be like, okay, I'm done with this
So it's like he's a pretty good useful to I was like explaining to my brother a lot of my ideas for for a video game
And like he was on he was nodding his head at all of them
Unfucking presidented with me telling him my ideas. So that really was a good sign for me
Yeah, what are we still going to questions I
Still okay, I have two points two pieces of advice
Keeping it in the realm of like you writing concisely for YouTube because that's what I know
That's our area of expertise
I have two pieces of advice that I've thought of during this for writing concisely as I explained that I have these two pieces of advice as
Inconsisely as possible by repeating myself 50 times the first piece of advice is
Never write an intro don't do it intros are always bad
They're always a waste of time right just if it if you want to do like a like a skit
Or like a funny aside put it in the middle of the video because no one's going to sit through an intro to get to your point
But if you just start throw them right in there to the point then they'll see that and get to whatever else other
Tell them to not watch the video, which is what you do half the time just like this video isn't good. Don't watch it
Yeah, because yeah
Audience I warn them when a video is garbage to piggyback on that a little bit
I'll say I think I think a lot of why intros get written is that people don't know how to start their paper or whatever
Like they're just looking for a way to like get the juices rolling
So I'll say write an intro and then delete it like once you've got the ball rolling and you figure out what you're saying
Just go back and delete the intro. I don't I think it comes from that, you know
High school college you have to have this many words
You have to have a thesis that is three seconds long your thesis doesn't have to be so many sentences long
It can be one word you get one sentence this thing is cool the end then get to the fucking point
I mean if you saw like my last video
My last video had the thesis in the title and I don't even say it in the like the title
Yeah, like how much does
Visuals matter in anime and then the first sentence video is obviously it's a matter of opinion, you know
So I just didn't yeah never write intros don't waste anyone's time
It's just jump into it you you have the compulsion to think that you'll lose people by jumping into it
But you won't the opposite is true and this is um
This is something that I've learned by sucking at it for very long and very slowly coming to terms with how to write for YouTube
Particularly and the other piece of advice that that I've learned mainly by sucking at it myself for many years before I
Slowly got the hang of it. Um is not every video has to be mr. Plinkett
Yeah, there's the compulsion especially for like people who write analysis type videos of
This video about this thing has to say everything about this thing
I'm gonna encompass the entire scope of it. Sometimes it works out. Well, you know Nate's Gurren login is a great video
But even that's in two parts. Um, yep
Yeah, I used to do that all the time and
It would really hamstring me because I'd say this. Yeah, you know what?
You know what YouTube review show suffers for trying to make every episode mr. Plinkett same to me
What's that mr. Plinkett that's true
Mr. Plinkett show itself has all these episodes that are trying to be mr. Plinkett and don't need to be and I'm just like what's like
No, what are you talking about? I think he means like like babies day out didn't have to be a 45 minute video
No, that was a 23 minute video and it was freeing because they all thought he was gonna do episode 3 of Star Wars
Then he did a kids movie. Yeah, that was fine. That's a joke
But like you know like say the um the Indiana Jones one that was just like the only point
I can actively remember is they don't have any violence that that was the Indiana Jones video is very meandering and all over the place
I feel like he was trying to force an hour of content out of it
And it was just like exploring like what they can do in the future like what sort of content will work
Like are we really just gonna have to do Plinkett forever? I don't like that was early days
I think they were still
I mean it's my point is that you can really hamstring yourself by trying to put everything into a single video
And you won't get as much content out as fast as possible. You won't improve me a math of that
Yeah, and I'm you know like for example, I'm looking right now
And at like an old like a gun buster my Japanese anime is that I wrote two years ago, and it's like 25 pages long
Yeah, I never got around to actually making it because I'm looking at these 25 pages of words
And I'm like I don't want to edit all of this
But now I'm looking at it years later and just thinking well wait a minute
I can clearly split this up into like four different videos if I yeah, and that would be like way easier and actually getting made that way
So just just don't not everything else
And I think that's the problem with like the extra credits problem where we've explained all the shit
I don't need analysis to exist anymore. I know it all now
But the whole point of continuing to make pieces in an artistic medium for the incoming generations
Is you have to keep making the point to people so I feel like we just need kids analysis
We need like specifically PBS Nerdwriter that is just like telling you all the basic shit
The cartoon dog talks about ludonarrative dissonance and you have a fucking moose comes in and talks about Xomkin's work, right?
And that way like all the adults can just focus on higher-minded shit
I'm glad Jesse brought all that up because me and Nate were literally talking about this last night
I think during the interview that yeah
This will be out the Nate interviews gonna be out
So I interviewed me and we were talking about how there was kind of this perception that we all had back in 2015
Where like we all looked up to 45 minute long
hyper detailed analysis like you know like mr. Beaton on Mass Effect or
Mr. Plinkett or
Sequelitis and like we all had this idea like that's the ultimate video. That's what we should all be trying to do
That's what matters the most and Nate did Girl in the Gone Part 2 and Jesse did the drowning in horse shoes videos leading up to
Horseshoe finale and I did the SAO videos the the asterisk war which I mean asterisk war at least split into parts in like a
Big way, you know
But like we all had this idea of like it has to be the biggest possible thing
And what that it yeah what eventually happens is you never make it
And then you end up with like more than one of those like it's one thing if you have one
You know you have to do right girl in the gone. It had to happen to be done, you know and like
There's there's a couple that I think probably I still have to do
You know
But like one of the biggest hurdles I ever got over as a creator was deciding not to write a book about ava
And just to make videos about whatever ideas I had about ava and and now I have like eight hyper successful
Evangelion videos and I still could make like 20 more
as the ideas come to me, but
Those would not be out
Like if I was still in the mindset that I have to make one giant ava video there would still be no ava video
And it's question. That's how stuff becomes that's how stuff becomes too much of a burden
That's how you get buried under your own ideas. That's how a boy gets trapped in the furnace room
And you don't want that you don't want that you do not what there's a spooky pattern there. Watch out
That's spooky bad video actually freaked me out. Oh man that that that bad is so scary
You don't even know guys every day
I watched that I watched that video
I watched that video while I was alone in a hotel room
And like the the music kind of got into my head and I went outside to have a smoke and I was just kind of like
Guys, we should make this this kids analysis show the the subtext submarine the vinid the venetian
Go to patreon.com slash to procrastinators
Whatever the fuck you are ls if we get ten thousand dollars, we will get hippo to animate
Uh, the animated series talking about analysis that way everyone
From write out the fucking womb. It'll just be our animal characters. Yeah explaining at analytical points. That sounds great
Real quick just for clarification for audience members who may be feeble minded such as myself all the points you just made
How does that comparable to at the beginning of this when you said you put all your points in one video
Whereas anime snob separates them into separate videos like is that kind of the same idea?
Well, what what I mean to say is like
I it's not that I put every idea into one video
It's that my videos tend to go through various points like my videos go through stages. It's always like
However many points. I think belong in this video, you know
Like um, I recently did this video series about miss Kobayashi's dragon maid and it was planned to be three videos
And it's just because I had a shitload of points
And I said well, let's break like I don't want to make a 45 minute video because it's not cost effective
To do that. So let's split it into 15 minute parts
And I had just enough notes about the main character to make one 17 minute video about her
Then I had enough notes about the other characters to make one 13 minutes video about them
And then I had enough notes about the art and animation that I can make a third video whenever I feel like it, you know, so like
Like those videos are
Fairly long individually, but it's because they're going through all of the points that I thought needed to be in one video
Like everything about Kobayashi. So it's kind of like five that anime snob videos in one video
I mean the real problem at the end of the day with anime snob is that the entire video is a waste of time because he's just wrong
He is just wrong. That's I mean, that's the worst part
Like don't don't take this as me in in any way endorsing the way he does things like his style of video could make sense
It's just that he's literally retired. Yeah
Yeah, yeah good anime
So 17 a Pomeranian talks about post modernism. I'll work on my puns. Don't worry
Okay, I I have a tip for for conciseness
um
Stop writing clever youtube titles. I don't like it when
They there you just stop it. This is a personal thing. He's on the war. What does that have to do with conciseness?
Because if you just write the name of the thing plus analysis or review, I wouldn't I'm
Way more likely to click on it if I don't know what it is
If you're trying to convince me to click on a video about the 10 secret hidden things and subtexts
That nobody has noticed about this other thing or anime
I I don't know the anime to begin with. Honestly hippo at this point
I would prefer numbers and exclamation marks because I've at this point gotten
completely sick of the nerd writer style of like the eloquent sentence that sounds all dramatic and hyphalutin, you know like
How this thing captures that just shit, you know like
It seems to work though
Yeah, it seems like it but it works
It works on the sort of people who think they know everything and would like to know the secret special extra things that supers intelligent people
I just want to know stuff. I just want to know about a thing
We will our fans will watch our stuff, but if we want to bring in new people
We have to trick them into watching the video to give them good people. They think they're smart
Well, I do because I want to fucking survive on this shit patrons if you don't bring in new
I will kill all the people
I hate them. I mean hippo stupid. What do you think of my titles hippo?
I can't remember give me a title you have
How I learned to stop worrying and and skip a cashew records
Or uh, well that one's funny. That one's got like a yeah, that one's a reference. So
In a very well-known reference. What's the one I did on kimono friends the lucid dream world of kimono friends?
I don't know. What do you think? I mean hippo. What book are you more likely to read?
satire about women or men are better than women
Like do you want the honest title or the cool title?
I want the cool one. I'm sorry. What I'm saying is I think you're talking about something more specific than what we're
Saying you're talking. Well, what hippo is saying is like
We should name everything like avan galley in review number five like why not give it a no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no, no what I mean is that people
they I've just seen but just recently there's like every single type of video
in that in that of that ilk seems to be under the assumption that you already
know the basics and you're looking for some extra shit and I will never click
on anything that implies that I know what I what I you know like a nerdwriter
videos every title is trying to play into your desire to be smart right like
he's constantly trying to reassure you that by watching his video you are
gaining an arcane knowledge that will make you stronger or give you a deep
appreciation for this cultural touchstone that everybody already understands
give you that nerd credit is so valuable and today's social economy oh my like I
would much rather just watch a straight review of something that everybody is
seen but I haven't no no game reviews for you hug you
let's say like Seinfeld right and I have never seen like a normal straight
review of Seinfeld and but I have seen plenty of annoying like extra videos
about the subtext and the extra things that you you know Seinfeld everyone
know Seinfeld here's some more I will never never enjoy that people complaining
about things that everyone's talking about on the internet that I haven't
heard like you know my introduction to Ludo narrative dissonance was movie was
the game over thinker episode called stop talking to me about Ludo narrative
dissonance and my second exposure to it was someone else being like oh god yeah
it was Jimquisition talking about Ludo scabib disco biscuits like oh jeez so
much Ludo narrative dissonance out there since everyone just spent all their
day reading blog posts by shitty blog artists like me Jimquisition I'm like
no I don't know you're the only person I listen to that complains about this but
if we can't have an intro where we tell people the basics and we also like can't
assume everybody knows everything what are we supposed to do well I'm not
talking about intros I'm talking about entire videos like if you know they're
part of entire video simple this is what we need the fucking we have a
German chef about German expressionism we have a fucking monkeys looking sorry
sorry sorry whatever sorry simultaneously trying to say that you
should like not just do summary but that you should also in hippo wants like
standard reviews but what hippos means is that he wants there to be videos that
are just a actual review of the thing without assuming that everyone's already
seen it it's really all it is is that it's the the flowery and the insinuation
of the title that makes me not want to click on it like if you if you are
talking about say the content of the video is exactly the same if you just
title it Seinfeld analysis then I'm gonna click on it because I want to know
but I think most people wouldn't click on that you gotta play the game title well
I hate YouTube then fair enough yeah I think hippo would title yeah I think
hippo would click on it if you said like why is Seinfeld so well loved you know
if that was the title you'd probably click on that because that's what you're
trying to find out well maybe not at this point because I just I just generally
hate titles video titles they got to go they got to go yeah your channel
banner your channel banner for hypocrites should just be the words I'm gonna
kill you you know you are the hypocrites so it's entirely appropriate that you
make YouTube videos about how much YouTube sucks and is a piece of shit yep
well all right how about we go to the questions now team let's do it let's do
it here we go I feel no ill will towards anyone I am just I don't like
YouTube I don't like seeing titles I don't like seeing titles and reading
them and having to decide on whether or not I hate it I mean why would you want
to review a show you like like why would you want to Seinfeld review if you know
nothing about it anyway couldn't you just read a summary to see if you'd be
into because Gibbs heard a lot about Seinfeld over the years so they just
fucking watch it well I can't have a television I don't know I think of an
analysis is good and interesting you'll just sort of inadvertently get all the
shit and eventually know all the obvious stuff I'm not really I'm not really
looking for a Seinfeld analysis I'm just I just don't like people being smart I
don't like people having smart that's really my entire point if you're trying
to be smart I hate you in forever like after watching like a combined total of
like 15,000 hours of Roger Vanderweed analyzing Sonic I already I now know all
the basic stuff without him ever actually attempting to explain basic stuff
just through inference mm-hmm so here we go people question number one read this
question Nate here I go okay at our old friend ice killer 159 asks yo PCP you
get to experience a piece of media for the first time again what do you choose
between a attorney and death question oh man yeah where you go Elton whoa whoa
definitely lost that's my answer I already know it lost huh even with the
ending oh yeah that's that we know is bad especially oh is bad this is this is
my communist classes are not fucking orange anyone who says the ending of
losses bad I'll fucking find you and I'll kill your whole family Jesse I think
you are as passionate about every opinion you actually end up caring about as
much as Nate is about the glasses thing like I think for you it's like 99% of
opinions you immediately discard because you know that if you let your
opinions sit there for more than five seconds it's gonna become like a hill to
die on I'm passionate about all of my opinions equally until I remember how I
feel about lost and then I'm passionate about nothing
if I could read what I was sorry hippo go ahead now you go okay if I could
experience something for the first time again it would have to be the final
three episodes of season four of Breaking Bad I don't think anything has
enthralled me as a viewer more than what was happening so the first of the
three is the crawlspace episode which is very famous where he laughs at the end
and goes yeah yeah god damn I that that was the bingiest binge watch I've ever
been I'll tell you and that was the cringiest cringe watch I've ever cringed
oh your show sucks for my answer for this like going on most of the like with
most movies and TV shows I tend to like it more the more times I see it so like
most of those I feel like I wouldn't want to hear or see for the first time
but like any album that I like for me like the most magical time with an album
is when I'm first getting into it and it feels mysterious and like I can't tell
the difference between all the songs yet and it's just like like for instance
Rat King so it goes is a great example where I was like playing this album on
repeat while playing fantasy star online for a few days and it would just be like
you know as it's going I pick up on little things I'm like oh here's that
song I remember hearing this part and like it just feels like this endless
magical you know like just getting to hear all these different things that I
didn't know about and then eventually once I've heard the album enough times
and I know exactly what's where that's where I start forming opinions like oh
this song's a little weaker than the others so I might skip that track or
like oh this is the good verse this is the you know that part like oh now I
now I've got like all these opinions about it and I don't have that sheer
just wonder of experience something I don't completely understand yet so like
especially longer albums like third side of tape by Lil ugly main because that
one's like too over two hours long and it's just like a random compilation of
weird songs that that are like all completely different from one another
so it was always like this total mind-altering experience to listen to
it until I'd heard it like 30 times and now it's like oh okay this is the part
where the obnoxious 10-minute black metal song kicks in let's skip that you
know yeah yeah so yeah any album really okay okay
what about the human equation do you want to hear the human equation again
human equation would be yeah that's that's an example of one that in the
early days was like very mysterious I believe the human equation is pussy plus
my face a happy boy did you are we still doing a PCP episode over the human
equation it's on the list if anybody else fucking listens to it we'll get
the boo and Nate and that's all we need I'll listen to it listen to it we'll
fucking make you listen to it did you hear over at his house force him tie him
up clockwork orange style only price ears open instead of his eyes I'll knock
him out and then put it like tie him to a chair and then he'll wake up he'll go
I can't move I don't remember what's happening now I don't remember anything
you fucking pleb by the way my answer this question without a doubt without a
doubt is certainly one piece I want to take that journey again knowing nothing
and luckily for you it's not over yet so you still can that's the great thing
about it man you should you guys I want to tell our audience you have never
heard someone read something more enthusiastically than Nate rage one
piece I'm sitting in the other room and just hearing Naco oh my god go check
out the new episode oh my god I didn't finish this fucking video yet I have to
make it I totally forgot yeah make that shit I'll make it today go check out the
new episode it'll be up like last week at this point of the potty cast and like
the things that happen to this chapter really were yet again the most
blowing things of all time it really scared me I was actually terrifying and
like beyond it was a new fun level I'm glad to find out that I'm not the only
like the only the only loud reader who passionately I scream I yell I like
like when I read comics I like I do all the voices out loud and I like pace
around the room doing my Kevin Conroy voice and my fucking Joker voice and
like if anyone if anyone else is in the house and I don't know about it and they
hear me have to go out of the house screaming and never come back if you
read a comic quietly everything goes according to plan there's no problem
but but you read a comic and you get a little loud everyone loses their mind
if I read a comic quietly then it's not really happening it's just a fake made
up a little book for kids if I read it out loud and the characters are really
here then it's real then it's real hip-hop did you have an answer for this I
I do being a many years veteran of World of Warcraft I'm very I'm very
disillusioned with it I'm very like tired of the high what happens with
World of Warcraft the reason it grips so many people is because the initial
experience of seeing how big the world is in all the places there are is
absolutely fucking magical as the best part of love with it and you just you
want to live there you want to go you want to do everything and I have I've
done literally everything in that game aside from the current expansion and to
the point where it nothing excites me anymore and it really it really is sad
because it's like so much so so cool that's the my fucking that's a great
answer and I feel that way about every MMO I've played sure like with wow it
was specifically just the undead starting country because playing through
that was fucking magical and then I got to the next area which was like the
badlands that thought it was lame so I just restarted and played through the
starting undead place like three times and just until I completely knew it and
then it was not as interesting hey same goes for like Terra or Black Desert like
any of those games when you first started it's just like whoa this this world
it's so huge about the soul the soul starting area was great but I love that
fucking place fucking trolls are the best race everyone else is shit and wow
only trolls are good you have a you have an answer to do yes actually as I was
thinking about it everything that I liked at one point then over consumed I
don't want to regress to a point of not having ever experienced it because it
was instrumental in my understanding of what makes things good and you know I
use it as an influence so I don't want to fuck with the timeline that badly sure
my god you're right to who because if I went back in time to when I hadn't seen
lost I might listen to people who say the ending is bad exactly what I want
there's this stupid dumbass show called the pretender which is sort of like a
proto like like hour-long weekly American drama type of thing that like alias
and lost sort of followed up on and it's like a late 90s thing has a lot of
weird superficial similarities with alias actually and it has an interesting
sort of character premise but it is the Ranma one half of America because it
just it doesn't progress anything ever and it's four seasons long and I just
watched it because I was watching it with my family huge ways to fucking time so
if I it did not like you know there's other shows that like I didn't like and
like I regret watching but I don't regret watching because it was it's like fun
and I think it's interesting how they fuck up the pretender is just mediocre
and stupid and it was just the one time in my life or for whatever reason I was
willing to waste that much time and not expand my knowledge of anything ever for
any reason whatsoever so if I can erase my viewing from history and then have to
begin watching it again my current self will have no tolerance for it and turn
it off immediately and I'll have saved myself like a combined total of like 50
hours so you do it all for those 50 hours yeah use all of it on D you know
what he means yeah the D board okay so that's everybody right we've all gone
through this yep let's I've got here's another question that I absolutely love
okay here we go so this is at pond itator asks at PCP who is the hottest
sailor scout I've spent a lot of time you don't know the well enough it's
absolutely marz is not even a contest not even a doubt wait it's Mars the black
hair the sailor Mars is the black hair I thought it was the coolest guy you've
ever seen the only male one oh that's all that's obvious you're right but aside
aside from the coolest guy I'm looking at up I'm looking at a pop vinyl sailor
Mars right now yeah it's got a picture of all of them lined up next to each
other and Mars is like far and away the hottest the only other one that I like
I mean I do appreciate Jupiter but Mars is by far the best I never seen sailor
moon now I'm just kidding the hottest one is homura I don't know who that is
from come out of magic is that is that is that cat like like the cat from
Sabrina the teenage it's the same cat yes the same thing cool I like that cat I
will fuck that cat okay I still like Captain Crunch and I'll stand by that
okay here we go at solely claw asks if gay was a physical object musical genre
or food what would it be two balls touch gay if gay if gay I'm not I was
gonna say didgy it would be didgy is the by first okay was a food it would
definitely wait they got cut off say that again what my your audio my my my
brilliant corn dog joke oh my god you guys weren't laughing I thought it wasn't
funny I was just like through my fucking corn dog joke out there just like
dead silence like no it finally happened yep it's over for you dude time to walk
into the into the into the snow and die anyone have any of the suggestions for
what gay would be do they say genre of music yeah that was one whichever one
sucks a dad get it okay let's move on to this question this is dead air let's
okay here we go here we go at our hero monkey away asks a very apropos question
what's stopping the other PCB members from doing their own me a math of a
yes I don't know if this is supposed to be an insult he says standards or work
ethic like no one else has low enough standards or they don't have low enough
work ethic to make I came up with one concept where I do a video every day
all year called 2018 too cool zero fucks given one video a day you're going to
hate all of them which is pretty great I do like that a lot I did fucking me a
for three years ago you asshole you didn't brand it hard enough I didn't
brand it at all he didn't brand it all it was a secret it was a secret because
he had money on the line as to whether or not he would succeed and if you
fail a lot of money would have ran away with the money yeah Nate you had to pay
me for that right you bet against me and I think you gave me 10 bucks I don't
think I actually was in on that bet I would have bet against you if I know
you were in on the bet I don't know if you ever paid out but you were in on it
are you sure about that yeah I know you were because Ben Ben was the only one of
the PCP who wouldn't bet against me because he said he wanted to bet for me
and I was like you can't do that and I will give you ten dollars I think you
might have it's possible I really don't remember being involved at all but I'll
trust you here's my theory I'm talking about is in 2014 I made a video every
day in October and I made bets with like everyone I knew like to see if like you
know to incentivize me to do it right mostly it was my mom and dad who like
we're betting the most and and they're the only ones I like really hammered to
pay me but like yeah it made bets with like everybody but I didn't like announce
that I was doing it because I was scared if I did it wouldn't get completed as
tends to be the case when I announced projects so it was only like at the very
end of the month that I acknowledged that I had just done this thing whereas
Nate like made it very clear opposite because you'll get bored if I announce
it then I have to do it or else I won't yeah well speaking of that I had an
idea of doing a July me a math I don't know what I should well I mean in the
meantime you've got your I know it's demon dark blood month bro it's not
really the same but it's it's good similar I like it's more than one it's
more than zero videos I want to say what I usually record all of us are
insanely prolific in that kind of way of me a math of a like Gibbon has had months
where he puts out videos like almost every day on Gibbon take Jesse's had
months where he's put out a video almost every day just on random channels and I
do literally put out a video every day like hey there's the air a furnace room
has no breaks there's been a video every single day that's in addition to pony
cast it's in addition to other videos and other channels I also I did do a video
every day in October of 2013 and I'm still bearing the emotional stress from it
most of those are hidden now but that that was right right I had an idea to
like do like next year do like me a math of a to maybe I'll actually make a video
but like the joke would be that I don't make a video and like I said maybe right
you said maybe I don't actually have to do it great even that would have been too
much work for me I'll just say it here
let's say here's a simple matter of like crop rotation we're like going out into
the world and watching movies and like being a real person to like form actual
opinions is like planting cotton and then yeah making a video explaining your
shit is like planting corn and I think like someone like mr. B tongue right
spent like 30 years just being a normal guy probably writing a lot of college
papers or some shit but never airing out any of his thoughts and then over the
course of a couple years he just drops absolute gold and then he runs out and
he only comes back once a year to like have another little bit of corn yeah so
for me I'm just kind of that's why that's really why I don't have any problem
with not making any videos I'm just I'm just fucking planting cotton up my ass
guys and it's gonna all shoot out one day and incredible rainbow I think I think
everyone needs to understand about me a math of a is that that that thing
wouldn't have been possible if not for the fact that Nate had not been doing
that for the last two years because 30 ideas in a row is a hell of a lot because
our work is all based on other stuff like it's not like Casey Neistat where
he just goes out and literally films his day every day and half the videos are
the exact same like he goes to the airport he flies to another country he
goes somewhere like we have to every single time have something new to talk
about and it's one thing if you go two years making one video every two months
you've got this huge stockade of shit you've been planning to talk about that
you've never gotten around to and then just boom blow through a bunch of it in
a month but if Nate tried to do me a math of a again right afterwards then
suddenly it's gonna be oh shit I'm out of ideas you know that's absolutely true
I there were plenty in that October is that I fucking completely like at the
end of the month you'll see the last like five videos are just like really
struggling to come up with something I do have a bunch of ideas that I you know
was just stockpiling to put as potential stuff but I picked the ones that I
thought were the best but but more so than that what what is interesting to me
about me a math that makes it sort of special I guess is that it really was
very time-bounded and like a one-time thing and it was an event like I to do
it even to do it for a year I really think people would get bored even if I
was delivering content you know better than ever and just doing that same shit
I don't think people would give a fuck after a while which is for you know
variety people are into variety they want to feel like something special is
happening everyone was so hyped to be involved with this thing that was going
on during this time and it was it was very effective but to do it to like
immediately do like the same sort of thing even like two months later they'd
be like oh yeah like we got it here the cheers they'd be like yeah a little
quieter then like maybe a month later so yeah okay we're doing this again all
right same shit so I don't know like yeah yeah that's the only reason I'm not
sure about doing a July one I mean it's not gonna have the same pipe there's
gonna be a few people they'll be like oh you're doing one now that's cool but
really you know I don't really want it to be I don't really care too much about
it being like a big like oh yeah branding and everyone buys all about that
bright shirts mostly cuz I can't be bothered to think about that I just want
to make I just want to get into the habit of being able to make you gotta get
one videos in a month I think it's that that skill is something I need yeah and
I think it's important for everybody to realize that like all of that branding
and stuff is it's not just that that's a good like marketing decision it's that
that's what allowed Nate to do that I couldn't have done it if he didn't make
it a big deal it had to have lots of pressure it had to be like a lot of
personal responsibility on the line personally for me that wouldn't have
worked on me but having money on the line worked right because I am a fucking
Jew and I will not like the idea that I was gonna have to pay out a hundred and
ten dollars because that's about how much how many bets I made yeah the idea of
having to pay a hundred ten dollars because I failed to make a video every
day was completely unacceptable you know it was funny I don't know if I
mentioned this in the interview yesterday but like I had actually been
planning on one of the things I was gonna make as part of me in math but was a
deal with the audience where if I don't succeed at making all this I will like
give the money away that I make during this month to like whatever we'll have
like a poll like I was really considering that but then I just thought you
know what like that is unnecessary I don't think people the problem with that
is it would people would start holding you to like oh it has to be midnight yeah
like then it would have been weird standards for stuff whereas this was
better but yeah that was that was tossed around but yeah I don't know I
guess there's a place for me in math was in the world but I don't know like I
would love a give me a math of some kind I'd love like what I want from give and
that's what me a math was was an excuse for you to just make tons of content
fast I want to know what you're thinking I want to see you do goofy what I want
from given is just in the same thing that I was inspired up with by me a
math of which is a middle ground yeah between like the absolute like I made
this in 10 seconds but it is fucking great that is give and take and the like
this took a whole month that is hypocrite like I want that I'll be
essentially what minuscule reviews are but like without pigeonholing in it into
being called a minuscule review you know yeah so there you go there's your
answer I guess next question let's see here how deep in are we we are one hour
and 49 minutes okay let's we'll do a couple more of these and then we'll
wrap the shit up okay how do we how we got here oh at oh at rain snow hail hey
what's up dude asks a which member slash friend of the PCP if not already doing a
podcast together would you like to at least try to co-host a show with co-hosting
shows people outside the PCP outside the PCP or is that what they said what
member friend friend oh slash member PCP okay so it'd be I think I got the
impression he means like which other PCP member do we want to have an
individual show with right so like who do you want to do things with that you're
not already doing something did you did you has been saying that me and him
should do something but we have no real concrete idea of what exactly concrete
reviews review concrete there you go shows with I've got a show with monkey
and a show with Nate and hippos the last one who I also want to show with but
yeah it would have to be the right show like everybody else I love working with
but like for a weekly show most these motherfuckers are horribly unreliable
like if like Ben who was actually signed up for this episode and he did not show
we haven't started a weekly show with Ben I just like the reason why I'm on so
few episodes of this show is I'm really good at talking myself down from
thinking that I'm gonna have much to say that will be useful and like I'm the
only thing that really motivates me to like to do podcasting is if there is a
ridiculously unnecessarily elaborate plan like which is why I'm so into doing
commentaries with digi where the idea is that we commentary every single main
video and we say literally whatever we want that is what gives it the challenge
that entices me so I feel like if I was to do a podcast it would have to have a
lofty ridiculous plan like finding the bed like a narrative or some kind yeah
some sort of weird gimmick okay fair point and if you like shows with gimmicks
go listen to the insufferable shows social media argument the podcast of
Jones dot com so viewers do I actually do when they have
no but I'm hoping somebody buys it and just makes it porn or something
fucking give suggestions for some overly ambitious podcast concept that I could
possibly be skilled in in some way hit me up with that we had we had teased the
idea between ourselves are doing some sort of like debate or like idea
discussion thing so maybe at some point we'll do something like that I think me
and Nate are gonna end up with like a bunch of podcasts together yeah we got
Aromango has been going really well we've talked about doing I don't know if
we should talk about some other projects we have like several other
brilliant idea that I think it's one of the best I've ever had so I hope that
it we get it going at some point super secret super secret let's real quick
why don't we just talk about just let's just name the ones that exist already
just to run through real quick so there's the PCP of course there's the
pod D cast with me and give which is the one piece weekly there is the pony
cast which is Jesse and give you know my little pony every week what am I
missing out there's insufferable social media between monkey and digi
Aromonga sensei Aromonga sensei digi and Nate and the naru cost of the
naru cast with mage and mage we're working on an episode to hell yeah there's
rowdy fuckers cop killers which is Munchie and Munchie and Ben yeah there's
the stealing your dad's as if it was easy which is me and munchie yep yep there's
there's the the commentary is it me and DeVoo do which is once a month there's the
homestuck thing that munchie's doing on his channel now though that's none of us are really
it was on there but yeah that's mostly his thing there's a sigh tries to get
monkey into because I is an honorary member right you guys all like readies an honorary member
and uh he's he's what he's part of the uh the like the the sub PCP I have in my head
that there's like like there's there's a secret 10 person like PCP it's like the dark pcp it's
the dark pcp yeah it's like it's like it's like latin still sigh uh um uh who else would be in our
night of the nega yeah i know the nega pcb well don't call me negative that's not as would be
digi we talked about this in atlanta that like it's a fighting game and it's the pcp and then
there's all the like the assist oh yeah they're the color swaps right the color swaps or are you
on the summons yeah oh the summons yeah okay so sigh is an alternate skin for digi and like
nine is an alternate skin for nate which is not an insult anymore because sigh has lost a lot of
weight and probably weighs less than i do now so it's no it's an insult on you digi yeah we're
insulting you digi to compare you to sigh i'm saying that it's not an insult to me because
sigh is no longer fat sigh is even it's more of a personality thing wait well it's not insulting
it's perfectly politically correct all i care is that i'm not compared to a fat guy that's the only
thing that matters to me okay yeah what is it i've got the perfect the perfect podcast that needs to
exist uh munchie and jeff something with them something with munchie and jeff being overwhelmed
munchie would destroy his mind yes exactly exactly digi i just thought wouldn't be great in an alternate
timeline where your friend brandon tollantino kept doing podcasts with you and he was actually
known by your current fans because then he could be an alternate skin for hippo and the only one
i could think of oh yeah oh yeah yeah i was actually wondering who'd be the old skit for hippo but
um uh well i think divu and uh and lockwood skill and lockwood still would be monkey and
i mean monkey would be a main character as well but how isn't locklin tall i don't i don't how we
do in this this relationship okay it doesn't matter okay here's our i don't even topic are we on
right now okay we're still talking about podcasts sharing podcast i forget what question that was uh
doesn't matter here's our last question for the day okay benjamin whistle at benjamin whistle
ash what do y'all think of cars what do you think of our cars but i wish i wasn't bored by them
and whenever because like there was a moment where i was thinking about how there's like this subset
of people who are just like oh yeah that's a 95 honda sieve bitch something or other and i'm just
like man you know whenever i'm watching a show and there's a video game console and i and my eyes
light up and like oh what video game console is that and i can tell based on any subtle visual cues
and i'm like man people who are like that with cars get to be like that all day outside i'm like
that's ridiculous how could you possibly deal with that much stimulation of intrigue also what kind
of literally are you the like cars what else do you like pavement do you like unicycles just
i have what i call car dyslexia any two cars that look anything alike i cannot tell them apart
um which makes it difficult to find my own car because my i guess the the design of my car is
very popular in like modern cars so they all look like mine sure it's very very confusing but you
got the beeper the right that thing you don't have that problem when you only ever drive $300
cars from the fucking 70 yeah yeah but like good old inlet g but uh g brain i mean i can't like i
can't differentiate enough between cars to give a fuck about them but like there was a period where
because my dad runs a dealership he also doesn't give a fuck about cars he just is good at selling
but he hired a bunch of my friends and like you an animal somehow them starting to work with cars
made them suddenly like all about cars like all they talk about his cars it was really really
strange like to see a bunch of like like otaku guys suddenly become like these huge car otaku
and like fucking always like buying forza games and like listening to initial d mega mixes and
shit like the initial d thing is cool yeah like they just got way into cars and they
would like talk about it all day and i'm like how can you even tell the difference between
these fucking things my dad is sort of obsessed with cars um you know he's always he's usually
getting like a new one and like he's like he'll always have like a nice car um at our house so
he'll like be he'll sell the old nice one he'll buy a new nice one he wants a constant rotation
it's like what brings him the most joy in life so that's great and like after he retires he's
thinking of like working in it with a dealership in some way be coming like an amateur salesman
just to make a little money um but like he tells me these stories like when he was a little boy
i believe it was he would sit with his grandpa like on uh like the edge of the road they would
watch cars come by and like the grandpa would quiz him like based on the headlight shape of the cars
it'd be like what car is that and it was a game to see how quickly my dad could tell exactly what
like model make year was the fucking car that was coming and at some point he just completely fell
in love with cars and is just super obsessed what pisses me off is that you can be that
and people think that's like relatively normal yeah they do same with sports like like you can
you can know this like insane autistic level of shit about cars and people are just like
hey it's just a car guy this is just this is socially about anime it's like oh i bet that
guy's never gotten laid you know like those are the socially well i mean yeah that's true though
yeah well putting that aside well that's the reason it's a self-perpetuating prophecy like
the people who are like that with anime they think of themselves as guys who oh i'm into
something weird you know whereas everybody needs don't have to think that you know everybody needs
somebody who knows how to fix a car you don't need somebody who knows what fucking i'm not talking
about people who know how to fix a car i'm talking about people who who just memorize car
shit yeah that's not really much of a mechanic or anything he's mostly just an appreciator of
how cars look and shit yeah most car people don't know the first fucking thing and they all think
they do but they don't know how to fix a fucking car you know i'm a car person i've been this whole
time it's a secret yeah the most well-guarded secret of all time tell me tell me three things
about a car that are true tell me three you can't do it guys you can't do it a famous creator of
the video fuck cars a car person at least just well mate uh-huh i lied just now i lied three
times i love i lie i lie i lie i lie i lie i lie i lie i lie i lie i lie i lie i lie it's about it's
about what we wish we knew that's how you get farther in life that's how you progress as a person
i love cars i i i think they're cool i i i deeply envy people who understand them and know about them
Like I say, I watch like regular car reviews on YouTube. I watch top gear sometimes. I look at car
Like I look at cars that are for sale all the time and fantasize about being able to buy all the cars
If I had a million dollars, I'd be the guy who just like goes bankrupt buying like 20 cars
You know my my dream in life my ultimate goal in life is to someday own
The blue viper that I owned in Gran Turismo 3 when I was a kid
And that's what I've been working towards my whole life that goddamn Gran Turismo 3 car
I want it. I thought you wanted a Jeep Wrangler. The Jeep Wrangler has put a stepping stone
Add that to the wiki folks, that's Canon lore. Yeah, all right
The Aztec that you drove in Breaking Bad
You can do that. That's a cheap drink. Yeah, I
Think cars is a terrible movie. Yeah
I think that cars 3 is a step in the right direction after the
One of the worst movies I've ever seen in my life. I don't like it
Toy Story 3 was better. Incidentally Jesse mentioned regular car reviews that guys like to me like the asop rock of YouTube
Like a guy who's like so high-level that I can't even completely comprehend it and that think that might I don't know
I've never subscribed to him. I've only seen a couple of his videos, but he's like the most legitimate like
He like he writes like a real classic journalist like
YouTube analysis videos. It's like his stuff like makes me feel weak. It makes me feel like I'm not doing enough
Like I am not a good enough writer if this guy is out there or a good enough man because I don't have enough cars
Cars are cool. I need to get my I need to get my oil change
Should we describe what
I
Drive a drive a Honda Odyssey a gold Honda Odyssey
Shit bus yeah, I drive a 2015 BMW X1
Yeah, you're just helping people out when they're on the quest to rob you because all your shit's in your car
Did you nothing's in my car? I bring it all in everywhere. It's true. It's true
We got it protected
Did nobody hear my my car? Yeah, I just got why you were playing that I was just confused
Remember when John Chon was funny. I remember have we not had a remember when John Chon was funny podcast
You should do that. He's definitely had more than enough John Chon complaining material
I guess that's true. I guess that's true and others
We have some like meta podcasts that have like slowly pieced themselves together inadvertently like so fuck movie Bob cast
That's like five hours long, but it's never been made intentionally
If you're if you're a PCP fan who wants an excuse to listen back to every episode and find something creative to do with it
Snip together every time we've talked about John Chon or movie Bob or like anyone else
We bring up all the time and just make that a podcast. That'd be cool. That'd be cool
Yeah
Also string together all the times at me and digi privately in the car talked about movie Bob with no microphones because it's fucking hilarious
Yeah, it's like really the only thing like hundreds of hours banging on about the same points that he's made five times before with like no update
I just love shit talking people. Yeah
There's no need to hold back when you're not on fucking, you know
Well, I'm not that I would hold back on a microphone about movie Bob anyway
Sure sure like there's just certain people who you just get glatch on to and it's like you just want to shit on them all the time
I know what you mean
You know what you mean and movie Bob's a big one for especially me and DeVue because we have a lot of the same problems
But just to shit on John Chon one more time speaking of
Conciseness I feel like there's some point to be made with his ridiculously slow upload schedule. Fuck you John Chon
Get your shit together be funny again
Drive to that set. So anyway, we Bob guy
I want I want people to bought to bug me as much as possible
To do the game over thinker PZP lecture because I am qualified to do it
And I think I could and it's the only thing I could do a lecture on I only want to do it
If enough people want me to do it though. I'm not sure. Okay, if you press press just spoiler
It will be just me and spirited and bitter no matter how hard I try not to be it's not gonna be funny
Like well, he is fat. So it's okay. Don't worry about it
Well, we're still talking about the cars we drives. Oh, yeah, I have a I have a funny anecdote, you know
Uh-huh. I got the best car, which is also the worst car
I drive around in like a I drive around in an old blue police car from the 70s or 80s just like
Victoria, yeah, but like I don't have like insurance or like a license plate. Oh
Wait like every
So like I've gotten pulled over a bunch of times and now it's at the point where like
All the cops recognize my car. Everyone knows it
I'm the only guy I'm the only guy driving around in a fucking blue police car from the 70s
So every I get pulled over every day and I owe a lot of money to the courts
You gotta get some fucking go down to the day. I have to get the Tim Horton's name
I have to get my donut in the morning and my coffee
Jesus you gotta I bought these I bought these new adidas just to be my donut shoes
I don't know what shoes in the morning. You're you're never gonna get your goddamn blue viper if you keep leaking money like this
You gotta get your shit together, dude. I need my morning donut
PCP fans also create a supercut impromptu meta PCP episode called Jesse Wood
generational poverty
Oh my god, that's great. Okay. We're done. That's it everybody. Thanks for listening
Thanks for being here everybody. Subscribe to monkey Jones. Make sure you send us more questions so we can answer them
We will answer your question if you use hashtag ask PCP. So make sure you do that or you can at well
No, I'm not gonna tell you that because it doesn't matter go to our Twitter at TP crass inators
But don't say questions there use the hashtag there you go everybody. Thanks for listening. We'll see you next week
Bonus episodes if you pledge $5 to our patreon patreon.com slash the procrastinators make sure you do all that
What was the latest one? It just came out. Oh, we just did a bonus
All the bonus episodes that have happened all of them
All you gotta do is pledge one time you get them all and last episode was five nights at Freddy's versus Chuck E. Cheese
Do you want to hear the throw down of the fucking century? Munchie lays some hot the only combinations
I've ever heard of their worse than this is fucking epic rap battles of history
Yes, we aim for the bottom and we go even further. So thanks for this everybody go pledge for a patreon
Go on here that shit and we will see you next week