I won't bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Mmmmmmmm, it's another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm starting, I guess. I guess I'm starting.
Another week has gone by, another week down the toilet, as always, and it's just me again.
But you know what? Rain or shine, neither hail nor sleet nor fog of war can stay these couriers from their appointed podcast.
It's episode, whatever, 309.
And it's the old, what do you call it, the old Bencast, haven't had one of these in a while, but sometimes you just gotta do it.
So it's time for me to bloviate and waste both of our time to fill air.
That's not true, I won't do that. I will touch upon some things that happened this week, and then I will go to voicemails and we'll just see how long that takes naturally.
Let's see, what happened? What was the week of April 10th like for me? It was my birthday on Thursday.
It was my birthday and I went to my parents' house and they, we got my eyes tested. I did an optometry appointment.
That was fine. That was great. They blew a little puff of air into my eye, which I don't remember that one.
I don't remember that one happening before. It felt weird. I didn't like it, but oh well.
I have the opportunity to pick some new frames when I get new glasses, but I don't know if I will.
I don't know if I can really improve my classic look, which is just the kind of thick rectangular dark frames. I like them.
I don't think, I don't think it gets much better than that for me.
My prescription, I hadn't been to the optometrist in like 10 years, thereabouts, but apparently my prescription has not changed hardly at all.
She said just a minor tweak, so that's pretty good. Glad I'm not deteriorating, at least not in that department.
One place that I am deteriorating, in a sense. I've been, I've lost a bunch of weight again.
This is, I guess this is now a pattern for me, is that I gain like 50 pounds and then I lose like 50 pounds.
I'm down to, I weighed myself either than I was down to 170. I was almost, no I think I was briefly above 200, maybe around Christmas or so.
Now it's April, or like three months into the year and I've lost like 30 pounds about, so I don't know, I guess I should just stop doing that.
I should just, I should just stop doing that. I don't see any need for it.
I've not been really exercising that much, I've just been dieting, but I guess that's sufficient.
It would probably, it would be better if I was lifting. I still haven't started lifting again.
I know I've been saying I was going due since the start of the year and it's been three months.
I think I've now been not lifting for probably about as long as I was lifting before New Year's and then I stopped because I got sick.
Everybody got sick with COVID.
Then you put it off and you put it off and you put it off and this is what happens.
Another week down the toilet and another and another and another.
Ah well. What else, what else?
Oh, I got, I got a funny video of my mom playing Phantom's Revenge.
It was very funny. She, I might, I'll probably post it or I'll probably, I'd like to post it somewhere.
Like maybe I'll cut it down to like some funny bits when she like talks about dabbing and stuff.
That was pretty funny. She thought she was not going to be able to play it and I said, and I said, no, it's just menus.
Like you don't have to be like a gamer. It's just like a puzzle to solve.
My mom likes puzzles. So maybe that convinced her.
But she, I mean, she, we didn't spend too long on it. I think she was, she was playing it for maybe like half an hour.
And, you know, she, she kept, she kept forgetting which button was like, oh, what's this?
Hello.
Oh my God.
Hello, Ben.
Hello, Giv. You sound like you've been punched in the throat.
Yes. It's just a bit of a throat. Don't worry about it.
Okay.
I was streaming. I was streaming Elden Ring. I forgot. I didn't notice.
You were streaming Elden Ring?
I sure was.
That can't be legal.
Well, you've been living under a rock, Ben St. There's so many. There's so many streams.
That's committing 60 frames a second of copyright infringement.
I wouldn't say 60 frames.
That's, that's FromSoft's intellectual property.
What are they going to do? Come to my house and congratulate me on being such a cool person?
Here's what they're going to do. They're going to come, they're going to come to your house.
They're going to stand outside the fog door at your front door. They're going to walk through.
They're going to start chucking dung pies and black fire bombs.
They're going to dodge roll through your, through your attack, and then they're going to punish you for heavy damage.
They're going to put their divine weapon from the back.
They're going to chop your tail off and receive the mighty, the mighty spear that, you know, obviously would result from such a thing.
And then they're going to apply a pine resin, gold pine resin to their weapon and electrocute you.
And then won't you feel stupid?
But I have a phase two, though.
Oh, shit.
And that's where I, that's where I jump up onto the ceiling and I delete the floor and the floor is gone and they fall to their death.
How'd you get a phase two? I want a phase two.
Mom, wait, how does, how does that thing go? Like, how G-Wiz?
G-Wiz, how come, G-Wiz, Bill, how come your mom lets you have two phases?
Yeah, yeah, that's the one.
I was just, I was just complaining about my week.
The Hulk based.
It was based. I know, right? Tell me about it.
What did I say? I was saying, I got my mom to play Phantom's Revenge and it was pretty funny.
Oh, what did she think?
I recorded some of it.
She thought, I think, well, I think she was, I think she thought it was pretty cool.
I think she thought it was like, wow, how does a person even make a video game?
Which is fair.
And she, I was saying, she felt, she was like, oh, I'm not a gamer. There's no way I can play it.
And I said, no, it's just a puzzle. It's just menus.
And she, and indeed, she died twice.
But like her second death, she made it, she made it further the second time.
She, she knew what she had to do. She just messed it.
Like she knew she had to take out the Soniches with the guns.
She just messed up and didn't select the right one.
So she accidentally killed one without a gun.
And so Virginia got shot and she was like, ah, darn, I lost it. I wasn't supposed to do that.
That was as far as I saw her get.
But she could have beat it with perseverance.
It's the easiest game ever made.
Even my mom can play it.
The easiest game.
Well, I suppose it doesn't have reflex requirements. You just need to click on the right things.
Exactly. There's no iframes.
God, Elden Ring. All right. I don't want to talk too much about Elden Ring.
But I will say, very nice.
Okay.
Very nice.
I am, I might, I might get Elden Ring at some point.
I think my computer could probably handle it.
What was the last big game with lots of detail that you played?
I don't know that I have ever played such a game on my computer.
Not even any other Dark Souls or on your current computer?
No, I have not played any Souls on my computer.
Wow. So cool.
I played Bloodborne on a PS4.
That's not your computer though.
It's not, it's not.
I don't, Hades is like the most, the most graphics game.
Well, you've played Noita, isn't that like intensive just because of the amount of pixels doing things?
It can be, yeah. It can be a bit intense on the old hard drive.
And I mean, it runs fine. Sometimes it crashes, but everybody's like, I don't know.
I feel like it's probably fine.
I mean, you could turn the settings down in Elden Ring and it'll be fine probably.
I was thinking of going on sale, but I asked on Twitter and people said it would probably be a while until it went on sale.
So maybe I should just buy it.
I mean, I was wondering that as well.
I expected it to go on like, oh, Steam Summer Sale, special Elden Ring as soon as I had already bought it.
But like, it's the Steam Summer Sale is currently happening. It's not there.
So like, yeah, probably, probably it'll be a Christmas thing if that.
Hmm. Yeah.
I would be willing to wait like two months for like $30 off or something.
But do I want to wait like eight months?
I just said fuck it because I wanted to have a fun time.
It's a good reason to do anything.
I went, I've been like, I made punk and she's going to be a dagger assassin with a bow.
She's going to stab people in Elden Ring. Yeah.
She's going to stab people. I've been stabbing people in the back. I've been sneaking past things.
The stealth, right? Dark Souls, it's linear.
You go through it and you're expected to at least encounter all the enemies.
But with the stealth mechanic in this game, you can like just get past a lot of dangerous looking things.
It's quite fun figuring out how I can like not trip the aggro range and like sneak past a whole group of enemies and climb a ladder.
You know, I haven't really seen anyone play in stealth.
I've seen like spellcasters and I've seen like I've heard people talk about like strength faith builds.
Yeah. I mean, big swords are cool.
But I've increasingly found that I prefer in any Souls game the ability to do an attack that takes the fewest animation frames possible before I'm allowed to roll.
So that's why I'm choosing a dagger. So it does like you can do like one attack in like a very short time and then have plenty of time to dodge out of the way of the incoming.
Slice.
Interesting.
You could go in and stab them a little bit, jump back, stab them a little bit.
And that makes it easier for me. It takes longer, I think, unless the dagger's really good.
But there's bleed damage build up and occasionally they just explode in blood. That's great.
Mmm. I like the sound of that exploding with blood.
Mmm. Getting hungry. Just thinking about it.
Yeah. I haven't played a Souls since. I played some Bloodborne but not that much.
And I played Dark Souls 1 and like half of Dark Souls 2. So it's been a while.
But I like the idea of just exploring.
Oh yeah.
I think I would just like exploring the world and I might get a little mad at some bosses but I can deal with it.
That's basically what I've been doing.
You get your Horus at some point. I think I sequence broke and just walked the wrong way and missed a lot of the tutorial at the beginning.
But I found my Horus and it came to me.
And then it was really just fun to look at the rolling hills and cliffs and be like,
oh, there's a cool looking church at the top of that thing. How do I get there and scanning the horizon?
Okay, maybe if I go at the bottom of that ravine, it looks like I can go up.
So you find your way down the ravine, up the ravine and it's just like traversing the environment.
And occasionally there's a bunch of scary little gremlins who go ran and you can jump over them or you can attack them.
And I've been exploring a lot of the game past the point where I should have really stopped to fight some bosses.
I was skipping a lot of dangerous encounters and bosses and castles.
I skipped the first main castle, which apparently you're supposed to go there.
You're told to go there and there's a big boss with many hands and he's got a big old thing.
But I just found a way around the castle and then I explored the second area of the game under levels and under equipped.
But it was fun because you can still run away from lots of stuff.
So I explored tons of the map and it was just fun.
It was just fun being scared and running away from everything.
That sounds cool.
You're doing that on the Pump character?
Yeah.
That sounds fun. Sounds cool.
I'm hoping to find a fire spell so I can be Pump on character.
I was joking that it was like this new patch for Pumpkin Alley.
I made this and this is the new game.
When people talked about Bloodborne and Dark Souls 3, I always got the feeling that what they were mostly talking about was boss fights.
That's fine and all, but I like that it seems like exploration is more important in Elden Ring.
I think that appeals to me more.
It feels more like you're role playing in a big open world.
I mean, I guess it is. That's the idea. It's an open world game.
The whole Dark Souls boss sort of bragging rights, I guess.
Oh, first try. I killed them and it's cool.
It's like a high skill bar to reach some bosses and it feels great when you get through a lot of them.
But at the core of the experience, I prefer not that I don't like bosses, but I feel more comfortable sneaking around in castles and dungeons and taking out enemies and figuring out whether I can make it through with the amount of healing items I have
and whether I should distract this guy and run past him or defeat all of them so that they don't come and run after me.
Decisions like that. When you're one-on-one with a boss, it's a different sort of game, which I still like.
But I love the exploration. It's really good.
Yeah, I should probably give it a little word.
Give it a shot. Take it for a little test drive for one of these dang days.
Although I haven't quite 100% of the Hades and I kind of want to do that. I'm getting pretty close.
So maybe as soon as I'm done with all that bullshit, I have a little in-game anecdote, a little joke that I laughed really hard at in Hades.
I haven't mentioned it, but it killed me.
In Hades, you get keepsakes from NPCs. When you give them gifts, sometimes they give you things you can equip that give you a special buff or whatever.
And in the endgame, you can get one from Hades. He'll give you a pin or whatever. It makes you invisible.
And when Zagreus uses keepsake, he calls out the name of the person that gave it to him.
And so when he uses the Hades keepsake, he yells out, Father!
Well, the final boss of the game is Hades. And so I learned that when you use Hades keepsake against Hades, Zagreus yells out, Father!
And Hades just says, What? I'm right here. Yes, I can hear you fine. It's so fucking good.
Father!
Father! What? What is it? Yes. I couldn't believe it.
There's so much fucking dialogue, and I've played that game for like 85 hours, and I still have new dialogue every time I restart.
Every time I go back to the house, every character's got a new thing to say. I have not exhausted any of it. It's insane.
It's wild.
Yeah.
Gaiman.
Gaiman!
First we made games, then we played them.
That's... That's how you do it.
Did you want to talk about Nika?
Oh, yes, yes. Okay, so you caught up with one...
I was kind of... I didn't read this week's chapter.
Oh, well, neither did I. I didn't know it was out.
I'm not sure. I'm up to 10.45.
Did you actually come out on a Wednesday?
Hold on.
Let's see, is 10.46 out yet?
I don't even remember which website I read it on.
There's a few. 10.46.
Okay, oh, 10.47 is out now. Well, I haven't read the last two then.
Oh shit, there is... Okay, yeah. Well, whatever.
Probably the things we were about to talk about could be explained in those chapters.
But yeah, with regards to Nika, the Gear 5,
spoilers for One Piece, if you didn't hear about it before.
Big spoilers for One Piece.
So I listened to the last episode. You and Sims, you talked about it.
And I forget... I wanted to insert myself into the conversation,
say, no, no, no, you see, you see, blah, blah, blah, One Piece, blah, blah, blah.
But now I can't remember what I would have said in response to you.
So I'll just say what I think.
Okay, 10.47 is coming soon.
Okay, yeah, yeah, that makes sense.
I like the thing you were saying with the themes.
Like it's thematically similar to what Luffy's power has always been thematically about.
The freedom, sort of.
Being like a rubbery, squash and stretch cartoon guy.
Yeah, it's like funny, and Oda likes comedy and silly things.
And it's sort of like, of course, he would make it as silly as possible.
I always liked when Gear 3rd was like ridiculous looking.
And then Gear 4th was like, oh my God, it's Gear 4th.
He's going to be so powerful. And he's like, is a gorilla?
He's like a weird, funny gorilla with tattoos.
And it's like, it's inherently silly looking.
But it's so cool because he's so strong.
4 is where it's like...
I don't even know why he looks like this.
But I guess when he looks like that, he's really strong or whatever.
So, okay.
Yeah, I can't remember.
Yeah, it's just sort of like...
It's kind of like whatever.
Gear 4 is a little bit like, oh, he went super, super, super Saiyan God mode
so his hair is blue now and that means he's stronger.
Is his hair blue?
I've never seen him in color.
No, I'm talking about in Dragon Ball.
In Dragon Ball Super, their hair turns blue for some reason.
The next one that has going to turn green.
It turns blue, but if he's...
Simsie was explaining, but if it's an alternate reality, like evil,
possessed version, if his hair would turn blue, it turns pink instead.
And that's different, but it's the same.
That's kind of how I feel about 4.
4, yeah.
I mean, I don't get the meaning of the tattoos and the...
I see that it's inspired by Japanese-type design things with the tattoos
and the cloud around him.
He's like some sort of a Buddhist thing, maybe.
Yeah.
But I don't know why exactly that is what he looks like from his perspective.
Absolutely no idea.
He's got the black armament hacky going all over him.
And he's fast, like Gear 2nd, but he's not giant like Gear 3rd.
So it's just sort of like Gear 2nd 2, I guess.
But I don't really mind it too much.
It's just whatever.
But Gear 5, this new one, they've been talking about Devil Fruit Awakening.
And the idea that you use your fruit in a way that goes beyond your own body, I guess, is usually...
Have we seen other awakened paramecias before?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean, in this whole fight, there's been a kid has used his magnetic one to turn Big Mom magnetic
so that he could stick all that metal to her because that's his thing.
He controls magnetic fields and then he can make someone else magnetic with his Awakening.
Law also has awakened his Devil Fruit, but I don't really understand the metrics, like what the fruit is normally
and then how the Awakening is different.
You could just do a bunch of stuff.
Is his Awakened ability not the thing where he can make someone immortal one time if he dies?
I don't know if that's the Awakening or just like an ability he could use.
Yeah.
How would you know?
How does he know that he has that ability?
I think it was something in his like backstory.
I mean, Law is like a bit of a too cool for school character.
He truly is.
His inclusion has always been a little bit baffling.
I like him, but like it is like the sort of like he's a teen favorite.
All the kids are like, oh, they love Law.
I see myself in him because he's always frowning.
Yeah.
Shadow the Hedgehog.
It's like whatever.
It's fine, but it's like whatever.
He's not like the coolest guy ever and his powers are a bit confusing.
Okay, so do you want?
Also, who else?
What's his name?
The guy in Wano, not Wano, the whole cake who fought Luffy.
Katakuri?
Katakuri.
His Awakening was to turn the environment around him into mochi.
Oh, he was a Logia, right?
No, he was a Parameshia, I think.
Oh, okay.
I think there was like a brief comment about it being a special Parameshia,
which is like who knows what that means?
I'd like to know where people get all this information about the devil fruits.
Is there like devil fruit scholars who have written down these things?
Honestly, yeah, me too.
That's like, that's one of the most intriguing parts of the world of One Piece for me.
And sometimes I get the distressing feeling that it's all just being completely made up
as it goes along and there's very little like thought put into it.
Yeah.
Sometimes it's so weird and obscure that it feels like,
okay, there's like something going on here that I'm not privy to,
but there's more to it than meets the eye.
And other times it's like, no, it's just too fucking weird and stupid.
I mean, I can imagine Oda was like, okay, I'm going to have a bunch of different funny powers.
Sometimes you can turn into an animal, sometimes you can turn into like an intangible
or like a usually non-solid object, like light or water.
I don't know if there's a water log here, but like smoke and fire and all that.
Yeah.
And then a catch-all for every other type of thing where you're not,
you're neither a beast nor a smoke.
Right.
And he's just like, yeah, that'll do.
That won't need clarification or like anything.
Nope.
Nothing confusing about that.
And then he just makes a bunch of like cool powers and he's like,
well, which ones do these fit into?
Some of these are potentially could like cross over halfway.
And he's like, ah, yeah.
Because he's already set the rules in place.
There's three types.
And he's like, well, this one's a special one of those that makes it different.
I don't care.
I just wanted to cool power.
And it's like, I can see his priority is just making the powers funny and cool.
Do you want a minor spoiler for chapter 1046?
I mean, I could look at it right now.
Yeah.
Shall we read it?
I'm just, I just skim through it and I just see the part at the end where he's like
grabbing lightning bolts out of the sky.
Like he's going to throw them like Zeus.
That's weird.
You're talking about.
Is that Luffy?
Yeah.
Luffy.
Nika Luffy is just like throwing lightning bolts like Zeus.
Okay.
Why not?
Uh, sure.
I don't really want to like sit here for like a bit and digest this chapter before we keep
talking.
But I also don't want to not know what's going on.
That's just me.
I was just, I was just looking, I was just looking through.
Um, but yeah, the Nika, I like the way it looks.
I like the fact that it's Tom and Jerry cartoon, Popeye, like silly, wacky, zany, uh, goofy.
And, uh, it's exactly the sort of thing.
It's the sort of, it's exactly the sort of thing gear five should be and the powers of
the awakening devil for being able to turn things rubber.
So like being able to punch someone like a cartoon, uh, through their chest in a way
that they would kill them if it was real.
But if they're made of rubber and it doesn't matter, um, then it's fine.
So he punches Kido through the head really hard.
Yeah.
Because he turns Kido into rubber.
Stretches.
Yeah.
It's just like, that's, that's exactly the right cool thing that it could be, should be.
Um, that's great.
And, uh, I think that I think you and Simsie also had this problem just that it's like
a little asinine that the fruit is like so special and important.
It could have just been, this is what Luffy's Awakening does.
Yeah.
It could have done, it could have done all the same things and the, and the explanation
could have been, oh, he's awakened his, his devil fruit.
He can turn other things into rubber and I guess it makes his hair turn into steam.
Yeah.
Just because.
I feel like the, the reveal that the other gurus say talking about the fruit being joy
boy related or joy boys fruit or something relating to liberator, the liberator, the
freedom fruit, the special one that is so important to the world government.
It's, it's.
They can't let anybody have it.
And it's like.
Okay.
To the point where they would sacrifice one of their CP zero members to stop Luffy from
winning the fight.
Yeah.
It's like, uh, but weird.
I don't really understand why they didn't do that.
I mean, lots of fruits are like really, really powerful.
Like, sure, I guess, I guess this Nika fruit is pretty good, but like, you know, Kaido's
dragon fruit is also like a really powerful fruit that probably if I was the world government,
I would think it was really important not to let some pirate eat it.
Uh, you know, same for like a hundred other fruits.
Yeah.
Turn you into a fucking like island killer level threat just by having it.
I mean.
It's like, like is Luffy's is the Nika is the is the Nika fruit.
Is it is it much more dangerous than the Gura Gura fruit, which lets you destroy a whole
island just if you want to.
I, I, well, I think the fact that they mentioned liberator and like freedom and joy boy.
When they talk about that fruit is implying that the damage it can do is not physical
necessarily, but it's like, like could upend their society politically.
So, but like, I don't understand how the fruit specifically does that.
I feel like that either implies that the power Luffy has is the power to rouse people to fight
against their oppressors or something, which is like has nothing to do with being silly
and goofy and he's not exhibiting any like power that does that as far as I know.
Like what it literally does is what you would expect an awakened gum gum fruit to do, which
is turn things into wacky rubber.
I guess maybe it could have some secondary effect of freedom, whatever that means.
It's just sort of annoying.
Well, yeah, well, yeah, it is annoying because the idea of like being the king of the pirates is like the
most free you can be and that's and Luffy wants that because he wants freedom and he
hates people being trampled over and not being able to do what they like.
And so he punches guys who stop freedom from happening.
That's right.
You know, he beat the shit out of crocodile, not necessarily because crocodile was starting a war,
but because it made VV upset that she was trapped in this, you know, it's more of a personal thing.
He wasn't trying to be a hero.
He was just trying to be free and that's just what he felt like doing.
And so I from what I like from reading the whole manga, it felt like Luffy has that sort of that attitude
that inspires people to fight for their own freedom as well.
And that's why like at the end of Dressrosa, he's got like an army following him because they are inspired
by him to like fight back against people that otherwise would not get challenged.
And it's like, oh, he's got this army.
He doesn't care about the army.
He doesn't want it, but they're doing it anyway.
And it's sort of like Luffy as a person is inspiring change.
He's changing people's minds.
He's making it so that the world can overthrow the world government and reveal the void century information.
But remember, one piece is not political.
It has no political messages in it at all.
It doesn't mean anything.
Don't get it twisted now.
No.
Okay.
I hear you.
The sort of the sort of thematic obvious direction it's going is like,
king of the pirates equals freedom.
So to become the king of the pirates, you must make the world free kind of.
So the world government will be toppled or at least the dismantled, disbanded, the Marines will not be bad people.
I mean, they're good people in the Marines.
So they'll probably still be there at the end being like, oh, now we're good cops.
That's fine, whatever.
But like the obviously slave enslavement of like people in Marishwa and all of the super higher ups and whatever was happening in the void century that they're trying to cover up is gets revealed and everybody around the world hears that.
And they're like, oh my God, I hate the world government now.
Revolution.
And it's like, but like, you know what?
That's great.
I just don't like the implication that that is because Luffy ate a fruit and not because he himself is inherently like he inspires people inspiring through his actual character trait.
Like is the fruit doing anything or is it not?
It's, you know, I feel like that they might never specify.
It might maybe, maybe, maybe, I mean, maybe Joy Boy was this like liberator God because of the fruit or maybe he just was like that.
And he also happened to eat the same fruit.
I mean, it could be like the devil fruits were created with the will of people in them.
And this one was created by Joy Boy and it has Joy Boy's will in it.
But it still, it still feels like that means that Luffy is not himself doing all of the good he's doing.
He's doing it because he has a fruit that he ate.
It could also, if I'm going to be charitable, I think what they're going for, what it is going for is like the fruit chooses the wizard Harry Potter.
The fruit shows Luffy because he was exactly the right person to be the guy who has that fruit power.
That's probably what it is.
Maybe in the same way that maybe the flame fruit chose Sabo or something.
There's some kind of destiny at work that's like Sabo got Ace's fruit.
Yeah, I don't know.
I guess there'll be more to be revealed.
Initially, the reveal was like, oh, that's cool, but why is that extra thing there?
I suppose it could be good.
It could be good.
I am, yeah, it makes me wonder about all that stuff, about the nature of fruits and powers and all that.
Yeah, until we know really what the fruit is doing, I guess I'm not sure what I think.
If it turned out that the Nika fruit just made Luffy into this freedom fighter dude and it was just the fruit acting through him and controlling his destiny, I would be like, ehh.
I feel like there's no chance that that is the intention, but it might be an unintentional implication if they don't make it more obviously something else.
Yeah, I hear it.
I just want to know.
Tell me more about fruits, Oda, please.
Tell me where do they come from?
Who made them?
Why?
How?
What's up?
I would imagine the fruits were invented in the Void Century.
You know who I really wish didn't die was Odin's wife, because she was from the Void Century.
You pick up on that?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
She traveled into the future.
She was from 800 years ago and that's when the Void Century was, so like, dang, would have been really good if she just traveled forward in time one more time and didn't get killed.
Okay, I forget if this was ever mentioned in that flashback.
Did she tell Odin what all of that was?
Did she tell him the secret?
All of what?
The Void Century stuff.
I don't think she ever really brought it up.
It's just mentioned that that's how old she is and that just happens to line up with how long ago the Void Century was.
I feel like there's a reason that that was the case.
Yeah, the number is not arbitrary.
So, like, information of the Void Century from her past to Odin could be if it could be past to Momonosuke or Kyori.
Yeah, absolutely.
It seems really important to me that she just happens to be the same age as when the Void Century happened.
That seems like that's there for a reason and there's going to be something with that.
It's the sort of thing that would be like after Wano is finished and people are sitting around being like, wow, what a battle, huh?
That shit was crazy.
Everyone's like, damn, remember when we all collectively hallucinated that Luffy had a weird mythical zoan fruit that turned his hair white?
That was like a crazy trip.
Good thing it was just a dream.
Yeah, and they're having a feast and then whatever.
And then Momonosuke's there and offhandedly just mentioned something about the Void Century and then Niko Robin's eyes wide and she's like, huh?
Well, wait a minute.
I've heard about that in the Ponyglyphs, but I wasn't sure what it meant.
Could you tell me?
And then she talks to him.
She gains more knowledge and that's like that would be a little scene.
I love it when Niko Robin gains knowledge.
She's so fucking smart.
It's so fucking hot when she gets smarter.
You know, I apparently was confused.
I had thought, and I guess I was wrong, but I had thought that Momosuke, is it Momonosuke?
Is that the kid's name?
Momonosuke, yeah.
I thought that Momonosuke had eaten a smile.
I thought his dragon was from a smile, but I guess it's not.
No, no.
It was from a failed recreation made by Vegapunk.
Isn't that the same thing?
Isn't that what a smile is?
I think Vegapunk lied about it being a failure.
Yeah, because it just gave him the exact same fruit as Kaido had.
It's the same dragon.
It's clearly not a failure.
Vegapunk probably would have lied.
I feel like Vegapunk is not a bad person deep down.
He works for the government because he has to.
Hard to say.
When the idea of the world government getting in control of an exact copy of Kaido's dragon fish fruit,
that would be very dangerous, and he doesn't want the world government to actually...
Oh, it was a failure.
I'll throw it away.
Yeah, it just made him a little dragon.
It sucks.
Don't even worry about it.
I mean, Alkiji and Akainu came onto the punk hazard and they started their fight and they had to leave.
Hey, Oblivionfall.
Hello, I'm recording.
Hey, Oblivion.
Should we all sync, by the way?
We didn't sync when you joined.
Yeah, let's sync.
Let's do that right now.
On the count of three, say sync.
One, two, three, sync.
Sync.
Okay.
We're just talking about one piece, Oblivion.
What the fuck?
There's one of those...
Are you up to date?
Well, actually, we're not up to date on the most recent chapter.
I'm one chapter behind.
I know nothing at all, but I also cannot comprehend.
That means we can spoil everything and you can say it by the time you read it.
Exactly.
Well, let me tell you.
I mean, you know that it's about a boy made of rubber, right?
It's about rubber ross, the pirate.
That's what I mean.
That's correct.
Well, the big thing lately is that it was revealed that the gum gum fruit, which turned
him into rubber, was not actually the gum gum fruit.
It's the gum gum fruit.
Oh, sure.
That's true.
It was a mythical fruit that gave him the powers of the liberator, sun god, Nika.
And that's what it is, actually.
The rubber stuff was just kind of a side effect.
Damn.
He's he's this like it's like a god power, basically.
So it's pretty wacky.
He's the wacky inflatable arm man in real life.
He is.
He is all that and more.
I got to say when I like now that I've figured out what he's meant to be like his hair is
white because it's made of steam in the same way that like the gears had like steam coming
out of him.
I think it's cool.
I think about it the cooler.
I think that is like a design wise.
I think that's part of it.
I also think if you might be like he's like aging his body rapidly is the implication
another implication you could take because there's like one power where he's like, oh,
I'm so fucking old because this is taking a toll on my body.
And then he goes, no, I'm going to fight.
I'm going to keep fighting.
But that's when he he like goes on Nika and his hair turns black again.
He's like takes too much energy.
No, you're right.
Never mind.
Yeah, I think it's just more like steam.
This turns into steam.
It's cool.
I like it.
He's so white.
Oh my God.
He's the whitest king there ever was.
He's the white.
He's the whitest kid you know.
True.
If you think about it.
What's up oblivion?
What's going on?
I remembered the topic but I forgot to talk about a few weeks ago when I was on.
That was so mad about because I forgot about it.
That's one reason I'm here.
It feels like feels like a while since I don't even remember it was like two months ago.
Last time was like maybe three weeks ago.
It wasn't that long ago.
No, I swear it was.
No, I'm going to the PCP.
You're a big liar.
You're going to prison.
Let's see.
PC prison.
Three weeks ago, Phantom Revenge is out.
Feet oblivion fall.
Got him.
Oh, I don't remember that.
I think it's when we had the...
Phantom Revenge?
What's that?
What?
It was when we talked about wheels and doors.
Oh, that's right.
If you can believe it.
Oh, sure.
But now the other reason I'm here is that my project's done.
It's not out, but it's done.
The video?
Yeah, all the animation, all the compositing and effects.
I finished them up yesterday.
Oh, the site to site.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It'll maybe come out later today.
Well, a couple days ago for when people see this, but...
I've been waiting.
I've been...
I haven't been...
I've been edging.
I haven't seen you around much.
So I've been assuming that you've probably had your nose to the grindstone.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Well, actually, for two weeks, I couldn't work on it because I had to work on a video
for DA Games.
I had to do this big five-minute-long music video in 3D that I made in like two weeks.
Funny, I can make those projects in two weeks, but my own project's taken me months.
I know how it is.
What's it called?
Actually, what's the name of it?
The DA Games one, I can link it.
No, I meant your video.
It's gonna be...
Oh, my video is Ancazonexcomzone.
Okay.
I think that's the title I'm going with.
All right.
You know, that meme from like September, it's been like seven months since that was the
game.
I don't know that meme from September.
Damn.
It was a zone?
Yeah, it was zone and minus A.
Zone animated, Anca.
Oh, Anca from Animal Crossing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was like music and then she just had sex on camera and then all of the little kids'
babies on Twitter, they're like, oh, my God, I've never seen sex before.
What the fuck?
Oh, my God, that's literally me.
And they're like, oh, my God, what the fuck?
And that became a meme because people were freaking out over that.
And then they were like, no, she's just dancing.
And then Zone made a dancing video and that's like everyone pretends it's their original.
I see.
Fascinating.
That was kind of funny.
Hmm, okay.
I do remember that Anca animation.
I didn't know there was like a story to go with it.
I didn't know a thing happened.
All the YouTube comments were like, whoa, when you realize she's not dancing.
Wah, she's actually fucking.
Wah, sex cat.
Wah.
Crazy.
And then they learned their lesson.
They now find the bowling pin having sex with the, no, the bowling ball and sex with the
bowling pin and they can't handle it.
What do they think of next?
It's like, I mean, you say what do we think of next.
Technology sure is amazing.
I mean, it was just another one of those instances where Totally Spies did it first.
Yeah.
I mean, look, wait, general or links.
Where do I put stuff?
Uh, general, I guess.
Yeah, yeah.
Um, yeah, Totally Spies did it.
I looked up the clip.
There's a video for it too.
Yeah, it's exact.
It's actually did it twice.
These pins are hotter.
These pins are hotter than that white one.
You would say that.
That food fight looking pin is gross.
I don't like it.
Yeah, we did it a second time with a different aesthetic.
We just keep doing it.
Yeah, and I've been thinking about like, has anyone like actually made a video going like
if I watch every episode of Totally Spies and like write down every single fetish that it
like started or at least contributed to because I know, but it sounds like the kind of video
that would get clicks.
I clicked on a random video and there was like hyper muscle growth like in there.
There's just an episode on YouTube called like the incredible bulk and I'm like, let
me guess, it's going to be like some hyper muscle shit.
And I clicked on it and there was and then at the end, the one of the girls goes muscular
and she has like, she has like titties and it's like sex and I'm like, damn.
That's crazy.
I can't believe they would do that.
It's weird because I remember Totally Spies.
I only watched like a few episodes, but like, I could tell that it was like sexual because
they were in tight spandex the whole time.
Wasn't that sexual?
No, but I was young.
I was like, I don't know, 13 or 14.
I was like, there's some sort of thing with girls here and I'm thinking something.
But like, I don't remember anything like ridiculously fetishistic going on.
I saw girls in tight jumpsuits and I said, this is too political for me.
I'm out.
I didn't really watch it that much.
I watched like, yeah, I watched a little bit of it.
Don't remember it.
I don't remember it being weird, but maybe in hindsight, I could be like, remember how
every time anyone got tied up in rope in my little pony, people would be like, oh my
God, it's bondage fetish.
I mean, there is plenty of that in Totally Spies too.
Of course.
Of course there is.
Yeah.
They're spies.
They're going to get like strapped to a table with like a laser that's going to cut them
in half.
That's just what spies do.
Totally.
Which is hot.
Yeah, I agree.
One fetish that I like, I just saw one artist like drawing it and it was like, and they
draw it a lot.
So it's clear they're fetish.
I found an image that's not too sexual to show off what I'm talking about.
I think the artist is Frank Tonius.
It's not a fetish I get, but it's like, we're like, you've swapped body parts with different
people who have like different shades of skin.
Like the arm might be like slightly brown.
Like your leg is black or something.
And that, I saw this artist, I followed them for big titties and I saw them drawing this
stuff on the side and I'm like, wait, Totally Spies has an episode where I did that.
There was like a woman who like every body part was like a slightly like different shade
of skin color.
Boy, that's really weird.
She had like stolen body parts from so many people and I'm like, damn, Totally Spies did
this too.
I'm sure there's more.
I'm sure if I watched the show, I'd find like hundreds.
I gotta be honest.
I've never heard of this particular fetish before, which is surprising.
I feel like I've heard it all.
I mean, I think I've only really seen this artist do it.
It's not like a super popular one, but it's one.
It sure is.
Oh, wait.
Hang on.
Oblivion.
You haven't done the Lord of Ghost Kickstarter backer reward survey.
There's a survey.
I need it so that you, I know your address.
I can send you the thing.
Oh, right.
It should be in your email somewhere.
I see the issue.
I think I'm looking at our DMs.
I think I may have been like just waking up in bed looking on my phone when I saw that
and then when I got to my computer, the notification was gone.
That makes sense.
I need to remember what fucking email I used so I can find it.
Yeah.
I'm worried that like a number of people don't remember their login details and as such have no way.
There probably will be.
Probably at least a handful of people will simply never respond to the query.
It's just the way it goes.
You just got to make your own best faith attempt to reach them.
And if they don't, then you know, you just got to let them go.
You just got to give up and let them fall into the abyss where they belong.
Yeah.
But yeah, oblivion for you are one of the people who I could contact otherwise.
The rest of them, I don't know what their names are on Discord or Twitter.
So if they don't respond to the email, that's the end and I can't get them their thing.
Yeah.
I, oh my God, I have so many fucking emails.
You know what would be in the like the subject line so I can search for it.
Well, it would be from Kickstarter.
Oh, true.
I'll narrow it down.
It doesn't seem to be associated with that email address.
Let's try this one.
Oh, yes, here it is.
Blah, blah, blah.
Well, you should be able to log into your Kickstarter account and you should see an
activity you should have gotten like a notice that's like a request for a survey response.
I mean, I'm logged in.
Messages.
Verify password.
Okay.
I mean, I'll try and forgive us all.
Blah.
Anybody listening who is also a backer.
Please check your email because there's like like 17 people left.
Hey, aren't you coming to the US and like, I think we were talking about it yesterday.
Aren't you coming in like six weeks or something like not that long?
I'm coming in May.
So yeah, I guess so.
Yeah, that's pretty close.
That's next month.
Oh boy.
That's fucked.
I'm going to see people.
I'm going to be in person.
I'm going to be terrifying.
And then I will have the, and then I will, I will get, I will, I will be that the Pluture
who has the zine, has the plush, has the comic.
Yes.
Yeah, finally.
I'll be that guy rubbing my hands together.
It was so satisfying.
The last few big sets of sending out the Lord of Ghost comic and the plush.
Getting all those boxes and envelopes sealed and writing on the serial numbers and the
printing out the labels and sticking them on the customs things.
It's like, ah, I was a machine.
I was doing everything.
Got so many done per day.
And there's like, let me check.
There's like four or five like completely empty boxes that had comics in them.
And it's a few more left.
You did it.
Almost.
I did it.
I almost, I basically did it.
There's a few people in Australia, a few people in America.
I want to do the American and Australian together in one big like collection because it's better
that way.
I still have some packages from like a year ago that I was supposed to go to Australia
and I still haven't sent them because they have, as far as I'm aware, they have not
resumed first class mail to Australia from the US yet.
So I just can't, yeah.
I got, I got like a Blu-ray and like maybe a Vapors copy and like, oh no, it was a road
to Radcon.
There's just like two envelopes sitting here, just waiting for them to be like, okay, we'll
mail to Australia again.
Thanks.
Okay.
So the last email I got like sending me a link to the survey was on January 23rd.
So anyone listening, if he wants to do a survey, look for emails around that date, I guess.
I found it.
I just had to scroll a lot.
All right.
You know what?
I'm, my project for this week, I have a, I mentioned it last episode, but I'm, I'm drawing
a Tales Get Strolled page.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
I just, I just started it yesterday.
I put it off for a few days.
I have until, I think I have to, I have to draw it in the next four days, which should be
doable.
I think there's like 18 panels.
This is not that bad.
These are set in, in the, they're in the world.
Well, some of them are in the world inside of Coyote's book, which I had forgotten what,
what it looks like, but it's like a purple like nighttime land with like gravestones
everywhere.
I must confess, I have not finished, not got caught up with Tales Get Strolled.
I also had to like reread the like the latest chapters because I was not caught up either.
I genuinely can't remember where I stopped.
I remember Pac-Man.
Yeah.
And I think Tales has just finished their, their training.
Did you get to the part with Cheeto Man and the big like mass grave?
I forget.
I know Cheeto Man was there.
You meet Cheeto Man earlier, but then he becomes like a big.
Yeah.
The mass grave.
That sounds very fun.
That's a highlight for sure.
Yeah.
Fucking Tales Get Strolled.
The, the, yeah, there's a, there's Satan.
Like half of my pages are like Coyote and Demaro and Gary's soul in Coyote's book realm.
And then the other half of them are Satan, sort of like monologuing in hell.
So that's pretty exciting.
Gary is a, it's funny, like there's, I have like some disagreements.
I have some slight disagreements with the way that some of the other guest artists have drawn Gary.
The last, the person who's drawn the most, Gary, sort of gave him like link hair.
He sort of has like a frilly sort of like link cut and I don't agree with that.
I don't think that's what his original art was meant to look like.
So I'm sort of giving it my own interpretation.
Gary, Gary is the guy who, he sort of has like an Android face for a lot of the comic.
And then he gets even more of his face destroyed and replaced with Android parts.
And then there's the part where he fights Demaro and he like covers himself in like magma armor because he's an earth bender.
And he almost beats Demaro, but then he dies.
And then his soul gets eaten by the eye monster in Demaro's forehead.
And then Coyote manages to free his soul.
And now his soul is just kind of hanging out and being a dick and like insulting Demaro because he's mad that he died.
Hmm. Yeah, sounds reasonable.
You know. And then Coyote, so actually Coyote has Gary's body.
And so Coyote is controlling Gary's body and Gary's soul is just kind of hanging out and like watching him do that.
Coyote is like, hey man, could you explain to me like how your powers work so I can use them?
And he's like, fuck you, man. You're a bitch.
It's pretty, it's pretty weird. It's pretty funny.
Coyote is like, I don't know.
I think this is after the part that I got to in my lecture.
Like I think this all happens after, but Coyote is like, he's like covered in wounds now.
Like he's got his ears got chopped off and like his neck got cut open and like his back, his spine got sliced open.
And so he had to like put his, his like weird like neutral soul strings and he had to use them to like stitch his body back together.
So now he's got all these like scars all over him that are like he's got these glowing yellow strings holding him together.
It's awesome. They're rules.
Great, great, great, great comic.
Happy, happy to be doing a page for it.
I do have the physical comic, but it's falling wild.
Really? I didn't, oh, I didn't get it. I wanted it, but I forgot to buy it.
Yeah, it's on the shelf. I mean.
Sorry, isn't it?
It's on a different shelf.
Okay.
Okay, I don't know if these pages correspond to the actual panel or pages of the comic, but I'm on 135.
What chapter is it? Because it's divided into chapters that are like 20 pages each.
Let's see.
The silver hedgehog.
Everybody's favorite.
Oh, chapter six.
Yeah, there's like, there's like 25 chapters now.
Lol. Okay. Yeah, this is volume one. So it's not the whole thing.
Yeah.
I mean, some of the, some of the guest art in like chapter, chapter four is like really good.
They got some, they got some dudes. Hold on, let me, let me find it. Let me find a really good one.
I was, I was, I was, I was refreshing my memory of the story and I was going through, I think it was in chapter 24.
I was like, yow. Yowza.
When a young man is suddenly trolled by two individuals from a nation of real life internet trolls.
It initiates a chain of events leading to an all out war between several opposing factions, influencing the lives of hundreds of characters.
True that.
The TGT saga chronicles the profound human drama resulting from these events, while at the same time providing an in depth examination of the themes contained therein,
including morality, vengeance, camaraderie, betrayal, romance, dark magic, drug use, and more.
Drugs.
It's, it's, it's, it's got, it's got all that and more. Okay. It's not letting me copy paste because the image is too big here.
Image is too fucking powerful.
What if volume two is out? I don't know if, if a CC is working on that.
I'm sure he's working on it to some extent. I don't know. I'm sure I would have heard about it if it were out though.
Okay, I got to just shrink this image a little bit so I can change image resolution.
I forgot Batman was part of the secret society.
There's, there's Batman, there's Cheeto Man, there's Dexter, Hello Kitty, Kermit the Frog, Ronald McDonald, Spyro, Vivian, and Woodstock.
Vivian from Paper Mario and Woodstock from Peanuts.
Yeah, I remember, I remember most of those. I kind of forgot about Batman. He's not that important.
Ronald McDonald, obviously, the unhinged psychopath.
Frogger and leapfrog.
How, how is it that I take a JPEG, shrink it, and then save it as, save the shrunken image as a JPEG and it ends up with a bigger file size than the original?
How does that work?
Bad.
Bad file.
How can this be? This isn't, this is not logical.
Alright.
Encoding us the word.
I just, I just want to show some of this cool, uh, here, I'll just, I'll just screen grab it.
There we go. Look, look at this shit. There's, there's like, there's like a lot like this. There's a big section at the end of Chapter 24.
Oh no, Road Runner.
Oh yeah. Oh yeah, they got Road Runner.
Is that the canonical end of, of, you know, the Road Runner cartoons? Is this?
No, I think he's, I think he's back. You know, all, all Coyote has to do is like, stitch his frickin' body back together and he's just fine.
Cause he's just, he's just a corpse being puppeted.
Here we go.
Meep, meep.
This one's a pretty, I guess he's killing Sonichu here. I forget why he's doing that.
Phantom, Phantom, Phantom Horn and Coyote. The two things they've got in common is the Kill Sonichus.
It's a new, a new show, Phantom Horn and Coyote.
Yeah. Best, best friends.
Uh, uh, uh.
What if Phantom Horn was in Tales Get Strolled?
We gotta get, we gotta get him in. I gotta get, uh, I gotta convince, uh, uh, I almost, I almost said Saber Spark.
Laserbot.
Saber Spark.
Saber Spark, the creator of Tales Get Strolled.
Ah.
Phonely.
Uh.
He wishes, he wishes.
Instead, he's only the creator of giving Tom a good mattress.
Is that a euphemism?
No, I watched a recent video of Saber's and like at the end there's this little, uh, funny little segment where it's like, ha ha, I have a friend Tom, his back fucking sucks, uh, but I'm using my mattress sponsorship to give him a good back and there's like this little
freedy like animation of Tom and he, it was like a PNG and he just falls over or something and it was funny.
That's very funny actually.
Tom.
Do you remember which episodes that is? I kind of love it.
It was very recent. Um, I'm gonna, I must subscribe to Saber Spark. I'm gonna go to his channel.
Was it on the Saber Spark 64 channel or was it on the main channel?
It was the Pinocchio movie video.
I'm pretty certain.
So it was on his main channel. Um, it was at the end of this.
Um, I just giggled at the visual of the little freedy Tom like just falling on the floor or something.
Let me, oh my god, there it is.
It's at like 16 minutes.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh my god.
16 minutes?
Yeah.
Or 15, 55 ish.
Poor old Tom.
He was originally sleeping on an air mattress and I was like,
Just silently lying down.
Nearly a million people saw him.
Absolutely not Tom.
Okay, I got my terrible little screen grab here.
Tom, what happened?
This is like an insane person room.
He's fallen and he's staying down by choice because these Helix mattresses are so comfy.
They sure are.
Link in the description.
Use our promo code.
I hate Helix.
It sucks.
I have no opinion of such a product.
I'm sure it's fine.
I'm sure it's the best mattress I've ever slept on in my entire life.
I mean, I hope it's fine.
My bank account.
My bank account skyrockets.
I'm sure there is a very big difference between like a $50 mattress and a $2,000 mattress.
Sure.
Considering you spend a third of our lives sleeping, it's probably good to invest in a good one eventually when I can afford it.
Not a $2,000 one.
I don't know.
Maybe not.
Yeah, like a $1,000 one.
I think it's like, I heard someone say like, I forget the exact number.
It was something like the quality of like a steak tapers off after like $60 or something.
You never need to spend more than $60 on a steak.
Yeah.
There's only so good.
There's only so much love they can cook it with.
Yeah.
The next thing up is like to boil it in molten gold or something.
Or I think Munchie said something about like, I think, this was obviously a few years ago when Munchie was on the podcast.
He said something about like, he wore like a pair of $100 shoes once and he was like, oh, shit.
It's actually good.
It's actually a different experience.
But like, there probably wouldn't be much of a difference between like a $100 pair and like a $1,000 pair.
Like I think by the time you hit like a hundred or maybe even like a little lower than that, you've like reached peak shoes already.
And then everything extra is just for show, I guess.
Just to brag about how much you spent on them.
Yeah.
I wonder what the threshold is for mattresses.
Got to hit the low end of like the good quality.
I feel like a pretty like basic mattress is like, what, like 200 bucks?
For like, not a shitty mattress, but not like a good mattress either.
Just like a normal mattress.
Yeah.
I have no complaints about my mattress, which I think was like 200.
I mean, my mattress is fine.
It's probably not even a hundred.
But like my back also fucking sucks all the time.
If I did like shell out like 800 bucks or something for like a pretty nice one, it would probably improve my quality of life.
I used to sleep on a mattress that was too soft and I had back pain all the time.
And now I don't.
Too soft.
It was too soft.
How would you lay?
What would happen?
Well, I would just, I would lie down.
I sleep on my stomach usually.
So I would just be lying down and my back would just hurt.
And sometimes I would try to like support my middle back.
I would try to like put like pillows underneath my like stomach to like sort of prop up the middle of my back to sort of prevent it from like kind of bowing down in the middle, you know.
And that didn't work.
The mattress just did not support me.
And I think it was sort of bowing under my weight because it was too soft and it led to me sleeping with a bent spine and I would be in pain all the time.
I don't often sleep.
Actually, I find it very difficult to sleep face down.
I usually sleep face down.
That's just how I've always done it.
I like sleeping on my side.
That's the perfect.
So sometimes I sleep on my side.
No, I usually sleep.
No, face down.
Face down for life, baby.
That just makes it easier for somebody to suffocate you.
Because your nose is already in the pillow.
I suffocate myself.
I sleep face down and I pull the covers all the way up over my head like a fucking freak.
Damn.
You like your little cave system?
Yeah.
And I'll have a little gap.
I'll have a little gap in the between the sheet and the mattress to let my nose poke out so I can breathe air.
I remember when I was young, I had this idea to make a sauna out of my duvet.
So I would wrap it tight so that there was no air coming in so that it would just get hotter and hotter as my body heat just reverberated around.
And it became like a sauna in there and I would just stay there for a long time and then I would open it up and I would like, oh, wow.
I don't know why I did that.
Wow.
But it was a fun experience.
That sounds terrible.
I would hate to be like wrapped up in a blanket and get really hot and sweaty because of my body heat.
I don't think I would do it to go to sleep.
I think I would just do it sometimes.
Obviously, to sleep, I would not put myself in a suffocatable situation.
Understandable, yeah.
Yeah, it's not what you want.
Sorry, I'm still looking at Tails Get Strolled.
I'm still looking at all these cool coyotes.
I think I'm going to draw a coyote.
A lot of these artists draw him with like very, he's like muscular.
Like he's got like a very human sort of like musculature.
I don't think I'm going to do that.
I think I'm going to draw him like he looks in the cartoons, you know, noodley.
It's just seems more canonical.
This is my opinion.
I think that's what I'm going to do.
Also, it's easier because drawing muscles is hard.
Hey, do you want to see a very early Gib drawing from 2007?
Sure.
Because I was looking through a bunch of my old art and I wanted to like try and figure out using context clues
on where it was stored and what the skill level looks like, how old it is.
And I believe that this, this is 2007.
Whoa.
This is so like Dominic Deegan.
You know what that is?
I don't know.
I was a big fan of Dragon Ball and I think some other things.
I think I was reading one piece as well.
I made an anime character and I didn't know how to draw their eyes,
but I think I drew them here better than I do currently.
Dominic Deegan is an old webcomic that was very like how to draw manga looking.
It was controversial for a number of reasons, not least of which was that his art never improved
despite years and years and years of practice.
Well, when you've reached perfection immediately.
Exactly.
So 2007 I would have been,
what the fuck is year?
Well, that was 2007.
I would have been 14.
It was 14 year old Gib art.
Wait, are you 29?
Will be this year, yeah.
Okay, okay, yeah.
I guess that checks out.
Who is this sword guy?
Girl?
It's supposed to be a guy.
I think I drew the jacket like that because it's supposed to be like loose,
like it's like loosely hanging,
but I didn't understand that it should be hanging lower.
So it looks like a breast.
It does kind of.
That's how wacky.
How wacky.
And those double swords.
I think I was like, I was writing a manga.
I had drawn a bunch of panels,
which I still need to like scan in,
which I think were also around 2007, 2008,
where I think I watched Princess Mononoke
and I had been reading Dragon Ball in one piece
and I decided I'm going to make a manga.
And it's, I'm discovering it again.
It's like, oh, this was cool.
I had like a notebook of like the story beats of the entire story.
And it's like, they go into the future at one point
and it's basically Jack and Daxter too, exactly the same.
Yeah.
And it's like the future city,
but these guys are, it's, I think it's like,
it starts off as Princess Mononoke with that sort of
the old, the spirits in the forest
and the town with the log walls.
And then they go into, they fight stuff as demons.
Then they go into the future and it's Jack too.
And in the future, Jack too, there's also demons.
They're the metalheads,
but they're called something different because I made them
and it's my idea actually.
That's right.
And then it goes further into the future.
No, it doesn't, it goes into a different dimension,
which is real life, human world,
where a character who is a self-insert,
who is like really upset and gets bullied and hates everyone,
gets infected by demonic powers
and becomes venom from Spider-Man, essentially.
And then they fight and they fight.
I can't remember what happened,
but there's also a Darth Vader character
and there's space and I want to make that.
I want to make a real comic.
I want to make the stupid 14-year-old idea real
because I have the power.
Do they come to the real world
and they find your self-insert
who's sitting there drawing the comic
and they're like, hey, stop putting bad,
stop putting conflict in our story
and you're like, no, I'm edgy and I'm going to take it out on you.
Raw and you turn into a venom and then you fight.
That character, I don't think it was like a literal self-insert.
It wasn't my name, but it was like the character,
I was designing a character and I'm like, okay,
so they're a teenager and they get bullied a lot
and they're very quiet and it's just a list of things that are me
and they hate life and they hate everyone.
They would kill and the demon energy,
they would kill if they could, but they can't.
But then from the past, from another dimension, the demons come in,
I get bitten by a demon and it is fueled by rage
and because I'm so angry, this character I need,
this character is so angry.
They involve the demonic power and they become super powerful.
But at some point, they become a good guy like Vegeta
because they learn to be friends, they learn to have friends
and that's what it's all about.
But they still retain the ability to turn into an evil angry venom
so they become like a useful character in the fights
against the Darth Vader called Lord Zenith
because he's like, I looked in the dictionary
for something that began with Zenith and Zenith sounded cool
and it also meant really like the most.
It's like, Lord Zenith, that's my main guy.
It's not the worst name I've ever heard.
Ah, it's so cool, look at all those notes.
My handwriting is abysmal.
I can't write a single letter correctly.
But I could still read it somehow.
Well, la di da.
Yeah, I'm something of an artist.
I've been drawing since I was one.
Look who made a little notebook about some stuff.
Yeah, look at it.
Look at me.
See?
Yeah, all right, done.
Crazy.
Okay, what else?
What else we got?
Topics.
The thing I wanted to talk about a few weeks ago.
Yeah, you mentioned that fucking hour ago.
Oh, I didn't want to go into it immediately.
No, no, no, I mean, yeah, sure.
I watched a show, a very good show,
about animation that came out two years ago.
So I'm late to the party, but keep your hands off Isoquin.
Oh, yeah, I saw that.
Oh, I still haven't seen that one,
but I've been recommended it by a number of people
and it sounds like it probably would like it.
Yeah, well, I watched the first episode.
Yeah.
Yeah, I watched the first episode when it like first aired
and I gave it a 10 on Mal
and then I'm like, I'll watch for rest of us later
and I didn't actually watch it until my birthday in February.
But it's really good, obviously, that's no surprise
because I'm an animator.
I'm going to be biased to a show that's entirely
just a giant love letter to animation and everything.
But the part of a show I didn't expect to love
was just how much focus there was on cutting corners
as an art form to make your animation production better.
You didn't like that?
I do like that.
Okay, good.
I like that, too.
The characters go on big monologues,
like very passionate monologues in one episode
about how like, well, for this shot,
we can just use a still image
and we can just pan the camera a bunch of times
to like imply motion and that way we can get a shot done
in like just a couple of hours
and then this shortcut we can take, we can do this
and like it's just a whole bunch of like
ways to like do things efficiently with less effort
and I'm like, damn, this is the opposite
of what I've been doing my whole life
and it's real obvious shit that I know already
but I've never had it presented by good anime women
telling me to do it.
That's all I needed was to be told by good anime women.
Yeah.
Kanamori is the non-creative technically.
Like she's not an artist
but she gets the other girls into shape
and tells them there's, you know,
like totally practically minded
and is like really strong, like strong force of will.
She whips those idiots into shape.
They're thinking.
Exactly.
But my magical mythical special thing
and she's like, shut up.
We've only got one month to do this.
You can't do that.
You can't do it.
I know.
That's great.
All the people who are artists
who struggle with, you know,
killing babies and all that.
Yeah.
Watch this and they were like, oh my god.
I wish I had a baby killer like her.
I know, I wish I had.
That was my first thought.
I just send a picture of Kanamori to my friend.
I'm like, I need her in my life.
And he's like, for sex?
And I'm like, no.
Fuck you.
No.
I just need someone to keep my ass in shape
and keep me focused on my work.
Yeah.
I need that.
It's what I've been.
It's the piece I've been missing
because I'm the overambitious.
Like every single thing has to be fucking extra.
And for the current project I'm working on,
I was already a bit too late
because I'd already like gotten too deep
into things being over the top, like complex.
So I was able to like reuse some animations
just with different camera movements
to get like extra shots
that I wouldn't have gotten otherwise
that ended up looking really cool.
So that was still something I was able to do.
Thanks to this.
But yeah, I feel a lot better
about approaching other projects in the future
because this project I started seven months ago.
Granted, the first three months,
I had like no time to work on it,
due to pencilmation being taken up my time.
And then having to finish all my commissions
and then edit the one, the PCP episode
with the voicemail reveal
and then edit a bunch of drawcast episodes
before that got streamlined
and then do a DA games video.
And I've had so much shit getting in the way,
but I feel like when I do work on Comzone 4,
which is going to be a much bigger production,
I think I'll really like storyboard it out
from the start to have lots of shortcuts
that look good.
And thanks to Azokin,
which is also just such a fucking charming
and good show, even without all the
really good practical like advice for animators
that's in there.
Yes.
It's just a very pretty location to have.
So that is probably like
easily top three favorite shows of all time
for me right now.
I want a fucking another season.
Yeah, I love that.
I've been meaning to watch it for like two years.
Maybe I should give it a shot.
Oh, I watched the whole thing in one day.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, how many episodes is it? 20?
I think it's 12.
Oh, yeah, it's a short little thing.
Yeah, it's a short.
Okay, well, what's my excuse then?
Just watch one episode, see how you feel.
No.
No, I'll only watch 12 at a time.
Yes, that's right. Yes, that's right.
I have to commit to six hour block.
I mean, I'm not an animator,
but in comics as well,
shortcuts are base and yeah,
I love to cheat.
I love to cheat at everything.
It's just, it's just good.
I like the concept of cheating,
but I don't do it enough.
Yeah, because it's presented
to the audience.
It's something to aspire to,
but you should be proud of.
And that's the thing that I'm like, yeah.
The art form part of it is like
knowing when to do it
for maximum efficiency
of time and resources.
So like, you could skimp on
the most important panel
and have it be underwhelming.
Or you could skimp on like
dialogue scenes, which is much more
like, you know,
scenes, which is much more like
a smart thing to do.
Skimp on everything that isn't like the money shot.
And then people will remember
the money shot and they won't mind
that there's so many panels
or sort of like whatever.
Yeah, basically.
I don't know if that's what I was thinking
when I did Clarissa,
but I did draw that after
watching Isoken, I think.
That was 2020.
Clarissa has like, occasionally
a cool big panel where she's got a gun
shooting, tooting.
And then a lot of the other ones are like,
I just need to show that she's going
into this door. It doesn't matter.
Yeah, that's
really, you can
when you
when you block out a panel,
right, you can get away with little
or no background like
90% of the time.
And it's always better
to do that.
One of the problems I had
when I was trying to do,
I was trying to simplify things for my
pony animations back in
2016. I'm like, I'm going to do motion comics.
Because comic dubs
are like a really popular way
to get millions of views.
You just take a comic and you like
speak over it. I'm like, I could do that,
but like, just have things
like move subtly
by like creating them in flash.
But I would always like do full on
backgrounds and shit and it's like,
why?
Why?
You probably got like half as many done as you
could have.
That was like 80% of my time
was spent working on the backgrounds and shit
just posing the character rigs,
was the fucking easy part.
And no one cares except you.
No one cares. Honestly, it looks worse
that way. It would have been better simplified
because it's too much visual clutter.
Oh, but fidelity.
Fidelity.
Oh, no, but the perfect
parallax scrolling
of the layers of the background.
Scientifically accurate.
Or whatever.
Fidelity.
Yes.
I remember, you know, I think
the thing about
that one of them
that whips the others into shape just reminds me
of a sentiment that I have
repeated recently
a few times, which is that
I miss
working on
stuff with like a group
or in like a thing
where it was like
with T-Bap, it was me and Nate doing
stuff and we would both be like, okay,
you got to do this and I'll do this
and like, what can we get done
in like one day? Okay.
Can we do this? All right.
We agree. We will take these
tasks and this is our responsibility.
Okay, break. Let's go do them.
And we'd figure out
like how much can we feasibly
do in one day?
Okay, that's what we'll do. That's the episode.
That sounds fun.
The deadline
is
something that cannot be changed.
And so all you can do is plan
your time
as effectively as possible.
That's how it was. The episode would come out.
We'd be like, well, we want to get the T-Bap
about it done like the same weekend.
So how much can we do
before Sunday?
All right. Yeah, I think I would just
leave it as like as long as it comes out
before the next episode, then
whatever.
Not timeliness. Timeliness was
part of the T-Bap mission statement.
Yeah, I probably would have got more subscribers
if I was quicker.
Perhaps.
Anyway, it's good to be part of a team.
It's good to be part of a well-oiled machine.
Not like the PCP.
Instead, I'm just a
I'm just a
lone freak.
I'm just a lone
gunman.
Just a lone sniper
in the tower.
I don't know what that means.
Pointing your gun at Eleazar.
He's how you get episodes out on time.
You just chuck it at him.
Eleazar is very reliable.
Eleazar slaving over a hot
PCP.
I can just say Eleazar.
With a red dot, like sniper dot around
dangling around his neck
from across the street.
He's so easy to
manipulate. I can just say Eleazar
puts Saul Goodman
on screen and he'll do it.
He knows where to find it.
He's doing it right now.
I saw some
sprite art of
Saul Goodman
in Ace Attorney.
Like him banging the desk like Ace Attorney.
Oh.
That sounds cool.
Was he in the style of Ace Attorney?
Yeah, yeah.
It was just him in the scene
instead of, I guess, Edgeworth.
But it looked like him in that
style and it looked, I was like,
I know that guy. He would.
He would do
law.
I was disappointed that the
Saul Goodman
from Attack on Titan
didn't look like
him much in the anime
when they got to it.
I was annoying.
I'm not familiar with that guy.
You know, I never finished
Better Call Saul
now that I think of it.
Well, it's the last season
is about to come out in like a week.
Oh god, it's not done.
It's not done. It's good.
It's pretty fucking good though.
Probably one of my favorite shows
with live action shows ever, definitely.
Bob Odenkirk is like
pretty, he's pretty old, right?
Maybe like 60 something.
Maybe not 60.
Didn't he like collapse on set
this past year? Like he had a health
scare or something?
He had a heart incident
quote unquote.
I mean,
most people are just like heart attack.
He's like, well, technically,
doctors say incident, but I mean,
what difference is it?
Yeah.
It was well filming the final
season of Better Call Saul.
Wow. Okay.
Yeah, this
the manga one just
looks exactly like Bob Odenkirk.
Yeah.
What?
Why does he do that?
What is that tech on Titan?
I think he must
I feel like, yeah, he could have just been
looking at Bob Odenkirk and
it's close enough that I feel like
this could be not an accident.
Aren't the Titans
usually have no hair
at all or very little hair?
It depends. This feels like a very deliberate
hairstyle to give a Titan.
It does. The hairstyle's spot on.
And the face and even the expression
just feels in character
a little bit.
I mean, I heard Better Call Saul is,
I heard that it's really popular in China.
It's possible it's popular in Japan too.
I don't know.
Better Call Titan.
Better Attack Saul.
Maybe when the last season comes out,
I will try and remember how far
through it I was and
go back and finish it.
I like Bob.
I like Bob and David.
He's a good man.
Fun fact.
Before I had seen Breaking Bad
or Better Call Saul,
I saw an animation called Better Call Saul.
Which is
a Monsters Inc. version.
Oh, Better Call Sully?
Yeah.
Call him as in quell him.
As in excise him.
Better Call Saul.
It's literally just
a scene
like the scene from the end of season one
just with Monsters Inc.
And it's like word for word.
Exactly the same.
Except they only changed
the names of a few characters.
They just swapped a couple of words around.
But most of the dialogue is identical.
And it's accurate
to both franchises.
Which is really funny.
And so after I saw that,
not knowing anything about the show,
I'm like Better Call Saul. More like
Better Fuck Chuck.
And of course- Better Feed Snead.
Better Feed Snead.
I didn't know that there was a character called Chuck
in the show who does get fucked.
And my friends thought that was very funny
that I didn't understand
the clever joke I made.
His brother is Chuck, right?
Yeah, his brother.
His funny brother.
So yeah, this is made by
Yukino Joe who I recently
found out
is a bit of a crazy person.
Wait, is this the guy who made the
Dog of Wisdom?
He did the...
I'm my original character, Blonic.
You know?
I found... I recently
saw someone
bemoaning the fact that the guy
who made the Dog of Wisdom was like
a weirdo NFT dude or something.
Yes, it's not just that.
If you look at his Twitter, it's like
he's trying to speedrun
having every single bad take imaginable.
Alright, let's see here.
He's attacked... I need to find his account.
Because
I don't know exactly what it's called
but I did like
some people responding to him calling him out.
Is it Cool the Joe?
Yeah, Cool the Joe sounds right.
It's linked on his YouTube.
He was attacking...
He's only got 2,000 followers on Twitter.
Yeah, I'm assuming it's in a Twitter account
he doesn't advertise much.
But he had a bunch of tweets attacking
Disney employees who were criticizing
Disney River anti-gay stuff
and he was on the side of
he was attacking them for criticizing
Disney which is like, why?
He was attacking animators
and storyboarders who wanted
the new deal for animation
or whatever it's called.
I see him being a little whiny, a little
bitch about it here.
He just seemed to be attacking animators
and storyboarders who want better
workers rights
and promoting NFTs
and all his NFTs got stolen too apparently
but he still supports them.
He's just doubling down.
No, NFTs are good.
I swear.
Well...
Die.
That's all I gotta say.
He's got a Hexagon
Icons
but I'm not sure
if it's like actually
an NFT or if it's just
a regular one that just happens to be
Hexagonal
I can't tell.
No, when I scroll up
it has a circular outline.
It's a fake Hexagon.
Why fake Hexagon?
Is it because NFTs got stolen?
That would be so funny.
If he's like, well I know they got stolen
but I'm still going to use it.
I'm just going to make it a Hexagon.
I don't know.
Look, that's all poor little psycho troll
didn't like that I called her out for being
a horrible friend and a lazy ass shit animator
You're a fucking slime.
Whoa, slime.
Sorry.
Wait, slime? What?
What?
Hold on.
I see him saying what the fuck
to Ross's
he put animators
into Family Guy?
Yeah, he's just been like
attacking every animator.
That was just a thing I read earlier.
I don't even know what he's responding to here.
I don't know what he's responding to
but I just
discovered a couple weeks ago that he's like
attacking animators.
He's attacking people in the industry.
He's complaining that
people want Disney to not be
homophobic. He's complaining
that people don't like NFTs.
T's?
NFTs.
I don't know. It's just weird.
Show the animator. I lost all my NFTs
frown face.
Is that a tweet from this guy?
That's his tweet.
And he retweeted it, I guess.
Why would you
It's
the Cuphead show
February 22nd. The Cuphead show
is terrible and NFTs are good.
Okay.
Yeah, that's weird.
That's a weird take too.
The war is bullshit.
Hulu Animaniacs pushed for
this war. Animation workers
do not deserve a new deal.
Okay.
What? Is he talking about the war
in Ukraine? Probably.
Is he blaming on Hulu Animaniacs
reboot?
Maybe. I feel like that can't be it.
He's got to be referring to the
animation stuff as a war going on.
Animators want better pay.
Oh, how dare you start a war.
I wonder what he meant by this
just screenshotting Biden
mentioning that we're back in the Paris climate agreement
and he just
screenshotted it and didn't say anything. What does that mean?
Did Biden put a fucking
It's weird for
the POTUS to put a little
colon P. I'll give him that.
I'll give him that.
That's not real.
That doesn't feel real.
Is that real?
I think
it's impossible
and therefore I will not look into it.
Hold on. We're
back in the
Paris climate
agreement colon P.
No results.
I don't think it's real.
So that just makes the tweet
even more mysterious.
What is he trying to say with this?
He probably found it
and assumed it was real and then he was like
look at this fucking president.
Look at this
groomer president using emojis
to make
to sexualize children
somehow.
Typical Democrat.
He's being all cutesy
but he's got an agenda.
He's trying to turn me gay with this little
with this little tongue sticking out emoji.
Well it's not going to work.
I'm going to turn him gay first.
Then we'll see.
I had an opportunity to put
Dog of Wisdom on Disney Channel.
I made an NFT instead of doing that.
NFTs don't seem that sick when compared to the
acceptable idea of success
where big money feels entitled to be so invasive
and then drag your corpse around
when you're gone.
I don't give a fuck what people say.
I've been condescending for a year.
I made the right decision.
What?
He made a tweet
where he says I'm against NFTs now.
Okay.
Wait, did he say that?
He literally said that.
It wasn't April Fools.
It was November 4th.
November 4th.
Last year.
I don't know, I'm just scrolling.
He's a hard man to figure out.
I like his animations.
They're funny. They tickle me.
The man, though.
Seems like he's mad.
Seems like he kind of made the wrong choice
by making an NFT instead of
working for Disney.
Maybe he's mad that he did that.
But he's got to double down.
Because then he lost all his NFTs.
Lol.
Okay, what a weirdo.
Okay, seems like...
You know what?
Seems like he's coming from a place
where things did not go so well for him.
And I think that's
funny.
I genuinely hope whatever is
going on in his head
he calms down.
Because it just seems like
he's living a stressful life and he doesn't have to.
He does seem
miserable
and confused.
I'd like him to not be miserable
It's not too late.
Alright, well
we got to kill him.
What I'm saying, the way we can fix this
is to end him.
Execution.
Let me boot up Elden Ring.
I'm going to go find him.
Draw him into your comic.
Draw him into my...
Are you that guy who did that dog
in a bar?
Yes, stab.
He says,
and I'm also a demon
with demon powers.
Prepare to fight.
I'd rather not prepare.
Dies.
Alright.
Let me check my little notes.
Did I have anything else
to mention today?
No.
Yeah,
I...
Lord Ghost things,
people put the backer surveys.
Please fill them out
after I get like a few more.
If there's like three people left
that just haven't responded
then I'll just send what I can
and deal with it later.
How did we get
on the subject of the dog man?
We mentioned
Better Call Saul
and then Better Call Saul
and then the guy who made it.
And I'm playing Elden Ring.
I'm streaming Elden Ring by the way.
If you want to watch me play Elden Ring
for the first time and not know what is happening,
you can go to
twitch.tv.com
and watch that.
Yeah.
Maybe what I can do
because my project will be done...
I mean, it's basically done.
It'll be possibly out today
and maybe the NSFW version
will be done before Friday.
I could be streaming Pumpkin Alley.
Maybe I could try and arrange it
to stream it when this
PCP comes out.
Or two hours after whenever people get to this part
in the episode so that they know
to go watch me right now.
That's assuming my husband doesn't have plans
and I looked with that but I could try.
Please do.
I'd watch that.
I would.
I try to watch every video and stream
of people playing Pumpkin Alley.
I know.
I was watching at fucking everything
when the PCP dating sim came out.
That was such a...
The two weeks after we released that
was so nice just watching everything
seeing all the reactions and stuff.
Yeah.
That was so fun.
That was so cool.
That was radical.
I should have retweeted
the dating sim on April Fools.
Oh yeah.
Two year anniversary at this point.
Yeah.
Guys, it's officially been two years
since the PCP was good.
That's what they say.
It's been longer than that.
Let's be honest.
You have to keep turning back the clock
like, when is it going to be good?
I knew it was good.
Surely it was.
The horse cast is still not good.
What the fuck?
You turn the last page and you're like,
huh?
What?
The horse cast is good.
I do like it a lot.
What have I been doing for seven years?
It's scary how British
you sound in the horse cast,
Kim.
That's because I don't
know how I sound now.
I sound like me.
But I definitely...
I haven't noticed the difference, but maybe it's been gradual.
It's definitely gradual.
I didn't talk much
at all.
But I certainly didn't talk
much at all on
the internet
before we started doing podcasts.
But I didn't talk
to Americans ever
before I was doing stuff like that.
So it was like
I'm surrounded by different accents.
I sort of picked them up over time.
My voice
sometime in like the first or
second year of the PCP
changed. There's like an
old Ben voice
and I don't know
I don't know. There's like
I can tell it's like, oh, that's how I used to sound
and this is how I sound now and there's
I don't know what happened to
change it, but like my voice used to be
like deeper.
Your beard is made
deeper and now it's gone.
It's kind of coming back, actually.
It's looking good.
Looking good. I'm down to 170 pounds.
My beard is coming
in.
Things are looking up.
I've got
it's all going
for me. It's all coming my way.
It sounds like you're about to cry.
Well, I mean
no.
Shut up.
It's all coming up.
Things are finally
going to go well for me.
Okay.
What was I talking about?
Do you want to do voicemails?
Yeah.
I have a feeling that some of them might
be bad and I am going to
not acknowledge those.
So
I
understand.
Yes.
You
wait.
Okay, we had
all right. Here we go.
The first voicemail
of the day. I'm going to post these in
general, I guess.
It is called, let me find
the number
uh
five seven
four four five seven.
This is called Breaking News, sorry.
Uh oh, what?
Kingdom Hearts 4
trailer.
I saw a
screenshot of
Sora's new design. I was wondering
what that was from.
That's gotta be fake.
What the fuck?
Let me, this is the tweet
I saw.
He's got normal sized shoes
now. He's no longer
chubby shoes, Mickey Boy.
Is that Kyrie?
Nah, it's a sallyoop.
They made this in response to that really
long video, Shitting on Kingdom Hearts 3.
I bet they did. Kingdom Hearts 3
is a waste of time.
I think that's the video, yeah.
I've been hearing everyone talk about it for the past two weeks.
I love that video. I've watched it like four times.
A waste of effort, I think.
A waste of effort. That's what it is.
Wait, that's eight months ago. Why did I only hear people talk
about that video a couple weeks ago?
That video was okay, but it was very...
I didn't understand
what he was getting at.
I'll be honest, I didn't play
Kingdom Hearts 3,
so I don't even have that strong an opinion.
Oh, no.
I saw it. I saw
Kingdom Hearts 3 being played in my living room
when it was brand new
and
there was something off about it,
and then we found out how short it was
and then we just gave up.
Yeah, it's not
good, but it's all right.
It's not worth the money.
That's definitely the
something I could say. It's not worth the money it costs.
It's not worth $60?
No, not at all.
Oh, plus for $20
or $30 DLC to actually have the rest of the game.
I sort of enjoyed.
Oh, yeah, and you go
DLC to get the real ending.
That guy said, like the only part
of the game that guy said was good, was the DLC.
He really liked the DLC
and like nothing else.
Like the Tangled is world is like
nothing interesting
and the Big Hero 6
world is really boring.
Toy Story World is kind of cool
and parts of the Caribbean
world is like, ah, finally a pirate ship
game that I like.
And I forget
if there was even
anything else.
It was frozen.
Frozen. That was a
boring level. I heard it was bad.
It was just sort of like
really, really
uninteresting.
And then the story doesn't really even exist
until you get to the end.
It's just sort of like
meandering around
and then, oh yeah,
the organization.
Now we can play the game.
But I didn't fight the final boss
because I was like, I don't care.
I don't care about that stuff.
I was surprised to find out
that Kingdom Hearts 3 is not really the end.
It's sort of
it's still setting up for more games.
I kind of thought 3 was supposed
to be the end, but it's not.
So, okay.
Yeah, I think something
something, the end
of the Xehanort trilogy
or whatever.
Some sort of villain
is no longer the main villain
and now it's going to be a different arc
of Kingdom Hearts, I guess,
is the idea.
Yeah, which
it's just weird.
Xehanort is
like, I mean in my
mind, he's the bad guy
and like
I don't know, Kingdom Hearts does not feel
to me like a robust
enough intellectual property to be like,
okay, that was just the first arc of Kingdom Hearts.
Now we're moving on to a whole new
fucking plot.
Well, as you can see in this tweet
the second image, that's Alleyoop.
So this is actually my game
is Pumpkin Alley.
They approached me
after playing the demo and they said
can we make
your game into Kingdom Hearts 4?
And I said, sure, here's all the rights
to my intellectual property
and I didn't want to get paid for it
and they just took it. So if you see a Pumpkin girl
they
it's all theirs. Got it.
Damn. Got it.
Noted.
Yeah, I don't know.
I guess I'll
eagerly await
when this game comes out and then I'll watch
YouTube videos about how bad it is
and I'll get a lot of enjoyment out of that.
I was kind of like
I played the second game
and I enjoyed it. It was a really, really good fun game.
Yeah.
And then I didn't want to play
like the 70 different things
that were
on PSP
and mobile, whatever they were
all over the place.
And so I was like, okay, I'll just buy the third one.
And unfortunately
it was like 12 years.
Yeah, unfortunately they did not design it
to be
playable after you just beat the second game.
You have to be a super fan
to even comprehend anything.
You have to have played all of the secret
like the side things.
The PSP and like the weird like
online the mobile game and all that.
You have to be
at least knowledgeable
about some of the bigger ones
like Chain of Memories or
whatever the fuck that one was.
I did play Chain of Memories
and it was awesome. Not that one.
It was like those other ones. I forget what they're called.
You mean like 368 over two days
and Birth by Sleep.
Birth by Sleep, that's the one.
They probably expect you to have played that
and I didn't. So
it's not much for me in that game.
Is Birth by Sleep the one about
Terra and Aqua and
Ventus?
I think so.
They've fallen asleep and you gotta wake up
and get born.
They've fallen asleep.
Okay, I will.
Thanks.
That's exactly what is
in that game.
Whatever, Kingdom Hearts is
fucking silly.
The trailer's out so maybe
five years from now, Kingdom Hearts 4 will come out.
Ten years, twelve.
That'll be exciting.
Alright, let's do voicemails.
First voicemail
is called
Nate Besman 2022.
Alright.
Three, two, one, go.
I did see that comment
about my usage of the word retarded.
I will never give up
the word retarded. Never.
I won't do it.
The euphemism treadmill has been spinning
along so fast lately.
I will never give up that word.
It is a rude word.
I totally agree. I'm a rude guy.
I'm a rude dude. What can I say?
Okay.
You know what?
I know people
that use the R word.
I personally
have ceased
to use it, but I would be
a hypocrite to get upset
at Nate using it
because there are other people
that use it and I don't
bishot them.
I let it go without comment.
I mean, it is his word.
It is his word.
True.
I didn't get to pass.
Lucky.
Damn.
It's just a hard one.
Of all the words to call someone dumb,
that's just a hard one.
I guess so.
Sometimes I just want to
say it hard.
I don't know.
It's got the R right there.
It's just stupid with a hard R.
Patard.
Star Trek Picard.
I don't know.
I've been very
resistant to stop saying it,
but ultimately when it comes to me,
it's dropping words from my vocabulary.
It's just about
the fact that I just don't want to upset people
in my day-to-day conversation and I've just met more
and more people who are upset by it.
I feel like
they've been told to be upset by it
and not because
the word actually gets used in an ableist way
that much compared to
the millions of uses where it's just
I'm like, ah, I'm fucking retarded.
Oh, I dropped something.
That's how I hear the word use my whole life
and I've only ever heard it used in an ableist sense.
A handful of times
really ever.
To me, it doesn't come across that way.
I feel like that's probably
it doesn't offend me.
I was bullied for being neurodivergent
and I had that word thrown at me a bunch
but I didn't care about the word.
I cared that people thought that I was stupid
because I think I'm smart. How dare you say I'm dumb.
I never cared about the word.
I only ever cared about
if I was being bullied for my weird behavior
in high school, I don't know.
The word was the least
of my worries compared to
the knowledge that they've hated me.
That's what I've heard.
That's all language
is that it's not literal
the word, it's the way
it's used
that can rub someone the wrong way
when it's saying I don't like you
can be more damaging than
a swear word hurled at a person.
I agree, but I also feel like
I can
I can swap it out for something else
it's not too difficult.
Whatever I think of like
times when I would say
fucking our word
I would just replace it with stupid
because that's basically the same thing
that's what I mean.
I've been working towards that
I have fucking stupid
I've been saying that more
I haven't completely dropped it
but I'm working my way
out.
Every time someone told me
that it bothered them
that I would use it
I was like okay noted
and I guess
there were enough of those times
I guess it really comes down to the fact
that a word used
can have unintended
effects
even if you don't use it in a disparaging way
some people just feel bad when they hear it
so that has to be
accounted for in deciding
what words to use not just
when you decide to say something to someone
in a certain way to make them feel bad
if you want to do that
but
knowing that there could be collateral damage
and maybe you could shrug
and be like oh people are so sensitive these days
but like I don't know
I guess they are what are you going to do
are you going to be annoying to everyone
I don't know how true this is
I would just hate the idea but like
because I feel like the word
in the mid-2000s was on its way
to just becoming a colloquial word like stupid
where it would have no more offense than that
because
it was becoming casual but then
there was like pushback to keep
the word offensive I feel like
almost
and I feel like
back then no one was really hurt
by the word that I was aware of
but now people seem to be very hurt by it
when I'm like
I have to wonder like is it because of like personal experiences
you've dealt with ableism that have like made you
that sensitive to the word
or is it because you've just been told
over and over that it's bad and you can't say it
if it's the latter
then you're just kind of
making the word hurt people more than it would have
if you just let it go
I feel like it's
more complicated than just a single person's decision
I feel like
in a society where
the R slur is an R slur
and you can't say it
somebody deciding to say it
says something about a person
that like
it maybe makes people feel
like if they're willing to break
social norms
what else are they willing to break
socially?
Bones, skulls, ligaments
I think
it's a gender
gender
I think it's not something you should
like
if somebody says the R slur they're there for
it's not like a deductive thing
but it's like it's understandable
that breaking a social
rule
that is not like written down it's just sort of everybody
decides yes we're not going to do this
it says something
about you as a person that you decide to break it
knowing that it's a rule
that people follow
and that it's you know the consequences of that
might be overblown sometimes
but it's
it's too nuanced to have like
one like either or
I think
language is crazy
and the way we use it and interact with each other
has changed so much over the past few decades
so I don't know
I don't know I just know
people told me that hey the word
is hurtful and I was like
oh okay sorry
but I also
I just worry
the best you can do is just
work on your
and I don't really have an opinion
because it doesn't offend me but
I don't know
I just took people out their word when they said
they didn't like it
I don't know
it's a bad habit for me to be like
why do you really not like it
I shouldn't be saying that
that's not fair
I know what you mean
I just don't know
I'm happy to drop it
it's again it's just gonna take me a while
because I've said it my whole fucking life
I said it back when I was being bullied and stuff
I also said it my whole life
and I never
it's like it's weird that like
weirdly the proportion
of the words usage that's ableist
I feel like is increasing by having people
stop using it in the innocuous way
but whatever
I just worry that
because I know there are some people who don't think
you can say anything at all
like you can't say stupid even
you can't say dumb
I remember Faust Slime had to make a huge apology
apology video because he said naners
which is slang for
bananas
apparently that was too far
and that's fucking
wild to me
that's a little funny
it is a little funny
but like
they call someone stupid
they're not like making a comment
about like their brain function
that they can't control or some shit
they're just calling you foolish
they're just saying that you're acting dumb
not that you're
oh you have a disability
that you can't help haha
like that's not what people are fucking
saying when they use those words
yeah but like it
it's uh
it's complicated
to know how to
like
a single person can't decide
the way society should be
and expect people to capitulate
just because
it's like
there's so many moving parts
if the wind tells me
that I shouldn't say a certain word
and it's something I said my whole life
obviously I'm going to be like
ah but I want to say it
and maybe I'll slip up sometimes
but like
if it's consistent and it stays
then I guess I'll just have to stop
saying it
because I live in a society
and the society is a certain way
and it's
sometimes sucks but what am I going to do
okay I don't know
I mean people
I just uh I didn't like it
when people were mad at me
yeah
and I was like well
I know how to avoid this outcome
yeah
I'm offended by people
putting words in my mouth
or putting meaning in my words I guess
but I clearly didn't intend
why can't I be mad at people
for doing that
am I doing that
is that what you're saying
no I'm talking to these hypothetical people
who want to remove all
insults to intelligence in the world
get rid of all of them completely
those are the people I don't like
I hope it's not a slippery slope
I hope that doesn't catch on
I mean
I feel like
I've seen pushback
you can't even insult people
for any amount of
like
it would become so cumbersome
that society would be like
nah we gotta have at least one
we gotta have at least one
so we can actually describe a thing
I've seen pushback against
stupid but I've seen
more
I've seen more
pushback against the pushback
where it's like okay
you could interpret stupid to mean
neurologically
disadvantaged or whatever
but you could also
just be bad decision making
someone could be
poor reasoning
yeah
or dishonest reasoning even
like if you wanted to be
super slippery slope about it
you could worry that the word no
and the concept of
disagreeing would become
like
you would be killed in the street
for disagreeing
and that's where
that's where the logic
would go if you were like super
neurotic about it
I just don't see it
being like an issue in the real world
maybe on Twitter
maybe Twitter and social media will get to a point
where it's just unbearably like
wokescoldy and they will
tear you to limb from limb for doing anything
in particular it's kind of sometimes
I mean it's sometimes like that sometimes like that
I mean I feel like wokescoldy
like
the aftermath
like it's a big hype thing that happens
once because it's the hot
new thing to hate on a person
or whatever because they did something
a social faux pas but then it sort of gets
forgotten and if the person doesn't
run away then they can just continue
to exist and nothing really
happens
well I feel like
we have learned nothing
but maybe that's okay
yes
no I have the F slur pass
because I'm in a gay relationship
but I don't like saying that word anymore
yeah
I said that before a lot
at some point I just sort of
felt weird to say it
I dropped it before
Kai started transitioning
and so
it became
retroactively a gay relationship later
but I'm like I don't feel like saying it
you're trans
I'm not
Kai is trans
Kai is my husband
I thought you said I
no Kai I'm not trans
there's no magic button
that'll make me an 8 foot tall
woman with giant titties
that button doesn't exist and that's the only
trans I'll accept for myself
so
goals
goals yes
who wouldn't want to be
8 foot tall mummy milker
there are two buttons one turns me
into that one turns everyone else
on earth into that I'm pressing
that button
true
that's the button
that's the test
that's the litmus test
I'm also pushing the everyone else button
I
have to think about it for a little while
do you get the F Slayer pass
if you're gay
if you press the button
if you do any gay shit
do you get the R word pass
if you are neurodivergent
I guess so
I guess it would make sense
I was bullied
for me being on
the autism spectrum
but according to people
you can barely tell
you're one of the good ones
I'm one of the good ones
I want to
test it on the outside but I'm neurotypical
I could barely
I could barely even tell
that you're
special
that's a thing
special feels like way more
of a slur to me than the R
word at this point
context of the sort of person who would use
that word so condescending
imagination
that sounds way slimy to me but
oh well
slimy
but like could in
20 years
oh I work in special effects
you can't say that word
could it end up that way if enough people start
using that word
why is it called special effects
it is a bit
not the same but it is a bit weird
to me
you can't say
colored people anymore
but we circled back around
and now people of color is
sort of like the more polite way
it's just the same words
I know it's one of those things where it's like
the people who
the kind of person who says colored people
is typically a pretty sus person
but at the same time it's like
why is the acceptable word
just the same thing but re-arranged
yeah
I didn't get it
I believe it's because the colored
people
term
came from
that community and they said we would like
to be referred to as this we find this acceptable
and everyone was like okay
yeah
just how it was
I don't know why I think they just wanted to reclaim
it maybe
remember when there were takes
about black bodies
remember black bodies
the black body spectrum
no different thing
I don't know
they're in the most pitched
part of
the BLM thing
in like 2020 or whatever
sometimes
some white person with like
some academic background would
say some shit about how
the police are committing violence against
black bodies and they would say it like that
it's like
why are you saying it like that
that is kind of
weird
I guess it was like an academic thing
I don't know it just sounded really bizarre
to hear it in the wild
in my head
that means they killed them and they're dead
that's when you call someone a buddy
I think it was quickly decided
that you know that's a weird way to talk about people
let's not do it anymore
yeah
I'm inclined to agree
I guess they did kill a few people
they did kill a few people
black body radiation is
when something's hot and it
emits
energy
in a spectrum
black body spectrum is useful
for art
for trying things that emit heat
what do you mean
next voicemail
just color it red
just make it red that's my spectrum
black body spectrum
wait a minute
black bodies, black body spectrum
autism spectrum
what
I'm just saying
I don't know if I can post this image
useful tip for artists who want to draw
things glowing hot
if you want to be specific about what temperature
the thing is you can refer to this chart
and grab your hues accordingly
this is interesting
if you want to be scientifically accurate
that's stupid
who wants to be scientifically accurate
exactly
I mean the colors are nice
I guess
but my manga is black and white
oh yeah
because we know
the fruit powers
that magma is hotter
than fire
and that's why akainu was able to kill
ace
we want to make akainu's magma that yellow color
and we don't want to go any
further than the 2100
degree orange
for ace's fire and then you'll know
they did it the other way around
do you remember
akainu was red
yeah he was they fucked it up
they fucked it up
they fucked it up they loved it
sorry
the search for
well this wasn't when I typed black body spectrum
but this popped up
and I have to
I'm just like
to me I have difficulty
picturing the bodies attached to the ends
of the arms so it just looks like a pile
of severed arms
duh
how are they lying there
I feel like they must have taken the pictures
individually
like two at a time
I think they would have had to be arranged in a very uncomfortable way
yeah like the ambient occlusion seems
accurate though where the skin's like touching
unless there was very cleverly
like photoshopped
I feel like maybe one or two of them
for a second I thought these were all the same
hand because they all
kind of have the same sort of nails
but no I don't like everything so
yeah
they do all have the same
and they have the exact same
arm length
yeah they do
these are all the people of the same size
and build
good for them
damn
alright so that was the first voicemail
yeah that was one voicemail
alright
it's called
Tommy J
three two one go
hey what's up it's me Tommy J
back again with another stellar voicemail
finally
imagine if you will procrastinators
that you are walking along
in a dark and enchanted forest
emphasis on forest
and suddenly
you're all of six and there is a fork in the road
among these paths
are the left path
and the right path
on the left path
is basically you guys
star a new podcast based on
video game development
and you have a variety of guests
not including oblivion fall
for obvious reasons
obvious reasons
of course you have to star a new patreon
which you don't get the residual
people that are already
subscribed and you gotta
change youtube channels
and just change the name
and that'd be okay
what the fuck
that seemed complicated
on the right path
which is the wrong path
but is also the right path
basically you guys
continue business as usual
and slowly but surely been
threatened suicide until
Nate and Tom both come back on the podcast
I guilt them into it
I feel like Nate should probably heed that call
being brothers and all
but we never had concrete proof
that you guys are actually related
so who knows
this was a completely unhinged
voicemail
stupid
the proof is that I've seen both of your surnames independently
through
paypal transactions
oh yeah
at various points that's how I know
how the mystery is gone
if we
if we could use this
rebranded to be a video game
development podcast
we could just use the same
the same patreon
oh yeah we could rebrand the channel
but we couldn't just rebrand the patreon
we would have to make a whole new patreon
it's not like you can change the url
you can change the url
they let you do that
you can change everything and you keep the patrons
they don't go away
I mean we could rebrand
I wouldn't want to rebrand to specifically a game developer thing
because we don't talk about
game development every week
so we would
we would literally just have
less conversations
less podcasts
yeah I would not
two best game developers
bitch about things that aren't
necessarily games
it's like
at that point why do anything
I'm already
at that point
I don't know
the podcast is just
about us talking about whatever
that's all it can ever be
alright next voicemail
is called
Tommy J
Agaj M
3 2 1 go
hey what's up
procrastinators podcast it's me Tommy J again
back at it again with another
stellar voicemail
in this voicemail I'd like to tell you
that the next five voicemails
are all me putting on
different voices so
enjoy so let's skip to six
ahead
I'll give him a chance
I would love for Tommy J to just be lying right now
so that we
it's just actually different people
I suspect this might not actually be
Tommy J
we'll see
we'll upload them at the same time
without his knowledge
I mean I don't actually
remember what Tommy J
sounds like
wait you just heard him
I think this might be an imposter
can you see the time stamps
were these voicemails all uploaded
within a few minutes of each other
no actually
the last two were
uploaded five days ago
and then the next one was five days
and then the one after that
was four days
and then after that three days
three days three days
so no some of these were posted days apart
yeah that makes me think it was a bit because
I think they have to be
because they would know that surely other people
would post voicemails if you spread them out
if you're going to do that you have to post them back to back
if you want to be sure
I think so
I think that clinches it
we didn't even listen to it yet and we know
we've cracked the code
alright the next one
is called
this meme needs to die
three two one go
oh my god
Ben no one cares
no one cares about Trixie
shut the fuck up
ah
okay you're right
and yet we get voicemails about it
I don't think Trixie's been brought up that much recently
there was this one
in a couple of the last
episodes there were some voicemails
about her
yeah voicemails
yeah yeah yeah yeah
well that's what I mean like somebody cares
this person
just brought up Trixie
on the PCP
technically true I understand
I understand the perspective
that like I care
more
about hating her than like
regular humans do
that like her
and I can understand why you would think that
but I assure you
every time I say something mean about Trixie
a bunch of absolute
psychopaths
like swarm out of the woodwork
and get like very offended
at me and say mean things to me
and they can't tolerate it
so I promise you there are people
there
there are people
that
do not share
your opinion voicemailer
but your point is
understood
okay
next one is called
I think there's no actual voicemail
I think it's just cyber shell
your videos suck and you just got lucky
you got fame
okay there's no voicemail
damn I can't believe they said that
about me the guest
agree
cyber shell complete hat
complete fraud
most people get lucky
cyber shell is definitely lucky that
some of their videos got big views
but they're good videos
so it was probably gonna happen at some point anyway
I like cyber shell videos
at least the recent ones
I like you know all the things about the sonic
oddities like
the sonic fandom is huge
and they're well made videos that are interesting
and funny like across
he was gonna get some amount of fame
I think he deserves it
I mean he was posting
his old sonic stuff was at a time
when like
I would say maybe if he had posted that same stuff
like years later
maybe it wouldn't have been
as big a hit because it was like
earlier youtube days
but like that's just
what posting be like
I liked the
the exploring chow
video I forget what it was called
I think it was something I bet
yeah that's the one of the new I really like that one
that was a really good video
yeah that one ruled
so there you go that's what I think
next one is called
I have an annoying voice
3 2 1
go
yes I use it
for the strength
of an unicorn
he shall eat up
some nations
his enemies
and shall break their bones
and pierce them
through with his
arrows
was that void gazer
I mean doid gazer
maybe
that's one of the quotes from
phantom's revenge
my favorite
work on your voice
it could be way more annoying
you could do some run for the cube type shit
if you wanted
run for the cube
it's the guy with the gummy rat who goes
run away from the cube boy
he talks like that
that does not ring a bell at all
oh god
well now I sound like a fucking freak
you know
the rat when the cube boy
sure
of libyan fall
I'll just fucking link it
sure
run for the cube
oh wow it's real
5 seconds of that will make you scream probably
hello
oh god
yeah okay I hear it
I hear it
that's unfortunate
alright I posted the next one
the next one is called
go
hey
do you think that christine
would have been able to finish this game
because I'm fucking gay
no
no I don't think she could be that
who christine
no I think probably
I heard black christine
I guess I meant to say that
do you think that christine
yeah yeah
we don't talk about
we don't talk about black christine
no
I think to beat phantom's revenge
you need
grit
gumption
fortitude
strength of character
moral fiber
backbone
you need a brain a heart
and a dick
and christine has none of those things
so
she can't do it
you fool
but I guess we'll never know
brain a heart a dick and no sex
in vet order
those are
that's the full package
okay next one
posting
next one is called
I'm doing this every time I die
3 2 1 go
for love
okay
okay he's reading the quotes
he's reading the bible
he's dying in phantom's revenge
and he's all mad
cause he's bad at video games
he's reading the quotes
get over it man
just beat it
just get good already
why don't ya
just watch my stream
just watch gib stream
and you'll be like halfway there
oh
okay next one is called
every single time
he's glory
yeah it's another one
single time
point made
game good you bad
uh
skipping that one
next one is called
happy late birthday
3 2 1 go
hi I just wanted to wish you a happy
birthday Ben
and uh also
fucking stop talking about tricksy
oh my fucking god it's so annoying
now okay
I don't even like the bet
damn I don't like the what
the bit
the bet the bit
I thought it was
I thought it was bet but I don't know what that would mean
I don't really know what the bit would refer to either
just cause he said that
I'm gonna go feed the cats
you're doing that now
I'll be like a second
okay
uh yeah happy birthday Ben
oh thank you
I made that little doodle thing on twitter
yes I loved it
I loved it
uh
oh I got something
I think yeah
Cassie showed me what she was drawing for you
yeah
what do you think of that
I loved it
so much
they said I was gonna hate it
but I didn't
I'll
they're gonna post it
well I don't know
they said they weren't sure what account
to post it on
so I'll
hopefully show it somewhere oh I made it my phone background
they wanted me to make it my phone but I was like yeah okay
that's fair
cause I hate the default background that my phone came with
uh
so it's that's gone
got the new one
it's based
anyway it was great wow I'm here
you know uh sad news
this week I just remembered
uh actually I don't know
sure it happened this week but it happened sometime
fairly recently
I got the unfollow from deadly comics
and that made me really sad
oh what I love deadly comics
I love deadly comics too
but you know what I deserve it
I am useless
I am nothing
what is the point of following me there is none
so you know what he was right
you know what he was right to do it
you know when you follow
Ben Steyn your twitter timeline
is wailing and gnashing of teeth
from one man
he stuck it out for years
uh but uh I don't know
sometime in the last
couple weeks I guess
either something
bugs him or maybe he was just like
I don't even know who this guy is
why do I follow this guy
is chris raygun still following me
I'm curious
Chris raygun comics follows me still
oh well
so I think it's I think you must have
you must have struck something
you must have done a Ben Steyn
man like it well that's stupid
I maybe uh yeah I mean
it's possible
that my uh Trixie negativity
might have been the thing
probably
it seems possible
I would say
I mean
I would hope
I mean why would they even care
but maybe they just don't like seeing posts about
like that
posts about like hey just fuck somebody maybe they just
maybe they see it and they're like well this is just frivolous
this is just a waste of my time and you know what it is
so he was right
with his decision
uh
and I support it
don't do that on my timeline
to follow his example you know what
it's fair enough
I simply have nothing of value
to contribute
so all I can do is spew bile
that's right
but I mean if spewing bile is what I
can do then
I'll spew till the cows come
spew away
basically
um
next one is called
uh
Killer Prince 930
yeah here we go
three two one go
dammit
at the rate I watch the videos
or take to watch the videos
I really get
late on the conversations
anyway have you guys ever heard of
the game called
the game called Undertale
yeah I have heard of that
yeah he's this guy
yeah okay that's I uh
wasn't that the exact the very first one
I believe I believe it was the first episode
yeah
you must have been listening to the the horse cast
so behind
he's got a bit of a backlog yeah
next one is called
uh
not a voicemail it's an image
uh here let me post it
I love visual media
oh
then Trixie said to me Ben you're just mad
that you don't get to fuck me like I do share
grandma let's get you to bed it happened it really
happened I have the
I have receipts
yeah I know that happened because I've seen
that this
I I I mean
whatever this is funny
this is funny
I like the implication that being mad
at someone implies that you're old
I
I tell that I tell that story
when someone asks me
Ben why are you so mad what did Trixie
people just legitimately still ask me like
what did she do like what has she ever done
to you like they ask me because they
don't know and then I have to be like
well and then I trot out this old
fucking story because
they fucking ask
I don't I don't bring it up
apropos of nothing
but it's true and it still
makes me mad
anyway next one is called
Ben's weekly reminder play
deltarune chapter 2
okay
next one is called Ben what did you think
of the Odin flashback with Roger
there's no there's
no voicemail it's just a question I
liked it
it was cool I I really
liked the Odin flashback the whole thing
learning about Odin and then meeting
seeing all
seeing young Roger was really
really cool it was
I did like it Odin
was I don't know
cool it's cool that he like
became a dad
while on board the
I mean he was an
totally insane character
like when he's introduced
he's so fun he was fun
um
he's just like
just a fucking like
wild dude
I guess it was a wild stallion
yeah pretty much
like a Japanese stallion I don't know
if they have horses in Japan
he he taught
right he taught all the other
crew members to read the pona
glyphs right that's what happened
or did it only
or did only he know how
I
yes he knew how to read them
because he was from one oh and that's where
they know how to do that
hmm
I'm trying to think that was
that was it I'm trying to think what else can I say
about other than Odin
was cool and I liked his backstory and I liked
seeing
you know him his like
travels with white beard and Roger
and stuff I don't know
uh those those guys are
those guys are sick
yeah I
loved it okay that's my answer
uh next one is
son of Marowak
did the okay here we go
okay three two one go
hey
Ben saying give a take
I'm a huge prover of going to the movies
if you two
are willing to go to see
Sonic 2 in theaters
I will pay for your tickets and snacks
God
huge promise let me know if you were
absolutely serious and I will
legit pay for your tickets
preferably in an AMC theater
give and take I don't know if you have AMCs
in your country
but
if I can pay for your ticket I will pay for yours
no problem
it's just a movie you don't need to
I don't want to go and see it
I don't I also don't want to go and see it
I you'd be paying
for me to waste my time
and I don't even want that
I want to go and see it
I want to
here's my reasoning
here's my reasoning alright
Sonic 1 just has Sonic
and Eggman is an even really Eggman
Sonic 2 we got
Knuckles we got Tails
and Eggman is very egg
like
if this movie does well
I'm just saying
if there was a Sonic free maybe Shadow
and I think the internet needs that
I'd like to see Shadow
I'd like to see if they use guns with Shadow
if Shadow has a gun
then I'll watch anything
that has that in it
they won't put a gun
they won't put a gun in the hands of a hedgehog
on the big screen
but I still wouldn't go and watch the movie
it would be really fucking funny
if Shadow of a Hedgehog
was in a real movie
and I think the best way to
make that happen is to pay for this one
buy a ticket and don't see it
you know first voice mail it
you should just buy their tickets and then they can just sit at home
and not leave the house
yeah hey now we're talking
why don't you do that
now I can get behind this plan
alright next one is called
while you were on Keto
I studied the blade
already
from Gibbon Rise Up
at KilbenSaint.com
that's a good one
alright 3, 2, 1, go
hey mate look at that the baby is doing
a little trick with the rattle I gave him
son of Beno Sento
son
I
train my body
to defeat you
for stealing
school
your defeat
will be delicious
as my
baby formula is
until next time
men go
kitten
are you trying to say
men go go take
yeah they're doing the kendo thing
the phantom horn does
is that an impression
the voice sounded different
I think it's
I think it's some
different person who has adopted
it's a new generation
he was reincarnated
as
Ethan Ralph and
Amanda Lynn Morris
child
was that a thing
I must have missed that
was what a thing
reincarnation of Samurai
Samurai
maybe that was last week
Ethan Ralph and Mae's baby
is
Samurai Samurai reincarnated his soul
into that
child
so that's why they sound different
yeah that's why he sounds different
not because like some guy decided to
just like steal the character
it's
cause he's a baby now
no it's canon
would you kill a baby hmm
I'm thinking about it
if he gave me
enough lip about stealing scrolls
I might think about it
Anna Maury would kill that baby
oh yeah for sure
cause that's what gets the job done
yeah
next one is called
way of the blade
way of the babe no guests
no survivors
from give you will be kiss or
crushed at you decide your
fate dot com
3 2 1 go
me
this baby I'm
turn off the baby monitor all right
I'm just like five minutes
so I can close my eyes
me
is sympathy
and anyone
else
in between the me and the
scent
will be
by my
all my
you
will
you have been warned
until
damn okay
okay rosanne you know
warning received you know I was
wondering
would get recast after shooting
that guy it's possible
now we know
he has
only expanded his range
proud of him
next one is called
Shrek's taint
ed
okay
3 2 1 go
so I'm watching
shark retold with some friends
and it was pretty good times all around
there were the bits where
the animators were clearly
being weird for the sake of
being weird and those parts
were kind of shit
otherwise you know pretty fun
time all around
except there was one part where
Shrek has now become irreparably
damaged
and now it's a little bit where there's
Christine Chandler
doing her thing
I was like oh no
for all this you know
considering everything that's happened
but
I can't watch Shrek anymore
it's just ruined
sounds like a you problem
can't enjoy Shrek anymore
damn
that's so tragic
animators
experimenting with weird styles is good
actually
controversial opinion
I thought they were going to say that stuff was good
they said it was bad that shocked me
I mean
for fuck's sake I'm just trying to watch
Shrek you know
I didn't boot up this
version of Shrek that was drawn by
a bunch of different anim-
I didn't do this to see any weird animation
I just want to enjoy the story
of an ogre getting his swamp back
I just want
the straightforward take
I don't know why I didn't just watch
the original Dreamworks production
but I don't want to be distracted
I saw the part by Ratboy Genius
and didn't even realize
how avant-garde
it truly is
I didn't know he was in that
I don't think
Ratboy Genius did a scene for Shrek Retold
yeah I remember that
it was in 3D
and they were weird fucking animation style
was it the dooluck
going into the castle a bit
I remembered Donkey
I thought it was in the forest
oh wait no
oh maybe they did a few scenes
oh god
yeah you might be right
it's been a while since I've seen this
but I just found someone to upload the clip by himself
what kind of a mind makes this
Ratboy Genius is
a
Hollywood composer
who worked on actual movies
and was a pianist
I think in Gattaca
he physically played a pianist
and he writes music professionally
and is very good at writing music
he has a
storied career and at some point
he just decided
I'm gonna make really just fucking
weird as fuck 3D animations
as a vehicle
for the music and the music is well written
it's just that the animations
accompanying them are fucking
strange as hell
my old roommates
were big Ratboy Genius fans
or some of them were
so I've seen some of it
and I've heard a lot of the
songs which are
I wouldn't call them
catchy but they're
memorable
the voices are the
weirdest part about them
but instrumentally there's some interesting things
going on than a few of what I've heard
even just like the background music
during dialogue scenes
sometimes I'm like oh damn this is interesting
I didn't know
that he was a
movie composer that's really funny
yeah I think
I found it out from
the interviews he did
in his channel
I think it was like there was free of him
this was one of them
I think yeah Ryan Doran is the guy
who
he's got a PhD
forgot about that
well good for him
and like music stuff yeah
how do you get a PhD in music
you do a very good job
I'm assuming you write your thesis on
duh I made
a song that sounds really good this time
dude my name
I am doctor music
these two notes
sound nice together
dude
I read a paper about it
is your PhD thesis
just like a symphony you just write a symphony
how does it work
no it can't be it's gotta be
some theory shit but how much more
how much more music theory is there
even to do
we know all the notes there's eight of them
that's it
we figured it out
there's dope
music or art
never heard of them
I don't believe
all these damn
progressive
freaks in congress
all these damn groomers
trying to complicate things
they don't even know what a note is
notes are a spectrum
sounds is a spectrum actually
I'm not part of the note binary
basic
basic music theory
it's either a doe, a ray, a me, a fa, a so, a la
or to your ado nothing in between
how many notes are there
liberals can't even answer
you get it
do you get my joke
yes I get your joke
yes
sacred music
apparently this is a strange article
a related doctor
sacred music
what's sacred about it
it's got to be like church music
hymns and stuff
I don't know what's there to study
oh my god
okay it's a doctor of sacred music
or the
sacred music doctor
I say in fake latin
how sacred blues
sacred music doctor
wait is this
is Ryan Doran
the rat boy
man?
Ryan Doran is the creator of rat boy genius
hmm
okay well you know what
I'm proud of him
I mean I found his IMDb
oh yeah
what's he in
he was in Gattaca
Trekry told us on IMDb
that's interesting
he's been doing stuff since the 80s
yeah he's been around a while
wait but he's
he was born in
so
doing stuff in movies when he was 11
oh the thing let's see kid songs
what I want to be
1987 so if he was born in 79
he would have been like 8 years old
maybe he was just like a child actor in that
yeah kid songs he played himself
that's funny
kid songs
yeah the bottom
yeah okay
he was uncredited
he played english kid
uncredited
and meanwhile
the star Ryan
bullman
how dare he have the same first name
bullman is not a real star
doran is a star
yeah he was just in a bunch of
like little kid
we can't credit two ryan's
that would be like that would confuse
him
looks like his
his real stuff was started
in like 2007
rap boys kingdom
when was gattica
oh gattica was 1997
yeah he would have been
yeah okay sure
hmm
fast I should get rap boy genius
on the draw cast
yeah you should
uh when we do the free
episode
uh
that would rule
I kind of thought he was
just some weirdo
I mean I guess he
already could also still be
some weirdo yeah that's true
yeah true
he can't get me being weird
I wish I could
I wish I could keep keep
uh anyway
let me let me get uh
uh
how many more voices there's we're most
of the way through uh shit where's the
where's the oh god
where's the tab
I lost track of the tab here we go
um
that one was
uh
that was yeah that was Shrek's
right um okay
the next one is guest what do you
think of Ben saint
that's just a question
oblivion fall
um
what do I think of Ben saint
that's what they want it would be so embarrassing
if I didn't pop on this episode you just have to
talk to a ghost right now but uh I would
when I first started listening to the podcast
I got Ben and Nate confused
um that's really funny
I thought I thought they were
it's funny I thought they were the same person
much like I thought uh mumpkey jones and
munchie were the same person for a couple
weeks at one point hilarious um
I thought that Ben
did the kingdom hearts lecture
and was not due lecture they were done by the same
person that's what I fought in 2017
for like a little while and then I
learned I was mistaken
some people have said we sound kind of
similar I don't hear it at all
but I mean I mean I don't I don't hear it
at all now but at the time
when I was first getting into it because not all the
episodes your icons weren't really
lighting up yeah
so there's a lot
is like like people
say their names at the beginning or whatever but
like you know if I'm just looking over
at my second monitor I don't necessarily see who
was talking so I'd get them confused
um
I don't know that's that's what I think of Ben
saint um I hope that's informative
similar to Nate saint similar to
Nate yeah
it's my it's my most
distinctive feature
uh next one is called
is Davoo's channel dead
and there's no voicemail it's just a
question
Davoo posted like two videos
in like this year I think
yeah it's more active than it's
been in a long time she's posting
I don't actually know what she's doing
she she um I need to watch her new videos
she made a discord
channel or she made a discord
server
moderated it with like weirdly
draconian rules where like
you were only allowed to post like once per
hour
and then left it kept it for like
two months and then decided like hey
I changed my mind I don't want a discord server
I'm deleting it so that's
gone but the channel
is I mean it
you know
I think your last video was like a month ago or something
so it's not dead
yeah it's more active I don't know
maybe maybe it's dead again
who knows
uh next one
is called
shoot shit that samurai
son voicemail was funny
I agree
um
okay the next one is a youtube link
from
cjthexisreal
at gmail.com
I guess this is probably a link to the
this youtube channel which
uh it didn't work
oh yeah it didn't work
oh well
oh wait I copied it wrong
I copied it wrong
here we go this is this is gonna work
for real
okay there is a guy called cjthex
that's cjthex
is a very good video
person I like their videos
oh really okay I don't know
they did a really good
they've done lots of good ones
a recent good one was their video
about inside by Bob Burnham
ah
I don't even remember how he came up
last last time
someone said something about him
voicemail
I don't remember why
this guy is a threatening mustache and teeth
is he like
does he
does he bleach his hair like that
I don't know
what condition clearly
it could be
well good
what condition makes your hair half white
it's kinda
I'm talking out my ass
alright
next one is called
ding dong here you can cancel
all my voicemails didn't
I was in jail
lol at gmail.com
well good news I already did
already didn't play all your voicemails
so if you're wondering why you didn't hear them
because you will never hear them again
fuck you
next one is called happy birthday Ben
thanks
next one is called
oh god why am I talking about
her too now
prince isolation at cause ben said
Trixie should pack it in
.com
okay
fine
these are like zero second
this one is not but all the other ones were
yeah alright
3 2 1 go
hey ben
and hopefully gib and any possible
guest I was just watching
the newest episode of the pcp
and first of all the moment
where Ben just starts saying
about Trixie
he just stops talking about Trixie
and starts saying she's so stupid
she's so stupid
is probably the hardest
that I've laughed at
a podcast or a podcast
why are you laughing it's true
that was hilarious
but it also brought me to a little bit of a question
that just popped into my head
Ben do you genuinely
think that
for Trixie to like quit youtube
and whatever she's doing
and like get a retail job
do you think that that's genuinely
smarter for her to do right now
than to just milk whatever she has left
as long as she can
or do you mean that more in the sense of
if she has any more aspirations
of growing she's just wrong
yeah that's all
bye bye
in terms of dollars and cents
yes I think that at this point
her audience is never coming back
and it would be more
the time spent making
videos now
which get like 4000 views
a piece
more profitably spent
bagging groceries
I think that's just true
that's what I think
okay
thanks for your question
next one is called
it's an image
from Gibb you'll witness Ben's
demise at my baby hands
oh okay
here we go
Samurai baby's revenge
on Ben saint
his little anti
Ben rattle
that's a nice
he looks more like a ninja
but I mean yeah he does
he looks like
he's got a chin
or something have you seen
oh there's a guy
on twitter
I believe he's
autistic or something
he's
he's very
he's hyper focused
on Simpsons
women
drawn in blue ninja
yeah in blue ninja
Simpsons something I doubt
he sent me a DM recently
wait what the fuck
do you know who I'm talking about
oblivion no
that sounds crazy
I can't remember exactly but it's like
they post
I think recently I've seen them post
like them
opening like having a bunch of tabs open
with paused videos
of various characters doing things
and then he plays them one after the other
switches to the next tab so it's like Homer Simpson
yes and then Patrick Starr
reacts to Homer Simpson falling over
and then someone else laughs
someone else does and he just goes it's so
odd yes yes he'll do like
he'll have like a character who's
mean and then he'll be like
okay I cut a scene of someone
else like laughing and saying
like you're an idiot well he doesn't cut
he like he films
using his phone looking at the screen
he moves to the next tab clicks
on it and then play clicks play on the
video so it's like delayed
because he's not that quick
my god this is
like this is like the happiest person
on earth they're just so easy to please
this guy it was not my
account he sent the
pcp account
he just sent me a message
uh on april
he's watching spider-man no way home
that's the tweet
that's the entire tweet
they're just so happy
he sent me he sent the pcp
account a dm that said hello and I said
hi and then he said
do you draw the simpsons
and I said no sorry
and he said you can sign
two petitions
and then oh my god
okay
well here
uh here are the tweets
that he linked me that were the
petitions that he wanted me to sign in lieu of
drawing the simpsons
okay
hello cat
fox broadcasting company
company have the simpsons
in female characters become ninjas
but no sexy
in season 33 or season 34
sign the petition
no sexy
it's not a sexy
but no sexy
just cause they said that
I know what I'm gonna do
they said no sexy though
oh my god
2100 have signed
103 have signed
let's get it to
I saw um
oh wait that's not the goal
I saw someone that I follow on twitter
raven
just made this guy some
drawings of
I think just to be nice
just made some
yellow simpsons people in blue
ninja costumes and I was like what is this
yeah I saw that as well
yeah
and uh
I found this guy and I'm like wow this is a fascinating
Ben Hughes
2642235
we should have
we should have him on the PCP
you know what
I would love to talk to this guy
okay the other genre of posts he makes
is like
it's like a big block of every
female character in the simpsons
looking at some sort of
like
prehistoric
prehistoric insect
simpsons females
stared in amazement at
Arthroplura a giant prehistoric millipede
as well as the largest land invertebrates of all
Arthroplura live to the
carboniferous to the Permian period
they're big as a car and Arthroplura
are herbivores
that image that compilation image
and they're all looking to the right
side of the screen
it's just like I saw this one too
this is a fucking
genre
stared in amazement at sando aqua monster
the largest carnivorous aquatic mammal
that lived in the oceans of Naboo
you're in crash nitro cart racing
with Nash
he likes the simpsons
he likes ninjas
he likes prehistoric
megafauna
oh my god
you're in crash team racing
and it's just a little
a little pasted image
wait wait
are you fucking serious
I'm looking at a different one
I'm looking at a different one of those
wow
it's a different Eeyore
so nice he did it twice
it's a different crash game
Ruth Powers Laura Powers
Allison Taylor two women from Homer
and behind the laughter babysitter
and their friend Eeyore
remembered Uncle Ben's word
they've done multiple of these
with great power
comes great responsibility
I feel
they look so troubled
wait wait the arms
they're holding the photograph
together oh yeah they are
they have two right hands
I feel
I want to believe
I feel like this is
too so comical
it has to be fake
but who has this much time
he's devoted
a lot of time
to whatever this is
it's the same sort of feeling
you would get looking at some other
like profoundly
autistic person
what was the guy who dressed up as Gumby
and did Thomas the Tank Engine
are we talking about the new storyteller
like yeah
I never watched his stuff but
that's the impression
it's just hyper fixated on this
hyper fixated thing
I think it's cool
I think it's like genuinely cool
I think it's pretty funny
like the
you know what you like
and you just do it
yeah
it's funny
it's really funny that
he gets genuine satisfaction
from like
he'll just film
Nelson going ha ha
at Scar from the Lion King
and he'll just be like
yeah
this is great
wait wait
oh my god that image yeah
it's just Lisa playing every video game
I found one of the videos he mentioned
I didn't realize they were recording their screen of a camera
so they're basically
a primitive form of video editing
where if I have videos open
in multiple tabs they'll play a section
then quickly switch tab play another section
and it says if the two videos are interacting
or talking to each other
it reminds me of when I used to like
edit Let's Plays by putting
a video tape into my
VHS player and hitting record
during different parts
of a video game
to record like my PlayStation 1 footage
and like edit like scenes together
for like a YouTube poop slash Let's Play thing
back in like 2005
this is just the advanced version
I'm watching the Spongebob one
yeah
yeah he's just
yeah he's recording
his screen
are you switching back and forth
just getting Sony Vegas
just put the clips together in Sony Vegas
movie maker even
I mean this just makes more sense
your likes the Simpsons
he does look at that smile
smile
this is
I love this one
the Simpsons females react to Will Smith
the voice of Oscar from Sharktail
his greatest role
slaps at Chris Rock the voice of Marty
from Madagascar at the Oscars
dude
the DreamWorks canon
it's real
is this the same
women
image compilation I think it is
it's the same like stock
every female background character
they spent the time
to get all of the images together
and they made their image and then they can be like
ah perfect now
whenever I need to use the image I have it already
now whenever I want to see every female
character in the Simpsons react
to something in a sort of
dismayed manner
well I've done
most of the work already
it's so efficient
yeah he's a well oiled machine
anyway I just
why did I bring this guy up
was Ninjas oh it's cause that samurai
baby looks like one of these ninjas
oh the samurai baby
yeah
that's all I had to say about that
he's Ben Hughes
would be a big fan
maybe I should
tweet it at him and see what he thinks
well it's not from the Simpsons so I don't know
no but he's a blue ninja
surely that must
surely that must count for something
maybe it's the Simpsons thing
I haven't seen them
put any different like non Simpsons
females into a blue
ninja costume
so maybe it's just Simpsons females
yeah
possibly it's sure he only seems to
he only seems interested
if it's the Simpsons
alright
well that's
huh
just one more
okay
Ben
they asked you to draw it
right
he asked me if I draw the Simpsons
you could have just drawn it like that
but they'd be happy
yeah
I guess that
that's enough to do it for him
that's enough
you know what
I think I could do this
no I think I could
I can't I have to
I can't let it tear me away from my
holy duty of finishing the Tales Get Strolled
page
is there like an episode that has
like I don't know
Lisa and Marge like sneaking around
doing something
in ninja outfits
hmm
is there a scene that has like
sparked this in this game
like was there a scene where
someone wore this outfit
possibly
I feel like definitely
Barth has worn like
a ninja costume
to sneak around
I think in the episode where he like
soars the head off of Jebediah Springfield
statue
yeah
although that was a black ninja costume
yeah it was different
I just googled it
yeah he wore a black
wait a minute
Simpsons
okay wait I found something
uh
okay no this is him
it was under an official the Simpsons
twitter account tweet
with some Simpsons characters
in blue ninja outfits
by the way
the Simpsons I have these images
and I hope in season 32
or season 33
uh
some episode where Marge, Lisa, Maggie
and other female Springfielders
characters become ninjas
and then oh my god
someone replies to him
shut up
and he says to that person
watch your language
oh wait okay we've got a whole thread here
oh my god
we've got a whole thread this is actually
I gotta
this actually just keeps going
someone asks him like what's with the ninjas
and he says
for someone to do
honestly though what is with the fucking ninjas
and he says for someone to do drawing
request of the Simpsons female characters
in ninja outfits
dress in blue their face covered by mask
belt swords bow staffs
nunchucks and their ninja skills for me
for what reason
because Bart Simpson is the only character
who wear a ninja suit so let these female
characters wear a ninja suit
based
equality but what if they don't need
to then Hughes replies
very well I don't have
to argue he then replies to himself
alright
uh what the
someone else replied
to
he doesn't reply to himself the guy says
it's just mad and then he says alright
oh yeah I didn't see that one but you're
Ryan
okay okay
Samori says quite an agreeable fellow
he is agreeable Samori says
can't wait to watch tomorrow's episode
to which he replies me too
wow
you know I'm feeling inspired
I'm feeling inspired
by this handsome
man
hold on
this won't take me a second in fact I
bet I can do this in like
just a few seconds
hmm
we'll see about that
there we go
you know I'll give him this one for free
I'll give him this one for free
wait
oh can I see
yes in a moment
Photoshop will behave for
just a second here
I'm on the edge of my seat
The Simpsons Female Stared in Amazement
at
fucking discord is being slow
The Simpsons Female Stared in Amazement
has saw a good man
there we go
why would you do this
hahaha
I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm gonna DM
I'm gonna DM them
The Simpsons Female Stared in Amazement
that looked like Bob Odenkirk
hahaha
oh what their DMs are close
I wanted to send this to them and really
I mean I'm sure they would get
a lot of hate
6000 followers dude they got some fans
hey
have you seen something on Twitter
called
Tinder Skitty
I've
I've seen glimpses
and glances I haven't actually read
any of the comics because it's like
yeah it's nice I'm sure it's
like a lovey-dovey couple
and one of them is a fucking whale lord
and the other one is a skitty
and everybody knows that
his dick is so big that
she would be fucking destroyed
but it's a wholesome comic so
there's no sex haha
and I'm not
it's not too interesting
I get annoyed every time I see one
oh god he did another one
really he's got so many fans
really he's keeping up this facade
this charade even
yeah it's I think it's
people like the
the idea of
thinking about how big his dick is
compared to her
but they don't go there
and so it's like fine to
repost to retweet
I don't know if it's
do you think that's it
I think there's an element of that
is it about his dick
he's so big
and she's so small
his whole body is big
it's not just his giant dick
it's not literally all that
because the art's nice
and I'm sure it's cute and wholesome
or whatever
I'm sure there's a few people who are like oh my god
well sure
if there was porn of this
I mean size difference is probably
what some people are into I guess
but like that's not this guy's
that's not this guy's fault
it's fine it's fine and whatever
it's not a fault I just see it
and I just think it's cynical
I've grown my eyes and I think
yeah I think the whole
I don't know
what if I made a pokemon
but I made one a sexy girl
and I made a cute little
cute little romance
I just like
the beginning
there should be a scene where one of them
just gets caught with a master ball
and there's just a human walks off with them
forever
some human
no a human caught my boyfriend
no he's teaching him how to use
self destruct
no
oh no he made
my waylord boyfriend his h.m. slave
no
oh it's kinda hot though
yeah
yes that's definitely should be where it goes
that's you know what at least that'd be
something at least that'd be something
uh yeah I don't know
it annoys me
and I hate it
but not for any reason that I can
articulate
I feel indifferent to it
generally it's just like
I can see why it's big and popular
people like pokemon people like
cute girls
like there's nothing
of value here for me I don't
see why
I have to keep seeing it
I'm gonna kill him
I'm gonna find him in real life
and destroy his body and mind
you're gonna bring your pokemon
and you're gonna challenge him
to a pokemon battle and he's gonna have
they're gonna be sent out and you're gonna kill them
like in a nuzlocke
you're gonna send out russell
back from the dead it's now a ghost pokemon
you call him again
he actually always was a ghost pokemon
actually
oh yeah
wait was he
I thought he was like a different pokemon
no he was a ghastly
and in one of the nuzlocke's and then
okay
nah nah he was a ghastly
um
okay whatever I have to
okay whatever I don't wanna look at this anymore
um next one is called
uh slime times
updates number
which the number is at
okay
me
me and ee or
is that him?
yeah yeah that tracks
this just looks like a guy
he's just a guy
he's got a youtuber face
a little bit yeah a little bit
he looks
he looks more normal
than I expected honestly
yeah that's what I was
found strange to
hmm
we've been conditioned to think that strange people
have to look strange
no
how wrong of us
absolutely we've all learned a valuable lesson
here today
don't you know the lesson is
don't judge a person's cover
by
what their personality is like
uh okay
next one is called
slime times we can update number 6
uh 3 2 1 go
hello rowdy freakers
and carp murderers
welcome back to the slime times
weekend update
this time I'm pleased to recount some festive activities
most of the rowdies
love themselves to live in the sewers
and take a break from gameplay
have revived
and resumed their gang violence
in some capacity
rowdy mischief in particular has been
on an outstanding grind set
furthermore as I record this
last night was the anniversary of the
famed rowdy brick night
where rowdies collected thousands of bricks
and used them to assault killer apartments
a special extra art contest
has been started in celebration of our
100 obelisk's fourth birthday
rowdy old hat matt is leading the charge
will apparently be bone hurt
beamed if endless war does not
appreciate the offerings
finally it seems stay that
ghosts have finally gotten their hands on the
technology or the grim magics
to have their own pets accompanying them
mega slime oids
the dark reflections
of the green slime oids of the living
in celebration of this
stay that warbredon invited
all flesh bags to the arena
to fight his new 12 foot
mega slime oid named warforge
both wins and losses
were had for the living
but the real loss was for that guy
you know
that guy who told us not to send in pcp
voicemails and then embarrassed his way into jail
by sending too many
how embarrassing
thank you somebody
uh
i didn't realize mega slime
i kind of thought mega slime oids were already a
ffff
and you could fight them in the wild
maybe that's what i was thinking of
i didn't realize you could not have them
before but uh it's good
that's a good inclusion that makes me happy
best game
ever made
there's more
there's another one slime times weekend update
here we go
three two one go
by the way
dear unsuspecting listener
did you know you could become
based by joining endless war today
it's true it is a free to play
text based mmorpg
playable entirely inside a discord server
not even any pay to
win mechanics or gotcha
skinner boxes though i'm sure what
remains of the shields at slimecorp
are working on such things as we speak
maybe ben could leave the server link
in the description of this episode
but just in case i'm going to just
read the invite link aloud
https
colon forward slash
forward slash discord
dot gg forward slash
lowercase m lowercase t
uppercase s uppercase
r uppercase x
lowercase e lowercase
k come hang out
have some slime kill some
people and don't tell me you
don't have the time because let's be
honest you're watching the pcp
that's it for this week
remember the slime time is the
best time we'll put the link
in the description
uh
video games
slime
multi-user dungeons and played
endless war of the game in a very
long time
same i i guess i never
only like once or twice did i actually
like
get on the grind on an alt and try to
actually like play the game
it was when yeah i was um
i was uh
i was the humble juve
and i tried i joined the
killers and i tried to
uh take out terse worthy
but terse worthy got his
ass and uh it was
tragic
i remember when uh the
gankers and shamblers were coming around
and there was a new thing
you could do as a shambler
where you're not like dead you're a
zombie and you can shamble
and destroy like the
functionality of certain districts and
buildings so that people couldn't play
the game anymore and that was funny
so i was i was part i was
i was a big shambler i was shambling
everywhere trying to ruin endless war
so nobody could have fun
yeah that uh
was like a problem that like
continued for a long time i would go to
um i would go to the cafes
to try and i wasn't
really playing the game but i was going to the
cafes to uh create uh
zines like in the in-game zines
of uh slime and punishment
and i would always go to the cafe and like
the cafe would be shambled and so like i
couldn't do it it's like some fuck some
idiot like shambled
the cafe and now it's in ruins and i
yeah and i don't know how to fix it
but uh
i think there was a whole
thing with that it was sort of tied into the
bicarbonate reign like dr downpour
was responsible for the shambling
and that was kind of a i think we were talking
about it in the last contest
i think we i think we were doing a
villains contest was the next yeah
we're gonna judge it in like a week or two
and we did the we're gonna do the villains
contest and dr downpour was one it's like everyone
was like whatever happened to dr downpour
he never got like a resolution
story uh but he was a
minor character for a while
uh i guess i guess
that like uh
now that phantom's revenge
has shown the end of of the
reign and everything
the dr downpour i guess that is that
it's probably in some sort of
different dimension what dimension
is the
endless war in that we could play right now
in our discord browser yeah yeah it's in c197
and that's
where phantom's revenge takes
place yeah yeah
so phantom horn comes from a different
dimension into this one yes
yeah phantom horn came from
a beta timeline and moved
in the alpha timeline
the uh nlaka calm
was deslimed and basically destroyed
and so they brought the beta
nlaka calm
which was not deslimed
to the alpha timeline
and just like landed it on
top of the deslime version
and just were like okay
we're good now
uh yeah but it's
it's from a different timeline but it's in
c197 alpha
so like everyone got genocided
and then replaced with a different timeline
yeah all timeline versions just came
and replaced all the all the fucked up ones
which is
just uh i think in my
in my mind there there
was an opportunity and i don't know if
anything will ever be done with it but i feel like there is
an opportunity there for like
the ruins of a deslimed
nlaka calm are like
crushed underneath the city
now that's that's canon
so i mean you
could maybe venture down there and find
some shit
who knows what
i mean um
chris chan sonichu and the like
merged cop killer uwupiti
virginia monster
we're both crushed down there too
so i don't know
maybe some weird shits going on
i don't know i'm just i'm just asking
questions
next voicemail
we're only got two left by the way we're almost done
uh oh
next one is called sponsored by sony
three two one go
four words
twilight sparkle boys
grail
see it wasn't that hard
there's your playstation 5
no thanks no buy
zoomers
twilight sparkle doesn't like zoomers
twilight sparkle let's be honest twilight sparkle
is a millennial
who loves jk rallying
oh no it's true
she thinks they have ak yearling
in the show don't they
isn't she a fan
yes
sad darryl do
darryl do comes out as like
an anti
they didn't have any sort of trans
allegory in there did they
not that i can remember
a twilight sparkle
transitioned into an alicorn
that's true
twilight sparkle yeah she is
i think she kind of is like one of those
you know one of those white ladies that make
tiktoks about how shitty zoomers are
you know what i mean
i yes
engaging in generational
smack talking like a fucking
weirdo and yet there's a whole genre
of person that thinks it's
cool
why would you shit on the youth
weren't you
once a youth the youth
the youth sometimes shit on us
but i mean that doesn't mean that it's a good look
yeah but that's because they haven't done it yet
right it doesn't mean it's it looks
cool to be like no the children
are stupid actually
we grownups are smarter
so die
die child
that's what i'm gonna say when the samurai
comes for me when rosanne
ralph shows up at my door
step in his blue ninja costume
okay i think
last voicemail
it is called
twilight sparkle
is depressed
three two one go
previously on the twilight sparkle
show
maybe this is just a hippie bleeding heart artist in me
from here on out call me liquid
saberspark
and now
for today's episode
it's been hard
they don't like empty voicemails
so i started adding them to art
it was too weak
so i became a ninja cyborg pony
but even then so many high concepts
so many funny characters wasted completely
on deaf ears
i don't know if i can make it to the voice grail
your ways you have lost
better when young don't be too smart
or better understand your medium properly
it's yatsu
not like an audio drama do what appeals to you
and don't chase the success
chase your own satisfaction cat being shot
by a minigun was pretty fun
you've been saying to be drunk
thank you yatsu krosha from hit youtube
show zero punctuation
i feel a lot better now
no big deal so what will you do now
oh big deal
i think i have an idea
oh shit
pig sounds to be continued
oh no pig sounds
well that's not the ending
i was hoping for
that's bad ending
they'll never recruit me
i'll never reprise my role
oblivion falls in a backslide
in a backslide into his old ways
i'm clean
you better be
you have to avoid images of pigs
i'm in rehab
i think it was major of light
in my discord
he thought that i'd like hated pigs
he thought that it was
like i specifically disliked pigs
i was like no i
didn't like being jump scared by the scary
squealing sounds of an angry
sow
no that was just
i wonder if i should
upload the video of me
in a forays reacting to you
listening to that
cause we were fucking losing our shit
i'd watch it
i just opened up obs
and were like let's listen to this episode
let's see how ben sane handled this
and we were just laughing
i'll probably put that on
listed and link it somewhere
i'd like to see it
yeah
maybe in a week or so i'll quickly
cut it together
let me know
if you're gonna stream
pump
i will
i messaged kai
i said do we have anything going on friday
he's like not really
so yeah
i should be streaming
around the time or shortly after
this episode of the pcp areas
that's where i'm gonna aim to do it
and then i'll play
pump and i'll play slime and punishment
i'll do both
fandoms revenge
back to back one stream
you made your choice
you can only play one
i don't know how long
pumpkin alley is
it took me about two hours
but i got really stuck trying to find
the last couple of
you might beat it in an hour
if you're like lucky
i'm gonna look for the lizards
i've heard talk of lizards
but i've seen nothing
it'll take a while to find those
playing the game
literally doesn't take very long
but finding everything
takes maybe an hour
an hour and a bit
you could get stuck looking for those lizards
you could get stuck
i still haven't found four
i've seen those spoilers
so i'm excited
i wanna see your stream
and maybe will you be doing that
now when this episode is going live
is that the plan
it's currently the plan
i'll have to make sure this comes out
i'll probably wait an hour or two
after the episode
so that way people have time to get to the part of the episode
where i announce that
make sense
i'll have to make sure this episode comes out
2pm on the dot on friday
yeah yeah
gotta be punctual
i also really gotta go back
and upload those podcasts
on those podcast apps
i still haven't put the time in
to figure out how they work
even though tom explained it to me
but i just haven't gone through it
and figured it out
busy busy busy
gotta draw tails get strolled
gotta make my stupid book
gotta do a podcast
but at least
i have you two
to help me through the hard times
oh no
okay i guess
i guess we're done i guess that's the end of the episode
yeah
that's the end
remember to go watch my stream
which will be happening all the time constantly
the elden ring
on gib and take
watch oblivion fall play pumpkin alley
and maybe phantom's revenge
watch your back
and go to markiplier.com
and buy some of that elden
bling
let's just
why does markiplier have all the elden bling
you know
cause he's so adorable
twilight sparkle would be a fan
cause he's such an adorable gamer
zaddy
he's got that cloak brand
where they badly photoshop people
into elden ring t-shirts
oh they don't have it up anymore
i was laughing at it in spork server a few weeks ago
no more tangents from me
it's
i got a pee
could you just make her face orange
or is there a pumpkin hat
i don't know if there's a pumpkin hat
actually no i think somebody did tell me
there is a pumpkin helmet
i don't know where to get it
but
my throat's fucked
your voice sounds like
that fucking ai touch to speak
speech thing right now
it's got that raspy quality
i can't talk
on a podcast i get destroyed
understood
i made her give an orange skin
and then i got a tattoo
i wanted to have the eye
like the indents
like lines going down her face
but i can only have
like one i can have a scar on one
side of her face so she's got
kind of a scar
and she's got like
you can customize the whites
and the pupil color of her eyes
her eyes are completely yellow
i'd like to customize
the whites out of this damn country
back where they came from
back to hell where you belong
blaggards
uh
so yeah
she doesn't look that great but like
whatever
that's okay
as long as it's
orange skin like pumpkin
as long as she's killing people
black
blaggards
yeah blaggards it's spelled
black guard but it's pronounced
is it the word that this woman said
in this short video
but let's see
i thought you said that for a second
and you fight
he says
return to the depths
from once you came blaggard
he calls you a blaggard
it hurts my feelings
it's racist
no
he's referring the black in black guard
refers to your soul
not your skin
anyone
any race can be a blaggard
if they're really bad
suck
you just gotta suck hard enough
okay
well gib said BRB
oh
we can't say goodbye
we gotta wait
we gotta wait until she's back
before we can end the episode
left too early
that's crazy
nice
today
uh yeah i
some work done during this recording
i think i've got the end slate sorted
it took me a while to figure out how i wanted it to look
but i
figured out
are we
done? gotta draw my stupid
i got four sketches
i think i got four or five sketches of the
see what tells me control page done last night
i think there's 18 panels
did you end the episode?
no we were waiting for you to get back
now we can end the episode
okay bye
goodbye