Hello and welcome to this week's episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm the best
guy ever and I'm here with Jesse Wood. I am the punisher, I'm not me anymore. I knew
identity as the punisher. You're a punisher of ears and eyes, Hippocrit. Go on, Gibb. Are
you calling me ugly and also has a dumb voice? Yeah, that's correct. Gibb. I'm Hippocrit.
I'm going to put in twice as much effort today. You're going to be the first villain
I fucking punish. Good. And we're happy to have back with us. Perhaps the most qualified
of us, given his channel RebelPixels on this particular topic, Tommy Oliver. Because Gibbin's
putting in twice as much effort, I'm only going to put in half to balance it out. That
math checks out. That math checks out. Okay. So yeah, today's topic is effort. Putting
in effort, working hard at shit. Wait a minute, are you implying that I'm four times as worse
as you? He's, wait. That's the math. No, it's wrong. To balance it out. All right, before
we get into that, I want to say that the inspiration for this. I'm offended, I'm so angry. We watched
this video of this guy. I don't know how old he is. I think he's a high schooler. And
he has, in the video, it's him with all these Game Boy SPs lined up in a row. Game Boy Advance
SPs. And he's been grinding out, trying to catch a shiny ponytail. I think like in a
live stream for around six months, I think it took him. And in the video, he finally gets
it and he flips his shit. He goes absolutely ballistic. And it seems like perhaps the greatest
one is light. And he becomes the punisher. Yeah, his response. And so, but the thing
about it is, the thing about it is the comments are absolutely flooded with people saying
like, wow, what a fucking loser. What a piece of shit. This is how you spend your time.
This is what you want to do. And so just as a result of seeing these comments, we felt
inspired to comment on this phenomenon. So I'll just say right now that this man, doing
what he did, this man set himself a goal, right? He arranged everything he needed to
do. He got it. He got it going. He started the engine and he grinded it out every single
day doing this. And this isn't like, this isn't like doing something new all the time.
He did the same thing over and over again to achieve this very specific goal of catching
a shiny ponytail. And he fucking did it. He accomplished his goal. And these commenters,
man, these commenters have, I mean, admittedly, obviously they've never achieved anything
hard in their entire lives and never worked for something. They've never reached a pinnacle
of experience as a result of months and months of work on something. But if they had, they
would know that it's not about the value, the objective value, whatever the fuck that
means or whatever goal you're trying to reach. It's about personal satisfaction. And this
guy achieved the goal he was trying to reach. And he, as a result, was the happiest man
in the world for, you know, however long that lasted. And fuck everyone who doesn't disagree.
You people are just jealous that you don't have a shiny ponytail. Go fucking kill yourselves,
you pieces of shit. And that's what I have to say about it.
Yeah, he was, he was a role model.
Well, you know what? I have a shiny Mew and I got it for free at a Nintendo event. So
fuck that kid.
Cause I'm better at the game than him and I didn't have to put in any effort at all.
I bet you were just as excited when you got that as when he got his shiny ponytail.
I was and still am. I still have my shiny Mew.
In fact, it was better that way because you, you were just so happy. You didn't have to
put in all the time like this guy did.
Exactly. The true, the true joys in this life are the things you didn't have to work
for.
As Ben would say, the only way to win is not to play.
As Ben would say, the only way to win is to take you on Dutch Ones.
It is a good idea.
So what's that give? Sorry.
The whole point of the putting in effort for something that's completely pointless for
the rest of like, like compared to everyone else and everything else in your life. If
it's pointless, but you still like it, is it worth doing all that stuff?
And I would say for that, for that Pokemon thing, I mean, you didn't seem very old.
So he didn't, he probably didn't have a lot of responsibility.
So I would say probably like 16 or 17 or something.
I would say that was a good idea because he can say, I got it.
Look at how cool.
I mean, honestly, how many other people his age are willing to dedicate that amount of
time to something, you know?
And I know he was like streaming.
So he's got like a community going on.
Obviously he's probably pretty into Pokemon in general.
But like, it's just impressive no matter what they want to do.
Like the guy who wanted to like eat a freight train and like did it.
It took him like 20 years or something and he's like digested every piece of it.
I don't know if that's real, but something like that.
It's like, wow, why would you do that?
That's probably actually causing you physical harm.
But he had a goal.
And I mean, all right, this is really what it comes down to for me.
Our lives are completely meaningless.
Nothing has any point whatsoever.
So everything we do is an arbitrary, you know, it's all arbitrary.
Any goal you set for yourself.
If you want to, if you, let's, like the people who are going to be like, lol, he just spends
every night playing Pokemon, why don't you go get laid, bro?
Why don't you go smash some puss dog, homie, my nigga.
You know, they talk like this because I'm a racist.
You know, that's a very offensive impression of me.
Yeah.
It's, what, what are they getting out of that?
You know?
God, it makes me so, I want to strangle every person who fucking says this shit because
this guy just decided he was going to do something and he followed through with it.
And you know what?
You know what?
That ability to follow through on something is much more of a valuable skill than any arbitrary
ass thing you decide to set it to.
If you can achieve something that's like takes months to do, you can do anything you want.
This gets a better person than any fucking commenter.
Exactly.
And that leads right into why I don't respect commenters and why I want to tell them personally
for the 100th time how much they sicken me and I want them all to commit suicide.
That would be ideal.
I fucking, leaving a YouTube comment takes no effort and that's why they're all cancer.
Yeah, really, that's the, that's the, that's like the secondary point here.
How much it is great to do things that take effort, but how little, if not a negative
impact you have on the world by doing things that take no effort.
I think Jabroni can sit down on the computer and you know, watching your video through
a glass-eyed fog of retardation and fucking slam their ape-like fists onto the keyboard
and, and hash out some ignorance, spew it in your direction.
Any monkey could do that.
In fact, I, I believe that most of them are monkeys or at least monkey-like, simian people.
Some kind of mutant hybrid created in, in the island of Dr. Giro or whatever the fuck
the animal guy was called.
Dr. Giro, a different guy.
Dr. Seuss.
Dr. Seuss, yes.
But, but if you fucking, if you watch a video on the internet and you disagree with it,
or even if you do agree with it, if you want to say anything at all pertaining to anything,
put in the effort, write something down, memorize something, fucking learn how to speak in public
or fucking turn out a camera and learn to dress nice, fucking comb your hair, stop being
a fat slob, all of you people, you're dumb and I don't like you and I don't like you
Tom, what do you make of all this?
I mean, I think, like you said, it's, it's that, you know, there is no purpose in life.
People ask, like, what's the purpose of living or like, why do we exist or whatever?
And like, the really liberating thing is that there is no point.
Like we're all just like some genetic accident and we're just happened to be here.
We're all going to die.
We're all going to rot.
So that means that the point of life is whatever you want it to be.
Well, except Jesse, obviously, but for the rest of us, yeah.
Right.
It's kind of why I'm like very jealous of obsessively, like heavily autistic obsessive
people who have like a big thing that they really love and they do it all the time and
makes them super happy, you know, even though they won't be able to get a job or anything.
It's, they're having fun.
I'm legitimately jealous.
My mother was a special ed teacher and so I met a fair amount of these people, but I'm
pretty jealous of just, you know, fairly retarded people because I mean, I'm not, I'm not trying
to shit on anybody.
I'm just saying that like, if what is important to you in life is, you know, getting your
mac and cheese for dinner every day and you get it and you're over the fucking moon because
you got it while you're watching, you know, whatever shows you like to watch on TV.
And that's, that's the limit of, of what your understanding of happiness is and you're
at a hundred every night because you get it.
That's, that's literally the ideal way to live.
So we should all be retarded is what you're saying.
Yeah.
We really should be retarded.
The only reason I'm at all interested in, in, excuse me, having any higher level of
intelligence than, than, uh, putting so much effort into, that's my effort right there.
The only reason I'm at all interested in putting any higher level of, of thought into any of
this is in the vain hope that perhaps humanity will one day rise above our, our bestial place
in the universe right now, maybe we'll become, you know, God's made of pure energy and our
existence will have some impact.
But frankly, like the universe.
If I'm going to become a God made of pure energy, I'm still, I'm still going to have
a stamp collection if I'm a God made of pure energy because I'm going to get bored otherwise.
If that, if you rule the universe, I mean, yeah, if that happens, it's going to happen
like millions of years after we're dead.
Right.
And personally, I believe that if I'm going to die, then I want humanity to go extinct
right after.
I don't want humanity to achieve without me.
I don't want them to continue because you're taking the, the cuja from Final Fantasy nine
route.
Yeah, exactly.
That's the best route.
He didn't have the right fashion ideas, but you know, his whole nihilism, his belief structure,
his desire to end all life.
You know, I can respect that.
He is not deserving of continuing without me.
You know, that's why Kuj is a great villain because, you know, he just, it's a totally
understandable thing that he did.
He thought he was going to live forever.
But then when he found out he wasn't, he's like, oh, shit, this changes everything.
And as a result, he's like, well, if I'm going to die, so does everything else need
to.
Yeah.
You know, Final Fantasy nine is, you know, can this be a Final Fantasy podcast?
Absolutely.
Whatever the crappy fucking topicals.
Kuj was willing to put in the work to blow up everything.
That's a guy you can respect, you know.
He went straight from zero to a hundred like that.
And that's, that's the kind of guy I want to destroy my world.
Hmm.
But you know, I mean.
You could destroy my box.
Yeah.
That's what I want.
We can, we all know this stuff.
We have something of a basis to talk about this from, because we're all creators and
we all do make shit that, you know, could mayor, that we throw into the void to hopefully
be valued, but easily could not be, despite putting tons of effort into it.
Right now, as I've talked about many times, working on a video, I've been working on four
months and months and months and just, just today in fact, and yesterday, I found two videos
that have come out.
Okay.
I wrote this video, but it's about Undertale spoilers.
The game that shall not be named.
I wrote it back in October, right, like a month after the game came out and it was ready.
I just needed to edit it.
Shit comes up and I'm still working, been working on it the whole time.
And in the meantime, I have seen not one, but two videos that cover all the exact same
points, rendering intellectually rendering my effort completely useless.
There's no intellectual benefit.
I could just, you know, make a video that points to these and that would be just as
valuable to the collective consciousness as the thing that I'm currently working on.
Maybe my production values are better, but it doesn't matter.
But the point is, I'm not going to stop because, well, I guess it's, it's because I care about
myself and making the thing I'm making more than I do about the intellectual content of
it, I guess.
So actually maybe I'm doing the wrong thing.
Maybe I should just stop and kill myself.
Never mind.
No.
You should make it.
Well, that's the whole thing.
Is that like you can't, you can't care.
It gets like the trap of YouTube and the internet and like this whole connected culture in general
is that like because everything can be like quantified and measured and like reach can
be like easily keeping track of now and like popularity and things like that, you know,
it's so easy to like get downtrodden and get distracted by the fact that like you have
X amount of reach when you want Y amount of reach.
Yeah.
And that's really annoying, especially I think it's gotten even worse kind of now that
we have Patreon because now like not only do you get like popularity measurement, you
have like monetary measurements as well.
That's true.
It's like everything about like someone's creativity now can be quantified in like real
world terms that like matter.
And so all of a sudden the thing you're doing for passion now has a lot of real world implications.
And if you want to chase that obviously, because like this is the thing you enjoy is what you
want to do with your life, but now it becomes a job and it becomes a competition because
you know, it's like a free market.
So you have to like make yourself marketable and you have to do all that shit.
And so all of a sudden you're kind of passions being poisoned by like the rest of life.
Yeah, totally.
So it's like you have to kind of disconnect yourself from that, which is super difficult
because like you want to keep consuming more content because there's so much at your fingertips
that you can like be inspired by and things like that.
But at the same time, it's almost like disheartening to see someone do something so much better
or have so much more success, especially when they're worse than you and they have more
success and you don't understand like what the secret sauce is there.
Both of these videos that cover what I have covered.
Each one, one has 115,000 views.
The other has 250,000 views.
I'm just curious to see how much mine will climb to when I finish it.
Man, I gotta, yeah, I gotta talk about that because that's a topic that's near and dear
to my heart.
It's more successful channels than you that are also way crappier than you who then release
a crappier version of a video that you were planning to make or that you have made.
Oh, and you've seen tons of that, especially in the pony days.
Oh yeah.
Anthony C. has been ripping me off for his entire fucking career and I'll go ahead and
say that on record right now.
Everything he's ever said in his videos is a crappier version of something I said in
my videos.
There you go.
But also, you know, lacking the self-awareness and the comedic timing and the intellectualism
and the wit.
Mm-hmm.
Right.
But I digress.
Uh, what the fuck was I saying?
I don't remember.
Well, if you're talking about shittier people making more popular things.
Okay, yeah.
Forget Anthony C. I was gonna bring this around to a guy that I really hate, which is a YouTuber
by the name of Nerdwriter, but I'm pretty sure we all hate.
I just found out who Nerdwriter was like two days ago because you kept bitching about him
on Twitter and I had to look him up.
I don't think I'd say I hate him, but there are some major grievances that I'm sure you'll
go into.
Yeah.
He's my favorite.
Uh, I didn't see it.
Donnie, get out of here.
Donnie possessed Gibbon.
That wasn't really him.
He's like a evil spirit that consumes this all.
Yeah.
So, one of my favorite cartoons of all time is Hey Arnold.
And I've been wanting to make a video about it forever.
And where'd everyone go?
Is this the-
We're here.
Did I break it up?
No, we're all single quiet.
Be quiet.
Waiting with aided breath for your words of farting and making noises. Anyways, my point is
Putting in the effort
No, I wrote a hey Arnold video like fucking months ago like five months. Yes shit and I saw in nerd writers comments
Some some fucking Jbrown in his comments was like hey nerd writer since you're the smartest fucking the best
guy of all time on
YouTube you should make a video about hey Arnold and he just responded to it and like okay
I will and and the fucking the clouds parted
Millions of thumbs up and people are losing their fucking minds. Yes nerd writer is finally gonna show the world about hey
Arnold, that's my fucking job
I'll do it better. I'll do it better than you can and he's gonna come out with some asinine shitty
Modeling manipulative fucking video about
If you look into it from the right perspective, you'll see that hey Arnold is about us
He's gonna ruin he's gonna ruin hey Arnold for all time is gonna ruin it for me
He's gonna try to take it from me just like everyone ever from of all time is stolen every idea
I've ever had and I've gotten no credit for it. Yeah, it's like that's the whole point right like we're talking about like putting
In the effort and stuff like and now we're just shitting on nerd writer
But like it does objectively massive amounts of work on most of his videos. He really does put in the
What are we talking about right now? I supposed to be talking about
I was gonna talk about
He's putting in the effort on hating nerd writer. We'll put yeah, that's true
Yeah, I am putting in the work for that. I think it's got a real point though
I was gonna say about the way my channel has been
Like I've I've thought about the way I make videos because my last video a few days ago the puzzle pirates thing
Hmm
Nobody is putting in effort for like making your channel big and grow and get all the stuff and doing doing the things
Nobody cares or knows about puzzle pirates and I've got like a few videos planned that I like very specifically for me
Like nobody would really get them unless they were very like like very similar
upbringings and stuff
So I'm not really like going
Putting in the effort to make it like a like a youtuber if you know what I mean
Yeah, it's just I just like and it's helping me like like if you were a youtuber
You'd be doing a review of the division right now or something like that or undertale
Yeah, I would be doing something that would get me views and I just it's not really making me
Motivate because I for a long time
I was thinking I got to do ratchet and clank 2 next because I want to talk about that and and the first one and people
Asking for it, and I just couldn't think of anything at the time
So yeah, yeah, it's it's it's better for me to just think of my channel as a hobby for the moment
And then I'll put in the effort
In into making it cool for me and then later it will it's not like it's just I'm just saying like you can put in effort to
To you can lack effort and it could still be good because if I was trying really hard to make videos to get big
I would not be making anything because I'd be like right because there's this there's definitely a
sense of like
Paralysis when you're when you're like oh god like eight you can say it on h3h you three's vlogs lately
They're like man like like h3h 3h 3h 3 has just reached like a million subscribers not long ago
And like now they've got their other channel because they're like too scared to make anything to put on their main channel because they're afraid
It won't be good enough. Yeah, it's like, you know, it's it's like that
Yeah
But do you think it's a serious problem and that's why I put in the effort to have multiple channels
because
The fact that I have a channel like my Japanese anime is or a channel like the blue glow or man child think you know
Those channels all have strong gimmicks and strong themes. Yeah, and a strong kind of content
Which frees up my main channel and the stress and allows me on that channel to just not give a fuck at all and post
Whatever inane insane crap that I want
That's true, you know, I was just talking to a to a to a guy
I know about how the interesting thing about your your channel set up your your multiple channel set up is that
Your the fact that you've got multiple channels with different identities is is part of the narrative basically
Yeah, and but it's just that that narrative isn't really the one most suited to succeeding on YouTube. Oh, yeah, and it's yeah, you know
Someone just messaged me
I never mind just you just make your own website. That's that guy with the glasses, but just I was gonna do that
I was different. That's smart. Yeah, I was I was I was going to
When Johnny with the channels
Yeah
Yeah, when Johnny old school decided that he wasn't gonna be Johnny old school anymore
He said I'll just give you my site and you can change it to your site
Oh blue, but it was like I would have had to buy a domain name
I would have had to yeah put an effort to make the fucking thing to make the website
So you got to put in the effort
I don't want
Smart you got to play smart not hard. Here's a question about effort. Do you think that effort is
Affected by passion because I would say absolutely
because
Any any video that I'm making
For the purpose of like well, I got to make this video
It's never gonna get fucking made. Yeah, but when I get distracted by some other totally stupid idea
Those videos like 90% of my videos that I've actually made are videos that are like distractions that I did to get away from an actual video
Yeah, that is the entirety of my give-and-take channel, right?
I was gonna say bring it back to what you were just saying is that like you're not some of you're putting an effort
You're not putting an effort you are it's just you're putting effort into things like
You can go with like passion or marketing, you know, like yeah, like the two kind of extremes
I can be like whore yourself out and talk about what people want to hear or you can put an effort to like be very authentic
And I don't know about you guys
I've said this many times before but I
Greatly respect anyone who would even put in the work required to run a YouTube channel
Even if you make shit at least you're doing something, you know, and and that's I mean at the very least that's better than your average commenter
Even if they're you know terrible videos at least this guy's show got something to show for and and creative people when they do that when they get
Distracted with other like, you know sillier or more personal projects in between the actual work
You'll trick yourself into thinking that you're doing a shitty job or not doing enough work
When really you're doing a shitload of work and you're making great shit
It's just not what you think you should be doing so you don't count it for yourself in your head and you make yourself
Like yeah, the last three videos that I posted were all like asinine crap
That just like came to me like that and I like made like you know ten minutes or whatever
I'm fucking crows video or the file which video or the and they all ruled incident everybody fucking loves those videos
They all have like massive thumbs up. Yeah, everybody's like yes, you're making good content again
And it's like well, I wanted to be making shitty content, but that's a lot of work
So I guess I'll have to settle for making good videos
Yeah, it's it's it's tough to when you're an artistic person
It's you get into a habit of second-guessing yourself
Well, like a lot of a lot of it is like the stuff that I value was often vastly different from what my audience values, of course
Of course
And that's kind of the problem when you I value like a two-hour video of me
Fucking around my room in corpse paint talking about raping children eating
That's and that's going to go I'm looking forward to it
You know the I think we've mentioned him on the show before but the new storyteller
You know that guy who dresses up as Gumby and read stories when I was thinking of he's he's the cool
He makes like videos
Like they're they're borderline on watchable
But they're so charming because he's I think he's like got a mental problem
And he lives with his mother and he plays with Thomas the Tank Engine toys and reads stories allowed
But like really far from the camera, so you can't hear what he's saying and they're like hours long and he's like hundreds of videos
Something like three a day and each hour long like that's the average putting in the effort and it goes back to the whole autism thing
Like I'm so jealous of that guy because he's having the time of his life making all these videos that nobody's watching
Yeah, it's just it's that's the whole thing right
That's the trap because when you care about your audience and you care about your popularity or your reception of your content
Like you damn yourself to always being not satisfied
Which is why it's so dangerous to kind of go pro as an artist
As you're you're forcing yourself to be you know, what's the word subservient or or at the behest of of you know
An audience even even if they're just you know, your viewers
You feel pressures no matter what to to optimize what you're trying to do
Which is going to affect the kind of shit you want to produce for example
I don't think it is in at all smart for me to continue producing
Uh best anime ever is best game ever is in the way that I have been
It it's taken me months to get these out
There's no way I can keep doing it and achieve the kind of stuff
I want to so I'm gonna have to radically change my formula and I've already taken a bunch of steps to uh
To make that happen
So, you know, I think my my vision is gonna have to change if I want to be at all successful and frankly
I think we can all agree digital success is pissing me the fuck off
That's the topic that needs to be this. Let's thank god. He's not here. Yeah
Yeah, thank god. He sold out quit the procrastiners podcast to go beyond anthony fantano's podcast
He's going on the hollywood hogan podcast as we speak
Making me fucking say
Yeah, he was literally on anthony fantano's podcast
Man, he's um, yeah, we need to kill him. We need to we have to kill him. That's the only yeah, we decided
We've decided we either need to kill him or we need to like abuse his power and get him to show all of us
But you know, but you see no we're much more comfortable killing him because we don't want pity
We we rather forcibly take them. Yeah
It it it sickens me to think that the only time that I gain subscribers
is when digi
Promotes me in a video and I'm not saying that one of us recently. I'm not saying I want him to stop promoting me
But I'm saying that I'm sickened with myself for not wanting him to stop. I don't that was like a triple negative
Yeah, we know what you're saying. We we have to it's we have to kill
It's sad to think that we're all dependent on the one of us
But I don't I want to I want to I want to shield forever. I was I just want to well, you know
The loser but I think the thing about this is the most loser right digi totally has found his sweet spot
And he seems he seems pretty happy with the content he's making and he's working really hard at it and it's great
So for him, it's absolutely perfect. Um
Oh, excuse me, but you know, it's it's just frustrating for guys like us who
Are just more are more inclined to make to taking longer to make things
And I mean, I don't want I don't want to oversell myself like I fuck around
You know quite a bit as well. I could do things faster, of course
But like, you know, my my dream video isn't the same as digi's dream video
Like his his his asterisk war thing was absolutely beautiful for for youtube
I mean, even then we're probably took a little longer to make that
Yeah, the kind of content he wants to make is also just happens to be the kind of content that yeah
That's why he's so successful right now diminish his his intellectual ability to you know, make the right content
He's done it all intentionally. Look at his leaving pony
Like he reset his whole shit after vast success because you know, he wanted to succeed and he's done it
He's capitalized on it, but you know, it's just something that I'll never have in my work. I will never
Value what my audience values in the sleigh
Because yeah, yeah, you just got out once you're once you're above it like like the red letter media folks
They're just above that shit doesn't matter anymore. They'll just keep making a half of the bags
It's I mean, I'm not going to say that those are super easy to make but they make them for themselves
Seems pretty clear. They they do not take shit seriously
It's it's great. It'd be great to have a situation like that. Yeah, maybe one day
It's interesting that you say that you're at a point where you have to
Change up your style with the best guy ever and try to make it so that you can get them out faster
whereas
I've I've decided on like exactly the opposite solution. I see whereas I have
Stopped giving a fuck entirely
I've been releasing like
as the most random
Like I posted a tweet where like I posted like the screenshot of like my video history of the last couple months
And it's like all this random shit that has nothing to do with each other
Like, you know, I used to think like oh man, you know, if I try to give my channel a strong theme and make everything fit
And look nice together on the video page. I'll get more. I don't give a fuck anymore. Well, good. Good. That's the sound of sucking dick
Yeah, it's the sound of sucking dick. Exactly time to fucking
Jack in your ding dong
And I'm just I've just had it with that shit dong
Yeah, I am he got lost in a tragic accident just as we all know he's a pirate
So we had to replace the wooden dick. Well, you know, my father Gepetto. He taught me a lot of things
And the main thing he taught me was how to jack me wouldn't
do
I can't believe there's a Pinocchio porn of that up to this point
Exactly a lot of that tree sap comes up
And a mosquito gets caught in it and that's how I gave birth to the fucking
And that is how Jurassic Park happened a mosquito got trapped and Pinocchio's sap jizz
And 2,000 billion years later Jurassic Park takes place
Little wooden boy
We put in the extra effort on this joke. Yeah, that's right. That's right. Imagine sanding down that that
Sanding down
To make it all smooth. You know, I I I had to I had to just listen to my conscience. Mr. Jiminy Dickett
Came down
Mr. Jiminy Jacket
Ah
By the way, I have a bone to pick with you Gibbo
What happens last week when we did our amazing procrastineers dark soul race
And I revived the once-in-future legendary hero of Lordran
Uh, what's her name Anita?
I I I I said
Gib you gotta post the the original Anita's occasion video so that people have context for her adventures
Oh, you wanted to post it on procrastinators. Yeah, or you know, link it in the description and Gib
He didn't put in the effort to link
The original by that time I had looked off of the thing
Well, which means that the the viewers had no context. They didn't understand it
That some of the commenters got mad at me. They said I don't like Anita's occasion. I have no sense of humor
I think you're gay. I think you're fucking
I'm a misogynist and I hate women's, you know, you know, we have a lot of misogynists in our audience
Can we just address that? It's sad but true. It's sad but true. We need to we need to you know
Get rid of this toxicity. I've been thinking of pulling our comments all together from procrastinators
You know, it's just I'm not ready to subject innocent viewers to that level of hatred of hate speech
It's just find the comment section to be really problematic and that's right. You know, that's right. That's absolutely right
The like bar itself can't be trusted to have a strong progressive message that we need that that is really
I mean the point of the show the point of the show is to instill our social values and the people who listen. So, you know
Fuck you
That's what I'm trying to say
Um, yeah, what can we say that's related to the topic?
I don't know. I don't know
We didn't put off an upper up an effort into this
Well, no, okay. Here's here's a question then would you wrap like which we're talking about how digi's super successful
Doing what he does and how like we're not there and how we hate him
Yeah, and how we want looking for more success and the only reason I'm not as more successful than digi's because I've
Been working at university. So I haven't had time to make the amazing video the best videos of all time
Which is a decent excuse actually
And you've been your animations, which are great, which we are
I'm gonna become way bigger than digi's
Looking forward to it not to mention you also are like in talks. You're you're working with an actual animation studio now
We forgot to mention that gibbons the most successful really in the real he literally is the most successful
He's the most legit the most the most most
Normie in the good way s guy of us all and he's gonna he's gonna make us all wish we were dead soon enough the way digi does now
Yeah, I'm looking forward to that. Yeah, this guy. He's gonna be the next fucking the next rebecca sugar
He's the next alex hersch lauren foust. Yeah, whoever the fat hip man. He is who made adventure time
He's gonna try to make youtube videos
Imagine how hard it is to work in the studio where the man's trying to fuck you the whole time
Imagine producing something like like like steven universe in that environment, you know
Or or any kind of real show that involves so many people working together
That's a that's a whole animal that gibb's gonna get into and I man. I'm excited to hear more about it
Let's say once you're you know, did you meet with her recently? You got like a meeting coming up meeting with her tomorrow actually tomorrow
Oh, yeah
Well, this is the last time we'll see him on this podcast. He's yeah, he's moving up in the world
Forget about us
Me and nate sitting here like two gay idiots sucking on my beer bottle
It's too it's too cool to be praised for being the the cool guy
So I it's it's on the hollywood bound
Wow
I'm the cool moving with jon tron in hallywood. No no ego raptor. Yeah elmo raptor
So tom you were saying something we cut you off. What were you saying?
Well, my question was going to be like because we're all doing different things
And did you's being very successful doing what he's doing? I don't think any of us would do what he does
Mm-hmm. I'm I'm kind of sorting. I'm kind of planning to mimic him in his style. I mean it was successful
Um, but whatever I don't go on the question. I guess it's like would you rather be successful
Doing something you're just meh about would you rather?
Be kind of unknown doing something you have
Tons of personal
Is the question at the heart of being an artist
You don't need to make that much money to be alive all of my enemies die
Seeing them all driven before me. Yeah, the lamentation of the women. That's my true
Hence becoming the punisher. I mean what what are you gonna do if not just become uh, uh, I mean
It's not fair to describe him even as an anti hero because he's just a hero
A man who kills everyone who disagrees with his opinion
This this word anti hero this this anti hero meme needs to go away
I'm you know, just because you know, here's here's the thing people
Good people aren't always nice people and nice people aren't always good people
Sometimes you need a guy who's willing to cross those lines that the other cowards won't cross
You need a guy who's willing to do what needs to be done to clean up these fucking streets and wash away the filth
Once and for all that's choking the life
of this city
Even even by his own volition batman is not willing to take on the burden of being willing to murder people
To achieve his goal, but the punisher on the other hand that guy will do whatever it fucking shakes to get his shit straight
Fucking dirty harry any any guy who kills people is my hero
That's that's why I've never really liked batman. He's such a high horse faggot
He is he is a very high horse guy. I mean he he'll try to spook you
He'll spook you real good
I mean not to get too far off base, but I always thought it was interesting that they do that with batman
But they lately I think they present that as like a weakness like a character flaw almost what that's the core of the character
That was his yeah, I've been thinking about this ton. That's a good point. I hate that I hate
This trend of like cynicism and how superheroes are perceived or written
Where it's like like how they really should be killing people all the time like this trend of oh batman creates his villains
Batman, uh, he made them all worse. Yeah, what is that? Oh, yeah, you know what fuck you
Batman doesn't kill the joker because he's fucking batman. You know, he's a good guy
The whole point of batman is what makes him great is that he has suffered fucking trauma
He's emotionally traumatized. He has he's he's he's mentally ill and because of that
He takes pity on his mentally ill
Enemies, you know he Batman my batman is the guy you ever see that episode of the animated series with that
With that with baby doll
Yes, she's she's oh, yeah, yeah, of course. She's this midget. She's a dangerous. It's the saddest story ever told
She's a dangerous fucking criminal. She kills people. She shoots people
But at the end of the episode she breaks down because all this shit just happened because she's had a fucked up life
And what does batman do he doesn't punch her in the fucking nose
He holds her and he takes pity on her and he takes her to the fucking police station peacefully
That's why batman's a great hero and I'm sick and tired of this fucking this this cynical trend of well
If batman would just kill all of his bad guys that's deathly his batman because he doesn't
Man, I while we're talking I gotta bring up
I gotta bring up the greatest batman story of all time which is in the justice league
I don't know like unlimited where it's it's telling the future where it shows
Where his worst enemy that that fat black lady whatever her name was who was like his moral enemy
Holy shit. Yeah, where he he there's this there's this crazy psycho girl
Who's mutating the whole fucking world and like all of new york city is going to be fucking leveled if they don't stop her
And so he's like, okay, we need someone to go kill her. That's the only way to stop her
So, uh, she gives batman this he's like, I'll fucking do it. I'm gonna fucking end this. I'll do whatever it takes man
They're like damn batman you you crazy nigga get in there
So he goes in and this lady who can read minds this little this kid named ace leader of the royal flush gang
She goes in there and he's just like
If he just walks up to her and she's like, hey batman, he's like, yo, what's up girl?
And she's like so you came here to stop me and he's like, yep
And she's like you're gonna kill me and he's like nope just gonna be your friend, bro
And he just holds her hand. He just holds her hand while she dies
She's just because because she's like, oh man
My childhood was all fucked up by these asshole scientists nigga. It was fucking gay as hell dog
You know what that's like, you know what that's like, don't you bruce? And he's like, fuck. Yeah, I do exactly
And you know what the cynic the cynicism comes from is a critical misunderstanding of who batman is
Even his man enemy says that's the real batman. That's the guy, dude
Batman is not batman doesn't be batman for vengeance. He doesn't do it to hurt criminals
He does it to prevent crime to prevent other children from going through what he did
He's doing it to save victims not to kill people. You know, here's the thing. I fucking love the punisher
I love kasey jones. I love vigilantes who fucking kill people and i'm sure most people
Tend to agree with these characters that criminals should be fucking put down and killed
I certainly agree with it
But that doesn't mean that i'm going to apply that logic to batman because the basis of his character is an entirely different fucking philosophy
That is equally valid. You can't
It also seems like most of his villains are indeed insane
Uh, well, yeah, I mean, I mean you kind of happen to be insane
He doesn't even come up against like just asshole brutes who want to kill people
They're they usually fucked up themselves. Yeah, I mean his original enemy was like the mob, right?
And the mob is like an evil organization that sort of justifies our legitimately mentally ill
They need help. They don't need to be murdered. That's right. That's right
Well, what was that related to the batman podcast everybody put a lot of effort into that tangent
We did you know what I care a lot more about batman than I do about putting an effort into anything
Yeah, me too. Me too. Uh, what got us?
Onto that I don't who cares. Yeah, who cares not interested. Okay
Gib what else you got for me lay it on the table
um
Okay, hang on
10 I laid it on the table eight put it seven six
five
four
three
Digi's here
one
Digi go anime is a japanese colloquial
That means commonly known as the the actor putting your friends dick in your mouth in a totally non-gay way
Just because he needs a little release. I mean his girlfriend just dumped him and you gotta give him some release
He's just your friend. You're just being a good friend. You're just trying to help him out in his time of need. That's all it is
That's all what anime is. That is what anime is dick on guys and gals. I jack
I jack my I
Mustard on my penis
ketchup on my hot dog
It digi entered the call, but he hasn't said anything digi. We can't tell if you're still recording the podcast
Of course, of course. Oh, yeah. What do you mean? This is going to the podcast. This is the podcast
I can't believe you've been going for an hour and 20 minutes
Now we've been going for 41 minutes in the in the main thing and we've been going great
We don't even need you. We've been putting on the best podcast
It sends yo, I want to I want to I want to pull all of jack Nicholson right now. I want to pull of the shining
Okay, everything we were saying earlier digi bro. Check it out
Go back and check it out
Go check it out. Go check it out. I forget what his wife's name is but insert that name go check it out
Yeah, go, okay, olive oil was the name of his wife
All yes, that's right
And he she should have known better than to trap him in that food locker with all that spinach
There was a one mistake. Yeah, that's why papa showed up at the end beat the shit out of
As you can tell did you you really really put in the effort? Yes
About this topic
Putting an effort. Yeah
Uh
God I'd rather not. Yeah
That's fair. All right, and that's it everybody
Thank you all for watching. Fuck you
Yeah
Yeah, uh
I'm supposed to be working right now. I'm supposed to be working right now
But I'm not working
I'm doing nothing
My dick I'm jerking
Myself. I'm sucking
I am an asshole
I am a stupid
I've got a deadline
Don't want to do it
Oh, and everybody say goodbye
Bye
I guess that's the end
Man, what a clusterfucker. What the hell is wrong with me?