Hey, what's up listeners? It's Ben Saint in the Boomer Radio Show Podcast Pro Crastinators Podcast Soundboard.
It's Ben Saint in the morning.
Announcement, bonus episode, emergency bonus episode. We recorded an emergency bonus episode this week.
If you're interested, there is for Trixie's funny appearance on who are these podcasts where she attempted to dunk on us.
As of right now, I have not listened to it, but me and Simsie and Gibb, if she ever fucking shows up on time, are about to listen to that, record that, and have a live reaction to that.
That will be the bonus episode. It should be up now, when you're listening to this, patreon.com.
If you want to hear our hot takes, my live take on that, and I will give you a live rating, 1-10, of how much my feelings were hurt, and how much I was coping, and how much I was seething.
I will give 1-10 ratings of those three things, and I will chart them as the segment progresses.
Okay, link in the description, patreon.com.
For Crastinators bonus episode, special. Okay, back to the regular episode. Bye.
I won't bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
I had a nightmare last night that I, well, it wasn't really a nightmare, but it was a dream where I recorded the podcast, but then I didn't save it.
I didn't close it without saving it and lose it, but I hit the save button, but I didn't hit the okay on the where to save it, so it didn't actually save.
So I left the audacity file open on my desktop, and I left, and then I realized, oh my god, I didn't actually save it.
It's just open, it still needs to be saved. If anything happens to my computer, the file will disappear.
Oh god, but I'm not at home right now, because I left, and I was like, I gotta get back there. I gotta save the podcast.
Well, if you have enough nightmares, you can put them in a stable.
Oh my god. Oh my god. Yeah, true, true though.
Gotta use your head.
That was a good, that's a pretty, I was watching some, I've been watching a channel that is specifically about Castlevania Dawn of Sorrow and Aria of Sorrow.
The entire channel is about that.
Wait, what?
You mean the whole channel is dedicated to those two games?
Yes, yes.
Wait, hold on. I want to see, what's the name of the channel? I've been watching it a lot. Yeah, he did a countdown of like, he ranked, he did tier list rankings of all the red souls in Dawn, all the red souls in Aria, all the blue souls in Dawn, all the blue souls in Dawn, all the yellow souls in Dawn, all the yellow souls in Aria.
And the nightmare, there's one, I think it's called Nightmare where you shoot a big horse, and that one's apparently pretty good.
That's a high tier soul from Dawn.
Yeah, I seem to remember.
No, Aria.
I remember the big horsey soul.
Wait, hold on. It is a tier list Aria.
I want to give this guy props.
He's got a tiny channel. Yeah, the channel is Jupiter Climb. He's got 1000 subscribers.
He ranked all the weapons. I just really like, I really like Dawn of Sorrow. I really like Aria of Sorrow. So it's just cool.
I haven't played that shit. It's probably great.
You never played those? It is great.
The only Castlevania.
They're the best of the Metroidvania Castlevanias.
The Castlevania I've played is three because I downloaded it on the Wii, eStorm.
That's, those are, three is like before Symphony of the Night.
Yes, yes.
Oh, it makes me so mad. I feel like it's so obvious that it almost doesn't even bear mentioning.
And yet every time I see Dawn of Sorrow and Aria of Sorrow, I can't help but be so upset at the art style change between the two games.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
I don't. Let me look it up.
The, the art, Aria of Sorrow, I think that, yeah, the first one, it has the beautiful like painted art style of, oh, who's the artist who did like Symphony of the Night, Castlevania?
It's an anime. You mean the front cover? No.
Or the backgrounds?
Co, is it Kojima? Is it Ayami Kojima, the guy who did all that?
No, no. Or maybe his last name is Kojima.
I know who you mean. It's the guy, the Castlevania guy.
The only Kojima I know is Hideo Kojima.
It's definitely not him. Symphony of the Night.
The guy who got the, he made a Kickstarter for a different non-Kojima, I mean Castlevania-esque thing that was pretty good, I think.
Koji something. I think his name is Kojima.
Kojikondo.
Not Kojikondo. Yeah, Igarashi, I think.
Oh, okay, no, but I'm talking about the art specifically, which yeah, is apparently this guy Ayami Kojima.
Oh, yeah. I didn't know that.
Anyway, they didn't, I guess they didn't have him for the sequel, Dawn of Sorrow, and so they just kind of look like fucking anime, and it sucks so bad.
Yeah, Dawn of Sorrow had more of an anime look to it.
It's so bad. It's so like, it's so flat and boring compared to the first one.
The front cover, I'm looking at them.
The front cover and the portraits.
Art of Sorrow looks like a Final Fantasy-esque sort of painterly-esque thing, and then Dawn of Sorrow does look like some anime-type tie-in game.
Dawn of Sorrow looks like fucking, it looks like, I mean, no offense, I guess, but it looks like fucking, what do you call it, like Ace Attorney or something.
No, the front covers for Ace Attorney are the worst part, for sure.
But yes, look, look, compare the two front covers, and that's exactly it.
Like all the in-game character portraits are painted like that, and then in Dawn they look like fucking, they look like fucking 90s anime characters.
It sucks.
I don't know, I didn't mind it too much, but I guess it depends on how much you like that kind of anime art style.
If you're a big fan of anime, maybe you would like it.
It's just so much more generic. It's so much more like you would see this kind of art anywhere.
I am looking at an image, oh god, I went to look at the image, it's asking me to download it, fuck off, no, I will grab a screen grab.
This looks a little bit like Fire Emblem characters portraits, which I don't mind, I actually quite like those.
This isn't annoying me too much.
I only don't like it because I think the first one is so much more unique.
I feel like it's a big downgrade.
Maybe Ben is just racist against anime.
That's true.
Putting these together though, I can see, is that the same guy?
Well, that's him at the end of the game when there's just a certain thing going on with him.
He's beast mode.
It's a spoiler.
Oh my god, Dracula's in Castlevania.
The story of Dawn of Sorrow is awesome because every Castlevania is about you're a vampire hunter hunting down Dracula, and in this one you're just a guy.
First of all, it's in the future for some reason.
It doesn't really even matter that it's in the future, it just is.
You're just some kid who wanders into the castle who gets trapped there.
But it turns out in the end that you were called there because you are Dracula reincarnated.
And then you have to resist your fucking fate to stop yourself from becoming Dracula.
It's awesome.
I think there's a secret ending in one of the games where you do actually become Dracula and you get killed by the other characters.
Before you fight them, it's one of the other...
It's Julius Belmont, I think.
Yes.
If you go down to the secret ending mode, you fight Julius Belmont, and he's a tough boss.
And you don't kill him though, and you tell him, like, I'm gonna go stop myself from becoming Dracula.
If I don't do it, I want you to kill me.
And then if you go and you get the bad ending, it's the scene from the beginning where Dracula is sitting on the throne and he has a miserable pile of secrets and he throws the wine glass.
And then, yeah, you get that scene, but it's you.
You're sitting on the throne and you throw the glass, and Julius shows up and he's like, I'm here to keep that promise I made for you.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, what a video game.
Yeah, that was pretty cool, I remember that.
So good, yeah.
But you know, since we're on the subject of Metroidvania, shouldn't we talk about the new one, Metroid Dread?
I haven't played it.
I don't have a Switch, I haven't played it.
Everyone seems to be really liking it.
Well, it's too bad Tom isn't here because I think he has played it, right?
Yes, I think I just tweeted about it.
Well, I kind of got it a bit later than everyone else because that issues with my order, but I beat it recently.
I beat it once on normal mode, and I got a playtime of like three hours and 50 minutes, which is pretty good.
And then I beat it again on hard mode following one of those sequels.
But you beat the whole game in three hours?
Well, it's not, that's the in-game timer.
It actually took me longer than that, but the game doesn't count on you.
Is it because you died over and over?
Yeah, I died a lot and it doesn't count your death.
Fair enough, I guess.
So it took longer than that, but that's like an accelerated speedrun time.
So when I beat it on hard mode, I was following one of the sequence breaking guides,
and I managed to get the playtime to like two hours and 40 minutes, which is, you know, not bad for a normal non-speedrunner.
That seems so short though. It seems like a really short game.
Well, normally it would take you around like 10 hours probably to beat it.
Yeah, that's what I would expect for a casual play.
But you know, most Metroid games can be beaten in under two hours speedrun time.
Well, yeah, but I mean you, but it was your first play, so it's not like you're using speedrun strats.
Well, I did the second time around when I played on hard mode.
The first time I just went real fast. I got lucky on the first time.
I only just barely made it under four hours, which is what you need to do to unlock, you know, all the artwork and stuff.
But anyways, CC says he wants to talk about Castlevania, should we let him in?
I don't know, that's your call.
I got nothing to say about castles and vanias.
But I don't mind, I guess.
I've gushed enough. I've gushed enough. Nah.
I just figured we should die.
I figured we should talk about Metroid Dread so you can put it in a thumbnail and in the title.
Oh, yeah.
Get all those SEO points.
That's pretty good.
Dude, Metroid Dread, two dimensions.
I played Metroid though. I can talk about Metroid, not Dread.
That's the clickbait.
I can talk about Zero Mission and Fusion. Those are my ones.
Zero Mission is the remake of the original one, right?
Yeah.
The first one I ever played was Fusion on the GBA, and then I played a GBA port of Super at some point.
I think those are the only two I've played, but they're cool.
There is no GBA port of Super. I think you're thinking of Zero Mission.
Maybe I played it on an emulator. No, I've definitely played Super Metroid.
That's the big one.
Everyone says it's the best one or the most iconic, and I still haven't gone around to it.
I like Metroid and Zero Mission and Fusion though a lot, so I probably would like it.
Super Metroid is my favorite, but I think my second favorite probably is Zero Mission.
Zero Mission is, even though it's a remake of the first Metroid, it's a lot like Super Metroid.
It takes a lot of inspiration. A lot of the upgrades and bosses and stuff are taken directly from Super Metroid.
Yeah, it's such a cryptic game for trying to figure out some of these things.
There's that one bug that's blocking your way from one angle, and it's got a really weird creepy music.
You have to go all the way around to the other side of it, and then it's just like the chrysalis is left,
and you walk through it, and then that is turned into a bus.
Yeah, I remember that.
That's something they added in the remake that's not in any other game.
Yeah, it's really hard to...
I was quite young when I played Zero Mission.
It was one of those video games that actually does justice to the wonder and exploration mind of a child sort of thing.
I wonder if you could go there. I wonder if you could do this and that.
I wonder if you bounce on explosions, one of the bomb balls.
Yeah, the bomb jump.
Yeah, the morph jump ball jumping.
What if you could jump all the way on the surface of the planet up to a ledge, and you could?
And I got up there, and I'm like, fuck yeah.
There's so many places where you can do that.
That's basically what Metroid is all about, and Super Metroid kind of does that even better,
because in Zero Mission it tells you where to go, but Super Metroid doesn't tell you where to go at all.
Well, I was so confused playing Zero Mission, I had no idea where I was going at any point.
I was too stupid to understand when there was a cutscene, that there was a way to get there.
It's just sort of like you go to a chozo, you get an upgrade, and then it goes...
and then it shows your map.
It goes...
and then a funny little orange marker on the map.
And they mark on your map.
But I didn't even have the map, so it was just like a dot off in the distance.
I'm like, how do I go that way?
Yeah, Zero Mission, it was a...
I explore the entire world over and over again every time, because I kept not finding the right way to go.
It was great.
Zero Mission, it had a pretty good balance between not giving you too much information about where to go,
but it does give you at least a little nudge with that little icon.
So you still have to figure it out on your own mostly, but you at least have some sense of direction and where to go.
Because in Super Metroid and Metroid 1 and 2, you had no indication whatsoever.
You just had to randomly search the map and figure out where to go.
You just sort of run up against a wall.
You run around until you can't run around anymore, and you're like, how do I do this?
And then you try and figure out how to do that.
Right.
But what I like about Super Metroid is that even though it never tells you where to go with icons and stuff,
the level design kind of has a lot of direction to it.
So as long as you follow the basic philosophy of, if I haven't been somewhere, I should probably go there,
you will almost always find a way forward.
There's a couple of exceptions to that, but that general strategy,
it pretty much always works.
It kind of funnels you into where you need to go just through the natural geometry of the world.
And I think that's pretty cool.
You know how I was playing for a little time?
I said I was going to play a bunch of NES games or franchises from the beginning.
So I beat Mario 1, and I sort of stopped doing it at Mario 2, but I want to do that.
And then Mario 3.
I also want to do that for Zelda and Metroid as well.
I could maybe play Super Metroid on stream at some point,
and then mute the comments because people tell me where to go,
and everyone would be seething and coping about how bad I am.
And that would be fun.
I would definitely watch that stream.
I'm a big fan of watching people play games that I grew up with, but it's their first time.
I think I mentioned that before.
For some reason, I get a lot of satisfaction out of that.
I guess it's just because I've beaten these games so many times that I don't remember what it's like to experience it for the first time.
So whenever I get the opportunity to see somebody else experience it for the first time, I'm always pretty excited about that.
Yeah, it's like vicariously getting something that is impossible to get yourself.
Even if it's been a long time, you'll eventually remember parts of it, and you're like, oh yeah, I get it.
I remember this.
They play a game you've played before, and they walk past something, and then they stop and stare and be like, whoa, what the hell?
They're surprised at something, and you have gotten so used to it that you didn't even register it.
You've forgotten it was there. You've forgotten it was funny or interesting.
Yeah, sometimes I'll be reminded of when I first played a game and the kinds of mistakes I used to make when I see somebody else have trouble with the same areas.
So that's pretty interesting. At least I find it interesting.
What game are we talking about? Which Metroid?
Well, I was going to ask, with regards to Metroid Dread, how does it feel similar or different to Zero Mission?
Because that's the one I know.
Well, it's definitely pretty similar.
It's a lot more similar to Zero Mission in Metroid Fusion than Super Metroid, as far as the controls and the design and stuff.
But it's probably the most similar to Samus Returns on the 3DS, because I think it uses either the same engine or a similar engine to that one.
That one had the free aim mechanic where you hold down one of the shoulder buttons, and you can aim in 360 degrees pretty smoothly.
I think probably one of the big differences between Metroid Zero Mission and Fusion compared to Super Metroid is the bosses.
Because in Fusion and Zero Mission, the bosses are kind of hard. They're pretty dang hard.
In Metroid Dread, the bosses are also pretty difficult.
They're strangely dark souls-esque, not just because they're hard, but because you fight a lot of dudes, night dudes or night guys.
Just big, all-king guys in armor with a spear and stuff.
You fight a lot of that for some reason in Metroid Dread.
If you like that kind of boss fights, you'll probably like this as well.
I really enjoyed boss fights personally in Metroid Dread. It was a lot of fun.
They're very hard. You die a lot, but they have really cool attack patterns to learn.
Every single attack has a tell.
Every time you know the tells, you can predict what attacks they're going to do before they do it.
It's really satisfying to just get a no-damage kill on a boss that killed you 50 times because you completely figured out his attack pattern.
There's also the counters, the melee counter.
Every once in a while, the boss will flash yellow.
If you do a melee counter, that mechanic is from Samus Returns.
If you do a melee counter when he flashes yellow, it triggers a really cinematic animation where you just unload all your missiles into the boss and do massive damage.
That's extremely satisfying to pull off.
True, though. I assume.
As far as exploration is concerned, it's pretty much like any other Metroid from Super Metroid, Zero Mission and Fusion.
It has a pretty massive map and there's a billion upgrades to collect.
You know those Shine Spark puzzles from Metroid Fusion? I think Zero Mission also had them. There's a lot of that here as well.
Did you ever do any of those Shine Spark puzzles?
I got it. I got my baby bells. I'm good now. I got them.
What flavor?
It's regular.
Oh, fucking pathetic.
I know.
A Metroid flavor?
A Metroid flavor. You put it on your head and it sucks your life force out.
There is Metroid flavored cheese just for you.
The plot to Metroid Red, which I'm not going to talk about because it's a spoiler, but it's kind of weird.
It gets kind of shown in towards the end.
I heard it in very minimal storytelling. There's not cutscenes and stuff in it.
For the most part, there's very few cutscenes. The story is kind of done in Fusion where you go to the computer room and you talk to Adam.
Adam the computer and he just tells you what's going on for the most part.
But Adam doesn't talk as much here as he does in Fusion.
For most of the game, there's no real cutscenes. But then, all of a sudden, in the middle of the game, there's a giant 10 minute cutscene that basically explains everything.
The very end just feels really shown in to me because the main villain is all like, oh, I let you live, Samus, because I wanted to see you reach your true potential.
I wanted to see how strong you'd get.
Is it for Chozo Dad?
Yeah, that's basically...
Abusive Chozo Dad. Samus, you're supposed to be a bird, idiot.
Yeah, basically.
Works for me. The Metroid game is about collecting shit and getting super powerful, so it seems automatically appropriate.
In some ways, I kind of like it because I sometimes like the cheesy, shonen tropes, but at the same time, it also feels kind of lame that this is what all Metroid has resulted in.
It just resulted in cheesy, shonen tropes.
They just reinvented anime.
I was kind of expecting something different because the previous Metroids didn't do that for the most part.
To see this is a big, massive revelation at the end, it's kind of weird.
The boss fight, the final boss is really cool, so it kind of works.
It's interesting because I don't think of Metroid.
There's a lot of world building and aliens and things you can study up on, but I think of Metroid Zero Mission and I think, I gotta blast those aliens.
I gotta jump and I gotta morph ball.
It's not a thinking series, not that a heady Metroid thing is bad or whatever, but when I think of the plot of Metroid, it's usually just go to a planet, do your job, and then get out of there before it blows.
It's like an 80s action movie plot of a video game.
That is for the most part accurate.
It was really only Metroid Fusion that started to step up the storytelling a lot, but all the previous ones barely had any cutscenes and Zero Mission since it's a remake of Metroid One.
That's why it has almost no story in it because that's what Metroid One was like.
They're mostly just side-scrolling action exploration games.
The story is pretty secondary to the game.
It's mostly just lore. There's a lot of lore, but there's not a whole lot of plots.
There's a lot of lore, but it's like lore that I don't feel curious to learn about.
I know that there's space pirates with Ridley.
I don't really care what they're being space pirates about or where they're from or what the state of the galaxy is in.
Who does Samus work for? Do they work for anyone?
I don't really feel curious about these things, even though there might be cool tidbits of information.
In Metroid Prime you can scan everything, and I'm like, yeah, but I don't actually care about anything.
I just want to shoot.
But it's weird because in other sci-fi universes I would like to know a lot more.
I don't really care about the scan information in Metroid Prime.
I think most of that is just fluff.
The writers had to earn their paychecks, so they just had to put together as many words as they can and increase those word counts.
But I think the lore of the series is something you would only care about if you played all the games and you're a hardcore fan.
If you're not that big of a fan, it's like Zelda.
The Zelda games don't have big plots either, and you'd only care about the Zelda timeline if you've played all the games and you're a big hardcore Zelda fanatic.
I don't know.
I feel like I do care, or I am interested in the Zelda timeline, probably just because it was an interesting infographic when I first saw it.
I was like, oh, what do you know?
They're linked to the past.
And the future.
Am I right? Hell yeah.
Cool.
If there was a map of all the planets in Zelda, Ella, Ratchet and Clank or something, I was like, oh, look at all those planets.
Well, what about?
Screw Attack.
I think the bottom line of Metroid Red is that if you like Metroid, you're probably going to like Metroid Red.
I probably will.
I'll steal it.
It's more of what you like about Metroid, basically.
Well, that's good.
But I felt like a lot of the bosses took a lot of inspiration from Mega Man, because most of the bosses are like one-on-one fights with a dude, as opposed to a giant monster or alien.
And there were a lot of mechanics added in this game that felt like Mega Man, like there's a slide move, a Mega Man style slide.
And then there's also like, there's something that's kind of like the dash move from Mega Man X and the air dash.
Those mechanics, they really make the bosses way more enjoyable.
Because you can kind of air dash over the bosses to avoid their attacks and stuff.
Wait, it's on the switch. I don't have a switch. I couldn't even play it if I wanted to. Damn.
You could steal it.
There are switch emulators.
Yeah, I heard there's an emulator actually that fully plays Metroid Dread, I think.
Really? Seriously?
Yeah, I read that in an article somewhere.
The switch emulator has been around for a while. My brother was like, oh, like he googled it one time and it just came up and it was easy to use to play switch games.
I think there's two major emulators that run Dread. One partially runs it and the other one runs it all the way. I guess it's fully playable, I think.
But I haven't tried it, so I don't actually know from firsthand experience how well it works.
My hands are clean.
Yeah, my hands are clean because I washed them.
Same.
I should stop. I shouldn't look at Twitter. I shouldn't look at Twitter.
Ben, don't be Twittering right now.
Oh yeah, that reminds me of something else I wanted to bring up.
So Riley challenged you to like a boxing match or something?
Oh god, we're going to talk about that. Yeah, he said he wanted to punch me or something.
It's kind of funny because at one moment it seemed like you two were working together to conspire against the May break-in story.
Yeah, I don't know.
And now you're like at odds with each other again?
No, it was the other way.
What did he say?
I don't know. He posted some shit on a YouTube comment that was like Ben just doesn't like Trixie because he's jealous because he wants her back but we've got her now.
And I'm like, okay, that's wrong. That's a lie. You're lying about me.
And he was upset. He was mad that I said he was lying about me.
And he said I'm going to punch you and he kept posting gifs of people being punched to illustrate what he intended to do to me.
And then the May thing came up and suddenly he's like, he completely switches to and suddenly he's like, oh yeah, you know, Ben, you know, Ben, you know, me and Ben are both just real genuine guys.
You know, we had our differences but you know, it's like, okay.
So you've fallen to a temporary truce?
I didn't. Nobody did. I don't know. That's just what happened. That's just what happened and it's pretty funny.
Yeah, I just rolled with it because I thought it was funny.
That was pretty much the end of the conversation. We exchanged one or two things about how the break-in story sounded kind of fishy.
Yeah, Riley says it's like fake and made up. I don't know if he says it may lie about it.
I don't know if I trust him but I don't really trust her either so I don't know what to think about it.
Oh yeah, that's the thing. He's pretty untrustworthy but...
I would say so, you know.
I think so, yeah.
You can't really take anything he says seriously.
It's not really.
Oh yeah, Trixie wrote that sub-stack article this week where she, in so many words, basically says that it's transphobia that I don't like her anymore and that's it.
So that's funny.
That was only a matter of time.
Yeah, pretty shitty thing to do.
Clearly dishonest. Clearly a misrepresentation of it but it's convenient to believe it so I guess it's sure.
Why not?
She gives a list.
She says, I don't experience transphobia in the real world.
I only experience transphobia in very specific circumstances and then she gives a list of circumstances.
And one of the things on the list is like people, someone that used to be close to me, you know, encouraging my patrons to not be patrons anymore.
One of the things on the list is Ben St.
You know, I don't experience transphobia in the real world but I do experience it through Ben St.
Through Ben St. specifically?
Yes, Ben St. of Boston, America. This is his telephone number.
Ben, you're trying to ruin the careers, the livelihoods of a trans creator.
I mean, what the fuck?
That's literally what I'm doing and I don't feel good about it.
It's a good point.
I feel heroic for doing so.
Who made me mad? Who made me mad to see that?
I saw a short clip on, it's part of a longer video, but I saw a short part of it where Trixie, somebody asks Trixie what you would have to do in order for her to forgive you.
Yes, and she said she would only forgive you if you commit harakiri, is that how you say it?
Harakiri, yes.
She said harakiri but the yigs didn't know what that meant so she amended it to seppuku.
And they knew what that meant?
Yeah.
I think that's more of a well-known term.
I think so, I think so.
She wants you to commit sodoku.
That's probably why, it's because of the memeability of seppuku.
Oh, I remember, I learned the word seppuku from that one kid's show.
It's called Mystic Ninja, I think it's called, but it's like the kid's show with the little goofy ninja.
One of the bad guys is a guy named seppuku maru who, his whole thing is just that he commits suicide and he cuts his guts open and kills himself.
That's a weird thing to be in a kid's show.
It is, but it's true.
Wait, let me show you seppuku maru.
Seppuku maru?
No, okay.
If you've never seen this before, I mean it's real.
Wait, I'm in the wrong server.
Make sure your seats are belted.
Yeah, this guy, he's like the evil henchman guy and he's just always like, oh, I'm gonna do it, I'm gonna seppuku myself this time.
He's so confident and cocky looking with his knife dangling.
This looks really familiar to me.
He loves disemboweling himself.
It's from Goemon.
He's got a one ton thing around his wrist.
Oh, one ton wrist weight, I didn't even notice that.
Yeah, I think it's called Mystic Ninja in the English dub.
Yeah, Goemon.
He commits seppuku in 10 times Earth gravity.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure he's in one of the games because I played all the Goemon games.
I used to be a big fan of the series.
I didn't know there was an anime.
You said this is from an anime?
Yeah, Goemon, wait, Ganbare Goemon is the show, I think?
Was there a video game about this guy?
If he was a boss, he would win instantly.
I feel like I might have played a Super Nintendo game about the same old Ninja man.
Yeah, he's from one of the Super Nintendo games I think that never came out in the US.
I can't remember which one though.
Hold on, hold on.
NES game, there's a...
This game, this fucking game right here.
I remember renting this game from Blockbuster, Blockbuster Video, and thinking it was cool,
but not really understanding how to play it and progress in it.
Oh, Game Grumps played that, I think.
I think they did, I think they did.
Yeah, I played this briefly, I never beat it, but this is one of the early Goemon games.
Okay, well I don't remember Sepakumaru from this game, but he doesn't even look like the same character, barely.
There were a lot of the Super Nintendo games.
There's like four or five Super Nintendo Goemon games, most of which did not come out here,
but I beat them all in the early 2000s when I first discovered Emulation,
and I'm pretty sure he's in one of the games, I think, because he looks really familiar to me.
Well fuck, okay, I typed in Goemon and Google, and I did see the kid, but I first got Ishiwaka Goemon,
a legendary Japanese outlaw hero who stole gold and other valuables to give to the poor.
He and his son were boiled alive in public after their failed assassination attempt
on the Sengoku period warlord Totoyomi Hideyoshi.
This is a cool guy, he's got a whole Wikipedia.
You mean you don't know about the legend of Goemon?
Yeah, Goemon is based on a real person.
I don't know nothing.
I knew that it was based on a legend or something, I didn't know it was a real person.
That's neat, I guess.
He's like Robin Hood?
I think it's like Japanese Robin Hood.
The whole live thing reminds me of what happened to spoilers in One Piece.
Oh, I don't even know what you're talking about.
I think Goemon is based on a real person, but there's probably a lot of myths and legends surrounding him as well.
Of course, I mean, outlaw heroes are cool, everyone has them.
He's Robin Hood?
Yeah, he said fuck the police.
Goemon says fuck the police.
And he's right to say that.
You do get attacked by cops all the time, you know, from that period, whatever the response.
Yes.
The guards.
Samurai.
No, I don't think so.
No, okay.
Right.
Yeah, I couldn't beat it.
I didn't understand.
I was too stupid.
I didn't know how video games worked.
You should have played Mystical Ninja for the Super Nintendo and also the N64.
Those were pretty good Goemon games.
Well, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I didn't.
They didn't call them Goemon.
When they brought them here, they didn't call them Goemon at first.
They just called them Mystical Ninja.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Which that title doesn't mean anything.
No.
Neither does Goemon.
Because he's not even a ninja.
Is he not a ninja?
He's just a guy, I guess.
Yeah, I suppose so.
A guy with a sword.
He sort of has a...
I guess, yeah, he's not really a ninja.
He holds like a pipe.
He has a fucking pipe that he smokes weed out of, and that's his thing.
In the games, he uses a pipe as a weapon.
What's even funnier is that he gets a chain pipe later on that he can use as a hookshot or something.
A what pipe?
A chain pipe.
A chain pipe with a chain.
It becomes like a long-range melee weapon in the N64 game.
Dude, like Castlevania, the whip.
Yeah, exactly, it's like a whip.
Is it King of Fighters?
No, it's Soul Calibur that the IV has the chain sword.
Yeah, there's a chain sword in Dawn of Sorrow, too.
Ah, Bog.
Ah, video game.
Fire Emblem, there's a...
Souls, you get the lightning puppet soul, lightning bolts.
And an axe with a chain on it.
You make the red minotaur, you make the big axe that goes around the whole screen.
A chain sword sounds cool, but I don't know if it would be really practical.
It seems kind of pointless.
I feel like...
Well, they had one in...
What's that video game?
Bloodborne.
So, I guess it would be useful.
You mean the cane sword?
Oh, right, it was a cane sword.
Yeah, it wasn't a sword, it was a cane.
No, it would probably not work in real life, I think, in my opinion.
I feel like the Go Amon series is pretty underrated.
More people should check out those games.
Well, I don't know a damn thing about it, so I guess you're right.
Actually, most of the Super Famicom games have recently been translated,
so if you are into emulation, you can play them now in English.
There's like four of them, I think.
Wow.
So, I would recommend that.
When I beat those games back in the day, there were no translations,
so I had to beat them in Japanese,
and it definitely hindered the experience a bit,
because those games do have some funny dialogue.
Yes, good.
I remember one of the bosses of the Super Nintendo games
is a guy who's obsessed with sports,
and all the enemies are themed after baseball and stuff.
An evil athlete by the name of Seppuku Maru
has been tearing my home apart.
That's where he's from, actually.
That's from Super Go Amon 4, I think,
or, you know, Go Amon 4, whatever it's called.
Sure.
So, that's why I recognize this guy,
because I beat this game that this screenshot is from...
Excellent.
Whoever is editing this should put this in the episode, this image.
Eleazar.
Yes, that is correct.
Get on it. Get on it.
Cool.
Speaking of Japan, period.
Yes!
I've been getting into...
In order to get away from re-watching Red Letter Media
for the 70th time in my off hours,
when I'm just not really... I don't need to do anything.
I've been trying to get some anime into my veins.
Oh, no!
No, but it's good.
I was recommending Legend of the Galactic Heroes
to some people yesterday.
Yeah, I think I tried to watch that.
It was boring, though.
Oh, jeez.
Well, all right.
Maybe it was something else.
But I watched some classic stuff,
because, you know, the past is cool.
All good, you know.
Yeah, a lot of cool stuff happened back then.
Yeah, I can always agree with that.
I saw a fucking Gauche, the cellist, the sealist.
How do you say celloist?
Cellist.
Cellist. Gauche, the cellist.
That was pretty cool.
And then Panda Copanda, which I love.
It's a cute little Totoro-esque Miyazaki film, pre-Ghibli.
Oh, yeah.
I saw your drawing.
Yeah, and I note that, because it was so good.
My art is so incredible and impressive
that people had no idea that I drew it.
They thought it was promotional material,
and I feel pretty cool about that.
Everyone was fooled.
Yeah, I mean, it did.
It looked like you didn't draw it.
It was too on-model.
Yeah, I saw that.
That was pretty nice.
Yeah.
Panda Copanda.
That's a good one.
Hang on, I got a list.
I got a list of stuff.
I watched the Inferno Cop, that was cool.
That was a cool little one.
That sounds cool.
It's a web series where it's barely any animation.
Was it a trigger thing?
I can't remember.
I liked it, though.
Hey, anime.
Japanese colloquialism.
It's true, though.
A couple of years ago,
I watched, for the first time,
I watched Yu Yu Hakushu.
That's so enormous to watch.
I liked Yu Yu Hakushu as a kid.
I never finished it.
I feel like they never aired the end of it
on Cartoon Network or wherever I was watching it.
I never saw the end.
It was good, though.
A good program.
I first found out about it
because I kind of got into a lot of
emulation in the early 2000s.
I randomly downloaded
Yu Yu Hakushu Super Famicom ROM
back in the day.
I quickly found out that the game
was based on
the original game.
It was based on the original game.
I quickly found out that the game
was based on
an anime,
and then I proceeded not to watch the anime
for a decade,
but I kept hearing about it
and I kept wondering about it
and I was really curious.
One day, I just decided
a couple of years back, I decided
I want to watch this thing.
I want to see what it's all about.
When I went into it, I had no idea it was considered good.
At first,
I thought I made a horrible mistake
to commit to watching to
several hundred episodes of
a new show that maybe
sucks.
What was the show?
Yu Yu Hakushu.
I didn't know it was good,
but I remember while I was watching it,
I saw
Trixie
back when she was
Digibro.
I saw her tweet out
a recommendation.
I saw her recommend
Yu Yu Hakushu.
She said it was one of the best
animes or something.
She liked that one.
When I saw that,
I felt kind of vindicated.
When I saw that, I felt kind of vindicated.
I felt like I made a good choice.
If the anime expert
Digibro thinks it's good,
then I must have picked well.
I watched the whole thing
and I really liked it.
Her recommendation
is probably
one of my favorite shounen
so far that I've seen.
Her recommendation is what got me to
watch Ultimate Survivor Kaiji,
which is so good.
When people talk about
Squid Game, I can go,
Kaiji did it first.
Kaiji was better, probably. I haven't actually seen Squid Game.
I haven't seen it either.
When people say it's like Kaiji,
I know what they're talking about.
Because I guess they're both about
people in death games
trying to get out of debt.
The most recent
anime film.
Well, yeah.
They were both about society.
The most recent one I watched
was The Little Prince and the Eight Headed Dragon.
I've never even heard of that.
It's an early Toei,
really early.
I think it said in the
credits that Issao Takahata
was one of the assistant directors.
Who's Takahata?
What did he do?
Takahata and Miyazaki are the two big guys
at Ghibli.
Oh, Takahata is probably
the guy that made this.
He's probably the guy that made this.
What's that stupid one?
Only yesterday?
That one that
kind of sucks.
I don't know actually.
Is the dragon based on
Orochi or whatever it's called?
It is. This Little Prince is
Susano and it's Orochi.
Oh, I played
the dog game.
I played Okami.
I recognized it's like Nagi and
Nami and Susano.
It's like
really, really well animated.
Really quite western.
It's so early on in anime production
that they're like still lip-syncing.
They're lip-syncing to the actual sounds
that the actors are making
rather than just opening the mouth flaps.
This looks really bizarre.
It's really good.
It looks very
modern?
It doesn't look...
Yeah, it looks like
Samurai Jack. I see there's
something. Yeah, Samurai Jack
was inspired heavily.
Samurai Jack was inspired heavily from this.
This is like a 60's
anime movie and it's like
one of the big
early things that is like super influential
and I noticed
that Susano himself
looks so much
like Toon Link that
it can't be a coincidence. This is definitely
like the inspiration for Toon Link
and a lot of other little things.
He really does now that you mentioned it.
Why is he writing
My Little Pony?
That is
a cute little freaking horse.
It's a flying horse, not a Pegasus.
No, he just flies.
He's so cute because instead of
flapping wings, he just
kicks his little legs really, really fast
to move quicker.
I'm trying to find a cool gif.
He flies with the power of friendship.
He flies with the power of
I'm a flying horse.
He flies with honesty, loyalty,
laughter,
friendliness,
kindness,
this play, why will it not play?
No, stick to it in this
trustworthy, loyal, helpful,
friendly, courteous, kind of beating, cheerful,
thrifty, brave, clean, and reverent, I believe.
How do I get a, I don't know
how to fucking make a gif be posted
in a fucking chat. I hate this so much.
Right click it,
and save it, and then
click it and drag it.
This sucks. This sucks so much.
Yeah.
Hell yeah, it does.
I want you to see the funny little
leg kicking.
Well, go to the web page.
You'll see them. Oh, fine.
Okay.
Let's see this little,
he's just flapping his little legs.
What?
This does not look like it was from the
60s.
Well yeah, this is before anime has
solidified a look.
It's very much like
copying the western
animation that is around before that.
It feels a bit like
like, um,
oh god, what were they doing
at this time?
In Disney and stuff, I'm not sure.
But it feels familiar with a lot of the
backgrounds and stuff, but different
because it's made in Japan.
It's cool.
It's kind of like how Astro Boy doesn't
look like a lot of modern anime.
What was called Astro Boy?
This looks like
they were,
you know,
Astro Boy and all the,
who's the Astro Boy guy?
The guy who made every fucking thing?
Osamu Tezuka, I think?
Yes, Tezuka.
The Tezuka, what do you call it,
ethos, is like,
cut down
on everything. Minimize everything.
Cut frames,
animate on thirds instead of twos.
This looks like it's the exact opposite.
They were like, no, we're gonna
make this
as hard as possible.
We're gonna fully animate all the mouths.
It's gonna be every frame.
It looks like they were like, nah,
fuck cost saving measures.
We're going all out and we're gonna make
a masterpiece was what they were going for
here.
Doesn't look lazy at all
because, you know,
early anime was made
because
they made it as cheaply as possible.
They pumped it out.
Yeah, this is before all that
bullshit.
This is that real shit.
Is this before Tezuka?
Uh...
No.
Let's see.
Osamu Tezuka.
I don't think so because I think
Atomic, I mean,
Astro Boy was one of the first enemies ever
and I think it originally aired in black and white.
Plus, it's TV.
This is a movie. They used to make movies
before they were doing TV as an anime thing.
Yeah.
Okay, so Astro Boy,
the Astro Boy manga was serialized
from 1952 to
1968.
So it would have been contemporary
with Astro Boy and
Tezuka and stuff.
So I guess it was kind of at the same
time.
Well, since then you had a dragon
d-d-d-d-d, released in 1963.
So maybe it'll be after.
I don't think the Astro Boy
anime would have been around, but
the manga certainly, certainly would have been.
The Astro Boy...
Okay, the Astro Boy...
Yeah, the anime series started
in the same year, 1963.
Wow.
Yeah.
Everybody's like, everybody's like,
let's just be animators now, and they all did.
It premieres...
Why does it say this? Is a Japanese television series
that premiered on Fuji TV on New
Year's Day, 1963.
A Tuesday.
I don't know why it mentions that it's a Tuesday,
okay. It was a Tuesday.
It was a Tuesday in case you were wondering.
Thanks, I was.
Well, at least it wasn't a Monday.
I don't even know...
I hate Monon's days. Anime would never have gotten
off to... would never have gone
the places it went if it started on a Monday.
Could you imagine
a fucking Japanese made
Garfield strip?
It's the same, but Garfield
just likes, I don't know,
sushi instead of lasagna.
I bet...
Yeah, the Japanese
Garfields.
I bet there are, like,
some equivalent.
Like, someone in Japan,
where comics are so popular,
someone in Japan had to be like,
wow, Garfield is the most popular fucking thing
in the universe.
I should just basically make Garfield,
but...
but me, but it's me doing it.
I bet someone did it.
It's hard to find, because if you type in Japanese
Garfields, you'll get memes upon memes.
You'll never find an actual real thing.
I mean, if you're a manga artist
and you're looking at, like, the landscape,
you're, like, and you're looking at, like, hmm,
you know, what is successful in my industry?
You're, like, oh...
Garfields.
That's, like, the Garfields
and peanuts. At some point, you must have
looked at the landscape and been, like, Garfield is dominating.
I have to make my own Garfield.
I have to ride Garfield's coattails.
That's the only way. Somebody must have done it.
Hmm.
Garfield, uh, why did you eat all my sushi?
Terrible.
Just terrible.
Garfield, let me...
You better commit seppuku now.
Garfield does not do that.
You better commit hirakiri. I mean seppuku.
Dude, the cat side of the bag now.
Rip off.
Japanese... I'm gonna look at a Japanese Garfield rip off.
Uh...
It turns out it was...
There was a Japanese Garfield that came out before
that inspired it.
Inspired Garfield.
Oh, Japanese Garfield leak.
Urusei Yatsura?
Oh.
Urusei Yatsura.
I think it's just a joke because she wears the
the orange stripes.
Okay, never mind.
This is a serious deep dive.
I want to find the one Japanese artist
who is like, oh, Garfield, I could do that.
I have a cat. I could do this.
I'm not finding it.
I'm not finding it, so maybe it didn't happen.
No.
They must have had...
I mean, they had, like, newspaper
strips, right,
in...
Not even sure.
Well, they would probably do, like,
4-coma, right?
Like the vertical. I mean, they probably formatted
differently, but, like, people made...
Japanese?
Maybe that kind of, like,
newspaper strip, basically.
Yeah, I guess they would usually do the
4 panels instead of 3.
I don't know.
Yeah.
There must have been some
publication, some magazine or newspaper
that was like, let's run comic strips
like an American style.
Let's just kind of do it like that.
Maybe it'll take off.
Maybe it didn't.
I don't know.
But...
When I Google
Japanese Garfield Rip-Off, for some reason
I get the real Ghostbusters
1993 video game.
That's probably where Garfield
was ripped off.
It was, like, cat in the game.
Okay, the Japanese version is
based...
Based on Walt Disney's Mickey Mouse,
which is part of the Mickey Mouse side
of Chemco's Crazy Castle series,
while the European version is based
on Jim Davis's Garfield comic strips
and the animated series Garfield and Friends,
what are you talking about?
What are you talking about?
I don't know. That sounds pretty crazy.
Depending on which version is played,
the player controls Mickey Mouse,
Peter Venkman, or Garfield.
Okay.
What's this?
They just made
the same game
and just they made 3 different versions
of it and one of them
is Garfield and one of them is
Peter Venkman from Ghostbusters
and one of them is Mickey Mouse.
Is this Peter Venkman
supposed to be, like, the John of this
universe? The real Ghostbusters
known in Europe as Garfield Labyrinth
and in Japan as Mickey Mouse 4
Maho no Labyrinth.
I see, so they just rebranded the same game
multiple times. Why do they do it?
Why not just
release it the same?
It must have just been, they made the game. I gotta play this.
Yeah, we gotta play all three
and compare.
They must have just made the game and they were like,
okay, we've got the Mickey Mouse
license for Japan, but
we don't have it for America, so
we gotta get another license. Okay, we'll
put Ghostbusters in it.
There's no information here. There's no, like,
why did they do this?
Here's what the gameplay is and here's how people
thought about it. This kind of thing has happened
before with some of these old
Japanese games. Sometimes
they would get rebranded with different IP
characters and stuff.
Then actually
it originally happened
with the original
Donkey Kong.
The original Donkey Kong was supposed to be a
Popeye license game, but they couldn't
get the rights, so they
just redid all the characters
and it was the same game, basically.
But then later on, they did
get the rights to Popeye
and they did actually release a Popeye game
that nobody nowadays knows about.
I think they played that
on the Game Grumps, right? They played the
Popeye game on Game Grumps, I'm pretty sure.
I don't know, but I played it on my
channel.
I'm pretty damn sure that, wait,
you played it?
When I was young, we had this
family computer and there was
a Popeye game on it. I don't know
whether it was a rip-off of the Popeye
game or a strangely emulated version
that my parents got given
a bunch of, like, here's some games
for the kids.
There was also a Huckleberry Hound
game
and some other cartoon thing.
Fascinating.
But I feel like I've played the Popeye version
of the thing, because you got bladders and the shit.
Yeah, I played
the, you know, let's
play, let's pun, whatever
you want to call it, of the Popeye game
on my channel.
It's quite a few years ago now.
I'm not sure if I saw that one.
What a game.
What a choice of game.
What a world.
I mostly show
it because it was short.
You know, I know.
It's the one where you gotta like
collect Olive Oil's hearts.
Like her, she's like extruding hearts
and they're floating up and you gotta catch
them.
You know, the plot is that, you know,
Bluto, the antagonist, he wants to
know which is Popeye's girlfriend and
you know, the joke I told in my play
through is, you know, Popeye
likes his girl, Popeye likes
his Olive Oil extra version.
Oh, god.
Yeah, true.
True, yeah.
It's a pretty good line, I think.
I saw, I saw a,
I saw a
a strip.
No, it's Popeye 2. Sorry, I had to interrupt.
But I found Popeye, it's Popeye 2
of the PC.
I played Popeye 2 of the PC when I was young.
This is nostalgia.
I saw a Popeye strip where like an
interviewer is asking Popeye
like his opinions on like
various political issues of the day
and Popeye gives
like his, his,
he's asking him about like, Popeye,
are you a fan of like prohibition
and stuff and
I mean, I'm trying to find it.
And Popeye's response is just,
you know, I just eat spinach, man.
I don't know what to tell you.
No, he says, he says,
he asks, what do you think about
prohibition and he says, I don't like
to think about it or something.
But that sounds like something he'd say.
There was more though.
He asked him like a dozen questions about
like the various social
ills that were plaguing like
prohibition era America.
He mostly, he mostly doesn't have
opinions about them.
Have you seen that Twitter account
that is like official Popeye
but Popeye is like super trans positive?
No.
Wait, it's official. I don't know what it's called.
I think it was official. It's just so like
Popeye, the official Twitter account
and it's just sort of like celebrating
like, you know, LGBT
issues and stuff.
And people like, oh, based Popeye.
No, I like it.
It was cool. It was cute. I feel like
if you asked Popeye about
that sort of thing, you'd be like
hey, Popeye, what do you think about
transgenderism and he'd be like
trans-what-ism?
He'd be
he'd be funnier
about it.
I am what I am.
Damn it. I found this.
They am what they am.
I found this
cropped version which doesn't have
all the questions.
It only has like half of them.
There was more. He asked me about prohibition.
Do you-do you drink?
I refuse this to answer on account of
it might incrinimate me.
What is your religion? Treat everybody right.
And if they steps on your sockum.
Yeah, like based.
Such wisdom. It was like that
attitude but for trans rights, it was great.
Right, right.
Sockum.
Rockum. Sockum.
Robots.
Paised. Okay, cool.
Popeye is a
he always taught the kids to eat spinach
and spinach is pretty good for you.
Yeah.
I-I-I...
Damn it. I just thought it was interesting
to see them being like
hey, Popeye.
It's the past.
We are in the good old days
but our society has problems.
What do you-what do you think about them?
Popeye, what's your opinion
on cancel culture?
What's your take on
what's your take on
the abortion bill that they just passed
in Texas, Popeye? Please, we need
to know.
That would be a great
political comic.
That's what this would have been
if this was made like today.
Instead of asking about prohibition.
Oh, wait.
This is...
You know, I used to strangely be a big fan
of the Popeye black and white cartoons
when I was a kid.
Look at him.
Yeah, I'm disgusted.
Yeah, I'm disgusted. Great.
That's an all-timeer.
That's like constipated
but more disgusting.
Yes.
I'm disgusted and also constipated.
I hope so.
What were we talking about?
Yeah, I was a fan of the old
black and white Popeye cartoons
mostly because I really liked the animation.
Sure.
It was...
I think they made it in like the 1940s
or 1930s or something.
It was a long time ago.
Before television.
And I was just really impressed
with how well animated it was.
I guess they would have shown
in like movie theaters, right?
Yeah, I read they used to show them
in movie theaters before a movie
either before or after a movie.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The...
Yeah, the television like changed
the format.
Yeah, everything was either like a short,
like an animated short,
or like a feature-length film.
And then...
That's Disney...
Yeah, because like when Disney started,
it was, yeah, it was pre-television,
so they made movies because it's the only thing
you could see animation in.
You'd see a feature length.
Yeah, the very first Disney...
Well, you would go to the theater
and there would be like a little short played
like a live action movie.
You would have the cartoons.
Yeah, I think the very first Disney
animated short was
Steamboat Willie.
And I think it came out in 1928.
Damn, Mickey Mouse is so old,
he'd be dead if he was a real mouse.
Well, I sure wish
he would enter the public domain by now,
you know.
Yeah, everyone's gagging
to draw Mickey Mouse.
I can't do it.
You know, those old Popeye cartoons
were really... they had really impressive
animation, even by today's standards.
Like, I saw somebody
comparing the animation of one
of the Popeye fight scenes
to like a Dragon Ball Z
fight scene.
And the Popeye scene actually looked better
than the average Dragon Ball fight scene.
It's because they had...
Well, they're more animated.
They animated on ones
because the idea
of saving money and time
to make it
so that you could animate on twos
and have less drawings
would make it cheaper.
But animation
it was a high-skill, high-paid
like luxury sort of industry
initially.
You only had so many of them working on it.
And then since it became so popular
it was like, oh, we got to mass-produce this stuff.
We got to make it cheaper.
And thus, Dragon Ball Z
was one to the other.
Yeah, I was in a...
When they syndicated the Popeye cartoon,
they made it a lot more cheaply
and it was a lot, you know, not as well animated.
I think this happened around the 60s and 70s.
And I didn't enjoy those
Popeye cartoons as much because
I just appreciated
the better animation of the shorts
they used to do in the past.
By the way,
this image here
that I posted, I think
this was blowing up on Twitter.
Somebody was saying, oh, based on non-binary Popeye
because he's wearing women's clothes
and he's like...
I promise you, I won't be mad at me
for wearing something.
Of course, I won't be mad at my little wifey.
What is it? I am amphibious.
Amphibious.
I wears both women's and man's clothes.
Arf, arf, I am Popeye.
What the fuck is he talking about?
I don't know, this kind of confuses me.
I am old.
It's just sort of like a funny like,
oh, Popeye wearing both men and women clothes
and then it's like, oh, non-binary icon Popeye.
I think it was like a joke.
But then Popeye, the official account got in on it.
I agree.
And then it started all that stuff.
I don't know if this was meant to be.
Why does he bark?
After coming out is amphibious.
He barks.
Yeah, you would think he would croak.
Yeah, definitely.
Popeye is definitely pretty cool.
He should be in Spanish, actually.
I have no idea.
Why is he married to this
surly strong man?
Probably for some reason.
I'm not familiar with this.
One assumes it is for some reason.
I was going to say something else
but I didn't think of it.
It's not for no reason.
When you're right, you're right.
Okay, okay.
Dude, segue.
Quick, somebody segue.
I have a segue.
It's from Popeye the Sailor, comic strip.
Clarissa Gunn-Spoke, comic strip.
Oh, right.
I finally read it.
What do you think?
Well, I don't think it's
much of a spoiler.
I'm very
interested in
what's going on
with the temple
and that dude's hat.
Something is up
and I want to know what's up
with that.
And that's where
I'm at with Clarissa.
Yeah.
Something's up and I assume
one day I will learn
what's up.
I'll string it along for like 50 years
and then I'll tell you.
It's like, hey, buy my new comic
and then you'll find out next time.
Never happens.
Ooh, that's how they get you.
Do the Dragon Ball Z thing
where Goku trains in the
chamber for like 50 episodes
and every episode is like
next time on Dragon Ball Z
maybe something will actually happen.
This planet will explode
in five minutes.
14 episodes later.
It finally blows up.
Yeah.
Yes, it was cool.
Are you making more?
When do I get to the end?
I will...
So I had written the end.
I want to go over it
and like see if I can
write it better because it's probably...
First draft is always
worse draft.
You can always improve little bits here and there.
So I want to go over it.
I anticipate
that very soon I will be
busy with Lord of Ghost kickstarter stuff
because the plushes have arrived
and they're sitting in a box.
I didn't want to take them out
just yet, just in case
I don't know
they get damaged
from being exposed to the air
or whatever.
Yeah, they crumble to dust.
Yeah, they're very fragile.
So they're just sitting in a box
and I've got the pins
and the rest of the artists
are drawing a lot of ghost stories.
I have drawn eight pages.
I have one page left to go.
One page left and then I can tell everyone else
Ben's Saint was faster than you
and it's truly embarrassing.
I'm never faster than anyone.
There's nothing more shameful
than Ben's Saint being faster than you.
It is, because not only am I slow
but also mine was the longest
by far.
But I did it, so
I haven't finished it yet, but soon.
I hope that shames them
into action.
So all of that is going to be
a lot of work.
But I will be
there at the ending of the Chorissa
and then sketching out a bunch of it.
Probably not
going to show anyone.
I was thinking of streaming it, but I'm not sure.
I feel like
I initially did those streams
last year because like,
oh shit, I'm so bad at working.
I need eyes on me to force
me to work and that was the stream.
But for this
finishing
of the comic and posting it,
I didn't stream it and I managed to work anyway.
So I was like, you know what, I don't
need to do that. It's fun, but
I don't need to. I'll do it if I really
feel like making an event of it.
I've always been kind of conflicted.
I'd like to keep it more like secret.
I've always been conflicted about
the idea of streaming a comic
that you're drawing because
on one hand it seems like
a lot of fun, but on the other hand it kind of spoils
the story and stuff.
So I would
I would
I'll do it in secret
and maybe
I'll stream other things. I'll stream
the beating Mario 2
or something, eventually. I'll get around to it.
I know the game is tough and you have been
anticipating that.
I've been waiting for that
momentous occasion
when you finally beat Mario 2.
I'll be so much of a gamer
to have beaten two Mario games
to have beaten two Mario games.
They'll make you
two points above
then Saint as a gamer.
I had all
the old NES Mario games
as a kid and I never beat
any of them because I was
a child and too stupid
too stupid to beat the game.
That's absolutely
shameful. I know!
You had the real deal
and you didn't even really do it.
No. I couldn't.
I tried.
Game's hard.
I assume I could probably do it
now. Probably I could
beat Mario now
if I wanted to. I just don't want to
is all.
Well now I wish I had
so I wouldn't be made fun of
but it's too late.
It's the only reason you would play a game
so you can make fun of people who didn't play it.
Yes.
I want to be the one making fun
of others. I don't want to be on the receiving end.
I want to be dishing it, not taking it
if you know what I'm saying.
Yeah, just like how
you never beat Final Fantasy
Tactics either.
No, I got stuck in the fucking
Y-Graph Castle or whatever.
Yeah. Stupid. And it's like one of
your favorite games too.
I don't know if I would
say it. I mean I like it a lot.
I don't know if I would say it was one of them.
Yeah. For a time it was.
The
Tactical RPG was my favorite genre
for when I was like
in high school. I love that shit.
I do admit though
that game is pretty complicated for a child
to beat.
Yeah.
I'm not exactly sure how I beat it as a child
but somehow I did.
I watched a speed run
of Vanguard Bandits the other
day.
The speedrunner
sometimes
sometimes the
speedrunner
is annoying.
The speedrunner
was very like reddit
core.
Her jokes were very reddit core and it made me go
ugh god.
Stop.
At least there weren't bad puns
being made constantly.
Ugh.
No.
That would be the absolute worst.
Yeah. I can't imagine watching a
let's play it like that.
Imagine doing a speedrun
making puns like lightning
speed
like perfectly executing everything but still
having time to say the puns.
That'd be impressive.
If you run the game
enough you probably have
you probably have a bunch of like jokes
and gaffes and goose that you've
thought up and probably said on stream
before.
For your big
games done quick
debut
you bust all those out
in a row. One after the other.
You lightning, you machine gun them out
for comedy
because you have your whole repertoire
to work with.
Then you can pull out all those
reddit jokes
to impress everyone.
Yeah.
Some gamers, man.
Some gamers are just
I'm trying to remember what specifically
was so reddit core about that one.
I don't know. They were just
very like
laughing a lot about like
dumb jokes.
References to something.
No. They were like
they thought it was really like
funny that like the game
had like crude humor
and like fart jokes in it
and like she thought she
made a joke about that as though it was
like a very embarrassing
thing and how it was so silly that the game
had politics but also
crude
jokes in it.
I don't know.
Could you believe it?
The goal of this video game.
I didn't know that game had
crude humor in it.
I mean it's got a little bit but
like oh and there's a character
who's like a ninja
she's like a ninja made mech
pilot and the speedrunner was just
like can you believe this character
yes you heard that right. A ninja
made mech
pilot and she's our waifu
now. It's like oh god
please spare me.
Please spare me.
Spare me. No.
So many things combined.
That game sounds pretty cool now.
It is it actually is
a very cool game. I remember
it was one of my it was like my favorite game
in in high school or
something like we're in like eighth grade or whatever
and I
rented it and I really liked it so I went
to go buy it. I went to GameStop and I like
asked the guy at GameStop like hey do you have
Vanguard bands and he's like yeah
I don't really like that game very much but we got
it. I was like okay
cool thanks for making me feel good about my
purchase but it seems kind of
unnecessary. Yeah
why do you gotta judge me for it?
It reminds me of a reflexive
game review. It's a
Final Fantasy Tactics tactical RPG
but you put your guys in
yeah you're in mech sort of like Front
Mission 3
and when you do an attack
you like choose like how you want to respond
to it and then it plays a little like 3D
it has a cool like full 3D
where like the two robot models will like
you know counter attack each other and stuff
it rules it rules.
Yeah I think you mentioned this
on on here before and I was
I probably was there for that because
it's so anime
I do remember this now. So fucking anime
I'll probably check it out eventually
you know I have a kind of a big
backlog of old games
that I play. Sure.
I think it's pretty neat
it's got multiple routes
do you like
depending on like your characters
like relationships with each other
you know you'll end up
supporting like one
like a different regimes
like which country do you want to support in the war
basically?
Which team of people do you ally yourself with?
That was also the case of Front Mission 3
I believe
but Front Mission 3
was kind of based on
real world
it kind of had like a futuristic real world setting
you know we'd use
actual countries and stuff
Vanguard Bandits is as anime
as it gets it's super
fantastical there's like an evil
mech that like runs on the blood of the innocent
that like the bad guy pilots
That kind of sounds
full metal alchemist to me
for some reason.
It's very
I don't even know it's very
it's very 90s fantasy shown in
cool
it's cool I like it
but I remember
I played in Beat Front
Mission 1 a while back
that one never came out
you know out of the US
officially but it has like
a translation patch
although I think it got officially released
on the DS in English
in the US but
I played the Super Nintendo version but
anyways what I liked about that game
that's kind of funny and the story is that
in the beginning you are a soldier and you work
for you know what's
the equivalent of like the United States
government or whatever
but it has a different name in the game
because it takes place in the future
and yeah
so eventually the government
you find out the government's evil and they're doing evil
experiments and
you defect
from the military and you become a fugitive
but then you like
you join
the opposite side
you join the enemy of the government you were working for
and then you fight
the government you were working for
so I guess you know
if you look at it in a real world setting
it's like you work for the US
you find out the US is evil
then you defect and you join I don't know
their enemy Russia
but then the thing is you find out
the KGB
then you find out that this other government
is also evil
oh no who would have thought
so then you just
wind up at the end of the game
a world wide fugitive
all the governments hate you
because all of them are evil
and I don't know
I thought it was kind of funny
um
that's front mission one
I think it's either front mission one
or front mission three I kind of forget
now because they both have really similar plots
uh
uh the um
yeah I played
front mission three for the playstation
and
I think yeah it's a tactical
role playing game grid based
fantasy tactics style thing but like
okay I was hunting
I might have mentioned this before I was hunting for music
to steal
from a video game to put in phantom's revenge
uh
and I settled the music that I ended up picking
that I thought was the most suited for the game
was the music from front mission
gun hazard
which I assumed is like
yeah I assumed it was it would be
like the same tactical RPG but no apparently
all the other front mission games
are tactical RPGs but front mission
gun hazard is like a side scrolling like
action shooter for some reason
I think I told you about uh gun hazard
one of the last times I was on
is that how you found out about it
no I think
I mentioned it last I had been I had been
like searching through
like games with like
people saying like what games had good
music I think I had found it
uh myself
somewhere I had I had been going through
lots of like like uh
youtube videos that have like uh uh you know
video game soundtracks in them
because I published
this actually I published a review
of gun hazard on my website back
in uh I don't remember when
it was like quite a while though
I was yeah I looked at because I was interested
I looked it up gameplay and I was like oh wow
no it's it's just they they made
one game in the series
just a completely different kind of game
for some reason yeah I did mention
it uh one of the times I was on
on here uh it's actually
probably my favorite
uh front mission game
because I'm a big fan of uh
side scrollers
and it has a pretty interesting story
you know also
yeah it looks cool I kind of wanted to
play it
if you can even if you can believe that
uh if
sorry that blows your mind yeah
well I certainly would recommend
it it is uh
you know this is the review that I
published in 2007
oh there it is
which is when I first uh discovered
and played this game
yeah I think it was yeah you are the one
that told me that it was a side scroller
and I was shocked I was like what the why is it
a side scroller
yeah I seem to remember telling you about it
um yeah that's right
I almost I forgot
uh yeah yeah because this is
this is a pretty obscure game that pretty much
nobody knows about
I feel like I'm the only person
that knows about this game and knows that it's
good and I'm the only one that recommends it
to people
that's why I thought it was the perfect game to
steal music from because nobody will have played
it and nobody will be like oh this is that song
from that other game
yeah pretty much
you know when it comes to obscure older
games I'm kind of an expert
on that so
if you ever need advice
on good music to steal from older
games have a
pretty huge list of obscure stuff
I think you you I think
you also recommended Mystic Arc
yeah I did I also
have a review for that
I looked that one up and I
thought the music was cool but it was too like
fantasy I like I like that gun hazard
had like had like a sci-fi
kind of vibe to it
it was more like yeah yeah
well you know gun hazard is
a game about giant mechs so
I know I know
so it's definitely
gonna have more sci-fi
to it I um yeah
yeah
damn imagine reviewing video games
yeah the Mystic Arc review
I published in 2014
hmm
I think I think
2014 was when Mystic Arc was
first unofficially translated
because there is no official translation
for that one
I see
I
okay obviously I can't
read these right now LeMau
um
you know by the way uh did you watch
that video that I sent you
a while back
which one
the Astros Playroom video
review that I did
yes I did I did watch the Astros Playroom
video
oh the little jumpity jump
3D
video was that
what did you think about that video
gave me a little chuckle
yeah
you should link it you should put link
there
put it in the description
gave me a little chuckle
it was like a
a different
sort of comedy almost
what's the word
non sequitur but not exactly
it's just sort of
yeah a little wacky
a little wacky
there it is
yeah it was a
bit of an experiment on my part
a lot of
it was my first time
trying to edit 4k footage
which was awful
really
my editing software did not like that at all
yeah
it kept crashing
and
you know first time doing a modern game
first time doing your video review
it's kind of weird
because I've been doing traditional text reviews
for like 10
15 years
but this is the first time I ever did a video
review
I mean I feel like
I feel like that's where the eyes are
that's where the eyes they're on youtube
though you're more likely to get
your review seen if it's a video
essay than if it's just a written
written one
how easy do you think it would be
get all of your text reviews
and just say
what the text was
and then have game footage
and then make like a million reviews
like that videos
well honestly
I don't think it would be too hard
I have over 500 of them so I could do that
for quite a while
oh my god that's content
think of the content
think of the amount of watch time
you could accrue if people be like
well I think
they type in obscure game into youtube
you gotta mind your paths for content
you already created
you already done most of the work
yeah that's true the writing
is kind of the hardest part
at this point the only time consuming thing
I think for that would be
to just capture the gameplay footage
you know that could take some time
yeah
depends on the game
could you steal it
you could take a long play footage
I mean I've done that before
it's like you credit the long play
where you get it from
but you have to provide credit for that though right
yeah just say where you got it
yeah
I don't know I have this kind of weird thing
where I hate using other people's work
you know
the way I see it though
is like if it's a long play
it's just footage of a game
it's not like they made the game
they're just recording the game
that they're playing
that's a good point
it's more of a service than anything
it's not really there like intellectual
property if it's just footage of the game
in my opinion
is that cheap
I don't think so
I suppose it's just a weird
mental thing I have where I feel like
I have to do everything by my own hand
including capturing the gameplay footage
you didn't develop the game did you
I mean
but the footage
the footage will be identical
if you capture it yourself
or if you use someone else
capturing the game right
yeah I know it's just a stupid mental thing
I have you know where I feel
I just feel psychologically
I want to be able to take full credit
for everything that's here
without giving anyone else credit
I am stealing music
from front mission gun hazard
and I don't feel bad about it
in the slightest
I'm taking it it's mine now
I feel like
you can extrapolate
that idea into like
well you didn't make the game
you didn't make the music
you're using in the background if you're using music
right
it's like
I don't think capturing
the gameplay is a line
that is
as arbitrary as any other I feel
yeah I know it's a pretty stupid thing
I'm just being dumb about it
you gotta be smart
we're gonna kick your ass
we're gonna kick your ass chrono
this is bullshit
in 2003
in 2003 some guy
made a banner from my website
and I did use it briefly but then eventually
I got rid of it because I just
didn't want to use anything
like anyone else
really?
even though he made it for you
he made it for free
so I was just like
okay that's cool
yeah
it was my hole
it was made for me
I just felt bad
I wanted everything to be made
by myself
I guess you can say it's a sigma male
mentality
definitely I would definitely call
it a sigma male mentality
very sigma trait
I made my own banner
which was way worse than his
and I used that instead
I mean
alright
I still have this banner actually
what if I
I'm gonna make you a banner
just to torture you
you won't be able to use it
yeah I don't know if I'll allow myself
to use it though
yeah
my
my neck is really sore
I'm moving my head around and it sucks
my neck hurts and I think the reason why
is because I was walking yesterday
I walked out I took a shower
and then I walked outside
and I thought I had some water in my ear
I thought I got some water stuck in my ear
so I did the thing where I like
shook my head right you shake your head
like shake the water to come out the ear
like I jumped on one foot and I like
jerked my head like get the water out
I didn't work
I don't think I actually had water in my ear
or if I did it was so little that like
it evaporated and it didn't matter
but yeah jerk in my head like that
fuck my neck up and
it hurts now
and also I'm hungover
when I have water in my ear I always do the thing
where you put you
press your palm up against your ear
and like suction it
I've done that
I've never tried
you know that episode of Seinfeld
where Kramer's got water in his ear
and he like he keeps jerking his head
and he like jumps up and down
Kramer doing that
well that's what I
I've never tried the hand suction thing
does that work?
well it's like a plunger
as long as the seal
the air is airtight
well yeah I mean
no but I do it anyway
it works because I learned it
when I was like in the swimming pool
I got water in my ear and I did that
and it's like and it's out
it's like oh cool
now I do that
for me sometimes it works
but actually I have now a
kind of a thing
a doohickey view
you want to call it
it's kind of like
I don't know what to call it
it's like a weird suction thing
that you can put in your ear to suck out
earwax
it's just a rubber
rubber ball like thing
with a tip at the end
I've seen those
do those work?
they can work if your earwax
is like movable
it would suck some of it out
and I think
maybe that could also work for water
if you have any water in your ears
yeah maybe
I've heard that like
sticking things in your ear
regardless of
like Q-tips and all that
it's a bad thing to do because you'll just push
the wax further in
the thing you gotta do
is you gotta get some
some olive oil
and I don't know
why this works but there's like
medical grade olive oil
ex-super virgin
I don't know what's the difference
but you drop like a few droplets of olive oil
in your ear and you lie down
and you let it go in there
and the olive oil
softens all of the earwax
and then you tip your head and it just all falls out
gross
I know it's gross
I'm gonna puke just thinking about it
but it feels like oh good
it's gone
yeah cause I had a really bad blockage one time
where I couldn't hear like
certain frequencies in my left ear
oh dear god
I couldn't hear like low notes so I was like oh this is fucking with me
cause my other ear could hear low notes
that sounds awful
so I needed to get that sorted out
and it just softens up the wax
so that it falls out
if you try to scrape it out you'll just push it further in
it'll be worse
we're here in the USA
we have special
liquids you can buy at the store
over the counter
pharmacy stuff
instead of olive oil
special American liquids
American like freedom liquid
yeah maybe olive oil works
just as well as that
pharmacy stuff
I'm just imagining the feeling of like tilting your head
and letting it just drip inside your ear
it sounds like a nightmare
it's strangely like good
cause it doesn't go like
I don't know it doesn't penetrate
it's just sort of like
doesn't break the rain barrier
no it's just sort of like
the over the counter stuff I'm talking about
like when there's a bit of water in your ear
when the shower, when there's water covering it
it's like
it makes that sort of feeling
the over counter stuff I'm talking about
is like ear drops that softens
the ear wax so I don't know I guess it's similar to
olive oil
I have heard of
stuff like that and also
ear foam that you put in your ear
that foams up
I don't understand
thinking about putting stuff in my ear
it's giving me the fear
it's giving me the existential room
it's giving me the ear fear
I had a bad blockage in my ear
a few times and I just
I went to the ear doctor
and they did this thing where they stick
like a hose into your ear
and they just shoot water into it
wait really
yeah they shoot
a ton of water directly into your ear drum
and it feels horrible
and
they call it like
irrigation, ear irrigation I think
irrigation
yeah exactly
and then the ear wax just kind of shoots out
and it spills into like a little
it shoots out the other side, goes straight through your brain
it kind of pours
into like a little cup they
hold next to your ear
you know
it doesn't feel good at all
but it did the job
cleared up my ears
that is
so weird, I would never think
to power wash the inside of my ear
that would be so loud
yeah it's loud and doesn't feel good
that's for sure
I don't like it
I don't want to talk about this anymore
but the good thing is
it gives you immediate relief
because the ear wax comes out immediately
you don't have to wait
like a few minutes or anything
Shiba Inu coin is up
it's not Dojo coin
it's a different coin
did you see Bitcoin went up to like
60 something
yes yes I saw
60 billion
I was and I'm still mad
even last week I was mad
about Bitcoin going up
and again
last week I complained about like
I was looking at it when it was around 40
and thinking maybe I should buy the dip
nah and now it's 60
so fuck me I guess
fuck me
what are you gonna do
I didn't buy any for a while
because I kind of
didn't do so hot last time
so I would just like
whatever
and now it's
it went up a lot so
I should have bought some
it is
yeah I mean obviously I wish I had bought it
when it was low and sold it when it was high
but you know
the same old story
the last time it was rallying
the last time it was going really high
I bought some as it was still going up
and yeah it went up some more
and I was like yes but then you know
and then I sold and I ended up
basically coming out
I think I lost like 100 bucks
or something so like
maybe not 100 maybe like 50
so
yeah it's like it's so easy
to look at the line going up and be like
line going up I should buy
line going up
but then you know it always goes down eventually
and then I don't know
the last time I
it's not like I was able to time it
or anything so like what what makes me think
I would do any better this time
yeah it
it went up a lot it went up almost 50%
in like a couple days there
but now you know it peaked and now it's a bit
down it's down like
it's down like 10%
which is a pretty big dip actually
so like if you bought it when it was peaking at
like 7
like you know 66k
and you're like oh shit we're going to the moon
or whatever
you've lost 10% of your investment
so that's not good I mean maybe it'll
maybe it'll bounce and keep going up
who knows well the strategy
pretty steep peak at the moment it's kind
of
the strategy I always use
is you can't lose if you don't
sell so if you buy and it goes down
just keep waiting and
hope to God it goes up again
that's the I mean
you could see it like that you could also
you could also look at it as
the long term value
of any of any investment
is zero like once you've invested
anything the money the consider the money
gone and like anything you
get back from it
is like okay
it's just a bonus
right like if you have a held asset
and it's simply held it's not
it's not worth anything you have to sell it
eventually if you if you're going to get anything
right
I suppose so that's
you know that's not how
that's not how the billionaires calculate
their their self-worth you know
I guess I guess that's
true I don't I don't really understand
the mindset of the people who are like hold
forever like literally hold forever
like
surely you will sell eventually I guess they
I don't think anybody thinks hold forever
but they think it doesn't matter how
bad it's getting if you hold it'll
eventually go higher than it was
I guess they they might never sell out
at a loss I think is what they they're actually saying
well that's what I said
they might be thinking that like
it will you know it will see
such mainstream adoption one day
that eventually Bitcoin will just become
their money right and then they will
spend it you know with
wallet to wallet transfers
instead of spending their
you know I think that's a
overly optimistic
viewpoint
I personally don't believe that would happen
I also
don't really think it's good I mean I don't
think it's going to replace money
I do I mean
it might see some more mainstream
I mean it is becoming a bit more mainstream
now I think that's what
the like the hold forever I think that's
what they're banking on they think that Bitcoin will just
become money one day
yeah yeah well
I don't yeah I guess all I
can say is good luck to them
you know yeah
I'm wondering about like
how
valuable Bitcoin can be
because like say
hypothetically everybody got in early
and they've got like
a bunch of Bitcoin sure and then
it goes to the moon and then you've got
like hundreds upon hundreds
of billionaires spending
money does that how does
does that even make sense
like how how does this
wouldn't wouldn't Bitcoin itself
lose value if everybody has so much of it
no no because
well everybody
okay well what you're describing
if you're thinking of physical things that people buy
like food and whatever
well if everybody had a little bit of Bitcoin
if you had spread out the Bitcoin
before it went to the moon you know it would still
the total amount of Bitcoin
worth would still would still be the same
the market cap or whatever would still be the same it would
just be more distributed among more
people yeah I think Bitcoin
there's a limited number there's a limited amount
of Bitcoin that that can exist
yeah I think there's a hard limit on how much
Bitcoin can exist so
yeah that theoretically
should never become
valueless because of that
you know like the dollar
you know how the dollar is valueless because we just
keep printing more of it
what do you mean it's valueless
well that's the case for like all
fiat currency
the government just determines what the
value is it has no intrinsic
value
sure yeah of course
and when I mean that's
you know whenever a government is in debt
they just print more money usually to
kind of deal with that
in addition to borrowing money and
all the typical things they do
borrowing money
is good actually
national debt is good
actually
well they certainly do a lot of that
so
I guess maybe it's good
it is
it actually is good like it's not
it's not bad that America like
has debt to its citizens
it's actually fine
as long as they don't default
this is business
well didn't they default one time
I remember
like years ago they
they defaulted on a payment and then
they had to raise a debt ceiling or something
I can't remember
are you talking about with the under Obama
this is
this is related to that article I linked
two weeks ago about the minting the coin
the trillion dollar
biden platinum coin
yeah they had
they had to raise the debt ceiling under Obama
and the republicans were like
oh he raised the debt ceiling
that's bad but it's like no
actually raising the debt ceiling is just
what everybody knows you have to do sometimes
but
if you can get someone else to do it
you can point at them and go aha
he raised the debt ceiling
he's a spendocrat
he's a spendocrat Jerry
I think
the only issue is if they like
keep increasing the money supply too quickly
which doesn't really
I don't think is related to the debt
but if they increase the money supply too quickly
then the value of the currency goes down
yeah hyperinflation
it can happen
I don't think we're at risk of it happening right now
I suppose that
was supposed to be the point of bitcoin
to try and prevent that from happening
but I don't know
the point of bitcoin
to replace fiat currency
was supposed to be the point of bitcoin
not memeing the point of bitcoin
is to be able to
have money
and buy things without paying taxes on it
that is the point of bitcoin
is to
be undetectable by the government
that sounds pretty cool to me
taxes
I guess so
I guess I can see the appeal
but I mean it's
it's not gonna
it's just gonna get regulated
it's just gonna get regulated and become
a regular thing
that you gotta pay taxes on
there's two outcomes
either the government just outright bans bitcoin
or they regulate it
like regular
like anything else
well it's hard to ban bitcoin
I don't think they can do that
I don't think they'll be able to
if two people
one guy has a thing and they accept bitcoin
another guy has bitcoin
what can the government do to stop that
transaction taking place
delete the apps
crack down on it
it's a little hard
bust in their door
they can ban that kind of thing
they ban child porn
and that's just
digital files that people trade
tyranny
yeah
I mean they could make it illegal
I just don't think it would work
I don't think it would be enforceable
I think it would lessen
the amount of people using it openly
but like at this point
it'll happen no matter what
for a while at least
well I mean the same can be said about
almost any laws
there's always gonna be some people that
commit a crime and get away with it
yeah
I guess so yeah
I think it would
I think trying to ban it would just be
kind of like giving up
it's sort of like
drugs are illegal like marijuana was illegal
for a while
and it was like stupid because like the government
could have
they could have gotten
raised tax revenue
if they just made it legal
and like saleable
and regulated
making it illegal had no upsides
it was bad for
citizens and it was bad for
the government
and I feel like banning bitcoin would be the same
there's really no practical upside
to trying to ban it
yeah I wouldn't want them to ban bitcoin
but
I just feel like they might
if it threatens
them in any way
didn't China make it illegal
or something
China is cracking down on bitcoin
farming
yeah I think they banned bitcoin mining
maybe
because of the environmental impacts
oh no god knows
because they can't control it
they don't like that
you know China doesn't care about the
environment so it has to be
a different reason
sure well
yeah
I guess it's true
okay
that can't regulate it
okay I mean that makes sense
that tracks
damn I was looking at
covid case numbers in China
have you seen this shit
no
it's
covid case numbers
come on
come on please load
you fucking
hold on I'm finding the graph
it's
it's unreal
you're putting out graphs for this
it's gonna be pretty serious
it is serious
well it's seriously awesome
it isn't what it is
look at this
new cases 26
look at it
that's not much
what is the time
April
well this is from
is this the whole of covid or is this
this is since early
2020 when it started
so it started out
pretty bad in China
and then they were just like no
there's no covid
yeah but how do you know they aren't
lying and manipulating the data
yeah I guess
that's true
I guess I don't know
because they have
they have an incentive to lie
okay
well question
I guess it comes from official sources
official Chinese sources
there's a potential for them
to like say whatever number they want
do you think
maybe this is naive
do you think though that they could actually do
if they could do that
then why isn't every country doing that
lying about their case numbers
well I do think there's probably a lot of
countries that lie about case numbers
probably not just China
but I think in China
there's scrutiny for them since they
censor a lot of stuff
and you know they have a history of
manipulating data
other countries don't have the same kind of
history or the same kind of reputation
do you think
this graph is
is a
is a big fat lie
maybe it is
I don't know I mean there's no way for me to know
if it's true or not
I can't
to believe that it's been so
perfect but they maybe
have a lot of
mandates and curfews
easily enforceable
yeah
you will not go outside you will be shot
people will obey those sorts of
rules you can't say that in the UK
because people will say you can't shoot us
freedom
we want to just go outside and get COVID
we just want to get it
it certainly seems
plausible that
their kind of government could
you know perhaps achieve this
it's just really their
spotty track record when it comes to
being honest about stuff
that's the kind of
that's the only reason I would doubt
Xi Jinping is
very much like
I need to
look the coolest
I can't be seen to be weak
in any way we are the best
at getting rid of COVID it's plausible
that those lies going on
but I don't know can't tell
well
I just think it's a funny graph look at that shit
look how flat
I mean it'd be nice if it were
real you know I certainly
hope it is
I certainly hope those numbers are real
optimistically
yeah
I'll choose to believe it
oh Bitcoin
Bitcoin's under 60
it's under 60 oh no
it's not going up forever it doesn't
it doesn't only go up
gilf
you better buy some now then
buy during the podcast
gold I'd like to fuck
gold I'd like to
fund
finance
yes
good good
nilf is
wait
nilfs are already a thing
not nilf n
like non
I was trying to say non I'd like to fungible
but like
you know NFT
I was trying to turn it into an NFT
but it doesn't work I know about NFTs
oh yeah I'm getting in
like to fungible token
yeah I'm selling some non fungible tokens
yeah I'm
minting some NFTs
you can buy them on my
you can buy them on my website
they're called road to radcon
the book
it's a book
it's non fungible because it's physically
a real thing
atoms and molecules that make it up
in the real world you can't funge it
you can't do it
exactly
buy one and try to funge it
I have like 50 copies
I have about like 50 something
copies that I might never
sell
probably just gonna sit in a box
in my closet for the foreseeable
future
viewers please buy
the book from me
I don't need 50 copies
you need one copy or more
thank you
but the cover art
on that thing is pretty nice
I know it's so good
Michi's so good
shit rules man
yeah
shit rules
that's why it's my twitter icon
I've had it for my twitter avatar for couple months now
I think
no plans to get rid of it
there's the interior illustration
of me
looks even cooler than the one on the cover
I had to put it in there
along with a bunch of her other sketches
she did a bunch of like sketches
of the characters first and then she went back
and she like made the actual
piece arranged them all in you know
we went back and forth
on like what should Brad look like
what kind of expression
should he have
what sort of face is he making
etc
it's a masterpiece
I put it in
I put it in my pinned tweet
is ordering instructions
I've got a few more
people are buying it like one or two
every day or so
so it's not
I'm surprised
way more people want it
I thought maybe like 20 people
would want to buy a copy that didn't already
get one from the radcon rewards
but no it's probably been like 100
no maybe not 100
it's pretty good
well hopefully
you sent May here a copy right
I did
send May here a copy I put it in the mail yesterday
God forbid
you would have forgotten that
she said
send it to my parents and said okay
I guess I will
what else can I do
you're a man of honor
I'm amazed she still wanted it
honestly
you're a man of honor and integrity
so obviously you're gonna
fulfill any obligations you have
even to your mortal enemies
even to my mortal enemies
yes
we're bound by something
stronger than politics
we're bound by money
a monetary transaction took place
and it must be honored
at any cost
unfortunately
your honor is always stripped
away to zero every time you keep
stealing a scroll
you just can't help it
you have all this honor
you could be such an honorable samurai
but you keep stealing scrolls
I know I can't help myself
I'm a fiend
by the way
you guys probably already talked about
the doid gazers album
have you mentioned that here
we mentioned it
I think so
I haven't heard of an album
the doid gazers album
that was released by
doid gazer himself
was it
yeah that was um
that was uh
that was a while ago right
yeah I think that was quite a while ago
I remember
I remember yeah he made a voicemail
he gave us a voicemail about it I think
he has a twitter account
he made a doid gazers twitter account
I think he has the album
hold on
let me see if I can find it
oh no it's doid gazer
I just posted the album
you know I linked the album
oh there
what do you know
it's uh it's pretty funny
I quite liked it it's already at
over a thousand views which is not bad
for some brand new channel
I just started
I don't see the
the link on the
on the twitter account
uh
wait
oh it's on youtube okay
I thought it was a soundcloud album
yes yes this is just
this must be a collection of the
are these the voicemails
are these the voicemail songs or
hmm
I think
I think these are unique
but I'm not completely sure
Riley commented
did he
he says when you put it all this way
you make some good points
that's so funny
that comment doesn't really make a lot of sense
I don't know what he means
okay I guess
yeah
I quite liked it
and for some reason I was mentioned
in some of the lyrics
really
I guess I'm part of the
doid gazer
why is a stereos here
a stereos in the comments
I don't know what
two days ago
two days ago a stereos
commented
a stereos says avoid the doid
he steals pizzas
I didn't see that
doid gazer responds
and the rumor also my fiance
better than your fiance
oh my god
this guy is sick
this guy is twisted
I assumed these were the same songs
from the voicemails
but if they're new ones
then I guess I gotta listen to them again
oops
I think it might be all new material
because
I don't recognize the voicemails
I heard in any of the songs
and
personally I feel like
they should have included some of the voicemails
in this album
because some of the voicemails
were really good
I really like them
he says special thanks to Tom Oliver
I'm not sure why
I'm not sure what Tom did
something
helpful I guess
he made a 3D avatar
for them
probably
hey
we've been going for about two hours now
speaking of voicemails
what do you think about if we start voicemails
do you think it's about that time
pretty good with that
well let's
let's fucking do it then
let me grab the first one here
the first one
let's go through this
three hours of voicemails
there's not
there's less than one page of voicemails this week
so it should be a pretty normal amount
okay
here's the voicemail and also there's a link
whatever
the voicemail is called read die dark
3, 2, 1, go
yo if you guys haven't already
totally check out the manga die dark
by Q Hayashida
she's most known for like Dora Hedoro
which is had an anime adaptation somewhat recently
but this is her new series
it's fucking cool
everyone in it is like a fucking weirdo
irreverent
sociopath or something
but they're all just kind of
going around space
and there's a funny skeleton robot man
so Gib would probably fucking love that shit
and the artwork's great so check that shit out
okay
does the link show the thing?
here's the link
oh
whoa
that looks pretty cool
that's pretty neat
that's a skeleton astronaut
with a pillar of skeletons
I'm sold
this guy looks like he's
boned
true? true?
boned as in like unfortunate
circumstances that led to
bad things to happen to this character
boned?
possibly
the next voicemail
dude we're boned we're gonna die
that's what I think that means
maybe he already did
next voicemail is an image
there it is
so the next voicemail isn't a voicemail
it's a voicemail
okay
it's a visual mail
it's the f
the f show
I think it's a p maybe it's the
procrastinator show okay so I think this is me and you
we're being showered with money
and then okay
I've wasted my life on studying
could have been a youtuber
good work kid
the government will pay you
I'm gonna study some more
forget youtube
I'll be a scientist
true story compliments please
wait
alright so this character
this orange character
is the voicemailer
true story
he's got fly honey
he's got fly honey sciences bitches now
I'm jealous
if he becomes a scientist
then he can cure covid
that's just that easy
it's just that easy
I don't understand so this purple
character is like ben sain
but specifically from rck or is it actually the
youtuber
ben sain
no I think it's just me
wait you mean the guy giving him the
you pass good work kid
I don't think that's me
I think that's just some government man
it's a shadowy man
in black
it's a government agent
okay so this guy
this guy is working through
he's listening to the procrastinators
podcast and he's just
teaming with jealousy
about all our success
as everyone does all the time
but then
he copes
he's seething but then he copes
the government is paying me
to study
to get a STEM degree
so actually I made the right decision
the thing I don't get about this image
whatever you need to tell yourself
whatever you need to tell yourself kiddo
the thing I don't get about
this image is how could you
watch the procrastinators
podcast in its current state
and then want to become a youtuber
you know
oh cringe
oh come on
man I invite you on the show
and then you do this
you say these things to me you hurt my feelings on purpose
well I'm just
echoing the comments of
no need to no watch
hey I'm just being cool
the procrastinators
podcast is just being
we don't need to do more than that
we're no longer just being
being cool now we're just being
next voicemail
if my
computer will understand
that I am trying to
click on something
please okay
the next voicemail there it is it is called
heartfelt games
three two one
go
the game the game
is this Trixie talking about
an album I think there's an album
called the game
I assume this is from
heartfelt the games
I don't know but I like
I like how short this one is
yeah
that's it's big
voice grail honestly
for a nine second voicemail
no
I felt like the
the games were not actually heartfelt
they sounded sarcastic they sounded like
they were doing a bit and not really
believing what they were saying it
they were doing an
8 bit
you know like an 8 bit game
what the fuck
next voicemail is called
rip doge
or doge
one go
jesus
is this a
I think this is a dr.demento song
we got 16 more seconds
we're gonna make it
got it cool
that was good
it was good but a little bit too long
for my tastes
I could have done it with one verse
but it's okay
is that um
I'm googling
I'm googling dead puppy's song
there is a dr.demento song
there seems to be another one
by
someone else
maybe
Bill Frenzer
has one called dead puppies aren't much fun
I don't know which one it is
whatever
thanks for the voicemail
yeah I think
I believe it's been hijacked
um next voicemail
is uh called
what is it called it is called
oh well um
it's called
www.volareathletic.com
slash ben apparel
uh three two one go
so I just found out about this group chat called
the council of bends
they call themselves the avengers
they sent a link to the merch store
if you are interested
oh yeah
there's just a whole bunch of Ben merch
now you know uh what your new wardrobe
is going to be like
just just just um
it's just a lot of stuff
like this
this doesn't even look good
these logos suck
it's not super great
I don't get it
there's more interesting ways you could do
you could turn Ben into a logo
or put it on merch
it's just like
we designed one thing in illustrator
and that's it
just put it on white t-shirts
did you know that Ben is also the name
of a famous tower in England
whoa
there on the shirt
ah cool
huge fucking Ben
did you know Big Ben is the name of the bell
not the tower
I did know that
oh fuck no
my fun fact wasn't that fun
I always forget it
but uh I know it yeah
um next voicemail
I gotta fucking close all my
fucking windows
I had a friend back in the day
who would constantly make
big Ben jokes
and he really hated it
a friend named Ben I should say
yeah I would
I would hate it too
um next voicemail
is not a voicemail it just says
please make the intro from episode 253
the official intro
um hold on
pro
craston
nader's podcast
what could it possibly be
that wasn't that long ago actually
that was from March
this March
oh yes
link
I can't be bothered to click on google
Jesus
fucking christ
you already had it
yeah I know
okay well yeah no
it would bust that guy that son of a bitch
yeah I mean why not
that's a pretty good one
it's alright it is good honestly
I'm getting sick of the uh
the American girl
parody parody
I've had enough of it
um yeah please
what you should do
is you should start every um
you should start every episode with a different pun
you know nobody has ever done that before
too hard
for me
um
where's my next voicemail
yeah I guess that would require way too much effort
for this uh
too much work
oh wait okay the next one is
get good one piece
and then there's an image link
there's no actual voicemail so here's the image
uh oh
okay yeah
there's 4,000 episodes
no that's 4,000 for Sesame Street
episodes of Sesame Street
didn't know that
so they had they been continually going
since it started
yeah probably
how many fucking seasons is that
I guess seasons is strange
I don't even know when it started
I guess they've been going longer than the Simpsons
no wait
maybe
51 seasons oh my god
51?
69 started
it definitely started before the Simpsons
the Simpsons started in like
1988 I think
yeah
maybe um yeah
close to the 90s
cool well
good good good job
next one is uh
we should marathon Sesame Street and talk about it
we do a
let's watch Sesame Street
a live reaction to every episode
how many
I want to figure out how many
hours that would be
okay next next one is
uh another fucking
thing
another image
okay third world or brain
surgery agriculture
chemistry romance warfare philosophy
seafaring art
first world or brains Pokemon
weed Chris Chan
I
I don't know if this is accurate
so is that supposed to be
me, Trixie and Ben
I
I think it's mage, you, Trixie, me
I don't think about Pokemon
I don't even like it
they got it wrong
wait uh mage is a third worlder
I mean not
I mean the Lithuania is not
Lithuania is not third world
it's it's it's not
like a powerhouse of
of Europe but it's like
she had she had shitty she had
shitty dubs she had shitty anime
dubs
that definitely sounds like
a third world to me I guess
nightmare that's second world
second life
okay yeah true
I don't know
I don't know if this is like supposed to be a serious
point that I feel like I
don't know if I can even
I want to I feel this makes me mad
this makes me want to argue but I don't
even know where to begin
so I think
it's a mage head
mage is always
always going on about
the nuances of chemistry
things on our streams
on our vtuber streams
we probably executed her and that's why
she's no longer on the show anymore
that was a big mistake
if you don't
know anything about Christian
then you can't be part of the
procrastinator's podcast
mmm that's
that's me I'm just always I'm just always
thinking about thinking about Chris
Christian
is the glue that holds this
whole thing together
my fucking
my weird my weird little hair lick
I don't like it I don't like
it okay
next voicemail
is
the where am I
where am I
oh it's janes
here we go found it
oh my god computer
fuck off thank you
okay janes three
two one go
I have an idea for a bonus episode
our taxi
versus squig game
huh
they put the mic so hard
I couldn't hear what they were saying
as she said I have an idea
for a bonus episode odd taxi
versus squid game
well I haven't seen
no I haven't seen either one
I may I may
watch some squid game at some point
it looks mildly interesting
I might give it a chance
I've heard a lot
about squid game
but haven't watched it either
nah here's what you do
here's fucking sesame street
versus squid game
I think sesame street versus squid
I have been
a lot of people have been telling me
to watch odd taxi and I have dug my heels
in and made it a
point of pride no I will never
I will never watch odd
taxi it's a part
of my identity now
Ben is not much of a movie watcher
he doesn't watch movies ever
not really
okay
next one
although I mean we don't know what our next bonus episode
is going to be so we'll have to
think about it
it should probably be more trick
scene and yug stuff right
oh no
those are always the best ones
there's nothing else to say about that
ooh she said I'm transphobic
she said it's transphobia that I don't like her
it's the only reason she can think of
okay that's it
that's all I have to say that's the bonus episode
that's the goss
we just do that for like two or three hours
just see
just cope and seal about it for three hours
ah yeah
next voicemail
is there it is it is called
uh
it's it's
it's like bleep it's like you know
dollar sign
percentage hashtag
ampersand oid gazers
three two one go
hey it's me
rectoid gazes
I look at the butthole
what
rectoid
sure
is that a word
is it is it like
metroid
rectoid
I guess he's talking like
he's combined rectum with void gazers
with doid gazers sure
rectoid okay
I get it I guess
uh by the way I just
want to say sesame street episodes
were one hour long
each really from
1969 to 2015
and then they changed to 30 minutes
really wow that's uh
yeah that's pretty long so
so if I get
44,000 hours
of sesame street content
I don't know
how they can do it that sounds
uh
quite frankly it sounds like torture to me
I think if you want to
terrorize if you want to torture a terrorist
to find out the location of their
secret lair just just play
sesame street for 44,000 hours
so it's something we should
be doing more of is torture
yeah we should do that in one ton
mm-hmm
it'll take me a second to figure out
how many episodes were
pre um changed to 30 minutes
oh
but it's it's it's up there
it's um
next next voicemail is called
ppr pcp public
radio
821 go
yeah I saw that tweet
yes I forgot
before the uh before the uh
before the uh
ben only hates me
because of transphobia thing
she was tweeting about uh
yeah like how mad
how mad she was at her family
for not buying crypto like she told
them to
oh yeah because of that
she's not what an ungrateful
fucking worm yeah
uh what a what a
what a what a
what's the word I'm looking for
they really ruined her life when you think about it
how how fucking
insufferable
imagine having someone
around who who goes like
I'm mad at you
I told you
sees bitcoin go up and they go to you and they go I told you
see I told you you should have bought it
why didn't you listen to me
how fucking despicable
if you had money from bitcoin
you could pay me with it
why didn't you have money
uh yeah I'm
poor but you have money so I
couldn't have I could you know
obviously me tricksy the goal I never
had any opportunity to like have money
that I could maybe have invested in bitcoin
I never it never could have happened
but you had some so you could have
done it I couldn't have done it so uh
you know but you could have done it and why didn't you listen
to me why didn't you do
what I told you to do with your money why didn't you take my financial
advice sleeping on
the fucking I don't even know where she
is right now it's unclear like where
they live
they're being cagey about it well clearly
clearly she's in
I assume I assume they're crashing
on someone's couch or something but I don't know
clearly she's in she's in your head
then
yes rent free rent free
she gets the rent free
housing there so what do I know maybe she's
a financial genius after all
this is so funny
scrolling through the fucking muppet
wickier
lister stress me street episodes
mm-hmm it's just it just keeps
going season one season two
three four five six seven eight nine
what 40
41 season 43
they've got to all be basically the same right
like how many how many
they write so many fucking
I would imagine how many different
they probably even do
yeah yeah
they probably repeated themselves several
thousand times well they
they do they do reuse
like animation animated bits
and skits right like
like an episode of sesame street will have
like recycled content from older episodes
in it I think
so it's I don't think it's all like completely
original content
every episode I don't know I couldn't tell you
I haven't watched it
I've never seen it so I have no idea you never
watched it even as a kid I did watch it
um it
yeah I I've never saw it
I think I must have seen
like a couple episodes when I was
really young because I remember big bird
and grow and Oscar the Grouch
sure but I wasn't like it wasn't like a normal
thing
the normal thing was telly tubbies
and then did they
have a like I was too old
for telly tubbies when it came out so
did they have a weird baby
thing did they have a UK version
of the sesame street over there
no no
they just aired the thing as far as I
understand yeah it's the same show
I'm surprised they didn't just have
the sesame street with like
British accents
no
no that would be
like imagine if they
British Muppets
imagine if they just use the same footage
but they dubbed over it
with British accents
same word the exact same words
is someone with a British accent
same language just
big birds like
grover
me chimney me chimneys on fire
I don't know what a British people say
fish and chips shrimp on the barbie
yeah they like
over like put like acid
wash and air PNG
fucking fish and chips over whatever
they were actually eating in the footage
they just dubbed the names of the food
you know sometimes
with video games
they actually released a different English
version for the UK audience
just to have the different spellings
and stuff they did it with
them with apescape
I know I know they did I know they
did that with apescape they just gave it a different
dub in America and the UK
for some reason yeah did they
I thought I thought the
you know they did the dub of
apescape 2 oh no yeah in apescape 1
I was thinking of apescape 2
because in apescape 2 for some reason
both all of the English
dub is the
the European English British version
I learned I learned that
I learned that fact from you
from your apescape yeah I did I wasn't thinking
of the first game yeah yeah
I remember that video that was a
pretty interesting video
it was it was it was alright
next voicemail
is another
fucking image
okay Nate the type of guy
to point a gun at a civilian
in GTA 5
then puts down the controller
and say I can't do this
wait is this oh this is a
whole album
an all immature album of Nate means
no it's just the one it's just the one
I mean
well he has a type of guy to do that
I get I mean what
do you think so what type of guy does
that I can't do
this I can't I know that the
mean format is like Drake like
Drake the type of guy to do something
like
cringe I guess this
format yeah
okay I have seen yeah I have seen the Drake
version actually
I mean Nate is it yeah
they could never they could never he could
never pull the trigger he could never swing the
bat when the chips are down and you got to
kill that civilian in GTA 5
Nate is a type of guy to never be
on the procrastinator's podcast
that's that's for sure
true though
true next
voicemail is called cheese
three two one
go
okay Ben
I bought me some cheese
and I bought a block of Swiss cheese
from the store
I just kind of suckled on it
it slowly fell apart in my mouth it was
wonderful
what?
that's not how you're supposed to do it
it's kind of gross
yeah
it's almost as gross as putting olive oil
in your ear and then letting all the goo
liquify out and it's
blew just out of your mouth
it's almost as gross as that
medicine is not always
medicine just sometimes is weird
feels good when it's over
what if you poured
I would never do that recreationally
do it for fun
I would deliberately get some ear wax
so I can drip some olive oil in there
satisfying
what if you poured hot cheese down your ear
that would be a
problem
I feel like it would leave your
doesn't it leave the inside of your ear
feeling oily like does it eventually
go away get absorbed by your skin or whatever
nah it just slips out
I mean your skin is oily
yeah I guess so
gross
wait
wait oh the baby bell
I've actually
I bought like so many baby bells
from Costco
I've like mostly eaten them I have a few left
but I've started to kind of hate them
I find them a little bit disgusting now
I've had too many of them and I'm like
I'll try to eat one and I'm like
it's
cheesy gross
I've lost my appetite for them
you're being kind of cheesy right now
I'm being a little ant
I'm being a little anti cheese
and I mean
it's just how it is
I'm spoiled
on it I guess
I'm gonna have to
I'm gonna have to wait
I'm gonna have to wait a while before I get another one
I don't think cheesy Manfredo would
appreciate this Ben
he
he better he doesn't take what he
is given and be thankful
for
next voicemail is called
no context
needed there it is
three two one go
Ben I bet
your fucking boy pussy
would be better than
Trixie's smag glass now
thanks
I don't
say that
I can I can I can I can
hang that's something I can hang my hat on
for sure I can hang that
on the wall that way for him
you put that in my pipe and smoke it
I can put that in my go him
on chain pipe
and smoke it and wax them
samurais with it
next voicemail is called
it is called
where is it here it's called
oh my god please
please it's called
geese are heartless creatures
there it is three two one
go
you ever look at a goose and think
what a vile creature
hmm
you know they're constantly hissing
and honking and those sounds
aren't so pleasant and
you know they got scary teeth
and
evil looking eyes you know
one of them once looked me dead in the
eyes and said
mister you have
you have waving hair
waving goodbye on account
of you going bald
and I felt
that made me very upset
why did it
why did they do this
why did they say that to me I don't
like them they're very rude
why are they so rude
why are geese so rude
I'm sorry that happened
why do we allow
these geese to exist
why don't we just ring them
by the neck and toss them about
you know
rough them up a bit
I don't like geese
what do you think about geese
it sounds like they need to be cancelled
if you ask me
I think
I don't know
I've never had a bad experience
with a goose so
I don't know I'm sorry
I had one long time ago
when I was small enough that they could
be taller than me if they
stretched their neck up
and they charged at me
and I ran
what do you mean they how many
where why
it was a school trip
actually
at some like Roman
thing
there's roman ruins
it's like look at that
you went to Rome
no in England the romes
they came and they conquered
England they put all this roman shit everywhere
so there's like a few roman stuff
like museums and things
sure sure
I remember the trip vividly for some reason
but then at the end
we were getting on the bus to go back
to school and I was just sort of
wandering around
and the geese said how are you gonna be late
you gotta go back to school and they started honking me
and I was like no I don't want to go there
and they nipped
at my heels
fascinating
I've never really had a goose experience
beyond that point
I hear geese can be dangerous at times
sometimes they get violent and they attack you
they sometimes can get aggressive
they can be
I've never heard of anyone being killed by a geese
but it's probably happened
you get your eye bit out if you're an idiot
probably a kid
a kid has been killed by multiple geese
like attacking them at some point
I could totally see that
I remember
there was an episode of Curb Your Enthusiasm
where Larry kills a goose
it was like a pet goose
of the guy who owns a lodge
and the goose
just went up to him while he was playing golf
and started attacking him
so
Larry had a golf club
and he just took a swung at the goose
and the goose died
he took a swing
they got long necks
you know what to aim for
you gotta do
then he had to hatch a plan
to find a way to bury
the body of the goose without
the guy finding out
of course
because if the guy finds out
he'll be banned from the lodge
or whatever he was in
yeah sure
you gotta do
you gotta do Robert Pattinson
in the lighthouse
you see that movie
the lighthouse
he grabs
a seagull
by the neck and he starts swinging it
and just like bashes it against
like a well or something
he just smashes the fuck
out of that seagull
I guess geese are kind of big
it might be kind of hard to do it to a goose
but birds are light
they have little brittle hollow bones
so maybe you could
I could probably lift a goose
you can probably kill one pretty easily
with a golf club
sure
how heavy is a goose
how
I finished the
Sesame Street calculations
yes
after this goose thing
geese are apparently
Canadian geese can be up to like 14 pounds
which is
I mean it's not that
that's quite expensive
it seems like most kind of goose
are about
4 to 6 pounds
up to like 7
but I guess maybe Canadian geese are bigger
that's the most
common kind that I usually see
there should be no problem for you
since you can lift like what
150 pounds now
my bench press
my bench press is coming along
my bench press is 150 now
if I can get it over 155
that was my old
not my old record
but before Covid
I was benching like 155
so if I can get over that
yes I'm strong now
so pretty soon you'll be able to take on geese
and also are
you know Riley in a boxing match
finally
yeah
I think feel like me and Riley
would be
I don't know who would win
I feel like we would both do very badly
in a boxing match
I don't know who would be worse
you need to get strong enough to be able
to penetrate the defensive barrier
of his gun
right
the gun fight
okay funny
May messaged me
after you know Riley said the thing about
the break in never happened
I didn't respond because I don't
want to talk to her
but she DM'd me on Twitter being like
Riley is just trying to start another
gun fight it was the only time
that like you know them
the yig crew has been relevant
and I just think it's really funny
that she group first to her husband
as the gun
it's his gun
that's the gun the titular gun
is your husband why are you calling it that
I guess they're not married but you know what I mean
very funny
I don't know
okay so
Sesame Street yes
there are Sesame Street facts
there is a bunch
I calculated
2017 when they
change to 30 minutes
I mean it was
I did all the mathematics
we have 4,917
hours approximately
of Sesame Street
now dividing that by
if you were to watch it 24 hours straight
204.8 days
straight of watching Sesame Street
which is unrealistic because you can't
stay awake and watch the entire thing
so
let's say the average time to be
awake is like 14 hours per day
you take that
you watch Sesame Street for those entire 14 hours
and you will be done
watching Sesame Street
after 351.2 days
almost an entire
full year
you could do it as your full time
job for a year
and maybe you'd get done watching Sesame Street
14 hours a day yes
I mean that's more than a full time job
that's
double basically because full time is like 8 hours
a day right
yeah and no weekends
so
slave labor conditions
make like I don't know
Quinton Reviews style
Sesame Street review
like the sort of videos
you see like
Jenny Nicholson I watched all of something
yes yes
if you wanted to do that it would take an entire year
at best
think of the views though
think of the views think of the amount of times
you could say I watched all of Sesame Street
so you don't have to
I'm a nostalgia critic
I was gonna say you'd probably be like the only person
ever but that's probably not true
probably someone somewhere
honest
I don't know I mean it's been on since the 60's
all of the kids
wouldn't have kept watching it
all of the kids are dead now
that used to watch it back then
I'm sure there's one
there's at least one kid who is autistic
enough to watch the entire thing
that's what I was gonna say yeah I could believe
that there was maybe some kid who was like
who was profoundly autistic or something
he liked Sesame Street a lot
and he just never stopped watching it
even now
I could believe
I need psychopedic knowledge
they should make a youtube video about it
he even goes out of his way to watch all the episodes
he missed
finding them wherever he can online
he DVRs them
yeah
next voicemail
we've only got a few more
I think
oh yeah there's only two more
the next one is called
my
computer
why does it do this
it's when I click a file until I click and drag it
sometimes it just stops
understanding what I'm trying to do and then I have to click a different window
I don't know what's going on with my UI
lately
right
it's called my revenge
three two one go
hey man
last week you called me a fucking idiot
because my voicemails are too quiet
well
what I have to say to that
in response is
am I loud enough for you now
is this what you wanted
yeah thank you
yes thank you
that was a good say
towards the end there kind of sounded
like an ego raptor impression
hmm
maybe
maybe a little bit
oh
this is um
this is not really relevant to anything
but I guess it's funny enough that I could mention it
I had to explain
the PCP
to two of my roommates yesterday
they know
they now know that I am a
YouTube podcaster
so that's cringe
that's horrible
I know
I know please give me condolences
I was walking home
from the printer
I had just gone to the printer to get the second batch
of road to rad cons
printed and I had the box
and I was walking and one of the guys
he was sitting outside
like sketching something in a sketchbook
and I asked him hey
what's your sketch and he showed me
and he was like what you got there
and I was like well
I had to explain
what road to radcon is
which entailed
talking about the PCP
and stuff and then I came inside
and another guy was inside and he also was like
hey what you got there and I was like
well gotta tell you about it
he asked me like what's the podcast
you don't have to explain everything
well yeah he asked me about it
he asked me to explain so what am I gonna say
no if you want to know all this
I'll tell you
he's a P on YouTube he saw my little icon
he said congratulations
for me because he saw that I'm almost at
20k subscribers
which is pretty cool I guess
he thought that was neat and I said no
it's embarrassing no it's a stupid no
I hate myself no please kill me
and this charade please
and then he was like
gladly
yeah
and he cut out his glock and he shot
ok alright
so that was
that was funny
alright last
last voicemail
it is called
it is called ideas 5 months
late
3 2 1 go
back in episode 261
Ben said why schedule protests
what do protests do if they don't disrupt anything
and for a bit of a nitpick schedule protests
still close down roads and make people take
alternate ways around town
for some people
you're probably not being put in a protest cage
in the middle of nowhere but the broader idea
I'd like to discuss is how should protests
be tackled in an ideal world
not all protests are for good movements like
civil rights, trans rights, BLM pro-units etc
there's anti-abortion, anti-lockdown
and anti-democratic stuff too
should the rest of society allow these to be
unrestricted disrupting large parts
of society because 1% of the population
thinks vaccines will make them sterile
hmm
well it's simple
the stupid protests
should be destroyed
ban them, ban the ones that are bad
and
fund the ones that are good
cops are good when they're
when they're cracking down on
people that I don't like
um
I think
well I mean uh jeez
I guess people should be
allowed to protest
even things that are bad
I guess I wouldn't say no they can't do that
uh
yeah you just count a protest
with another
bunch of people
the same argument people use about
freedom of speech and stuff like that
well freedom of speech is good
actually
uh
you know I meant
there's like the mayoral race
going on in Boston right now
and um
one of the contenders
who I think just got endorsed by
the Boston Globe
which I think is kind of a big deal
uh
Michelle Wu is uh
I don't know if she's the frontrunner or what
but I met her
I literally met her outside of the
Boba Tea place
no it was the Waffle Pop
place that I went with
munchie and kazi a couple times
and
she was just standing out there with like a little entourage
handing out cards
and she asked me like hey
what would you like me to do
as mayor and I was like
uh hey remember that
straight pride protest that they approved
uh don't do that anymore
and she was like
yeah okay that was dumb
uh
so if she becomes mayor
and then and banned
straight pride parades it was my fault
I did it
uh
yeah so what was I
what was I even talking about
um
you were just saying before that
you would allow all parades now you're saying
you want certain ones not to be allowed
it's not okay the thing
about the straight pride parade is that it was not
merely allowed that it was like
official like it was like
the cops showed up to like
they cordoned off a parade route for it
and the cops were there
to escort
it and keep
people from
fucking them up
yeah it's
a movement that doesn't
really warrant a parade because
it's only
a backlash against gay pride
like you wouldn't do a parade
unless you were trying to
make a statement
yes true but
I guess a parade is not the same thing as a protest
I would I mean
if like I wouldn't say like they're not
allowed to like drive their float
down the street or whatever like they have the same right
to drive a truck down the road
as anyone else but like it's different when it's like
okay this is an official thing
like the city is like announcing that it's an event
we've given you like an official police
escort like that's not
that's not freedom of speech
that's like
you know that's
the government endorsing it
basically the local government
is getting involved it's like
state sanctioned stuff
like imagine like an
lgb parade
right without the t
deliberately and that's the
it's like oh it's like this is
the face of the
you know the city or the mayor or whatever
it's like this is what they're allowing
pretty much pretty much
without the t that sounds like
then saint to me
what
you're saying that I'm lesbian gay bisexual
I'm saying you're you're you're saying
you're on t
got it
somebody else
spider if you're
you call spider on twitter called me low t
because
because I told him my lifts
I told him my lift numbers and he wasn't
super he wasn't impressed
okay it's true though
I am it's you're also
you're also anti-t though
you know as far as trans
is concerned because
remember Trixie
what you said yeah
I remember I remember
I remember it like it was only yesterday
when she said I'm a girl now and I said well
I hate you for that reason and that was
that was what happened
that's how I remember it
you're both low t and anti-t
yes true
my two favorite things about me
anyway
protest I mean
fucking
well shit I think
I think people's
to be effective a protest needs to be disruptive
and yeah I think that even that
goes for things I don't like
like if fucking anti-vaxxers want to have a protest
and they want to block roads to make a statement
like
I mean I guess they should have the same
protection the same legal
protection to do that as anyone else
I mean you know
yeah I would
yeah they have the right to do it
because it's like it only
takes a change of government to make it
so that now you can't protest
you know if you couldn't protest one thing
before yeah then it'll be
it'll come back
and then I mean
I mean you might the reverse
you can't protest leftist things that would be bad
so like
just blanket allow
I think so you might get arrested
like sometimes in the
course of protest like if you block traffic on a road
like that's illegal you know you might get arrested
or something if you
you know
and that's okay
it's fine
people know that that's going to happen and they do it
they can cause a scene and they're taking
the being in prison
for a little bit it's part of
the jail if the argument is
should we allow protests then obviously
yeah we should
right
was there anything else to this question I feel like
well he was asking how should they be handled ideally
I don't really know
what else to say about it though
you know I remember years ago I got into
kind of a small argument
on AOL
instant messenger
with someone about protests
this was back in
2003 when Wind Waker
had come out
and I was arguing
with someone from the UK
and
I wasn't really arguing
he got real mad I wasn't
and I think I told him
he wanted to protest the wars
that were going on
so he was attending local protests
and
I said I agree with this position
I was also against these wars
but I kind of told him
I don't think the protest you're going to
is going to do much good because
in general when
governments invade countries they don't
really pay a whole lot of attention to protesting
and he got really
he got really offended by that
and I wasn't trying to
offend him or anything
but he got so offended by that
he basically blocked me for like
10 years after that
oh jeez
I mean
I guess you're right
individual actions are weak
and like a single protest
isn't going to stop the war
I mean
I don't know much about
the actual validity of those things
I know there was a lot of war protests
and
with every war
there's been a bunch of people saying
stop it
a bunch of damn beatnik hippies going
don't stop killing people
how dare they tell the United States
government to stop killing people
don't they know the United States government
is literally neurodivergent and a minor
yeah exactly
I mean it's
it's a new country
but I think there was a lot more
opposition to these wars than
maybe some wars in the past
they were not very popular
they were not very popular wars
that's
I don't okay
they were
they were kind of popular
people were
largely pretty okay
well I mean obviously not everybody
but there was a lot of
people who were like yeah
we're mad about 9-11
we gotta do some war
but there's always
people who are into it and not into it
but I think in general these wars
they kind of got compared to like
Vietnam
Vietnam was not a very popular war
a lot of people hated it
a lot of people were against it
so I kind of think this is
similar situation
but
I just thought that
in general protests don't
have much effect on
stuff like war
they tend to have bigger effects on
other smaller issues
but when it comes to like
big issues like war
they unfortunately don't seem to have
almost any effect
which sucks
I don't know I mean
I think you're kind of correct
but it's just sort of like
it doesn't really matter
that they're not effective
because in aggregate
like many people protesting about the war
will
at the very least
influence the politicians
in a way that they're like
oh if I want to get votes
I can't be pro-war
and then they'll try not to do
war stuff so much
Vietnam was not popular
everybody was like stop
Vietnam
and we eventually just kind of did
we just kind of gave up on Vietnam
because we weren't
and like
so many Americans
it was unpopular and people were
protesting it and everyone
popular opinion was just like this war is bad
and we shouldn't be doing it
and eventually we did stop
right?
the fact that it was publicly unpopular
I think might have been part of
why it stopped
it might have just kept going
that's basically what happened with Afghanistan
I guess
unfortunately with Afghanistan it took like 20 years
it took so fucking long
oh my god
it took so long because they had a lot
of money
from the oil they were getting
at some point
no no the US
and the UK
there was money in it to stay in it
but I think
protesting
and they seem to have convinced
people
in a large enough amount that it's
okay and good
that we're over there still
people grumbled about it but they didn't really change
their vote too much
yep
it was just
it was like
people didn't even really talk about it like it was
a war
it was just kind of like we're there
and that's just how it is
and like it was
it was called the war in Afghanistan
and people
but people didn't really talk about it like it was a war
it's just
kind of like a thing
they did call it the war on terror
for a while I guess
for a while
do you like terror
what are you pro terror
you crazy
that's a halloween
neurodivergent and a minor
protesting is cool
I used to support protesting
it doesn't change anything
but I guess I'm just really cynical
about it sometimes
people do those
petitions on change.org
whatever they collect signatures
and sometimes
it doesn't change anything
yeah I mean
true
I think that even though
it seems
fruitless
a good argument for not doing it
that's true
except for maybe a waste of time
it doesn't make
the war last longer to go protest about it
I don't know
I don't know if you want
I don't fucking know
whatever
good for him for wanting to
make a statement
like I said I supported
his stance on it
cause he was basically trying
to get me to go to
protests and stuff
you should look up local protests in your area
and I was like
I'm not gonna do that
I just said
I'm just gonna play wind waker
it just came out
bro wind waker just came out
I'm a wall
I'm not
emotionally available for that
exactly so
they didn't sit well with him
so he blocked me
he just didn't like wind waker
he was like fuck no
he looks so cartoony
they copied it from the little prince
in the seven headed dragon
the eight headed dragon
he looks like the same guy
but they made him
you can go out there
you can go out there and protest
and I'll provide you moral support
while I play wind waker
I'll send you my thoughts
and prayers
okay that was the last voicemail
I'm reloading to see
what
there's a new
nope we got one
we got a last minute voicemail
why would you reload
I don't know
but I did
it's called
the blue glow skull monkeys
one hour 17 minutes 23 seconds
okay
three two one go
I just realized
that there is a lecture I could give
and I would be able to go into a lot of detail
and present a lot of interesting information
but nobody would want it
at all
it would be the least wanted lecture
of all time
and it would be the brony community
well I'll tell you what
I wouldn't fucking watch that lecture
I know
why did I say that
why did I say I wouldn't watch it
I had to be joking
because I definitely would
I could not
what was I thinking
when the whole brony
lecture thing first happened
and Trixie decided not to release it
at first
on a personal level I didn't care that much
because I was never really into the brony
stuff
but then I saw you
talk to someone on twitter about it
and someone said
why don't you do a lecture on the pcp
history
and then you responded well that's basically what the brony
lecture was
a lot of it was
so when I saw that
then I thought well darn
now I actually want to watch
the brony lecture
it was like
a lecture about the brony culture
from the lens
of the horseshoe crew
and how we all met in all of our history together
a lot of it was focused on
on us
as a part of the
brony
I am actually pretty bummed out
that I can't watch that lecture
I know
man I know
for the record I'll say it again
I don't agree
with the decision not to release it
but that's not like
I think some people
think that's like the one thing
that's the straw that broke the camel's back
that made me like
I hate Trixie now
that was just one
little thing that was like bad
but it wasn't like
it's not the main thing
it's
the attitude
towards the people who
paid for
Radcom and other things
it's literally just because
she's trans
it's literally
the hot clipped
it's the thing
when I think about
what made me
not like Trixie anymore
it's things that she said to me
I can't believe you would treat me this way
I can't believe you would say that to me
and mean it
terrible
I remember those big money connections
the big money connections
and like oh Ben
you don't get to use my big money connections anymore
fuck you
and the time that I got mad at May
for being a Nazi
message me to be like you're just jealous that I get laid
Ben
you're just jealous that I get to have sex with my Nazi year old friend
and you don't
those are the two big ones
very funny
I don't
agree with a lot of
stuff that she's done
but
I kind of feel like a cyber shell
on this kind of thing where I personally
don't like hate her
or dislike her
well you know
my issues with her are completely personal
so it's not like I expect everybody else
yeah I think you're completely justified
in hating her
but
she's never done anything against me
so I don't have
any personal justification
first they came for the Ben Saints
yeah first they came for Ben St
and I said nothing because I was not
Ben St and then I looked
and Ben St was gone
no
I miss him I loved him so much
why didn't I save him
the only slight thing
she kind of did is that
for me anyways
she didn't give me the ransom I paid for
but I don't really care about that
that's pretty irritating
that's pretty annoying
that would be enough for me
I don't think that was like
her intention I don't think she maliciously
did that I think she just forgot
that's
I mean
forgetting is still bad
that's just
people pay you
to do some things
I didn't mean to rip people off
I just didn't mean to take the money and run
I just did it though
I do think it's irresponsible
but I just don't care enough
to make a big deal about it
I understand not caring to follow her up
but it's not okay
that she was irresponsible
yeah I'm not saying it's okay
I'm just saying that I'm not upset about it
even though I could be
maybe I should be but
yeah
that's fine I get it
I mean what is it like 15 bucks or something
it's not much
in question here
so fucking much
I could do anything for $15
I imagine
I mean for the
for the product
of a short little rant about whatever
even if you don't know what it is
yeah this thing
whatever it sucks and it's like 15 bucks
for that
I didn't actually watch it lol
she was making quite a lot of money
from those rants
honestly she shouldn't have stopped doing that
she should have continued
because
it seemed like it was working
it seemed like it was working pretty well
for a while there
I think she stopped because she was getting too many of them
and she couldn't like do all of them
or was taking too much of her
time from other stuff
but I feel like there would have been
a fairly simple way to solve that
problem which is
you just limit the amount of people
who can be at that tier
well you could do that or you could increase the amount
of money that it costs
and that way less people would
buy rants
and that would make more money per rant
yeah
if the demand
is exceeding the supply
you raise the price
and then you're going to lower the demand automatically
you would still make money
but you wouldn't have to do as many rants
so I don't know why she just stopped entirely
that seems like a really stupid business decision
but
yeah
I mean
it only takes a few minutes
and she's making you know
yeah you just got to price it so that like
if the amount you're charging
is like a worthwhile amount
for the time that it takes you to do it
and I don't see why
yeah like then more is just good
like more is just good as long as it's worth
as long as the return on what you're doing
is positive
I mean if I could
make money that way
I would never stop
that's for sure
just so
I guess bizarre to think
the people in large enough quantities
that she couldn't keep up
would be willing to pay
$15
every month
to support her but also for rants
that was so
like the amount of like
goodwill and like
fandom that she had at her disposal
is unfathomable
compared to where we are right now
it's pretty
it's pretty starting
it sucks that she was so like
disrespectful towards her fans
and kind of like
didn't treat them very well because they were
real nice to her and they supported her a lot
you know
much too nice
I don't respect it
I don't respect Trixie fandom
or Digi Bro fandom in 2021
I don't respect it anymore
I don't know if there's much left
of it has vanished
yeah
what are we talking about
why are we talking about this
we've been over this
we've
this is all well trodden
this is what the people want
you know most people
there were a few people that
pledged for the one month
and then unpledged
from the bonus episodes
pledged stuck around
are still patrons
as of this month
so I mean I'm very happy
about that
mean the pcp patreon
yes that's what I'm talking about
because we got the big bump
when I released those last three episodes
including the cyber shell
goss one
yes thank you
I hope you enjoyed the fun
patrons I hope you
enjoyed the fun fact challenge
post your fun facts down below
if you got them
next time you should do
unfun facts
depressing facts
no I don't know
did you know the ear
you put oil in it
this is what happens with the ear
some day you're going to get
crippling arthritis and all your bones were hurt
yeah
I drink my milk
I'm there man I'm there
I'm in
sign me up
a couple weeks ago I had the episode about
broken back so my back was bothering me
pleased to report that my back is pretty much
fine it doesn't really bother me
anymore hardly at all so I think
I think I just had to
I think I was aggravating it by like
twisting my back I was trying to crack
my back because it gave me like a
temporary feeling of relief
I was like twisting myself so far
that I was like pulling the muscle and like
causing it
injury so we just like stopped doing
that even though I wanted to
and it kind of just
it kind of went away so I think that was
the problem I was
I think if you
you work out and strengthen your muscles
properly you can kind of reduce the likelihood
of back pain and stuff
but if you work out
you can cause back pain so you gotta
be careful
people say oh
deadlifts are dangerous you'll hurt your back
and like well it's possible
but also if you don't
lift and you don't exercise
and you don't keep your back muscles
strong then you
that is
then you are much more likely to have back
problems because you are weak
and your body is
decrepit
so it's really damned if you do damned
if you don't
anything else on the docket
for today before we close
just a reminder
the Clarissa Gunsmoke
and the bandit king comic
go to gibbentake.site to read it
you wanna read it
cause it's great and it's good
post your theories
post theories
post theories about what's up with that hat
what the fuck's up with that shit
what's going on with that
make a cow
sona
a cow sona
mean a cow boy sona
well it could be a cow girl sona
that's why I stopped
cow person sona
but not furry
I said I wasn't gonna crack my back anymore
but I just did it
go to gamerstavern.com
if you wanna read a review
on front mission gun hazard
for some reason
yeah I kinda do actually
I might actually read that one
just because I'm
I think it's weird
I think it's really weird that they made that game
go to youtube.com
gamers tavern show to watch
videos with puns in them
all the videos contain puns usually
true
you can follow me on twitter
at gamer tavern
without the s in the middle
mmm
speakpipe.com
if you want to leave
a voicemail
you know who else takes voicemails now
anamorphentime
the anamorphentime podcast
I believe they also have a speakpipe
where you can send them voicemails
speakpipe will like fill up
I told Tyler
he asked me how to set up a speakpipe
or he asked me how we did voicemails
and I told him about speakpipe and I said
it says there's a 100 megabyte limit
but there's not
you can just go over it and
they won't stop you
and he was like cool
how they're gonna stop you
they're gonna send cops to bust down your door
you need to get a warrant first
I think they would
you would
all that happens when you exceed it
is they add a button that says
action required add more storage
and it's like you're gonna need to add more storage
if you're gonna want to keep getting voicemails
do you want to pay us money
to upgrade your account
but if you don't press the button
they don't actually stop you
they're gonna figure that out
you would think they would have figured it out
I think they must know
this is a very obvious loophole
in their system
this can't be an accident
is this like the windrower thing
where the creator knows
how easy it is to crack the software
I don't know
you can just use it
without needing to buy it
if you want to get past the warning
maybe
I have no idea why it's like this
but it is
and it seems like they must know
there's no way that they aren't aware
of this
I can't explain it
patreon.com
become a patron give us money
free fun fact challenge
et cetera
I guess that's it
any final last words
before we wrap up
uh...
that's what I'm doing
the lord of ghosts
lord of ghosts also
someone pointed out
that by accident
I accidentally did something spooky
for spooky month
because I've spent much of october drawing
the lord of ghosts
it was
sharker bob
at least drawing a comic about a ghost
is on theme for the month
damn it
damn it if he isn't right
yes
okay that's it happy halloween
everypony
bye
we didn't even mention
wait this is gonna
it's gonna be like two days
two days before halloween
happy happy that
okay bye
goodbye