Hello everyone, and welcome back to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm
the best guy ever, and we're joined by Gibbontake, and Ben Saint. There he goes. Truly hilarious.
The joke police are here. They're not lovin' it. They're not lovin' it.
Hey, I'm peacefully whoop whoopin' over here. I'm peacefully whoop whoopin'.
Is that like a personal attack or something?
You're beating me with batons.
No, my scholarship!
Alright, let's cut right to the chase. Listen, I have an announcement to make. There's been a change in my life.
This is an important one. This is probably the biggest paradigm shift in the last five to ten years of my life.
Alright, it goes by a singular name, and that name is Drakengard III, Kuroi Hana, 100% Shower Speed Runs.
That's the summary. I will now elaborate on the subject matter.
Please.
Yes, so there's the song. It's the final battle boss song in Drakengard III.
Wait, wait, create demand and then fulfill it.
Indeed, indeed.
Drakengard III final boss song in Branch D.
Last thing, you fight a big demon flower boss with a bunch of ladies in it.
The song plays called Kuroi Hana.
I have become the hero, the founder, organizer, chief executive of the speedrunning community around showering while listening to this song
and attempting to beat speedrun strats at various percentile categories to take your shower as fast as possible.
Yes, that's right. Why is a video game song have to be linked to taking a shower in any way?
Why not just do it with a timer? Fuck you, it doesn't matter. This is just how it works.
This is the community, and if you don't like it, then you can just leave.
So here's the deal. Let me break it down for you.
There are seven tiers of success that you can reach in an average speedrun of the Kuroi Hana 100% or any percent runs.
Let me just say right out the back, any percent runs, literal trash, if you do them, kill yourself.
Don't do it. It's a mistake.
Hold on. Set the foundation for this. Why would you want to take a shower at a specific amount of time?
Why would anyone want to speedrun anything?
Is it good to have a short shower? Is that where this came from?
Absolutely.
Is it safe water? Is it for the environment?
The origin of it was simply I was listening to Kuroi Hana in the shower, because it's like an almost an eight minute long song.
So it's good and long. It's plenty of time to shower and stuff.
And I was like, I could be efficient about this.
And I got into a pattern of listening to the song every time.
I understand.
So here's how the lore breaks down.
So during the boss fight, in this climactic moment of Dragon Guard 3, basically the song is slash the boss itself.
You play as a dragon Mikhail fighting against this big flower thing, the Intoners or whatever.
So there's six Intoner girls.
And each of them, in fact, you guys should just take a look at the aesthetic of this fight just to get an idea for it.
There will be links in the show notes to this.
Here you to take a peek at this. Just skip in like a few minutes in or whatever.
So these big white girls who you have known, I mean, they're literally white, they're like stone.
They've been like your main character and the other bosses basically of the game.
But now they appear bursting out of the petals of this flower, which is kind of the source of all issues in the game.
So it's broken down into seven chunks.
The first chunk is with zero.
And then it goes five, four, three, two, one.
And then finally all of them together.
So we call these categories getting a one or a five or a four or three or a two or a one or or the shame.
We'll shame for all of 15.
All right.
So getting a zero category is the Holy Grail.
No one's ever done it.
That's an under one minute and 35 second category.
Can it be achieved?
Scholars still speculate to this day.
We think obviously the optimal strats are going to be had because running doing an average run requires, of course,
shampooing, conditioning, full body soaping.
You have to get the full body coverage.
There can be no skipping.
That's what makes it 100% run.
Oh, and just so everybody knows the rules of the game where the time is concerned.
Timer starts when you get into the shower.
So you're dry at first.
You then get wet in the shower and the timer stops when you turn off the water.
Toweling.
Some people include it in their categories.
Not I.
It is not part of the speed run.
There you go.
That's the facts.
So you get under a one minute and 35.
That's the Holy Grail zero.
You get under a two minute and 13 second.
It's a fiver.
Then two minute 59, three minutes and 40 seconds, four minutes and 20 seconds.
That's for 20 very based.
And then a winner is five minutes and six seconds.
Anything beyond that, you're in the 15 category.
It's absolutely embarrassing.
So I have taken the liberty of doing several runs and I'll tell you my scores right now.
Over the last week, my, my original personal best here was a four minute and 34 second.
That's a one or not great, not great.
Then I was, I was able to achieve a three minute and 15 second run.
And so far that's my best.
Solid three year and I'm hoping to bag a four on my next run.
And you will see, by the way, if you look, click at the links down below, the rules will be posted.
This will be our central hub.
This link to this video, because this is a community activity.
This is the song that is being used seven minutes, 56 seconds long.
You will see my comment as best guy ever under there describing my 100% personal best of three minutes, 15 seconds.
And I want to see other people flooding this comment section with their 100% speed runs to see who will be the fastest shower Kuro black flower boy.
There you go.
So there's the challenge that's been thrown down.
We're going to operate on an honor system until money gets involved.
And then we'll get in contact, of course, with AGDQ.
We'll get some on camera runs done right now.
Community.
We're just, we're hoping to grow.
So we want more people to join the community and see what people are able to achieve.
You know, everyone's going to be lined up in the men's locker room.
So that's pretty good.
Now we can't.
Unfortunately, it's true.
We can't ignore biology.
Small people have less surface area to cover.
They have an unfair advantage, but that's just life.
But they also have smaller brains.
That's true.
They probably won't be able to optimize as much.
It just means we're able to use our instincts better.
It's true.
And you know what?
Oh, right, right.
And also, you know, a large discussion was had about what about people shaving their head and going bald to optimize these strats.
It was concluded that you must have hair and a separate category has been created for bald individuals.
It's only fair.
This is the most contentious decision yet.
That is contentious.
I don't know.
I feel like no hair, short hair, and long hair are like...
I feel like there's a middle ground there.
There should be categories for each of these.
I feel like if you wanted, you could split it.
I think for each category of hair, you have to trim it to the exact designated length.
You're going to have to...
It's going to be...
It goes to the higher...
Well, I think what it's got to be is weight categories.
And if you're in a weight category, you are going to want to trim to the shortest possible length for your weight category, anything else in your suboptimal.
Actually, there's also size categories.
So you have to submit a full body plaster print of your entire body for the judges to measure to gauge how much surface area they have to cover during the shower.
I would actually suggest...
Okay, what you need to do is fully fill your bathtub up, immerse yourself in the bathtub, measure the displaced water, and give a volume measurement of yourself by measuring the displaced water, and base the categories on that.
What is the opinion on glitch runs?
I've managed to do a glitch where I can skip through the water and I don't even have to get wet.
This is a glitchless run.
I'm running glitchless.
It's the most popular category because one person is doing it me and I'm winning so far.
The glitch runs, they're just a separate category.
You just don't turn on the shower, you win.
Yeah, pretty much.
That's why any percent runs are such a joke.
You walk in, you touch water for literally...
It's measured in microseconds.
You just touch the water in the shower and then immediately clip out of the wall and hit the timer stop.
It's not good.
It just doesn't make for a very compelling run, is all.
I'm trying to think of holes I can poke in this in the name of glitch testing.
In the name of stress testing the concept.
It has been discussed.
I mean, do you have to shampoo and condition your pubic hair as well?
What about arm, leg, and back hair?
What about your eyelashes?
Taking under advisement.
Eyelashes, taking under advisement.
Only hair on your head.
Right now.
Do you have to condition?
Actually, do you have to shampoo?
Yes, you have to condition.
You have to shampoo and condition.
These are in the rules.
There was also, of course, discussion about what's the correct order of operations.
Should it be enforced by the rules that you have to shampoo, then condition, leave the conditioner in your hair?
And then soap, and then washed all out afterward.
It was decided no, you can do it in any order, but you should do it that way, or you're an idiot without proper hygiene.
But that's another factor.
I mean, if I want to win the speed run, the hygiene is the least of my worries.
I just want to get it handled on as fast as possible.
There's been no bonus found.
There's been no bonus found in doing it in any particular order, so you might as well do it.
It gives you the luxurious hair.
See, we've thought about that.
Nobody said I need to get the shampoo and conditioner out of my hair.
If I just get the water on and then put the shower and just turn the water off, put the stuff on afterwards.
I'll tell you what's really split in the community right now, though.
The two-in-one shampoo and conditioner products that are so popular these days.
That seems like a no-brainer.
Absolutely tearing the community apart as to whether or not it's allowed.
What about one of those six-in-one conditioner shampoo, moisturizer, body wash, whatever?
That seems like such an obvious tech for the run.
You're obviously right.
The thing is, though, that gets into the core discussion about what is the spirit of the event meant to be.
It goes beyond simply, like, there has to be discussions about that.
I feel like it's perfectly within the spirit.
Because if that product really does do all those things, then, like...
Yeah.
Which raises the question, why doesn't everyone just use it normally under normal circumstances?
There's also the question of outside tools.
Like, for example, could I simply step into the shower, turn in the water, pull a lever to dump a bucket I have prepared with massive quantities of all-in-one body wash shampoo and conditioner?
Have it completely blast over my body in two seconds and then wash it off.
We've got to standardize the shower head, the brand.
Right.
That too.
What if you technically have the...
Now you have the shower head on, but you leave the drain closed, causing the tub to fill as though it were a bath, and you actually jump into the bathtub and roll around in it to get yourself wetter faster.
That's because you do have to get fully desoped at the end, too.
That might be a more optimal strat.
The clog at the end might be an advantage.
Actually, I think that would probably make washing your feet and getting the soap off your feet more difficult.
I don't know if that would actually save any time, but you know, you've got to exhaust all possibilities.
You might lose a few frames at the end if you have to step out and then wipe the soap off and you can't just do it in the shower itself.
You could lose frames there, yeah.
Definitely.
Damn, this is a rich meta has evolved.
I want to hear people give details on your strats.
Let's see who is doing the best next week.
I will be looking at the comment section of that video.
I want to be flooded and be able to be deeply confused as to what's going on on this video.
It's got 4 million views.
They've had their time.
It's our time now.
I think at first, I was hearing you talk and I was like, what is this?
This is bizarre.
This is a strange and esoteric ritual.
This is some kind of death cult.
But now I'm fully invested and fully on board and it makes perfect sense and even a child could understand it.
What's the community's opinion on Nightcore and or Vaporwave renditions of the song?
I forgot this was about a song.
Wait a minute, what's even the point of the song?
Ben, we already covered that at the beginning.
It doesn't matter.
It's the spirit of the event.
It is totally arbitrary.
It gives us fun categorizations to use.
Seven tiers.
Which tier are you?
I'm tier...
Wait, what tier am I?
I think I'm tier 3.
I'm no more tiers.
I'm tier 4.
Which is shameful.
No more tiers.
That was good.
Incidentally, no more tier shampoo.
Up banned.
You have to deal with the tiers.
Extra tiers.
Extra tiers is the only approved shampoo.
What if you just shampoo with a fucking bar soap?
Actually, I would liquid soap versus bar soap.
Lufa or no Lufa?
These are allowed.
I'm sure they're allowed.
I was assuming they were allowed but I would want to know which one.
I guess you just have to experiment.
I've been a bar man.
When you got the bar, you don't have to pump the thing to prep the Lufa which might lose
time.
You don't have to wait for the bar to soften under the hot water.
I feel like the liquid soap spreads faster.
I feel like Lufa is probably a time sink.
That's going to be allowable.
I shouldn't be in the sink in the first place.
What about Lufa on a stick that lets you save the frames of bending over to reach your
soap on a rope?
That could make sense.
Time saver?
I don't know.
I don't know what it's for in the first place.
Really makes you think.
Just optimize your shower, bro.
That's the point.
But to this very specific song from Dragon Guard 3.
The real lesson, the real high level is you get out of the shower.
You break your PR.
One day you get a new PB in your category.
And then you realize, wait a minute.
Why don't I do this with every single thing I do every fucking day with the same song?
Playing the song at all times to optimize.
Every time you finish anything and start any new thing, you smack the timer like you're
playing speed chess and you just start the song and you go.
Was I a 3-year?
Was I a 1-year?
Was I a shameful 15-year?
Eating, eating, cooking breakfast.
Here's the deplor.
Eating breakfast.
Driving to work.
Yeah, absolutely.
Raising child.
Bonding with family.
Just as optimal as possible.
Why aren't we bonding by playing Dragon Guard 3 and beating the final boss as fast as possible?
It's a 15er, by the way, because you're fighting all of the intoners at once.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1, and 0.
The total of which is 15.
There's some deplor for you.
Summoning salts.
Your next video.
I expect to see the history of Castlevania.
Stop.
Mario Kart.
No fucking punch outs.
Cease.
This is the one.
We've got a story history.
We are going to be at HQ.
We're going to win.
We're going to do a silly one at the end.
If we hit $10 million raised for whatever the fuck, then we'll be doing actually beating the boss in Dragon Guard 3 while showering, doing both at the same time.
That's the equivalent of the blindfolded.
Yeah.
You've got to optimize your strat to avoid it being destroyed by the water.
You've got to dodge the shower droplets.
The individual droplets, yeah.
So there it is.
The category is exploding.
Okay, good thinking.
There it is.
Boy, that really got my noodle going.
We were talking about this on the stream the other day, and it is now real. It's official.
Please join in.
We await your comments on that video that I don't own.
What, on Twitch?
No, this is the official Dragon Guard 3 song that is being used as the hub for all these things.
Got it.
Man, oh man, you think you know a video game.
Think you know a person.
Think you know a person, and then they tell you, hey, I just beat my PB in this.
Whatever, the Kuroi Hana.
Man, I thought you were a fiver, and they say, no dude, I'm a threer.
I'm a fourer.
I'm a oneer.
Actually, oneer's bad.
I'm a threeper.
Wait, a threeper.
Is that a thing?
It goes, zero is best, then five, four, three, two, one, fifteen.
I feel like there's something else that's called a threeper, but I don't know what that is.
That's a creeper, Ben. That's Minecraft.
No, it's like, is that like a name for like a hillbilly from Michigan or something?
No, that's Uper.
What's a threeper?
Damn it.
Okay, let me know in the comments.
Urban dictionary?
Urban dictionary.
Yep, yep, here we go, here we go.
Let me see.
I see a threeper, which is probably like a $3 bill.
I don't know.
Did I only dream that threeper?
A threeper is getting three things for the value of one.
Not a threeper.
Those shirts are a threeper.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't know.
Okay.
Well, that's it, lads.
That's my story.
Great.
I'm sticking to it.
Where's yours?
We've all grown on the stream or on this podcast.
No, no, no.
You haven't grown until the holy grail is hitting that zero tier.
You have to be, I know it can be done.
I know that a sub one minute, 35 second run is possible.
Someone out there do it.
Yeah.
But we need, don't forget, full body coverage of the soap.
That means behind the ears, between the toes.
I feel, you know, who's, who's, if you, okay, if the requirement, so you have to clean your
full body, right?
I feel like.
Absolutely.
Yes.
That's going to be so hard.
At least one coverage.
You know, people miss, people miss spots.
How are you?
How can you differentiate between someone who misses a spot and someone who doesn't?
Who's going to know?
Well, the judges, the judges will review your body.
They'll have to judge your cleanliness afterwards.
You go into one of those airport, like scanning things.
They scan for dirt particles.
Yeah.
Well, okay.
You then have to take a long, you then have to bathe yourself again afterwards.
Much takes much more time and then take the bathwater, you know, tested for like what percentage
dirt it is in order to determine your overall cleanliness.
Sure, sure.
I mean, it's not just about that though.
It's actually more about, cleanliness is important.
That's one metric used, but also surface area covered and touched by soap.
Yeah.
Both factors are used.
So the optimal start, of course, is if you're dirty, that's not going to work out.
You got to, I mean, you see an average Twitch, like let's, or speed runner on Twitch.
They'll do multiple runs.
Do multiple runs.
Shower before you're ready to shower and get yourself warmed up.
Get the gunk off the biggest chunks so that you're just ready for your optimal.
Just cover real fast with the bar or your optimal, you know, Loof or whatever.
That's, yeah, that's the way to play.
That's what we get yourself warmed up like any other speed runner would do.
I don't know.
It just makes it's just like doing research, you know, as every speed runner does.
To save the frames.
All right.
Same sort of thing.
What's, okay.
I've, I've heard from Michelle and I think from you.
Yeah.
That shower shampoo is a sham.
Oh.
And in some, like using it.
We are sponsored by Big Shamp.
I am.
I am being paid lots of money by Big Shamp to encourage people to sacrifice the precious,
precious oils down the drain.
Where, where the Big Shamp collects them to sell them back to you in more shampoo.
Yeah.
Talking, listen.
Me and Michelle are divided on this.
Talking about Big Shamp got Michelle banned off Twitter once.
So we should be careful what we say.
This video might get demonetized.
Yeah.
This channel might be, might be stricken from the record.
We just don't know.
We're at risk.
It might be cleaned up.
So, so, so I guess let me just say that when we say that a Big Shamp is stealing your oils,
what we mean is in Minecraft.
Correct.
No real life inclinations whatsoever.
It's all an abstraction.
And it's, it's not.
Jeff Bezos.
You hear that?
You hear that Bill Gates?
I'm making mad bucks.
Please use my Amazon link to Amazon.com slash Big Shamp forward slash Nate's money.
Yeah.
That's the full URL.
Oh, here it goes.
Amazon.com slash Nate is in cahoots with Big Shamp.
Yeah.
Okay.
There you go.
That's cool.
Okay.
All right.
I'm done.
That's it.
Well, hey guys, you know, you know, when you're like thinking I'm going to be productive
or that'll be really cool if I'm productive or something today.
And instead, you have the stupidest possible idea that's kind of funny and you want to see
it and then you Google it to see if someone else has like saved you the trouble of doing
this really stupid thing.
And then you find out that they haven't done it and you are the only person to even have
considered this really stupid idea.
And so instead of being productive, you spend hours upon hours downloading nostalgia critic
videos so that you can link all of them together so that he can say hello and the nostalgia
critic every single time he does it in one video.
Cool.
Is the idea to have him say it like layer it on top of each other so like you hear him
say it every single time in one second or whatever.
I mean, I could do that as well, but I was just thinking of having like a super cut of
from the very first to the most recent, hello on the nostalgia critic.
That's classic Gibbs stuff.
You can't do it, dawg.
I've been doing it.
You know, Crip Converter, that is the really good YouTube download specifically for its
function to download only a portion of the video.
So download the first like minute or two.
Yeah, the first 10 seconds of each video contains the hello on the nostalgia critic.
So I'm not taking up a lot of hard drive space.
Don't a lot of them start with the later on they do, but you can you can you can choose
I can, you know, manually just choose the point where he says it.
And so I'm so instead of instead of working on my Tezuko manga project, which is something
that is much better.
I'm sensitive.
Yeah.
I have been I've been looking at nostalgia critic and I put it in the timeline just to
see like the first 38 episodes and I was I was really he was really funny.
Just he just says it over and over again and his his head wobbles a little more every time.
That sounds great.
I want to see it.
I'm looking forward to it.
He gradually low shed his inhibitions.
Yeah.
And you can you can see week to week that is like his sideburns grow and then he shaves
them off.
Something's really funny about watching it all in a line.
How many times does he has he said it?
How many times do you think he said it in his life?
How many thousands?
Probably near to like a thousand.
What do you think the nostalgia critics pee be on saying hello?
I'm the nostalgic critic is like what's his speed run time for saying those words?
I'm learning that he is.
He varies like initially he's sort of slow to calculate which one was the speed of the
video speeds up like his delivery sometimes when he's excited when he leads right into
another sentence.
Sometimes he's like says it in a depressed way but like I want to see the general trend
like could you plot on a graph how how it increases in speed over time or whether it
does you know this is all this is all science here.
This is going to be like a very scientific footage video for people to use and dissect.
I'm very excited.
How long do you think it's going to be?
What were they?
What are they?
I think he said.
Oh shit.
What were they thinking?
How long how long will the video be if you put if you were to put all of them back to
back?
I don't even know how many nostalgia critics he's done so I couldn't even park it but
are they not numbered?
I mean it's got to be a playlist.
They are numbered but like with seasons I'm looking on YouTube he's got like his older
episodes are uploaded in seasons season one season two which I think are just like yeah
thanks for watching this episode.
I'm sorry I'm making noise.
What was I saying?
You don't know how long it's going to be.
Yeah I mean it could end up being like 40 minutes or something ridiculous which would
be funny.
Oh just for fun I did wait oh wait is this a playlist of every ABGN season but each
one.
That would be one to watch on two time speed.
Indeed indeed but this one it's every ABGN season but I think each season is rendered
into one video so this doesn't help at all god damn it.
Interesting.
Oh no yeah.
Oof.
Yikes.
Oof bro.
Gonna have to scrub.
Oh you know what that reminds me that does in fact take me back to the past when I remember
when I did me a math of a one.
Wait wait that's the wrong guy Nostalgia Critic doesn't take you back to the past.
No no no I think I think Nate was saying that like a super cut of what were they thinking.
What were they thinking.
I think I think he only says it like about 10 times I don't think he says it quite as
much.
Yeah yeah.
He just sort of like because it recurs it's just something that people remember.
I think he starts to say it more often and then maybe less often it kind of there's probably
like a sort of like a there's a period and fall much much like the much like the infection
curve of the COVID-19 pandemic.
Oh indeed indeed once wrote down my thoughts in a notepad document of of the ABGN like
eras like which ones were good basically I mean I'm trying to look for it but the basic
just is it's good and then he's working on the movie and it's bad and then it's sort
of good no it's good again sort of hit and miss.
I rewatched every season for some I just put them on and let them play like not that long
ago.
I don't know if I mentioned this before I feel like it was kind of you know a waste
of time but what did I expect you know.
Let me hey my point I was saying before it was just that a guy when I made me a math
of a one like four years ago a dude says it said if you do this I will make a video putting
all these together.
Now at the time I was like oh well I would kind of like rather post that myself I don't
know I mean maybe I'll do that but but just for the record he did not do that so that
guy is a pussy ass bitch and I did succeed so fuck that guy little bitch okay I'm looking
at my document from 2007 to 2010 is the AVGN golden era where basically every episode is
like a peak classic AVGN screaming you can't go wrong 2011 he starts working on the film
and then 2012-2013.
Guys that was that long ago yeah 2011 to 2014 it's like movie era where there's not
so much happening.
Dude feel old yet the AVGN movie can vote can fucking fight and die overseas yeah nine
years old yeah.
I think he really hit his stride somewhere between 2001 September 10th and 2001 September
12th there was just a sweet spot right there where he was really you know knocking it out
of the park knocking it all the way down wait guys please back me up please yes wait wait
I didn't know is that a 9-11 joke I missed it yeah of course it was okay how was that
not cuz I was looking at what numbers are Nate you understand this you know who'd back
me up I say it backwards I say 11-9 Sheldon would have backed me up.
Bazinga.
Alright well I still have just not watched this motherfucker more than like three episodes
one day maybe I don't know what the big bang theory the AVGN the AVGN or 9-11 bin lad same
guy same guy same energy hey here's a here's a new development in the red manosphere the
gibbosphere the whatever the fuck yeah yeah yeah yeah gun girls Antifa now yeah that was
my favorite thing now I don't know it's hard hard to say a lot of a lot of cool shit happened
this week but that was pretty based Antifa gun girl brings a smile to my face it's it's
so perfect for our character because she's always been like hates authority to the point
of like ridiculousness and it just so happens that she's a right-wing gun nut in order to
get the guns to do so because the girls is based on I was thinking she could be a right-wing
gun nut because she's gun girl and but she's also a cab she's also yeah Antifa because
fat cops cop killer you know yeah yeah she's not she's not open carry she's open fire
open shell casing when they I literally for some reason I just cannot hear you talking
at all for the last like minute am I really quiet or something is there's something for
me you were but maybe it's just me I don't know I don't know my thing looks okay can
you hear me now let me give you one of those okay cool how about one of these I heard that
brother your your soundboard is so much louder than you are is it really well I'll work on
it you're not leaning into the mic enough or something I like I like to write up on this
bitch I don't know I liked I liked seeing I liked seeing a pro pro protest and black lives
matter stuff from most of us I like I liked seeing it from hippo I like seeing it from
Tom also based who else was doing it Munchie hasn't been on Twitter Munchie was on the
video deafening silence over from over from Nate over here Digi sort of pro but like
in a weird way that you can't quite understand what she's saying we've all we've all we're
all in this together all right that's that's politics is beneath me no I don't I don't like
I don't like Japanese animated what is this voice much I don't know if this is a voice
modulator or soundboard okay it's me it's Megatron it's Megatron that's all that's yep
I like I like Megatron Megatron do you think black lives matter yeah Megatron
of course not that's so bad of you how come on knock was like to this prime he needs to
come in here shit set you straight is the kind of folk don't that there's no Megatron that
turns into like a human meanwhile meanwhile Optimus Prime couldn't be on the show because
he's at he's at the protests he's social distancing he's wearing his mask you know he's holding
up a big he's holding up a black lives matter he's turned into a fucking truck and he's mowing
police barricade as we speak they're throwing tear gas in his windows the police are breaking
his windows and putting little handcuffs on his little wheels or whatever dude it's not it's
not good to run people over but Optimus Prime supports looting Megatron I don't like where
you go I don't like some of the implications of what you're saying right now all all lives matter
Megatron even human lives stop it we're gonna cancel the old spark we're gonna get rid of the
all spark is an all right dog whistle Donald Trump has declared the Autobots and a terrorist
organization this is starting to seem just like a like a gray alien speaking to me what
in the Michael Bay movies all fucking Autobots all Transformers are just gray they're just
weird gray masses so gray gray lives matter hey Megatron I fucking don't like your attitude
and if I saw the all spark I wouldn't even let you know about it I would say
the culture of the police in America shifted irreparably when the Decepticons arrived on
America scanned to determine who you know the most easily infiltrated authority figures were
decided they were police all those Decepticons became police cars when you see a police car on
the street it's a Decepticon smash each window report it to your local Autobot a splinter
terrorists sell they'll know what to do
they're terrorists because they have the all spark but we will attain it when they claim they claim
that there's no leadership but I know that their leaders have the all spark and we will find them
and we will make our Decepticons supreme uh uh uh uh uh so don't forget to vote Republican kids
for more Decepticons we we got a we got a deep platform this guy this guy is spouting this is
hate speech uh this is unacceptable um this is this is uh but he's got the robot card though
propaganda no no that's identity politics don't give in don't give in he's co-opting
he's recuperating liberal he's recuperating liberal identity politics to to undermine solidarity
uh
incredible oh he's still here
no i can't just cover your ears everyone just don't just don't let it in just don't let it
don't let it okay no more all spark no message received thank you megatron thanks
thanks megatron thanks for coming on the show yeah what if you wanted these you tell what i've
told you we needed guests yeah we needed guests and we got them thank thank you
that was great we appreciate uh ladies and gentlemen we got them yes
okay all right yes good speaking of guests speaking of guests we were uh of me
me we we we good pzp members uh uh we were a guest on vik and hope stream uh vik contacted us to do
a charity stream and we raised over a thousand dollars for the for the for the uh richmond bail
fund uh this was this was yesterday uh it was really good and real cool and they played
sonic adventure 2 for 10 hours i was on the i didn't realize um i i'd left before and i i went
back to to watch the remainder um that like a bail is around a thousand bucks i didn't think it was
that high either to to just like it seems like a surprising very obviously like restrictive amount
of money yeah like like it's so obvious where like the point of it is it's pretty yeah cash bail
really is a fucked up is a fucked up thing that should be abolished haha fuck the police i can't
remember the the exact rates but like i remember hearing something that seemed very strange to me
about like uh okay you criminal we're sentencing you i don't know what the person did but like it
was like okay you'll get it was like a like month in jail or like it was like something like a
ten thousand dollar fine and i was like i'll take the month in jail where between those two things
jesus christ well we're not we're not talking about fines we're not talking about paying right
separate fines we're talking about cash bail like to release do people their point do people know
like i feel like there are some people don't understand this because i think a lot of countries
don't have cash bail and even in america where we do have it i think that a lot of people don't
quite understand how it works well all right for anyone who doesn't know cash bail is like you get
arrested you go to jail and then there is like a process of like where they have to like i don't
know file for your trial and like await your actual trial to determine your guilt and most of the time
they will let you leave jail to um you know and you just have to come back for your trial um but
in a lot of in most cases they will have something called bail which is you basically have to post
an amount of money that is determined like based on how what you're accused of like different crimes
have different bail amounts and you have to put up that money as collateral and then once you do that
you know then it's like okay we'll keep that and then you show up for trial and you get it back
right so like i guess the idea behind it is that like well the worst thing you're accused of the
more you have to post bail because it's like a higher stakes thing i guess it's theoretically it's
to like be more of a deterrent for people fleeing harsher sentences or something in
in practice it is just a it is just a barrier that like you know uh poor people of which there are
a lot of just can't pay even the smallest amount of and a lot of people you know you know what they
always said like during the during the fucking uh uh primary uh race for the elections we heard all
the time that like the average american family can't uh like pay a sudden five up five hundred
dollar uh expense and so you know bail is usually it's like that that would be pretty small for
bail so like a lot of crimes is there a reasonable alternative what's uh what's there is there is a
reasonable alternative and funnily enough it's nothing because um there is there is like no
data does not suggest that cash bail actually works as a as a deterrent for flight because like
not showing up for your trial like is illegal and is another crime that you can then be charged with
uh um and cash bail just doesn't work and so so the real issue here is simply that and the one
last thing effectively as a just oh yeah gone gone uh and the justification i would say is that like
if a crime if if you are if you are not a flight risk to the point that like any amount of just
like money can be just sort of handed over and like they'll just trust you to come back for it
then like letting you go without that i don't know like then if you can be allowed outside
at all awaiting your trial then they should probably just let you go and do it yeah can you
if if something if something is a if something is a like a heinous enough crime or enough of a
flight risk that they shouldn't be letting you out of jail even for money then like they shouldn't
let you do it for money you know yeah like if i mean i don't know how it works but like if say
you're accused of murder like suspected of murder they shouldn't let you out even if you have the
money right i don't think i'm pretty i'm pretty sure they something like that probably doesn't
allow for bail yeah i think i don't know for sure but like not every crime not every charge
allows is like yeah you can be held without bail awaiting trial the thing about it is the cash
bail system if someone can't paste their bail then they might just have to sit in jail for days or
weeks or months or who knows how long uh awaiting their trial which would cause them to lose their
job miss uh you know miss payments on their house possibly get evicted from their home
all because they couldn't post that initial like bail payment which happens all the time
and what that leads to is people uh accepting plea bargains uh even when they're you know accepting
like un like unjustly long like sentences as part of a plea bargain just so that they can get it done
and get out of you know jail awaiting trial so that they can go back to their job and not lose
their job not lose their home or whatever this happens all the time this is like one of the
tactics that has led to the like the ballooning of the of the of the like the prison population
in the last like 40 years uh and that's part of the problem and that's why and the thing about
a bail fund right which is what we were raising money for on on the the the vican hope stream
was like if you give to a fund like that what i think is really cool about it is that they will
they post bail for someone but then when that person goes back to trial they do get the bit
get the money back and then they can use it again to post bail for someone else so this is just like
a fund of money that that this organization now has to like keep people out of that situation
i just described you know in the future going forward like this is not just going to be something
that's used for relief during like arrests in the wake of the protests like the cash bail thing is
always a problem it's not just right now although for right now i think a lot of these organizations
are focusing on keeping protesters out of jail which is good um anyway that was that was pretty
based um oh speaking of that unless anyone else has anything to say because i this was
uh separate from the separate from that stream which was giving to the for the Richmond fund
i i donated to my my the massachusetts fund and because i did that and then with the help of a
little guy of a guy uh uh by the name of uh uh cuttle sol or or cicada um did you see that tweet
going around oh yeah yeah the one the guy the one angry gamer making the list of traders to america
and it's basically just people who support black lives matter or who have donated to like you know
like like funds related to that or or just are in favor of it in general i am on the list
and it's not that long a list it's like a couple hundred there's like a couple hundred
brands and a couple hundred people it's like famous people like youtube youtube
eat celebs and stuff i'm on the list i'm on the official list of quote unquote traders of america
uh uh in a collaborated effort with cuttle sol i was i was uh i was uh outed to this person
to this individual and i was rightly placed on the list uh right above ben schwarz the voice
of sonic the hedgehog in the recent movie of the same name uh binging with babish bill nye quote
unquote the science guy and billy eilish parentheses singer um so you know i'm in pretty good company
uh do you have a link to that i i i did look at it i wanted to be on there as well so i think um
i don't know why he thought that i was like i guess he was just in the right mood and he saw
someone this this person like linked my tweet where i said that i donated and he was like
eh this person's got somewhat of a twitter following oh they did donate to the thing so
okay they're on the list they're a trader and i gotta say for this for this reason alone that
500 dollar donation was the best 500 dollars i ever spent because it made me officially a traitor
of america um such a funny one angry gamer to know what's what one angry gamer is very obviously
just doing this for attention and it worked he got like he got like people like ethon clyne was like
what did i do like responded to the tweet because like ethon clyne you're a little too Jewish though
no thanks it was you know it's like hmm you you tweeted about black lives matter you just made
the list buddy hmm honey you're on the list now mm stay in your lane next time this is like the
smug tone with which this guy like but he's it works he's got yeah he's gotten like yeah famous
people have been like i can't believe i'm on a list of traders law i guess it's just funny it
makes a funny story to call yourself a that someone's calling you a trader uh and i agree i am
guilty i'm here i am giving it attention but i don't know it was making the rounds on twitter all
yesterday one angry gamer aka pissed off video gamer the famous where is the link did i did i
close the link how could i have closed the link uh i want to i'm gonna link it in the chat
this is freaking it's it's really annoying when you go to the website that has the list you have
to do this like really convoluted fucking uh capture shit i i assumed that maybe he was getting like
someone was fucking with the website or maybe just traffic to it was like higher than his bandwidth
would allow and so there's all this capture shit uh oh i found it i found it posted in the chat
in the procrastinator's podcast well it's oh my god that sucks that's what is what is with that
link okay it's really long anyway ah do your so that's my fucking story about being a trader being
antifa i always knew it i always knew it but now i know it for sure if one angry gamer says it
then who are we one angry gamer just to one any one of them all it takes is one angry gamer
god said all right i will look i will i will send an angel i will send an angel to saddam
and gamora and if i find even one angry gamer they will be spared but guess what he didn't
and they were turned into salt i can't see look out for my uh competing oh yeah i i'm not gonna
click on it uh i don't want to no need for traffic here he's got enough attention uh but look out for
my competing website where i will also be making a list of traders that's going to be called uh
one seething gamer uh you everyone will be ranked every human being on the planet will be ranked
ranked from zero to ten and how much they make me see this is my will be on my ongoing quest it
will be a paid subscription thing wait hippo i gave you the wrong link actually i'm gonna give you
a this is the right i linked you to the wrong fucking okay here here's the actual link i don't
know why i posted that other one i'm a fool okay there it is sorry sorry this one's more reasonably
sized yeah okay anyway what are you saying well congratulations on your success who who else is
here uh uh um uh oh ea sports uh euro euro gamer is a trader of america uh instagram um maybe they're
from america picks picks are um uh pokeman parenza who is on here for for her role as a thought
sometimes he lists exactly like what their crime was well that's traitorous behavior we all know
he lists who they are a review tech usa rihanna seth rogan um victor victoria justice i don't
know who that is um jack jacks blade jacks blade is on here uh pewdie pie uh big big lefty uh
antifa antifa organizer pewdie pie all of these links are like oh here's the proof like some
screenshot or a tweet link jk rowling damn she's a trader of america and a fucking and a
fucking terror for this week what is maybe a poorly defined category trader of america no
shit no shit justin beaver misguided traitor what does that mean wait maybe he's getting you
know a bit more of a pass i thought i thought i saw that justin beaver beaver's uh uh said like
homeschooling gone wrong oh garfield eats garfield eats is a trader of america garfield even though
it's from like saudi america saudi saudi america or whatever hellish thinking bolly i don't know
i remember um anime expo trader of america noted noted arc system works you know guilty gear
guys sonic fox uh in parentheses traitors of america human being on the face of the planet
that's not very nice really that's me yeah because i think he's because of the furriness
like he adds furry and next to well i mean agreed agreed and and here and here i am uh
oh he must have added someone because i've moved down it's an alphabetical list but i've moved
down from number 32 to number 33 i am number currently number 33 on the alphabetical list of
see i wish this was ranked in terms of who's the worst trader i would like to know but that would
be pretty hard because it seems like this guy does not vet his list very well uh chugga conroy
youtuber chris ray gun chucky chevy chase parentheses comedic icon uh where is hypocrite
where's give and take that's not that game grumps there they are the threshold of trader is uh
that's i'd love him to define i think it's just like lil nas x black lives do matter
then you're a trader to america that's literally i'm safe thank god if you if you tweet if you
tweet anything about black lives matter or probably just like anything
progressive at all probably and he was in the right mood i'm sure there's no like hard line of
like what gets you on the list or what doesn't i don't know i suspect you're right uh but supposedly
it's about supporting uh the protest or whatever because we the list start he explains it at the
top let me read here a number of individuals companies outlets and media institutions have
stepped forward to announce that they support the groups enabling riots violence vandalism theft
assault and murder dab taking place at the hands of vandals and thugs across the united states of
america and even looking to find out which companies brands and content creators have
betrayed the trust of the american people by aligning with groups that support the destruction of
uh western values uh this list will enlighten you as to who the traders are so you can stay
informed there it is it'll be informed not yep this is journalism what we're looking at is journalism
and they said all games journalism was bad and western value this is what i call in the trend
this is what i would call ethical games journalism uh where i forced to point out an example
which in these modern days i feel like i am constantly these feminists sparking at the door
discord i'm howling at the moon
megatron get out of here buddy is megatron a brony i think he probably is he's got definitely
he's got the look in his eye they're both hasbro products don't you know oh you brand connection
they're probably best friends i wonder if there was ever a transformer uh in in the
friendship is magic there's gotta be some reference i mean that's a fucking those boys are in deep
dude do you think there's a transformer
hmm uh no
like a transition or are they all by definition trans they're all non but wait actually i suppose
they are binary unless they're those kinds like optimists that have multiple forms uh you know
i feel like this might vary from canon to canon do do do do they have a gender like before they
come to earth i don't there are clearly female seeming in the old robots on earth right in the
old cartoon there were like okay they they don't they like they like take their form when they get
to earth right well but the form that they take is actually usually like like optimus was a fire
truck yeah because there's a fire truck i think he already looked like normal humanoid optimus
his normal humanoid optimus is like his normal like off world form like that's what he looked
like before informed by the fire truck this is like elements of that in the design clearly yeah
this is a host of juju situation yeah um i i feel like i feel like they i'm i'm i think they have
a fucking i think there are girl autobots which means there are guy autobots or
like before like before because from the cartoon which means which means that they have gender
but i don't know if they can be but are they assigned a gender at birth right you have to be
you have to be assigned a gender at birth to then become trans by changing your it you know
we don't know the anatomy there could theoretically be some sort of gender
since i am sure they don't have fucking dicks and p-holes they are probably not assigned to the
gender at birth the two sexes dicks or p-holes and therefore i don't think they can be trans
oh wait now that is true this is my i see i see any any any fucking hey what's the generic word
for an autobot or like a member of the species that is either a an autobot or a decepticon the
only thing that comes to mind is transformer but i don't know if that's actually legit or not
okay uh wait they're from no wait they're from a planet right robot what's the name of their
planet or they're they're cute oh shit i should know that they're from a big fucking hyper cube
in space right big minecraft flick there is a name for it there was a show called like uh
transformers colon something and it was like the name of that because it took place on there like
after everyone was fucking dead uh oh i can't remember mega trans formers yeah home home planet
is called yeah cybertron i don't know this cybertron so maybe they're like cybertronians
or something that would make that would make sense but then again would every like if you're
like a deer and you're brought from earth somewhere are you an earthling or are you like a deer you
know is it like what's the sub category there i think you're you're both well i think i mean
you're both i think that the only thing that lives on cybertron are the these things well at this
point that's definitely like like it like if you are from thank if you are like i don't think they
like also have like others like native species i think it's just this one kind of being comes from
this thing uh yeah yeah maybe it's not even uh maybe it's an artificial planet created by someone
it looks like that it doesn't look like a normal uh uh place it's like a big fucking like spherical
like clockwork thing well i gotta google it it's like it's like it looks like um it looks like
fucking uh uh uh coruscant but like that's also been hollowed out and like the inside of it is more
coruscant but you know is is that hard to believe that uh over time this civilization could have
hollowed out their planet because they don't need you know it could have been i don't know i just
kind of it doesn't feel right like these like i'm pretty sure that they that these cybertronians
don't have like a biological origin but maybe well i mean maybe like they were created by
like originally but you know not not their specific maybe i don't know maybe not maybe not
maybe the all spark just sprang from the nothingness maybe maybe uh uh well let's see where did
where did cybertron where did cybertron come from i don't know is there a wiki i bet there's a
fucking i'm sure we gotta talk to victor cybertron planet us up i think wiki uh uh general uh
marvel comics cybertron was a was the what was the adopted form of the lord of the light gods
primus who trapped himself and unicorn in baron asteroids it's a god trapped in an asteroid
which or a does a marvel or a multitude of gods which they then shaped in their physical forms
while unicron turned his prison into a transformable humanoid body primus reformed himself into a vast
Saturn sized machine world home for a robotic race he created to fight unicron with similar
transformation abilities okay all right there you go it's just a god manifesting as a as a machine
sphere gave birth to a species uh yeah all right there it is now at least according to this now we
know if they all agree on that i know unicron is no that's just the first one that's the first one
from the marvel comics continuity okay from the cartoon um oh okay yeah um 12 million years ago
no that's that's later okay i guess maybe they maybe they don't go into where it comes from
in the real quick just listen to this sorry okay this is this could we could probably spend the
rest of the episode just talking about uh transformers canon please don't indeed okay let me leave
you with this one detail no i went so that that second god or whatever unicron i just went to his
wiki page on the transformers wiki and this is the description at the top of the page quote
a unicron or lots of unicrons did lots of stuff in the primex universal cluster it's not all very
clear primex that is the description universal cluster okay and then on the right there's a
there's a cool picture of unicron which is captioned with i usually don't look nearly
as cool as this as he holds the planet earth in his hand um who's writing this uh all right
they're not taking this very seriously that's from the transformers yeah yeah the tf wiki.net
which sounds authoritative i mean what article i linked the unicron article unicron in generation
one oh okay well this is gonna have all kinds of the oh wait which is distinct from the main
there's a main unicron that was generation one the the cybertron article is much more professional
unicron's main page it because cybertron is the home planet of the transformers and usually the
body of their creator primus cybertron is blah blah blah blah blah okay you know what on the main
one let me just say unicron is the eternal arch enemy of his twin brother primus also known as
the lord of chaos the chaos bringer the planet eater blah blah blah blah blah there you go he
wants to consume the multiverse understood thank you but would they say trans rights though
i don't think they would i think they're cowards but they say they'd say transformers
transformers rights no not good enough they're recuperating it
it's an alt right dog whistle on this wiki there's a lot of shit going on here uh all right well in
any case um i just let you know i've got a voicemail unless uh you guys want to uh let me go for an
hour i i got a thing a little little thing to talk about speaking of being a traitor to america
to traitor to western values uh i've decided my punk only fans is doing well uh it's really funny
um that's there's a brand new image set of punk showing her gourds like you get to see them for
real saw it damn how did i see that wait did you post it in a discord server and that's how i saw it
it was that's costing yourself my business yeah costing her my business you're a leaker
i did that well it was just you munchy me and kazi yeah but i've decided because most of those
people because the only fans is five bucks a month i'm going to consolidate that into my patreon
because patreon takes less of a cut than only fans does only fans is kind of i see kind of a
shit kind of an asshole what kind of percentage like ten percent less more um all right it's one
fifth i think twenty percent yeah so what so what you're saying is that these images are also
going to be available on your patreon yes at the five dollar exclusively yes good so so if you want
that you you got it i must now give i have been pondering this does this do these images inform
pumps uh canon like idea like is this canon pump it must be you know alt universe i don't know it
could be could be just uh um like is all porn of every anime character canon i mean you know i mean
if i'm just curious if the creator of the character is making it and it's like all done in character
then and i would then i would say i would assume that i would i would assume that it is canon until
notified otherwise well yeah that's why i'm asking the thing about it right is that
punk is a vegetable i don't want to follow no slut i don't want to know so cheap ass bitch ass
he thought well that's what that's what she is i'm sorry punk is a is a vegetable and and not a
mammal and so uh the things that are attractive about human females and males she doesn't understand
she doesn't care so it's like it's like doing this stuff isn't even sexual she doesn't even
understand she's like how these idiots have given me money that is like the the canon character
interpretation so she's not being slow that's why she's just doing stuff it seems like she's being
a slut but uh in fact we are we are incorrect what does what does constitute a sexual display
spilling your pumpkin guts you know it would be it would be on the inside no no no no showing her
stamen no it would it would be it would be things like uh pollination like bees yeah yeah yeah
like like plant things like showing her roots the stamen yeah yeah yeah yeah the seed her seed
pods she is like if you give her a bouquet of roses she will get like super blush like oh my god
i can't believe you would do this like you fucking pervert she throws them back at you these are just
like a handful of good joker china's you've handed me now remember all those absolutely
hilarious bucket jokes in homestack yeah row the potential is this is this is this is the the angle
i'm going for okay i got you i got you i mean obviously it started as a joke and it's not going
to be like a running thing when punk has her like uh return as a canon character in a comic which will
happen punk too uh you hold the camera during my only fan shoot uh yes thank aliex takes the pictures
on our phone aliex aliex getting all the money punk's just right yeah but yeah that's that's
that's about that go to go to patreon dot com slash give and take yeah probably do that
sounds seems like a good idea like a plant um i got some i bought some more worm stuff
yeah just yet yesterday yesterday okay i bought like a big shipment of the isomalta oligosaccharides
which as you as i've said many times is the main ingredient in my um in my uh fucking uh the worms
that i've been making but i have i want to start branching out and using even weirder stuff here
let me tell you i spent like a hundred dollars on some more uh fucked up shit yesterday i'm gonna
experiment right because the the the gummies that inspired the the sweet smarts brand that inspired
me to like try this they have a bunch of different varieties and they have different textures and they
have different uh uh like ingredients so i wanted to get some more shit and just see what can i do
to get like different consistencies so i got um sure uh uh locust bean gum powder
uh guar gum uh kappa carrageenan uh agar agar powder um yeah okay what else what uh wait
did i buy pectin yes wait i ordered i ordered that yeah okay pectin yes uh citrus pectin
and i'm so fucking excited for all these weird powders and goose um i gotta i got a big box of
like a big like sampler of like all these different like food colorings i got a new i got new uh uh uh
flavorings i got rose flavor dude dude i got rose flavor and i and i i was i wanted to taste it
so i made like a little drink out of it i just put some rose flavoring in some water and i put
it and i put in pink i put in pink food coloring and black food coloring to get like just a little
rosy tinted like a sort of translucent black color to the drink and i was drinking it and i was like
this is amazing this tastes fantastic i'm gonna make i would make like black rose flavor right
they'd be like rose flavor but i'd dye them black that would be the the the flavor of that worm
ah right and it'd be like yeah it's like animal crossing um epic i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i
i guess this is like imagine i guess this is my new thing i guess this is my new like hobby or
whatever is like i i should get i should get different molds i should get more molds it's
yeah fish molds because like they have i try make it like hmm how can i make them how can i make
their consistency more like swedish fish how can i make their consistency more like a fruit roll up
how can i make their consistency more like this or that or the other thing product we just pecked
and do it just carrageen and do it what even are these things perhaps we could perhaps we
collab been and when i finished making my latest plaster mold uh for measuring my you know square
inches of surface area for my speedrun categories i thought you were gonna say dick make myself that
too dick will be part of the equation it will be part of the equation okay so you can fill that
up with your goo and we could make a nate mold maybe you know we could like it's you like just
posing like the statue of david or something and i just like fill that yes fill it up with like
pounds and pounds of this weird of this weird shit and then we can all eat it together
we can all like descend upon it and take bites out of it uh devour nate as you reach the dessert
cool what flavor do you want to be excellent uh i guess some sort of like lime yeah lime green
is good you want to be like let like lemon lime maybe yes that would be great maybe i can mix up
some kind of like citrusy like mountain dewy kind of flavor or something yeah i mean my favorite
has always been orange but lemon lime is good for the for the color aesthetic so i like that okay
well we can have oh oh oh there's i saw what was that other the the company i was ordering flavor
i've had like a flavor that was like a particular kind of orange but i i can't there is things like
blood oranges one i love blood orange wait wait wait wait um um can i i gotta find it i
i think it was the product where is the where is the product no uh i'll say while you do that
yeah i love blood orange mochi which i have had at Whole Foods uh every other mochi is so much worse
than the blood orange mochi including mango which masquerades really if it was the orange equivalent
really blood orange is so i mean hey everyone's got their own taste but this is like like there's
chocolate lame gay not cool blood orange is the best uh that's my expert opinion if you go to
Whole Foods you get those that's the one i highly recommend sometimes i'll want to be like oh i should
get like you know get like six of them i'll mix and match every time i'm disappointed when i'm
eating one that isn't blood orange just get six blood orange it's the way to go sounds delicious
and not highly recommend it at all no not keto at all no no no bur burgamut
burgamut haven't heard of it burgamut orange i hadn't either but it's some kind of like little
like green orange it's an orange even though it's green hey go figure am i right imagine that i
should have orange is a green until they should have got oh i forgot i should have got rice flour
because like i think i wouldn't i wouldn't use a lot of it because it's not keto it's not but if
you just use a little bit of it for like consistency next next time i go on a spree of like buying weird
shit i'll i'll get like a little a little bag of of of rice flour just just to just to like sprinkle
in just just see what just see what i because that's the main ingredient mochi right uh yes that's
right that's right yeah so you know pounded rice whatever i think i just pound rice or at least
in the old days i'm sure it's more complex i think there's uh there's really just pounded like with
hammers yeah i mean back in i mean i'm like a very inefficient way to make flour well this is a
historical like like an ancient technique technique of yeah they have like a very deep bowl i mean
mochi it's like it's like an art that people used to there were like artisans who specialized in
mochi back in the day yeah sure yeah cool okay indeed i noticed gib left by the way don't know
what's going on with that wait he did oh he i mean he yeah he just disappeared i don't know why
maybe um maybe his like he's got a no i was gonna say he's got a thing on his computer that like
turns off his internet at a certain time in the evening it's a little before that i think it has
caused him to uh spontaneously vanish from streams and the like before but probably it's not late
enough wait no oh yeah yeah well no it would be nine you can reach his like total amount of computer
usage time for a day i think and that might be i mean maybe maybe but i don't know but if that were
the case he it would be he would be leaving if it were time base he would have left at like
nine twenty five p.m. or so which just doesn't seem very like something like that um so probably
not that what else would have on my list oh i um i've been making pizza but making keto pizza
why did i put that on the list i did a tweet okay i did a tweet about a pizza image i saw that i
wanted to make and i asked the people to give me their pizza recipes yeah which i will ask for
again here i'll link the tweet to people uh because i want to eat this specific kind of pizza uh
because it just looked so good i think it's just like a like a thin crust margarita pizza yes and
i uh want to make it it looks like it's great rt some kind of artisanal uh freaking um definitely
a margarita hey what happened uh internet cut out lol we were mocking you as if it was your
like oh he reached his time yeah it was it was the it was the time limit it was the the the too late
to stream the cold turkey it's 4 30 time for your dick flattening sun get in here it's time for
my going to bed flattening my brain flattening that that crust that crust looks really good it
reminds me of papa geno's yeah people were saying did you work at a pizza it's similar
i'm sure this is better than papa geno's but it's got that same sort of like
bready bubbly crust consistency that's i really like that's my favorite yeah my favorite i want
this shit i'ma make it one of these days uh when i get around i definitely want to be able to make
that pizza bread that is my favorite right is when when it's like authentic italian um restaurant
like pizza that is like fresh from zeovin like uh like yeah whatever the what do they use the giant
oh here's the questions and the and the big uh the big like the big like paddles yeah yeah
have do you guys have any experience with a pizza stone because i think that a pizza stone
is the answer to getting the crispiness in this kind of way because i need like a hotter amount of
probably the really fancy boys make their pizza on a pizza stone yeah i was looking around it's
like 30 to 40 bucks so like not exactly cheap but i might like hit up a thrift store and see if i
can just find one that's like five bucks or something do you just like take the trays out
of your oven and put a pizza stone in there no you you put it on i mean okay you just put a
stone in there and it heats up for a long time and that makes it like i think generally it retains
heat really well so it gets hotter i think the idea is that it heats evenly or something because
like of the okay like the the the conductivity of the pizza stone or whatever i think that's
what that's the reason why it's it's different from like a pan and people are telling me this
is the way to go and i'm willing to invest because i want to give the shot i mean if you want if
you're wanting to make deliciosa authentic italian style pizza i mean indeed seems seems like the
pros use a stone but i don't know could be a could be a spook could all be a scam could be a sigh it
would be worth trying to just get the dough really good and then putting it in the oven and if the
oven is the problem then then you get the stone yeah you know that's a reasonable idea i'm gonna
i'm gonna do some experimenting i want i want this to be a thing i do oh it does this looks so good
like the i mean i would probably put more sauce honestly because i love sauce but just like little
bits of cheese the leaves the incredibly crispy thin crust yeah i'm god damn it's driving me wild
one day one day oh and you know what on this front some people are like nat what about your diet
or something i've actually been so fucking good about exercising the last two weeks and uh well
not counting my calories every single time but uh been better good on my diet and i counted them all
today i'm doing it again so shut the fuck up everybody i got it under control i can make a
pizza once in a while and it will not break the bank feels good though i've been feeling great
like break the bank no need for yoga my my profit margins are so razor thin i can't i can't afford
i can't afford a authentic uh a ball maza mozzarella i can't afford instead of i can't sit
of a grandma's heart surgery i have to get this pizza stone bro it was one of the other and
she would want me to live well rather than her she wouldn't want to live in a world where i can't
enjoy the authentic break of an experience just like in the old country precisely then
a grandma you say in front of her tombstone as you chow down
it's like cough coronavirus into her face epic simply epic grand mazinga
cool um yep so that's my quest i'll get back to you on that so this will be my gummy bear thing i
guess i have one more thing i could talk about from this week which is i played i played dnd again
the further adventures of higgs ozaks the dry um the frog man uh and how's he doing uh the thing
about we we had like a pretty long sesh this was this was on saturday i think and um the thing
about it is that the entire it was like all just arguing it was like we did have a fight but it was
like the the fight maybe lasted like like 45 minutes it was like three and a half hours of just arguing
about no we should join the mage's guild no we shouldn't join the mage's guild no we should we
should go to ice wall no we should go to junction no we should go this other place
or no we should we it was just it was just uh you know that's that's the experience that's
that's what it's all about i guess that's the tabletop life baby uh i mean i guess it was fine
i guess it wasn't too annoying i'm not i'm not even trying to complain i'm just saying it's funny
that this is this is what this is what the really the nuts and bolts of it boils down to
is just like and i'm just and i'm just over here i gotta tell you i gotta tell you i have
this is separate from talking about the the game in in specific but in general i have the
hugest pet peeve and a bunch of my fellow players do it and i it is like really hard for me not to
get like annoyed it is really hard for me not to like say something sometimes and be a dick because
i know no one wants to hear it because i guess it's just a preference but my preference is better
and everyone who disagrees is fucking stupid and playing the game wrong um i hate it when a player
will like will like want to do something right like they want to like maybe they want to look
for something like they think they might they think they might like want to look for some
somewhere because they think they will find something like in a room or whatever and they say
can i roll for perception to find x like if they want to find a clue it's like
can i roll for perception to find a clue i i hate that so much but what what you're supposed to do
in my opinion and i kind of think that anyone who has a different opinion is just wrong and not
valid is you're supposed to say okay well i'm gonna investigate the room i think maybe i'll find
this right you might even not have to add that last part i kind of think even that's a little
bit leading maybe you should just say okay i'm gonna investigate the room i'm gonna look for
stuff what do i find right you don't say when my when my fellow party members pick up the die
on their own when the dm did not tell them to and they say i'm gonna i want to make like a um
i want to make like a uh uh i want to make a insight check like to see if he's lying it's like no
you if ideally the dm would say make an insight check on their own and you would and then you
would roll and then they would tell you if they're lying or maybe if they don't do it maybe you just
say hmm does he sound sincere do i think he's lying and then the dm would say make a roll
and then you would do that and then they'd say yes you do or no you don't or you're not sure
that's the way you do it everything else is wrong and ruins the game okay my favorite is when i you
just you're like i'm gonna do this instantly rolls dice for anyone can say anything i got a 20 i win
it should be i will really strongly feel like 100 of the time you roll the dice when the dm
tells you to when the dm tells you a roll is required and at no other time yeah that makes
okay let me get this straight so like if some character's talking and it's never up to you
what role you're making the dm tells you what role you don't say can i make a perception check no
you can make one of those if the dm says make a perception check jesus christ so so like there's
a character talking and i i'm being in character and i think he's probably lying so i say out loud
i don't trust this guy um and the dm would say well roll to see if you can like how would that
work should i you would say that should i not say a declarative statement no you can you can say that
i mean i guess you could say that it would probably be a little more effective it'd probably be a
little more helpful to say to ask the dm for clarification like do i think he's lying does
it sound like he's lying or even just even just is he lying because the answer to that is make a
perception check or make an insight check um uh you that's that's how you should do it the there's
just i really think that it is an i just really think it is overstepping a player bounds to be
deciding what roles they want to make that's not their job and i think then remember when i really
think it's like it's like it's bad i hate it it makes me remember college academy we had that dm
i think his name was kevin something i mean i'm not going to say his name if i remember it
powers kevin powers okay well there you go it's a common it's not that weird a name so i don't
feel like we're dodging anyone all right sure this guy had an incredibly deep voice and he was the dm
in like the dnd clever the it was it was it was like a summer program that we did yeah yeah and
yes and you know ben was older than me so he did it first yes there was a whole bunch of cool stuff
about that but about this guy specifically i remember there was a class you could take that
it was the class you could sign up for was called fantasy because it was structured like college
right you would choose your classes as though where you were picking from a college curriculum
but they were just you know it was some of them were more like educational and some of them were
more just like kind of like sort of camp activities and it was held on a college campus and you would
go from room to room in like in a call yeah and this it was a stone hill college in massachusetts
and um oh yeah yeah there were there were ones on like rocketry where you would build a little
model rockets or i did that one i did that one a lot uh it was really popular and and one of them
was called fantasy adventures and it was a but it was just you play the indy lol that was the best
one yeah it was the best one everybody and kevin powers was this this like fucking scrawny ass
stork of a man i say man he must have been pretty fucking he must have been like probably like 18
at the time but you know we were in like middle school so it seemed like he was he was probably
like a college student or something or maybe i maybe a woman is like 20s his voice was so low
it made him seem older i think that he was not i think he was maybe like very early 20s at the
oldest i could see that yeah yeah but he seemed like i just considered him an adult at the time so
yeah yeah um yeah and he was so scrawny but he had this deep booming voice he he sounded like a
a little bit like george tekay but like yeah he had a vibe i don't know he's like
yeah it's the i i do not one time we asked him about like like the subject of like j rpgs came
up i don't we wouldn't have been in the same class so this is just me but yeah i am the subject of
like j rpgs this stuff came up and he said like mm i do not loathe despise or detest games such as
final fantasy that was the best compliment he could get i do not loathe despise or detest
one time he just showed um the record of lodos war the anime we watch that we watch and in hindsight
based i don't understand what the relevance is other than that it is a movie that has like dnd
like tropes in it like elves and bards i guess the idea was that it was like a good example of like
what like adventuring should feel like with like all different like like a character sort of
playing a different role in the party yeah it does feel like a very dnd like adventures sort of
story he also he please he showed us that was where i saw he showed me um um print the princess
bride and the justification for that the justification for that was like this is what combat should
feel like or can feel like it was like yeah making like like incorporating witty banter
into your like it doesn't just have to be the idea was like combat doesn't just have to be a
dull like dice rolling affair you you can like yeah you throw in some witty banter and then
he played the fucking sword fight scene he was like this is this is how it ah this is how it
should be they don't make them like they used to honestly i think he kind of just wanted to show
us some of his favorite nerd shit uh which is totally which is totally fine yeah and no problem
when i was uh i was briefly a japan like tutor or whatever in college uh where like the people
who were like years behind you would like you just help them practice or whatever on sometimes um
there was uh one time the the the tutors who are tutored me would just play us anime and so i followed
suit by when i was older i think i think i showed everybody um i know he showed us sayonara zetsubo
sensei which actually is a pretty wait that's pretty high-level complex puns wait kevin kevin powers did
no no no this is when i when i was in college when i was like learning japanese uh from like
older kids or older young men or whatever uh anyway i think mate what did i show him i don't
know yeah actually i don't think we didn't show him anything i think i just watched sayonara zetsubo
sensei and i grilled them in grammar because i was a hard ass as i recall kevin but they learned
kevin powers had a rule okay i maybe i got my like hard maybe i got my my philosophy of dnd from him
i think i must have yeah he like i'm kind of a stickler for the whole for the don't ask the the dm
to make a role thing clearly i think that is important but nobody else agrees and i just
guess i just got a fucking deal with that um uh kevin had a rule in his thing which i think is
good like if you if you if you follow the spirit of it i think it is a good rule that improves the
game but like with kids i think it just was like too much of an ask and it ended up derailing the
game yeah a lot but i don't know it i'm not sure if i think its effects were good or bad in this
particular scenario but his rule was not only like never ask can i make a role his rule was never
ask can i do something right you never ask the dm can i do this thing um the appropriate like the
only thing you should be saying is like you you might like you it like it's up to you to gauge
your character's capabilities right yeah like if there's a if there's a 10 foot gap and you
want to know can i jump over it like you should know like can my character clear a 10 foot gap or
like what sort of a skill role is required for a 10 foot gap how likely am i to do it like that's
up to you to decide it's not up to the it's not up to the dm to tell you yes if you tried to jump
you would make it so his rule was yep if you say can i jump the gap he in turn he automatically
interprets it as you attempting to do it so if you yes i remember that oh yeah can i do this you
your character you have done it to find out you have done it make a role yeah oh i remember that
and it was pretty it was great it was pretty it had some pretty funny consequences that was good
shit he knew what he was doing i feel like that's i feel like that's a little harsh uh and maybe if
your dm is nice they should say like i don't know what do you think or i don't know can you or do you
want to roll to find out or something yeah i suppose i think if you're a little more but i think he
wanted to really make a line in the sand like that's not how you play you're not asking the dm to
tell you what's gonna happen you're this college academy man you're here to learn yeah you're here
you gotta you gotta either like what do you think or if you don't know are you willing to risk finding
out right mm-hmm but i was gonna say one example that came to mind uh when you when you began this
about his well all the stuff was that um he would ask us uh no no what was it oh god i'm blanking
there was a very specific thing oh yeah right right that the thing that you started at the beginning
of like um uh like i i searched the room i want to roll to search the room or whatever yeah uh
whenever we when i someone said that he would always say he would have the same answer or the
same question he would respond with he would just say it's like i searched the room he would say
where do you look and i'd be like i the the corner there is nothing in the corner yeah the the floor
okay yeah i yeah he was definitely he was operating in like an older mindset under a system that was
that had less like mechanical complexity and require and like lean more heavily on on role
playing and i think for sure i think yeah like now like dnd like the like fifth edition and
like later editions explicitly you can just kind of have like an investigation skill and you can
just sort of be like make him kill himself if you heard that shit i bet yeah i'm sure he wouldn't
like and he can and you can just kind of make a role like i i investigate the room and and even
that you wouldn't necessarily even have to be that specific maybe unless yeah depending on the dm
and like i get it on the one hand i get it because like if your character is like a detective right
like they are they are a like a great detective or whatever they are like an investigator they're
maybe like a rogue that specializes in like perception and like fact finding and like information
they have really had like they would know how to search a room thoroughly in order to like you
know leave no stone unturned in the pursuit of clues or whatever like they would know how to
do it so to a certain extent i can understand why it shouldn't like the character would know
where to look the character would do a thorough search if they're good at this so i i kind of
get it on the one hand but on the other hand it's like well doesn't it take something away if like
you're not you if like it's kind of taking the power out of the players hands like the players
not making the decision of like of course what's what they're doing it's just sort of it's like
sonic running through a loop you know you're not playing the game the game is playing itself
you know what i mean and you know that's a that i i understand and it's about tradeoffs because
that's a that's a good example because i actually really love i do not really like the original
sonic games but i love the advanced games where it is simply flow state and there's like no decision
making required you just watch a thing go whoosh and it feels pretty sick well i would never okay
but unlike that you're not you don't get a cool visual of sonic the hedgehog running at san xp
huge when you're when you're uh when you're uh you're uh you're basically just batman dnd character
is like you know ransacking the the the villain's lair for a fucking like whatever you know yeah
you're right you're right yeah yeah yeah yeah no he was good times there's a there's a there's the
older dnd mindset was more like it was like it was kind of like you were the character more so
than like your character your character's like identity defines what they do i don't know one
might say old good new bad who would be so bold there's i think that a lot of the role playing
like i think that the like the new the newer mechanics that include things like an invest
like a deliberate investigation skill do encourage this kind of like oh i'm uh i'm gonna roll for
perception to find a thing uh here is like bad role playing that and that encourages that kind
of thing even though i understand the justification and i kind of get it but i think i don't have too
much of an issue or i think i think i think i kind of think i would be okay with it if people didn't
then fall into maybe not everyone agrees with me that it is a bad habit personally i think it's a bad
habit i wouldn't necessarily mind the mechanical the mechanical like option being there if it didn't
lead to these things that i consider to be bad habits and like detrimental to the role playing
experience um but they do in my opinion they do you think that uh like again i don't really care
what people do they can play however they want but like it makes me wonder that like if that's the
kind of game you want to play it feels like it like a jrpg would be more your your kind of thing uh
but i mean you know doing things in a group i get it obviously it's gonna be fun however you want
to do it's fine but it's like it's like if you're just if you're if you're saying okay i don't want
to harp on this too much but that's like one less if you're saying like i i invest like i
investigate uh do i find uh i'm like i'm gonna i'm gonna make a perception check to like see if
there are any enemies out like approaching or whatever it's like are are you that's like it's
like a that's like numbers that's like i don't know that's a mindset wherein the game is made up of
numbers you know yes it is for sure is the wrong i don't it's not the mindset that i want to be in
when i play the the game yeah yeah that's the x factor yeah yes all right well i think that i
think i've said enough about that i made a whole fucking i made a whole fucking video remember
that d&d that time that that tom made a video about d&d yes i do d&d good and i made the one
saying d&d bad i think that wasn't my whole justification that wasn't my whole reasoning
but i think i went into it more in that video and that video is probably like shorter than
the like the the rant i just gave about it uh it's not that long was it like 10 minutes i don't
remember go check it out check it out if you feel like it i guess okay but do not listen to tom's
counter argument no don't give him a chance for air no he is a he is a freaking RLL role player
he is a he is a munch he is he is one of those like what's the word uh he's a munch he's a number
munchkin he is a he is a min maxer he is everything that's wrong with the with the genre
damn fuck you tom die from a harsh man all right i got voicemails if you guys want to go to him
they're all lined up ready to go yeah uh speak pipe link you know what it is ladies and gentlemen
link there it is okay well i got it right here okay so first voicemail there's like uh what do we
got eight total uh oh god the first one here christ don't worry they're not that long okay okay this
first one right this first one is from jelly beaner uh called shaggy is an ass man and there's a there
i received another message or two about this which is just that in the uh the pro anon cast
they're having a civil war that's tearing them apart about uh ass versus tits so okay let's just
hear what they have to say let's hear what shaggy says okay yeah uh we we know we can we can go
let's let's i have okay let's let's play and hear what shaggy says okay go like i've got a serious
conundrum for you guys ass or tits i'll give you a hint it's ass man it's tits it's always
no fuck you die die that's it that's the full message answers tits next they they they came to me
for a for a statement because i made that twist that said tits are epic recently right right right
um and and what i responded to the exclusion of everything else presumably no that's that's my
stance i let me explain um in the situation like tits i would prefer but tits with no ass combined
is strange if you have it's a bad look if any ever like a flat bored but i was like there's
something wrong there but if you have a butt and you don't have tits that's some that that works
so like in two out of two out of two situations the ass is like the solid foundation upon which
the tits can rest yeah but overall sure i would like i i am more of the tits man
but then it needs the ass as support i feel like you've just made an ass argument maybe uh i mean
there's a meme to show we're talking about this the other day uh due to uh this contentious thing
tearing the world apart i uh a point was made that um like asses there is less ability for an
ass to be as horrendous as tits can be in their worst situation so it's something of a situation
where ass is something more of a safe bet and tits can potentially be more spectacular at their
heights i mean i'm sure somebody would agree yeah yeah tits can be more spectacular like there's
only i yeah i i would be i would be more impressed by like incredible tits than i would be by an
incredible uh yeah higher heights higher heights it's because it's the um the uh what's the word
that there's is not a lot of it the scarcity the scarcity of good tits compared to the ease of
having a good ass you know yeah i'm saying yeah i think so yeah i think so uh incidentally uh i i hope
that the pro anon cast is aware of this because there is a in-depth discussion on this subject
now it is it does have a conclusion but you should go check out the prison uh prison school
manga where they go in depth into the deep biological like pre-human evolution roots did i i generally
disagree with that with that argument we don't okay just because we evolved from that doesn't mean
we have to stick with that forever okay i don't know if i've heard this the particular thing
you're talking about but i've heard i'm skeptical of like pre-evolutionary justifications because we
don't know we can only speculate and nobody like really knows like what the evolutionary purpose
of like tits or ass or like why exactly would be they we are shaped this way is like in like a
social context we can't say you know man's opinion yeah you know that there was this video by lindy
beige of all people talking about um the the strange uh fact that women human women do not
have breasts only when they are like fertile in a like a mating season sort of way because other
mammals their breasts are then you know you can't basically basically can't see them but when
they're having babies they you know expand and then afterwards they go back but humans have
sort of evolved to a point where because it's more visual because we're upright he goes into all the
possibilities of like why it is that humans have like breasts for all the time rather than just for
being pregnant this is an interesting video i'll try yeah okay maybe maybe the moid race was uh just
getting pregnant consistently so like it wouldn't biologically there was no need to kind of change
it's it's interesting to speculate on why we are different from other mammals but it but again
we can't like we can't know we can't really know why there is there kind of is no why
yeah yeah or maybe there is rage is on yeah um well we'll leave it to the scholars over the
pro and on cash to hash out i was gonna say did you see yeah did you see that the this image
you probably did the tectonic improv made a ranking of course ranking the first 100 episodes
you know what ben let there's a voicemail about that you know i'll just play it out of water right
okay here let's let's play it and uh here what do you have to say right there go
hello everyone just wanted to call in and mention that i recently made an infographic
ranking the first 100 episodes of the pcp from best to worst and if you haven't seen it check it out
something i want to bring up about it though is the starfleet section i gave each episode that had
a starfleet mentioned a little icon but didn't tally the total amount of times it came up in
the infographic so consider this a podcast exclusive scoop starfleet is mentioned by name
38 times over the course of the first 100 episodes simultaneously a lot and also not as much as i
thought all right that's all i wanted to say thanks for your time there you go that that means
since starfleet is referenced in 20 he has on this infographic starfleet is referenced in 20
out of the first 100 episodes which means that starfleet is referenced an average of just under
two times per episode that it is mentioned in so most episodes i guess that yeah well no because
there might be like certain episodes okay though the record for most starfleet references was
achieved in weird utilitarianism episode totaling at 12 so 12 out of those 38 are just from a single
episode which makes sense considering the topic of that one yes this is a best guy ever is the only
member of the procrastinators to appear in each of the top 15 episodes he puts some particular
emphasis on these top 15 and lethal aurora mage and mother's basement do not appear in any top 15
episodes damn much dream talking mage too much dream talk that's right you lose you you you
just collapse in the rankings if you talk about dreams it's been proven and there's been some
debate i mean you know obviously everyone has their opinions the the much contentious uh the
the much lauded yellow episode things we can't get into not making number one has the people
rioting in the streets yeah that someone would defy that seems to be most peoples that seems to be
the most common pick for number one yeah yeah i'd say so it gives the internet just die again
we lost give again we'll see if he rejoins what a jerk what a freaking rube everybody loves the
virginity episode though so that certainly belongs up there somewhere it seems schools i think i think
tectonic has some weird big connection well not i'm not trying to call him weird but like school
sucks being this high is unusual i bet he has a some you know maybe he has an opinion on it hard
agree a hard agree with some of the things stated on that or maybe yes or maybe not maybe or maybe
not i don't know maybe it's good is that is that a good banter episode i don't fucking remember i
don't know you know i he would know he would know um uh well there is check it out yourself people
it's it's there should we should we go on to the next oh he's back he's back yes gib hello welcome
let us i missed the entirety of that voice call and whatever you said afterwards really well it was
have you seen this that's enough this image from tectonic i i saw the image the rank i can't remember
so many of the episodes and the contents of yeah i am so i can't i don't really have much to say
about it i guess was this made in the context of the rewatch i do not know i do not know i mean he
said he just went in no you know i don't think so because i don't i think the rewatch started
way before the pcb was even founded and i don't think they're even to the beginning yet so uh
like maybe that before oh as in they're starting from like pre-pcp yeah yeah that's right that
i i think i think i saw him post this somewhere and said i am just in like you just saying i don't
know why i did this yeah uh here you go and there it is well when they get to this part to the first
100 episodes in the rewatch i guess i'll be interesting to see if people agree with these
rankings or not yeah consider it consider make your rankings folks all right let's move on to our
next one yes i was curious what you two thought if you could briefly oh i mean we were just saying
that like everybody loves things you can't get into yellow episode uh virginity cast is great
i you know the rest in terms of how they're ranked i don't really have an opinion
yeah yeah no strong opinions uh okay let's go to our next one this is from gay boy scout
babysitter oh yes uh okay listen up here we go go on a recent twitch.tv slash definitely best guy
ever stream nat told a childhood story about his gay boy scout babysitter who ruined the family's
legend of dragoon for ps1 game nat said he was fuzzy on the details though and would need to ask ben
about it so can we please hear the full story about legend of dragoon for ps1 do you remember this ben
do you remember this incident about the game breaking right there was there was a discus being
thrown uh yes a kid in a kid in our boy scout troupe he was my age this kid jeff right i don't know
why i think i brought the game to a fucking boy scout meeting just to show it off or something
and this other kid just like took one of the discs and like threw it yeah and it broke the third
disc and i was like what the fuck you just broke fucking my video game and he was like
uh it was the third and three dis before dis and i was he was like oh you'll never get that far in
any way what oh god no are you fucking kidding me this man was not a rpg gamer i don't remember if
like and i think we we did in fact get that far and we oh yeah i did insist like no you broke my
thing give me like fucking pay for it you broke my shit and i think like the they did they like his
mom was made did make him like like you know pay me some money for like a replacement or whatever
which is good but we did never we didn't get it till a way later yeah yeah like we had already
gotten that far in the game and we're held up by it and so and so and when he finally got around
to like giving us the the money giving me the money for it and like i ordered like a replacement
yeah we had been like stuck for a while i never i eventually never i eventually never finished the
game uh you you did yeah i think i only got to the end of the second disc and then never
gotten me further in it so he was right no no i got there i just didn't play i just didn't go
any more it's not the same it's a principle i have a i have a memory though it was right but
it was a self-fulfilling prophecy he made that come true piece of shit jeff you i clearly remember
you buying me a copy of the legend of dragoon was it like at this time like for my birthday you
got it or something like years later because that's what i have in my head of that i bought you
i think that maybe maybe okay i think i thought that i i had the game or or did you was it your
game when when he broke it i thought it was mine yours i think it was yours at that time did it maybe
like he bought me the replacement maybe i just like used that money that he gave me to buy the disc
and gave it to you because like you had gotten further in the game than i had because like you
know i just don't know this is going back a long time i've lost some of these details yeah or maybe
or maybe that's the best i got or maybe like it was my game he broke it i like got that far and
then quit playing it he eventually paid it back for me you had played the game yes and had and wanted
it again and i hadn't decided like i didn't even really care to replace it that much or had just
forgotten about it but then eventually i got you a copy of the game as a gift because you did want
to continue it i feel like that's the gist maybe or something like that i think by by the way i think
the reason i was confused and mix things up because like i said like the boy scout troop
leader whatever i was thinking of the another guy remember it was the i said babysitter mat one of
the guys from our troop like an older guy came over and he babysat us and i believe we were playing
frisbee with another ps1 discus related you know crisis we were playing frisbee with final fantasy
eight disc why didn't break the disc but i think something else broke because i remember us all
being like oh shit what did we do fuck we broke something i don't know if i was i involved in
that i remember that something like that did happen but the details are very fuzzy yeah long
time ago i don't know why we would do such a thing what a bizarre world boy scout troop
members are the worst people yeah they're reckless they're full hearty fuck them and they're too
cavalier and i don't care for it things cannot be replaced aren't the boy scouts like fucking
disbanding or something because of all the like creepy sex shit uh i heard some talks of bankruptcy
i'm not sure yeah that's it they went bankrupt i think they went bankrupt boy scout association
or something like uh well i think it would be boy scouts of america right boy scouts of america
is its own like entity i'm yeah it's separate it's like a separate uh a thing based on the i don't
change their name to the scouts to not exclude women anymore or something well um try them all
four exclude women it's fine just do it who cares um um um uh boy that's a fucking quagmire it is a
quagmire no doubt about it um all right whatever we got another voicemail over this fucking place
this one is uh from pancakes i am become death destroyer of sound boards uh yes okay take it away
go bruh hi pancakes here listen no one hates sound boards more than me why is that especially if
they're wielded by weak willed and weak minded people uh Nate however i'm 100 for everyone
having a sound board on the pcp because sound boards are like nuclear arms you see if everyone has
one no one's gonna get a sound board they're flying after easy money they don't have the moral
courage they don't have what i have uh did you did you build your own sound board yeah brick by brick
piece by piece over like months and i mean did you choose what sounds are on it oh yeah of course
of course okay to prepare each one and you know stick it in there and um i i'm with this guy
honestly down bitches i yeah i'm tempted to take it i'm tempted to follow this advice that's pretty
good right um easy money you're very powerful you're very spiteful uh understood uh yes we've
got a new voicemail called attack my titans okay go so i recently found out that about a year ago
there was an attack on titan art exhibition and within this exhibition there was a single room
that was completely black and in the room there was the i guess the artist the mangaka created an
audio experience of what the finale of attack on titan will sound like and you can actually find
this on youtube it's really cool super haunting really fascinating uh i have no interest in attack
on titan until now where i just want to read it all because i'm fascinated at how this experience
can be connected to the manga basically i guess a discussion or question is has there ever been
anything that has just really interested you like one single thing that you heard about from a piece
of media that you instantly wanted to read or watch or experience thanks so much here's about that
question uh boring but the actual the first thing about what this is this like audio experience of
what the ending of the series will be like by the mangaka that's that's pretty kooky i i googled
it i could not find it on youtube by by the attack on titan guy he made an audio experience of the
end of attack on titan do i have that right apparently yeah that's just nice soundboard
easy money yeah that's what it sounds like
that's uh shut up that's uh uh very strange is there dialogue i don't know i don't know i don't
i could not find the damn thing i wonder like i want to know like how long it is and stuff i mean
you're supposed to go there and like sit and listen it's probably like well i don't know i can only
speculate i assume minutes as opposed to hours would be my guess but i don't know i don't know
uh if anyone could find this link it because i couldn't find it and it sounds
at least worth checking out um it's partly on youtube so there you go is there any one thing
that's made me interested in a piece of media um art uh is good i don't know uh see it's boring
seeing people with troll avatars on uh something awful made me wonder what Homestuck was lamal
i guess reading sweet bro and hella jeff which i did independently made me then read Homestuck
you know because i love sweet bro and hella so the real question is what made you read Homestuck
yeah that's the actual question yeah gibb care to comment
he just not care to comment all right we'll move right along uh maybe he's just gonna think
again i don't know uh all right next voicemail this one is we got two more this is from mozilla
fennekin simply titled oppression go hello it's been a while here in voice jail i've gained the
system enough to acquire a computer with internet access except i can only browse speak pipe and
reddit but i happen to stumble across the capital of reddit r slash small dick problems here i
witnessed the most oppressed minorities in society boys with a small pp with every piece of media
we are deluged by the glorification of big dicks someone does something cool like save a kitten
loot a target high gamer score that's big dick energy right there but bad things racism boolicking
corporate greed watching anime that's small dick energy the board of small dick problems is an
archive of real men who are discriminated against by all of society these men have lost the potential
loves of their lives just for an unfortunate sequence of genes women have it so easy men are such
primitive thirsty creatures that women of all sizes are valued sure there might be a bias towards
larger breasts but they're countless men who prefer the small flat lolly chest but nobody and i mean
no woman ever i hate this call yeah seven inch dick is cool but i'm all about that three and a half
you know yeah we must take a stand for our stout gentlemen and unite against the common enemy
yeah women enough of these fake woke care okay that's our hashtag all largely bored all right
got it small dick very epic very funny okay got no note to all say that joke literally 10 times as
fast uh and it will just be good yeah all right voice jail next voice he's already in voice jail
us how do you what i feel like i feel like we haven't cracked down enough on voice jail there's
still how are how are they able to send voicemails from voice jail this there should be like like if
that if that's if they can still if they can still do that from voice jail then what are we doing
we're not what's even the point we're not we're not pressing them enough to pay they need to pay
the voice bail so they can leave more voicemails that's right our our checkbook is open uh wait no
your checkbook is open our bank routing numbers are available for input so yes let me money is what's
required listen i'm i don't remember i think this was munchie's idea but i i thought it was really
funny and i think we should do it uh we did we did the we did the charity stream with bick and
hope i think it would be funny and cool and we should do it we should do a charity stream
a charity stream for the voice jail bail fund well but then we give it to an actual charity
that's that's real use me that's that's that's what i think i think i think we ought to do that
for like a special shackles for heckles uh uh i think it was munchie's or maybe it was someone in
the chat the comment i don't know i'm putting it out there that i support this idea um okay fair
enough and i'm uh yes okay anyway okay we got one more voicemail and then we are out of here
all right it's uh oh the end of ukrainian myth busters remember him everybody's favorite all
right yes go hello this is the ukrainian myth busters we would like to thank you for the support
on the pilot episode of this evening episode of the series because of your love and your support
we will be counseling the show the government has allowed us to discontinue the program and we
will be released from our pages thank you so much we love you brocaro nato baratica
oh no i'm gonna cry the show was so popular the state allowed them to cancel it uh that's pretty
much like like one piece goes for 20 years it does so well that it's allowed to die gracefully you
know hopefully anyway uh the ultimate privilege indeed indeed the the the right to die in peace
in dignity it's the only gift we can reliably give uh thank you thank you for your struggles your
one episode touched our hearts and this finale uh won you uh the academy award oh oh fucking oh
fucking boy you know what i love about this guy he's not afraid to end a joke that was 30 seconds
uh and it's over forever it's done uh great i'll give him that i'll give him that it was it was worth
the time uh yeah agreed agreed okay crania you you crane uh uh forever in our hearts all right
we're all done really that's it pipe link that's it that's it that was eight we got through eight
we went through it pretty fast okay mother fucking speed pipe link uh lead more voicemails
good ones will be played bad ones will be destroyed and you will go to jail um and uh
patreon.com slash the procrastiners new bonus episodes out uh oh swords versus guns yes uh
what a heck of a time it is go weigh in on the debate in these tumultuous times uh you need to
know your weaponry more than ever uh and also uh the discord and whatnot but five dollars for bonus
episodes i i want to say someone pointed this out yeah in the patreon in the in the patreon
discord and uh um i want to say uh that the patron discord was very active this week due to uh uh
some some uh stupid drama in which i defended myself rightly against a bunch of cowardly attacks
from disingenuous bad faith actors uh so if that's not content for your if that's not content for
your money i don't know what is so uh only only patrons get access to that and i guess that's
content so uh consider that a bonus uh for patrons this month uh if you're into that kind of thing
it is content uh do you wish to extend an olive branch to any degree absolutely not understood
but there you go my my my olive the the extent of the olive branch i am extending is to uh
cease talking about it now noted uh i got an olive garden for you oh i would love rose
i have nothing against endless breadsticks more like endless war to ketosis more like
really bottomless breadsticks more like bottom feeder you are soup salad and breadsticks is not
a bad combo uh that's what i'd say about that all right anyway uh uh right uh oh yeah we beat
patreon boom speak pipe boom and twitter at tbcrasnayers uh updates etc working hard more
stuff's coming soon uh working on rad content so uh stand by lads uh we'll get you that out as soon
as we can uh anything else from the peanut gallery i will have the olive branch i will defeat the
deceptive how we know i'm the deceptive cons fuck the auto watch uh thank you for listening everyone
just go back to the soundboard that's it all right see you soon everybody no no wait wait
no no you haven't read the lord of ghost comic by now you're stupid you never will that's true
you gotta go to give me a tip don't say it and read it there's a certain point where you gotta
pull up the ladder behind you it's just uh it's just a reasonable thing to do they didn't get on
yeah you know you gotta leave they haven't seen it it's time to delete it from the website
that's right that's right you know it's beautiful it's more beautiful when it's when it's uh a
fleeting the the the the daedora from Naruto artistic method as opposed to the sasori it was a
moment in time and the moment has passed more ever indeed correct all right that's it we're
done everybody see you next week bye